Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
We've got a couple fun things on tap today.
A little bit later in the show,
I'm gonna talk about, this is Scott Garner, by the way,
joined by Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
Hi, fellas.
Hello there, good to see you.
Yeah, so a little later in the show,
I'm gonna talk about my recent trip to Las Vegas
to experience Chris Angel's restaurant, Kablip,
and his new show at Planet Hollywood, A Mystica.
So looking forward to that, that's coming up.
But before that, hugs are back!
What?
Hugs are back!
Hugs!
Hugs are back, ladies and gentlemen.
Gentlemen, I ask you, where my hug at?
Where my hug at?
It's right here, it's wherever you want it to be.
And it's at, well, most importantly,
it's at the Disney resorts worldwide, maybe.
I don't know, nationwide.
Nationwide, at least.
Nationwide, Hong Kong back open.
Hugs could potentially be there.
Okay, okay.
But mainly hugs at the one that we're close to.
We could drive right now and get a hug from our favorites
because there's no more ban.
The hug ban is gone.
The iron curtain of the hug ban has been torn down,
torched, they burnt the curtain up.
We are no longer prevented from hugging all of our pals.
If you don't know what we're talking about,
Disneyland, okay, obviously many elements of it.
The whole park shut down for a long time, as we know.
For the pandemic. Disneyland, yes.
As did Disney World and all the Disney parks.
And they've all come back in waves.
The rides are back, but there's plexiglass
and the shows are gone.
But as the months have gone on,
we're finally restoring everything.
And the big thing was the characters are around,
but they are distanced.
Maybe they're standing up on the train station,
as we've seen.
And they wave as an opportunity to take selfies,
but there's no physical contact.
But one of the final elements of the Disney experience
to restore has been fully restored, and that's hugs.
You can hug.
We're hugging again.
We're hugging at the parks again, folks.
I think the interesting thing about all this,
and this is all kind of stemming from
specifically a New York Times article,
the headline being,
After a Two Year Ban, Hugs Are Back at Disneyland.
Weird thing to see in the New York Times.
It's the coverage, kind of across the board,
giving us the willies a little,
of everyone agreeing upon the phrase, hugs are back.
So I did see one or two more levelheaded publications go,
traditional character meet and greets are back.
Little clearer.
Yes, yeah.
I think that's the odd thing that's going on here.
Okay, all these publications, hugs are back.
Let me go through a couple more.
This is a local one, Coast FM.
It's official, we're hugging at Disneyland again.
LAist, Disneyland wants your hugs again.
What?
Disneyland didn't want our hugs.
We wanted to give them to Disneyland,
but they wouldn't accept them.
That's a weird one.
Disneyland wants your hug.
Disneyland wants your hugs.
Disneyland is powered by your hugs.
Bring your energy to Disneyland.
Just the idea that ever it was state,
we don't want your hug.
You can come into the park, but you put that mask on.
You cover up your filthy mouth,
and we don't want one hug out of you, okay?
We don't want you hugging your family, not here.
You do that at home.
We certainly don't want you hugging Mickey Mouse
and Donald Duck.
They're special, and if they get sick,
the whole company goes down.
Yeah, that is the tone of these headlines.
Yes, you're right.
There's a lot of severity
mixed with, throughout the copy of these articles,
this notion of the hug ban,
which this phrase I take some exception to.
I am not convinced that ever there was a discussion
at the deepest levels of the Disney company
where they used the phrase hug ban.
This is not, right?
I don't think so.
I don't think there was a need to do that.
Like I need to say that phrase.
Yeah, I kind of self explanatory in the distance.
Did Dr. Fauci say there was a ban on hugs?
Did he ever say that phrase?
I understood the distancing thing,
but did he ever, I'm trying to remember the Fauci impression.
What is it?
This guy, he talks like this, right?
Like, is a ban on hugs?
We can't hug anymore.
Yeah, is this in the current, you know,
hissy fits of like the DeSantis crew.
And it's like, and the hugs aren't even
on top of everything else.
There's a hug ban.
Yeah, I could see like,
what I'm trying to remember is if there was ever
one of those Jim Jordan,
those 10 minute back and forth that you see on Twitter,
him grilling Fauci, getting nowhere,
Fauci answering every question,
but him like getting all flustered.
Is it, well, okay, well,
we're not answering that one, are we?
No, he did.
He clearly did.
Oh, yeah.
Like, was there ever that exchange?
And yet you say, you explicitly said,
no, there's a hug ban.
You put a hug ban.
Do you know what that's doing to our kids?
My son can't hug Horace Horace Collar.
He hugs him once a month.
It's for his therapy.
My little girl, my little, my six month old,
she can't go hug the rabbit.
What's the name of the rabbit who,
it was the old character before Mickey.
What's the name of the rabbit?
I don't know.
She, but she, look, she loves it.
She doesn't know his name.
I don't know his name, but she loves the rabbit.
Senator, Senator, you're referring to Oswald,
the lucky rabbit, Senator.
Am I?
I don't know.
Now you're, you're telling me that.
You're saying Oswald's his name.
He is, his name is, well, Senator, his name is Oswald.
Oh, I see, I see.
So we dictate from on high the name of the rabbit.
Senator, I give you an answer to the question.
Jim Jordan, not a man I ever want to associate
with the concept of a hug.
Don't whatever, I would recommend people
not let their children anywhere near him either.
A lot of these folks.
Yeah, a lot of them are, I don't know about him specifically,
but a lot of these people are on record
with hug related issues, I would say.
That's true, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So wait, and then there's one more.
So there's the severity of the hug man.
What you get, like what, how did this play out at Disneyland?
Okay, we're starting to, we're gonna reopen the parks.
What did they actually say?
It must have been something closer to,
well, the character, that's tough
because we still have the social distance
so maybe there's something we can do
to, you know, they can wave from,
they're still on opportunity.
There is no way that any, but unless,
unless we have characterized Chay Peck as being a heel
and he has shown his evil cards in the recent past,
did he come in, I don't know if he,
I don't think he carries a cane,
but maybe just for evil purposes, he carries a cane,
he whacked it on the conference table and said,
hug ban, that's what it is.
We're all beating around the bush here.
Hug ban is what we're doing.
You mean like a madman meeting
where he just wanted to underline
exactly what they were getting at it.
Like, it would get to the core of the idea
of what we're selling here
and we're selling that we're banning hugs.
That's gonna be this new policy going forward.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
And yeah, he has a cane.
I assume it's like a diamond encrusted cane.
Like whatever the,
Poppins banker, head banker.
I was gonna say like kingpin, can't type cane.
More like kingpin, yeah.
Yeah, we brought the kingpin up recently.
One of our favorite characters in fiction.
Yeah.
Yeah, so yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
I bet he wears that big white coat too around Chay Peck,
that is the big white kingpin coat.
Oh yeah, yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Well, I see, is there maybe kind of like a,
you know how Oswald Cobblepot
like cleans himself up for appearances?
Like when he's making his mayoral appearances
in Batman Returns.
Right.
He's a little more dressed
and that's the Chay Peck we see.
But Chay Peck behind closed doors
has like bile running down his chin.
That's a full, full penguin.
The black blood, the fish bits, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He definitely has black blood, yeah.
Like the penguin.
He just orders big pictures of black blood.
Yeah, that's, yes.
Scared assistants bring it in.
Which also is in the commissary is labeled
Walt's favorite black blood, like most food items.
It's starting to get to the point.
I saw someone say, there was one of the buffets,
it's like there are 13 items labeled Walt's blank.
Really?
Between desserts and main courses.
And it's just like, what?
Walt's poke, I don't think they had that in his time.
Well, it's beloved crow nut.
Smoothies were not popular at this time.
Let's add the other CEOs if we're doing this then.
You know, E. Card Walker's favorite cobbler or something.
Favorite dip.
Michael's.
Jell-O molds.
Yeah.
Michael's favorite.
Michael's favorite pudding.
In the 80s, Michael's favorite cocaine.
Cocaine, yeah.
Oh yeah, favorite Chasta, favorite Tab.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
So anyway, this all just strange to me.
The real journalists are writing about the hug ban.
And then the craziest one,
this headline goes on a little longer,
but the beginning of USA Today's headline about this,
Miss Warm Hugs.
Warm?
Who brought warm into it?
Hang on.
The warmth of hugs is not exclusive to Disney parks.
No.
I have hugged people in this time.
I have not waited to hug people
since the beginning of this hug ban.
And when I've hugged people, there's been warmth off of there,
but the human body is warm.
I would say a character hug is probably less likely
to be warm because you're hugging fabric.
That, yeah, there's a barrier
between the heat of the human body and the,
I mean, unless somebody's really overheating in that costume.
Yeah, some of those costumes, I mean,
might absorb the heat of the sun.
But I feel like they're pretty stiff.
They're pretty sturdy
because they gotta be used for a while and take a beating.
They've got to absorb a lot of hugs.
Yeah.
Have to be hug resistant.
Rough felt.
And a lot of those, I guess a lot of the characters,
like have, the fabric is black
and that's absorbing a lot of heat.
That's true.
You could end up with some pretty extreme warm
because of that.
Here's what I'll say about the warm hug discussion
we're having here.
I don't believe I've hugged, oh no,
I've hugged Chewbacca because he forces you to hug him.
I've got, yeah, Chewbacca on here.
But I haven't hugged a character,
like Chewbacca is the only character in years
that I've hugged.
Have I taken photos with him?
Of course, I still like doing that.
But I don't go up and hug them usually, I don't think.
Or maybe I, wait, hold on, maybe I hugged Mickey
in Orlando.
He wants to hug you in his magic show.
It's not conscious.
Like reading about all this stuff
and reading about families being excited they were back,
I was like, oh okay, sometimes I like to get,
see a couple angles on a topic or a few angles on this.
This is definitely one that until people
started covering it, I hadn't really considered that.
Oh yeah, kids can run up and grab the characters.
Yeah.
It's good, I'm for this by the way.
I know, I know, I know.
I'm just trying to think of the warm.
I just, people would be more normal about it.
As you were saying that, I was trying to figure out
if I can remember the heat of the hugs from the characters.
And at first I said I don't think I've hugged
many characters, but as I go back through it,
I think I've hugged a lot of characters in the last decade
if I think about it.
Like Minnie hugs you, she's hugged me many times.
You're playing real cool here.
Have I hugged, I'm not sure.
That's where my mind went.
Who have I hugged?
Cause I didn't think I, but I'm like,
I'm sure Mike hugged Minnie.
Like guarantee it.
I've hugged Minnie a couple times,
but it's not because I'm forcing a hug.
I just want, first of all, one of them was
a character breakfast at the Contemporary,
like seven years ago.
She comes over and hugs me, okay?
She hugged me.
I didn't go like, come here.
Like I didn't do the fingers or anything.
Like there's a photo and she comes over.
Like the natural gesture when you wanna hug,
your fingers all go out all spindly like a witch.
Yeah, I didn't do that.
The fingers.
But it depends.
I think certain characters invite the hug more than others.
So a lot of the characters,
I feel like if we've ever taken photos with them,
just give you like a little handshake
or a little acknowledgement.
Yeah, like a little pat.
I don't think Ruella DeVille is going in for a big one.
With an adult man.
Yeah.
With maybe a kid she is.
Maybe with a kid.
But I think Minnie is instructed to hug everyone.
It's more, it's Minnie's personality.
Yeah.
So I think it depends.
Can I read from this New York Times piece,
there was a little chunk that kinda hit me.
A little chunk.
Hit me for a couple.
Little hug chunk.
When it reopened last April
with extensive health related modifications,
Mickey and Minnie and their cohorts
were kept at a distance from guests.
No hugs, no autographs, no secrets whispered in little ears,
only waving from afar,
which bummed out some families so much
that they canceled or postponed their trips.
So yeah, item one.
Little secrets whispered?
Little secrets whispered.
Little secrets, no secrets whispered in little ears.
So this is the children specifically.
Does that happen?
Don't, I'm here to say, don't.
Just don't.
Like you cannot, I'm not,
I don't wanna give any credence to the psychos
in the press right now,
but that's weird regardless of anything.
But is the, what is this possibly based on?
What do you mean?
Is anyone at any interaction that you,
now granted our ears aren't little anymore.
No.
We don't have little ears, we have big ears.
But. Big ears.
I don't, when you were a kid,
did a character whisper you a secret?
I can see the tableau,
I can see the miming that like, you know,
Chippendale leaning in to whisper,
but not actually saying anything.
Minnie makes the smooch.
Yeah, Minnie makes the smooch.
For adult men.
That's the closest I think that has kind of,
it happened to you, a secret smooch.
Multiple smooches, multiple minis.
For multiple minis.
On both coasts, I believe.
Bicoastal smooch sounds is what's happened to me.
Mike's mackin' with minis all over the world.
Yeah, that's true, but they weren't secret,
I didn't get a little secret.
Yeah.
So.
And here's the weirdest thing,
is that that struck me as well, that's very bizarre.
Then I read the LAist article,
which is of course Disneyland wants your hugs again.
It's been more than two years since Disney characters
mingled with theme park guests,
rubbing noses, whispering secrets,
and most importantly, offering hugs.
What do you mean, two?
What?
Whispering secrets?
Talking about whispered secrets?
Is this on some sort of official Disney copy?
Cause Disney on their like Instagram
was using some of the hugs are back terminology.
But are they the ones being like,
we can whisper secrets again?
Secrets are back, little secrets,
little warm secrets are back.
What is, what are we,
I think this is all weirdly applied by these writers,
unless I'm crazy.
Do listeners out there have stories of little secrets
being whispered in warm ears?
Cause you're not, they're not allowed to talk.
Yes, yeah.
Only is that, so is the idea out there like,
I'm not supposed to talk, but I'm talking only to you.
Cause they should be arrested if they're doing it.
Come on, lean in, lean in.
Goofy wants to tell you a secret.
I hit a man with my car and I drove off.
Don't tell your parents.
Is that a, is that a?
I have two, Goofy wants to tell you a secret.
I'm two children stacked on top of each other.
What are they saying?
I'm naked in here.
Yeah, of course.
That's what, that's the nightmare of the psychos
Jason's talking about.
When you get to college,
you can abandon your traditional family values.
Yeah.
That is not, I think what those people are talking about
in those articles.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Also, are the, like, are the secrets from the character
or from the person playing the character?
Or like, you know, is, is like Jane Doe and actress
in a suit whispering Jane Doe related secrets
via the guys of the, of the, the Daisy suit that she's in.
Right.
Or is, yeah, Mickey like leaking Disney with secrets
in character, is the performer leaking in character?
I saw a screening of Lightyear earlier this week.
Not good.
Like, what is it?
The hair deck has a lot of problems.
It's just the shape.
It's the face.
I don't know.
Everything's off.
He looks like Sonic somehow.
The early version of Sonic.
Long Sonic.
It's like they took the teeth right out of the first one
and put them in the, put them in Lightyear's mouth.
They're reusing, we bought, Disney bought Sonic's teeth
and got them cheap because nobody wanted them.
I don't know why.
Don't tell anyone kid.
This is a secret.
They try to make a joke in the movie about like,
this isn't based on the toy.
It's based on the man who was the toy was based on
and it just doesn't land.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm trying to finish this secret.
Come on kid.
I got 20 minutes that I got to change
and get over to Universal where I'm a minion.
I got minion secrets to tell.
I don't know.
I don't know what this means.
This is strange.
This is journal.
Are we all, I don't think we like to invoke the phrase
fake news, but is that what's happening here?
I guess.
Is the dying New York Times,
the dying and lying New York Times making up,
seek whispering secrets to us
about secrets that don't happen?
Well, I mean, if you go to YouTube
and search hugs are back Disney,
you get a lot of results.
So again, everyone agreed on this right.
Just like everyone agreed on like, well, what's worth?
What is worth mean to you?
What is Star Wars worth to you?
A couple months rent, a couple months,
few months rent.
Strange group think that got us to hugs are back
and also to whispered, whispered warm little secrets.
Warm little secrets.
Now, how about this?
Do you get secrets if you meet Peter Pan?
He is a face character.
So he's allowed to speak.
Gaston is allowed to speak.
Face characters at a whole other level of strange.
Cause I sure, but couldn't,
but they potentially can give you little little secrets.
Yeah.
I choked on little don't want good.
You should, you should choke on all of this.
I don't want to know Peter Pan's little secrets.
I don't know.
You've got pretty much an open book.
I don't know that you hopefully have much to worry about.
That's maybe my issue with him is how,
what an open book he is.
I think maybe he can button it up a little more.
I'm going to visit you tonight, Scott.
I know where you live.
The biggest secret of all is you can be a boy forever.
Even if you lock your doors,
I prefer coming in through windows.
The internet's made it easy to find everyone's address, Scott.
No.
Do do do do do do.
Peter Pan has the internet.
Yeah. And he knows secrets.
Yeah. He is the same who is lookup ability
that Taylor Lorenz does in the Washington Post.
So maybe, maybe these are the characters
that will tell you a little secret.
Is the ones that are,
have a human face and are allowed to freely speak
to the guests.
I don't know.
I haven't gotten a secret from one of them,
but I'm saying perhaps.
I have to think the guests are so much weirder
to the face care.
Like, cause I know they can spend a little more time
on stage cause they're not hampered.
A lot of them are, you know, indoor meet and greets now
with the princess fairy tale halls, those kinds of things.
So they're, they have to get out of the suits less.
They, so they spend like more time in front of the crowds.
Right. So are you saying they have more or less time
for giving the secrets?
They've got more time for giving secrets.
Okay.
But I feel like the,
the guests might be the ones giving them secrets.
Being extremely secret.
Oh, I'm sure there's little secrets being given
by the guests to the performers constantly.
Yeah.
I guess that maybe that's what they mean.
Maybe.
You go, the hugs are back.
You can go hug one of the rescuers.
And if you have a secret, it'll be safe with Bernard.
I don't resent them,
but this is a marriage of convenience now.
And then Bernard guy and Bernard suit just
left there like, uh, what do I do with this information?
Bernard, the love is gone.
Bernard, what do I do?
How do you and Bianca keep it fresh after so much time?
You're so different.
She's so much classier than you.
How does it distract?
Oh, I guess that's a trick.
They learned.
Wait, oh, I see.
So maybe us growing apart, maybe we need to go more apart
and that'll bring us more together.
You solved our marriage.
He shrugs.
Just like, hey, okay.
Tip of the hat shrug, the two things they can do.
Mime's hopping on that giant bird.
Fly away on.
Falls backwards.
Is there a, do the characters have,
cause they have their handlers.
Do they, is there something they can do?
Can they tug on the arm of the handler?
There's, oh, there's a panic.
There's a panic motion.
Yeah.
I've been told too many uncomfortable secrets today.
I need to go freshen up backstage all of a sudden.
Oh yeah, Bernard is feeling, he's feeling a little warm.
He needs to go have a soft drink.
He remembered a mystery he needs to go investigate.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
To rescue his appetite.
This is all so strange to me.
Jason, also you're right.
There is some, there's a weird thing going on here.
I think we all, look, I would love to spend
as little time as possible in my life
and on the podcast talking about this new thing,
which is anyone who disagrees with you about anything,
you just call them a groomer.
It's the most bizarre, dark, dark.
Everyone stop and think about how fucking dark that is.
And it just happens all the time.
Our elected officials just throw that out there every day.
So it's weird that there's so much of that
flying in Disney's direction because of this don't say gay.
So all that's going, that's the point of view
of like hardcore conservatives is Disney are groomers.
And the further you go, there was just a crazy protest
at the Disney lot that's all the most insane Q bullshit ever.
They moved from Tin Horn Flats,
which is a bar that was run by a Q guy.
Little bit north.
Yeah, not far from here.
That was an old like kind of saloon type place.
And then all those people moved from that weekly thing
over to protest.
It feels like that.
It's not weekly.
They only did it once.
Yeah, yeah.
They did it once and there were some smaller ones
during the shutdown.
Every now and then I'd see like a couple people around there.
But yeah, and also to be sure,
a lot of those people commuting in,
like not exactly local, I'm sure maybe a handful.
And some people just walking by going, what is this?
But yeah, a lot of-
As part of all that, whatever, it's a catch all.
I don't think they even all know what they're pro,
cause some people are just like,
don't get mixed up in politics, Disney, all the way to,
well, Disneyland has underground mines
where they capture children and make them,
whoa, whoa, what are we talking about here?
And it's now, they're bringing back all of the,
you know those stupid, like the letters spell out sex
and the Lion King, the things we've been talking about
since we were nine.
The rescuers.
They're all back and they're all proven.
Oh, the rescuers, there you go.
Yeah, the picture, the one second of nudity, right?
There's like a piece of-
Is that, I always get them confused.
That one rigid tools.
I've talked about rigid tools before.
I think that's from the Roger Rabbit short.
Yeah, that's not, no, that this is,
there was just like a literally,
like if you would have to freeze frame on one second,
somebody put a true like picture of like a naked somebody
in that movie.
Got you.
And the animators just snuck that in for fun.
Single frame.
For fun, yeah.
Just a little fun.
Anyway, all that stuff that,
there is not one example of it past 1994.
It's all back.
It's all proof that they are like,
what's the like, Adrena Chrome, all Adrena Chrome,
all that stuff.
Yeah.
This is mad.
Anyway, this all is, it's the miserable pocket of humanity
that's opened up.
But so there's all that and that's what Disney is.
And they're indoctrinating children and all these horrors.
But then also Disney stopped allowing hugs in the park.
And then you end up with like this horrible account,
Libs of TikTok.
Oh yeah.
They took a video of a girl who's running up to hug
Winnie the Pooh.
And then somebody, a Disney employee, the handler,
dives in front as if like, no, no, no, do not.
It is bizarre to watch and it's strange that we're at this
point in our society, but it's the disease, not the,
whatever they think is going on.
But okay, so this video is posted with the tweet,
pathetic, never forget what they did to the children.
So we want hugs.
We want all the hugs, but also Disney, our pedophile groomers.
What, how do you?
Scott, it's almost like you're saying that some of these
people are insincere in their actual beliefs and they might
be just saying shit to fucking flamethrow and try to win some.
Just making.
Dumb proof.
I'm just saying it sounds like that's what you're saying.
These are human beings and humans surely who would never
resort to this kind of will never be happy or satisfied.
You mean, you mean to tell me that much of American life
in every aspect is just based on people openly lying
to your face and getting away with it.
And then when you go, you're lying, you're making this up.
They go like, no.
What is that?
They duck away.
They have, that's the emoji with no mouth on it.
I don't know.
I mean, I, I, I saw a couple of people like, look,
if you step back and look at this, all the people screaming
about pedophile and like secret stuff about it, it's all like,
this is just an insane right wing.
Like this is the current flavor, not just of like the,
every five to 10 years, there's a wave of anti LGBTQ hate
that just bubbles up.
But also it's just like, oh, they're also trying to get
people to not watch sports.
They're complaining about the NBA, the NFL being too woke
now. So they're just trying to cut off stuff that like
families or middle America does like Disney organized sport,
like just to solely keep them in the insane, you know,
the insane asylum of right wing media of reactionary media.
You cut them off from anything where they might find a
community of other people who are different than them or a
community of shared interests outside of whatever Donald
Trump's toilet rant is this week, like whatever insane thing
is going on or isolating them from like any entertainment or
experience that might give joy or, or might like help them
step away from all of the, the, the myriad of things that make
them full of rage.
No, they need to be, it can only rage rage 24 hours a day.
About a thousand things.
Yeah. Yeah. So it's just, yeah, it's just, it's not, I think I
said on the heritage USA, it's like, we've just all given up
on shared realities.
Like you can't rationally talk to a lot of these people.
Like you can't try to win them back to reality because so many
are so far gone.
Yeah. Yeah.
But they're God willing, hopefully not the biggest cross
section of the country.
They're just the loudest.
Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
And the most irritating with the worst social media presence
you've ever seen.
All that darkness said, like, look, it's all the hugs are good.
I, as far as like that, like this is now on the table for, for
children. That's great.
That's nice.
I don't know that I fully buy it.
I guess parents, you know, parents would have to say if it
is true that like that their kids were like crushed by the
inability to hug the characters, I guess, you know, that probably
is true in some cases.
Yeah.
I don't know if it's like, if it's fully across the board, I
feel like there's a lot of reasonable, like, oh, yeah,
sorry, we can't do that right now, but we will.
I don't know if that's like, that's going to be the number
one topic when the child turns 21 and is in therapy is that for
two years they couldn't.
That's well, that's what I'm saying about this.
Never forget what they did to the children.
That's implying is like scarred because of this one, you know,
how kids remember everything that happened to them before two
and a half.
Yeah.
This will, this is sending them on the course to like a drug
addiction.
Oh yeah.
Also children are disciplined all the time.
Like, and that the other thing,
Oh yes.
Imagine a kid being told, don't do that.
Yeah.
Unprecedented.
The other thing I saw people pointing out is that like these,
the people most like frothing in the mouth about pedophiles,
they're not helicopter parents.
They're not raising their kids diligently.
They give the kids the iPad.
They check out.
The kids can find anything on the internet.
Like God knows what they're looking at.
Yeah, absolutely.
The yeah, I don't, I also wonder what those videos like did the
like conservative parent like send the child to poo to get that
video.
Oh yeah.
Because I bet, I bet.
Yeah.
Like that's, that's total like red meat,
video content for all those terrible sites.
So I wouldn't be shocked if that was like, they saw that that would have,
they knew that would happen and they sent their kid in to be a prop in their
political game.
Oh yeah.
A hundred percent.
Like, yeah, like the weird little, yeah, the teens that I saw wearing the like,
not my cunt, not my president, like 13 year old shirt.
What do you wait?
13 year old wearing like a not my president shirt at Epcot center.
And it's like, what are you talking about kid?
Like who gave you that shirt?
You don't care.
Yeah.
The rich future of all of the people who were like, who people who will be
dropping their whole lives.
Yeah.
I was a viral mask freak out in supermarket star in 2020.
That was 25 years ago.
Yeah.
Pretty sweet.
Pretty good.
Good times got picked up a lot of places.
Yeah.
My parents were pretty big into the satanic panic in the eighties.
Like we had a safety sign, you know, and we checked all the candy and Halloween
for razor blades.
My mom did that too.
Well, that's true.
No, the razor blade.
I mean, yeah, that was kind of a thing.
All this said, I do wonder what are the numbers of like families canceling trips
because you can't hug the characters.
I would have to say it was probably due to the, you know, novel Corona virus
and the societal unrest and general anxieties and increased pricing, more
pain in the ass planning, more difficult travel, being more difficult, park
reservations, not being able to get food reservations or park reservation.
Like the parks being more unpleasant these days.
Everything being a lot.
Yeah.
Your money going a lot less farther.
The concept of resort, the definition of resort really being stretched at how much
legwork you, the consumer has to do now.
Yeah.
I would say all of that combined might be playing a factor more than just the hug.
But now, but they are back.
They're back.
Are we, hugs are back.
Are we, are we going to hug?
Are we hugging now?
It's been a while.
Would this even have occurred to you if there weren't headlines about hugs or
bed, whatever?
I mean, I guess we're not the audience for it necessarily, but now we got hugs on
the brain.
You're saying, am I excited to hug?
Was that, is that something that like I'm getting?
Yeah.
Well on the next Disneyland visit, will you sort of like, oh, you know what?
I can hug now.
Generally speaking these days, I'm only interested in taking a photo with a
character that's the obscure character because I'm a high, you know, I'm a
smarter Disney fan who really, you know, loves the obscure characters like Robin
Hood, the Hipper characters.
I'm a Hipper Disney fan as well.
Yeah.
Robin Hood, you know, he's obscure, but yeah, I don't really, I do, I do wait
for like a photo op like that, but I, other than that, we don't, we're not really
like waiting on Main Street for one of the fab five or anything.
No, if they come out, they're like, come out a side door.
So if you happen to catch them, I like, if you catch them, but they don't usually
like to take a photo with you in that, that spot.
Yeah.
But I would take a photo of them alone.
Was there walking?
I want to, I would examine that tiny little bugs land that he had man on the
last for a while.
Well, that's a delight.
I got to poke around.
That's a true delight.
Oh yeah.
That's fascinating.
Yeah.
Ant-Man has a shrunken bugs land, which was there before the Marvel campus.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's funny.
Walks around.
You can, and he'll show it to you in a little bubble.
Fantastic idea.
And that, and now canonically that's what happened to bug.
Yeah.
Really good.
Drunk.
I'm going to ask them about the logic problems.
Like, well, I thought this was an old star campus.
Isn't, isn't this a manufacturing plan before this was here?
You should have, I mean, I would like to see you have a dialogue and try to
get one over on that.
Moon night just beats the shit out.
It just goes ham on me.
Drags you up to the top of the Avengers.
I got a little secret for you.
Nobody gives a shit.
Shut the fuck up.
You're a fucking tool.
This one's from Bob.
Bob tapex favorite Marvel characters, Moon Knight, cause of how violent he is.
Cause of how bad he beats people.
Can I play him?
I want to play him.
It's only second to only the Punisher.
Um, I, uh, here's a question.
Does anybody have this, this POV that in a way, um, well, I'll just, I'll,
I'll just say it for myself in a way I might slightly miss the, the, the, uh,
distanced waving of the characters.
Uh, and, or I, you know, maybe I kind of hope and wish that they will still do
some component of that because I like that you've had a guaranteed, oh wow.
It's, it's, it's the big five.
It's all the characters.
I saw them.
I waved at them.
That's kind of all I wanted to do.
And I'm a little bit biased in that area because as I mentioned in the live show,
I took my son to Disneyland for the first time.
Most magical part of it by far, as soon as we got in, as soon as we got
under the train track, uh, there's Mickey right at that end of the train track,
right past the bridge, big wave interaction that he lit up at.
It was so magical.
Like clearly waving right at my son.
It was really great.
So this notion that those, these are like hollow and, uh, cold, I can
attest to is not true.
Like, yeah, my, my son's first Mickey interaction was really magical done this
way and we got to have it without waiting in a goddamn line for 45 minutes.
You know?
Yeah.
I, my stat also picked up on it's like, I hope they keep the things where it's
like, you know, uh, goofy and Max are fishing off the, you know, pier in
California adventure.
Great.
I really like that.
Or these, I mean, the very nature of these Marvel interactions are they're up
walking around on that Avengers building.
Um, and I don't know if that's like, does that stay or are they on the ground
more? Cause I kind of like, I think those are going to pass by that they're
like the Royals and they, they wave.
They like, with the people on the ground.
Yeah.
They're like patrolling.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
They're keeping an eye on it.
Marvel stuff.
And I've said this over and over again, I get, I, I, they change characters out.
Moon Knight is on is there already.
He's on top at night.
He shows up at night and there's a bunch of smoke on top of Avengers, uh, the
Avengers, whatever it's called the building headquarters.
Uh, uh, and yeah, like all that stuff is all the stuff and I don't, when it's
not a galaxy's edge episode, but that's all the stuff we want more of a galaxy's
edge, but they they're packing it into Marvel land and yeah, all that distance
stuff is cool.
Like the, the, the topicality that's probably not the correct word, but the,
like the currentness side, the fact that there are so many Marvel projects that
maybe work with a little more frequency than the star.
Oh, that's not true.
Star Wars.
All the Star Wars things are very popular, but then a lot of them aren't allowed
in the universe of galaxy's edge.
Issue.
Yeah.
So that what Marvel has, which is just, it's a free for all and anybody can be
there.
So when every new show comes out, characters are there with top of the line suits
and they can really smart.
So smart and they can have different outfits.
Oh yeah.
Mr.
Knight.
Well, cause there was moon night and then there's the other ego.
Yes.
Sir.
Night was in a little suit.
Mr.
Night is wearing the suit and they have moon night and it's regular, like
superhero outfit.
And then Loki when Loki was in his like prison jumpsuit was walking around in
his prison jumpsuit for like two weeks.
It's great.
Uh, uh, and all that stuff.
Like I remember early on they were in Epcot.
There was like, like Pooh Bear was just like, had like a little net and he was
trying to get butterflies.
Yeah.
People were walking by going, Hey, look at that.
Like that's actually more of what I thought was a little kid of like, I want
the characters like hanging out, like live here, right?
So they're just like hanging out here.
Going about their busy.
Yeah.
Those little, those little scenes in a way, aren't they cooler than just, I
took a staged photo with, uh, I guess.
You want both.
I mean, especially the little kid.
Yeah.
I hope it's a blend.
I hope they keep some version of what they've been doing.
And practically it also disperses the crowds cause that's, that's people
occupied not on attractions and not at restaurants.
So you're getting people around.
Well, I, you know, I did, I did think about that and I do like what it does
for if, if character meet and greet lines, swallow people and they're
less in ride lines.
I love that.
That's great.
If it can like, or we lost a hundred people to, uh, to, you know, to meet
Daisy or whatever it is.
Yeah.
So I, I, yeah, hopefully, hopefully Chaypeck will let the money flow for both
of these things and not just like the one that he thinks makes more money.
Cause the other thing is ambiance.
Yeah.
You know what that, that adds to the atmosphere of the park.
I think, uh, uh, ambiance and also live entertainment in general is coming back.
Uh, more and more.
Um, but I think those were things that were missing early on when like a lot
of the restrictions dropped and it's just like, oh my God, what are all these
crap?
And it's like, well, all the ancillary stuff is not eating up people like it
used to.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
You don't have people who are the people who like plant and wait for a parade for
two hours so they aren't in the line.
Yeah.
Less of those like, yeah, the little it's all competing for, we're all going to
try to get on the ticket attractions all at the same time.
So it's a little chaotic.
Yeah.
Is it, here's a question I have about the hug ban, the dreaded hug ban.
In a way like, okay, am I crazy that there there's the, there's the, we had
to stay distance for a while.
Uh, and there's obviously the current virus risk, but are, are we not dealing
with the most, the biggest masks ever made?
Well, right now, these are not a medical gray, but like, isn't, is not a Mickey
head giant mass is Mickey's head.
Can 95 certified.
Is that what we're at?
Yeah.
You would think you would be able to adapt the mask, the Mickey mask, the
Mickey helmet to have the full and 95, at least you'd least just wear it under it.
Yeah.
You could easily wear a medical grade mask under it.
I wonder if you may, but if you're, if you're doing medical grade mask and then
Mickey head on top of it, maybe now the breathability is, oh, it's not great.
It's terrible.
No, but they were certainly doing it.
Yeah.
But I'm sure they, you think that, do you think those characters, do you think
these characters have masks on now that there's now that hugs are back?
I think it depends.
I think it's a, it's dependent because, because most mask mandates are going away.
So I would assume it might be up to the performer, but I could be wrong.
It would depend.
I don't know what their internal policy is with the cliques.
These are close interactions, I suppose.
But I don't know if you're outside, I don't know what the science even, I
don't know how many seconds you really need to be in the presence of someone.
I don't know how, like, can you catch a Macron just by whispering a little
secret for 15 seconds?
I don't know.
Biggest, it was the reason to Institute the, the hug ban and the unnamed, but we
know that there was a shadow, a warm secret thing as well, right?
Cause that's more under the umbrella of the general hug ban.
Yes, exactly.
That was the, yeah.
Little secret, cause there secrets are breathy, right?
You're putting extra breath into it to like make the words cut through.
Yeah.
So there's a lot of breath going into that.
And that's, yeah, that's going to spread these variants, maybe more
than just regular speech.
Secrets.
Yeah.
It is that is scientifically proven that secrets give off more aerosols
than a regular sentence.
That's for sure.
So what's made us all so crazy for the last few years, nobody's getting there.
We're getting our secrets out.
Um, yeah.
All living with all of our worst secrets.
Yeah.
They, the gossip, you know, the hot gas, the tea just doesn't hit over zoom as
well.
The tea doesn't hit, you know, also a good way is if you've ever seen, I don't
know if we've even posted a video of it.
There's of course a great Chuck E cheese instructional video on cleaning the suit
that you can find online.
Yeah.
Uh, where they say, I think the spray Lysol inside the head to clean.
I, I, someone messaged me and said they worked at a Chuck E cheese in high
school and they're like, that happened maybe once a year.
Of course.
Oh, that best.
But I don't know.
I don't know.
Does Lysol Lysol would probably kill.
Yeah.
Kind of killed her own virus.
So maybe you just on each break, you go in and you Lysol the head.
Although then you'd get, yeah, then you got a long, you're in a rain fog.
Yeah.
You pass out from.
All right.
So the Lysol of the head is not a good idea.
Maybe for a regular cleaning.
I have one more question about the hug situation.
Um, who do, who do we most want to hug?
Now that this is what the Instagram asked as well.
And I was going through the comments and I was trying to get a, get a sampling
of what people, um, people want to, who want, who want people.
Was the question posed to Instagram?
Yes.
On the Disneyland Instagram.
Oh, we didn't do this.
So we know he didn't do this.
We will, but, uh, somebody's, these are just, I'm not going to say who, what
their username, but somebody said Pinocchio at the top of my list, which I
was like, really?
Okay.
Um, you know, people obviously Mickey Minnie, uh, obviously, uh, one of my
favorite ones is, and I, I know what they meant, but they said Winnie the Pooh in
July and I was thinking that might be funny cause they like have a month
preference for certain characters.
It's best to hug Winnie in July.
It feels like it's going to be a clammy Winnie.
Right.
Yeah.
Especially if it's the critter country.
Maybe not in California, dry or heat out here.
Warm hugs, not clammy hugs.
Yeah.
Um, but you know, I was looking through these comments and I was like, these
aren't hip Disney fans.
These are just the normal characters.
They're not saying anything cool.
Like, uh, the great mouse detective or anything.
You want a hug?
Oh yeah.
Basil from Basil.
Basil and Brad again.
I would, I would light up at the movie.
I haven't seen in 30 years character Basil.
If I saw him in the park, I would get, I would wait in line for that.
You're waiting for Basil.
So I guess I'm waiting for Basil.
I didn't think of it until just now, but that is who I'm waiting for.
I think, um, you know, a big character, uh, big Al, I think is probably a good
one.
That's a lot.
He can really give him a hug.
Chewbacca we mentioned.
Yeah.
Big Al out a lot.
It's usually sometimes I see him more in Florida buildings.
A lot of more Weasley bears.
I still Weasley bears.
Yeah.
Riddell.
Wendell is out.
I think a Groot could be interesting.
That seems to actually, are you allowed to hug Groot?
That's what I, yeah.
If it's, if it's kind of a puppety, he's like a rigid, he's on stilts.
Whoever it is, is on stilts and he's kind of a plastic.
I bet you're not allowed to hug Groot.
Well that full size Groot is there like a teen Groot?
Cause little Groot was one of the, I think one of the robot little meat and
Greek one where they fussing with that.
They did that in Florida.
They had a little robot baby Groot.
You don't want to hug that too delicate.
In California, they have full size Groot.
I don't think teen Groot has been seen anywhere as a character.
I don't think, but maybe you're saying maybe you could hug him.
Maybe, maybe coming for Thor love and thunder.
Well, cause of love in the title.
You mean, you could, oh, no, just that he's probably in that movie.
It would probably be walking around Avengers campus.
Hugs and thunder.
Yeah.
What about Korg?
Why isn't Korg in?
That's pretty good.
He'd be Tycho.
Like TT's character Korg.
But you would want him to do like some.
Rock monster.
Yeah.
You would want that mouth because some of the mouths you can move, you
would want him to, you know, riff with you a little, like he could tell you a
secret.
I see a Korg could tell you a secret.
Yeah.
I, you gotta get like an improv performer though.
Well, yeah, that's, yeah.
You gotta get him doing, doing some funny prov.
Yeah.
I've ever heard you call it.
So anyone has ever called it.
Yeah.
You just get some problems going.
If you're on a tight cassette, some problems going down.
That's yeah, you're right.
No, you're right about that.
He calls it prov.
What he does is prov.
This flag means prov.
I is the, is the hug ability more about fuzziness or size, like kind of
floppiness.
What do you think makes a character the most huggable?
Well, is it also like, like a Victor?
Can you, does Kylo Ren hug?
Like, can you cajole?
Oh, I don't think he's supposed to.
Who probably wouldn't like it.
Probably wouldn't like it.
You kill him with kindness.
Yeah.
Stormtrooper.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I'm not, I'm not as an adult man.
I'm not looking to get it, get in there really and get a long warm one from
anyone, any of the characters.
I don't know.
Secret one.
I'm not looking for that.
I swear to you.
I don't know why it says it seems like I'm defensive about this.
I'm not.
So I'm not sure that it's, I think like, I will say this hugging Chewbacca is a
little gross.
Oh, interesting.
The fur is like a little matted and it's kind of like, and also there's something
I don't think I don't like about it is that like I see him hugging everyone else
and it loses its specialness a little bit to me, even though I think it's like a
kid, like the big reveal when Chewbacca comes around, if they still do that at
the, at the, uh, whatever it's called.
Galaxy's Edge.
No, no, no.
The other one, the Star Wars launch bag launch, but thank you still hanging in
there.
So, yeah, well, yeah, nothing else for it.
So now we need to put, but the way they did that, they do that meet and greet is
really cool and like you would see kids, kids like, cause Chewbacca basically kind
of comes around the bend and he like greets you and welcomes you in.
Like it's a whole thing and it is a really well done thing, but like he may
Chewbacca makes you hug him before the photo op and like he's hugging like
everybody and the fur is matted and I feel like there was like a weird like
smell, maybe.
Uh huh.
No, probably a vague smell, not horrible or anything, but I was like, this is
kind of not, I don't need to hug this performer kind of in it built into the
character, right?
He's always giving hugs and those.
Yeah, sure.
Right.
Yeah.
It's kind of grabbing everyone.
Uh, so I like that.
I like the idea of it, but I'm saying actually doing it isn't the best thing
there was a rug made of Chewbacca's fur.
It would just naturally get so filthy.
Yeah.
Like that level.
It's just, it's, it's thick.
Cause it's long fur, like poo bears, greasy, who bears fur is like, it's a thin,
thin coat of fur.
He's got, he's a bear.
He's got, or he's a plush bear, I guess.
That's my answer for hugs.
And I, again, I'm not out there seeking long, warm hugs, but if I were to go back
with my son who had a very nice, it was a very nice wave at Winnie the Pooh, sorry,
libs of TikTok, it's possible that those can be very nice.
Um, but now that hugs are back, I think I would join him.
I think I would, cause there's a way.
You would join him in a hug.
I think I would, uh, I would show my son a hug.
Uh, I think if, because there's the little loop you can do in Pooh corner where it's
yeah, yeah, right.
Where you hit, I want to say it's Eeyore and Tigger and Pooh doing that grew.
I might be the most sentimental for those and I've gotten to pass them on to my son
already.
Yeah.
He loves them.
So like, you know, I'm not going to, I'm not going to make a big point of the
hub, but if hugs naturally happen, that would be your probably be nice.
And Eeyore, I hadn't thought about Pooh seems obvious just cause he's the most
heartwarming character, but Eeyore might feel nice because the character is a
character that needs a hug.
That's true.
Yeah.
You're doing a service at that point.
Cheering up Eeyore.
What if that's nice?
What if that's serious?
Cause yeah, they have this perfect little, if you've not been there, they have like a
kind of, yeah, a line that basically takes you around to a stage station.
I think they're all kind of around the corner from each other.
You don't see them all.
Yes, exactly.
Here's this little nook and here's the next, the next warm hug.
No.
So I think, look, if anyone's listening, this is going to be impossible, but
anyone listening, they see Scott and his son come.
It would be really funny if you got like, you hit you went and you got Winnie and
you go over here and you get Tigger and then you go around the bend and he goes,
hi, it's Peter.
And Peter is in the third spot and you didn't know Eeyore has been replaced.
The Disney people have to coordinate.
They have to know I'm there.
That's why I said it's impossible.
Yeah.
Like do do do.
Hey, come on, Scott and son, let's go.
I accidentally winged a flock of birds and I need to take a little rest here in
country because I'm hurting a little before I get the rest of the way to
Neverland.
You are told too many secrets and he overheated.
Now I'm taking his place.
I'm not about travel bans and restrictions and putting up borders, but let me be,
let me be clear about this.
Peter Pan is not allowed in Poot Corner.
Okay.
All right.
Pan is banned.
Pan is banned in Poot Corner.
I'm just thinking about this.
Like the logic puzzles they jump through, you know, they put together the hoops they
jump through sometimes.
Peter Pan, you know, he can fly so practically go anywhere and the power of
imagination and, uh, you know, youth.
Imagination can get by any land and make it make sense.
You know, so.
The power of a big cement wall, which I will build if that's what it takes.
Um, if I can, I'll do it in Florida.
If I can convince DeSantis to build a, I'll like, uh, you know, I'll, I'll tell
DeSantis that Chaypec said he is, uh, he made fun of his tie or something.
Oh really?
And then we get, now that they're now that the, you know, Reedy Creek is gone.
I think that allows me and DeSantis to work together to build a big concrete
wall to keep Peter Pan out of, uh, at a Poot Corner.
There's.
There's, you should have, there should be a video of your son running at Peter Pan.
And then you enter the frame, like the, like the employee in that other video and
check pan into the rivers of America.
Hell yes.
Gladly.
Can't fly now.
Can you?
Like, you're not like, there's a great, I, Jason, I think those was a crazy dog
market, uh, Jason was talking about.
There's a performer, a wrestler named Keith Lee, who does this move where he
does a crazy, like kind of chat, like check with his shoulder to another guy.
And send some flying.
And there's a great jiff of him doing this to Adam Cole and he knocks him into
the audience.
And I just imagine that's what you were doing to pan shooting him into the
rivers of America.
Like just with crazy velocity.
This is, this is something I'm going to have to watch out for in my parenting
journey is that I might just like run up and rush elbow somebody who in the
corner of my eye looks like Peter Pan coming from my kid, but I didn't realize
it's just wearing a green shirt.
Yeah, right.
Were there any stores where you wear a green is the uniform green at any, at
like a Friday, TGA Fridays.
Maybe.
Oh yeah.
Or like whole foods.
Yeah, maybe I forgot.
I don't know where you wear green, but I might, yeah, some poor employee of
somewhere is going to get shoved into a shelf because I know, no, no, I swear.
I thought he was Peter Pan too bad.
It wasn't worth a little secrets to my son.
Couldn't take the chance.
So Scott, uh, that's our parent pan is banned and don't.
Don't come to our shows wearing green shirts and pants because it activates Scott.
It's like a man, shurian candidate style, a code trigger.
Ironically, it's what turns me Hulk, even though Hulk is green.
Yeah.
It's a whole colors make me Hulk to reduce the pan in the world.
Um, okay.
Well, I think that covers hugs and hugs being back warm hugs and, and
special secrets.
I did see, uh, my chat did point out and this, this is actually the
thing that made me go like, Oh, well I like that.
Uh, you know, the, the.
Care of the areas where the characters had been distanced, you know, greeting
like the car they circle fountain area and the front steps of the main street
railroad station, you, the guest can now access like you can go through there.
And I was like, Oh, you know what?
I like both those little plays.
I like going out those big steps at the main street station.
I like that little fountain wooded area by the car fake circle.
Okay.
So by taking away the presence of the characters, now we can go to these
places like, yeah, I see.
Okay.
That's nice.
So we regain some liminal space, like I guess that's good.
Um, okay.
So, uh, stairs are back because hugs are back.
Great.
There's a back.
Um, so, uh, with that being the section about hugs, I wanted to talk a little
about, uh, what felt like a warm hug of an experience, which was my, my whirlwind
trips to Las Vegas, uh, very much Chris angel fueled, um, which I haven't told
you guys too much about, um, so kind of right after we got back from New York
on a Monday night and then it ended up being, it would have had to time out to
where that I would have had to be on a plane Wednesday morning to Las Vegas to
do this whirlwind trip that was planned by our friend, Jason Waller and Eva
Anderson as well, um, just suddenly, uh, basically everybody's been waiting for
Chris's new show, a mystica to premiere.
It was long delayed.
It was supposed to happen a few months ago.
Um, suddenly it's up and running and there's a little bit of a pace to it
maybe, but maybe due to some concern that a mystica might not be long for this
world, I think the ticket sales have been a little bit rough, so it felt like
got, uh, got a strike while Aaron's hot.
Uh, gotta go that.
So it being so quick after the New York trip, I was like, I don't know.
Look, I've been away from the family and I, I, I essentially said no.
And then Jason and Eva kept needling me.
And by the way, you guys were invited to this as well.
Oh yeah.
I was being on the text thread that is largely, it started David Copperfield
oriented and has become, there's just more going on in the world of Chris angel
right now.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, I was, I was back visiting family.
Oh, that's right.
On the East coast.
So I was stuck around and Mike is, uh, uh, sane, more sane than I was.
I was like, oh, tired.
Yeah.
By the end of it, by the end of New York that I was like, I don't know.
Oh, that's so I, I was, I was very exhausted, but then I just, I, well,
here's what pushed me over the edge.
I pretty much had made up my mind.
Uh, too crazy.
Not going to do it.
But then it was sent a seating chart for the Chris angel writer for the, uh,
it basically he does to show, he does his long running show mind freak, and then
he steps down for a little bit.
And then at 10, the late slot, he does his new show, which is a prequel to the
old show, which is we explained when we did an episode about all this with Eva.
It's strange because the mind freak doesn't really have a story.
So how can you have a prequel show to a show without a story?
Um, curious about all of this, but then I saw the Chris angel theater seats about
a thousand, this is at the planet Hollywood hotel, uh, about a thousand,
uh, over a thousand, uh, the seating chart for that night show, uh, about 20
were filled, it was so raw.
And I saw that and just like, I gotta go.
I have to go.
I think I think I'm going to be upset.
Uh, um, much as Eva and her husband, like, look, you're good.
I don't want you around here.
I want you bumming around cause you didn't get to go to Kaplip.
I think I arrived at that point with Aaron.
Uh, all right, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to go.
Um, so 24 hour trip, basically we go to Burbank airport, land in Las Vegas,
uh, meet up with the, uh, the, uh, Mr.
Crew, um, a great group of people.
Jason Walner is there.
Eve is there.
The great John Daly has been on our show is a such a fun group
doing a very stupid thing.
Uh, we land at the airport, a bunch of hassle to get a pass
van to get us all on the road to immediately, um, not even going to
the street, not even going to the strip straight to Moapa Valley to where,
uh, Chris Angel's restaurant Kaplip is open, uh, land go, uh, go, go
straight over there now, as we talked about in this episode on the website
for Kaplip 45 minutes is what is said.
It's only 45 minutes away from Vegas.
Uh, Eva has gone.
So this was not news to anybody, but experiencing this in reality.
Um, w w a rushed drive, a rough drive, because we were like, we had
a whole day of other stuff planned.
So like, boy, we got to get out there and get out and we're calling
the people who got there early.
Like, can you just order our food?
Let's get it.
Move.
There were some concerns about maybe that kitchen is going to be a little slow.
Uh, so we're, we're gunning it.
We're through the desert.
Uh, and in at gunning at speed, hour 15 hour 15 from the, from the airport,
which is admittedly a little south of the strip, but like, if you're anywhere
with traffic, if you're anywhere where people are in Vegas getting out of
there is going to be a hazard.
There's no way on God's green earth.
This is 45 minutes from.
And this, if you haven't been to Las Vegas, the airport is like
shockingly close to the strip.
Like you can get from the airport to like the Southern most like.
Massive can see the Mandalay Bay is like practically next to the airport.
Yeah.
That casino.
You can get there.
We once flew out of a weird wing of, uh, of, of that airport and walked from,
uh, MGM grand, which is very south.
Like there's a part of the airport that is walkable.
It's very, it's just one of the many endless curiosities about Las Vegas.
So if you're picturing like one of the Chicago airports or Philadelphia or
JFK, where it's like far outside center city, not the case in this, it's far
from like Fremont street, it's far from downtown Las Vegas.
But it should do, would not add a significant amount to the trip.
Our four hour 15.
We took, I took a video of precisely when we were 45 minutes away from
Kaplip and it's pure desert.
We are, we are so far past.
Landmarks.
Yeah.
You guys saw that.
And here we are.
It's 45 minutes remaining.
There are no building.
We're so far past the buildings, but one of the buildings on the way out of there,
by the way, is like a big, very cold industrial warehouse for Cisco.
Cisco is the company where they get all of their food, where Chris just
admitted for no reason we ran out of food at Kaplip opening weekend.
Uh, we didn't order enough from Cisco, Cisco, which is they like, they do like
cafeteria style food basically.
Yeah.
So we're like, our food is we passed our food.
We could go into that building and get what we're going to get.
We're look, John, I believe looked up like, wait, this burger is exactly
the same photo on the Kaplip website and the Cisco website.
They did not even dress up the burger in any way.
Um, so a big journey, but a fun journey driving up and seeing, cause we've,
there's not much there, right?
It's a small building and a small building in person, but we've spent so much time.
We did an episode about it and there's this text that's going about it.
So we like, I know every nook and cranny of this building, the flag pole.
They tweeted about the flag pole and the refrigeration units surrounding the
corner and like, it's the pole.
We're here.
I don't think I've felt that way since my first few Disneyland trips.
We're like, it's the Matterhorn off the freeway.
That means we're here.
It felt like that level of joy again, only to be a let down.
Once we get in there, um, we get it.
Yeah.
Much like more claustrophobic place.
I think then I realized that it's like much smaller in person.
We booked the magic room by the way.
So we had the magic room to ourselves, which was also about a third of the
size I imagined in my head.
Um, here's the shocker though.
The Kaplip meal, my Kaplip meal.
Not that bad.
I actually, yeah, I might even say a specifically good.
Wow.
Strangely, I couldn't believe it.
I don't think everybody would have that answer.
I put a lot of thought into what I was going to get and Erin, my
wife coached me through like, well, here's the foods I think would be most
likely to at risk for food poisoning.
Right.
Yeah.
It's like maybe lettuce.
They aren't storing properly your chicken.
You might want to stay away from.
Yeah.
You always think it's like, like it's a lot of times food
poison can be unwashed produce.
So yeah, yeah, sure.
A place is not like, like salad is not their A game.
You gotta, you gotta watch out for that.
Uh, yeah, that was, there was, there was a, at one point we asked somebody who
worked there, what their favorite thing on the menu is and they said, Oh, that
Cobb salad, you gotta love that Cobb salad.
And somebody in the group had the Cobb salad and I'm looking at the remainder
of it and I'm like, this is your favorite.
This is like, this looks like hospital food.
That's the best.
Like my thing was okay, but I, that salad seemed very suspect to me.
But I think nobody got sick.
We were all, and I, and on the way back then I was saying to Jason, boy, I
can't buy, you know what I actually, maybe I kind of liked that food.
Maybe he, maybe Chris pulled off the trick and Jason said, quote, diarrhea
will be the prestige.
I had to say that one out loud.
I liked that a lot.
That is good.
Do you remember the name of the item you had?
I had the mind freak burger, um, which I felt like, you know, that's, that's,
you got the iconic name and it's also, it's got the, the onion ring.
It's got onion rings on it.
It's like a barbecue onion ring style burger, which I kind of miss having a
Carl's Jr. so maybe it took me back to that.
Oh, sure.
Um, and with like an onion ring up, up top, like on vertically stacked on top
of it, so fun presentation.
What Eva said when she was on about the mind freeze, the drip, the mind
freezes were great, Gambusa, ice crushing it, the king, he does it right.
We asked around, nobody's seen Gambusa in a little while, but, uh, so not a
lot of Gambusa information.
Okay.
Did meet somebody there who works there now who for a long time was
Chris Angel's personal chef.
Wow.
Quite a figure to meet some real intimacy closeness to Chris's inner circle.
So we were bugging him for secrets a little bit.
Um, one of which that he himself said that he and Chris, what would
their, like they, they eat very strictly.
Uh, I think Eva looked at, even knows that Chris only eats, uh, is it just
like chicken and rice for today?
Yeah.
Something like that.
And then I think I asked somebody else, Hey, is, um, uh, there are people mad
that it's not sugar's home plate anymore.
The restaurant that it was before.
And she said, yeah, people come asking all the time is sugars coming back.
And we say, no, cause Kablip's staying.
Kablip's not going anywhere.
And there's like a little bit of edge to that.
Said it like George Costanza.
Kablip's getting mad.
It's getting upset.
No, it felt like something you'd say if you'd like barricaded yourself into
some, you're going to have to drink a blip out by the legs.
I think we took quick glances at the menu for sugar's home place and, uh, not
the biggest departure, likely also supplied by the Cisco warehouse.
Possibly.
But also you, I think they had a bar there and you could gamble at the bar.
And they took that out.
See that they've removed elements.
It's not like good elements.
A lot of bars have video poker machines built in that to them.
It's weird.
You would take that out, but then put in, you know, pictures of, we do have
Chris hanging out with pit bull.
So fantastic.
Yeah.
I have to think it's like both the regulations and then just like, well, if
you're going to have gambling machines, you need to have cash on hand for the
winnings for the payout.
That's true.
Yeah.
Um, oh yeah, maybe logistically they didn't want.
Right.
Um, anyways, we had a lot of questions.
We were all everybody while this, while the restaurant part was fun, we were a
buzz over the Knights entertainment, a mystic of what's in store for us at a
mystic, so we're asking, what do you know?
And, uh, the former personal chef said, well, I've, I've seen it a bunch of
times, it's better than mind freak.
It's incredible.
Oh my God.
And we asked him about something that we had heard about that.
Maybe there's something not, it's not that you get wet.
It's that something happens to you in the audience.
Maybe you get messy, you get covered in something.
We didn't know what this was going to be.
And he was cagey about it.
Like, oh, I can't say that's a little seek.
I can't whisper you that little secret.
Um, so we, but, but it was confirmed that like something's going to happen to us.
And I don't know what this is going to be.
Do I need to be concerned?
Is it a, is it gross?
Is it being slimed?
Is it Gallagher watermelon gunk's style?
I don't know what to anticipate here.
Yeah.
Maybe, maybe if there's a rope in your room, you wear it downstairs.
Like a tarp, like as a smock, you know, pull it out right before.
Yeah.
Cover the face with it.
Um, but you know, we did go in with, you know, not, we not wearing maybe our
finest, although in a way this, these are fine items we did buy kablip shirts.
So, uh, Jason's in a kablip shirt.
Eva's in a kablip shirt and I am as well.
So we're, we're dressed in the night's because also because of the kind of ticket
we bought and because it's in the first month of the show, meet and greet with
Chris angel, we're going to meet Chris angel because we did this.
Uh, so now cut to show time.
Um, it's, it's, uh, the theater is more full than I thought.
Still a pretty weak crowd, I would say for an opening week of a big Las Vegas
show from a, essentially a household name or as close to a household as you could
get in Las Vegas.
Um, uh, but so I was disappointed that it wasn't just 20 people, but still kind
of a funny, like, uh, smattering of folks.
Um, we're, we're piling in and we're immediately confronted with what the
thing is going to be that happens to the audience because there is just so much
loose white confetti on the ground, huge chunks of confetti.
Okay.
So it's a big confetti blast.
Well, that's not so crazy.
That was nothing to be concerned about.
Um, oh wait, one aspect before we got into the theater, we had a dinner at a
steak house right next to the theater at planet Hollywood up on the second floor.
I believe it's called the strip house.
Um, nice dinner, good restaurant.
Liked it on the way to the restroom.
There's a little private room with a glass window that you can see into who
should be in there, but Chris angel himself, the steak house right before the show.
Wow.
Um, so, uh, and he is basically like leaning over a table with a bunch of
papers in front of him, which he's working on, he looks like he's crunching
numbers and he's wearing little glasses.
Yes.
I've seen a little glasses, I think.
I've seen a little, yeah, maybe.
Um, it reminded me so much of when Homer puts on glasses to look smart.
Yeah.
He's doing like the crunching numbers in bed.
Um, I liked it.
I thought it was, it was cute in a way.
Um, so, but he looked stressed out and it just added to like, what are
we getting ourselves into?
How is, how full is this place going to be?
What is the show going to be?
He's, uh, he's like doing his doing taxes essentially in the steakhouse,
even though he's got a show.
Like we've got to be in there in 10 minutes.
Why is Chris still here?
So, well, you've got to let the chicken and rice sit for a second.
Let it settle.
Yes.
So anyways, get it.
I have, sorry.
This is the picture of the glass.
Is it easy?
Glad I need to know.
Oh, let's see.
Uh huh.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
Was it, well, was that sent to the thread or did he post that?
Oh, okay.
Gotcha.
Wait, he posted himself looking stressed out in the paper on, he's got a paper on
the table.
He's not, he's, I think looking at his phone, but he's in front of like, well, a
bunch of wine.
Oh, that's exactly what we saw.
Yeah.
A lot.
So I think office is de facto office.
Like, yeah, I think I would have to think like Chris's room at the steakhouse.
Yeah.
I guess so.
And it's right there.
Then you just walk right over.
Uh, it's very convenient.
Boy, that's sharp.
Okay.
Yeah.
So those are his old glasses.
So you yourself could see Chris.
Um, anyway, oh, something I forgot to say.
So the theater is pretty full.
Like we paid a decent amount for these tickets, but I think they're giving them
away for free in some, so.
Some buy one get one free deals for sure.
Go.
Yeah.
Or something.
If you stay at planet Hollywood, maybe they're handing them out.
I'm not sure how they're getting rid of these tickets, but it all, you figure out
the math of it because only the people who paid end up getting the meet and
greet because there weren't that many people at the meet and greet.
So anyways, uh, show begins and, uh, here's where I don't have much to say about a
mystica.
Eva was very specific.
We, we can't do an a mystica episode yet.
I have to see it one more time.
Right.
I have to analyze this a little more.
That my full bearings about a mystica.
Save that for later.
So maybe full of mystica coming down the road, but what can I say about it
without spoiling it?
Cause I would encourage people to see it and to find a free way to see it.
Sure.
Cause I think those exist.
Um, it is a stunning blend of not very much magic, um, the auto tune songs that
I've determined since that at least one of them was written by Chris's wife.
Uh, very like, you know, he's there in that Evanescence pocket for sure.
You're in 2022.
Um, there is a lot of very nineties standup comedy magic, which involves some,
uh, impressions of types of people that are also a little, maybe more shocking
than Evanescence type music in 2022.
And is Chris doing this magic?
No.
Uh, so yeah, so, so why is Chris stressed out in his office?
Not even though he has a show.
Well, because Chris, we were, there was a question with everybody.
Is Chris even in the show?
And, and like, because it's all, it was framed so confusingly, like, yeah, wait,
is he like trying to pass the book and like set up something that has his
branding, but he's not in it.
The answer is he shows up about an hour in, you get an hour of other stuff.
Wow.
He's a presence in it.
You hear his narration.
Um, he's, he basically the, he's taking you through his life and telling you
like, Oh, then I would got into Houdini.
And then you see a guy who was being Houdini and escapes from the tank
and that kind of thing, uh, but he doesn't show up till an hour.
He since has said he's intending to not be in the show anymore at the end of the
month.
So if you're in the Vegas area and you want to see Chris angel, and if this show
still exists, when you're hearing this, just do it soon.
If somehow I'm tantalizing here to go to this somehow,
Jane and I were talking about like, ah, can we squeeze in a Vegas trip more to
see the mirage?
Well, we've never seen the mirage volcano and that seems like it's only got a few
more months life left in it.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah.
You don't know what else this weird like projection thing at the wind,
I would recommend like you go, it's like an outdoor.
Yeah.
The garden.
I want to see the frog.
That's just read it.
Some of those areas.
Yeah.
I would highly recommend that to anybody.
A floating projection or it's like a world of color, but weirder.
So anyways, uh, yeah, he's, he's trying to get out of his own show basically as
little as I can.
I don't think certainly he did not perform any magic.
It's a bunch of just like he, his hands are like lower and then they go, they
shoot a fire and then some preplanned delusion happens in front of them.
Um, thought we had them figured out with the confetti thing, but we had no
idea what was coming for us.
Um, uh, okay.
So full for context, we are in the fifth row.
We're very close to the stage is a big row.
That's, that's this whole group.
Um, and at some point three giant fans get pushed right up at the front of the
stage aimed square at us.
And to be honest, I have the foggiest memory of what plot wise prompted this,
but I believe that it has something to do with a blizzard.
I don't know why.
Maybe this is something that happened to this is Chris's tragic backstory
that he was in a blizzard once.
Right.
Um, could be that.
Anyway, regardless of justification, all of a sudden you are just blasted
bombarded with the thickest layer of white confetti.
The fans are so powerful.
There is so much paper flying at you.
Like you cannot see, you can't like make heads or tails.
If you weren't sitting in a chair and you knew which direction you were facing,
you would feel like you were adrift in the ocean.
It's the only thing I can compare it to.
It's like if you wipe out in a wave, if you're swimming the ocean and something
big surprises you and then you're trying to keep your head above water and where
am I facing and where's the shore?
That's how it was as chaotic as that as noisy.
It's like getting your bill or like if you like crash landed in the ocean from
a flight that went awry or something, it was crazy.
And we're at your bend.
It's blast, really loud fans, really loud Lincoln park kind of music.
You really can't make heads or tails of what the hell is going on.
Just just pure bombardment.
And then it starts to let up a little bit enough for you to see a couple of things.
One, you look down, at least in our case, even I both got like too expensive of
drinks when we got in there.
I believe I glugged my wine pretty fast as I want to do.
Eva had about half a beer to go.
She looks down just pure confetti, just soaking up the drink ruined, expensive
drink ruined.
So we're getting our bearings.
Oh my God, the drink.
Holy shit.
And then I turn just to look at the aghast face of faces of this entire row.
Jason's Eva's next to me.
Jason next to her.
I look over right in time to see a huge plastic bag.
Whip Jason in the face.
Just smack like kind of like where you're like, are you OK?
Did that hurt?
And then you realize, wait, that was not just confetti.
There was garbage in there.
There was literal garbage.
And you look down on the ground like, wait, there's like paper towel rolls and like
and really long strands of confetti and plastic bags and just like.
So this is what happens to you in the show.
You get pelted with garbage.
If you go to the show, you are literally pelted with garbage.
Wow.
That's the answer of what a mystica is.
Gosh, it's a magical garbage pelting.
Now, I have to say, when we we did a show at Christmas time,
a small theater at Lyric Hyperion Theater here in Los Angeles.
And for that show,
I was punching.
I had a hole punch backstage and I had a bunch of printer paper.
And and Erin was helping me do this, too.
I was getting like a handful of like confetti, a handful of white paper
that I could dust off when I was coming in, like I was coming in from out
out in the cold. Yes.
I used about five or six, less than 10 pieces of paper.
Again, enough hole punchy punches that you can fit in a hand.
I was finding those pieces of paper in my bag, in my jacket,
in my sweaters that I was wearing.
I was finding those four months.
Yeah. After that show.
So to then to be pelted with garbage.
Well, the operation it takes to get all to collect all of this paper.
So is it reuse garbage after each show?
I feel like it's got to be right.
Like what seems like it has to be going on where they just leave it all on the ground.
Yeah, I think I think that's going I I don't I don't want any libel
situation because there's a you got to be careful with this camp, with the angel.
Can't the garbage. Yeah, the garbage budget would have to be so high.
If it's all fresh garbage.
Yeah, they're blasting that.
I mean, maybe that's some of the financial struggle of the show.
But I'm like, why did they not clean it up from the prior show?
It was like, yeah, it felt like an inch thick on the ground when we walked in.
So then by the time you're leaving after and then, by the way,
end of the show happens again, they close with it.
Really? No fans are back.
And that one's worse. Wow. So crazy.
Because the Blue Man Group show that I remember seeing as a kid,
they blast the audience with strands, streamers, like strands of stuff.
And but it all kind of ties together and you just pick it up
and throw it on the ground and pretty quickly as soon as the lights came up.
There's people with brooms.
Oh, there it is. There is certainly not that.
No, no, no. Yeah.
Operational issue, I think at least opening night.
Yeah, there's got to be reuse.
Maybe they call it recycling.
Like we're helping the earth by that.
We promise our garbage is that's not hygienic.
I don't think so.
So I think your drinks getting in your eyes of it,
like the force with which it hit Jason,
this was truly hilarious to see.
I never forget seeing that particular whippet getting wanged by a bag.
Was it as hard as when Katy Perry, that clip that's going on,
Katy Perry getting slimed from a box?
Oh, getting blasted in the face by a symbol.
Yeah, I like the strand of people noticing the violence of the sliming.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I am just laughing at either Matt.
There's one or two things happening.
They shredded a bunch of stuff and industrial shredders
and then through the wrappers and the paper towel rolls that they were using.
Just all right and throw this in the bin too.
Or they pre bought bags of shredded material,
dump those in bins, the distribution bins, and then through the bags
and after it was like, all right, clogging out.
I'm out of here.
Well, is it just are they like working with the garbage,
the waste management at Planet Hollywood?
Like, hey, we have some we have an idea that could help both of us.
Everything is on the table as far as an explanation, I think.
I wouldn't be shocked with any of these explanations.
Follow the garbage.
Where does the garbage come from?
Wow. It is so fascinating.
There were such long strands of it that I grabbed them and I grabbed
a bunch of long white
streamers and like wore them like a boa for her.
For her immediately after meet and greet with Chris.
I don't have much to say about this.
We waited in line. We felt pretty amped and we were so excited to approach him.
Three of us in shirts of his restaurant.
Sure. Like this is this is entirely a trip devoted to him.
We have all spent hundreds of dollars in his name.
And so we walk up immediately, just point to the shirts.
Chris, we went to Kaplip.
We went to we were at Kaplip earlier today, Chris.
Oh, that's as much as we got out of him.
Pretty much everything is.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody tried to move
deep into the interaction, which is pointing at Mr.
Waller and saying, you know, this is the director of Borat 2.
Oh, he maybe went up like three percent.
There's a little lilt in the.
Oh, that's that's all he got.
And you're like, this this is, you know, that you want to say, like,
you know, this isn't normal, right?
You know, like maybe to you, but like we've been outside of Las Vegas,
something I don't think you do a lot.
And I'm telling you, people are not traveling to your restaurant
and to your specifically your show that isn't going well.
They don't know about it.
How do you know the only the only people who know about it?
It's it's like all a family tree that descends from Jason Waller.
From us to the audience of the show. Yeah.
So like, you know, you're meeting a very important person
in your fandom, right?
I hope you realize the fandom, I would say.
Yeah, I think so.
So I guess that's why he was nice enough to do that.
Oh, we'll give him a little more.
So so that was that.
So if you want to get pelted with garbage,
and try to find a way to do it for free, a mystic is for now still up and running.
It was a truly unforgettable experience.
But guess what? I come back.
Oh, wow. You've been to.
Generally, only one.
Oh, shucks.
Well, this, you know, this one egged on by Eva.
Eva said you got to do it.
And and she even helped pick out
what she thought were most suited to your personality.
The Kaplip shirts that you guys would like the most actually kind of forget
what Mike's is.
We'll unbox together here.
What does this say?
Wait a minute.
I don't think this is this isn't this is the wrong one.
Actually, no, that's not right.
It's also I were guessing on sizes.
This is not the one that we asked for.
It says not show girlfriend just a place to eat, not show.
Girl. Oh, oh, oh.
Just a place to I don't know what this means.
And this isn't the one that we asked for.
But anyway, but that is mine.
That's yours. Thank you.
Here, I'll toss it over.
And then I really hope they didn't mess up yours, Jason, because we want to.
Oh, thank God. OK.
For you, Jason, American flag, Moapa Valley, proud America.
Yeah, thank you.
There you go.
Oh, where that show your colors.
What did my was my supposed to say?
It's whatever was the most uncomfortably sexual.
I don't know. It's not occurring.
I don't know if it's the one some maybe a sexual mix sort of.
I don't know. Not show.
Girl, not your girlfriend.
I think just a place to eat.
But what is and what's the place you're sexual?
Yeah, I guess.
So like you're having like an affair or something.
I'm not sure.
It's very not clear.
I don't know. I know. I kind of like that you ended up with a very confusing one.
It's confusing, but I think it's dirty.
Jason, you think it's dirty?
I don't. I think it's trying to be a little body, but I don't understand it.
Well, from what I understand, EEC has two meanings.
I don't know anything about that.
Girlfriend. These good boys wouldn't know.
OK, I'm just saying.
Well, enjoy those.
And you know what?
Let's why don't we wrap this up and let's go.
Why don't we all put on our Kablip shirts and then
big round of hugs?
Hugs are back.
Kablip is Kablip is great and hugs are back.
Let's all and let's go head down to that.
Let's let's go hug some characters.
OK, see if they like our Kablip shirts more than the owner of.
Do we feel comfortable enough to an upcoming Disneyland trip?
The three of us have planned to wear the shirts all together.
Be a tad inexplicable, wouldn't it?
Like, wait, are they all wearing Disney? No, no.
Do those three grown men want to make sure they don't get lost in the crowd?
They want to make sure they can identify each other with their shirt.
Maybe it's a bachelor party.
Although my shirt is dirty, so I don't want them.
Although, no, it's confusing. No one will think it's dirty.
Yeah. Well, you have to read it for life, to stare at it for a while.
To determine that maybe it could be if it was a little more clear.
That's a good point.
Yeah, you're safe. Probably safe.
I think you're fine.
What is yours? Does yours say something on the back?
I did the don't wine drink beer.
OK. All right. So confusing. Pretty.
But yeah, I don't know if we were trying to get you the one that said like
Kabloop is the sound a turd makes when it goes in the toilet.
Which is painted in giant letters in the bathroom.
Yes, it's up on the wall in the bathroom. Yeah, that is.
There's last list. Poop splash humor.
OK, so I recommend all of these experiences.
Head to Kabloop, head to a mystic.
And of course, go enjoy the privilege of hugs.
The band is over.
You have survived podcast the riot and we've all survived the dark time
of the hug ban, the darkest eras in history.
We won Moapa Valley, proud America.