Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate.
Hey, we're going on a road trip to route 66,
to a barren route 66 in France.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson's along for the ride.
I'm here, Parle Vue Francais, of course, as usual.
We've done a little French lately, I feel like,
and I'm excited about it.
I guess really what I'm saying is we did an episode
about Armageddon, and that's what I'm remembering.
And I actually have another French episode to pitch you guys,
and I should've done it off mic, but anyway,
Jason Sheridan is here too.
Jason in first and then do the pitch, yeah.
Hey, what's going on?
Baron, a ride that's barren in a weird way,
a barren in an incorrect route 66 kind of way.
Sure, yes, no, I don't think accuracy is in the picture here.
Some might say, like the French say,
an attraction so small it's bone.
Now that's the French.
That's the right.
There's a lot of top-notch French lately.
What's your pitch?
Oh, what's your pitch?
French Street at Universal Hollywood,
whatever it's called.
That little French street.
Where it says Mouin Rouge on it.
Yes, International Street.
It's got the little car with the sidecar in it.
You can take a picture in it,
I think that's on the street too.
Sure, yeah.
I really like that street, honestly.
I've been up there alone a few times
in the last couple months, and I go,
you know, this street is a nice little thing here.
I think it's gonna be gone soon.
I think it'll be replaced by more minions or something.
Well, there was a whole rationale
of what those were and why.
Supposedly those were backlot style sets
like you can film here,
and I doubt much of anything ever filmed there.
There's some event spaces over there as well.
VIP lounge, I believe is over that area.
Yeah, but it is funny that there's just this little themed
country street there.
With no attractions.
Right.
Yeah, it's a confusing zone.
It's a confusing zone,
and there's other countries represented as well,
and I forget, there's an official name.
Isn't it International?
Yeah, something like that.
We'll say it on the episode, but I'm just saying.
We'll lock it down.
I was like, we should really do this, I think.
This is good.
This is good content.
No attractions, we're in.
Yeah, no.
Somehow that became our wheelhouse.
I wanna be the champion of that hidden gem
in Universal Hollywood.
It's like, it feels untouched to me.
It feels like one of the last untouched places.
Yeah, I like it.
And then there's a Mel's Diner right like 20 feet away.
Right, and there's a little bar also by the min,
it's right across from the Minions Ride.
We've talked about that, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
So you just get like shots.
Yeah, you could get hammered right across
from the Minions Ride. You can get hammered.
Yeah, the bar in Universal Florida
is like a full sit-down restaurant
with like fish and chips and you know,
meat pies or whatever.
And so this one is just like plastic shot glasses to go.
Yeah, so before we ever do the world showcase in Epcot,
we're gonna do this mini world showcase.
This little one that you,
there's no way you've spent time there
unless you're an annual pass holder.
Exactly.
Milling around depressed because every wave is 50 minutes
somehow despite there being not much to do in that.
There's like four rides in that park.
I guess that's why everybody just.
Yeah.
I do feel like it ramped up.
You go and just, where are we?
Only Transformers last time I was there was manageable.
Transformers I got right on,
but everything else was.
Which works out for you, your favorite ride.
It's a pure ride to Rise of the Resistance.
The better ride between the two.
Transformers.
Are you fully sticking with that now?
Is that become the story?
I'd love to completely pick that as my new identity,
but now I'm just saying there's aspects of it.
That's all I'm saying.
But I do really like Transformers.
I still really like it.
I think it's really good.
And it does what I wanted as like a kid with a IP
that I liked.
That's all I'm saying.
So I'm not, I'd love to fully say all the prequels
are the best movies ever.
I'd love to fully say Avatar is going to be
the best movie of all time.
And I'd love to say Rise of the Resistance
is not as good as Transformers,
but I'm not completely there.
You wanna have these edgy opinions.
Yes, I wanna be an edge Lord like you are.
But I can't be.
The show's already got an edge Lord.
Back off, back off the edge.
We went for only room for one on this edge.
Back off with your edgy opinions like Avatar,
the most successful movie of all time is good.
Yes, that's true.
I did see Doctor Strange and the Avatar trailer
got a big cheer in the audience.
Well now, that seems odd to me because Vice Magazine,
a writer for Vice said that they heard
that somebody laughed at it in the theater.
And that was good enough for them to report
and print as facts.
Right, right.
Excellent journalism.
Well, my report is that people cheered
and somebody yelled, Jake Sully!
In the theater.
Wow.
Someone being you?
No, unless I had an out of body experience,
which is possible I suppose.
Like I Doctor Strange in the moment,
you know how like when he like hits Spider-Man
with his whatever magic and like his soul leaves his body,
that's possible where I was like kind of floating
above myself and I went, look at that guy.
He just yelled Jake Sully and it was me
and I didn't realize it.
You were avataring into a different body.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Watching yourself, imagine watching yourself
getting to experience the emotion.
That would be really, if it could be a three camera shoot
while I was watching Avatar so I could watch Avatar 2,
then watch a movie about me watching Avatar
and seeing all the times I like was elated,
all the times I would cry, all of that I think would be nice.
Well, you know, like you mentioned Vice Variety,
you know, the big trade magazine pointed out
that adults are going gaga for multiverse movies.
Oh, well, that's true.
Well, that's another, we can't talk about,
that's gonna open up a whole multiverse of conversation.
Some might say they're going goo goo gaga.
These are grown adults you have to understand.
They have many complicated words at their disposal
and yet you talk to them after they see a multiverse movie
and they're all saying goo goo gaga.
They're all saying goo goo gaga.
But look, Jason and I are comic fans,
we've lived with multiverses our whole lives.
So, you know, this is no odd unique thing.
This is a normal Sunday for us.
Yeah.
You know, dealing with multiverses.
You were way ahead of the, yeah.
Yeah, it's a bunch of posers now
showing up at the multiverse club.
Right, there was a cartoon 20 years ago
or 15 years ago already called Turtles Forever
where it was a multiverse of Ninja Turtles.
So, come on.
Come on.
Imagine the idea that's, why is it that suddenly studios
are excited about a mechanism where
we can throw a bunch of casts together?
Yeah, no, I don't know.
It's not about that.
It's about multi, I just, the studios just earnestly believe
that multiverses are fascinating.
They said this is a new interest of theirs.
Yeah.
They're into quantum physics, they're into multiverses.
Sure, yeah.
I just love how, again, everyone talks about it
with like politics and world events and stuff
that like in America everyone has like
a three month memory where it's just like,
okay, yeah, multiverse, like some sort of,
maybe all the characters are in one universe
or multiple universes and they come,
like imagine a dark universe, okay?
What would that be like?
The dark universe.
Like if the multiverse.
You're saying, how are we not talking about it?
And yet we spit on the dark universe.
If it just circles back around,
like I know there's ones I'm forgetting
where it's like they were trying to make like multi,
like shared universe.
Or shared universe is different than multiple.
But eventually it's just gonna tick back around.
Well, deepfake like Boris Karloff and Bela Lugosi
would have met Tom Cruise and Johnny Depp,
the dark universe stars.
Oh, you think the old mummies would have met the new mummy.
I think there would have been a mummy multiverse movie.
Yeah.
People crying, people in tears.
Because they brought Boris back.
Boris, Brendan and Tom all together in a movie,
I think would have happened.
It still might happen, honestly.
Blah.
What was that?
I was trying to think,
what does deepfake Carrie Fisher say in Rogue?
What does she say?
She says, blah.
Rebellions are built on hope.
Blah.
She's a vampire.
They fly now.
Blah.
Easy vampire.
Yeah.
So I think any of that's possible.
How many minutes has it been without Tom?
Without talking about, well, maybe we're,
are we avoiding it?
That's the question.
Well, much like people used to run from their lives
to their second family across the notable highway Route 66.
Wait, what?
Route 66 is a, you're saying that this was a highway
to cheating to a point of Route 66.
To fleeing your responsibilities and starting life anew,
just driving east on that beautiful road,
the mother road.
That's what people did.
They, your, Route 66 existed to get people away
from their families?
I think it was a convenient byproduct.
Wait a minute.
You said secret family though.
So that actually to me indicates that people were going
back and forth on Route 66 to go
to their two separate families.
Yeah.
I mean, I think there's a lot of configurations.
Maybe I'm just combining two possible ones.
You hate this road.
This road led only to the death of the American family.
Yeah.
And the Barneys Beannery in West Hollywood.
Yes.
That's what?
That's Route 66.
The end of Route 66, the furthest west
is like where the Barneys Beannery in West Hollywood is.
It's that spot?
Yeah.
That's strange.
Oh.
Okay.
You knew this fact already?
I did know this fact.
Life is a highway, I would say.
Life is a highway.
Okay.
So let's talk about today's bad ride.
This is called Cars Road Trip.
And no, this is not something in Cars Land
in California Adventure that you have missed.
No, we haven't done any of those.
And who knows when we will.
We had to make it a priority to talk about
the weird jammed in Cars attraction
in the worst Disney park, Walt Disney Studios Paris.
I got excited about this when talking about
another horrible attraction from that park, Armageddon.
It's so insane.
I can't underline how insane and weird this park is.
Oh yeah.
And this one, this is essentially a new attraction
though a redress of something they had.
And it's weird, it's just, like I don't want to just,
hey, we're shitting on it to shit on it.
I find it fascinating.
Yeah, oh yeah.
This is a place that tourists pay to go.
Thousands of people, maybe, maybe less
according to some of the videos I've watched.
Technically, in theory, thousands of people
could go on this attraction every day.
And then you watch a video of it.
Why?
How is this what it came to?
Yeah, I mean, I have a lot of stuff
I'm fascinated by about this.
My initial fascination when they announced it
was the concept art that features an oil tanker
greeting an impending fiery death like it's an old friend.
That's the greatest part of the whole thing.
It's for sure.
It's the greatest part.
And then what it actually,
the execution is even weirder.
Yeah.
What else?
Walt Disney Studios Park is one of those weird phrases
where it's just like, this is not, this doesn't make sense.
It's like, I think we mentioned when you brought us back
a blip shirts and the back of mine says, proud America.
Not proud American, proud America.
So it's just like a little off.
No one has said this before.
Walt Disney Studios Park, you find odd.
I find it odd because like Walt Disney Studios
would kind of make sense.
But also that's not really what they've called it
in years or if ever.
So it's just kind of weird because it's not a studio.
It's a simulation of a functioning movie studio.
It never was a studio.
It's not the only one of these in the world
where it's called studios
and then there never was a studio.
But what you'll find is I think a new universal studios
location just doesn't have that premise of sound stages
and we film things here anymore.
They've bailed on that.
But this was a park that was opened in 2002
kind of predicated on and you're gonna see
the magic of the movies and the magic of big sound stages.
But nothing ever was filmed there.
Nothing will be filmed there.
I guess besides that weird special I found
that ends with a big giant ghost of Cuba Gooding Jr.
Some things for that special were filmed
on the root of this attraction.
But that does not count.
You can't say we're gonna take you to a back lot
and then film things only at the opening of the back lot
and then never again.
That doesn't work.
Right.
Yeah, you found the one thing filmed there
outside of a handful of commercials.
Yeah, this ride.
Fuck it's.
People, when Pixar Pier opened,
we remember the discourse.
People were like, oh come on,
this is obviously 50% done.
It's not fully themed.
They took the California Scream and made it in Credit Coaster.
This is not even, they did an okay job,
but they obviously didn't have the biggest budget.
There's the, this, the in Credit Coaster makes,
this looked like it's Rise of the Resistance.
As far as-
Far as Transformers.
Far as Transformers is the best ride of all time.
The most emotional ride of all time.
You're speaking in emotions.
Yeah, yeah, emotion wise.
But yeah, like it's so, yeah,
imagine if like they had what feels like,
like what's minus like 50% of the budget,
75% of the budget, 90% less budget.
Like it feels like the cheapest version.
Like imagine California Scream in
and they didn't even put any like static pictures
or they didn't change the mute.
Like it's just a truly like feels like a crazy,
like we had a week to do this.
We can build four things,
pick four things that we can get in here.
That's about all you see.
It is essentially a trip through an empty forest.
Yeah, right.
Where like every, I don't wanna guess on the amount of miles,
but let's say it was a four mile journey.
You see one thing every mile.
Yeah.
And can I just say, I can't put my finger on it.
This forest doesn't sit right with me.
There's something about this woods.
I know it's art of fish.
I mean, I know it's created out of a dirt field.
Well, or, but is it?
I think what maybe,
I don't know what the landscape was like
around Disney studios or around in the Disneyland Paris
area in general,
but I think what's unselling to me
is the possibility that that's just how it came
because it doesn't feel like a magical rivers of America
kind of forest.
It feels like just,
this is the natural wilderness of this plot that they got.
I, okay.
I kind of see that.
It's just, I think it's just some of the trees
are pretty grown in and some of them are pretty low.
Route 66 is very long
and I'm sure there's some sections with woods.
Are you suspicious of low trees?
Is that what you're saying?
I don't know.
It just feels weird.
I'm sorry.
So you're saying like these,
I'm just trying to figure out exactly.
You're talking about like kind of these lower trees here.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah. I think it's just the,
I think it's the lack of like fake desert.
I mean, you get it at the one point, you get it.
You know what it seems like.
Adapted thing.
But I think the most unnerving thing
is the very last set of characters you see appear to be
in the like killing field from Miller's crossing
where like the gangsters take everyone they need to off.
You know what it looks like?
And I'll, we'll talk about the Miller's crossing thing
in a second, but it looks like something like that.
Somebody just planted some Christmas trees
to sort of fill in the trees, like right around here.
So maybe some of the trees were planted.
Like this feels like maybe these were planted
to just make it not feel like there was a gap
between the gravel and the bigger trees.
I'm just saying like why else would it just be
running around a forest unless that's just what they.
I don't think I really have.
I don't think a lot of this forest is artificial.
Like I think I think it'd be more magical
if it wasn't just like.
Yeah, if they were imagineered trees,
they would look like immaculate and cool or something.
This just looks like whatever.
Yeah.
But I think.
It makes it all the stranger that this started at this.
This ride we're talking about is a recent redress
of a back lot tour and it made it really weird
in that back lot tour that well, then if it's a back lot,
why are we just driving through empty featureless forest
for so long with sometimes props sitting next to it?
That's not what a back lot is like.
No.
So yeah, that's the whole thing.
We really, we should have maybe,
we shouldn't have done both things
because there's too much, the original tour and this,
but it is, there's so much confusing stuff
about just the initial version that then compounds
into this even more baffling version.
My argument for addressing any of it now would be,
are we really gonna wanna come back?
I mean, you're doing with it.
Well, I actually haven't looked at the original version.
I'm kind of in the dark.
So we're doing like, yeah, we're, this is the,
we'll do a prequel later maybe.
Okay.
Yeah.
Do we really?
I don't know, I'm not sure.
Do we really want to do a,
let's back up and talk about this awful studio tour.
Your best hope, Scott, is that we just forget.
Yes, that's right.
Because Jason and I forget, which is very possible.
I forget everything these days as I get older.
Yeah, or it's like a Tuesday and you missed a flight
and you're stuck and Mike and I have to do a second gate
because it's like the next day is last Wednesday of the month
and we're just cheering like,
Also, you know what?
French studio tour, French studio tour.
As you know on the show, the longer,
the more you protest and the more it grows in my brain.
Oh God.
That's the problem.
Okay, so separate.
Well, I'm just saying, I think the way to handle me
and Jason with this type of thing from now on
is when we go, maybe we should have done another topic
and you go, yeah, for sure.
And then I think that won't even register.
If I challenge or go, ugh.
I think that's probably what it is, yeah.
Okay, all right.
Yeah, because an elephant never forgets and neither do I.
Unless you were casually agreed with.
Oh, well, yeah, it just backs up my greatness.
Then the elephant goes, yeah, it's great.
Yeah, terrific.
Okay, okay, well then where are we?
What do you wanna talk about?
Oh no, we're talking about the cars.
We're talking about cars.
Yeah.
Back lot tour.
Okay, it was an unpleasant tram tour attraction.
Yes.
Which will be its own unpleasant episode now, seemingly.
I don't want to, actually, I don't wanna do it.
Yeah, see, that's what I'm saying.
I think we can do it in five minutes.
Here's what I'm, okay.
It's kind of a mystery to me.
I don't know how I feel about it, you know?
Okay, they built this studio park.
We gotta do, all right, none of these have ever
not had a tram tour.
We have to do a tram tour.
There's no other option.
They could not, because also,
that's just gonna flesh out the acreage.
If we make everybody get on a tram
and then we take them somewhere,
now we put that on the map
and it looks like we've got way more park
than we actually have, because this was the smallest park
ever, truly under, in a 10 minute walk,
you could go from one end to the other,
go all the way to Aerosmith Alley and back.
So tram tour is great.
That's gonna increase the acreage by a lot.
So there was this strange back lot tour open
from 2002 to 2020.
And the main feature of it is that you saw some sets
from the movie, Rain of Fire.
First thing number one, Rain of Fire not filmed there,
filmed in England, but they moved some sets over
and rearranged them like they might've looked.
Okay, now thing number two, anyone tell me,
just off of what you know right now,
any facts about Rain of Fire?
Sure, starring Matthew McConaughey and Christian Bale,
post-apocalyptic future where dragons are real
and they've destroyed much of cities and humankind
and conventional weapons don't really work,
I think, against them, so it's a lot of harpoons
and edged weapons, that sort of thing.
You are an expert in Rain of Fire.
Yeah, I've never seen it either.
It was just a slow part of that summer
and Rain of Fire was on trailers played a lot
before movies, before TV shows,
a lot of Access Hollywood extra coverage.
Could you have done any of that?
I think I knew McConaughey, but I think that's about it.
You knew McConaughey.
Dragon, McConaughey.
It's a rare movie where Bale talks like Bale.
It's that really thick.
Oh, right.
What are you talking about?
The yelling at the through voice.
Whatever his natural accent is.
I have just the briefest clip of the trailer of Rain of Fire,
which might be lodged in your brain,
but it kind of spells out the rules of Rain of Fire.
It makes me, this movie sounds like such bullshit nonsense.
I almost want to watch it.
There's nothing magical about it.
They made it flesh and blood.
You take out their heart, you bring down the beast.
You bring down the beast.
He's sort of flesh and blood.
Bring down the beast.
Swinging a massive axe, as that line is said.
He of course,
Vati McConaughey of course plays Denton Van Zan,
who is a sworn enemy of the dragons.
Denton Van Zan.
Because he watched his mother, Mama Van Zan.
Van Zan, not Van Zant like little Stephen.
No, not related to Stephen Van Zant, no.
Van Zan.
So dear Mama Van Zan,
he watched get killed by one of the first dragons.
He also, from what I could tell from clips,
he takes time to see.
He explains, they live on ash.
They eat ash.
They eat ash?
This is the rules of dragons in this movie
that you don't,
they don't shoot fire at you because they're mad at you.
They shoot fire at you to make you into ash
and then eat the ash.
They don't wanna eat you.
They have no interest in meat or muscles or skin.
They want to eat ash.
Well, this sounds like it's really filling out
the studio tour episode if we combine it
with a full rain of fire viewing.
But yeah, you flush it out with a rain of fire watch down.
Is that in any dragon canon for any dragon story
that they eat the ash?
Yeah, rain of fire.
The main dragon canon.
Yeah, or the most important one.
Wow.
I almost like it.
I agree with your question,
but I almost like it the most
because they made up a dragon rule.
They eat ash.
I mean, look, I like the idea of it.
Am I comfortable with it sounding a little bawdy
because we keep saying it so much?
If we think about it.
Oh, you're the one with the dirty mind.
I never, that wouldn't have occurred to me.
Did that occur to you?
So it sounds like somebody with a lisp saying,
we know what it sounds like.
Look, I'm on Twitter.
I see what the perverts write about this type of thing.
I see that.
And so that's what it sounded like to me.
I'm so sorry for.
Eating pushy and eating ash.
Pursing Sarah.
Pushy.
That may be the worst thing I've ever heard, actually.
Eating pushy.
Just pushy.
Well, keep in mind, I'm doing,
this is not, this is McConaughey saying it.
So in the world of Rain of Fire, pushy is its own.
I'm gonna say this because of the Patreon.
Wet ass pushy.
Wet ash pushy.
Ash pushy.
Oh right, wet ash pushy.
Yeah, you're doing that too.
Okay, well.
All right, well, we're really letting it all hang out.
So that's what, so is a tour that taught you about eating ash.
You went to a French field to learn about eating
and how to eat ash.
Like every, every adolescent does.
What was the time in your life?
Basically what this was,
so there were two major tent poles on this tour.
One was that you go to the sets of Rain of Fire,
you see the ash, and you wonder how it was eaten
or will be eaten.
And then, and there's like a fireball
that shoots out at you, not from a dragon.
They didn't even set up like a fake dragon to do it.
Just a fireball comes at you.
You kinda go, whoa.
That is the finale of the tour, is a brief fireball.
In the middle of it is the thing that they kept.
So Rain of Fire sets are gone.
They are ash now.
They're all ash.
That's all gonna be the land used for the redevelopment
of this play that will hopefully will be good
in this frozen and there's rise resistance
and all that stuff.
What they kept was Catastrophe Canyon,
which is a thing that's been in Florida
or was in Florida for a long time.
It was like there, invented from the ground up,
earthquake kind of thing where that whole tram shakes
and there's a bunch of fire, controlled fire effects,
and then a big flooding.
I always liked that in Florida.
Impressive fun in Florida.
I think they probably did the math.
Well, that is red rocks.
That's fake rocks that are in the realm
of Radiator Springs a little bit.
Kind of the only thing in the realm of Radiator Springs
besides the cast member, besides the characters.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But all right, that's good.
We don't have to rebuild that.
So maybe from that starting point,
we can make up a whole new cars thing
on the backs of this attraction,
which by the way, the previous, the tram tour,
you ride out, you pass by some props,
you go through Catastrophe Canyon, you come back,
you see the same props you saw.
Then you pass by the line, you watch the people
in the line where you just were.
Then you go watch, then you go look at the ash
and then you come back.
So this is a tour where you see the same things twice,
including the line.
And you have to imagine there was a lot of like
the misery of the people trapped on this tour,
staring down the people in the line
who was looking for like, is this line worth it?
And the people on the tram going, I'm afraid not.
I cannot lie to you, sir.
This is like Johnny Gargano's nightmare
of the being on the Carousel of Progress,
repeating the first few seeds
and then doing the whole show again.
Backing up.
I have to see the 102 Dalmatians car again.
Two, 102 Dalmatians.
Imagine like Space Mountain to Disneyland.
It's so fun when the cars come back in
because like the line and the unloading area is same place.
So you see everyone clapping and excited
how fun that ride was.
I can't wait to get on it.
Imagine everyone would just dower after every like.
Well, we did it.
It was accomplished.
The jet or whatever it is,
there were spaceship rockets back in
and everyone was just like.
I got to sit for a while.
Being on a bench that moves is a novelty.
People in the, why 200 years ago,
this wouldn't have been possible.
If the rocket jet or whatever it is flies back in
and everyone, there's just like a big,
like a big exhale from all the riders.
And then they come for a cigarette.
Group sigh.
Now, have they changed this effect?
Has there anything other than a group sigh
from this new attraction?
I am not sure.
Let's talk about what happens on this new.
What do you see on Cars Road Trip?
Well, first of all, it was supposed to be,
I think they were gonna call it Route 66,
but that trademark is taken in France.
So they couldn't call it that.
Yes, specifically taken by a group called Tempting Brands
who owns the brands for Route 66,
a company called General Magic,
and then a luxury high-end clothing company
called Marie Antoinette,
which seems questionable that your high-end
like sleepwear and lingerie is named after Marie Antoinette.
What happened at the end for her?
Well, they're grabbing appealing parts
of all of our history of American and European history.
Yeah, just a phrase, Tempting Brands,
that it's got a certain odd,
it's not boring enough as King Feature Syndicate,
but it's got a weirdness to it for sure.
It's so uneasy.
It's interesting.
It's more interesting than King Feature Syndicate.
Yeah.
There's a name, a soul,
and yeah, not the actual idea of it.
King Feature Syndicate's so exciting.
They have Beetle Bailey,
but I'm saying Tempting, it sounds more interesting.
It sounds more intriguing.
You have to almost have to say,
you can't just say Tempting Brands.
Like you have to say Tempting Brands.
Tempting Brands.
Tempting is a word you have to say.
I guess I just said it boring, but Tempting, Tempting.
So Tempting Brands struck,
so this had to be called Cars Road Trip,
and thus they laid out a bunch of big letters
that say road trip,
and that is what you're greeted by
when you get on the Trant.
Now you're thinking, okay, I'm entering the world of cars,
so is this going to be a race?
Am I gonna climb aboard a car
and experience life from a car's point of view?
And then a slow moving tram pulls up without a face.
It is the way you are on is not an alive car,
which I don't understand.
Maybe you're, I guess we are starting in the human world
and making our way into the cars world.
This is, we're entering the alternate cars dimension
where anything with wheels has a face and eyes.
Is there a Trant, is there,
Scott, you've watched the Cars movies recently, right?
Yeah, they're on a little less these days, mercifully.
Okay. Yeah, there's been a...
Are there trams in the Cars universe?
I don't know if I've seen a tram.
There's logistics there where,
who's the character, Mac, the truck,
the Lightning McQueen sleeps in.
Yeah, he goes into his butt.
See, that's what you, you're tempted to say that.
However, from watching it many times over,
I've learned that his trailer is not, yes.
The truck is only its head.
So anything that removes from the body.
So yeah, unfortunately it is not his butt.
His butt would just be like a tailpipe, I guess.
I actually didn't realize that.
I didn't realize that
because I had the note, their ass catches on fire
at one point in this ride.
Oh, so the tanker is not its body.
Well, we just explained something about, you know what?
Yes, I had the exact same thought
because at the height of the now Cars,
Tastrophe Canyon segments. Cars, Tastrophe Canyon,
which I kinda like.
That's okay. That's okay.
That is, but yeah, I agree.
It has the very convoluted, it has an aftershock.
It's like a freak of nature.
It's a canyon that is an aftershock every minute
is the justification for what's going on.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, crazy.
It's a nightmare.
It's weird though.
It's a play on, it's a pun of Catastrophe Canyon,
a name that Disney made up.
Yes.
Like why, so it's not like doing the Grand Carzian
or something. Right.
Or it's something that exists.
Right.
It's a parody of, or not a, I guess it's kind of a parody.
It's like doing Walt Drives Knee Studios.
Mm-hmm, which is pretty good too.
That's okay. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That was, that was, that was a,
not a bad thing to produce quickly.
So anyway, what we were saying was
things build to a torrent in Cars, Tastrophe Canyon
to where this tanker truck, who is not Mack,
because he's painted blue. Right.
He is a Dinoco fuel truck,
which is the consistent Pixar gas
going all the way back to Toy Story.
Yes, right, right.
It's the gas station where Woody and Buzz get lost
and used in the Cars, the Cars-iverse.
A Dinoco truck gets lit on fire.
He is on fire, but I guess we explained it.
It isn't his ass.
I get a, anything that attaches to a truck.
So he feels no pain in that moment
when he gets lit on fire. Right.
Yeah. It is not him.
He's kind of amused.
He's speaking in French.
I couldn't really catch what he was saying.
Yeah. I couldn't really catch what he was saying.
I couldn't really find a translation.
Yeah. Well, if he's French though,
he's always lighting himself accidentally on fire
with his cigarettes.
Yeah. So.
He seems amused though.
Again, the fire doesn't, the fire like starts on his ass.
It's not like the concept, his non-ass, excuse me.
It's not like he's, he's kind of looking at,
and the concept art is looking at the fire and smiling.
The fire kind of happens all around him, but he doesn't see,
he seems kind of amused.
And then the water rushes in and puts everything out.
Because he knows that that's going to happen.
Like, is this him doing an illusion?
Is this a, like lighting yourself on fire
on stage in a magic show?
Oh, right. Yeah.
I guess so.
Is he like, he's like an American expat
sitting at a French like cafe.
And he doesn't even have to order anymore.
They just know him.
So they just bring him his espresso and he has this cigarette
and they light a cigarette and he doesn't even need to,
he just leads the money when he's done.
And they just, they just keep bringing it, you know?
Maybe. So he's, he's out in this French field.
Like this is how he gets his jollies for the day.
This is his routine.
He likes a lot of everything around him to light on fire.
Maybe because when it's all said and done,
he wants to eat some ash.
That's why he's smiling so big being around that fire.
It's like a car dragon.
It's a nod to the Ernest, Ernest Hemingway's book.
I think it's, The Sun Also Rises.
It's about a World War I, like American veteran,
I think just bumming around Paris.
And it's often alluded to in the book,
but they can't come out and say it
because of the time period that like,
his dicks don't work from the war.
So like he's very depressed.
So maybe this is the version.
This is a nod to that.
He's just sitting in the Catastrophe Canyon
waiting to eat ash because his car's dick don't work no more.
The Sun Also Rises, that's the movie with Robert Evans,
Evans is in?
That's right.
Yeah.
It's the kid stays in the picture.
Kid stays in the picture.
So I always think of when I hear the Sun Also Rises,
the Sun Also Rises.
That's how I think of it.
So why wasn't this like, when they made it as a movie,
it should have been called his dick don't work no more.
Imagine the box office for that.
Or did he produce it?
I'm sorry, he's not in it.
He might've just produced it.
But he's involved enough to have to say it.
Yeah, maybe that's the one where he goes like,
Ava Goddard, I had a fling.
That's like he was producing Sun Also Rises.
I forget.
No, I think he's in it.
I think the producer says the kid stays in it.
No, that's a different movie.
That's the one he's like the Matador or something.
I think he's the, I think there's both fighting.
Oh, well maybe.
Sun Also Rises, there's both fighting.
I will look it up, I don't wanna be wrong.
Okay, you look it up.
You keep going.
I'll read some of the things that happened on this ride.
You get in a tram, it says road trip in big letters.
Then you start moving.
And then there's a video that stars Sally the blue car
from Cars and Cruz Ramirez who is in Cars 3.
She speaks English, Sally speaks French.
It's very confusing.
I don't understand.
That's the thing I don't understand in the parks in general
is when is the call made about what should be English
and what should not be?
I'm always getting confused in all the different
foreign parks sometimes you go, well, that doesn't seem
like they did both language.
Like sometimes, yeah, sometimes it's just,
and like, yeah, sometimes it's just one language
and you're not sure why.
Like why do they elect that, yes, Cruz Ramirez
will speak English, but Lightning McQueen is French.
And Mater is French.
That's very strange.
Mater very anachronistic.
Yeah, but also funnier.
That is good.
I do like French Mater.
Yes.
That's funny.
I think I wrote, I think he in his little tableau
at the end says, I'm not making this up.
I think he might say significant.
I have significant in, maybe someone just says significant.
Is there a Mater short where he's also French
or it's Larry the Cable Guy doing like French words?
Not sure.
My son is, the arbitrary opinions of my son,
cars short, Mater's tall tales, no.
Oh really?
Yeah, no interest.
And then I might've said before,
first act of cars gets scared of the tractors.
There is no second act of cars as far as he knows.
Straight to the race.
Often it is only race.
That's all we do is the big race at the end.
No cars two or three.
Zero interest.
Really?
I don't understand kids having these opinions
from the first frame.
He goes, no, no, no.
But it's the same characters.
I'm as bored by this as I ever by the first one.
Well, but he knows Paul Newman had passed by that point.
So you put on the color of money or like road to perdition
or the sting, he's like clapping along.
I am not trying any of the new ones.
We're taking them down the cell.
I really, I want Jason to have a child just so I can see
what movies he forces the child to watch at like one
and a half.
But Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.
The Sundance Kid.
Do you want to watch?
It's a kids movie.
Do you want to watch The Sun Also Rises?
Which Jason, you were correct.
And I was initially correct.
Robert Evans is in The Sun Also Rises as Pedro Romero.
Uh oh.
Oh yeah.
I'm worried about what that entails.
Well, that's like the touch of evil.
Touch of evil where
Charlton Heston is like a Mexican police officer.
Yes.
This is a very common thing up through five years ago.
Yeah.
2019?
The weird, yeah.
I think I brought this up ages ago,
but I watched that Russell Crowe Leonardo DiCaprio
spy movie Body of Lies.
And Oscar, a younger Oscar Isaac is an Iraqi CIA asset.
And then Mark Strong from, you know, the Kingsman movies.
And I think he's the Junker Don in one of the X-Men movies.
Plays the head of the Jordanian intelligence agency.
Like, you know, the country of Jordan.
Right.
Is Mark Strong juggernaut?
Is it Mark Strong?
No, it's Vinnie Jones.
Oh, it's Vinnie Jones.
I always mix those two up.
Vinnie Jones, because he says I'm the juggernaut bitch.
That's right.
X-Men The Last Stand.
Yeah.
Anyway, stop the conversation dead.
Okay, so.
Sorry.
X-Men The Last Stand kind of underrated.
Yeah.
Honestly.
There you go.
You got a little more.
Kelsey Grammer.
Yes, yeah.
Of course.
Oh, that's that one.
Okay.
That's the one, wait, I saw that one and have zero memory.
If we're talking multiverse and characters coming back.
Oh, we're not.
We're talking car.
No, we were.
I don't remember.
We bring, make.
Go ahead.
Make 70 year old Kelsey Grammer
put the beast makeup back on.
That's what I say.
I want him as beast.
He's the perfect little casted beast.
And I want it back.
I want him back.
Anyway.
Sure.
I've said my piece.
I have no support from the room.
All right, get out there.
Get, if you're listening to this
and you were working Hollywood,
you heard what my.
Kelsey Grammer back at the beast makeup.
So now, so the premise here is that we're doing,
it's like a kooky sightseeing trip.
So you see route 66 style oddities, like a big wrench.
You pass by the big wrench and you go, hmm.
And it says so big, it's nuts on it.
Okay.
All right.
We did one down.
Yeah.
Then you pass by a big lug nut.
World's largest lug nut.
Our friend, Lightning McQueen and our neighbors,
Giuseppe and Guido or Luigi and Luigi and Guido.
They're neighbors to you, not a friend.
I'm just not that close with either of them.
They're cool.
I mean, I.
And our neighbors.
I need tires every few years.
So I see them and make small talk, but.
They're not, yeah, lightning close.
You wouldn't have lightning party.
Yeah.
And you looking at this, the world's largest lug nut.
That's gonna, and it's like, all right, it's kind of, yeah.
It's bigger than me.
Yeah, but it's not.
Couldn't fit it in my pocket.
Not by a long shot, but you're not.
It's not like the biggest ball of yarn.
Like that's impressive when you see the big ball of yarn.
You done the big ball of yarn?
No, I've seen a picture of it though.
It seems impressive from the picture.
Yeah.
Where is the, are there multiple big balls of yarn?
Oh, I think at this point,
there's like probably the most notable one.
Well, that's an episode.
Anyway.
I drove across country.
I stopped at the, do you know the Continental Divide?
That's where like, that's the dividing line where like.
The four states?
What are we talking about?
No, I haven't been at the four quarters.
What is that called, the four corners?
Yeah.
The Continental Divide, I believe is where,
west of this water flows west.
Oh, oh, the directional.
And east of this water flows east.
I see.
It's the dividing line for the way like water systems flow.
Okay, and you've been?
Yeah, it's just a, it's just a bunch of,
it's a painting on a road and a souvenir shop.
Okay, well we'll do that one too.
Yes.
It's coming soon too.
I bought a, I bought a Roots,
I have a Roots 66 t-shirt from there.
It costs like $7.
It costs like an insanely low amount.
It feels like sandpaper.
But doesn't it, well, doesn't it,
I mean, it hurts you cause it's like sandpaper,
but it also reminds you of all the torrid affairs
that this road is.
Torrid affairs, all those roadside motels,
God knows what was going on in there.
In the, in the sand.
Destroy the road, destroy all roads.
So they lead only to ruin.
One family on one side, another family on the other.
Yeah, so east of this line, you see one family
and west of this line, you see the other family.
Exact midpoint between all these people's two families.
And that midpoint is the only place you can get peace.
A cup of coffee, some peace and quiet.
Really uncomfortable t-shirt.
One family gets one water flow,
the other family has the water flow the opposite way.
So, so much of this attraction is quiet,
like sitting in silence.
Even though they made little videos for it,
it's still kind of, maybe there's a little bit of music,
just dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Yeah, at least like, like Life is a Highway,
Rascal Flatts should be playing at least the whole time
to get the energy up.
I do, I can report that my son goes nuts
when Life is a Highway.
So you have one big thing in common with him.
Yeah.
You both go ape shit for Life is a Highway.
For Rascal Flatts' version.
The Rascal Flatts' version of Life is a Highway.
But let me, all right, I have to open up old wounds,
but I've been obsessed ever since it happened with you
saying that the dueling piano bar
should play Life is a Highway at Hell at the Moon.
Yeah, yeah.
Now that I'm more familiar with this song,
there's so many lyrics.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun,
no one know, do you know?
Like the people at the dueling piano bar
are not going to know all of the verses
of Life is a Highway.
Yeah, it's a lot, I don't know the lyrics
to Life is a Highway.
I'm not 100.
How can we expect these piano players to?
Life is a Highway though is a pretty popular song,
so I don't know, I don't think it's crazy.
I didn't ask the piano player to play
the Yankee Hotel Foxtrot Wilco song
a magazine called Sunset.
I wasn't going that crazy.
I think there was a shot.
An album cut.
Mm-hmm.
The great song.
The magazine called Sunset.
I know the lyrics to that song, yeah.
I probably knew that one too.
Oh, Jason knows it.
So you're dueling piano.
Yeah, look, I don't,
You're dueling Wilco.
I don't, I, you know, I don't like to give people advice.
I'm parodying, I don't have children,
but at some point you're gonna have to introduce
into the Tom Cochran version.
Yeah.
But I think you should wait.
You can't be expected to go to school without.
I think you should wait though.
You know about Tom Cochran.
You should wait so we can appreciate it, you know?
Yeah, cause I think that's, yeah,
it's a little more sophisticated,
so I think he needs to be a little older, seven, eight, nine,
before you introduce him to the Tom Cochran.
Maybe he kicks off middle school by saying,
hello, peers.
Did you know that there is a different life as a highway
besides the one we all grew up with in the Cars films?
It's a little bit, it's got more of a,
more of a like a yelp to it, a growl I'd say,
but equally fun.
Anyway, let's begin our educational experience anew.
Look everyone, my dad helped me put the lyrics on this song.
In all these cities and all these towns,
in my blood and it's all around.
Well, there it is.
Yeah. Great.
He knows the lyrics.
So it was not crazy that a piano player
that plays hit songs would know life as a highway.
It's also not a piano song in the lead.
There's no piano in the song.
Yeah, but that's okay.
You can do fun piano versions.
No, you can merge, but I'm saying,
I think you, it's gotta be such a slam dunk
to change the genre of the,
of the song that you're asking for.
Yeah. I did unfortunately clear out the bar
because he did play my suggestion
of Ben Foltz Five's boxing.
The sad song.
The piano song.
The lyrics from Howard Kasell.
Boxing's been good to me, Howard.
Yeah.
Yeah, you're doing piano bark.
Yeah, we could do it.
You've got a ton up in the knocking.
Ben Foltz B-sides, Wilco B-sides.
What, what?
Yeah, we would have a-
And life is a highway every 15 minutes.
Yeah, but Jason has to sing it
cause he knows the lyrics.
Yeah.
But yeah, there's look,
are we better than that guy who was playing piano?
Yes.
Both of them, right?
Yeah, both of them.
I feel like there's only one that-
Was there only one, was it not a dueling?
I feel like, yeah, they were on their last legs already
and there was only one piano player
at the dueling piano bar.
One of them saw the slip that said life is a highway,
rolled his eyes and quit.
Yeah.
Take this job and shut up.
I'm outta here.
All right, we're doing Freebird again.
It's like, don't stop believing Freebird.
I don't even remember what else he played that night.
Piano Man.
I'm sure, yeah, that's gotta be-
Yeah, Piano Man.
There was a guitar player though.
Remember he jumped on the bar?
No.
You don't remember that?
Do you remember that?
No, because the special was
a $3 Sky Vodka
and I kept ordering doubles.
I was probably concentrating on what is going to happen
to my bodily functions.
Wow, really?
With all of this blue pumping through me.
That was exciting, I feel like.
There was all of a sudden, I turned around,
there's a man playing guitar behind us
and I feel like, was it Sweet Child of Mine?
I'm sure we said it on the episode years ago,
but it was something like that and he was playing.
He came from nowhere.
There might've been a saxophone player too.
He may not have worked there.
He was at Carl Strauss with his electric guitar
and he just plugged in.
Okay, well consult that episode.
I have zero memory.
Listener will do it.
Tell us.
For me.
Okay, let's keep plowing.
We go to Carstestripy Canyon.
We've talked about this a little bit.
A truck with a big smile on his face
gets surrounded by fire.
His expression never changes.
This is where I look, I feel for the Imagineers,
I would say.
I don't put any blame.
Yeah, absolutely.
You're like, well we gotta try to do something with it.
I blame whatever, at whatever higher up point
they were unwilling to release more money
and at least something that allows the car's face
to change from smiling to frowning.
One function in that face to reflect the fact
that he is surrounded on all sides by fire
and his butt.
It is crazy.
It is like the dog meme, this is fine, I guess.
It's so much like this is fine.
Maybe it's the French trying to comment on America
by using our iconography, our central,
our formerly main road, Route 66.
It's a tableau of modern America.
It's actually a very poignant ride if you think of it that way.
I do think of it that way now.
So yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
So it's so funny.
I don't, obviously everybody who's on this ride
is bored and doesn't care.
No one's put two thoughts
because this ride is so uninteresting,
but I feel like this should be cars full of laughter.
Like when you're watching these YouTube videos,
but no one seems to give a shit.
No one cares.
They didn't like the little graphics
of like other cars based roadside attractions,
which you don't actually see.
They didn't really like.
Yeah, you get a bunch of graphics
of things you don't get to see.
The painting, there was kind of a cartoony painting
of Route 66 on the back of a building you go by.
Great.
Yep.
Then you go back by it again.
The trees are starting to grow in front of the painting.
This is just, this maybe we should do some episode
like this where it was like,
where we try to like put an IP overlay
and we try to imagine if we had the budget,
what appears to be this ride's budget for this overlay.
Like it's like $10,000.
You have $10,000 to overlay.
What's the most, let's just say hypothetically
living with the land, Scott.
You have $10,000 to overlay IP on living with the land.
You, all right, 20 bucks.
Get a CD player, get a speaker,
speakers to put in the boat
and start playing the song again.
How many votes they got?
Maybe seven, eight.
All right, so now I have,
I still have well upwards of $9,000.
Maybe just press play on the song
that they actively chose to not use anymore.
In all these cities, in all these towns.
No!
Now they're down, that's an idea.
Living with the land is not a highway.
There's a man, how about a magazine called Sunset?
The Wilco overlay for living with the land.
Just get a guy playing the songs on it on every car.
Oh yeah, a little piano, a mini piano.
Yeah, that's great.
On every boat.
Yeah, now we're talking.
Yeah, and you give suggestions.
So the first dueling piano boat.
Yeah.
So Cars, Test, Trophy Canyon happens.
You see more slides of things you don't get to see.
You don't get to see the Great Wall of China made of tires.
And then there's a lot of buildup of that.
You're quickly informed.
Oh, Mater's doing art now.
I haven't seen his art.
Oh well, maybe we're gonna see his art.
Here's some pictures of his art and look what he made.
And he made an Eiffel Tower out of car junk.
And it's called the Eiffel Tower.
Yeah, it's made out of garbage.
The woods around it seem like they've been cleared
or flattened, again, real Miller's Crossing,
true detective crime scene types.
Deep forest crime.
Yeah, you're right.
It's not a pleasant, lush forest.
It's a forest you go to handle business
that you never speak of again.
He made a fake billboard that says, let's go Buick.
I guess that's a slight,
that's like a Let's Go Brandon thing in the car universe.
Let's go Buick.
Brandon becomes Buick.
They all hate the president of cars, president Buick.
There has not been, yeah,
there's not been a working man's car.
There's not been a GM car.
There's not been a Chevrolet car in a while.
President Maserati, president Buick, president Maybach.
It's all these rich guys.
The Eiffel Tower is not that tall.
You're kinda like K.
Well, it's impressive that a car did it
because a car has no arms.
I guess he did this all with his tongue,
with his big, fleshy tongue
that we know all of the cars have
because lightning breaks a tie at the beginning of Cars 1
by sticking his giant flesh tongue out, which counts,
which they make you watch in slow motion replays.
That's so, like,
That's unpleasant.
If I walk into the family room and the tongue is on,
I am never happy.
Yeah, that's.
Oh, the tongue movie.
The tongue, tongues it should be called.
If you know a better way to eat ash, I'd like to hear it.
Get her done.
So, and then you're kinda heading back to home base
and then Cruz says,
Route 66 was so much fun.
And like, are you telling us or are you telling yourself?
Who are you trying to convince here?
Yeah, that's kind of like the end of any long road trip
where you're kind of wiped out.
And like a few days later, it sets in
of how good a time you had,
but you just want to get out of the car.
Yeah. At the very end of it.
Yeah, very much so.
This is weird.
What a strange, how like.
So strange, yeah.
And just like the plight of Paris,
where, you know, there's great new attractions going up
all around the globe,
even in this kind of embattled cutback,
bummer, chapec, Disney times,
still all of the properties are getting great new attractions.
And then poor Paris gets cars road trip.
They get a tanker truck with an on fire, non-butt.
And that's the, here you go.
Enjoy, this is your new ride, guys.
There's one big detail that we have not mentioned
that I think adds to the absurdity of this attraction.
So this was announced a while ago,
was originally slated to open summer of 2020.
Obviously that did not happen.
Instead it opens July of 2021
with the rest of the parks reopening.
So this is a brand new attraction.
The park's been closed for over a year.
Finally it's opened.
Yay, it's open.
We're all going back.
Oh, there's a new, there's a new thing.
We gotta go see the new.
What are we seeing?
Like just the weirdness of like already,
like those first few times back to theme parks
after staying at home inside
were so interesting and bizarre.
And then to have this weirdo attraction on top of that,
I can't imagine, you know?
Well, maybe it benefited from that.
It's like, well, boy, that was not sitting inside.
That's true.
There was no opening of a zoom window anywhere in there.
Yeah.
One of the ride throughs online I was watching
and it was very funny.
It was still when everyone had to wear masks
outdoors in the parks.
And you see like an employee
like walking in front of the camera
and they kind of like look and see all the cast members
and they go like,
and they like pull the mask out of their pocket,
put it on, because they realized,
uh-oh, I forgot.
I'm being photographed.
Yeah.
Did everyone see, this is another recent Paris thing.
Did everyone see Mickey dancing
and lighting up the Eiffel Tower?
I did see that.
Yeah.
I did not.
You didn't see this?
No.
The actual Eiffel Tower I'm talking about.
Oh, okay.
Not the, not the Eiffel.
Not the Eiffel Tower.
No.
Mickey for some reason is like doing a like
phantasmic show in front of the actual Eiffel Tower
and lighting it up.
And do you know why this was?
30th anniversary.
Oh, okay.
Of Paris.
Disneyland Paris.
When there are a long way from people throwing tomatoes
at Michael Eisner.
Mickey gets the keys to the Eiffel Tower lighting rig.
The keys to the rig.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So there is, that was, that's a much more spectacular video
than anything you'll see here.
All right.
So they're doing exciting things in Paris then.
One-offs of Mickey dancing.
Mickey, I think honestly, Mickey should do more of this
dancing in front of like land, world landmarks
where he lights them up in front of Mount Rushmore
or Stonehenge, you know?
So if you want to watch these videos,
those have like lights.
Well, they will now.
Natural, okay.
So maybe we're going to install lights.
Yeah, we're going to install lights in some of the places.
It was a grand, Mickey and all the biggest celebrities
in France, Jerry Lewis's heir, the cast of Cuties,
Macron, not Marie Le Pen, no no.
Wait, Jerry Lewis was at the Eiffel Tower?
Okay.
Is he, is he still with us?
No, no, he is dead.
He died of heat.
That's why I said his heir.
I was just wondering where you were going with that.
He did like one last trip of telling everybody
women aren't funny and then he croaked.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
I'm going to get a few of these in before I wrap up.
He did a Comedians in Cars, then he croaked.
Yeah.
He was on Comedians in Cars and then that was it.
He croaked.
We're just having coffee in a car, then he croaked.
Mid-episode.
Jerry Lewis died on an episode.
Jerry took him to two modern coffee places.
It wasn't like a diner using the same machine for 50 years.
He served him a full-strength Starbucks coffee
and it just killed him.
So too strong.
Yeah.
What do we do with this thing?
I mean, this is just a sitting duck.
Do we burn it down for insurance money?
I mean, already.
It's already burning every day.
Yeah, yeah.
So just maybe let it loose one day.
Yeah.
Let that, let that butt fire get out of control
and it's all ash.
I think they should take out some of the,
I think they should just make it worse somehow.
Take out some of the trees, take out some of the fun signs.
They should make people do the forest clearing.
Yeah.
That's what, suddenly you stop the gates open
and like everybody's handed an axe.
Everybody.
Go clear cut.
Oh.
No tram, no tram.
Everyone has to walk it.
Yeah.
The tram breaks down maybe.
Walk trip.
You have to walk back.
You like, you wait for a little while
for the French equivalent of AAA.
It doesn't show up.
You just start walking.
Yeah.
And then add some narrative about a secret family
that you're going to visit
when you get to the end of the destination.
That's a Lesna.
That's, I mean, everyone's got, you know,
a mistress in France.
Oh yeah.
That's true.
They might like that.
They might be happy.
Yeah, no, that's not a big deal.
That's the novelty of recreating Route 66.
Imagine that they, there was,
there's a country where this had to be done.
You had to travel great distances
between your secret families.
We're uptight about secret.
Do you have to pretend you don't have a mistress?
Jason's uptight about.
This is a backwards country.
Jason's uptight about secret families and mistresses here,
but that's our United States upbringing.
Yeah.
It's over there.
They don't give a shit.
We'd be looser.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Couple months in France and we'd all have them.
Is there a podcast,
the right equivalent podcast emanating from France?
Do we have like three?
Oh, maybe.
Three French doppelgangers
who are not so like uptight about body material.
They love body material.
You can hear them light up a real long, gross cigarette.
Yeah, well you can hear the smoking.
Packing coughs.
You can hear the smoking on the mic
in our French equivalent podcast.
Yeah, they have sex with the mistress's drink.
Oh my gosh.
In between talking about Disneyland Paris.
You guys take it from here.
Give me a moment.
They all sound like Kenan's PRS cargo from all that.
Pretend I am a dragon from the rain of fire.
It's a different podcast.
It's not this one.
We're a little more buttoned up and we do.
We go explore the world whether you ask us to or not,
whether the attraction is good or not.
We made it.
We survived podcast the ride to the second gate.
Cars road trip, we did it by maybe,
have you already forgotten?
Yeah, I don't care.
Okay, great.
I don't care about this ride at all.
Okay, so maybe we don't need to do the tram tour again,
but there are a lot of great other topics
that we need to jackal here on the second gate.
Sorry, I got a little brain fart.
I'll edit that out.
Okay, okay, yeah.
So I was saying podcast the ride, the jackal gate.
There's a, sorry.
You did it again.
Well, what am I saying?
The jackal gate?
I don't know.
Why am I saying?
Is it like a French thing?
Like an old French movie or something stuck in your head?
I don't think so.
I think I'm being like,
I feel like in that moment where I'm saying that word,
I'm being possessed by some other worldly demonic figure.
I don't know what's making me do it.
What I'm trying to say is if you keep it tuned here
to podcast the ride the second gate
for your three bonus episodes every month,
there's gonna be a lot of great,
many great jackals in store.
What am I, God.
Oh, that's weird.
It's entertaining.
Nothing but brain farts.
I'll edit it out.
It's entertaining the second gate.
It's like a video game come to real life.
You know?
That's yeah, I think that's what we offer here.
Yeah.
Yeah, as exciting as if characters
from the video game realm stepped off the screen
into your reality.
Yeah, I think we just need to cool down,
listen to one of our favorite musical artists,
Jackal Moore.
And then we'll be, wait, what am I saying?
Jack, I meant Macklemore.
Did you mean Macklemore?
I meant Macklemore.
You obviously meant Macklemore.
That's weird.
Jackal Moore.
Why did I say that?
I don't know.
Huh.
That's what I wanted to know.
I don't know what's coming over us.
Who knows what's coming down the road
on podcast The Ride of the Second Gate?
Only one way to find out.
Stay subscribed.
Stay jackal, fuck.