Forever, dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains the origin of cosplay.
Lord Zed worship, toy vendor stalking, and Jason saying the name of a company that makes sweet pickles.
All that plus Mighty Morphin Power Rangers Live with guest Johnny Gargano.
It's podcasting time on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who if they were Power Rangers would all have giant swords that resemble wet fish.
My name is Mike Carlson.
I guess I would also say like mackerel or something when I was doing that. Jason Sheridan joining me as always.
Explain yourself please.
Well here's the thing, I was thinking about what's like a lame animal that we would have when, you know when they say like mastodon, pterodactyl, those are dinosaurs obviously.
But they've changed you know so many times during Power Rangers and I figured what would be our animals that our zords would look like.
So I thought wet fish makes the most sense.
Jason Sheridan here.
Hi, yes I'm here. Yeah I understand it now.
I understand it now. I mean I think a lot of fish are pretty you know majestic and cool.
But that's probably why my fish, that's why my animal would be a wet fish.
Okay fair enough. Scott Gargano here.
Well first off what other way would a fish be?
That's their natural habitat so it's no slam on a fish to say the fish is wet. If they are wet they are living their best life.
Yeah it's a good point.
So are we.
Dry fish actually would be more embarrassing and would more play into the joke that I was trying to make that we're three losers.
Yeah but also maybe more sad because of dry fish you were thinking about their mortality.
And while we might die in the face of a Power Rangers type battle, I don't regard ourselves to that degree of depression that we hear fish choking on the deck of a boat.
That said I also there is some I don't totally disagree with the metaphor and I think within it we would still pick like are we who's a cod and who's a trout.
Yeah. There's one with like a really harsh like scrod or it's not scrad.
Scrod is something Jason definitely ate growing up.
Scrod? The scrod guy?
I've not actively ordered scrod but I've likely sampled scrod.
But that is like a mundane like when they're not when we're maybe not serving the top of the line fish maybe scrod is what we're looking at.
Yeah isn't it like a bottom feeder is what they would call it? Like that's the that's like a real like cheap dirty fish.
I can't speak to that. I think it's definitely a fish where you're getting like a salad and a drink and a dessert with it. You're getting it on a platter with two sides.
A lot of support like as with forming the big mega ranger needs help things added to it. What's the when they all form what's it called?
Oh it's a Megazord or a Megazord or a Megascrod is helped out by mashed potatoes and a beverage.
Jason's version of a Megazord is when a soup and salad combine to make a meal.
When you get both. Yeah.
It's a big transfer. It's like going into his stomach.
Iceberg lettuce go!
Blue cheese go!
And that's the salad that is most of the salad you have described right now at these sorts of family restaurants.
Two ingredients the ultimate salad ready for battle.
The electricity soloing. We have a guest though we have to bring him we have so much to talk about here.
Folks you know him from WWE NXT pro wrestling in general because he's Johnny Wrestling.
Ladies and gentlemen it's Johnny Gargano.
Hi guys how are you? Hi Johnny.
We're doing fine we're talking salads here on podcast.
I heard you did. I like the idea of I appreciate now that I'm here to kind of be the power ranger export as well.
Because you had a mix up between Megazord or Dragonzord.
Megazord would be the correct answer. Yes.
That you were looking for by the way but yeah I get it.
First of many. My knowledge is not so great.
So you already you've proven your knowledge vastly beyond mine.
I'm sure it'll keep up.
So are you guys were you guys did you guys watch Power Rangers at all?
Yes. Oh yeah.
Okay. Did you? Okay.
Not me. I explained this on the show once when Power Rangers came up before.
We did a little like small component of Power Rangers once before.
And I said that I was really into the Ninja Turtles and then Power Rangers came around and I started telling my parents about it.
And there's a bunch of them and there's a red one a yellow one and they're all different types of animals.
And my mom just said hey what if you skipped this one?
And I was like yeah I can see that. I can see the logic in that.
Yeah then we save the money on the toys. Okay all right not doing it.
And that was the end of that.
So where did you go from? You went from Ninja Turtles to where? What was your next?
Probably like reading Entertainment Weekly.
Oh no.
I was reading Owen Gleiberman reviews.
Because I went through the natural progression of Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles to Power Rangers.
Like those were the next step in evolution for me.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Power Rangers, then pro wrestling.
That was like my evolution.
It would have been mine I think if that was the only missing component.
I'd be right there with you.
Yeah.
We'd be in the ring together I think.
Yeah. Oh guaranteed.
Johnny, any X-Men in there? X-Men between Ninja Turtles and Power Rangers?
Yeah so I was a big X-Men the animated series person.
A big Spider-Man the animated series person as you can tell from my back wall over here.
I have many many a superhero toy and whatnot.
Yeah.
So yeah that was like my I think I started at like Sesame Street.
Because I saw Sesame Street Live growing up.
And then obviously went to Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
Then like there was a pits off of like Spider-Man, X-Men, Power Rangers, all the superhero stuff.
Batman the animated series and then ultimately pro wrestling.
And I always felt like I had like a weird thing in my head where I could only like one thing at a time.
I don't know what it was. I felt like I was cheating on something if I liked something too much.
Right.
I don't know why that was my weird bugaboo when I was little.
But that was apparently a thing that I did.
Oh I tried to like everything at once and just permanently damaged my brain for ever basically.
Yeah.
Power Rangers I like you're a little younger than I am.
But Power Rangers I like knew is maybe not something I should like because I was so sophisticated.
But I did like it regardless.
And would like I remember I did get the Dragon Zords when I said that like I'm really embarrassed that because I know what the difference is.
Sorry for calling you out.
No, no, it's OK.
I was sitting here as a Power Rangers fan like what is he doing?
You're a bigger Power Rangers fan than I am for sure.
But I did drag my like 9 p.m.
My mom like or 855 Toys R Us called us and they were like you know with that Dragon Zord you have on hold.
We have it in stock and I begged my mom to go that moment.
She's like we can go tomorrow can't we?
And I was like we cannot go tomorrow.
So we like bolted to Toys R Us to get that Dragon Zord.
So like the Dragon Zord to me was like if I had to pick one present one Christmas present as a child as the one that was like the height of my happiness.
It would probably be the Dragon Zord because my parents Christmas storied me.
If you understand that reference.
So I wanted the Dragon Zord so much.
That was like the number one thing I wanted on my Christmas list that year.
And I opened all my presents and it wasn't there.
And I was heartbroken only for my dad to be like is there something behind the tree and then for it to be behind the tree.
So but that was like a thing that my parents did after that.
They saw how well it worked out.
They did it like every single year then after that.
But they did it in like new unique ways where it'd be like okay the Dragon Zord was behind the tree.
What can we do next?
Okay we're going to leave this pinball set on his bunk bed and say that Santa fell asleep in the middle.
And while he was delivering the presents he had to take a nap.
And he left it there like hey Johnny go let the dog outside.
Oh the presents at the bottom of the steps now.
So I say I say all the time now looking back on it as an adult.
I'm like my parents really should have just sucked it up and been like we're going to have a bad Christmas this year.
Because after that I kind of expected like where is the big present going to be like what's going to where's it where's it going to end up.
One year they should have just been like you didn't get it.
So then the years after that there's always that little hint of danger where it's like maybe maybe it's not going to be there this year.
So that's that's my parenting tip for anyone else out there that I will eventually probably do to my son now.
Yeah so you have a new son very new.
And so you're saying every three or four Christmases you're going to really let him down.
Yeah hopefully he's just a bad person that year so I can kind of justify it.
Oh sure yeah.
We'll see we'll see.
When he's four and he's really bad.
Yeah.
Life lesson.
My parents I also got the Dragon's Sword for Christmas one year and it was out of the box with like everything put together and any like stickers or decals put on it.
So it was ready to go.
And I think that was the last year my parents went that far because those were so complicated.
I think maybe one year I got an N64 like some sort of video game system where it was like set up and ready to go.
Right.
You're saying that's the last time they put like some hard effort into assembling.
Well no but like in addition to wrapping then having to assemble these plastic toys that honestly are pretty easy to break.
Yeah my mom put my mom and dad assumed my dad was there put together the Ninja Turtle sewer for me so it was out of the box.
Oh yeah.
Christmas morning and that's probably the most like that's the best Christmas memory of seeing the sewer which fell apart immediately and never stayed together.
I had this I had this you either sewer too but I get I got weird presents in weird ways.
So my parents said I couldn't get the sewer for some strange reason but my grandma at the time got it for me and put it underneath like my dad as a restaurant and she used to sit at like the desk at the restaurant and answer phones.
She'd be like Johnny go underneath the desk and I crawled underneath the desk and the sewer was just sitting underneath the desk and like she didn't tell my parents.
She got me this tour.
So I had a little surprise like secret sewer underneath the desk at my parents restaurant.
You were constantly on guard for presents.
I know you just never knew what could happen.
Yeah I know.
You were worried not being well like being scared or something of like I'm going to turn the corner and there'll be a present there.
Yeah I kind of miss that that little bit of like danger now because back then especially with like the Dragon's Order the sewer or these hot toys at the time where like you couldn't find them like there was a very real risk where like the movie Jingle All the
Way is real like that was based on Power Rangers obviously because there's a very real risk where like a parent couldn't provide that toy for their child for Christmas and I kind of miss that now because like with eBay and like thing in the internet like
something's always going to be available if you're willing to pay an astronomical price for it.
But like I missed like the danger of I want I'm a psychopath.
I want to like go to Toys R Us if those still existed and wait at midnight and try to get this toy for my kid.
I feel like that'd be fun.
Maybe I would hate it after a while but at least once I want to try it.
Well guess what the danger of not getting things you want is back.
What would the supply chain issues.
Let's go Brandon right.
You got your wish.
Not now.
Not on the theme park.
You said I could start doing it on this one.
Not this one.
Not my podcast I do under a pseudonym.
Yeah let people find that one on their own.
Yeah well the so I want to talk real quick about toy collecting in general before because we have a lot of talk about Power Rangers Live today but a couple topics real quick.
So we're talking about toys because there's doing a lot of retro toys now you see you have some also to the listener who might be listening.
This is a video we're doing a little video now so if you go to I assume Brett forever dog YouTube will probably put this up there.
Or YouTube.
Or YouTube whatever works.
Or it's just part sword or no one sees it or it goes into a vault and you don't see it till we die.
It's possible.
Any amount of options.
We have a prince like vault that we're putting a lot of video content into.
Johnny Power Rangers episode.
Our 20th for our state will release it posthumously and it'll be very exciting but you'll be able to see what we're talking about is what I'm saying.
You're at the forever dog studios by the way.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Where there are lights on us and we don't look ashen gray as we usually do on camera.
But these lights are hitting my massive forehead and I am trying not to be self conscious about it.
Now you know.
You need that for next time.
We'll fix it in post.
Yeah.
Johnny yeah you have a ton of of vintage toys and I believe yeah retro like new retro packaging toys.
And there's so much stuff like Ninja Turtle stuff I've talked about on the show before.
Some of the Ninja Turtle stuff is what you're describing where I have to drive to targets to try to find it.
And I think it's actually the ones right.
Yes.
Yeah yeah yeah.
The NECA cartoon line specifically because the movie line is only at Walmart.
The cartoon line is only at Target.
Of course we all know that.
So so there is some yes I completely agree with you that there's some like old school thrill now I get when I'm like dry like oh you think targets got it and like I have a couple buddies and we're all like in different parts of town.
So we're calling each other and like oh I got the one on Sepulveda they don't have anything.
Oh I ran into the NECA rep which is a guy who comes and stocks the shelves and then I'm just like lingering around him while he's on stock like taking the box stuff out of the box.
You run into the guy who stocks for that company.
It is like running into a celebrity if you ever run into a NECA rep because Target cannot stock NECA products themselves.
They need a third party to stock.
So there's a NECA rep that comes in with boxes and he comes into and he goes into the back and he grabs the boxes.
Excuse me.
And then he stocks them.
And he has to grab them.
It can't just be a touch.
He has to grab them.
Yes.
He's got to sink his claws into it.
Just legally.
Same rules.
He has to touch all four sides of the box.
Have you tried bribing?
Hey buddy there's an up and up tramex in it for you if you give me a heads up.
I say the most embarrassing things.
I'm like oh so is this like sort of your normal time when you do that?
And you can tell he's just like oh get away from me old man.
There's a Starbucks refresher in it for you if you give me a heads up next time you're here.
So I've only had this happen once running into the NECA rep which is just a very fun time.
That's like seeing Santa under the putting things under the tree.
So I completely agree with that.
And there are still little pockets.
But yes by and large you can get stuff on eBay for just like maybe ten dollars twenty dollars over retail.
But real quick.
So we see Johnny you have like a great setup.
I have a question just in general because I am what an out of box collector in general and you're an in box collector.
And I'm fascinated by the display because I think you have recreated almost a toy store shell like shells of a toy store.
Is that what it is?
I did. Yes.
And also to kind of I guess for the people that are watching I did this on purpose as well.
If you look up here there's also a Toys R Us logo.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
So we really recreate it.
It goes to the ceiling.
If you're watching you can kind of see all this.
But yeah so this was very purposely done.
I miss Toys R Us very very much.
And Candice and I went to Ikea and we found these shelves that with pegboards and whatnot that you can kind of recreate your childhood in an essence.
And like you said I am an in box collector.
I believe the artwork on the box is some of the fun in the nostalgia as well.
Like seeing like the Spider-Man the animated series logo and like the X-Men logo like that sort of thing.
Like I don't know.
It just warms my heart.
And also I feel like they're easier to display for me because if they were out of the box and I'd have to like put them on shelves and like display them and I'm bad at posing and things like that.
So this way like I can just have pegboards and kind of stack them like three deep and kind of collect more in itself.
And I actually have the only NECA product I have.
I have the NECA Toka and Razor down there because I'm a big TGP Ninja Turtles movie guy as well.
As my first movie I saw in theaters.
But yeah.
But to be fair I do have a out of the box.
All my Hasbro collection my wrestling Hasbro's are out of the box because that's just that's an astronomical price to pay.
I'm sure you can talk to Matt Cardona about that.
That's the astronomical price to pay for in box WWF Hasbro's.
And those are vintage.
Those are.
Yes.
Yeah.
So makes sense.
Do you feel like he's missing out by not for you like in your case that you set up jam sessions between the Ninja Turtles and Doc Brown and Marty.
Is Johnny missing out on.
I don't think he's missing out because I really have like tried in my older years to really appreciate everyone's philosophy about it because I do get that going into a Toys R Us aisle was the most exciting thing in the world.
And that's the thing is you're stimulating that old memory in your child brain of when you'd round the corner you'd go past all the Barbies and everything and you'd round the corner for the action figure aisle and you didn't know what was in there.
So anytime you go in there there's that much stuff all in boxes.
You're getting that surge of serotonin or whatever it is.
I should tell Candace to just buy me a new toy every week and just put it on the ceiling.
So every time I walk in I'm like oh what's in here this time.
Yeah.
You could.
You could stock like an end cap display of something new too.
I have enough weird things with my childhood that like Candace puts up with like another another weird thing I have that she deals with all the time which this year we didn't do it but I did all the time where I have a weird thing about Christmas to where the presents can't go underneath the tree until I go to sleep.
So she has to like.
Wake up in the middle of the night and put the presents underneath the tree.
We do that for you.
We do that.
It's for me.
My family does that as well.
I don't see a problem with that.
Oh that's you too.
You still have to do.
You go to sleep there's no presents.
Everyone goes to sleep and then my mom I think has resorted to just getting up early.
I think used to stay up late.
Wow.
Yeah.
Which she can't imagine would not usually like so has to for one night of the year push herself to the limit.
I think it's as much her as me at this point.
So yeah.
Well that's nice.
Yeah.
One magical night.
You get one magical night a year.
Come on.
Yeah I get I understand that.
I think we've gotten lazy about it.
We used to be like that but now in my mid to late 30s we've stopped doing it.
Well you were mentioning your wife Candace LeRae who has been on podcasts right before and I also wanted to check in on something because she told us a story to a couple of years ago about an idea you would have.
An idea you had.
I'll let you tell it.
An idea you had for the birth of a child.
Oh right.
And I want to know if anything like that happened.
No.
Okay.
I think I can.
I was looking at it from an outsider's perspective of obviously like Candace said my idea was to kind of recreate the Lion King.
I don't know if she went full deep into what my pitch was but I wanted to get like a Rafiki ass monkey to come into the delivery room and I kind of wanted to you know maybe spread the news to the people waiting in the way.
Obviously with COVID and stuff as well it was a little harder to sneak a monkey in the delivery room.
It used to be 2019.
This is this cake.
I definitely could have done it back then but now it's so many restrictions.
I was going to kind of pitch kind of put it out there that maybe it's not going that well to kind of bring the mood down in the waiting room for the family.
That's what people want to hear what your closest relatives in the family want to hear.
Maybe it's not going well and then like I come out and my head's down I'm like oh no it didn't go well.
Then like the monkey busts out and like he holds up the baby and a big like big moment happens where everyone's losing it because Rafiki monkey shows up.
He does a Lion King thing with the baby and the baby is presented to the family.
Obviously now that we had the baby and seeing everything that it goes through that that did not happen.
Nothing like that happened.
Taking you through the process lets you know that immediately it's instantly handing a new a frightened newborn over to a monkey who you have just met for the first time as if like knowing the monkey would help.
But a stranger monkey.
Yeah maybe a stranger monkey.
Not a friend monkey a stranger monkey.
Well they're famously reliable creatures you can predict what they're going to do moment to moment.
Lion King is based on real life right?
Based on true events.
There's also a detail of that that I liked.
I guess like any logistics of getting a monkey is crazy for sure but I like your detail of a Rafiki-esque monkey.
I couldn't tell you what type of monkey that is but it seems like it's not one that I've just you know they're not just like sitting around they aren't at the theme park shows at the zoo.
Yeah that seems like a very specific varietal.
So like no no no this monkey won't do no but they're trained they'll be nice to the baby don't care it's about the look.
Rafiki.
Candace of course asked me how we would sneak the monkey into the delivery room and I said well obviously we dress him up like a doctor.
I mean that's obviously what we do right?
Yeah.
Dress him up like a doctor.
Sneak the monkey in.
Monkeys don't look cool.
He told the children to wait for this baby to come out just hanging out.
This is great this is like something that would happen in Disorderly's the Fat Boys movie.
This is like this is hijinks.
Then we got to dress up the monkey like a doctor.
Rafiki is a mandrill which I am not a hundred percent on but I believe might be an especially violent kind of monkey.
Traditionally.
I think he'd be cool.
We understand the gravity of the situation.
He's nice.
I'm doing the birth thing right?
You want me to do the birth thing like the movie?
Yeah.
I got it.
Some things are sacred.
Even to mandrills.
Again.
So there were no hijinks during the what's probably good.
No hijinks during the birth.
Especially good because I made the mistake of I don't know if you guys are aware of it but the movie Fatherhood on Netflix.
You guys know what that is starring Kevin Hart.
Oh I've heard of it but I haven't seen it.
Based on true events to where everything goes well in the delivery room.
They have the baby.
It's all great.
And then Kevin Hart's wife dies due to a pulmonary embolism which I googled it.
I googled it immediately after watching this movie.
So Kevin Hart has to raise the baby by himself.
So I made the mistake of watching that movie on Netflix.
Candace went to go get her hair done.
We just found out she was pregnant.
Went to go get her hair done.
And I was like I'm going to sit down with my dog and watch a movie on Netflix for the heck of it.
I watched this movie.
I'm like Fatherhood this should be great.
And then I watched this movie.
I'm like oh my god.
Like this is a very real thing that could happen now.
So the whole time that was my number one thing in my head was like pulmonary embolism.
You got to move.
Can't have blood clots in the legs.
So I became that guy where I was like learning everything I possibly could to make sure this doesn't happen.
Because if I have to raise this baby by myself.
Boy oh boy.
And also I told her I think if something happened where Candace went down during the pregnancy and I had the baby I would kind of dislike the baby a little bit.
That's immediately.
That's a victim.
That's one victim.
Right over in the very beginning.
He's got one down already.
One down.
Who knows how many more to go.
Candace said if like there was a thing going on in the room where there was a decision to be made between her and the baby who would you pick.
I said well I'm going to pick you because I don't know the baby.
Like the baby could be a murderer.
Like the baby could have turned out bad.
I could be saving people right now.
This is such a like a roller coaster ride between like monkey prank and then like the worst reality possibly.
You really went you really went on both sides like.
I did.
Yeah.
Getting a little peek behind the curtain a little bit.
How my brain works.
Sure.
You took it dark by the way.
I'm not I'm not wishing ill on Candace or anyone involved.
But if something actually bad happens.
Baby's great.
That's great.
Well yeah that's one.
We're not in the dark the monkey reality.
We're in the happy timeline.
If you if something had gone wrong and then you still had the monkey thing loaded up.
Oh now is it just like hey can you exit through the window.
I have some actual bad news to report.
Yeah we definitely I don't think that like this I guess one way of thinking would be the monkey would kind of if the monkey delivered the news it'd be a little like I don't know.
Like would it be better.
I don't think it'd be better right.
One and it's in might seem insensitive but it might kind of brighten the mood as well because everyone got to see a mandrill.
Yeah.
Right.
And roll is cool.
Yeah.
I guess it depends on if the monkey delivers the news before or after he rips some faces off.
That's true.
That is true.
It could just be a real bad day in that room.
But no no luckily everything turned out great.
He's an adorable little guy.
And yeah no monkeys were were utilized.
No people were harmed by monkeys.
No in the making of this baby.
It was a fairly regular delivery for the most part.
It went it went a week but I mean it was a fairly regular delivery.
Sure is a while.
And we were just talking before I had seen that like I think you were trying to induce pregnancy by like doing like an eight hour.
Were you waiting for figment popcorn bucket that day.
No no that was a different day.
Oh my god.
That was a different day.
But like that that's a perfect example of pregnant Candice.
Pregnant Candice.
We have serious FOMO and well I do in particular and I abide by one Disney rule and that's if you see something and you have the opportunity to get it you better get it because it's going to sell out and it's going to be on eBay and it's going to be a million dollars.
So if you have the chance you got to get it.
So we went to Epcot that day to where the popcorn bucket was on sale and the line got down to about four hours three to four hours.
And the rumor the rumor online was it was like seven hours.
So hearing three to four hours when you've been hearing seven hours it was kind of like man like three to four hours ain't bad if we went in this line.
So and when you're pregnant wife how pregnant was as pregnant as you can get I think at that point.
You can be the most pregnant you can be.
Wow.
Most pregnant you can be without a baby coming out.
Like if your pregnant wife is like I'm OK waiting in this line.
What are you going to say.
You're going to say like no I'm tired I want to go home.
It's like you're OK doing it.
So of course I'm going to do it.
So we definitely waited in line for the figment popcorn bucket.
It was only like three to four hours.
So it wasn't that bad.
It wasn't bad at all.
Three to four.
I'd be complaining about it after 10 minutes and I don't have the ability to get pregnant.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. But then like you said like Candice had the idea to walk around Disney to induce labor.
So we walked around Disney Springs the night before and the morning that we were supposed to go and get induced because Candice was hoping we'd be able to walk and it would help induction.
So the morning that we were going to induce we actually had breakfast reservations to get Tonga toast.
So like Candice booked it.
She's like let's go Ohana.
No not Ohana.
It's Kona Cafe.
Yeah.
He's got it.
Yeah Kona Cafe.
Let's go to Kona Cafe and let's get Tonga toast and eat breakfast.
So we drove out to Disney and morning of the induction drove out to Disney ate Tonga toast had a great morning.
And to be fair that's one of Candice's favorite memories because she would always she says now she was hoping to walk around Disney and she just or she'd imagine it'd be like a TV show to where the water would break.
You'd be like my water broke.
We got to go to the hospital like one of those fun little instances.
Well when her water broke the next day two days later at like four in the morning she said it was like a cartoon cartoony pop that happens like a real cartoony pop right right and then like liquid just doesn't stop coming.
So she's like in hindsight I'm really glad my water didn't break at Disney.
It's kind of awful.
She was thinking it was going to be a TV thing not a TV thing.
I was with the Lion King thing as well.
Not like that at all.
Because then the park has to put up signs that say you may get wet.
Yeah.
What is what's different about Tonga toast than I know it's different than regular toast but what is what what is Tonga toast specifically compressed you never had Tonga toast.
I'm not a Tonga and where is the Kona Cafe that's Disney.
It's in the Polynesia Polynesia Polynesian.
What makes it is also in the Polynesian which I also recommend very highly great stuff, especially the noodles, if they're back, but I think they're back.
They are back.
So he knows so much about this.
He knows.
I've stayed there.
But not recently.
No not since 1991.
That's what I'm saying.
Yes.
Somebody ever stayed since 1991 and you're up on their current menu items.
I keep up on what the you know fans the real heads are talking about.
The noodle thing was a thing for a hot minute.
People were real mad about the noodles.
Real mad about the noodles.
I knew about the noodles too.
It was a hot thing online.
The Tonga toast is basically like it's like a brick like a brick of toast filled with bananas.
They like it's like French toast but they like roll it in cinnamon sugar and it's stuffed with bananas and you pour like strawberry syrup on top of it.
It's delicious.
My number one if I had to pick one Disney World breakfast I think I would go Tonga toast.
I think that would be my choice there.
I don't know.
I wasn't looking at what anybody's feeds were doing but with the video ability we have currently was there just.
Did Jason's eyes get glazed like donut glade.
Did you just like tear up to the street doing a clay only the listener can tell us.
I mean I just usually have a certain level of donut glaze on me at any given time.
I just naturally secrete it.
Yeah I have not had it either.
I will I will have it next time though.
It's great.
Highly high recommendation.
That's probably one of my highest recommendations I can give is Tonga toast.
Yeah.
All right.
Well on that note today's toast pick.
Today's toast pick is Tonga toast.
Let's I think OK let's get to the main course here.
Power Rangers Live.
I think let's get titles correct.
Oh yes.
There are a few of them.
There are a few.
Yeah.
What I saw of the video that we watched I think is Mighty Morphin Power Rangers World Tour live on stage.
But what does everyone else have?
That sounds about right.
I don't remember but it sounds about right.
I think the shorter one was just Mighty Morphin Power Rangers Alive.
Sure.
Gets the job done.
Yeah.
There is currently a placeholder website for a Power Rangers live show.
Yes.
It is a WordPress.
It is one page.
There is a video play button that is just a PNG file.
It does not play anything.
But I did sign up to find out if it's coming to my area and it is there are tickets for sale in Philadelphia in November.
There was a stunt show in Japan Power Rangers show in Japan when we were there a couple of years.
We didn't see it but they there.
At the Tokyo Dome.
Tokyo Dome.
Yeah.
Tokyo Dome city at least.
I don't know if it was in the Tokyo Dome itself.
But yes.
So there's been versions of it but we're talking today about the first version.
The 90s at the height of Power Rangers Mania live tour that went around the country.
Right.
And it is like it's documented pretty well.
This is like we've talked on the show about the Ninja Turtles coming out of their shells tour.
There was a this was a thing people were doing at the time.
Obviously Sesame Street Live.
He-Man was predated that.
We talked about He-Man.
We've talked about.
Yeah.
So this was their version of it which I would say this is like almost maybe the biggest budget version.
I'd say so.
This thing is pretty impressive.
From the video.
When you look at it.
Who all of the people here today experienced this live in person?
Johnny.
Johnny did.
Yep.
I did it.
Yes.
Did you do it or no?
I saw it.
Not me.
I have specific memories.
I saw it at Philadelphia's Convention Hall which was an old venue down by the University
of Pennsylvania.
It used to be called the Philadelphia Civic Center.
This is where the Jackson Five did their first concert for Motown Records.
Wow.
A lot of NCAA games were there.
WCW programed their 1989 and 1992 Halloween Havoc pay per views and the 94 Slammery there.
And it is long since bulldozed.
Oh wow.
How could they?
One of my biggest memories of the show.
This was just forever glued in my memory.
It doesn't have anything to do with the show itself.
I was sitting next to someone who smelled so strongly of gherkin pickles.
This is a childhood like eight or nine year old memory.
Gherkin.
Specifically the sweet pickle.
Very specific memory.
Gherkins.
And it just haunted me.
The whole show was so distracting because I was like their coat is bleeding over into
my skin.
Am I going to smell like gherkin pickles?
Why does this person smell like gherkin pickles?
What is happening?
Gherkin.
Which has pulled my attention so many times during this show.
Questions.
How do you know gherkin as opposed to other pickles?
Well I was a nasty little pickle kid Scott.
Ow.
Ow my ears.
You didn't say pickle boy though.
I didn't.
Thankfully.
No.
But nasty.
That's really the crazy word there.
I think I had been really into gherkin pickles as a kid and then for a while I could not
eat them because I was so haunted by this memory.
I don't even know if I said anything to my family.
My family might be learning about this very glued in my memory instance.
How could you not tell us?
You've lived with this for decades?
Yeah.
Wow.
Maybe they worked at the factory?
I mean it could be.
Was it nearby?
There was a lot of larger factory food production factories in Philadelphia at the time.
I think also one of my memories of the show is there not being, I mean there was plenty
of Power Rangers merchandise for sale at the time.
At the show I don't remember really coming back with a souvenir.
And that was a real souvenir kid.
I had, watching, it rehashed my memory watching YouTube video.
I definitely bought one of the weird sword things that they show in the crowd that people
have, like the weird rainbow sword thing, but had nothing to do with Power Rangers.
I don't know why it was for sale.
Obviously they just had them left over from something.
They were like hey we're going to sell them for a Power Rangers show.
General events.
And I looked online, so me and Candice looked, and the only merchandise we could find was
a denim jacket with Power Rangers World Tour and a denim vest with Power Rangers World
Tour.
I don't know why if those were on sale at the show.
It felt like they would be.
But what a weird particular choice of souvenir to have is a denim vest or jacket to sell
for children.
Yeah, that, the children.
But they also had a program.
I did have a program as well.
So that was.
You can find the program online.
We did, we did a, we just, in February we did a lot of celebrity restaurants for Celebruary
and almost every restaurant had a denim jacket or vest.
So it feels like that was a 90s thing that like business people were like well we gotta
sell a denim vest.
We have to sell that.
Leno had only been on tonight's show for a couple years, so everybody, and everyone was
taking their cues from him, comedically and stylistically.
Of course.
He was our America's fashion voice.
That's right.
So what other choice did you have?
He had to use denim.
Johnny, where'd you, where did you see, what were the circumstances of Power Rangers Live?
Okay, so I saw mine in Cleveland, Ohio, where I grew up and where I frequent very often.
It's my hometown.
And I remember I went there with, it was me, my mom, my dad, and my friends and their mom.
I also remember, especially during that time period, my mom used to make me costumes all
the time.
Used to make, there's pictures of me as a child dressed like the Green Ranger, dressed
like the White Ranger, dressed like Shawn Michaels when I got into my wrestling phase.
So I remember I dressed like the White Ranger to go to this Power Rangers Live.
And I'm not going to say I invented cosplay, but it was one of the first incarnations of
cosplay because a lot of parents and people were stopping me just to try to take pictures
of me in my sweet White Ranger outfit.
So they'd be like, hey, you hit a pose.
And I'd do a pose.
And so people on their disposable cameras have pictures of young Johnny.
If you live in Cleveland, Ohio, and went to Power Rangers Live, you might have a little
White Ranger kid posing on your disposable camera somewhere and it'd be me.
So yeah, I remember that in particular.
I also remember, so I was a very shy, socially awkward kid growing up.
So like I didn't want to get picked on.
Like I had a weird thing.
Like don't pick on me.
Like don't call me on stage, which is weird, obviously what my job ended up being.
But don't call me on stage.
Don't like call me out in the crowd.
Like on the video, as you'll see, like when the putties run the crowd, I'm horrified.
I'm like, don't I don't want to hit like a putty to grab me and pull me up on stage.
That was my worst fear as a child for some reason was being pulled up on stage at any point
and being like, look at this kid.
I thought that wouldn't happen.
Just look at him.
The part of the, you remember the part of the Power Rangers Live when they brought a random kid on stage.
Everyone look at this kid.
We don't usually do this, but when a kid's dorky enough.
Bring him up.
Man, yeah, I yeah, I said that's because I saw the Turtles Tour and I had a similar thing,
but they did not have as many bad guys in the audience.
They didn't really even have many foot soldiers.
But this thing had putty like tons of putties.
Putties are like the goons of Power Rangers.
If you don't know.
And it was the second generation putties with the little putty like Lord Zed logo, which if you hit, make them explode.
It made them easier to beat.
I don't know why they upgraded to an easier to beat thing,
but they all of a sudden had like light gray with a little like target on their chest essentially.
And if you just punched it, it would destroy them.
Yeah, it's pride, I guess.
Yeah, Zed came first.
I was not. I did not like the putties on the show.
I was happy when they died.
But I don't know any other way to put it.
They make this Scott.
They make this horrible noise that's like, like, yeah, I did not like that.
Can I say that a lot of why I didn't mind when my mom just plainly said, don't get into the Power Rangers.
And I agreed.
Some of it was because in rewatching it, I go right back there that I do find so much of the show like nails on a chalkboard.
The putty sounds is one of the things.
And then the helmet head, Alpha Five.
Alpha Five.
I hate the I so thoroughly.
I didn't like it.
Then I know it hit the same register as like baby bop on Barney.
That was kind of around the same time.
Just like too irritating, too irritating.
And my crit did everybody love Alpha Five?
Am I a monster?
Kids like the Alpha Five.
Yeah, I like a little fair.
I watched I just watched the YouTube clip back.
My mom was in town for Mother's Day.
So we watched it together to prepare for this.
She was there when I was a kid.
And she even said, like, man, he said, I a lot.
Like, so she even got like a weird head where she was like, I hate Alpha Five.
So I didn't be like an adult thing now where we hate Alpha Five.
But I think I remember kids probably loved him.
He seemed like he would be loved.
But yeah, I think a little bit of slapstick in like a, you know, half hour show goes is pretty good in an hour and 10 minute stage show.
There is like a lot of slapstick.
There's a lot of hijinks in this.
I was not I don't I did not dislike Alpha, but I was more of a Zorda.
I like Zorda better.
Zorda is a disembodied head in a tube played eventually by Brian Cranston in the new movie, which is great.
But but my my thing was with I just will get social clips from this show that I feel like like when I'm watching this show,
like when I'm watching it, like I'm ignoring any words that are said.
But some of like when I'm watching the monsters yell, I go, this is maybe like my ideal version of entertainment.
Like when Goldar is just yelling Power Rangers, I go, this is maybe the height of entertainment for me.
He suits screaming like this feels like Shakespeare to me.
I'm not listening to anything he says. Doesn't matter.
It's just like this aesthetic now has been so burned in my brain that I love it.
And at the time I loved it because like the kids are fine.
I like Tommy. I thought he was cool.
I thought they were all cool. Yeah.
But the monsters were the thing I think I like the best.
Is there some of that for you, Johnny, where like this is live entertainment that is fighting and where you cheer good guys and boo bad guys?
Was that like getting into your brain is like, I like this.
I like the feel of this.
Do you think it had anything to do with the mental chemistry of getting wrestling?
I definitely think that like I say this all the time.
Like I when I was little, I wanted to be a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle.
Then I wanted to be a Power Ranger.
And then ultimately I wanted to be a pro wrestler because I feel like a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle and Power Rangers weren't real jobs I could attain in real life.
Yeah. And we take it seriously, I guess.
There's only six slots too. You got a lot more chances.
That's true.
So I think like it's one of those things where like I could put on a different little costume and fight bad guys and be a pro wrestler.
I think it definitely played a part in my ultimate evolution and becoming a pro wrestler.
It's just because, you know, I couldn't be Tommy from the Power Rangers growing up.
What'd you say? Like there's so like, you know, there's Johnny, there's all this talk about, you know, where you're going to wrestle next.
Let's forget that. What if somebody came to you with a third option and said Power Rangers live on tour, you get to be the new Green Ranger and you can like sort of maybe do better.
Like the fighting would be a lot better if you're doing it, I would say.
Yeah. At one point I asked Candace, how much do you think these guys got paid?
Oh, oh, oh, don't know.
No, don't look at the back.
That's bad. Real bad. Yeah.
Yeah.
Not knowing anything.
We're traveling every night, right?
I mean, we're traveling city to city.
So they had to feed them some soup or something.
They got nothing.
They got one cup of soup every night.
I think, you know, there's a decent chance because like the actors on the show on Power Rangers were so screwed.
They were doing some stuff too. Like they were like going hard.
Some of them were like some of the karate stuff, like obviously they weren't coming close at all in their strikes or anything like that.
But like, right.
At one point, and I don't want to spoil the show, but at one point when the Power Rangers jump out, like they all like had their moment where they all like show up on the screen and they're like, I'm going to jump out and have my moment.
Like they were jumping off the stage and like the fact that they didn't get seriously injured blew my mind.
Yeah.
They were doing some, it was like slam dunk contest for a minute with Power Rangers.
Yeah, yeah.
There's in the I think maybe it was one of the videos of the press event they had where like there's a couple of big falls they take.
So, yeah, I was going to say I think there's a decent chance because the actual actors that did Power Rangers were not in this show, but their voices were.
But there's a chance that the actors who were actually doing the stunt work for this live show were paid better than the actors on the show because the actors on the show were so screwed over.
Like people were fired.
Half the team was fired just because they wanted actual real money that was being generated by the show.
I was not thrilled with that cast change because the leader of the team was named Jason and suddenly it's a guy named Rocky.
Oh yeah.
But I believe the storyline so intently and I was like, well, they have to go to that peace conference.
So on the other hand.
You thought the reason.
I was like, what?
They won't give them sag representation.
They're making hand over the bond companies making money hand over fist.
You know, so it's crazy and I don't want to get too depressing here because because it sucks to like think of the reality sometimes of the stuff we watch as kids.
Brett, I have a clip here, clip three.
If you could play real quick.
It's so crazy that the actors are not getting paid very well.
And then this is the video going out to entice like places like cities to bring Power Rangers to them.
So whenever you're ready here, hopefully this works.
The number one rated kid's trip in October sweeps.
Look at this. They're just shit talking all the other shows kicking bonkers ass.
Power Rangers clearly marry Melody's Tom and Jerry kids.
Seven each shift.
We're just looking at a bar graph.
The show remained on the very top.
Bonkers way at the fuck you.
You bonkers.
Power Rangers destroying the cat Bobby's World.
You're getting the great Bobby World doing pretty good across the nation.
Yeah, that was high.
Yeah, I cut the ego.
We're good.
So I've got a 10.6.
Yeah, Bobby's are highly rated show.
Apparently rating that don't exist anymore.
Like the when the finale of This Is Us will not come close to one random Bobby's World.
What the hell was those seeing those numbers really makes me think how popular television was back in the day.
Crazy.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh my God.
And Power Rangers had Darkwing Duckle.
They got a three point six.
Yeah, I think Darkwing Duck was wrapping up its run.
You know, Bobby's World still might be on top.
Bobby's World was hot.
The storylines were compelling.
Yeah, well, it aired earlier in the lineup.
So you're losing kids as the block goes on.
So by the time it gets to X-Men, you might be a little.
They got chores to do.
Yeah, sweep the yard.
I was impressed with the cats performance, quite frankly.
I like to eat.
Yeah.
But Power Rangers obviously was like doing so well, making so much money.
The actors on the show getting screwed.
But yeah, live performance.
We don't know.
There might have been a union.
They might have gotten OK pay is what I'm saying.
Maybe to be part of this touring entity that might lead into something I was going to bring up, Mike, which is so the impetus for doing a tour was that they on
Presidents Day in 1994, there was an event held at the Universal Amphitheater here in L.A.
that was done in conjunction with the DARE program, which was this initiative in the 90s to get a bunch of black shirts to a bunch of kids for them to end up at Goodwills, ironically, decades down the line.
Very successful in that.
Maybe not in anything else.
So working with the DARE program, the Power Rangers did a live event.
And the idea here was that this was going to be just a Universal Studios thing and they were going to do it in one of the theaters they have in the park, maybe in the cone in the barbarian stage or something.
Then they got wind of how many people were interested in seeing the Power Rangers.
And it like it was just going to be like, I don't know, we'll do a little thing in the afternoon.
Right. So many people were coming.
They had to upgrade it to the Universal Amphitheater, which holds six thousand people.
The Gibson?
It became the Gibson Amphitheater.
Yeah, right, right.
And it became so six thousand people it holds.
They had to do six shows, ultimately.
Thirty six thousand people came, which is one of the top days in the history of Universal Studios.
Thirty six thousand.
Thirty six thousand people showed up on one day, which caused the freeways to back up.
And this, which brings me into the clip that I labeled freeways.
This is a little like, you know, to start getting the word out about the Power Rangers tour,
like, well, you're going to have to book this in your mega venue, because look what happened when we barely even announced it in L.A.
And then it caused pandemonium throughout the city.
Power Rangers gridlock in the northbound Hollywood freeway.
It was a monstrous mess of traffic.
Their power is so great, their mere presence backed up freeway traffic for 10 miles.
So widen your freeways and prepare your town for the end of the decade.
Widen your freeway.
Change your zoning laws.
That's where all that construction was in Cleveland during that time.
Oh, they were widening the freeway.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They had to.
Hurry, cancel everything else.
Cancel funding across the city.
All other programs canceled.
That, that Universal Hollywood event happens with the original cast.
And then by the time the live show goes on tour, then the new cast and a new cast of Zords has taken over.
That changeover happened right after.
OK, OK. Wow.
That changeover.
I mean, so all the Power Rangers listeners, if you don't know this, all the Power Rangers stuff is reused footage and costumes from a Japanese series called Super Sentai is kind of the umbrella name for it.
So every see they would film seasons of that and then eventually send the costumes to the American productions where they would write new stories and then film the actors, you know, without the helmets on and stuff.
Yes, it would be a mix.
And you could tell as a kid that it was a mix.
Yeah.
Like sometimes you go, well, this footage looks older than this other footage.
Yes, when they show in the show seems ancient.
Yeah, when they're fighting outside, it looks the footage looks 10 years older than when they're in the school.
It's like faulty towers.
Like he leaves as faulty leaves and then goes to like much darker footage shot way different than how it looks inside.
Yeah.
So, yeah, they were like there was all this cost saving things they were doing for the show.
But not for the tour.
Based on what happened, the early Carmageddon that shut down all of Los Angeles, they knew that they had gold on their hands, as well as gold are on their hands.
So when they were going to start this tour, they knew like they had a lot of money to spend.
We'd have the number somewhere.
I think.
Let's see.
The guy was the guy who pitched his take on it was told by Saban.
You've got three million to mount the show and a ten million dollar budget to take it on the road.
I don't know what things cost, but that seems high to me.
And they also just loaded this thing up with a bunch of people who mainly did concert tours.
People like rock and roll impresario Ricky Farr.
Did you come across that name?
I saw.
I just like the sound of it.
Rock and roll impresario Ricky Farr.
Yeah. Well, impresario is a great word.
Yeah. Yeah.
It was a it was him and a bunch of people who did who mainly before this did like Rod Stewart tours.
And there's a lot of I found a couple of articles where they're framing it in light of like, I mean, what would Rod think of this?
And how do you know and how do you get Rod level production values to the Power Rangers?
And and they would say, well, we measure it against.
Well, if Rod would like it, then it'd be good enough for just a really strange juxtaposition.
And then also a guy who was a promoter who put the thing together.
His name was Marcel Avram.
And this is a photo I have, Brett, loaded up.
I'll describe it for people who are just listening.
But if you could if you could pull up Marcel Avram, just, you know, the level of Titan we're dealing with putting the show together.
That's Marcel on the far right with the beard.
He looks like a Brett Gellman character.
And he is standing. He's in like a big hand huddle with bad era Michael Jackson, who is between the very tan Siegfried and Roy, who are both wearing cowboy hats.
Wow. Look at those outfits.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Some very bold, some very experimental cowboy uniform, as well as I believe that guy's name is Frank Grillo, Michael Jackson's manager for a long time, who's in Goodfellas.
He acts in Goodfellas.
I was going to say, why is Paulie Walnuts there?
He's very much that. And he's he's in Wayne's World.
He's like the music guy in the limo.
Oh, yeah. They have to impress.
Yeah. What a tight. What a weird guy who was in Michael Jackson orbit.
But anyway, Marcel Avram and that guy not only put concerts together with Michael Jackson, but also sued sued Michael Jackson several times, once for five point three million dollars for not she sued him for millions of dollars.
And then they settled and then he tried it again.
I don't know. Let's try working with Michael again.
And he just didn't show up.
And these people, this is who we're dealing with, who we're putting on.
What I'm getting at is this is more than just people are doing a couple of kicks on stage.
This is concert level.
Yeah. Big pyro bursts throughout and trying to keep a Rod Stewart pedigree.
That's a yeah, those are heavy hitters.
Yeah. Business.
And you are.
And you see it on stage, I think, especially we'll get to the finale.
But the finale is very impressive.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
It's very, very cool.
And yeah, first is like Turtles where Turtles feels like that show was on a budget, you know, like the set was like, OK, there weren't that many dancers.
And then there wasn't much fighting.
They replaced the fighting with songs.
Yes. Yeah.
They just like, incidentally, well, we have to represent the idea of fighting.
We have to kind of like move around slightly to suggest what fighting might be like.
This is much more of a full on fighting stunt show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So so I remember I remember I was very disappointed going to it because I expected the actual actors would be there.
Right. Yeah.
So I expected like Tommy was going to show up and like take off his mask helmet and be like, hey, guys, like I'm Tommy.
Good to be in Cleveland, Ohio. Like that didn't happen, obviously.
But I will say watching it back now, like it goes so far outside of the normal Power Rangers script.
Because the normal Power Rangers set up obviously every single Power Rangers episode you watch any single one now as an adult, you can kind of catch on.
It's Power Rangers show up. They do some stuff.
They make a bad guy. Bad guy shows up. Power Rangers fight the bad guy in little form.
They start beating the bad guy in little form. They make him grow. He grows up. They get the Zords. They beat him with the Zords.
End of show. Every single show that happens. Watching it back now and watching the live stage show.
They don't do that at all. Yeah. For some reason, the Zords fight the little guy, the little Luma Tor monster.
And like the Luma Tor monster beats the Zords by himself in little form.
Yes. And then the Power Rangers are like, oh, we got to fight him. It's it's very wild.
And I will say I also was very taken aback by the random magic. They decided to kind of have a magic show.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't know why they had magic for some phrase.
And they were like, we got to make the show entertaining.
Let's add some magic and turn the Power Rangers into birds for a random reason. Yeah. Monkeys or birds or.
I don't believe they say the phrase Parrot Rangers.
It seems like it was right there. Yeah, I know. Right there. They blew it. Yeah.
Here I have a clip just of the show to give people a little taste. Audio and video and a clip of there in here.
There's some magic. We can cut this off at any time. But this is clip eight, please.
This is like Zed, Lord Zed. So Lord Zed is one of my favorite characters in fiction also.
He's so fun. He's so cool looking. We've talked about Ivan. He's a lot.
We love Ivan news. Johnny, I don't know. You and I have a news fan.
I like Ivan news. I'm a big Power Rangers movie guy. Are you more Zed or Ivan?
I think Zed. I'm more Zed, I think. Yeah. I have a Zed helmet back there.
Oh, yeah, I've seen that. Yeah, yeah. I've seen that. It's fun. Yeah, it's fun.
Zed was scared. Scott Zed came in on the second season.
And when I say second season, I mean, there were dozens and dozens of episodes and then Zed showed up.
But they kind of Power Rangers for a little while would air every weekday.
Wow. New episodes. Yes. Eventually shifted to kind of like a new one once or twice a week.
He was married to Rita. Yeah. So he was the original villain.
And I like Rita too, by the way. I'm not trying to put Rita down.
But it seems like Rita became kind of a joke in the face of. Yeah. Yes.
She was always kind of like schticky. But then like Zed shows up and like, oh, he's a bad guy.
He deposed Rita Repulsa. Eventually, she concocts a love potion and forces them to get married to each other.
As you do. Yes. They treat. They treat her like shit in this. Yeah.
Yeah. I was kind of uncomfortable by reading this live show.
I was like, wow, there's so many to her.
And she look, she has an annoying voice. That's that's part of the character.
That was in there, too. I couldn't. Yes. But but they're mean to her in this clip.
So you're going to get in this clip. You're going to get some Lord Zed's plan.
You're going to see why I think he's one of my favorite characters in fiction.
You're going to see them being mean to read and then you're going to get a little magic as well.
So so whenever you're ready, it's all here. Yeah.
Yeah. I plan to do away with the Rangers and capture this entire city in one fell swoop.
Oh, yeah. Right. I've heard that before. Please cover this witch.
I'm so mean. They were they dated before this. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, their buddies are taking Rita away now. They weren't exclusive.
And they're doing this straight up David Copperfield like magic trick, putting her behind a curtain in order to draw the Rangers away from their home and away from.
So then she's like doing the trick where she disappears basically.
And unleash him upon this town. Then as the power rages come to fight my creation, Goldar will ambush and capture them two at a time and bring them here.
So what will we do with them? I mean, a great voice.
I haven't decided yet. There's a very complicated plan, by the way.
Two at a time. We're going to take the Rangers and then they're going to come to the arena.
Yeah, we're not with the magic.
The magic.
So lifting into the air. Yeah, you can stop the clip whenever it's not that impressive of a magic trick.
I'll say this. It's Rita. How does this play out?
So it takes Rita like is like behind the curtain and they're trying to act like they've like put her in there and she's now ascending somehow.
But like she there's like a minute or two where she's clearly just like crawling out a hole or something.
There's like it wasn't like an instantaneous thing where you see that trick sometimes.
But it is obviously the setup to some sort of a disappearing act trick.
And yeah, they were using those little things.
She like does she she comes out then she's replaced by a smaller.
Oh, yeah. So so yeah, when the clip keeps going.
Sorry, I cut it up, but she turns into like a small version and they put her in a little like box.
And yeah, that's one of the one of the many mean things they do to her in the show.
She comes back to it. She's also, by the way, she's got a purple outfit, which was not her normal outfit.
If I'm if I'm not mistaken, she usually had like a was it a gray or a brown outfit?
I think it was brown. Yeah, yeah.
It could have been purple and it was just so desaturated.
It's also possible the VHS footage was not kept up the finest.
I love going online, but I hate that big tech companies can see what I'm looking at.
I hate it so much. I wish I could like the companies on fire.
Which just so happens to be the power set of Sebastian Jackal,
Crystal Lloyd's character from UPN's Deadly Games.
Coming up on the second gate, we take a look at Sebastian Jackal, who he is, why he hates Dr. Gus Lloyd.
And I bet we'll have some laughs along the way.
So head to Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
That's oh geez.
P a t r e o n dot c o m slash p o d c a s t t h e r i d e.
This is not an Internet security product.
It's an episode about Sebastian Jackal,
Christopher Lloyd's character from UPN's Deadly Games.
Once again, that's Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
For all your Sebastian Jackal needs.
On the topic of Rita, can I ask for one of my clips?
And the clip is called Hey Rita.
I have this clip too, Scott, but you go ahead because I am very excited.
Wait, really? 100 percent.
I have. Well, say anything you want to say.
How did you come across Hey Rita?
OK, so we were talking about turtles and I was saying when I was watching this, I was like, man,
it would be fun if they had song like original songs.
And I was like, they don't have original songs in this too.
But I go, I wonder if. Yeah, here we go.
I wonder if the Power Rangers ever did have original songs.
So you look it up and there is a I'm sure as you discovered a full Power Rangers music album.
Some songs used on the show, some not written by this guy, Ron Wasserman,
who wrote the theme song to Power Rangers, also co-wrote X-Men theme.
This is a legendary guy, genius, hot in Cleveland theme.
Mummy's Alive theme. This is a guy who's done.
Look at his IMDB. It's very impressive.
So, yes, it seems like he believed that kids could.
I think like a lot of kids composers held back and were softer.
Yes. He was a guy saying, no, kids can handle metal.
They can handle ultra fast drums.
And that's that's what he brought into the theme song, which, by the way, he was brought into Saban told,
OK, we need it by tomorrow.
And it's got to have the word go in it.
Does he comes back the next morning? Go, go Power Rangers.
Wow. Yep. Yeah. They give him a very clear assignment.
Hey, tell you what, I'll give you two to goes for the price of one.
I've been obsessed with Hey Rita since high school because I found I found a I found a cassette at the ninety nine cents store of a Power Rangers album.
This seems silly. Most of it kind of drag. Who cares?
Yeah. But this song has something special.
And the challenge I issued to anyone who hasn't heard Hey Rita is to try to make out a single lyric of Hey Rita.
OK, so that'll be for Jason and Johnny to hear.
Yes. I know the lyrics already.
I don't remember this at all. OK, OK.
Hey Rita.
Rita.
All right. I caught girl.
Yeah.
I think I heard something about it.
It is a key to a.
Yes.
It looks like the lyrics are online.
Oh, wow. I mean, I just like is I because I've always thought I heard the word to keto perhaps tequila.
No, I don't think tequila is in there.
Would you like some tequila?
Yeah. Well, it's saying you want me to read it.
Yeah, I guess so.
OK, mystery. So here's the dig the seed and grow girl.
No, incorrect. Incorrect.
Dig the scenic road girl.
No sense.
And then this.
Although you know what? I don't think the lyrics, the people who wrote these down know exactly there because the next line they wrote, whack the something girl.
So they don't actually know either.
I do know that's whack the weed.
But then I don't know. I've always heard whack the weed won't grow girl.
What is that?
This is not officially produced by Ron Wasserman.
They're guessing as well.
I guess they're guessing. What's that?
That big litany of OK of tequila burrito.
Here's what this says.
This is saying and it might be guessing.
Hey Rita Senorita, the wickedest Chiquita.
Where did you come from Rita?
Hey Rita, treat a cheater.
Treat?
Is that a euphemism for kill?
Maybe.
If you see a cheater.
I'm not sure. What are you up to Rita?
Oh Rita, won't you be there?
Get off my lander, Rita?
In my head that's always been get off my lamborghita.
Like as if they needed a rhyme so bad that they had to tilt the name Lamborghini into lamborghita.
I think that's better than some of the actual lyrics Mike is reading.
Some of those are stretches and very dull phrases.
We should get Wasserman on here.
I would love to. Yeah. Let's get the official word from him.
There's a weird spoken word point later in the song too.
Do you have that? Do you want to pull up a separate clip?
I think well maybe I should.
Or we just describe it because there's the...
It's kind of like a bridge.
The Power Rangers. I thought about leaving that in too.
It's like the Power Rangers you could not defeat so Lord Zed he put on the heat.
He shrank you down, put you in a trash can.
And now you're floating around space yelling at him.
I'm so glad that...
That's more by the way the character at least.
Yeah that's more context to what actually happened.
It kind of happened in the show.
Or whacking weeds.
Wouldn't she whack and weesh? She's not doing gardening work.
She has bunnies to do that for her.
I'm so glad that I at 16 was as delighted by Hey Rita as you were finding it out just several days ago.
It's magic isn't it?
The rest I wouldn't recommend the album but that Hey Rita.
The go that...
UT La Tequila.
On that album is also that Green Rangers song which they did use in the show.
That's a good song.
I think you should find that album and listen to it Johnny.
I feel like there's a couple bangers on that album.
For some reason I totally...
It's a loop to Hey Rita. I probably fast forwarded it onto my cassette tape when I was little.
There's a couple things now that I appreciate more as an adult.
Sure.
It's a little bit of a smithery.
Wasserman should have been hired to write original songs for this show as well.
That would have made it the ultimate version of this.
You got in there...
Not to jump around but I feel like it's not a show necessarily.
We have to explain the plot in glorious detail.
There's that one song that is...
It feels original to this unless it was in the show.
It is a song...
I don't know if you have the clip of it.
It's a little bit craft-worky.
Like ding dong dong dong.
The only lyrics repeated in a round are...
Silly putty building silly monster.
Silly putty.
I like that song a lot.
That's not on the album I don't think.
Maybe it is.
I don't have the clip sadly.
This is one of the most impressive things in the show.
That song covers the space where the putties are all putting together a big clanky robot monster.
Which does not exist.
There's nothing there and then they put a bunch of cans together.
And then it is just walking around.
Somebody slips in there during the building process.
And then it gets chopped apart again by the rangers before you're right.
That's pretty cool.
I don't know exactly how they did that.
I saw that monster called the hollow monster.
That was an original character for the stage show.
And Lumentor the fire lion.
Johnny do you remember...
Was it Lumentor or Lumentor?
I think it's Lumentor.
I wasn't sure either because some people online say Lumentor.
I thought it was Lumentor so I don't even know what it is.
I thought it was Lumentor.
It sounds like Lumentor but I don't know if it's Lumentor.
I have a clip of that.
We can see what Zed is saying to make sure.
It sounds like there's no N in it when people say it.
But all the Power Rangers wiki has an M in it.
It does sound like medicine you take for high blood pressure or something.
Ask your doctor of Lumentor.
Lumentor.
But he's original.
Let's just get Lord Zed yelling real quick.
Clip 10 please.
So Zed will be yelling his name here.
He makes it sound so impressive that this is this new character.
I like Lumentor.
I like the look of him a lot.
I don't think he looks as scary as Goldar or Lord Zed.
Also, if I'm thinking back to my childhood, I was really upset that they would make Goldar a little bit of a buffoon.
Because initially he was...
Am I crazy here?
Initially he was so scary because he's the first monster they fight.
He's the first monster.
I was so freaked out by him.
He sort of falls into the...
What's the character?
Babu and...
Squat.
They were like comedic characters and he sort of fell into that.
So I wanted to return to the fearsome Goldar.
But anyway, here's the clip where Zed introduces and we'll see if we can figure out exactly if that N is there or not.
So Rita is now back out of a different magic trick box.
So mean!
No. No N.
No N.
That's Lumentor.
He's scary!
Isn't he magnificent?
A mere touch from him can turn him into this.
I mean, I guess he is scary.
But he's kind of cute.
He's cuter than the other characters.
So yeah, you can stop playing.
Do you think he's scary, Lumentor?
What do we think?
He's got an eye patch.
Yeah, that's cool.
He had to get in some kind of a scrap for that to happen.
No, he didn't.
He could have fallen over in his apartment.
You could see a poke in the corner of the...
...redemptive.
Lumentor is tripped on the rug.
No feng shui in Lumentor's apartment.
I think I like the flag of like
talking about how Lumentor can't handle water.
I think they handle that like immediately.
I think like my babu or squat brings up like,
Oh man, it's hot in here.
I'm thirsty. Get me some water.
And immediately he's like,
No water. I can't have water.
Like immediately.
Okay, so that's how that's gonna go.
We're gonna have all the kids chat more rain.
In like two minutes straight.
Really like a design flaw.
Because these characters were molded out of clay by...
Is it Finster as the character?
Who I was a big fan of.
He's got fun ears.
He never fights, which I always kind of wanted him to fight.
Is he like a monster, a sorcerer, a scientist?
What would you say he is?
Kind of a little bit of all of it.
He's a monster.
Not in the show though.
But like that's a design.
He's designing the characters out of clay.
He's sort of playing God, let's be honest.
He made great little clay monsters as well.
So much so, I was so believable that this could actually...
I could do the same as Finster.
I remember me and my mom went to like
pack of tans when I was little.
And I got clay. And my mom bought me a bunch of clay.
Not play dough, just straight up clay.
And I tried to like recreate monsters
from the show.
And put them in the microwave
to get them to come to life.
Obviously, spoiler alert,
they did not come to life.
And we had to buy a new microwave.
Wow.
So that was like your best thought.
The microwave was the place you thought, oh magic is made.
Because Finster doesn't put it in a microwave.
He just kind of...
Put it in a little conveyor belt oven.
So you just were like, you have to cook it.
They bake for a while. They're like babies.
They bake in there for a little bit.
And then they come out and they're done.
A monkey announces them.
It's also funny to think though
that your child brain was like,
what I'm going to do right now is unleash
a monster in the house.
I have sculpted a monster and I'm about to
unleash it in here. I guess you assumed...
To be fair, it wasn't a very good looking monster to be fair.
True. It might be a stick figure monster.
Or like a little arms, legs,
old face monster. I guess if you created
though, then you could be the one to like
tell the monster what to do. So I guess it maybe
wouldn't tear up the house necessarily.
You might not be creating a monster. You might be making...
I essentially did that now with like a human.
So basically I'm just living in real life now.
I have a baby to live my monster life.
You didn't make a monster. You made a new
best friend. Yeah. Yeah. That's true.
So yeah, Luma Tor
is original, again, original character here.
Who I like. Again, I don't know.
People are probably thinking I'm putting him down.
And I don't want to put Luma Tor down. I like him.
I just think... You expect when somebody's
created new for like it has to...
As with Ivan Ooze, it has to reset
the bar. Yes, Ivan Ooze reset
the bar, villain bar,
for me. And this one is like
this is fun. But this is... I would see
Luma Tor on like a
regular show. And I figure like they could
have gone... Rod Stewart's
guy could have gone bigger and forced them
to get a more impressive, scarier villain.
Were the aliens also
original too? Or were they on the show? I don't remember
this at all. Those first... Yeah. So the show opens
with these aliens kind of... Yeah.
Like exhuming or finding Lord Zed's
temple. I don't know what you'd say.
They're just fans. They're fans of Lord Zed.
They're UFO fans. They're like me.
Like I am. They want to observe him
and like discover how to be as
evil as him. Yeah. A bunch of Lord
Zed's stands have crossed a boundary.
They will not
leave him alone to give him his privacy.
I didn't see for sure, but I think they are
original. I'm not sure. I think so.
And then they kind of... I feel like they did nothing.
They don't pay at all. They don't pay anything to this show.
No. At all. Don't need to be there.
They're not time killing. Yeah, not even like a Greek
chorus or they don't even add any commentary
or they're not like Statler and
Waldorf. They don't do anything fun. Nope.
So, yeah.
Is it to explain... Is there like...
They have to do some plot mechanics
of why all of this is happening
in your town, which in your
case was Cleveland, but unnamed. They just said
your town. This town. Yes.
Instead of Angel
Grove, the typical home
of the town. Is that why a
UFO crash lands, which unleashes...
Again, I'm a little lost. I don't know. But
like typically it's all happening
because all these people hang out in
Angel Grove. Yeah. Angel Grove, a town that is mostly
like barren cliffs and large
open green fields.
That's 90% of Angel
Grove. If they built more housing developments
there'd be no room for anybody to fight.
Start building up the suburbs
and then these monsters have to leave.
There's some explanation
in one of them, and it might have been the press event. I can't
remember because it's all blur, but one of the
things I watched, they
throw in a line like, and our
plan is to bring the Power Rangers
here from Angel Grove.
So they've built in the idea that
they're not going to be in their home base or something.
We're luring them to your town
to... And then I said
in the first clip, capture them
two at a time and
put them in the cage and then the
other two will come and then...
But then I felt like 99% of the show took place
in Lord Zedd's temple
sort of thing. Yeah.
His big dirty cave.
His big nasty cave.
The reeking of Gherkin
pickles. Reeking of
Gherkins. And the audience needs to
chant, like, clean the cave.
I will not clean the cave.
I didn't...
Johnny, you were saying you did not...
You were so scared of being pulled on stage.
I feel like my childhood anxiety
was raised whenever they're like,
help us chant, we need your
help. And I was like, I don't want this
responsibility. I just want to watch the show.
Watching the YouTube clip though, kids
were fully invested.
And it looked like none of the kids had adults either.
It looked like watching the YouTube clip, there were just
children everywhere. I never saw
maybe I saw one adult.
Just lines of kids just going crazy
and losing their minds. And I was never
like, I was never like, I would maybe be like,
more rain, more rain, more rain.
Or like, don't look at me, more rain.
I also didn't want...
I was horrified.
I'd be chanting like,
we need rain or something like that. And Lord Zedd
would be like, hey, you, I see you chanting
down there. I'm going to come and kill you.
So I didn't want to be
caught. And this is like, this
went not just for Power Rangers Live,
but like every stage show I saw.
Maybe not Sesame Street Live,
because I got like a Big Bird feather
that I still have to this day that I'm very
proud of. But like
I saw Sinbad on stage and I was
like, I don't want Sinbad to call me out.
I saw David Copperfield. I was like, I don't want
to be a part of a trick. Double Dare lies.
I was like, I don't want to do this.
It's too much responsibility.
I was in the front row of Monday Night Raw.
And I was afraid that Kane
was going to... There's like a
very famous clip of
me, like a Monday Night Raw
from like 1998 or 1997.
And Kane is like ringing the bell
10 times because he killed The Undertaker.
And he goes and he grabs the
Timekeeper and he beats him up.
And he sees like a fan standing in the front row
and he grabs him and he pulls him over the guardrail
and starts beating him up. And the camera like pans
over and you just see little
chubby Johnny Organo like sitting there in the front row
like, like
horrified that Kane is going to come over
and murder me.
That's amazing. I mean, if
you had a camera in my childhood home, I would have also
had the same reaction just watching the
TV for some of the demon stuff,
some of the satanic stuff. You know what's funny
is I think you were talking to three guys who probably
had a similar feeling in the audience of all these
shows. I'm remembering now,
funny enough, the first time I had that in my
adult... One of the first times I had this in my adult years
is you used to wrestle in Recita and PWG,
which I would go to. And this,
the first time I ever went, the action
would spill out because it was a very small building.
And I was having the same
sort of panic initially. Eventually,
you get used to just like standing up and moving
when people are fighting. But I
remember going, oh, like I'm part of this.
And I didn't realize I was
part of this. So
the old feelings of it came back.
Especially back in Recita, that was like the Wild
Wild West where there is no guardrails and everyone's
as close to the ring as you possibly get.
So I don't know how many times there'd be
random celebrities just sitting in the crowd
where you do like a dive and you land on
like little Dwight
from the office.
It'd be wild.
Yes, but it was that same thing
of like, oh, we're all part... We're actually, because this building
was so small, we're all part of the show.
So we all have to move. And we're
all like anything can happen at this point.
I say all the time too that those shows
I used to do in Recita probably took
years off, not just my career, but my life.
Given how hot that
building used to be. Yes, yes.
It was like 99 degrees.
And imagine having to wrestle for like 30 minutes
in front of just the craziest heat you could imagine.
That was wild times.
Very, very wild times.
We all have been to
Recita and it was never
a nice climate in there.
It was not...
It was never like, oh, it feels
great in here in this Legion Hall.
Wow. But
Rest In Peace Legion Hall has been torn down.
But yeah, yeah, this
is still... I do
feel like if you're in front row anywhere, I'm like,
OK, I don't need to...
No, thank you. Yeah, right.
I'm still that way now as an adult.
And I do stuff
on stage and I do stuff on television.
But I'm still like, if I'm not in my
element, I'm like, oh, please
don't pick on me. Like if I went to like Turtle Talk
or Crush, I'm like,
please don't pick on me.
Or running like Star Tours. I'm like, I don't want to...
Please don't put me on the screen.
I don't want to be seen, please. You know, real quick,
I'm remembering now when Candice was on,
she said something about the ride
Living With the Land. Oh, boy.
And she expressed that maybe this was not your
favorite ride. Oh.
Me and Candice have very
not similar
tastes when it comes to classic Disney attractions.
Right.
I have very strong opinions. I think
I share the same opinions as Matt Cardona
on a lot of... We should
plus him up. Oh, sure.
He's very brutal. Just like out, out.
That one's out. Yeah. Well,
look, I don't want to get you in any trouble, but
I wouldn't mind you taking a little bit of heat
off of me because I think there's some listeners I never
got back after I said I didn't like
Living With the Land. Scott is the most anti-Ridiculous
with the land, yes. And there were listeners who were very
upset with him. Oh, still.
I still see it. It dogs me
to this day. I'm like, I'm a heel of
Podcast the Ride because I was like,
I don't know. I just, I don't think seeing the
plants is that interesting.
Candice is on me all the time because, number one,
like Hall of Presidents, like
not, not... Mr. Lincoln,
like I'm out. Like any of the, any of the,
any things where I have to learn
while I'm doing it. Yeah. Like any
things where I'm like, I got to learn about this,
I am 100% not
invested in. American Adventure.
My wife just really snapped on American,
just like how many more people
are we meeting today?
How many more historical figures?
You were just like, wait
one minute. Will Rogers about to show
up and he's going to make you laugh. He's
got a lasso. He's got a lasso.
You have to, you got to
say what you think about living with a lamp. You got to
help me out here. I have an ally
finally. I mean,
get rid of it.
Like,
I'm not one of those like
attraction people where I'm
like, we got to preserve the
aura. I'm like, no, like add an overlay
to it. Add some, like plus it up. Add
like something I care about to the attraction.
Again, it's a hot take on a lot
of things. But I'm very much
so, A, we need to
update things as they go. Like,
I'm sure the new Guardians ride is going to be my new favorite ride.
Like, Rise of Resistance is my top ride.
Like, I'm very much so a new technology
person as opposed to a
historical one. New exciting thing shows up when you enjoy it.
Wait, let me say this. I've, cause when
it comes up, all I'm saying is there was a point
in time where that ride had a song
and somebody in the boat talked to you.
And now these things are gone and we're like,
yes, good. Keep there being no
song in it. That's my point.
If nothing else, put the song
back. Like, I don't understand why
it has to be preserved in a
decaying state, in a like
lesser state than it was.
That's all I'm saying, folks. This is all
I'm trying to say. Scott, not here.
The lack of guide is definitely a
cost cutting measure, for sure.
So we shouldn't be celebrating that.
I love that there's no guide anymore.
Me and
Candice get into arguments all the time. Not arguments.
But he did discussions all the time.
I have a very strong
opinion on the It's a Great Big
Beautiful Tomorrow ride.
Oh, here we go. What do you got?
I mean, I, so
I say this
as someone who experienced
the ride, maybe in a way
it shouldn't have been experienced.
Everyone knows, obviously, it
circles around and things like that.
And they go to each scene and it takes
about five minutes per era
that we're in. So at one point,
me and Candice rode this ride. And this might be
before I hated this ride. And maybe
I say this is the catalyst.
This is my Joker story for why I
don't like this ride.
So we get
about 15 minutes in. And Candice
remembers this experience way differently than I do.
But we get about 15 minutes in.
We watch like, because it's
about a 20 minute ride, we get to
the third act of
this scene, whatever era
that is in the 40s, maybe
could be the 40s, wherever it is at this point.
So it plays.
It starts to turn to go to like
the last one, but it stops
and the ride freezes
because maybe someone stood up. We're not
sure about this. And then it goes back
and it goes back and it goes back
and the ride starts over all over
again. So you got to sit there for another
15 minutes and it just happens
again. You're gonna sit there like
we got to go do this thing all over again.
So they restart the ride. So we're about
like, I'd say 35 minutes in
at this point of the same thing
over and over again. And I'm like, I'm
done.
I'm never coming back on this ride.
It's a great big over 35 minutes.
Every time.
You're describing Jason's dream.
Progress isn't always smooth,
folks.
And hey, Johnny, you're a new father.
You're gonna be thanking your lucky
stars for that ride. Nice cool
20, 25 minute nap.
So, so it's funny you mentioned that
because, oh,
she just came.
Candace is here. Candace came in.
The dog's losing his mind
now. It's funny you mentioned that
because the very first ride
we took our son Quill on
was the Wheel of Progress.
Carousel Progress.
Carousel Progress, whatever the heck it is. I don't want to even
call it by its right name because I don't have that much respect for it.
I like it. Wheel. I'm gonna start calling it that pretty hard.
This is basically a wheel because it felt like it kept going over and over again.
Sure.
So we took him on the Carousel of Progress.
And I trade great pride in
the fact that being his
father, he started losing his mind
about 15 minutes in.
And he starts crying.
And Candace is trying to feed him.
But he starts crying and crying and crying.
And I'm sitting there very proud.
And afterwards I'm like, see? See?
He didn't like it.
He didn't like it. That was his first ride.
He did not like it at all.
It could not hold a less than one year old's attention for more than 15 minutes.
Almost everything holds a one year old for 15 minutes.
And then he went on Space Mountain and he loved it.
You held him up like Rafiki the whole way.
Yeah, of course.
What is the oldest, is there any old kind of ride that you do like?
Haunted Mansion, obviously, right?
Yeah, of course. Haunted Mansion, love Haunted Mansion.
Haunted Mansion, like Space Mountain, OG Space Mountain, still love that.
But you know what, these like boring Walt things.
Do you like any boring Walt things?
Like what? Like what do you classify as boring?
Train? Like everything we've listed.
The train. Do you like the train?
No, I mean, it's fine. It's just not.
So like we're obviously more, we go to Disney World more than we go to Disneyland.
Even though it might be a hot take that I prefer.
I do prefer Disneyland to Disney World.
I don't know if that's a hot take or not.
We like that take. We agree with the take.
I'm sure you guys, I just feel like it's easier to do everything in Disneyland in one day than it is in Disney World,
because there's just so much in Disney World and like there's so many different parks and things like that.
And we got married there, so that's a whole other thing that I kind of I feel like I need to say that because if I don't I'll be in trouble.
You got married there.
Yeah, yeah, no, that's not so controversial.
What about Epcot movie, like 360 movies?
You ever do the 360 movies?
Do you learn about Canada with Martin Short?
No, I don't think I've ever done that.
For a good reason.
Maybe next time though.
Maybe, you never know.
Like me and Candace, I don't know if she told you when she was on the podcast, but we got a chance to go to Walt's actual office when we were in California.
So we went and saw his actual office and Candace started crying.
So she obviously has a much deeper connection to Walt and all the history that I do being from California and Disneyland and things like that.
But I didn't start being, I wasn't a Disney person until I met Candace as well, because being from Cleveland, Ohio, all we had was like Jogga Lake and Sea World and Power Rangers Live.
So I didn't do any Disney trips when I was younger.
If you were in the office of Ron Wasserman, writer of the theme song, you would shed a tear there.
He wrote Hey Rita here.
The wickedest senorita.
What else can we hit about the show?
You got anything fun in the clip realm?
I have a clip.
Oh yeah, go for it.
This is a moment later in the show.
Just to set it up, Alpha 5 has got the kids to chant to help the Power Rangers.
And I think the big thing about this clip is it kind of shows the limitations of using some of the Power Rangers material.
Brett, do you have that?
Huge arena.
Yeah.
Okay, so this is a shot of a field.
Yeah, the Power Rangers are running towards camera.
So far.
Now we can kind of see them.
Just now.
Come on guys, hustle.
And then they burst through the screen.
That's cool.
That gets a big response from the crowd.
Okay, you can stop it.
But just that footage of them running from so far away.
Oh my god.
Like okay, oh man, a lot can happen when we're waiting for them to show up.
That clip also illustrated a thing that I like.
I just want to translate to the listener.
But I like the way, the physicality they bring to the fighting, they also bring just to the dialogue.
Because what the White Ranger was saying, they're like, alright guys, we need a plan.
Because Lord Zed is on the attack and we are going to be in trouble.
It's almost gesticulated.
It's all like, how many movements can I do on every syllable?
It's all pre-recorded audio.
So they're like, yeah, they're gesticulating to go along with the pre-recorded audio.
They don't have to be making the sounds from their lungs so they can go ape shit with all that word punching.
Yeah, but that was towards the end of the show.
Very funny moments towards the end of the show where they summon all their zords to fight Lumetor.
Okay, good. Yeah, you're going to get into this.
And then they are using the stock footage of the zords projected on a pretty standard like 4x3 screen.
And Lumetor, there's no on stage zords.
Lumetor just fights next to footage.
Footage of the giant creature.
It does give them a chance to use the kind of regularly used footage of the zords exploding and the Power Rangers getting tossed out of them,
which always made me really anxious as a kid as well.
Yes. Do we have the clip of that or no?
I don't have the clip. Sorry.
I have a clip of the finale in which you do get some massive action, which might be worth it.
What is that? I think I call that more light.
You were describing. This is the only part.
This is the only part that I remember.
Okay, this is the only part that I remember actually being there live because I remember having one of the little reflective light things.
And I remember the big inflatable Lord Zed for some reason.
That's the only thing I remember.
Maybe because I was horrified that he was going to like come out and kill me.
And I didn't want him to see that I had this reflector thing that was murdering him.
Specifically the other children all kind of break.
I was a reasonably smart kid, but not smart enough to know it behooves companies to not murder the audience to make money.
They should keep the audience alive to keep doing shows and making money.
Maybe I thought because I was dressed like the White Ranger, he would get confused.
That like I was the White Ranger.
Yeah, we were like, I was probably the worst kind of.
Yeah, yeah, I wasn't a civilian.
I was a part of it.
You had enlisted.
I mean, I do have the official Power Ranger.
I am an official Power Ranger.
I like a certificate that says I'm official young Power Ranger that I signed up for.
I think I was part of the fan club and I got an official certificate that says I was a young Power Ranger.
So yeah, I did officially enlist.
I don't know what I signed up for, but they deputize young children to also be in the Power Rangers.
Yeah, yeah.
Target on your back.
There's a funny we can.
We actually I do have a clip.
We can play it after this.
There's it is so funny because so much of it is like, you know, we're teaching martial arts.
There was a Tommy video that I had that where Tommy taught children how to do martial arts.
Oh, there's about 10 minutes of like, do not do this.
Do not fight children at school.
Do not do that.
It's only for for discipline.
That's what we're doing.
If you know how you watch that show every week where people beat the shit out of each other.
No, do not do that fun stuff.
This is just to learn the art of this.
Yeah.
When I was a kid, I actually had my parents sign me up for a karate class only so I could get the geek.
I never went to a karate class.
I only wanted the outfit.
So they decided to get the outfit so I can be at home.
And I watched the Tommy instructional video.
So that's how I taught myself karate is I didn't go to any of the real the real classes.
I wanted to learn from Jason David Frank and stay.
Of course.
Yeah. Yeah.
Power Rangers definitely led to an increase in karate class enrollment.
But yes, it did also lead to recesses of like, what do you guys want to do this recess?
Do you want to fight like Power Rangers?
Yeah, let's do it.
And just like the wimpiest little kick said, like the moment we saw authority, it's like scram.
Amps gray.
I know a Power Ranger fan if like you see someone throw a kick and go, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like they all always had the sound effects.
Right.
And any kicks they threw that accompanied it.
Yes.
Oh, that's how you know.
That's that's Ranger style turtle style.
Would you learn?
That's what you learn.
You say maybe you throw a cowabunga in there, but you aren't accompanying.
You know what it led to for me was this is some of my other negative Power Rangers Association was one time.
Only once I was like walking up in the hills by this park and then some kids came up to me, younger kids than me, little.
Oh, wow.
I'm wearing sunglasses, which was enough for them to say, hey, you're Lord Zed.
And I was and I said defensively, no, I'm not.
And they said, yeah, you're him.
And I was like, no.
And I ran away from the littler children.
Oh, wow.
There was no threat for all I knew.
They could have liked that I was Lord Zed.
There was no violence.
They didn't start kicking me.
There weren't little kicks, little kicks in my direction.
But somehow that was scarring enough for me to remember still.
And that held and this held me back from being able to truly embrace what's on the screen right now.
Wow.
That's sad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry.
That's what I want.
A dark memory being told.
Sunglasses made you Lord Zed.
I mean, he's got sort of like what kind of sunglasses were they?
Were they like the old like the the weird square ones?
Knowing me and my lack of style ever, they were probably abnormally large and aviator like for a little child.
So were they red and then they had like a metal mask under it?
Also, was that the sunglasses you were wearing?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kind of spike coming up.
Yes, there was all those industrial gnarled metal that covered my mouth.
And it was that time in puberty when your muscles were exposed.
Oh, yeah, where my where my the flesh, my skin got completely translucent and you could see everything inside me.
That's probably why.
Now, so that was not a good Zed memory for me.
This is a new Zed memory that I like, because for the listener, what we're looking at is final.
They do in a Rod Stewart esque display of rock and roll spectacle.
They create a big Lord Zed.
And how do they do it?
By making a big inflatable figure done kind of like King Kong and initially was done at Universal Studios where it's kind of like torso up.
So that saves a little bit.
They don't have to make all those legs.
So it's just kind of chest up and they puppeteer him kind of, I assume by it's probably just like a dozen guys in black clothes back there just like shaking them around wildly.
And it is cool.
And this involves the kid participation in what Johnny said he recalls strongly from from being there.
So here's this.
This is your kid.
Yeah, yeah.
Little Bobby Buttnik.
Pyro.
Yes.
Tommy Tommy's little.
Sabo?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
More light, more light, more light, more light, more light, more light.
How good does that thing look?
I do love that effect.
It's really cool.
And then that, you know, obviously he gets defeated, which is just him inflating.
They just let the air out and then he just flops down onto the stage and kind of ignore.
Hey, kids, don't worry about all that loose skin.
Yes.
The square, the vast square footage of loose skin kicking around the stage.
That does illustrate, though, one of the things I didn't like as a kid was like, why does only Tommy has have his weapon?
Like he has a sword.
Scott, shortly into the first season, all the Power Rangers each got a different weapon.
And then when they were really in a pinch, they would combine their weapons to make a gun, which is kind of weird to say.
Like the guy who tried to attack Dave Chappelle.
Yeah.
A real knife and fake gun combined.
So that was a big deal for me as a kid.
And the toy makers were kind of psyched, too, because, yeah, eventually the next line of action figures had the weapons and the blasters.
They also had blasters that kind of became nightsticks and then definitely became switch blades.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
I had one of those.
If you had the gun, yeah, the regular gun from the first seat, would you like open it and it would turn into a blade?
Yes.
Yeah.
What do you got on the front?
I'm curious about it.
Do you have a clip from this martial arts?
Oh, I do. Yes.
From the Jason Davis.
Yes.
Oh, I love it.
I do have a clip.
Let me look real quick.
Johnny, you did that.
So you had this tape.
This was your education in this area.
Yes.
This is what prepared me for professional wrestling, I think.
I didn't actually go training at a school for pro wrestling.
I just did this.
This is where I developed my skills from.
I hope this doesn't have the answers to any of your weaknesses.
Does this give your opponents potential?
It might.
At the Z spot?
You don't have a Z spot, do you?
It's hidden, though.
It's harder to find.
It's not just right.
Yeah, I'm not going to tell you where it is.
It's not advertised.
Clip seven.
This is when Tommy's giving some sort of instruction.
He's telling you what not to do with his martial arts training.
Yeah.
So, yeah, whenever you're ready.
And it's a long video.
It's like an hour long.
Oh, yeah.
And here it is.
All of it.
Yep.
Unless you can control your mind.
Once you do this, your body will fall along.
Okay.
If you know what I'm talking about.
I know exactly what Tommy's talking about.
Alpha, please don't interrupt.
Sorry, Zordon.
Mean to Alpha for no reason.
Now, before we get started, here's a few rules about martial arts.
Have a couple drinks.
Take some tequila shots.
First, remember to practice martial arts either at home in a large open area.
Okay.
Away from lamps, furniture, you know, the stuff that could break or hurt you.
Or in a karate school like this one.
And always make sure there's an adult there when you're practicing.
Either your sense of your mom or dad.
So I'll bring up the point I'm making.
One second.
You especially don't want to practice martial arts.
Dragon sword.
No.
Hey, guys, you know better than that.
Wow, it's the Green Ranger.
Why don't you guys tell us why you shouldn't practice martial arts at school?
We don't know.
We wanted to.
Right.
Someone could definitely get hurt.
What else?
And you can get in trouble.
So make sure you two guys remember that.
Okay.
All right.
Well.
So here's what's confusing about this clip if you know the show at all.
He says don't do this at school.
He makes it very clear.
Do it in a karate space or a gym or whatever.
That's the set of the school that he's in from Power Rangers.
Yeah.
So he's pretending he's gaslighting a bunch of kids saying this is not the school you see on the TV every week.
I just put a bunch of mats down in the cafeteria.
But this is a karate school, not school.
Don't do.
Yeah.
Don't fight in school.
I think my first question at the Green Ranger appeared in front of me would have been, hey, can I see your giant flute knife?
I really want to take a look at that flute slash knife.
It is a key as a flute.
He is a it's like an ocarina knife.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
So we like pun plays it like this.
Do you have that Johnny?
Do you have that toy?
Yeah, I don't want I don't want to flex or anything.
But I have a 24 karat gold version of it.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Can you play it?
Yeah.
Is it playable?
No, you're in shorts.
OK, hold on.
This is a San Diego Comic Con.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
It's dusty.
It has a bit of a different San Diego Comic Con.
I saw it on a documentary and I was like, wait a minute.
They made a 24 karat gold dragon dagger and got it to prove me for Christmas.
From from eBay.
He's like, I brought up like the you can get anything anymore.
I mean, but yeah, so this is a limited edition 24 karat gold.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
I know.
Right.
Clap for that.
That's awesome.
I know.
But it's not play.
Can you play it?
I think so.
Yeah.
It's a you can do a concert with this.
Hold on.
This is unbelievable.
Oh, hold on.
Demonstration.
I'm going to hold down the so it's like you're blowing on it.
New theme song.
Oh, is it working?
Hold on.
Oh, sorry to put you on the spot.
Here we go.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, it's a song.
OK.
The famous that's how you that's the calling the dragons.
Yeah.
A little tune.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
That's awesome.
I think like you.
I think it's a little bit of a.
Yeah.
That's awesome.
I think like you do things.
Sure.
It's also good for home defense.
It is great.
Yeah.
Twenty four karat gold Dragon Dagger exists.
That's wild.
Damn.
That's awesome.
That's an item.
I'm impressed by that.
And I didn't even grow up with this show.
I know.
Did you have a would you have a favorite of all the toys back there?
Power Rangers or not or anything else?
So like I think like I said, the 24 karat gold Dragon Dagger is probably my biggest
flex.
Yeah.
You got to late.
You got to throw a softball up for me.
Sure.
I didn't realize.
I am such a big Spider-Man the animated series fan.
So I have like the complete set collection of all the Spider-Man the animated series
toys like the original or the new retro ones.
The original.
Yeah.
The new retros as well.
But the original like the OG.
Oh, yeah.
I see it there.
Yeah.
All up here.
And like I said, like I'll pan the camera up.
I have like the Daily Bugle play set.
I have the Tri-Spider Slayer.
And all those I didn't see all those helmet.
Those those Ranger helmets.
There's literally a Lord Zed helmet right there.
It is.
Yeah.
Wow.
And are they terrifying?
I'm not asking you to do this, but are they wearable?
You want to you want to see them?
Hmm.
Kind of.
It's up to you.
Yeah, I can grab them.
If it's easy.
Only if it's easy.
Okay.
If it's easy.
Yes, I do want to.
Now, look, it's not just him because I just went to a birthday party that you guys were
at and the there was a present at the birthday party.
Wait, he's got.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Look at it.
It's beautiful helmet.
It just goes over my head.
Yeah.
It has like a voice modulator as well to where you can talk like Lord Zed.
Oh, wow.
So why don't we do the whole episode that way?
I know I should just wore this the whole podcast and talk like Lord Zed.
If you were just popped up like that at the beginning.
I mean, we've all been zooming and in Google hang outing for years now, but that would have
been the most terrifying thing of this entire pandemic run.
Like Lord said, is join the chat.
Happy birthday.
It is true.
Happy birthday over Zoom.
I figured this is the first time we met.
So I probably ease into the Lord said showing up.
That's sure.
Next time.
Art Attack.
The next time I do the podcast, Lord said Lord said reviewing living with the land.
Oh, that'd have been boring ride.
No scientists.
I couldn't even find the scientists.
They were supposed to be in the lab.
What about cast members?
Why don't they give the tour anymore?
These puny hydroponics do not impress me.
Yeah.
So that'll be a good thing to look forward to.
What else should we hit about this about this live show?
Do you have it?
Do you have clips?
Is there anything or Johnny, do you have any memories of this that we that we have missed?
Is there something part of the spec?
We hit the magic.
We hit the recordings of clips of Power Rangers running very slowly through a meadow.
What what any other memories of this this fun childhood event?
I'm trying to think now.
So like I said, like the the I think it's kind of a backtracking a bit.
But one of the biggest letdowns to me was they did this big introduction like the the
Zords are going to be coming.
So they do like, oh, we're going to go to get the Zords.
And then like we talked about, like the Zords are just on the screen the whole time.
Like they couldn't spring production for just to have like one Zord show up and just kind
of roll out. They have a big hollow monster, a big inflatable Lord Zed.
They couldn't have a big inflatable Megazord or anything like that.
But I mean, that was my biggest letdown.
They had two of the actual people not showing up.
But sure, they have. Yeah, they had two inflatables maybe at the end, because I get
you want to save that for the big the big finale.
But yeah, then the Megazord came out and attacked.
What is it called? I'm going to be so embarrassed.
What is it called when the Megazord and the Dragonzord combine?
Is there a name for it?
Oh, I'm trying to remember now.
So ultra dragon Megazord, Megadragonzord or something maybe.
Oh, it might be Megadragonzord.
There was different incarnations of it because they like change the names.
Yeah, it's the White Tiger.
White Tigerzord. Yeah, it's the White Tigerzord in this instance.
And then it becomes one of my I had that too.
I had that toy, too.
Yeah. But then his next one, he gets is a giant falcon that the tips of the wings
are missiles.
So like the falcon would like fold its wings and then it would just launch
missiles like I thought that was the coolest thing as a kid.
That is good. Wow.
I can't be mad. I wrote this down.
I don't know about you guys, but the putties to me.
So watching watching it back, it really felt like the putties
were going into business for themselves.
Like at one point, at one point, the putties are just like doing like dances.
Yeah. Yeah.
I had a little they kind of had a little bit of tumble monkey to them from Lion King.
Like they kind of had a little bit like they do one of the most amazing things
I've ever seen as well, where they were all sitting in like a row
and they turn over where they're all on top of each other.
But also thinking back, like the putties are like doing this
very intricate dance number.
They're like going into the crowd and like high five and kids
and like being genuinely pretty cool. Yeah.
These children and then like the children just still want to see them get killed.
Like, I'm very surprised the kids didn't kind of turn their backs
on the Power Rangers.
And the putties are so so much more relatable for me now.
And they're like coming out and talking to us like they're right there.
They're like one of us.
The Power Rangers are celebrities up on a pedestal. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Yes. They were putting the revving fun with the kids. Yes.
And it does seem odd.
It feels like, yeah, they were not maybe supposed to do that, but like they don't.
They didn't want to be mean to kids.
They wanted the kids to like they were desperate for the kids affection, maybe.
So they were like, yeah, goofing around more like I wonder if there was like
an instance where like when the show first started, the putties were too scary.
Yeah. The kids were too like, oh, we don't like these putties.
We're like, we got to make this way more silly than it need to be.
That's why they added the magic and they added
the weird beat, the the uncomfortableness with Rita.
But sure. Yeah. Yeah, that makes sense.
But yeah, it would have been funny if the kids like silently protested the Rangers
and they turn their back to the Rangers during the middle of the show
to say, we don't care for what you're doing.
No more light. No.
It was also interesting to me that like they took.
So they made a spoiler alert for anyone that's going to watch this on YouTube.
They took the yellow and black ranger
and kind of eliminated them for like a good portion of the show. Yes.
It like you came to see these two and they got turned into a monkey and a bird.
And you don't get to see them get their full action on until the very end.
And they have this like long dialogue and pre-recorded video of like, oh, man,
sucks, we're birds now.
What are we going to do?
Also create some fun Zordon stuff of him saying bad news.
The black ranger, the yellow ranger birds now.
I like his I like talking like Zordon.
I feel like Zordon is kind of like you do Zordon.
It's not just that you go deep.
It's that it's kind of like a Kermit the Frog, but pitched down.
It's sort of a very easily thing to it.
Hi, ho. He's also so on here.
He's also sad. He also sounds very sad.
He said, Saki, yeah, I didn't.
They didn't take me on tour. They wouldn't spring for me.
There should be too many writers. I got greedy.
There should be a toy like Brian Krantz and didn't do that at all.
No, I Krantz. It was just straight up Brian Krantz.
He wanted gravitas.
There should be a toy.
Yellow Ranger is a Zordon toy where you put your head in a tube
and then it gives you Zordon voice.
That's good. Yeah, good.
It makes you sad, too.
It makes you sad.
Depressive agent.
There's a depression gas.
I was having a good day today.
And no, I'm not. Oh, jeez.
People don't know what it's like to live in a tube.
Not that easy being in a tube.
So you're a Zordon fan, maybe first and foremost.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I like Krantz and one.
And yeah, yeah, that's the only voice that I embrace.
It's the opposite of an I.
So so your ooze Zordon, those are your top two guys.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Oh, yes, I have a good I have an answer for who are my Power Rangers guy.
For sure. It is Zordon and an ooze, which I was saying we went to a birthday party
where our friend Andrew and the party favor was was a playing card.
It was like a fun pack of playing cards that he hadn't opened.
And so you didn't know what was going to be inside.
And I feel like I hit the jackpot because not only did I get a pack of playing cards
from Power Rangers, the movie specifically, as opposed to the show,
which were also in the pack.
So I don't know what you guys got.
But my I was just opening it like, please, ooze, please, give me Ivan
ooze, a character we did an episode about on the Patreon who I didn't care about
or had seen before until we did that.
One of my favorite things we found and not one, but two oozes.
Look at that. It's no, you know, it's no like I have a new rookie cards.
Yeah, yeah. It was when he was in his prime.
He was never better than in ninety five, including the one that Jason,
you for Mark Town, as soon as I said it, this is really the this is the prime card.
Who is on first?
Oh, wow.
Who's on first?
I appreciate that.
Is yeah, say classic routine, right?
Love these cards. Thank you, Andrew.
Yeah, well, what have we I mean, we were coming to a close.
This thing seems like I think I would have enjoyed it if I went.
Yeah.
The guys who put it together were feeling pretty high on it.
I have one more quote from Rock and Roll and for sorry, Ricky Farr.
He says this.
I can't tell you who, but I've already been asked by a major artist,
a household name, if I can incorporate into his next show some of the kind of magic
and illusions that we're representing with the Power Rangers live on tour.
Wow. Who do we think it is? Who is it? Who do we think that is?
OK, I know that he as I said, Rod Stewart, his name checked a lot.
But the other one I saw a bunch that this guy represented apparently was Morrissey.
Wow.
Usually he's taken maybe he gets a Morrissey call on one phone, hangs up,
takes a Power Rangers call, so I and I'm no Morrissey.
I don't have him memorized whatsoever.
But does anyone recall Morrissey having a bunch of magic
that one of Morrissey's enemies was shrunk and put into a cage way above?
Inflatable version of himself.
I don't remember that.
Mega Morrissey, he's in his final form.
He made a giant inflatable guy wearing a shirt that said like the meatpacking
industry, you know, and maybe all right.
Oh, yeah, that yes.
More veganism, more vegan.
Look up Morrissey inflatable.
Let's see.
You know, just anybody I guess out there think about it.
If you saw something in 96, 97 or so where there was a big inflatable guy,
a bunch of magic tricks, this could this seems like an area
where the Power Rangers might have had some lasting influence and understandably.
Because what kind of what concert wouldn't be made better by a giant inflatable.
There was even discussion after that of this is really weird.
OK, what about further possibilities of morphine rock cross pollination?
Might we someday see an arena spectacular in which Lord Zed, weary of battling
the unflagging Power Rangers, turns his nefarious attentions instead to somebody
like Trent Reznor? Whoa.
What? And then the guy responds well with a chuckle.
Nine Inch Nails is a client of mine,
and I'm afraid poor Lord Zed wouldn't stand a chance against Trent.
But I think he'd stand a pretty fair chance against Pink Floyd's pig.
So we're imagine I love like this is an article in the L.A. Times where an adult
is imagining scenarios where Lord Zed fights Trent Reznor and the Pink Floyd pig.
That's awesome, by the way. Yeah.
What a life. Rock and roll adversary Ricky Fargo.
Lord Zed being like, I hurt myself today
to see.
He got the Trent's got the sole job, not me.
Damn it. I wanted that Oscar.
Gosh, well, there's still I mean, there's still possibility of Zed.
Maybe if Reznor scores a Zed movie like a Zed origin movie.
Oh, yes.
Wait, why are we breaking them off into the first one?
Not do well enough. Yeah, I want spin offs.
I want. Yeah, Zed solo solo, obviously canceled the second remake, right?
Then they were going to do a sequel to the pirate.
Yeah, I think so. Yeah.
I think they canceled it.
I don't think it did super young.
I want young Zed.
Young Zed is like a show on NBC.
Yes, he's like a little boy right over young rock.
He's a little guy shows up and he's a little boy, but his muscles are potent.
You can see his muscles.
And that's it played by Jenny Gargano.
Oh, man. Yeah.
Who could it be?
Oh, wait, I was saying you were young.
Oh, I don't want that.
I don't want that responsibility to play young Zed.
I can't bring that. That's like Hamlet.
That's like Hamlet. We got the helmet already.
I do have the helmet.
If that's the only requirement, then yes, I can play young Zed.
All right.
Well, here's owning the Hasbro helmet.
I got it. I got it in the bank.
Well, hopefully at least Power Ranger Live people come to you after this.
After I gave them the idea that you should stop wrestling and become
a full time Power Ranger live performer. I'd love to.
I'd love to.
So people out there do it. Do it.
Yeah. Any of the Power Ranger live people out there that wants to see me on stage
as the Green Ranger or White Ranger this instance, I'm more than down.
Yeah. I'm prepared. I'm fully prepared. I'm trained.
Yes. You are.
I have a certificate to prove it.
You have a great reel. Yeah.
And that's good because the later seasons of Power Rangers,
they're getting slammed into concrete a lot more often.
Is that true? No one's.
Oh, that could be good.
More practical.
Yeah, it is practical effects.
I haven't watched it.
Oh, God. Jason David Frank came back for this episode.
He got German suplex on the conference.
He's a tough guy. Jason David Frank and Austin St.
John, right? Yeah.
Austin St. John, they came back a lot. They did.
They are like recently recently.
Yeah, I think so. Yeah. They're in the family.
Yeah. So anyway, Jason David Frank, in my in my memory,
it was like the number one guy of my childhood.
Like no one touched Jason David Frank.
I saw Michaels.
It's like a one two of Jason David Frank and Shawn Michaels to me.
Sure. Like my my role models growing up.
Yeah, I can see that.
Yeah. Tommy was very cool.
He was so cool.
And he like Kimberly liked him.
He did. Wow.
So much so that I didn't even have a favorite Power Ranger until Tommy showed up.
I like I like held my reservations.
I was like, I don't know. I'm not feeling anyone yet on this team.
And then Tommy showed up and I was like, there's my guy.
There's my guy right there.
Everyone thought that way.
Yeah. Now that I'm thinking about it,
I am unlocking some sort of memory where I was like, then maybe Kimberly would like me
if I was as cool as Tommy.
I think I did like I do think I liked Kimberly.
I do think so. So. Yeah.
Well, who wouldn't? Yeah.
Come on. Well, I think you served as a
white ranger upping the stakes and the quality of this episode.
Jenny Gargano, you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks so much for joining us from afar and via video.
This is a blast. Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
You can find me on Twitch at Twitch TV slash the Johnny Wrestling.
You can find me on YouTube at Johnny Gargano, Twitter, Johnny Gargano, Instagram,
Johnny Gargano, all those fun things.
I do I do a bunch of fun stuff.
So, yeah, check those things out.
Cool. Fantastic. Yeah.
Well, this is a blast.
Thank you so much for giving us so many an excellent toy store to look at.
Oh, yeah. Anytime.
Anytime you guys want to come visit the toy store, feel free to get that serotonin
hit from. Yeah, right.
And as for us, you can find us on the socials at podcast The Ride.
We got merch in our tea public store.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast
the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
And for a pickle that with a smell that will linger
in your memory for decades, it's Gherkin.
Got to be Gherkin. Check out Gherkin's everyone.
The Gherkin man speaks, Jason.
Yeah. The new mascot is so long.
Goodbye. Forever.
Dog. This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.