Five, four, three, two, one.
May the fourth, believe it or not,
is the day that it is today,
which is a day when people talk about Star Wars stuff
for some reason, and that's what we're going to do
here today on podcast The Ride the Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner, hi Jason Sheridan.
Hi, yeah, it's the Star Wars day, everyone.
It's the start, like dead on the dot as this is released.
Dead on the dot.
What are your plans?
A lot, you know, there's been a lot of mid pandemic,
May the fourth, so what do we all do
now that we're on the loose?
Mike Carlson.
Yeah, it's a good question.
How will I celebrate?
I will probably more prominently display
my Dexter Jettster toy, sort of maybe on the mantle.
As usual, it's kind of put back in my display, but.
Well, take him on a little journey.
There's a thing, I think in my house,
you could get, there's like the Nativity scene at Christmas,
which Nativity sets come with the three wise men,
and I think we would make the three wise men travel.
They'd be like over off in the credenza,
in the corner of the one living room,
and then they'd make their way to the dining room,
and then over by the lamp, and it like,
so by the time it got to December 25th,
now they're priced.
So you could take Dexter on a little journey.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Yeah, over the weeks heading up to May the fourth.
I thought you were gonna say like,
he should be one of the wise men, which I agree with,
but I was just trying to figure out what other three,
like is it, it's Dexter and like, Subulba maybe.
Who are the wisest of all the prequel characters
who would bring gifts?
I mean, Yoda is obvious as a wise choice.
You want prequel only characters.
I think we want prequel only characters.
Any of the pod racers, Team Toppa Galeys.
I don't know, I'll have to come back to this.
I was thinking the last time,
cause there was a little bit of this talk in the last,
in the episode with Mad Apodaca,
I feel like there should be,
we should be part of starting a support group
for significant others of podcast listeners
who now talk out loud about the prequels
way more than they used to or ever have due to listening.
And it's not just us, it's Doughboyz and anything,
Bug Affiliate.
I feel like podcast world is dominated by prequels.
And now there's people who don't listen to these podcasts,
who have to hear these names every goddamn day.
That's true, yeah.
And we should do something to help.
I've spread the disease,
way before we did this podcast,
like Jason knows, I've been talking about
every one of the pod racer names,
as long as he's known me.
Yeah, yeah, you've wrote it into stage shows.
Yeah, like say eight or nine years ago.
Yeah, and we worked like, some we knew.
Podrace the musical, you wrote a full,
tried to mount it off Broadway, couldn't get the funding.
Couldn't get the funding.
Some we knew was House Sitting once,
and you threw episode one on the big screen.
It's like eight or nine years ago.
Yeah, yeah.
It was like motion smoothing was on or something,
so it just looked like a Windows XP.
It looked better, it looked better honestly.
Oh, you think it looked better?
Yeah, it looked good.
Something was not calibrated.
I think it was like a standard,
it was a regular DVD going into a massive television.
But yeah, once we all started doing these podcasts,
then this infection spread to the general population,
and there was a different type of pandemic.
There was a different type of.
What happened to me?
I didn't know any of these names.
I had a, because I was thinking about this
because I was, I had some video on,
I don't even remember what it was,
but realizing that Erin, my wife,
who's never seen any of them, that she recognized Watto,
that she like laughed at the appearance of Watto
and sounded like, you've never seen these movies.
Now you know who Watto is.
Right.
Because of this spread of this,
which I guess a lot of people would say is not a bad thing.
No.
It's just interesting.
It is interesting.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Can we go back?
Scott, did you say that like your household growing up,
the three wise men, essentially elf on a shelf,
their way to the nativity?
Did I understand that correctly?
Yes.
Yeah.
That was a way to keep things going for all of December,
for an evolution to be built.
I wonder if this is,
I feel like this is not only my house,
but maybe I'll feel crazy if it was.
No, I never considered that,
but I think that's so charming.
And that's really like,
that's like an advent calendar of like,
where are these guys gonna be next?
Yes.
Something that goes all through December.
I think it would just be weekly moves.
I can't recall a specific spot.
We also maybe bailed on this and only did this one time
and only moved them once,
but it kind of makes me want to bring it back.
Yeah, it is good.
A little journey of those guys have very prequely names.
I don't know the names of the Kings.
The three wise men?
Yeah.
Offhand.
What are the names of the three wise men?
Why do I know this?
The three wise men.
Let me look.
Names.
Let's see, Juan Sandage.
No, that's a pod racer.
Let's see.
Oh, these are not that famous.
So I don't feel like shamed for not knowing these.
It's Gaspar or Caspar,
Melchior.
Melchior?
And Balthazar.
Oh, Balthazar.
Much like the sorcerer's apprentice.
Yeah, yeah.
Balthazar.
Those are good names though.
They are cool.
They are cool names.
They'll all be prequels characters.
Okay.
They're gonna be in that galactic Senate somewhere.
Oh yeah.
The Balthazarians.
There's a whole species based on them.
Yeah, like Balthazarians.
The voice, warming the voice up
for the rest of this episode.
The voice.
Everyone should get their voice warmed up.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
A, B.
Harmonize with Lucas.
Arrr.
There you go, Scott got it.
You take the fifth.
I'll be on the third and you take the fifth.
By the light.
Yeah, we're gonna do barbershop as George Lucas
on this episode.
Let's just, yeah, we'll whip it into shape
before we do it.
Yeah.
This episode is about Lucasport.
And if you're looking at that word
and have never seen that word,
that's because this was never built.
And for me, this was recent information.
Yes, absolutely.
I only knew about Lucasport within the last few years.
This was a designed and planned and drawn development
for Disneyland specifically that never got finished.
But it was going to take over,
if green lit, it was going to take over a ton
of Tomorrowland and be a way to give George Lucas
and his properties a big futuristic presence
and also utilize a lot of the dead zone of Tomorrowland,
which it's crazy to think that some of it has been
a dead zone since 1984.
Oh man, yeah.
And it's interesting, we're doing this right
as the Tokyo parks announce a massive Tomorrowland redo,
including just demolishing Space Mountain
and rebuilding a totally new version.
A whole new Space Mountain, that's crazy.
Yeah, I estimated cost of this project, 56 billion yen,
which at current exchange rates,
when the dollar was stronger, that would be 500 million.
The numbers I saw was 437 to 438,
but somewhere around there, millions of dollars.
Wow, wow.
Like we're pushing half a billion dollars
to redo Space Mountain and the surrounding areas.
And it's not, you know, I've been there,
it wasn't even like, oh yeah, this isn't such trouble.
It's just, they went, oh, you know what?
We can make this look nicer.
Exactly, yeah.
I mean, I think, you know, pictures I've seen Tokyo,
Disneyland, the Tomorrowland still looks
aesthetically pretty good, but I read up,
write up on the project, the new stuff
and what Tomorrowland's like on the Disney tourist blog.
And it's like, oh, it is kind of suffering
from a similar problem that other Tomorrowlands have,
where it's like, oh yeah, and then there's Star Tours,
and then there's a Monsters Inc ride,
and then the logic starts to fall apart a little.
Sure.
In terms of theming. It's not one cohesive.
Yeah, yeah, it's very all over the map there, I would say,
but very cool.
Very fun still.
I'm a little sad that we are losing just a pure 1983.
Yeah.
I mean, it was so wonderful being there.
It like, I mean, it's, the Space Mountain
Disneyland in America feels very similar,
like campus-wise, like they're clones of each other,
but the little touches, just like the whatever,
like the weird like pipe roof and the,
like the like moving walkway to get up there.
Just little things are very, oh, this is exactly how it was
in Disneyland in the 70s and 80s, which it's, you know,
it, hey, it rips me up when one of those changes.
Yeah.
The design looks cool. It looks good to me.
Yeah, it does look cool.
It would be, it would be a bummer losing the shape of the
ridge, that original Space Mountain building,
which I still like better, I think, than this new design,
but I'm still like, yeah, cool. Let's do it.
Like, why not?
Well, this is the spirit that you wish all over the parks had
and could afford to have is just,
there's no pressing reason to do it.
Yeah.
Like there's, whereas in the American parks,
there's things that have just been rotting for decades
and decades that really need to be changed.
And then in Tokyo, they have the luxury of, I don't know,
what do you think? It's like house remodeling instead of
waiting until something is like rusted over and like the,
you know, it's going against a code.
I know.
They're just, I don't know, let's get to that now.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah. I don't even want to,
and then there's stuff where,
and this is going to cut me off because I could go on and on
about this.
Then they're going to just redo the outside of Ralph Brennan's
jazz kitchen and make it look like nothing.
Did you see these pictures?
I did. Yeah. Yeah.
There's some downtown Disney changes coming there.
They're sort of like Palm Springs,ifying it.
I feel,
I didn't know they were redoing Ralph Brennan's.
I missed that.
I got to show you a picture.
I know. I mean, we're getting a did tie funk.
I know that's pretty cool.
Your blood pressure shouldn't go this high, Jason,
but I'm going to show this to you.
And I want, I just want you to sort of temper.
Well, look, no, I thought I was coming here today.
It was going to like, to Scott, you know,
an uva bar.
Oh, they're being re-done.
New names for these two.
I'm suspicious, but I, you know,
a uva has slid a little bit, I will say.
Okay.
Too expensive now.
So if, if they keep the space, then that's good.
Jason is inspecting the new Brennan.
Is it staying?
Oh, it is.
Yeah. I don't know what this is.
Yeah. What is this?
They're just kind of painting everything white.
Everything's, everything at downtown Disney's getting a Palm
Springs sort of veneer.
So they're making it look less like a New Orleans style
building.
I get, yeah.
Anything with like specific character, I guess,
is starting to go well.
Although I don't mind, like, I like Splitsville aesthetically.
I like that that is kind of, that's sort of Palm Springsy
sixties mod meets current bland.
I do not mind that.
And there's other buildings at downtown Disney that I think
are not good.
I'm in, I'm in favor of some downtown Disney remodeling.
Yeah. No, I'm not.
No, no, I'm not a purist for, for downtown Disney.
The way it is.
I just think like there's no personality in that new
Ralph Brennan's jazz.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's all I'm saying.
That one is confusing.
Cause that always seems pretty busy.
Like when we had that meal and we were shocked at how good it
was.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I think that,
I think the great Ralph Brennan taste will remain.
Oh, well that hopefully, hopefully they're not making
that bland like the outside.
You say it's exciting that Din Tai Fung is coming.
There's no way I'm ever going there. Right?
Like the way the level of crowded that those places are.
Yeah.
Notoriously. So as documented on Americana brand memes.
I, yeah.
You're going to have to go there.
Cause we have to do a new saga about it.
So you're going to have to, we have to wait all day.
We all have to do it just for journalism's sake.
I mean, I think like, you know, flipping Katal to like,
I, I've never been there.
I know there's a substantial paella menu.
I don't, I, I've looked at the menu before and I'm like,
oh, it's like Spanish and Mediterranean food.
I don't know that the name necessarily communicated that to
the average Disney guests, like the average public.
No, it seems like nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. I'd like to try it before it closes.
It always seemed interesting,
but I just never got around to it.
So yeah, I kind of get that.
Didn't I, Fung's an interesting get that area will probably be
mobbed because it's going back by like,
Yeah. Where is it?
The movies that the stuff they're going to start demolishing
the movies and I saw a sandwich out sandwich,
which is coming back.
Cause it's becoming a cart.
Yeah. Like it's going to be random places to get us Earl of
sandwich. They said, I don't know. I don't know how.
You're going to go down one of the, like a little alleyway.
And there's going to be somebody with just like 10 of the,
like a turkey and Thanksgiving style sandwiches.
I don't know how Robert is putting up with this. I'll,
I'll say that Robert should not have to deal with this.
Yeah. He should be, he's actually have a brick and mortar store.
He's focused on his son right now. He is making sure that the
breakfast club gets off the ground.
As long as Robbie's in a good place, Robert will be too.
You know, Robbie's got a great deal coming for like a
Stromboli delivery company fronted by a Tik TOK guy who's like a
twin, but really mean to his other twin and people love it.
Oh man. Yeah. He's doing a ghost kitchen for Ben Shapiro.
I was excited about that.
Shapiro's burritos. All right. They're extremely bland.
So bland. All right. Well, look, we, there'll be more of this talk.
We have a important discussion today about Lucas port.
Lucas port. Yeah. Lucas port. Which it's like, okay.
If you, if you don't know anything about this,
presumably we will be posting some of the art that is
cropped up for it. And that's the, it looks so great.
Oh my God.
I know. Yeah, I know this thing even more. Cause like, I think you,
I don't know if we'd all agree, but like Westcott was this, you know,
the West coast Epcot that never got built.
And I think that for a lot of us is like the dream thing that never happened.
But the more I look at this art and there also is a version of this
where, which was in a second park, which we'll talk about a little bit.
This might be number one now for me.
This is, yeah, that was not really cool. I mean,
there's some amazing unbuilt Disney stuff. We haven't really,
really dug down a Westcott being, I think the other big one.
And then tomorrow land 2055. Yeah. Which is cool too.
But this thing, this thing, this with the star Wars,
he ticket like, Oh man. Yes.
Architecture wise, it is this amazing
crystal cathedral. Yes. Looking, you see, you were,
you said something in your little warmup, JSA,
that's like a crystal superstructure. Yes. It's so awesome.
It's, you know, it's all abstract and multi-tiered. It looks like that crazy.
It's like a giant version of that crazy KFC down on Western for Helen.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
It was much bigger and crystal and not a KFC.
Well, Tony Baxter kind of overseeing this all, of course,
tried to get the giant crystals in the original land pavilion proposal.
Oh yeah. He loves crystal, giant crystals.
And I, I, I just don't know the science. Like to me,
these seemed like, you know, Bart melting ants with a magnifying glass.
I'm like, how do you keep this from just heating inside?
Like the sun shining on it.
That was a problem at a Vegas, a very like bright glass Vegas
casino. I forget which one is that right?
Trees got lit on fire around the pool. A couple of palm trees got nailed.
Sure. There's a lot of, you see some glare in Vegas in general. It's like,
how is this not frying people down below?
There is some stuff where like you see in Vegas or you just think about in
Vegas, where it's like, this isn't a front to God's creation. Like it is amazing.
I mean, I saw the water level by one of the, like, uh, is it by the Hoover dam?
The, the, the water's very low out in the desert out there right now,
where it's like an intake pump in the aquifer is below,
above the water line for the first time, maybe ever. And it's like, oh,
you don't want to see, you don't want to see that.
No, not terribly. Yeah. Yeah. Um, I don't know. They don't get into the details.
If we ever talked to Tony Baxter again, I would be interested.
Let's write that on the list of how do you make sure that guests don't fry like
ants inside your giant crystal structure? They're trapped in your crystal.
Yeah. Um, because I would assume he would have had to think about that,
but maybe not. I think he's, he knows what he's doing. This seems,
I think it would have worked. Um, it,
it also like, yeah, it's just this, like, I mean, it's, it's,
it's eighties retrofuture. It's so beautiful. It's really up my alley.
And it's all, yeah, it's all crystal prism and a big atrium that like,
that contains these, the idea of these little, I mean, it's very Epcot too.
They sort of stopped doing this post Epcot,
the idea of this little indoor campus that contains multiple
attractions connected by little bridges that get you up and above the train
track and, you know,
into disparate corners of this, this huge building.
And there's a good like side view drawing of what it would be,
like a cross section drawing that's on that's out there that you could see what
you're talking about pretty well.
Cause sometimes you see this stuff and it's like very abstract,
but like you can kind of see exactly where, I mean, I'm assuming you've,
it's going to be hard to see this,
but like it's a cross section and there's levels and it feels like a,
like a base. I think we've talked about this before as a kid.
I love the base of like a heroes and it's like little secret passages and
different rooms and like it feels, especially with a giant crystal thing,
it feels like other world, an other worldly type of base.
Yeah. And all the concept art and there, there were three, there were, you know,
physical models of it too.
It's like almost central that the monorail goes around it.
The people mover goes either through or around it.
The train is reroute it. So we, so there's all this mo that kinetic energy,
we always bring up. There's all this motion.
There's all this transit around it, like kind of like importantly,
like, and these aren't going away. These are important. We need,
you kind of need these.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
They find a way to route attractions through or around it.
And then rocket jets would have moved inside.
Yeah. Those are,
which is maybe feels weird to trap those instead of being open.
I think they would have been up higher.
I bet it's like cooler to look at those maybe then to be on them,
but up higher is, is cool as opposed to what they did,
which is bring it down lower essentially right into the hub.
Yes. Which, yeah, that's a problem. And I'm sure as soon as they have money,
they'll get rid of it.
I mean, we've only been saying that for decades. So I,
so much of this stuff, like the, the circle, not the circle vision,
the Carousel Progress Theater,
which became in inventions after America Sings,
it's still haunting the land. It's still there.
How is, how is this the one thing?
It seems like just one of the most valuable pieces of real
estate in the world to me,
like that is a huge plot of land that you could easily blow up and turn into
something very cool. How is it? Maybe it isn't, maybe it's awkwardly small.
Maybe there is not enough space out of that Carousel Theater to really do
something. Well, I think, no, I think you can do something. I think that I,
I'm guessing here, I I'm speculating, but I think it keeps falling under the,
well, we got to do a lot more. So why would we do a little thing?
We're going to have to gut the whole thing. Like we're going to have to get,
Autopia has to go, like we have to get rid of so much of this.
And every time probably proposals pop up, it's like,
it's either all or nothing.
We, yeah, yeah.
Probably what keeps happening with it as opposed to,
and it's such a pain in the ass to do it as opposed to they could just kind of
take bugs land away. That's a corner that nobody's going to go to for a while.
And we'll trade everything out and put new stuff in.
And that's an easy fix too, because it's like bugs land,
isn't making them any money. There's like,
was there even a gift shop in bugs land? No, I don't think so.
There was a couple of food stands. Yeah.
So there was like, Oh, the most popular thing we own. Yeah, that's going in. Oh,
it's food and drink and merchandise. Yeah. Of course that's going in.
Like there's no vastly more than there used to be. Yeah.
That's a rubber stamp, a quickly rubber stamp that.
But with Tomorrowland, it's a little bit, yeah,
it's that doesn't have the slam dunk nature for the money people.
I have to think just if they were to demolish the subs and Autopia,
the just demo and filling in the land,
that would just be so expensive before even putting something new there.
I think so.
It's like shut down for four years. Also, everything has to be shut down. Yeah.
Except maybe like a tiny little walkway to space mountain,
but also space mountain will probably get a redo too. Yeah. Even though.
And no clear IP to fuel any of this because the clear IP,
as with this in 1984 and what,
like when we didn't know what the galaxy's edge plan was clearly Star Wars,
Star Wars equals future. Yes.
And I feel like there's been plans where you end up with a big Millennium Falcon
over there. Yeah. That was about that sort of thing.
Before the full galaxy's edge. That was the idea. Yeah.
But now it's on the other side of the price.
It doesn't make sense to do more Star Wars over there. So what fuels it?
There is no future thing on the way, unless it's this Tron.
Our only hope is Tron. Yeah. The only possible thing. Yeah. And that's still,
I mean, I assume that's probably,
that's the best idea they have to is to do a version of Tron here and then just
make it aesthetically look like, you know, whatever they're going to do in Florida.
But that attraction will be over.
The original Tron will be in Shanghai will be over 10 years old.
Yeah. By the time it were to get built here.
I also wouldn't be, I know we're all over the place in this,
but I wouldn't be surprised if the Tokyo space mountain isn't going to use the
guardians coaster technology. Oh, I wouldn't be shocked.
A little more going on a little more like tricks and storytelling.
I saw one frame, like one screenshot of a Lee or no Disney put it up,
but one screenshot of like what the thing looks like. And I think like it's,
so there's a lot of screens on it. Spoiler alert.
So it does look like you're going through space. Yeah.
It does feel like a very, a really souped up space mountain for sure. Yeah.
So are we like,
I don't think they've definitively said if they're bulldozing the whole thing or
not, like they could keep some of the structure and build that for Tokyo.
Yeah. They could. Yeah. But they're, they're completely gutting space mountain.
I know that they're gutting it,
but I don't know like if they're leaving like the bones of it and building a new
case around it. I don't think so, but I know I could be wrong.
I think it's a totally new thing. Okay. But I could be wrong.
But that's my guess. But anyway, yeah. Some like foundation, some base of,
yeah, yeah, but it seems pretty new. So I guess you,
I guess what I'm getting at is I guess you could do like guardians space
mountain and like you could do that here,
but then you'd have to overlay it at this guardians and it wouldn't be space
mountain anymore. So I don't know.
In Disney and proper yet, unless they break that rule, right.
Which why not? I don't, I don't know. I, if, if it's,
if whatever it takes, if we, if we need more star wars over there,
not in galaxy's edge, fine. If it takes, if Marvel goes, whatever, I do not care.
Let me see. New things so bad.
Let me see how much you want new things. If it's Peter Pan space mountain,
do you want it?
Peter Pan galactic Peter pan galactic flight.
And it's like kind of a, it's like a new, like steampunk future pan.
And he has like, and they turn the little rocket ships into like little,
like I guess kind of like pirate ships, but they're like steampunk.
Like so the pirate ships you would see on an island of treasure,
like a treasure, some sort of island, a whole planet treasure plan.
Okay. All right. Is that how much do you want it new?
All right. All right. Okay. Pinocchio space Pinocchio.
More, more okay with okay. Yeah.
Pinocchio 30 99, which is coming soon. I hope.
Which is just AI. Okay. That's right. Yeah. Oh, I take an AI coaster.
That sounds great. Yes. Space mountain is now AI the ride.
David, we are on a roller coaster.
Okay.
Mommy.
Okay. It's like the ending of ET,
but it's the kid robot and he doesn't call you by your name.
Just everyone that goes by mommy, mommy, is that mommy?
And it's an exciting ride. But then at the end,
you have to sit underwater and watch David pray to the blue
fairy for, I mean, it's not years,
but you get like a full five minutes of sitting still and watching him in tone.
I wish I was real.
You do get one like very kind of melancholy, like happy day.
The end of the ride is like one perfect day with mommy. Like,
I believe, uh, kind of executive noted its way in of like,
you can't just end this movie with this child. Is that what happens?
That I recall correctly, like the,
the hyper evolved like beings in the future grant him a wish and it's like to
have like a happy time.
That is a, that is a movie with a fourth act. That is a rare structure movie.
And then he prayed for 1000 years.
I honestly, as we're talking about it, I'm like, I don't,
I was thinking like, Oh, maybe I should revisit this. And I'm like, no,
I'm getting upset. Like, I don't want to think about it.
He remotely thinking about a probably good.
I saw it whenever it came out when I was like 13 or 14 that I did not have the
emotional bandwidth to really stick my teeth into it.
Cause now I'd probably be like, I don't like this.
I don't want to finish this one.
Imagine being a parent, imagine having a little boy. Oh my God.
I might need a sec. I need to go smoke a cigarette or something.
Watching the boy like,
like her drive away and leave him in the fort. Jesus Christ.
Oh, yeah. Oh yeah.
Well that's the new theme for space mountain though, sadly.
And your deal with the devil you just made here.
Damn it. I shouldn't have left myself open to any possibility.
But the ride is you getting in a futuristic car and leaving your son in a
forest and driving away as fast as you can.
That's the new ending is like you getting back home and realizing you don't
have to take care of this creepy boy.
And they're like, uh, what's the lost daughter, the ride.
It's like there is an animatronic Jude law sex worker robot who's kind of
glib. So you get that. That's fun.
And if we're after character interaction and intimacy, they should make,
it's the first Disney experience where you could fuck an animatronic.
You get to find a West world finally coming true.
Shapek would make it happen. He's all about little up charges. That's true.
Yeah. Yeah. Sure.
What better way to like dole out little up charges at a time than through
robotic prostitution.
Sure. And the Disney play app features are just people like going on and on
about like, you know, Stanley did not live to see this project done,
but we kept, we have his notes and we looked at his original art, you know,
a lot of the original Kubrick work on it.
We think Stanley Kubrick would have loved this roller coaster.
Yeah.
For Kubrick ports. He Kubrick. Oh, well,
I believe we're getting ahead of ourselves.
I want at the end here to just sort of blue sky, some other director ports,
some other ports about this. Yeah, absolutely. Like that's what,
I think the strange thing about this is even the idea that this would be called
Lucas ports, because what you don't have in Disneyland is another
area. There's okay, there's, there's Pixar, but Pixar is still an entity.
It's not Lasseter port. There's no Lasseter port. There's no Lasseter pier.
No Lasseter place. Yeah. So it's strange that you would take another person.
I mean, or if they had, or if they had called it, what, uh, if,
if galaxy's edge was called Abrams port, sure. That would feel very strange.
Johnson port.
Abram, Johnson, Abrams, Kennedy, Kennedy port.
Yeah. Sounds like a law firm now. Yeah. So right. Did that? Yeah. No, that's not,
there is yet no precedence for it. And not since it really is.
I was thinking how strange the name is. It's a cool name,
but it'd be so weird if today there was still Lucas port.
But if you think about it, it is the same format as Disneyland. Yes.
Disneyland, Lucas port. Oh yeah. Yeah.
That's less weird if you view it from that angle.
It's interesting though, that that was the name,
like they were considering that as the name because of how much I think faith
they would have that George Lucas would continue probably to just like churn out
hits, which George Lucas, I mean,
he produced Indiana Jones and would go on to make more star wars,
but years later, like it wasn't like he was, you know,
doing a new movie every couple of years, like Steven Spielberg wound up doing.
But at the time I think I could, this is also speculation,
but it feels like we need to invest heavily in this guy and kiss his ass as
much as possible and name.
Like we want him involved in this so much.
Let's name a whole land part of Disneyland after him. Yeah. Right.
What, but what is interesting is like, yeah, there's a star wars roller,
like an insane sounding star wars roller coaster.
But the rest of the concept art is kind of like interesting,
like future redesign, right? A version of alien encounter,
the Astro jets. So it's not all star wars. Right. That's it.
That even, I think again,
adds to my point where it's like it wasn't even like they were like doing
everything Lucas. So it was,
there was still stuff that was like space mountain was still there and that was
not necessarily tied to George or these other things were not directly from like
THX or something. Yeah.
There was no American graffiti ride. So like, they still were like,
we're going to name the whole place after you,
even though it's not necessarily everything of yours. Sure.
Which actually your spirits,
but would they have then owed adding the Howard the duck is walking around?
Yes, they would have owed that which is radio land murders.
There's a radio land murders show radio show and audio,
a little audio play. Yes. Yes. They owed all of that. And, and because,
and if tomorrow I was in the same state it is now we would have still had Howard
the duck walking around and like I'm a guy playing young Harrison Ford driving
around in a car from American graffiti. Yeah.
We would have still had that show going on.
It's weird how much American graffiti there is at universal studios and then
none of that has ever gone. Just that you've got those diners. Oh, right. Right.
They're like, they're in both parks that there's a big,
this fifties drive in, but that's what that's from. Right.
Mel's diner is the diner in the movie,
but I think it's also like a kitschy looking,
a bit of Americana where they need to sell hamburgers anyway.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. True. Is the, uh,
is the name of the sequel to American graffiti more American graffiti?
Absolutely is Michael.
Maybe the funniest sequel title I've ever heard too,
cause it's like really just like literally, yeah, here's more of it.
You like the first one more. Here's more. Uh, I wish more sequels. Cause like,
you know, we always hear like rise of so-and-so and it's,
there's these overused sequel titles and yeah, well, let's just do more. Yeah.
More red notice, more red notice.
They have a chance to just read to reset how we brand these. Yeah.
So just please more studios. Another bird box. Yeah. A second bird box.
More. Yeah. Uh, so yeah. Add more to any of the movies you like.
Um, yeah, let's, well, when I talk about this,
the ride a little bit, the, the, the primary thing,
which this was the first imagineer designed attempt at a Star Wars attraction.
And this would have been a massive indoor roller coaster that has set pieces,
animatronics, and mainly the big innovation decision points where you can veer
off onto different paths.
I think basically six different combos that you could do that involve what are
the, the, the choice that you make is like, do you, uh,
do you fight or fight or fight? Yeah. Uh huh.
And the, the fleeing takes you where, well, it's, what are,
what are all the scenes in this all told you start in Dagobah with Yoda and Obi-Wan.
Yeah. And it's like, yeah. So,
so you're in like what looks like from the art,
just like kind of space mountain ish roller coaster kind of cars.
We're in like a cool glass tube, essentially launching into space.
Yes. Uh, and then there's like full animatronic Dagobah and I guess it's like ghost
Yoda, maybe not real Yoda. I'm not sure like force ghost, but I'm not sure.
I don't know. It might not be cause there's, you see scenes from Star Wars,
I think like that happened like during the movie. So I'm not sure. Um,
but then apparently it would have been like a full animatronic show and trees
and everything like Dagobah. And then as if Yoda was using his force,
the car lifts up. And did you read this?
And what would happen is the whole scene basically would have lowered down to
make you feel like you were rising up out of the swamp.
His entire set, the whole,
swamp moves to make it feel like you're flying. But in reality, it's lowering,
the swamp itself is lowering.
I saw something that said it's you.
This force is strong with you. That's why the thing is.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But I'm yeah, practically. Yeah.
Yeah. Illusion would have been done. Uh, which just like this, for this alone,
if that was the whole thing, I would have been like, oh yeah, please. That's neat.
Uh, very, very cool. That's, and that's directed at you. That's what you're at.
The force is exactly. This is all the stuff I'm like, that's like lacking.
Like risers. I'm like, yeah, like more about me.
Isn't very about you, isn't it?
Do you feel like you're just along for the ride or I mean,
I know what's about me and we're like helping and stuff, but I don't know.
I want someone to talk about how like I'm the five force sensitive. I,
I'm the guy, you know, I want here.
Maybe if a rise of resistance was just one per car, I would be happier.
You know, like you, I don't want to share.
The worrying count on like a display. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But all of the, you share all of it. You shared transformers, you share star tours,
but you like when the holograms say you, you're my only hope. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And it's like, if I'm the rebel spy or whatever too, which has happened twice,
you know, but the rise of resistance, like, okay, let's get it.
Let's make me feel a little more special. So much shared spot. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
So yeah, Yoda and also just Yoda robot.
Also be great. Yeah. Um, where do you go from here?
Uh, circling some AT-ATs, uh, what else? Uh, dual.
It just said between Darth Vader and a Jedi, I guess,
I guess it kept it open.
They're unclear. Yeah, exactly. So yeah, this,
the coaster has three guest choice points where you would choose to dogfight or
flee.
Who would ever flee? Well, I mean, if you went on a lot, I guess.
I think the one, some of the tracks were more family friendly, but they,
they're assuming that all the riders are rational actors. When in reality,
if a couple teenagers are in that car and they see little kids go like fight,
fight, we want loops as many loops. Let's terrorize these children.
It seems, yeah, it seems if you were going to fight,
then the coaster itself would then have loops versus fleeing.
You'd have a smooth flight,
which is so crazy because like that has to have a whole bunch of different,
like physics and it's not physics,
but like one thing has to go so much faster than the other.
And like to be able to build something that complicated,
I don't think there's any coaster still that's been built like this.
That's this complicated. Yeah.
That have that many variations. And I mean, look,
the show building would have had to have been massive and they had the full
parking lot to work with because there's no second gate. Right.
There's no California adventure.
We're going to go over the like berm. Like,
they would have had to build massive show buildings.
So that's what some of the sky bridges would have had to get you to like all
the way out of the park.
But then if you think about where California adventure is, so like right at the,
so just a big corner of the parking lot is gone.
Basically you got to walk people.
I guess a precursor to Indiana Jones where there's a big old walk before you get
to the ride. Yeah.
That building where it's like when you're on the parking tram going to Disneyland
and you're like, Oh, that's a big warehouse. And you're like,
you are looking at the haunted mansion.
You are looking at the actual Indiana Jones would have been another one of the,
but when you think about, but this would have to be,
we're really talking multiple point,
like six different sections of coast and they all have to hook up and arrive.
It's insane. Yeah.
Justically it's like air traffic control. It's crazy. Space wise.
That's the, it's hard to pine for this thing in this ride too much because
that's insane. There's no way it would have had to take over like half of the
parking lot.
The only people I could see building it is the Oriental land company,
the Tokyo group. And even they, I feel like would have scaled back because how
much would it, this been not even in numbers back then,
but I feel like this alone would have been at least rise of the,
at least half a million,
500 million dollars,
the money it is. But like, I'm sure there's a version of it where just like,
it doesn't have, you don't have the choices.
You just put them on the path of like, yeah, yeah, that would have been,
you're right. That would have been the first thing to go. Yeah.
Cause that's not essential. It's a neat idea and it'd be neat for something.
Yeah. To do this.
But you could easily just, you know, give them the path that does the loops.
Yeah. Nothing's ever, you're right.
Nothing's ever done this coaster wise.
There's rides where you go off this way or that way,
but there is not, but those are more slower dark rides or trackless resistance
is kind of like that would just lick little differences between the way you go.
Yeah. But a coaster, yeah, we were talking about it kind of ride still has never
been. Yeah. And like with Hagrid's and universal Orlando, it's like they're,
they're just now kind of experimenting even more with sort of like this,
there's a drop there and you go on another track at the end of that.
So like there's like stuff like that. That's kind of innovative in the code,
but that still feels like simple compared to what this is.
And it breaks down all the time. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They open that thing too early. They definitely open Hagrid's too early.
It feels like, but if, if there were,
if you had to account for parts like that track switches over and over again,
and Hagrid's still only has one way that you can go. We're talking,
that Hagrid's is inside a building and then there's three different Hagrid's
right types of Hagrid paths. And then also what?
75% of everyone would just be hitting fight. Yeah. One of the track,
one of the tracks would be like getting a lot more use than the other.
Just hitting both because people just see something light up,
realize it's a button and just smack them. You know? Yeah. That being said,
obviously we build this, please like build the crazy version of it.
Yes. But it is, it is in all serious,
like what I've complained about as far as rise of resistance is I feel like it
doesn't put your body in a sense of panic during it.
Like I think some of the best rides do like Indiana Jones.
I was I on transformers alone yesterday, universal. Yes, I was.
That ride makes your body feel like something's wrong because you're
constantly banging into the back of it. Very unpleasant. Very physically
unpleasant. I dropped my phone. I thought it was lost.
You want that. You want to have your head banged. You want a question.
And you want to drop your phone. Yes. Uh,
and like some of the art in this is like you're,
you're going through like the tunnels of what I assume is probably the death
star, but might be a star destroyer. Um, and I was like, well,
this would like solve that problem of like having your body feel like it was
panicking a little bit.
Like it is an Indiana Jones or on any of the best e-ticket rides.
Isn't this the word you used about Buzz Lightyear that I get on? I panic.
Panic was wrong.
Panic so central to hear what you want out of these experiences.
I think panic is just something I feel a few times a day in general.
So the word is in the forefront of my mind.
You want to get it out in a controlled way.
You want to release the panic in a way that is fun and not, uh,
applied to the stresses of your life. Yeah, I think that is probably what it is.
Uh, I overuse the word on Buzz Lightyear. I apologize to the listeners.
Uh, more sort of anxious about getting a good score, but, um,
but I was on transformers yesterday.
I was like kind of just trying to like not look at the screen and like feel what
it was doing to my body, the ride vehicle. And it is, it is unpleasant,
but I think that's good. I think that's part of the ride.
So you tried to do kind of a Zen thing of just like being the moment,
feel what's happening. Feel the world around you. I do feel it. It sucks.
Remove the glasses.
Count your account, your breath as they're screaming, like, look out. It's,
it's Megatron.
Your shoulder. Yes. Your left shoulder is smacked into a hard piece of plastic.
Yeah. What does it feel like? Uh,
do you hear a tinny version of I feel good coming out of a
robot's walkman?
Yeah. Yeah. Uh, that is what I was doing.
That's like when I have the like bell at the end of a meditation session,
like a light bell to tell you it's, it's ended.
That's the, I feel good. That's the, yeah, the, I feel good slowly brain now.
So don't open your eyes slowly. Open your eyes and take in the,
the last song is like, give it to me now.
That's the last song we're talking about is I feel good earlier in the ride.
There's a little bit of I feel good towards the end. I think. Yeah,
I guess it's toward the end or is I'm trying to think where this,
where the songs are to me now. It's like a disco song, right?
Is that pulling into the station? Is that what you're thinking? I feel that.
I thought he catches you and goes, I feel good at the end.
Have we done transformers? We've not done transform. I was on the ride.
Really? I was on the ride yesterday going, did we do this?
I've talked so much about it and I was like, I can't remember.
Accurate to the movies because you find them on cable and you go like,
did I see this?
Well, yeah. And the way that I've been on that ride a bunch of times and I can't
tell you the plot. I don't know what song you're talking about.
I know my friend is there. I know.
James song. Isn't there a Rick James song on there in the ride?
I think it's something like that. Am I wrong? You know, they really think that's,
wait, that's wait, maybe it is. Uh, give it to me. Baby is on.
Is that the song? And you were on it yesterday and you don't know it was on it
yesterday. Yeah. They need to,
they need to add some of the later movie innovations into the ride.
They need to have Stanley Tucci drinking a bag of Chinese milk.
Uh, they need to have like Anthony Hopkins just kind of like walking around with
a cane going like they've been here much longer than you think.
The Knights of Arthur, you know,
we're all of our new oddball choices.
You have any proof of this, Mike?
The song Bumblebee plays at the end of transformers ride when he catches you.
And somebody says, is it give it to me, baby, by Rick James?
I've been trying to figure it out forever. And then somebody says,
doesn't he play? I feel good by James Brown. Yeah. So I guess
that little dude, wait, but then this, so somebody says, oh,
that's what it is. And then somebody play. Yes, that is give it to me, baby,
by Rick James. This is fascinating. I've, I, is this so weird?
Is this the dress? Is this the blue dress might be the blue dress in my head?
And I didn't go on it yesterday and maybe both songs are in it somehow,
but why, what I've always picked up on, I think it's,
I know you're right. Cause it's the, but I swear I've heard like,
give it to me. And like I've heard,
are there multiple choices somehow? Does this sound familiar to you at all?
Do you have any idea?
I don't think there are multiple choices.
I'm wondering if one song plays when he catches you and one song plays.
It might be that. Yeah. So, well, let's all just see each,
all three of us try to remember this when we're going like, what happens?
What should we do coming up? What should we do?
Wow. I was like, I was sure the first half of the ride yesterday,
I was sure we did an episode and then I went, I don't think we have.
We've just come up a lot.
We've just explored it and Optimus looms large with his being proud of you.
Yeah.
I do think this is if you're implying any sort of, like,
any Transformers is better than Rise of the Resistance, then you're a,
you're a nutball. I'll say it.
There is elements of Transformers that is better than Rise of the Resistance.
This is, this is heresy.
I really like, you've always been a little,
you've been a little anti-rise the whole time from episode,
from the first time we talked about it.
You're not wrong about that. I have been a little anti-rise of the resistance.
Yeah. But the strong parts of Transformers are also the strong parts of Spider-Man.
Oh yeah. Well that's no, I'm not denying that. No, but that's true. That's true.
I don't know if I don't think there's time right now for my full dissertation
after I've been on Rise so many times.
What's better in Transformers than Rise of the Resistance?
Well, you get a lot of FaceTime with the characters and.
I characters I don't know or like, or want FaceTime with.
Beside the point, beside the point.
I don't get any character. I want to see a face.
It doesn't matter who the face belongs to.
You get a lot of FaceTime with the characters.
There's a lot of action happening. I still find Rise of the Resistance a little empty.
I feel it's part of an empty journey, especially like when you're,
and it's part of it because just the size of it is so big and they can't do so
many robots, stormtroopers shooting at you, but it feels empty.
I want like a lot of stormtrooper activity and shooting,
and then you feel more like stuff is happening.
And I truly do believe that the smoothness of the ride takes
takes me out of it a little. Like, I feel like it's too smooth.
It doesn't feel like we're in as much jeopardy as we should feel like.
I think that was a big thing with when listening to Tony
and other people talk about Indiana Jones, they want to ride a vehicle
that felt like you were in the action a lot more.
So that's how they figured and developed that. A lot of jostle. Sure.
A lot of jostling, because that's the weird goofy feeling
you feel off of these rides after you're done, which tricks your brain
into thinking you were actually sort of in some danger.
Oh, and where you get off and feel a little wobbly.
Yes, I think a lot happened to you.
And you lose like a few brain cells because your brain shouldn't be
jostling around in your skull like that. Yeah.
So it's like I think that it could feel a little bit more fuller.
But obviously that's a lot more money.
And I think that with Rise, yeah, it's such a smooth ride.
That ride vehicle works really well on like Poo in Japan.
But a thrill ride being triagles.
But a thrill ride is a little different. I hear you. Here's my things.
It's that you are in physical environments does so much for me.
Transformers is such screen chaos that does make me kind of woozy.
And I would I would take smoother over.
Yeah. Just feeling insane from Transformers.
And like after like I have no idea where I went or what I did or why.
Yeah, I would. Yeah.
I mean, that's you're right about that.
And I don't have very much except for Optimus now, because I feel so like
he's such a father figure to me now.
I don't have much affection for the Transformers characters.
I do the Spider-Man characters.
But like, I I don't know what it is.
I don't know if it's that I like I see their like their faces are so clear
to me by the end of the ride.
I feel like I've hung out with all of them,
including the Spider-Man characters in Orlando.
Sure. You know what I'm like?
Spider-Man characters I love, but we don't get to see very many characters
on this Star Wars ride.
And obviously, yes, also, I'm a man in his later 30s
who would like to see some of the old characters.
But that's not even not what I'm talking about necessarily.
Yeah. Jason, where do you land on any of this?
I don't know. I mean, I think
Rise of Resistance is very impressive.
I'm sure I like it more than Mike.
My big thing was riding Runaway Railway is that it's a lot of similar
technology, but it is just so much more fun.
It's a lot more fun. It's really fun.
And I think there's lots of fun stuff.
I think the most fun element in Rise of the Resistance is the escape pod drop.
Yeah, because it's just such a switch.
Big surprise. It's like, oh, my God, there's another ride element.
There's another ride system in play.
We've done so many at this point. Yeah. Yeah.
That late in the game that they still have something up their sleeve.
Yeah. And that it's telegraphed like there's like if you're really paying attention,
you see the other ones in the far distance in the screen drop
and then you drop like there's just so many little moments of delight.
A little little or little little. OK.
Just want to make sure.
Either either in this case and then you come around.
There's a happy ending because you see the you know, Lieutenant Beck's OK.
Like, yeah, of all the everything you're describing,
I like so much more than anything in Transformers.
I cannot go along with you on my favorite part of the Rise of Resistance
is the pre show with Lieutenant Beck. Yeah, because there's a character,
Mon Calamari in there.
You can get right up on top of him.
I mean, not on top of it.
Not yet. He shows up.
I want them to let me get on top of him.
He shows up in audio form like when you are trying to escape.
Yeah. But I bet one more animatronic
Lieutenant Beck in the middle would be nice.
I saw a lot of your problem. Yeah.
And like Finn, like Finn, no one even unless you know where to look.
You go, hey, do you see Finn on the ride?
And people go, what? Yes. Yeah.
Where was he?
And you're like, well, there's a box and it was far away.
And he was, you know, it's something I kind of like that the Finn
animatronic is not that great.
It reminds me of the ET cops.
It's obviously better than those.
But I like like what the what the ET ride was able to get away with.
That's a glorified mannequin.
Yeah, that's kind of how with Finn's inability to move his body
and then that he's off in a corner, it's there's something kind of like
retro and charming to me about it.
Yeah, I don't dislike it.
I just it's like no one even knows where to look.
I've had many people were like after riding it, not many, a couple
where I go, yeah, then Finn, the Finn animatronic, like a what?
What are you talking about?
I go, yeah, he was like behind the box.
Does he move? He might not move.
He might be a statue, like the Incredible Statues.
Or I think there's some at Universal, too, where like,
I kind of don't mind the stat, like the little statues.
If you have enough lighting, you got to hit those little, little,
little statue.
I I kind of don't mind them if the lighting cues are good.
Like, yeah, I prefer a statue with a decent lighting set up.
Then just a screen that might, you know, it's not going to be like those
avatar screens where it's like, oh, they got to keep James happy.
They got to keep those screens looking good if they're going to leave them in there.
You know? Yeah, sure.
But yeah, I know that's just a part.
Yeah, partly me pining for this version of the ride is
because it's got more of the old characters.
But also it does feel like it solves a problem that I'm talking about,
where it's like you get like a cool it's almost like what I what you want
from something like is this the cars model, the Cars Land model,
where you do get like great show scenes and then the parallel elements
are and it's very much from the movie.
But it feels like its own thing.
It doesn't just feel like you're stepping through.
There's that tricky balance they have to strike of you get everything
that's in the movie, but it's not just taking you through the plot of the movie.
And that is my concern.
Looking at this, what this ride might have been is that if we're
if it's Darth Vader, we're going past the Darth Vader fight
and we're seeing the Death Star blow.
Are we not in just we're passing by the things that happened in Star Wars,
which would be cool.
It would certainly be cool.
But I feel like they I'd be so curious what the story was in their head.
Yeah, they don't say what it is exactly that happens on this.
But I mean, there would be some loose, loose explanation, I assume,
of like either you're going through like famous things that happened
or you're like assisting in moments or something.
I don't know. Sure. Sure. Yeah.
I assume you're assisting if you're force sensitive. Sorry.
Oh, I just don't want to forget to mention the third attraction
that would have gone in this in the crystals would have been
the early pitch on Alien and Counter. Right.
Yeah. Seemingly before
the it was the Nostromo before it was supposed to be even before the Alien.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I didn't see that.
Yeah, I didn't I didn't see that mentioned.
I think the apocryphal story is that they got the rights to use Alien.
They realized this would be way too scary for like an alien encounter.
So they stuck it in the great movie ride. Right. Right.
Because both those movies were pretty big.
And this isn't also this isn't Cameron Port.
This is no, which is all, by the way, an awesome would be awesome.
I mean, Cameron Port, though Lucas would go on to consult on the
the version of the Alien and Counter that came out. Right.
Yeah. You forget he was.
That's weird. Part of Alien and Counter in some way, too.
Yeah. And so it it would have been interesting.
There's a good review time video on this.
And I think a thing they point out that's really interesting
is that Alien and Counter, when built in Florida, had to fit in that space.
And but if they had built it from scratch here in the Lucasport
project, they could have made a massive like or multiple massive auditory.
Like it could have been totally different. Sure. Sure.
But a similar concept. Right. Right.
I mean, this this thing looked it looked really neat.
It would be I mean, if we had a locked in time, mid 80s
Star Wars. Oh, yeah.
With with animatronics from that era, there would be a certain
there's a version of this that happened where it's an untouchable classic.
And that's the definitive Star Wars ride.
Yeah. Other than like the track needing to be replaced.
I think, yeah, it would be really hard to demolish
this in the same way that it's kind of still hard to demolish.
Like they can't the you have to keep the fantasy land dark rides
for some sort of like reverence to the past.
I mean, obviously, like like it's for kids.
Those are kids rides primarily.
But yeah, it's so hypothetical.
Like either if this had gotten done, is this just Disneyland classic?
And then there's Lucas ports at the other parks.
Or is this just an unachievable?
I kind of think they ran the numbers on this quickly and realized
this was not going to I bet this was not on the table for very long.
Yeah, I guess. I mean, obviously, like they had models and stuff.
So they put some work this because there's some stuff you come across
that seem more like ideas and one drawing of it.
But it seemed like it got pretty far.
But you would think that you'd ran the numbers on the ride itself
and then didn't do anything.
Yeah. Yeah. Centerpiece is essentially impossible to do.
And yeah, because that would be the rest that would, I'm sure,
be like the impetus for doing it is like this
the craziest ticket we've ever built. Yeah.
Had a very interesting like
afterlife or half life where it's like if you notice in the model,
it says welcome to venture port.
Which I believe is what they were going to call this whole structure.
Well, that if not Lucas, it seems like they were debating.
Yeah. This port is that too weird and personal to him
or is adventure port and venture port as a name?
It comes up again in Westcott is just like the central area of Westcott.
But then it also comes up as its own second gate.
Yes, they were debating doing a second gate at Disneyland
that would have had, you know, it would have had all this Lucas
port stuff that didn't get built.
Yeah. I was going to you probably were going to say the same.
I was going to have a figment and dream finder thing.
Wow. At Disneyland, Indiana Jones and Jules Verne area. Right.
So all of that. Yeah.
You know, the long planned discovery base sort of like this would have been.
I mean, this all would have been Baxter.
I was going to say this is Baxter land.
If you've got Jules Verne in there, that's his number one guy.
Indy stuff. That's all his stuff. Yeah.
So like that would have been a version of Westcott.
And then when I was reading that, I was like, do I want Westcott more?
Do I want venture port more?
I was like, it was a tough.
I don't know that I even have a good answer.
And this is separate from Discovery Bay.
That's a different project.
The hypothetical projects are so fascinating, even to our land 98
before budget cuts like could have been cool, could have been cool.
I wasn't against the notion of it.
It just sort of every step of it turned out so badly.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
So so venture port would have been.
Yeah, I guess they were just taking these designs and like, well,
if you're not going to do in tomorrow, and maybe we can get more money
for a full new park.
And then, yeah, like Indy would have been over there.
I think Indy would.
And then maybe with more stuff around it, because Indy also has a full
version of it's a bigger can.
Maybe there's multiple rides.
Yeah. Big Indy show set.
So, yeah, I was like, I was like, because like Westcott,
which we've talked a little bit about, which had its own like world showcase
and the hotels seem very cool and the way you could like
hang out there 24 hours a day, which is what we all want.
And there was like a crazy 45 minute boat ride that took you around the park
through tons of robots.
But big crystal thing in the Star Wars, you take it.
Mm hmm. Tough decision.
I don't know. I don't have to make it.
But Baxter has the best unbuilt slate.
Everything you've ever heard that he wanted.
Yeah. It didn't get done is so incredible.
Yeah. But then, you know, a lot of Tokyo Disney, Tokyo,
DCC does have lots of jewels, very stuff.
It does have a more built out Indiana Jones area.
So, yeah. So some of that is fulfilled.
Yeah. He was correct.
Like whatever comfort that likely gives that everyone's wanted to like
the version that they did of what he wanted to do is the most beautiful
theme park in the world.
Yeah. It's truly next level.
Yeah. And it's interesting.
I don't know. Like interesting to think also.
Again, if they built this, would this be how dated would this look now?
Yeah, it could be.
Again, I would love it so much.
There's there's concept art they did of the interiors of the atriums
and the little bridges.
And it looks so much like that star tours campus that I loved in Tokyo.
Yeah, yeah. A lot.
It is like such great 80s future and like, I don't know, it's all.
What do I even like? It's just like pipes, narrow corridors and blocky.
And I mean that I have to remind myself I don't.
I'm worried now that they're going to do something to that area.
I don't think it's part of the Space Mountain thing.
But it's but I'm worried. Yeah.
I don't want Tony Solaroni going anywhere in those brick is that that area.
Rules. Yeah.
I saw a couple of people talking about like, that's a lot of money
just to do Space Mountain.
Like this could be a full tomorrow land like maybe.
And I I wouldn't be surprised if they didn't show any of that.
They just show kind of the courtyard. Yeah.
Out front. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. Please don't tell them.
Don't tell me. I hope tomorrow and Astro zone is going anywhere.
I don't know. I would I would mentally prepare for it in 2028.
Whatever that's. Yeah.
I got to go back one more time.
You should go back. OK.
It is strange because some stuff like I don't know that there's a there's a ton
of design styles that you would call timeless.
But like stuff always comes back around.
And I feel like mid century modern, if it ever starts to dip out of style,
it comes back around so fast.
I mean, that seems to be a lot of the design elements coming to downtown Disney.
Yeah. Of like this is a throwback, but it's a throwback
that just keeps coming back in style.
Yeah. You know, you always keep landing.
And but this like a super 80s new edition in tomorrow
and might feel a little. Yeah.
Could be a little dated. Yeah.
Yeah. Depending on there's there's actually some like this art to me
looks a little more timeless if you can see that, which is like the main piece.
But then the other like there's another piece of art that has the the Astro
jet or whatever the hell they're.
And that looks like if I go, I can imagine how that looks.
Just like an old convention center.
Yeah. 30 years later, I could imagine people going like,
so it doesn't look any like so good anymore. Sure.
Yeah. Like that looks less mad.
This picture looks a lot less cool and magical than that big,
beautiful picture of the whole land.
Yeah. Right. Right. Yeah.
So, you know, original Star Tours still has kind of a caked in mid 80s
that I don't think bothers.
Yeah, no, that's true.
That's true. Super.
You know, they did kind of a refresh and modernized it and screened it up
a little bit. But, you know, just the lobby and exterior and everything.
Yeah. Out of place.
Really, this whole I guess you have Lucas port to thank for Star Tours
because it caused them to do the math of how do we do a Star Wars ride?
Well, you'd have to have all of these.
There's so much universe you want to explore in so many different planets.
How do you do all of that?
We don't have the space to do it.
Well, is there some way to do it in a small space?
Thus, they find flight simulators.
Thus, Star Tours gets done.
Yeah. So they did like this all is the the homework, the path
they had to go down to get to an amazing ride.
Yeah, it is so crazy, though, when you think of how small and scope
it ended up being, how big it was.
And then like it was like a room, essentially.
Yeah. Yeah. The craziest, biggest thing with all the characters as robots.
And then a tiny little room
moves with like none of the care.
I mean, obviously some in the in the queue, but no characters basically.
Yeah, yeah. R2 and T3PO.
But then it's it's Rex, a great new, great new character,
which no can't be mad about that.
But it is funny to think about how small it got from how the blue sky phase.
Yeah. But it's all fascinating.
I mean, just the art is jaw dropping.
I'm so glad it leaked.
It's very cool to see it.
And I just like those logo, the logos of.
Oh, yeah.
Venture Porter are awesome.
I would. I mean, I know we're not.
We maybe could talk to Tony Baxter again one day.
I don't think we'll ever get to talk to George, but I would love some
like tall commentary from George about what his ideas
or what his thoughts were at the time.
But he also this might have been like, here's what we have planned.
He's like, I don't know.
How's the end of it?
You know, we have no idea how involved he was in Luka.
This might have been presented to him.
Here's what I really here's what I want.
I want Charlie Rose to be uncancelled for a day and interview George.
George seems to like talking to Charlie Rose.
A perfect pair. Yes.
Canceled Charlie again at the end of the day.
Yeah, then he's back to cancel back to cancel.
But George and Charlie just talk about Lucas Port for two hours.
I just went in with Better Call Saul back.
I was going back into Breaking Bad, and it's so funny that in the finale of
well, the Charlie Rose.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The last episode.
But then in the final episode that Walt shows up at Gretchen and Elliott's house
and I saw you on Charlie Rose yesterday.
Charlie Rose is part of that.
He is in the Breaking Bad.
So every in like Better Call Saul, everything you're watching.
Just keep in mind, Charlie Rose is out there.
Yeah, he doesn't show up.
We haven't seen him on TV, but like it just let him lurk
like a ghost over everything that happens in Better Call Saul.
I mean, they're saying it's going to link up with Breaking Bad a lot more as we go
on here. So I think it had he Charlie.
All right. He can be uncancelled for two days.
The one to shoot his cameo on Better Call Saul.
Look, I don't approve of what the guy did.
No part of the story.
No, my Vince Gilligan, that just sounds like Jimmy Buffett.
No, you're right.
There's a piece.
Someone showed me a photo of him with Jimmy Buffett.
And I'm trying to remember Jim.
Well, that makes it. Oh, they'd be thick as thieves.
I think the same voice.
Maybe that's why your plane got shot down by the Jamaican government.
Wow. I got a time to turn that into my next show.
Yeah, we could get Frank.
I think Frank Bama could be one of Saul's clients.
And please, while Jimmy is still with us, like, let's
let's explore the Buffett verse with Kevin Gilligan behind the wheel.
Better Call Saul is going to finally link up to the Jimmy Buffett verse.
Better closer than you've ever seen.
Saul's going to find Joe Merchant.
Let me see if I can Google this, if this exists.
A photo of Gilligan and.
Well, what else do we have to address here?
I mean, well, I guess we bring up a good an interesting point,
which is devoting land to an auteur to an auteur filmmaker.
Oh, yeah, here it is. It's available.
It's Jimmy and Vince. Oh, wow.
On set, I think. On set of what?
Of Saul or Breaking Bad, I think.
He came and visited. Yeah.
Got it. He should contribute an original song.
Oh, man. Yeah, I think I think this might be.
Unless Vince was his visiting him on the set of Hawaii.
Oh, no, no, no. It's on Saul.
It's going. Jimmy.
Jimmy's caption is this 2015 going Hollywood in Albuquerque
with Vince Gilligan on the set of Better Call Saul.
Wow. Jimmy was there.
They didn't get him in the show.
Vince, come on.
They should standardize that the only way that he ever does cameos
is running away, holding a couple of margaritas like in Jurassic World.
There should be some scene where the cartel rolls into somewhere,
opens fire and he ducks away, holding a bunch of margaritas.
What a good idea. I was just enjoying my desert Airbnb
and then this Winnebago blew up.
The first caption, this is on Facebook for some reason.
The first or the first comment is from a lady and she just wrote,
now, that's two handsome men.
And I can't disagree.
Bam. You're not wrong.
Thank you so much.
They share the same voice.
They got the same voice.
A handsome voice. Yeah.
I created Better Call Saul.
405 in an out burger.
Better Call Saul.
You know, it's interesting to think about, like, if Lucas
Board had been built, because Space Mountain had already been opened
when they would have been working on this, that that means Tomorrowland,
this hypothetical Tomorrowland would have ended up with two roller coasters,
a concept we are just now start getting around to in 2022.
Yeah, yeah. God willing, with Tron and Tron and Space Mountain in Florida.
Yeah, roller coasters can go next to each other.
Yes. Never believe that they can't.
I know I am.
I have to say that Japan news, I am a little surprised
a Space Mountain is being demolished, even with the idea of like,
we can do better.
One, I think maybe I'm just a little thrown by the optimism,
by like the like iterating just because like, it seems like it's time.
You know? Yeah, sure.
Yeah, we're used to a certain.
You've been. Yeah, you've been let down so many times here.
You're used to it.
Yeah, especially because it's just like the newest DOW or media thing is like,
well, streaming services are tightening their belts.
You know, it's like it might be the end of pumping out.
You know, investors are running for the hills.
Let's talk about more fun stuff than that.
But then it affects the thinking of the other wings of these massive.
I know. I understand that.
But Universal's having great success with their parks recently.
Yeah, the parks are doing great.
Peacocks in the toilet.
Jason, no more talk of the industry drying up.
Make it a loss leader like those hotel rooms, those cheap hotel rooms they built.
Let's talk about and we should each have one comedy pitch
and one legit pitch for director based lands.
That's what I think we should do.
Obviously, I'm going to go with my I won't tell you which one is which,
but I think I'll I'll first throw out Smithland Smithport,
which you got the quick stop there, which is a convenience store and in
pro in the same way, like on Galaxy's Edge would have performers with their own
language, you know, and they would they would say, you know, one of them would say
they didn't have to they weren't even supposed to be there today.
That would be what one person had to say every time you check out
there and there would have to be, you know, we can all think of I haven't.
This is I'm doing this off the top of my head here.
But, you know, you would have, you know, dogma ride.
There would be a practical rubber poop monster.
Well, racing to the to get into the cathedral.
Yes. Yes.
While the loophole is still in effect.
Yes. Rickman, Alan Rickman, animatronic.
Yeah. From from that race through the streets of Trenton.
Race to the streets of Newark.
Yes. There should be a ride that simulates his career where you can decide
do something new or go back to the old shit again.
Back to the present.
Oh, shit again. Oh, shit again.
View a skewniverse. Yes.
So there's a there's a button one button says view a skewniverse again
or Jersey girl.
And I would hit Jersey girl because I remember Jersey girl being sort of charming.
But I thought it was all right.
You could read this and probably you got some you got a ride there.
I don't know what type of ride it is, but definitely have a ride called the Dick Poner.
Now, got to tribute the Ticket is based on the tweet.
That's the big.
That's the big. Yeah.
Yeah. That's the big ride.
If you don't know what we're talking about, just look up Kevin Smith, the tweet.
And I'm assuming it'll pop up.
I got to be the first one.
Strap in for an experience.
It's like boning like you're cheating on each other with each other.
That's right.
And you know what? That ride is going to age well, because 10 years in.
Still, there's still
there's at least 10 years of life in that.
Yeah. Yeah.
You're right. OK.
They're skip 15 seconds ahead if you're easily offended.
Please keep your hands, arms and clit brown, taint areas inside the vehicle.
I mean, we could all pitch, but I think that's the
real stick. I don't know.
If you've returned to the office and you're listening to this on speakers,
congratulations, you're being sent home.
I gave a warning.
That's fair. That's fair.
Smithport.
All right. Get building Smithport.
I have a pitch. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Port Thomas Anderson.
Oh, OK.
So you got to explore.
I mean, the you know, there's a bibbidi bopbidi boutique
style shopping experience where you enter the house of Woodcock from Phantom Thread.
And you this actually got branching pathways.
So you either go to the like dress fitting experience
where you get like an immaculate couture dress made for you or you get the
I'm working or romantically involved with Woodcock experience
where it's like a nightmare.
But then towards the end, you realize that like you can control this nightmare.
Like maybe it's a nightmare both ways.
You get to eat the special.
And of course, the food you get to eat the special mushrooms.
Oh, man. You're flat.
And it's like and the long order and the bacon.
Yeah. And then you can.
I mean, you got to like even galaxy says his t-shirt.
So you can have a buy t-shirt that says like
I went to Port Thomas Anderson and all I got was flat on my back.
Sick with docile, you know, like whatever she says about him.
I you know, there's other stuff.
There's a there'll be an attraction where you can beat up a bathroom
like from punch, drunk love.
It resets itself. Yeah.
Yeah. Screens.
You just like, yeah.
And you get the score at the end.
What else did you beat up the bathroom?
Mm hmm. I like what I like about this is this is all like modest budget.
I think, too. You can do this.
You don't have to do a biggie tickets like the Kevin Smith
tweet ride is any ticket.
It's a massive, massive show building.
It's a little more.
Maybe there's some more interactive, like theater elements.
You know, I the licensing on inherent vice might get a little complicated
or there will be blood that I feel like you could do a ride.
You could do like a scene by scene.
There will be blood ride.
Well, you could feel I mean, Geyser Mountain.
They you do you do guys are out there.
We got blasted out of an oil well.
But then also a bowling alley where you're doing bowling.
But then part of it is to like escape without Daniel bludgeoning you to getting
smashed. Yeah.
Milk. Yeah. You can have the mushrooms, omelet and the milkshake.
You know, and then like you do like superstar television, Boogie Nights style
show where your mom and dad get picked to come out of the audience.
And then it's like, you know, you get you get where it goes from there.
Yeah. And Hard Eight Casino.
OK, sure. There's a walk around Sydney.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's fantastic.
And then just a stage of Hame impersonators.
Oh, Haim. Haim.
Excuse me. I never get it right.
Haim impersonate like Haim face character Haim sisters.
Reenacting the videos in front of like a screen like the
Mandalorian screen set.
So it looks like they're walking down Ventura Boulevard by the book.
Oh, yeah. By the one Barnes and Nobles with a marquee.
They can slide different streets, different valleys, different parts of the
San Fernando Valley. Yeah, that's great.
What do I want to do?
Let's get let's do Kelly Port.
Let's do a Richard Kelly.
Yes. I thought you were either going David E.
Kelly. Oh, that sounds good.
Then you get is that like Ali McBeal?
L.A. law.
I mean, hey, why not?
Yeah. Sorry.
You know, well, all the Kelly's can be in this.
So you choose a path.
Do you go to David Kellyport and get to have a big party with the dancing baby?
Or do you go to Richard Kellyport and get on the mega zeppelin
from the finale of Southland Tales?
Finally live your own Southland Tale.
Yeah. And and that, too.
There's a superstar limo of or not a superstar, a superstar television of
where you get inserted into a porn with.
Oh, right. Right. Sarah Michelle Geller. Right.
Sure. What's her name?
I can't. As if anyone would know.
Get your Southland Tales knowledge out.
Get the body. He did.
Krista Kapowski, Krista now, obviously.
Oh, of course. Yeah, of course. Of course. Of course.
Oh, it's like I was really I had an intimate moment with boxer Santeros.
Boxer Santeros, I probably could have pulled if I sat here
long enough.
The I mean, you get to live the experience of the box.
2009 adaptation of that in the box short story, you get to open the box,
you know, where it's like you get one million dollars if you press the button.
But someone dies.
Hmm. I don't like Richard.
He stole Boxer Santero.
Boxer Santeros was a cut pod racer.
He stole it.
Oh, man. It should be all directors from now on.
They get their own land.
You know, he's going forward.
Well, they had the right idea then, and they've gotten off the trail.
It's time. It's it's time to get back and it's time to build the dick boner.
Quite frankly.
Man, here's an early 2000s ass memory
buying Donnie Darko on DVD in high school.
Everyone's getting their mind blown watching it in someone's basement.
Oh, yeah.
Taking it to college, realizing everyone else had the Donnie Darko DVD
because it was always on sale for five to ten dollars.
Shortly, a year or two into college,
going over to the Repertory Cinema to watch the Donnie Darko
Director's Cut release, despite all of us watching it so many times on DVD already.
You were that in the Darko. Whoa.
Everyone was excited for Darko, my man.
Everyone loved Darko.
I saw once and I was it didn't I'm not trying to be cool or anything.
I just was now I was like, oh, yeah, OK.
Mm hmm. I was not way into dark.
I was way in this Kevin Smith.
I'm not, you know, I'm just saying it's interesting.
Yeah. Were you into Garden State?
I like to garden state.
Yeah, I thought Garden State was Braffport.
Braffport. Braffport for sure.
It's the well, that's you're just you're you get in, you strap on,
and then you're given headphones and you send you're told that this is going
to change your life, I swear.
And then you feel what it's like for your life to change forever.
Because you heard it. Yeah.
A sharing is creepy by the shins.
I mean, that's how you guys feel, right?
Like your lives change forever as soon as you're it'll change your life.
I swear. As soon as I heard the song or saw the movie.
No, the mid the song song, the song.
Oh, yeah. That song I had been listening to the same.
Oh, for that album, I had gotten three years before two or three years before.
Yeah, sure.
Well, look, Mike, maybe you could learn a lesson on the Scrubs ride
that you can't do this all on your own.
You're Superman.
You want these personalized right?
It's true.
I would like to see.
Yes, I would like to see that the Scrubs theme song,
I'm No Superman be visualized in a ride.
That's what I actually Jason brings up a very good point
that if you could show me the lyrics with robots,
that would be great.
There's we have fears that Lucasport would be dated, but Braffport
when installed in 2005, I think would be some things are timeless.
Braffport sounds real, actually.
Now the more we say it, the guy I'm going up to Braffport for the weekend.
You're like, oh, yeah. Where is that again?
It's Northern California, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Northern sounds kind of Wisconsin to me a little bit.
Yeah, perhaps. Yeah.
My parents in Braffport.
Yeah, one of those little islands, South Dakota. Yeah.
Yeah. Braffport.
It's kind of it's good.
It's good. It's fine.
Braffport holds it.
Everything closes at nine.
Really early eight. Yeah.
Well, that I guess.
Happy May the fourth.
Happy May.
Well, that was all that was all over the map.
We chose a lot of different.
We've fled and we and we fought.
We did it all.
You survived podcast, the ride Lucasport edition.
And again, I know it's going to get rowdy this year for May the fourth.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Just try to, you know, not
try to not lose your mind.
Yeah. Look, those these those helmets are constrictive.
And if you vomit inside them,
you get you get trapped with your own vomit.
You passed out.
Is there any new Star Wars stuff right now?
There's no one coming.
Oh, we want coming out soon.
Star Wars celebration is happening soon.
That's right. Is that the first one back?
I think it might be.
Yeah, I would like to go to that.
Well, people people have been talking about.
And this was already a phenomenon before Covid Coachella cough.
It's just that there is an art.
I read an article about this last night where it's like some people get
they just spend so much time eating, you know, getting that desert dust in their lungs.
They come back from Coachella with a cough.
And now this year, people came back from the return to Coachella
with either that or Covid-19.
Will there be a Star Wars celebration cough?
Yes. The answer is yes.
Oh, OK. The answer is yes.
And it's concrete.
We people always thought San Diego Comic Con.
People always talk about coming back from that a little fluid.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Force flu.
I got the it's not Covid.
It's just a little bit of force flu.
Yeah. Yeah. No, that'll that'll happen anyway.
I would like to go to it.
I did recently ask about press passes.
It was too late.
I was told no.
So we tried.
That's not an episode coming.
That is not an episode of Star Wars celebration.
So, yeah, anyway, sorry, we fucked up.
But other episodes coming soon.
Coming soon. Yes, for sure.
Keep it tuned here. Thanks, everybody.
Goodbye. Bye.