Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following podcast requires your participation.
While the hosts do most of the work, you must mentally help steer their conversation and
keep them from veering off topic.
Your paddles are your positive thoughts.
You'll know you failed if they go on a lengthy, uncomfortable detour about high school swimming.
Now let's get ready to row.
It's Davy Crockett's Explorer Canoes on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about theme parks hosted by three guys who will soon
be bragging about exerting mild physical effort for nine minutes.
I'm Scott Gardner, one of those guys joined by Mike Carlson.
Hi.
Hi, yes, I'm Mike Carlson.
Did you mean 90 minutes?
Because that's how long I would like to brag about doing something physical.
We will be.
Okay, we did exert physical effort for nine minutes and we will be talking about it for
night.
The nine minutes was on the ride we're talking about today.
Davy Crockett's Explorer Canoes, which we will discuss for 90 minutes.
I think most of that will be bragging about, you know, pivoting our arms slightly.
Right.
And like just like feeling like the bicep pump, you know, because like Arnold Schwarzenegger
in the famous movie, I think Pumping Iron was always talking about the pump.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
I've never seen Pumping Iron, but I would imagine from the title that pumping.
And I don't want to get too body here today already, but I guess I have to now because
he's like talking about like the pump is like an orgasm.
He says that.
Okay.
I'm going to say when we're talking about just a general paddling, we're going to be
like, you know, the paddle is as good as an orgasm.
I assume that's sort of the type of thing we're all sharing.
But I don't know.
I guess we'll bring Jason into this discussion.
Jason Sheridan.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't know how I feel about all that.
Okay.
Well, I guess the first thing to decide is are we using the word pump because we're kind
of pumping or is it paddling?
Is the paddling is like a pump, which is like, I mean, I think proper respect.
You know, to the attraction would be paddling.
Okay.
But I know Mike seems really enthusiastic about this pump situation.
So every paddle gives us a pop, which is like a pump.
Yeah, that's that's a good compromise.
I'd like to say that we can use anything anywhere that starts with P to describe the paddling
motion.
So as long as it's P, I think it's all on the table today just to keep it a very it
so we don't say the same word over and over.
I am glad that we're again at Forever Dog Studios, beautiful Forever Dog Studios in
North Hollywood, but where hopefully the with better mics and more professional setup, the
constant P and saying pop, which causes a pop of itself.
I might be doing it every time.
I don't really know.
But I feel like I'd be more likely to, you know, over Zoom, less professional.
The technology, the technology here at Forever Dog.
The P is not even something to worry about.
They have they have some some system that takes the popping problem and it fixes it.
Well, so I can say pop and P and pump.
Say pop P and pump.
And podcast the ride as much as.
Yep.
Jason, you can say P pod.
You can say any sort of different.
Pooh poo.
Yeah.
And everything's going to be fine because of this new system that Forever Dog, only
podcast company that has this.
The other one is P is a bad ear wall.
You're getting a little Trump in there.
You're getting a little and they're the only ones that the only ones that have this.
The only ones.
Let me tell you.
I will tell you this and let me tell you.
Yeah, no, I don't.
I don't care for that man.
I'm just imagining the psycho who's like listening to podcasts and is like, yeah, they're popping
their peas.
These motherfuckers.
Well, I'm sure some.
Waking them snap.
Yeah.
So but not but not for Forever Dog podcasts because there's no P problem.
I'll give it for Wait, wait, don't tell me, you weirdo.
Yeah.
Mad weirdo.
So many P pops.
Unlistenable.
Forever Forever Dog.
And then the then the phrase is under it.
It just says no P problem.
And that's how the advertising is based, like to get new podcasts on the network.
No poppy peas.
That's right.
Yeah.
Today is about Davy Crockett's Explorer Canoes, the canoe ride at Disneyland.
I say canoe ride, but it's not it's not a canoe themed ride.
It is canoes.
It's canoes that you go on.
These have been at a lot of the Disney parks over the years.
They don't all have them currently, but Disneyland has had them almost since the beginning.
And it's it's possibly a possibly a thing that people don't realize is an option.
I think that's very overlooked that I think we've done very rare.
I've done very rarely that you can take a nice canoe ride with a bunch of folks in your
during your day at Disneyland.
Yes.
I think most people most people when they see the canoes going around sort of like behind
or in front of or Mark Twain River Boat or the big pirate ship, I think they probably
assume that's performers.
Maybe that's what I thought.
They're initially well, not their animatronics, but they're I mean, that would be cool if
they like atmospheric.
Yeah.
Or something like that.
That's a bunch of Disneyland employees going around in a canoe paddling and not.
But then there's like a bunch of people in them and different clothes.
But most people aren't paying attention.
And maybe I wasn't paying attention initially.
You really thought at some point in time that this was an illusion done by a bunch of uncoordinated
of different ages.
Like people in XXL won in a minion shirts paddling.
You thought those were cast like those were plants.
I'm saying like maybe initially when I went to Disneyland and I wasn't paying attention,
I wasn't leaning against the railing, looking out into the water and noticing, OK, there's
an eight year old in the boat.
There's are in the canoe.
There's a 50 year old like I didn't.
They're just it's atmosphere.
It's something you're not paying attention.
You just saw canoes.
I didn't know what was for me.
I didn't know that was possible because it's not something they heavily advertise.
It's not certainly you never see that on a billboard as you're driving on the five south.
There's never been a billboard.
There was a sign.
There was a sign at the entrance ramp like a standalone sign, which I don't know if I've
ever seen before.
Like you mean to get to the canoe to get to the canoes.
There's a sign that said Davy Crockett Explorer Canoes, which is where I learned they're called
Davy Crockett Explorer Canoes named after the legendary psycho Davy Crockett.
I don't know anything.
Was Davy Crockett bad?
I'm sure if he's a man, if it's a man who lived before, you know, really any time he's
a man in 2005, after which all men are great.
But they are now perfect, but they were bad before 2005.
You can imagine if you can remember back that famous on the frontier or famous in the old
West, you're already like, what's it going to be?
I feel like when we talked about the Mike Fink keel boats, there was some crazy stuff
in there about all these guys.
Yeah.
And that was like that was a show.
There's a Disney song that they still play in the parks.
I think Davy Crockett theme or whatever.
They start to sing it at the end of Country Bears.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Yes.
In Florida still.
But he was, you know, they superheroed him in Walt's day and on Disney television and
stuff and he's just the left.
They haven't.
This is one of those rides where they haven't noticed it's still there.
I feel like.
So it hasn't been rethemed or anything.
It's still like Davy Crockett and no one like other than old people like know what that
is at this point.
Yeah, it just sounds like the atmosphere.
Like just if you call something the Hoot and Holler, it sounds like an old West thing.
You wouldn't know. Oh, there was a series called Hoot and Holler that ran from 67 to
63.
Right. And I guess Davy Crockett, like this, I guess Davy Crockett was his main.
Did he ride a horse?
Probably rode a horse. Right.
Well, what a great history podcast.
Yeah. So Davy Crockett probably rode a horse.
He had to ride a horse. Right.
I think there was a horse business.
Everyone rode a horse.
I think there was some canoe business, some boat business.
So he had like, OK, I'm just trying to put this into something that I can understand.
Like he had a Batmobile and a Batboat.
So Davy Crockett had like multiple probably.
I'm not sure that Davy Crockett had a canoe.
Is the real. I was trying to find other.
There was no proof that he ever was in a canoe.
It happened on the show.
I think they just well, they needed to rename it something that they had.
Yeah, they need an area.
They needed to rename it something less horrifying that it's opening day.
Yeah. So, yeah.
Well, look, it opened as the Indian War Canoes.
Yes. Not good.
No. On July 4th, 1956.
On the day on Independence Day, they opened the Indian War Canoes.
Which was like, OK, it was part of a greater area
that used to be where bear country is now called the Indian Village.
And that was a Disneyland for the first couple of decades of its run.
And you might say that Walt Disney did not have the best read on the culture.
An excerpt that I found from the you might if you can you imagine that?
Yeah. According.
This is an excerpt from the book More Mouse Tales by David Koenig.
OK, the Indian War Canoes.
Walt insisted only authentic Native Americans operate the canoes
and adjacent Indian village where they created sand paintings
and perform ceremonial dances.
He even went Walt went to a Navajo reservation to recruit them.
Unaware that Navajos are from the desert and none had the slightest idea
how to paddle or steer a canoe.
So he just took an arbitrary like, yeah, you guys, right?
Did no research about the tribe or where they generally
lived or what they don't believe this.
Walt Disney didn't know the nuances and didn't know the difference
between different Native American cultures.
That's great. I can't believe it was not.
Yeah. And there were like Native American performers at Disneyland
for many years. Yeah.
Where you could like where like I've seen like different debates of like,
obviously, some people were like, this sucks.
Why is this is Disneyland?
And it sucks in the sense that like you're exploiting Native American culture
for your Mickey Mouse Park.
Mm hmm. But then other people are like, well, there was some representation.
So sure. As opposed to then how it played out, which is this was.
So it was an attraction, the rare attraction where there was the like
there was a rule about it, like that it had to be
a Navajo Navajo man, I guess, two restrictions there.
It'd be a male Navajo piloting the canoe.
And then very bravely in the 70s, Disney
allowed anybody to.
So, yeah, in a glorious move,
white people were allowed to finally steer the canoes.
Well, a very progressive decision.
Yes, specifically very jacked people usually doing this.
Well, that's yeah, that's a thing.
And I've only been on this canoe trip twice.
Everyone who does it is very good shape because they are just canoe
paddling all day. Yeah.
Yeah. I didn't realize.
I feel like I am tricked once again by Disney boats,
because I talked about piloting the Mark Twain once quickly realizing like,
oh, this steering wheel does nothing.
Why am I whole gripping it like death gripping it?
It's on a track. What am I thinking?
Mark Twain is on a track.
Yeah, the Mark Twain and the Columbia are on tracks.
When you were driving and you get the certificate.
Yeah. Oh, you thought you were actually moving?
For a split second, I was like really, really, really
really holding on to it.
I'm like, what am I? Wait, what am I doing?
Like I can like step back.
Well, was that instinct or was that because you actually thought I'm going to steer this thing?
It was the pirates and I knew I didn't do anything because I kind of jerked it once just to double check.
You tried to crash the Mark Twain just to see what would happen.
We were in a big open area and I was like, does this do anything?
Like, does it wiggle it a little?
Because, you know, I've heard there's antique cars at a lot of amusement parks where like
you steer it a little, they're on a track, but you like a little.
Yeah, like Autopia.
My old control.
You thought maybe you could like take it up and on to Splash Mountain or something.
I didn't go that far, but this one is a functioning boat.
You are paddling, but on the official Disneyland website, it says, no, before you go,
the boats are lightweight and most of the paddling is more for fun than actual propulsion.
While your help is appreciated, the river guides who sit in the fore and aft of the canoe
are capable of navigating the waters by themselves.
So like you don't have to do a lot, but the first time I did this,
the vibe from the cast members were never stop paddling.
Never stop.
We got to do this.
And my arms hurt like all day.
Yeah.
Well, you warned us.
I had the desire to do this and maybe do an episode about it.
You were very like, just so you know, your arms will hurt all day.
But then we had very leisurely like laissez faire paddlers.
They had a lot of breaks built in.
They were talking to us a lot and it was much more pleasant.
It was a much more pleasant experience, although we did do this on the hot dog day.
Yes.
Yeah.
But I think there was I think we were only three hot dogs in by that, which is one per.
So we were not wrecked yet.
Towards the end of the day, it could have been more of a problem, but I did like that.
It felt like a necessary pairing.
If we're going to eat hot dogs all day, exert mild physical effort for nine minutes.
Yeah.
We were not so full by the end of the day.
Maybe it would have been worse, but I don't know.
I feel like I could have paddled at the end of the day.
Sure.
Well, knowing what it was, which now I, you know, you gave that warning, Jason,
that was my recollection as well.
That maybe the last time that I did this and I may have been 13 years old,
that it utterly wore me out.
I also, a couple things there, it might have been in the dead heat of summer when I imagine
it might be a little unpleasant to do this canoe attraction at any point, at any age,
any physical capability.
But I also, I think something occurred to me while doing it and realizing it was pretty mild,
that I was a weak ass 13 year old.
Sure.
I think I was in really, really terrible shape.
Do you think, we were all in bad shape at 13.
I think there's no denying that.
And are not, by the way.
Well, now nobody's an Arnold style pumper.
Who's pumping now?
We're all checking ourselves on the monitor.
And now we wait, are we?
I don't know.
Maybe I am in good shape.
Let's see everybody, I or everybody flex.
I will say I did do a pull up a couple months ago, a single pull up.
And I was like, oh good, I can do a pull up like still.
Oh good.
And it took me forever to be able to do a pull up because in elementary school,
I remember kids would be doing pull ups and I was just, just like,
like the most comical version of like making noises and I couldn't do it.
My scrawny arms could not pull me up.
And then I do remember in high school at one point, I did a pull up and I was like, whoa, what?
Something happened.
The change happened.
I did a lot of hangs.
Sure.
Like, just hold on for getting up there.
It's usually was a little high for me getting up there was half the battle.
Did you have, because you would do, you would do different challenges.
We had the bent arm hang to see how long you could hang.
It wasn't a pull up.
And then you hung, it was just hold on to your arms and see how long you could do.
That's what I'm saying.
They would usually pivot to like, oh, this one ain't doing a pull up.
Yeah.
So what can we do that still feels like you crossed some kind of threshold?
You achieved something.
Yeah.
Gotcha.
How long we talking on these bent arm?
I'm trying to remember.
I feel like I was actually pretty good at the bent arm hang.
I could hang for a while, but I feel like maybe it was like 47 seconds or something,
which seems not the long time.
Yeah.
No, but I have a feeling that if I tried a bent arm hang, I would be saying pretty quickly,
was that 47 seconds?
Did I beat Mike?
And they've been somebody, anyone timing, timing me would say, no, that was eight.
It was eight seconds.
Uh-huh.
You have six more of these to go.
Should we challenge each other to physical challenges during this episode?
I think so.
I don't think we're, well,
There's not a lot of room in here.
We could, I think we're sort of near a recreation area.
We'd have to, we could like go do a jog, see what's there in terms that could test our
abilities and jog back and then see how, not just who did the best, but who is like too
wrecked to continue.
My bet would be all of us.
That the entire, it'd be a good thing to utilize this video that we're using right now.
For us to suddenly leave and then come back just wrecked, just drenched in sweat.
Beat red.
Yeah.
We, you know, it's just running up, you know, there's Universal Studios is not too far from here
and running up the hill off of Lancashire maybe is what we should be doing.
We should run up because there's usually a tram that takes you up there.
Yeah.
The run would be rough.
The run would be insane.
Yeah, the walk is awful.
Walking up it is insane.
The walk is bad.
I did it when I was like, I'm just going to do the walk.
It's a nice day out.
It was like the middle of summer.
No, that was the worst idea.
If you fall, you will roll down the hill like a barrel, like it's screwed.
Like you don't do it.
It's really dangerous.
I haven't been so concerned about the fall.
I don't think I'm going to.
You're also falling in a way that you don't just face plant.
You don't just go forward.
You would have to fall to the side and then, and then the roll would have to continue.
You'd have to be so even on that slant for it to become a full roll all the way down.
Okay.
Well, you're trying to like angle it so you end up in the Sheraton.
Like you stop the fall by like pushing yourself into the Sheraton valet port coche.
In your in your dream of this, you're rolling down the hill in a little ball.
You like hit like a curb or so or hit a bump and you just break through the window of one
of the hotel rooms and land in the bed and fall asleep immediately.
Well, you've flasked it up for sure.
And then you don't have to pay for the room.
You got to go up a couple stories that you have to hit a bounce that perfectly gummy
bear bounce style launches you up to like the fourth floor at least.
I don't remember where sloppy Telly's room was.
Telly's is probably sweet at the Sheraton.
Probably at the top floor, right?
No, I think he might've been the second.
I think he wanted to like, it's just a quick walk down the stairs.
And now I'm here at the bar, baby.
I don't have to I don't have to take that eight second elevator ride.
Yeah, it's the Telly's only 10 steps away from the swig of vodka at all times.
I can get down to that stinky lobby real quick.
Did you see there was a thing going around a couple months ago?
If you don't know, we're talking about during the Universal City Walk saga.
We we were talking about how Telly Savalas, star of Kojak, lived at the Sheraton Universal.
If you don't know what we're talking about, what Kojak is and we really.
Yeah, sorry. You have to look it up.
He also had a singing career that I've been fascinated by lately.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, some really good videos.
But he had a bar, the bar, he would go to the bar at the Sheraton like every night
because he lived there and they called it Telly's still called Telly's.
But there was some article like People Magazine or something where he was just like,
yeah, I've had affairs and my wife isn't happy.
It was like the headline on the thing.
That's not exactly what it was.
But it was like some major publication and he was just like, yeah, I cheat on my wife.
So what, baby?
Really interesting.
Honest.
Really interesting man.
Appreciate the honesty.
Yeah.
There's maybe another thing to talk about at the right.
So this seemed like a fun thing to do that we're going there for our hot dog day.
And then what's I think, Mike, you threw out what's an attraction
we've not done on the show or done altogether.
And this seemed like a fun one to do because it's involved and interactive.
And so we were excited to do it.
We went to go do it.
We're on the stairs heading down to grab our paddles and for our canoe ride to begin.
And then Jason says, with a lot of judgment, I feel.
So this is main feed, right?
This is main feed.
Yeah.
Very.
What's wrong?
Answering the not posing it for debate, but asserting not since Lucy attribute,
I think, has there been this kind of jockeying for the main feed?
Yeah.
The almost anger that it would be asserted any other way.
I got another one coming up.
There's another one coming out that I think could be topical.
Something is finally returned.
One of the final things to return.
OK.
And you're saying it a main feed and not on our picture.
I think I'm curious to see what everyone's opinion is.
We just get it out now.
What do we do?
The red car trolleys finally coming back to Disney's California Adventure.
Main feed.
Yeah.
Because Suitcase and a Dream is involved in that.
Oh, that's true.
Am I finally at my day of reckoning of having to deal even more with Suitcase and a Dream?
Suitcase and a Dream will be unpacked.
If you don't know what we're talking about, it's a song that is like kind of a techno beat,
but it's about Newsies and them singing about Mickey Mouse coming to California.
And we've talked about this like the kayfabe Mickey origin where he met Walt on a train.
It's like Walt didn't create him, but they were like two bums on a train and they teamed up
basically.
So this is a song about having a suitcase and a dream.
I think that means that's coming back or we don't know?
I don't know.
OK.
I don't know about live entertainment.
But we will talk about this red trolley on main feed.
Historic in the Los Angeles area.
This city was just covered in red car trolley lines for years.
Yeah, but not this specific vehicle.
Not this one.
It's paying tribute to the historic red car trolley, which you cannot navigate, right?
They don't let you drive that.
Drive what?
They do Mark Twain.
The red car trolley.
Oh, no.
No, because those controls are functioning.
Uh-huh.
Sure.
I was just wondering if there was some fake steering wheel or something.
I don't think so.
I guess they don't have a steering wheel.
That was kind of what you said about this.
I feel like then a brief rationalization of it was like historic.
And you like banged your arm like that a little bit.
Well, I feel like sometimes we get a little tickled with our little second gay weirdo episodes.
We do get a little tickled.
I agree.
I find myself reaching sometimes of like, yeah, what's the main feed?
In theory, the main episodes of this podcast.
And I'm like, yeah, carousel.
But then suddenly it's like, you know, Lucille Ball did a voice on an episode of Rescue Range.
That didn't happen, obviously.
Because we would shut this down and go watch it right now.
Yeah, absolutely.
We would talk about it every episode.
Yeah.
Well, then I got home, talked about having a nice canoe experience.
And Aaron said, oh, that's nice.
You guys are going to do a second gate about it.
And I was like, oh, yeah, well, it's a whole thing.
It came up.
We had a little tip about it.
And I guess it's going to be on the main feed.
Yeah.
So no, I don't mind this.
I'm just I just thought it was a very us moment for that discussion to be that question to be posed.
Sure.
Yeah.
So here we are.
Here we are.
No paywall.
It's happening.
Yeah.
Video for you.
Yes.
On video.
I keep forgetting that's there.
Yeah.
That's good.
Turn your back to it or else you'll be.
It's like Celebrity Big Brother or something.
You're wondering where my eye line is.
It is staring at this.
It is odd.
It's like having a fourth person in the room and it's a three headed monster.
That is all of us.
Right.
And find a new eye line.
I try not to look.
Yeah.
Camera.
I think it'd be much weirder to just look in the camera the whole time.
The first time.
Yeah, that is weird.
That is.
Yeah.
If you're watching on video right now, let's all look into the camera.
Our own different cameras.
Give everyone a nice stare.
Okay.
Jason, find yours.
And.
Everyone listening.
You know.
Shut up and hold your pose.
Hold your pose.
Okay.
Now we just need to give everybody a frame.
Yeah.
Got it.
Okay.
Creepy frame.
What were you saying?
I was going to say everyone listening on their phones is just like I love when they
talk about the video set up.
Yeah, they do like that.
Well, it's new and they're going to learn to like it.
Yeah, that's just because we run the show here.
Okay.
We tell them.
We tell you what to like.
Let's talk about our experience.
And you know what?
Let's use the medium for the people watching the YouTube link.
Brett, can we pull up a photo of us having a blast on this canoe?
This is a post Jason and his hot dog mountain shirt.
Yeah.
This is a great little slide show.
Wonderful picture.
Let's hold on this one for a second.
This I feel like is a Jason in his element.
Not just in a hot dog mountain shirt, but just past the Mark Twain knowing that you're
feeling the Mark Twain's in the air.
The smoke stacks are blowing a familiar smoke to you.
You're out on the high seat.
This is a very satisfied Jason, I feel.
Sure.
Yeah.
Are you as happy here as you appear to be?
I think I am.
I think I finally relaxed at this point.
I realized I didn't have to paddle as much.
Were you cheating?
Was I cheating?
Yeah.
No, I was full on paddling.
But at the start of it, I was really pushing.
I see.
Because the other time I went, it was like there weren't that, but there was a lot of
kids in the boat.
So whatever adults were there, it's just like, oh shit, we actually have to do this.
We had to move this boat.
I had not seen the website where they're like, yeah, you idiots don't really have,
you can just play paddle, whatever.
Well, I was wondering what the situation was.
That's interesting that they're public about that we are ballast and we don't matter.
Where you maybe figure that out is the steering.
The fact that you are turning and pivoting, and yet there's no point where the main canoe
operator in the front is saying, all right, now you guys on the right a little less than
you guys on the left a little more so that we turn and pivot a little.
The direction you're going is always very good.
You're maybe vaguely hoping with forward momentum since it is a long vehicle, but
steering, I feel like, is never...
You're not doing anything to help the direction.
No.
Yeah, there's no way.
Because that way you would crash into Splash Mountain or something.
You would definitely hit the wall.
It's like they were like, all right, here's what we got to do.
Which the mechanics of this are very impressive that it's two folks, it's no more than two
people, one in the front and one in the back.
That they are making a 20 person pretty long vehicle move and steering it and doing it
over and over again.
We did it once and now we're talking about it for a while.
This is just their job.
They do this many, many times.
When I was paddling, Scott, were you putting a lot of effort into it when you were paddling?
How do you much...
Do you feel like you were taking it easy?
I wanted to maybe just feel a little burn.
A little pump, yeah.
Get my little pump pop.
At least a little pump.
Just feel a little something to say I did.
If I feel like I was doing it, I feel like the first time I did it, I was doing it in
an inefficient way.
I feel like I was doing a big like really trying to do that, which I think that's a mistake.
You do like...
Form than the actual...
Yeah, I think I feel like I had really good form this time and I was actually expelling less energy.
I think I was really helping.
I was really helping the journey, I feel.
Yeah, did you feel like were you judging yourself against other canoers and us?
Yes.
While you're behind me, you're next to Jason, you've got a better...
Was I behind you?
Not directly.
Jason's right behind you.
I was behind Scott.
Because I wasn't looking...
I was next to Mike.
I wasn't critiquing you or Jason as far as you're paddling because I couldn't see,
but I was looking at the people in front of me and I was saying,
I'm doing better than them.
I'm paddling better than them.
Yeah.
I was as well, but the person in front of me was a child,
so I felt like the rhythm was not there.
No, yeah.
I'm willing to forgive.
So you smoked that little kid.
Absolutely.
You showed them who's boss.
Yeah, yeah.
Not with might, not with physical, but just with understanding pattern and meter.
Really, it's music if you think about it.
Paddling a canoe.
It rhymes.
Having paddled a canoe once, what I always say about it is that it's music.
Yes, it rhymes.
It rhymes, yeah.
Very lyrical.
I kept poking the kid in front of me and going, do better, do better.
And he just wouldn't do better.
So I was poking him with the paddle while I was on the middle stroke.
We had a canoe.
My high school gym had a pool in it, and I feel like there was a metal canoe
that they would throw in the pool at some point.
During the two weeks we were in the pool and they're like,
now we're going to fill the canoe with water and now you got to swim to the side of the pool.
It's basically fuck around the canoe for a couple days.
I don't really quite even remember paddling it or anything.
We're going to throw a canoe in the fucking high school pool.
We're going to throw, yeah.
Whatever.
Enjoy.
Seems like enough, right?
The pool wasn't that big.
I mean, it was a regulation size pool.
I'm trying to think how big my pool, did you have a pool in high school?
I don't, I truly don't remember.
This is how checked out of athletics I was.
You would know.
I don't think I know.
I cannot picture if my high school had a pool.
Did you swim though in gym class ever?
No.
Okay.
It'd be weird if I said I didn't remember a pool, but I did remember swimming.
Yeah, well that would be very odd.
That would be in a toilet.
We had.
My head was flushed in one.
We had to swim.
We had to swim in gym class.
Did you have to swim in gym class?
Yeah, we had to swim in gym class and it was the later,
I feel like the first couple of years in gym class, it was all dudes.
And then the more honors classes like I had, like the gym class would be like,
all right, it's this gym class is all the nerds.
Wait, they were your high school was divided by nerds and jocks.
Are they all?
Well, but like in like an administrative.
Just in terms of like the timing where it's like, all right, if they're taking this AP
and this AP, like the only time they can take gym.
So they all end up in gym together.
I see.
So so like all the nerds won't hurt each other.
The jocks.
Basically, yeah, that was much more pleasant.
So you weren't in AP canoeing then?
I was not in AP canoeing.
No, I was in the nerd gym class where everyone was like, please, no one.
We've all made an agreement.
No one look at each other's bodies like.
Oh, well, that was because in the old to the sky in the old days, the kids would swim nude.
What?
Yes.
How old old days?
The 60s.
I don't know that.
What are you talking about?
There was no any type of short like I think Huck and Tom would.
I don't know that.
Hold on.
I'm pretty sure that I'm correct here.
But kids, I didn't know 1960.
No, I don't want to get arrested.
I'm just trying to get his friends, the family from Tuck Everlasting would swim nude at the
old swimming hole and you would realize they weren't aging.
I'm pretty sure I'm right.
Yeah.
Swimming naked.
My high school team did, says Chicago.
Now, I'm pretty sure there's a lot old family members of mine talked about this unless they
were punking me, which is possible, I guess.
I guess I'm gullible.
So you get so you take you strip nude and get in that.
I Mikey, I did not swim nude, but I think there was a time when certain high schools
were like the boys would swim nude.
Why?
Why would this?
What would this help?
What would this solve?
I don't know.
What is one benefit other than to particular creeps who work at the school?
How is it?
I don't know.
Saving precious fabric money.
54 cents.
This is like mild covering.
Critic boarding scandal nightmare.
I'm finding multiple articles about this being something that people would have to do,
not of probably our generation, but of older generation.
My we didn't even share like everyone would just walk through the shower,
like rinse off after swimming.
No one was like stripping down.
Like I never took like a shower after gym or whatever in school.
I have no recollection.
Well, I didn't take a shower.
I didn't take a shower after regular gym.
You would go through the shower after swim class, but you would keep most kids would
keep the suit.
Except one or two guys who are like, I'm going to be the naked guy.
I am the captain of the football team.
I look like I'm 25 years old.
I'm going to get naked.
It's true in gyms though still.
Some people really thrive on being the naked guy.
Yeah.
That was my chance.
But what era do you and when did this change?
I am an expert on nude swimming for high school boys.
I just know that there were certain high schools where this happened
and I've heard tell of it.
And were they firebombed?
Did they have their rights revoked to be a high school?
I don't know if there was a naked high school registry.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know.
If you want to do a second gate about this topic, we can.
I will go and research it.
And see, but this is the good old days.
This isn't some horror show like children checking out books from the library.
Like our current dystopia.
This is just, I think this was just what was done in certain areas.
Yeah.
This was not a weird bad thing.
And no one thought it was weird or bad.
Kid crotch Arkansas.
Look, when I was, I swear I heard about this when I was young and I was like,
this is crazy.
What is going on?
Why would you ever do that?
Hey, hurry along kid.
We're trying to put asbestos in.
Get to your nude swimming class.
The painters are coming to put on a new coat of lead paint.
Look, not our generation.
I swam with little red shorts like Mickey Mouse.
Okay.
We wore little buttons.
They wouldn't let us swim with our own shorts.
Also, was that what your experience was?
Wait, no, what is this?
Well, we were supposed to wear the school colors for our regular gym clothes,
which were maroon and gray.
So like anything maroon and gray, you know, shorts or sweatpants and a t-shirt for swim class.
They were just like, oh, fuck it.
Just whatever swimsuit you have.
Who cares?
No, we had to wear new short, like their shorts that they washed as if they were like the
glasses on Transformers.
We had to put on new red, little red swim trunks every time.
Little red, every uniformed little red trunks.
They were shorter trunks than I like to wear it, at least at the time.
So lining up, getting your shorts line.
Yes, you would have to get in a shorts line.
You would be handed shorts.
Did you request a size or was it kind of one size?
Yes, there would be a size.
There would be different, I think there would be different like bags
and you would get different size shorts.
You'd say large and they'd say no, extra small and you'd say, oh, maybe next time.
Yeah, they would say that doesn't look as good on you.
They would assess it.
Here, spin around.
No, change to the extra small.
So yeah, you would get shorts and then you would put them in a big thing and they would wash them.
I don't know why you couldn't wear your own swim trunks.
That's crazy.
Yeah, this is my experience swimming in high school.
Did anyone get in the big washing machine with all of the used shorts?
It's like a prank.
Then you know, really?
No, no, no.
I mean, so like, I'm just going to I just need to clean the machine and then why are they in there for the washing?
You mean they're like a pervert?
Yeah.
Okay.
They're like, you know, something was really up at your high school.
Somebody that guy was a holdover from the 60s era.
Oh, like with the nude swimming.
Yeah.
No, I don't remember anyone doing that, but I was honestly the part where you would turn them in and
take them off and put all that was like, I wanted to get that done as fast as possible
because it was so strange because you would have to like.
Shorts check in.
Yeah.
Turn in your sopping wet shorts into this bin.
Yes.
This is what I did.
Like this is I would have to like you put the towel around.
I was so nervous about it and like pull the thing off.
Community shorts, everyone.
Yeah.
I did think it was weird because you were wearing like, hopefully they were washing these things.
This is communism.
It was a way to teach you why your socialism is bad.
This is what happens.
Now you all end up wearing shorts instead of buying your own.
It was the closest thing I had.
Like we had to like school uniforms or something.
You didn't have school uniforms.
No, you had to share Mickey style red shorts.
We had to we wore Mickey style red swim trunks.
And then did the gym teacher have to do a load of reds?
Like a lot of laundry.
Someone did.
Every day.
Every day they would supposedly wash our swim, our little red swim trunks.
You know, I do remember the gym teacher's office had washer dryers in it.
And I think it was for like, I always assumed that was for like football uniforms and stuff.
And maybe it was.
I'm for sure.
It's probably for collecting.
I think we've I think we're continuing to solve the mystery.
Yeah, I've never heard this one.
Mike's comfort with certain things.
Mike's feelings about certain things.
I didn't.
Okay.
I did not.
Just for clarification.
I did not swim nude, but I did have to wear like.
No, they got shorts were said many times.
Little red shorts.
They painted the picture.
Okay.
I just want to make sure that people know exactly where my damage comes from.
And it wasn't the first part.
It was the second part of this whole chunk of this podcast.
The red shorts are more humiliating.
I feel like the nudity.
To some degree.
Yeah.
But honestly, once I was in swim class, because our teacher was really checked out,
he would just go and like play solitaire or be on eBay and we would just do whatever we wanted.
But there was no canoe involved.
I gotta say the swim class unit.
That's not one you want to be checked out on.
Oh, well, I feel like badminton floor hockey.
Yeah, you can check out all those.
But you mean the one where like kids are just jumping off a diving board and in my case,
doing wrestling moves to each other off the deck.
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Yeah.
Probably not a good idea to be in your office.
Barely checked in.
Running and running on slippery tile.
Yes.
Yeah, no, he was and nobody I think got that hurt.
If that hurt at all.
I didn't get hurt.
Soon enough, the water is not just red from little red shorts, but red from blood.
I do remember an embarrassing time when I did.
I was getting a back body drop by these two dudes who would I would run at them in the pool
and then they just kind of lift me up and flip me over back into the water.
And I do remember my shorts like flying off once, which was like, oh, my God.
Oh, that's just so gone at that point because they were used every day.
It's like Bart Simpson.
Yeah, that was that was really awful.
Yes, that was that was like a nightmare.
Like, oh, my God.
High school nightmare scenario.
Two men, two men, two boys also clad in little red shorts, lifted you up in the air in springy red.
I don't know.
Yeah, boy, what happened here?
This is a really bad territory.
Yeah.
And that was like that's like, yeah, that is the one time I remember just like being just mortified.
So what's out there?
Now I put it all out there on audio and video forever, dog.
Thank you so much.
I'm glad I went.
I went until we had video to say that all of us, for God's sake, find this is there.
There could be no drier facts in an episode about canoe.
Find the driest fact you have in your notes.
Oh, oh, that is canoe.
What do we got?
Canoe is a Canadian word.
That helps.
Great.
OK, that is not anywhere near.
They call this the Beaver Brothers Explorer.
No, that doesn't help.
No, brothers doesn't help at all.
That week, we're still in weird territory.
I do like that name, though.
This is close to a couple of parks.
My dad did not even remember this being at the Magic Kingdom.
So I did not do this as a kid.
This close to the Magic Kingdom in 94 closed in Paris in 94 to only
has been two years at Disneyland Paris.
Why did they even bother?
Strange.
Nobody wanted to.
It was one of those miscalculations about the French.
Yeah, they want to.
If they started allowing wine everywhere and they probably should have allowed them on
the canoes, they should allow that on the boy.
I would really like to.
I mean, if there was assuming they could put in little cup holders, if I could
paddle a little bit.
What about pumpkin pop?
I grabbed my pinot pump, pop and pinot.
Now we're talking on this canoe.
What about you could attach a little glass of wine to the end of the paddle?
So when you were like, and then like you bring it back up and you take a little sip
and then you put it back in.
I like the idea here.
It just feels like there's probably a splash.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
I think a camel back is probably most efficient.
What about a baby camel back?
Like the bag, the plastic bag with a long straw.
Oh, sure.
But you know, you're doing that with wine and now it's very strange territory.
Yeah, yeah.
Though, hey, I don't know.
Not a bad idea.
Not a bad idea for dad here.
Take that out to the park.
Little discreet tube.
Sure.
And when he starts playing baseball or something, let's talk a little bit about our experience,
though, on that day, because, you know, talking about having wine or whatever on the.
I will say this in that spirit and in terms of what you're after in a ride in your in your 30s,
this is a very, it's a very adult ride, I would say, a very adult attraction in terms of it's
not a lot of hassle.
There's a lot of relaxation, just like, you know, getting out and being in the fake wilderness.
Like in the was did Matt Appaduck say, would you call Soren a mom ride?
Yeah, it was a mom ride.
Yeah.
Well, maybe canoes is a dad ride.
It feels very like part and parcel with the, you know, if I want a little resort experience
in the parks, maybe I have some wine.
I do Soren, I do canoes and I don't get stressed out by a bunch of.
Right.
Beeps and buzzes.
I just just to just to say exactly what Matt said, because it's so good.
He called Soren the Josh Groban of rides.
Yeah, I forgot that.
Yes, that's yeah.
Is this like the Yellowstone of rides?
I don't know.
I haven't seen it.
You get a nice.
I haven't watched it yet.
I'm going to see it though.
You get a lower view.
You get like a water level view almost.
Yeah.
Of like the CC, the death beaver, the beaver chewing on the railroad.
That's so yeah, maybe people have not seen that.
That's a newer in the kind of the revamp of Rivers of America.
That's a detail I forget about that.
He's chomping on that bridge.
Yeah, it's great.
It's really, really great.
It is the only thing.
Yeah.
When you're talking about an adult experience and that's when we when we say that we mean
something different.
We mean forget what the last 10.
Yeah.
None of that stuff.
None of the body talk.
But yeah, an adult, it seems like you want to feel like the air.
You want to feel the nice air.
You want to feel like a stillness and a calmness.
Some scenery.
Scenery is nice.
And this definitely has it.
I think the only I guess I'm getting ahead of myself with the plus up for something like
this would be longer and just like sections where we're just sitting for like 10, 15,
20 minutes.
You're just describing camping, I think.
Maybe what you're after.
Or in a boat in any sort of boat, I suppose.
So now an expedition has to go out instead of continuously go around.
It has to take several breaks where everyone just kind of like sits.
Yeah, like there would be multiple canoes then then on the Rivers of America,
where they just say, OK, now kick back.
And so you put your feet up a little bit and you kind of like put your head toward the sun
and then you relax.
Some breaks.
Yeah.
It has some like breaks where they would just talk to us.
I could not hear what the cast member was saying.
Yes.
They were talking a little too quietly, but like we were in the back.
Also, yeah, that's unfair.
Yeah.
Get louder.
Yeah, I mean, they should be.
You want to hear the whole.
I could hear what they were saying.
Also, I couldn't hear shit.
I got the.
Stopped by the moose and the tracks from Mind Train.
Yeah.
Through nature's.
I'm just saying I'm agreeing with what you're saying, and I'm just saying like the ultimate
version of the adult experience is like kind of spending an hour on the water or something.
Yeah, that's the ultimate version.
I'm just looking at blue sky and I understand it's not practical.
They got to move.
Got to get these canoes in and out.
People, the demand is high.
We saw the line.
There were at least 10 people like the, you know, the endless grind.
Capitalism.
Yeah.
In and out.
Honk, honk, honk.
Why can't we slow our theme park canoes down?
Exactly.
Enjoy the fake elements.
Hi, folks.
Michael here.
I have a question for you.
Are you trying to find love?
Of course you are.
We all are.
And it's so hard these days, isn't it?
Even with modern conveniences like all the dating apps like Hinge and Tinder
and Grindr, it still can be such a pain in the neck, right?
Well, I have a solution for you.
What about taking a vow of celibacy and devoting your whole heart to the character Sebastian
Jackal, a character that Christopher Lloyd played on the UPN show Deadly Games?
It aired about 25 years ago and aired for one season.
So what I'm saying is, admit that no human will ever be on your level
and that you will worship Sebastian Jackal as a god.
To get started on your new Jackal-based life, go to patreon.com slash podcast the ride,
where we offer some episodes for five dollars a month.
We will be doing a Sebastian Jackal episode next week.
You can pay us, listen to it, and then acknowledge that the only person in your life should be
Sebastian Jackal.
That's patreon.com slash podcast the ride next week.
Sorry, Cathy Ireland, a person who guest starred on the UPN show Deadly Games.
My heart belongs to Jackal.
I did read that, you know, it does go faster than some of the other boat rides, kind of set by
their track.
You do end up going a little faster than the Twain or the Columbia because you're just going
at whatever speed everyone's paddling.
Yes.
So there's the guy.
There's not an exact time.
So I guess if you had a really slow canoe, it could be an hour.
Yeah.
And some in a situation where like all the people paddling decided to paddle like against
like to paddle backwards and fight against the guides.
Then, yes, it would take longer.
So this is one of those group think kind of things we've talked about.
You go on the Indiana Jones ride and you get everyone to agree to not look at Mara.
Right.
And then what happens?
Probably the ride continues.
And it's fine.
Normally.
Yes.
There'd be no way to stop it.
You'd have to light the vehicle on fire for anything to happen.
And it would stop right there.
In this case, though, if you did have a group of 20, you may I guess you could get out there
and then have some secret code.
Yeah.
Or just like a group text goes out.
Everybody feels the vibration.
No words are said.
Yeah.
All of a sudden to the chagrin of the main operators.
You start going that other way.
It is interesting.
I wonder if something like that's ever happened.
They've been running this forever.
Did they have an unruly boat like a bachelor party boat or bachelorette party where everyone's
like, we're going backwards.
And then they just started paddling back.
You have the most control.
It's the ride with the most control to the people on it.
It is really are.
And all this live your Star Wars story.
Yeah.
But this is the real you are in control.
The Yippee day, the day Disney was shut down by the Yippee.
Did the Yippee start to paddle back?
They brought their own paddles, probably.
How come you said that?
And then you were like, oh, yeah.
And I was like, I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
Yippee's?
No, the Yippee day.
That was like, oh, of course.
Yes.
No further explanation needed.
Let's continue.
I heard Jim and Len talk about the Yippee.
Yeah, this is probably worth its own deep dive on it.
But it was when a bunch of hippies like bought park tickets and just flooded the park.
And there were just so many of them.
They like took the park over.
They like, yeah, it was like a year.
They did.
Yeah, they did.
It was a little burnouts 1970.
Yippee was more like they were a radical anti-establishment group.
OK, they were more.
So they were a little more.
Yippee's or Mel Yippee's, there's force to it.
The youths international.
The youth international party.
And little did they know when they grew up, they would all become yuppies.
They would all sell out.
But they made a big, they took over Disneyland one day.
It was chaos.
Then what happened?
I don't think they did that.
I don't think they damaged the park that much.
I think they were just very unruly.
I think they were unruly.
I think they just went.
I think they just shut the park down.
They basically paddled the canoe backwards.
Yeah, they just kind of scratched their butts.
I have not found any evidence for why the yippies were a problem.
Well, I'm going to have to prove that I'm not an idiot.
The big Los Angeles magazine story here.
Atlas Obscura, San Francisco Gate.
So there's this whole story about how the group of 70s radicals tried and failed to invade Disneyland.
We'll just find one.
What's one thing somebody did?
He spit in Snow White's face.
They all got naked and swam in the river like a bunch of Chicago youths.
I don't think there was naked swimming.
They were pranksterish protesters is the phrase this article used.
Well, that sounds like an improv everywhere.
It does.
There was a women's liberation rally to liberate Minnie Mouse in front of Fantasyland at noon.
So they were annoying.
They were just like, this is too annoying.
Yeah, that all does sound like early national lampoon or something.
I don't know that they were, who knows?
They maybe they had some points.
I don't know, not about Minnie, I'm just saying.
We'll get into it at a certain point.
Well, it led to riot cops on Main Street.
Oh my God.
So yeah, I mean in California, they call out riot cops if you cough wrong towards the mayor.
So, you know.
Yeah.
We have a couple of bad state.
We have a couple posted outside the door.
Yeah, making sure we didn't.
We don't talk about little red shorts.
Rick Caruso.
Rick Caruso is heavies at every podcast network to make sure no one makes fun.
Right. They're like, you guys like the Americana, but you're not going to vote.
You're not going to vote for a piece of shit.
This piece of shit billionaire.
It doesn't make sense to us.
There have been unruly incidents, maybe accidental.
Well, this one may have been, well, you know, it depends on who you ask.
This is, I want to say, circa 1990 in the LA Times.
Shocking headline.
15 dumped in drink at Disneyland.
Mishap.
No one is injured, but it was total chaos as canoe sank.
Patrons blame overloading, but park officials cite splashing and rocking by riders.
So the park is blaming the people.
Yeah.
But pretty much all the regular folks they talk to.
Okay, here's quotes.
This person, I think, was just a rider.
There was total chaos going on.
It was comical because they kept saying it won't sink.
Keep paddling.
And it sank right there.
Somebody had to be rescued because they could not swim.
I would say maybe don't go on the canoe ride.
If you can't swim.
They have life vests.
I think all children have to wear life vests and they're available for adults.
If you aren't comfortable.
Oh, yes, you could.
Because I saw a parent putting on a life vest.
Yeah.
That if anything happens.
I'm a little surprised they don't make.
I am too.
Yeah.
You would think this is for Disney safety.
You would think they would make you wear a vest.
Well, check this out.
In this article, weird little specific.
This is a legal issue.
This article got a quote from a spokesman for the US Coast Guard who said,
There's a federal requirement that all boats must carry flotation devices,
but it does not apply on private waterways, including those in amusement parks.
Wow, really?
This has been regulated.
Yeah.
So like anywhere else, because, yeah, you go on certain, you know, just like little day cruises
and you got to put one of the or they need to put them on, but they have them.
But they wouldn't have room in that canoe, probably.
Right.
So, yeah, Disney with their own private waterways.
And hopefully this is one of those things that DeSantis gets in there and makes right.
Finally, Disney's been.
Well, he got rid of it before.
I was going to say it doesn't.
DeSantis want less, less regular life jacket regulation.
So, yeah, but in Disney's case, you want more.
It's hard to square the circle for him, but I'm sure he'll figure it out how.
Yeah.
So so once whatever creates the most chaos, he is the Joker, folks.
Look, I'm just going to say if you vote for this guy in the net,
you're literally voting for the joke as we put it in terms.
You can understand you pee brains.
He is as smart or Joker, Governor Joker, President Joker.
We had a governor that we was fun.
He was a pumper and a popper.
But this we don't want to go joke on her.
Gov joke.
No. But so what you're saying really is that there might have been a scenario
where you had to wear a life jacket on the Mark Twain, which is which is the boat.
You don't have like nobody or anything.
They had to like have them.
They had to have them on there.
I see.
But I don't know, depending on further restriction.
Right.
Again, if DeSantis gets his way, then maybe then, you know, some little ragtime band is
playing on there for the finale of Fantasmic.
All the characters are you got to fit big life vests.
Or water wings, maybe.
And oh, a little kid swimmer.
Sanis will make you on a water ride where water wings and that's going to slow everything
down.
It's going to cost Disney so much money to get water wings.
What they deserve or not really doing anything about the thing that came up.
And he's also going to make everybody wear a certain set of little red shorts before
they get on a water ride.
OK.
And he's going to have them in a big bag and he's going to have people that collect them.
And you have to wash them.
That's going to be more infrastructure that Disney doesn't have.
The good old days are back.
The good old days are here again.
Yeah.
Yes.
Means little shorts.
Did you guys watch any of the footage from Shanghai, Disneyland?
I briefly.
Yeah.
Where like they have the canoes, but you go through, you go buy a lot of fake rocks,
a lot of good fake rocks around here.
That's a lot of like ships, a lot of pieces of pirate ships and stuff.
There is a little more adventure because the area is Adventure Isle,
which is more and Treasure Cove.
So you're going by pirate ships because they're a little more
Pirates of the Caribbean centric there.
They've got that big ride.
So we're not.
Do they maybe not even have a frontier western zone at all in Shanghai?
Am I crazy?
I don't remember.
Yeah, no, it's not.
The land's changed a little bit.
They don't really care about the old Mississippi.
It's not the American West.
Yeah, as we talked about, we did an episode on that, right?
What?
On Frontierland?
West?
We did it.
Yeah.
Frontierland.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we were talking about in there was like, that's not, you're never going to build this again.
Yeah, yeah.
There's not, there's not, there's not been new IP.
Yeah.
Lens itself to really making new interest in the and Woody from Toy Story can only do so much.
He's already not really, he's not a real cowboy like
Davy Crockett.
Yeah.
So you can't just woody-ify all of it.
Yeah, and the Lone Ranger was not a hit.
So I think that's not happening.
We'll see how this all plays out, but maybe Johnny gets another chance.
Oh yeah, I think that's going to happen for sure.
I think for sure.
The relationship with Amber is really, I think it cost me Lone Ranger too.
Just PR team.
I think it was set to go.
PR team's doing their best.
Well, the movie, the Lone Ranger was years ago still, we were talking about it.
I had a Zoom.
Johnny, what happened to your business part who mysteriously disappeared?
One thing at a time.
We're talking about Amber.
Okay.
He pooped in my bed.
Can't say what happens after that.
Really good impression of Johnny Depp.
I will say this though, you're doing it about 10 times too fast.
Oh, I see.
It's maybe the slowest I've ever heard someone talk during those videos.
Smiling bunch.
But it's not frontier.
He he he I have to do.
Oh God.
It's too real.
Did he say he he he out loud?
That's too real.
I don't know that it happened.
I'm not, I try not to watch a lot of this.
It's all so grotesque.
For the video, I got to blow my nose, right?
Just let me blow my nose.
His PR team really is working very hard.
They got the bots.
They got the Twitter bots.
They have the bots.
They've got half the theme park news media.
We're already in the bag for them.
That's true.
Yes, that is true.
Those people were bought and paid for years ago.
What?
Oh, now here's another thing.
This is another like 90s news article that involved this attraction.
But it starts with another one, which is the Jungle Cruise.
And I talked about how they changed.
This was 100% Navajo run.
And they dismantled the Indian area.
So it became all right.
But still just men.
There were not female canoeists.
Oh, that's a good question.
Couldn't tell you.
Canoeers.
But I don't think I realized that until the mid-90s, there was a lot of gender segregation
in terms of hiring on these attractions.
And the Jungle Cruise was the thing that dismantled it.
There was a woman named Suzanne Barnaby.
She was an Adventureland ride operator who'd worked there for 15 years
and was just always told, no, you can't be a Jungle Cruise skipper.
Didn't understand why exactly.
Then took a trip to Disney World where there were just women doing it.
And there was never any big stink.
There was no policy.
It was just like whenever they started in the 70s and just never instituted that.
So it never had to be dismantled.
So she came back to work and was like, she went to Disney World and there were women doing it.
Can I do it?
Yeah.
And then she was doing it four days later.
And then they started dismantling that all over.
And I didn't realize there was a...
I don't think we've talked about this in the show.
There was a ton of that apparently that storybook land, canal boat operators,
the people like telling, pointing out what all the little miniatures are.
That was all women.
But Jungle Cruise is only men with his other ones.
I didn't know that.
Because in this article, soon female conductors will be working the Main Street Omnibus
and Disneyland Railroad and female sailors will be on the Columbia and Mark Twain.
There were only men on all of these attractions till the 90s.
Why in the world?
Yeah, I did not know that.
And like a lot of things as you go back through history, you go, that makes no sense.
Really fucking dumb.
I credit it.
At least they like as soon as anyone said one thing about it, they changed it.
Well, pointed out.
Yeah.
I believe both are cast members and Arca New were women.
Yes.
Yeah.
True.
Another bit of that is that they're talking about, well, why did it come to be this way?
Why was it only men in the Jungle Cruise for so long?
And then here's a little snippet from this article.
Disneyland had experimented with the notion of female jungle guides before.
Some worked during the summer of 1974.
But a spokesman for the park said at the time that the public was not ready to accept women daredevils.
What?
Daredevils?
Meaning the jungle, the people who fake shoot at a hippo and tell a bunch of bad jokes,
those are daredevils?
Yeah, I guess that's a yeah, that doesn't I don't know.
It was a word different words used to be different sometimes.
You know, words often were different.
I'd like to think we've come a long way, but then you watch a Jungle Cruise movie and
there's a lot of jokes in there about like and women are doing it for themselves.
Like there's a lot of.
It's you're talking about.
Yeah.
Well, there were women there like were there that was when the evil can evil start 70s.
My question here is, yeah, is this a daredevil centric time?
What with evil can evil?
We have the nation at evil can evil fever.
American icon like there were no daredevils as far as I know.
I don't know the history of daredevils, but we had the most prominent daredevil in history
and he's male, so nobody could square the idea.
Yeah.
Female daredevil, much less a female standing in a slow moving boat on a track and telling
an occasional they can't suspend their can evil and his daredevils debuted on January 3rd, 1966.
So you they burst through in a big American flag paper.
He had like how's your daredevils now?
Was he how do I say this without slandering?
I just can't slander the dead.
Wasn't he shitty?
Wasn't he a shitty guy?
Evil can evil wasn't he like that's probably right.
I gotta look up people can evils by asking the question.
I think a question can't be slander.
A question can a question be slander.
Can a question be slander?
That's a good question.
Any of these questions.
I like Jason.
I think you can separate the stunts from the performer, you know?
So I'd like to not think that I'd like to not remember evil for any of his badness.
I think evil was didn't hurt people.
If the stunts didn't the stunts only hurt evil.
Yeah, I think mostly evil got hurt.
Yeah, I'm gonna jump.
Was evil evil is Jason asking?
Yeah, I'm gonna jump over 50 children but land on a remaining set of 50 children
who are right after the 50 I'm jumping.
I remember on Fox a lot and maybe it wasn't a lot but I remember on Fox when I was a kid
that Robbie can evil would often be doing a jump of some kind.
Yeah, yeah, they were a lot.
There was a lot of big hokey primetime specials which I enjoyed.
Which Robbie really you can't use a real name after your dad's name was evil.
You can't just go like I'm Robbie.
You have to like demonic can evil like something even crazy or something even darker.
Prime evil.
Perfect.
He's caveman themed.
Even evil junior would be better.
It's cute but it's better.
Is it the kind of juvenile Robbie which Robert can evil be better?
That seems more like he should be in a suit.
My name is Robert to Knievel.
I'm here to jump a bike over some school buses.
Which way to your school buses please.
There's Robert.
So yeah daredevils I mean Walt Disney was such a weirdo conservative that I'm sure that
like yes the jungle cruise was a dangerous ride and for their safety.
It's for the safety but don't want to mess up their hair.
Is it also maybe that they were just like well women don't what did he have like a
Jerry Lewis impression that women weren't funny and like they can't pull off the
jokes on the jungle cruise that are so integral to the whole experience.
There's no way a woman would be able to joke with the guests.
There's just no way.
Maybe or he was gonna he like mentioned it casually to Jerry Lewis at dinner who convinced him.
Oh very possible yeah they were at the Tam and
serious women can't do the jokes.
That's why Jerry I can't do the jokes on the cruise.
It's not gonna work.
There's a dare for daredevils.
Your impression is that he has like elbows with his hands and shifts them around.
I've never seen a Jerry Lewis movie who cares never meant shit to me.
No jokes though because that's something I didn't realize.
I think there may have been a maybe not a full policy change in this attraction but
my memory of it is closer to your memory Jason where it was a guy who was very driving and
like do not stop keep going keep going and it seemed it was kind of like an oppressive
not fun experience but this it's leisurely you're taking your little breaks and even as
you're canoeing you're getting little jokes.
I didn't know that it was a joke based attraction.
Yeah I really enjoyed the jokes I wrote down some of them but do you remember them off hand.
Well if it did any would strike your fancy.
I remember this attraction where they could be a little mean to you like they can tease you a little.
And I saw in the videos and I remember I don't remember the context when we were there there
were jokes about it being and of course we're in Orange County and I was like what do you mean by
that.
I don't remember the context of those either.
Like in the video they're like the people are judging the people on the island are judging
us if you're not going fast enough after all this is Orange County and I'm like hey man Orange
County is massive and very weird like it could be any number of things you could be implying.
You're not sure what they mean.
I feel like that was a joke for herself like she was like she knew what she meant and probably
got some enjoyment whether she was trashing Orange County or saying something funny about it.
I'm not sure.
My favorite of the jokes was towards the end she says hey put your hands up if you picked this ride.
Yes.
A couple people did that and then she said now you know who doesn't get to pick the next ride.
That's funny.
It is funny this is one of those rides where and Jungle Cruise has sort of evolved into it more
where decades of apathy have turned the jokes into isn't this thing bad that we're doing.
Yeah.
And it happened to Jungle Cruise.
We're off in the corner.
New hot attractions have surpassed us.
Yes.
Which is a funny angle.
It is funny.
For anything to come from.
But it's like it's definitely like floating under the radar of what you know corporate
Disney would want for a ride.
It would want to be exciting and you're living your adventure and you know everybody's got a role.
That's all that language about any new Star Wars thing or Marvel thing.
You're the superhero and now this one is like doesn't this suck.
Hey who picked this?
This sucks doesn't it.
You're all rowing now you're using your arms.
You got a new work.
Yeah you shitheads.
What do you think in doing this?
This is stupid.
Why are we here?
I like it.
It's this little like.
Which is funny.
Aggravated it's this like mad younger brother of an attraction.
I like it.
It's spirited you can tell.
I'm sure there's camaraderie with the guides like it's got to be this fun little.
Well there's flexibility.
I don't mean to say fraternity because there's a lot of women doing it but.
Yeah it's a fun fun.
I bet it's a fun little club like being a lifeguard for the summer or something.
Yes I think it's a fun club.
Jungle Cruise is a little bit more restrictive because you do have to do
a lot of the same jokes and the same like banter.
But we've all seen different people.
Some people I've seen who do the jokes and it's really like kind of cringy.
And some people I think have figured it out.
But the people I've liked the most doing Jungle Cruise lately are people like this.
Who have figured out how to do it very dry and flat and like no one's listening.
No one's paying attention because that's the tone of the person we got on the canoes.
And oftentimes are the people I like on Jungle Cruise which is a little depressing.
But it's the tone of who cares?
Are you paying attention to me?
No you're not?
Okay like that's that works for both of these rides at this point.
It's like sardonic snarky in a way that would work for a stand up.
Where I genuinely did laugh at a bunch of...
Yes.
Yeah she's roasting other people on other rides and like you pass by.
That's a cool thing about it that you go right by where the point in the river where the splash
mountain logs dump out.
So you can be right at the like you watch one coming at you essentially.
Yes.
Right on its level.
So that's a fun vantage point.
It is the ultimate Disney Disneyland nerd thing to be like we got to see the log coming from a
different angle that we've never seen before.
You know the log you've seen a million times.
Well what if you saw it from a different angle?
And I agree I'm not I'm one of the guys who like oh look at the log.
Oh wow.
Look at the log.
I can see the log from a different vantage point.
Yeah yes a new camera angle got added.
In this case she said over there is splash mountain.
That's a ride where people come off of it upset because they were splashed on a ride called
splash mountain.
She's roasting the kinds of people get mad on that.
I like the other one you pass by the haunted mansion.
You want to hear a joke about the haunted mansion?
Long silence.
That's the spirit.
And then that's it and that's a little creeper.
I didn't even get it for a second.
You took a second.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
This one yeah I wonder we I guess we should have gone on multiple times because I wonder if like
is it true freedom?
Can you do a tight nine?
You develop your own tight nine on the canoes and you don't have much oversight.
Yeah.
Because that's how it feels because the time I went on it a couple years ago it was totally
different.
Person was like making few jokes but not like this.
This was this was joke a joke a minute.
I saw the one video I watched there was a joke along the lines of like they were about halfway
through the ride and they're like all right everyone we're going to start paddling some
more put your paddles up in the air on three we're going to put them in the water A B C
and everyone put it in the water and they went no I that's fine that's a solid that's an easy
that's good and that's fine that's that's true listening yeah if you just say something in the
pattern of one two three A B C like yeah that's good that's great that's good so yeah it does
feel like you can have your own comedic like comedic persona yeah when you're doing the
canoes so you could do your Andy Kaufman-esque comedy you can do straight ahead Leno style
stand-up you could do anything you wanted which seems like that's maybe this is the one this is
the position with the most freedom yeah to play a character in the park and if the guests don't
like it the cast members are jacked and can shove them in a locker that's right yeah nerd yes you
have to you will be jacked after two weeks of doing this I wonder if they ask you before or it's just
you get jacked doing it I don't do they say can you do the bent arm hang how many seconds can you
how many seconds are you ready to pump are you hot can you pump and then even but even that maybe
that doesn't matter and they're just like you'll get there you'll get there after a week of doing
this I think they've I think they lose people quickly I've read that they lose people just
during the you mean during one of your you mean they quit not that they fall into the water
no not not literally they lose track of them yeah people because they have to they do it for a while
they get like the hulk where they can punch the ground and like launch themselves and they just
don't see them again they just fly out of the parks yeah straight into the sky sure that's an
exciting way to quit um another fun thing about this I didn't know that they did canoe races yes
and this is not just the employees of this attraction it's all over the teams from all
over the park get together hundreds of I found a recent one I don't think they've been doing it
maybe in COVID era I'm not sure but at least in 2019 they did it with 144 teams so like you gather
everybody in your little attraction unit and uh head down there and see how fast you can get your
canoe all the way around the rivers of America yeah very fun it does seem fun I I would like to
be in a canoe more yeah that's what struck me absolutely like I enjoyed it I would race I
would like to race yeah sure I get a competitive spirit from time to time you might be able to
because it seems like it's more about teamwork and 20 people functioning as one right than it is about
having a lot of previous canoe knowledge because you'd think it would be a given who's going to
win the canoe race the people who work on the canoes right but look they're used to their
configuration or it's you know two people and 20 loser tourists right right maybe they don't you
know or they come in too cocky or something but usually it's like I think it's often other teams
winning this thing uh-huh um a loser of as somebody who did not win but who made uh some
social media out of it is uh now Disney parks president what's the title he was in charge of
Disneyland at the time uh uh Disney parks executive and uh hunky dreamboat Josh tomorrow daddy yeah
participate have we done has it been daddy haven't we called him daddy before I think we've called
him daddy before okay I didn't think I was mit wall we've called make Walt Mickey's daddy yeah
but Josh tomorrow is just daddy yeah card Walker is this is addy and e-card Walker is
car daddy yeah 70s Disney executive e-card Walker let's be very clear his dad who kind of talked
like um Mr. Strickland I feel like Hank's boss oh right hell I feel like a similar kind of
I think that's freewheeling vibe not a full episode we need to just learn about card Walker
find our favorite card Walker clips main feed to main feed right maybe e-card Walker yeah that's
coming that's coming soon that's coming that's our way back into pod mass that'll get him yeah
finally got right up again Josh tomorrow did not win but he had a lot of a lot of fun and he
made an episode of his not recently updated Instagram stories only web series out of office
with Josh tomorrow what we know about this no you may look it's not the most produced thing in
the world because Instagram stories you know you can't exactly make a little package there
right save it save the story yep you can go to Josh tomorrow's Instagram and it's yeah it's one
of those little circles that's uh that's backlogged yeah so if you want to watch uh daddy tomorrow uh
pump and paddle so what are you watching this for maybe you're not watching it what are you
listening to it for so this is recent the last like five or six years or so this was 2019 2019
like as recently as they were doing it and just pure stats by the way because i don't know i have
no way to measure my guess is that a typical i think we were on this for like nine minutes i
could be wrong maybe it was longer i'm not sure uh i think i think the the record the all-time record
for canoe racing was broken in 2019 three minutes and 33 seconds one lap yeah really
that seems fast right that seems very fast typically and this has been going since the
60s they've done this for a long time i think typically you're in the four to five minute
range but there's a really yeah that one like wow iterated the record i think so whatever team that
was it was not josh tomorrow's team one and done that was the name of the team yeah one spelled
like you you how do you get how do you get on his team i want to know that sure uh what what view do
you want you want put right behind that bicep you want you want next door in case he like needs a
mid-race massage i don't know yeah i think any anywhere in the vicinity of him on the boat on
the canoe is one of these things with the video component that we should just have a josh demaro
photo yeah i was waiting for him to come up we don't at the ready i don't we can't look this
is a long shot bread i don't know how this works but if you could if you could google image josh
demaro like d apostrophe a m a r o and just bring them up so that we can all admire this man just
surprise us with it if you can yeah if you're going out for this is just this happens on dis
twitter where he gets like people talk about what a hunk he is twitter to me what why it's such a
pleasant pleasant phrase oh yeah it's a great pun first of all great twitter yeah twitter it's a
really fun phrase we're part yeah great wordplay we're dis dis oh no that's all right twitter
we're technically in dis twitter look mouse twitter mice twitter if anyone has a locker at a second
i'm just giving you the reality i don't know if they have one here are you gonna find an adjacent
middle school we're going up to city walk okay i'm gonna rent a locker that's how sensed i am
you're gonna pay for the mommy at the mummy ride there's a lot there's nasty no we have to
go down to the mummy we have to go to the mummy ride we have to go in the park
haven't had one in like eight years yeah we don't uh it's gonna take a lot of that's okay yeah
i'm a tall man surprise i have zero idea if i can call for a josh demaro photo and then see one
but you at home can you can google it whenever you should i should say mike was a good sport because
i was uh it was fine in the boat and i liked paddling getting in the boat my i had a backpack
on and the paddle and the boat was drifting like just far enough from the dock where i was like
i don't i'm gonna fall in this fucking water like i was just my balance was so so like i grabbed
mike's hand mike's hand was up and i don't know if he was intending to help me into the boat but
he certainly did i was absolutely intending to help you in the book i said oh my god jason's
about to fall in the fucking water oh my god yes look i was i don't wish that it happened but a
man i know right if you fell in the water if you had and you can swim like you you should have at
that point mate like you should have just sort of swimming like over to tom sloan's island or
something to try to like get away just because it would be content at that point people diving in
after you like a big swim race going on well halfway through i mean that that would was going
to be one of my plus ups is having the option that halfway through the boat starts to sink
and you all have to swim swim you all have to manage i think tom's island will be better
story wise because you could take the raft over and then after you are on the island for a while
you come back and the raft has been dismantled and they're like oh tom and huck were here and
they took your raft apart those little scamps and then you all have to build the raft back
to build your own way yeah that's fun they took it apart they like baseball bats to it
they they were just they were just goofing you know they were just goofing on your raft
so well you know that would be better in like a scenario where people we are were aware so
they were wearing bathing suits or something yeah you know but that is a fun if it's like a
if suit truly oh no something's gone wrong and now it's now we're sinking and now we have to get
out and paddle not paddle paddle with our arms away yeah not with actual paddles or like you
just grab a barrel like you use the barrel to float maybe that'll help you move right and then
you bring it up and then you use it as um clothes after when you're on land put the straps on it
that was my weird swimming experience and forgive me if i brought this up before but like a boy scout
camp they for the swimming merit badge one of the things involved you had to jump in with clothes on
yeah oh i had to do this flotation stuff like you so if you have it first off they're like the easiest
way to do this if you have like slacks and a button-up shirt and i'm like so i'm like on a
business casual cruise like why would i wear this you're like james bond jumping off of a super
villain's yacht so so a button-up shirt you can like kind of untuck it and you can force water
into it so it kind of makes a de facto life vest and then if you take your like a long pair of
long pants off tie the legs together put that over your head like a life thing and then you force
air and water into that that becomes an even more supportive thing yeah i had to do this for swim
class to complete like the last level of swim class and yeah i don't think i had to wear like a
tux or anything but i were like i think i wore like snap off pants or something which is really
cheating right if i think about it we're like breakaway that like a yeah you'd wear in a sketch
or a or a male stripper would you didn't have breakaway pants did not have no what you know
why would i have breakaway pants it's for like basketball season yeah i know what he's talking
to me you mean where you take the pants the bottoms off and then they are no no they have track pants
the sides have like snaps on them and you take them off like for for basketball or something i
wasn't a little male stripper here we go like that's not yeah that was for first
boards a quick reveal your little red shorts yeah no it was not for a big reveal it was for
it gets winter and you want to wear your basketball shorts not leather and not little like leather
like there was no coming off of it no leather flare when i was in seventh grade that was not
the situation but figuring out the kind of pants we're talking about um one more little thing you
guys asked me on the way out to note an important yes yes detail and i did do my homework about this
and that is i think it's kind of neat that you are handed a paddle you are entrusted with this paddle
i like them you're given a little job you have to use this and then hand it back at the end of the
attraction and in this case uh we were struck by the detail that the brand of the paddle is listed
on the back so i took a photo and i did my research last night the pad the official paddle company
of disneyland is bending branches you can buy bending branches paddles at home you can buy them
at rei the co-op uh they are a midwest company founded by dale kicker and ron holtman uh dale
and ron uh developed in wisconsin they developed a tip protection material called rock guard in the
early 80s and that set them apart from other paddle makers great in the business uh but here
i am going to ask for if we if we do have this photo prepared brett uh because this one this one's
important if there's a photo of a guy paddling who is not one of the three of us if you could pull
that up uh that's no that's me jason no all right and that's all right this is uh this is ed vader
ed vader is the uh president of bending branches and i think he's very well regarded uh some fun
promotional materials ed vader seems like this is ed vader like darth vader uh we've spelled with a
t but yes okay because i thought it was a robbie keneval situation it's darth vader luke skywalker's
brother world is much nicer son ed vader my name's ed vader um and you know what it's funny this i
feel like we caused this by by addressing it or thinking about it ed vader has been the president
for a long time but he's uh as of a couple months ago we're finally retiring after a storied career
as a paddle president and ceo so we just with looking on the smiling face we had podcast the
ride want to officially which it wish ed vader a happy retirement thank you you changed the disney
land experience i love thank you your paddles this is a solid wooden paddle the boats of course are
fiberglass making them a little lighter than like a wooden canoe sure sure oh ed yeah look at it now
he's sailing off to freedom he's got his whole life ahead of him now but something tells me that
even though canoes became his line of work i don't think he's gonna give it i think it's gonna be
part of his retirement year too you can't you can take the paddle company away from the man but you
can't take the paddle out of the hand of the paddle company man well said i need to take a break
in one perfectly said uh i rehearsed for hours yeah i really needed that to go we can do a take two if
you want no i okay why i thought it was good but take two when it was perfect on the first go wow
um they should do more like they should have the paddle company advertising over the davy
crocket nay like you know like how they say you know sun kissed presents or whatever give us more
of the paddle they don't present davy crocket the dead historical figure presents the canoe
but all but they but bending branches and ed vader and therefore dale kicker and ron holtman
they they only present the paddles but you couldn't do the canoes without the paddles
paddle separate episode main feed right sure main feed yeah all right paddles vader vader
retirement second gate covering ed vader's retirement party which hopefully we're invited
to now by bringing it up thanks for everything ed uh anything else you want to say about this i
had a great time on the canoes and you know what i might throw this in the rotation of i'm down
there solo i don't feel like waiting a lot of lines i just want to do something see a lot of stuff
at the park i don't i don't know i think i'm popping down to that canoe a lot more i mean i
think all the rivers of america are nice options for the mark twain the sailing ship columbia
less so the rafts to whatever it's called pirates layer at tomsore island you know you just go back
so that's utilitarian yeah that's just for getting getting there yeah it's it is good i do i did feel
like oh yeah i should do this a little more often i am i'm interested to see the different types of
experiences versus when you have a different guide or a different paddler or whatever um where
yeah will we get an aggressive one where they're trying to beat some sort of record was it or is
it all fun jokes yeah so i would like to do it more um experience the variety yeah experience
they don't have to this is a very it's a completely analog attraction it's not like indiana jones they
didn't need to make a computer no figure out how to make your attraction your experience different
every time it just will be because of the elements yeah nature and human nature it'll be different
every time yes um i'm realizing now when when when i hear the word paddle and i don't know why i
didn't think about this until just now i was in a eighth grade play real quick this is at the end
of the episode i know it's coming too late eighth grade play we talked about sicko plays like your
swim class shit right not one of my sicko plays just a regular just a regular junior high play the
first play i was ever in was called crazy camp and it was one of those where they just stuff 32
characters in a play so we can get as many kids on stage as possible like made this up on the spot
yeah are you looking at crazy camp crazy yeah i'm looking up crazy by the rights and it is of course
a pioneer drama production yeah many of the plays that i did the one that has like 30 speaking
30 speaking roles and i was the camp inspector and i i'm trying to remember if the character
was like mr twilliger or something or am i thinking of a simpsons reference but it might
have been the same but i decided when i auditioned i decided to put an english accent on it which was
i'm sure terrible i'm sure it was not i don't know if there's a video of this but my character got
lost a lot because the kids would fuck with him and the catch phrase i had in the play was i would
be like my hair was messed up and i'd come out and be like i lost my paddle and this was a big thing
and this by the way killed this is my first memory of in a real place killing with the line
i've lost my paddle and whatever my bad english accent was with at the time and then once this
happened my friends would use it to make fun of me for years including probably recent fairly
recently too so i'm just remembering now the word paddle is triggered memory well of doing crazy
camp the thing i think is to reclaim it and make it yours yeah if you were ever if you ever felt
like well i think initially you were being left with then you're being left at it's time for you
to bring the character back and be left with again now it seems like if i'm assessing this
correctly that it was kind of a burst in energy like suddenly you show up something's going on
and then you come in all of flustered and say i lost my battle okay so maybe i'm gonna do the end
of show plugs and if you could and i think use the video i was gonna say the camera now so i think
maybe find a spot where you're out of frame and so this will be a list this will be a video
exclusive but you'll get the sorry while we're getting set mike were you adam apple or were you
willard because i'm looking at the cast list i was not either of those characters but i do
remember the main character one of them's name adam apple officer dumb seem i do remember no i
was not officer dumb okay oh mr turwillitur it is turwillitur with a t will it tur yeah
a trustee for camp john can we get the script can i actually get the lines no you gotta pay for the
script i bet i can find i got the first 24 well now we're at forever dog can someone torrent yeah
brett could you torrent the crazy camp script script in illegal script pirate bay from what website
are you on uh pioneer drama dot com i've got i've got the cast list i've got the first like 20 pages
of this script yeah no the my big thing happens later than 20 mr turwillitur but yeah let's make
this point of view i think hide however you want to hide figure it out um but just pop in some i
think here squeeze to the side a little more uh okay so i will do the i will do the end of show
plugs here but just interrupt i'll trail off a little and just like throw me for a look because
you have to get this information out that you lost your paddle uh okay so here we go you survived
podcast the ride uh davy boats davy boats edition the davy boats we had fun talking about the davy
boats uh and if you want davy boat extra content you can find us on the socials at podcast the ride
merch is available in our t public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast
the ride the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride that's just five dollars and
there's a lot of fun stuff going on i've lost my paddle then what do we do well hold for laughter
what would they what would the other characters do well first of all you have to pause because the
laughter was yeah minutes and it's still going so we all have what do we do what do we do now
what do you think the other characters would do um i think that like there was a character that
would just like uh take me and like usher me off stage i think that was the bit like oh he like
he's lost his mind because he was stuck out on the lake do you want to read this longer line at the
top of the screen i would love to wow live reading okay well it's her my knees are old and bad okay
okay uh wait somebody else has to read dumb dumb officer here you still see it if i do that
i'm gonna try should i uh oh my god there's a lot oh you would say tsk tsk as well he would say tsk
tsk uh okay um you're looking for adam apple okay i'm looking for adam apple who adam apple apple
oh you mean that crazy college kid who runs camp john smith the same i'm gonna do more frank nelson
as i go along here i had trouble with him all last season he doesn't run a summer camp he runs a funny
farm one time his kids covered my patrol car with straw a tsk tsk you're awfully flipping about it
but never would have found it if i hadn't seen a herd of cows munching around a funny looking haystack
it was giving out traffic reports i can assure you there'll be no more of that i'd like to believe
you as a matter of fact the trustees at the bank have sent me to investigate conditions at camp
john smith that's why i'm here where here camp john smith this isn't camp john smith this is camp
pocahontas oh i have a poor sense of direction john down hey look down left john smith's on the
other side of beautiful lake lukey loo looky loo you can't miss it there's usually a pile of tin
cans and rubbish surrounding the place there used to be a buffalo roaming about a buffalo
angie old thing looked like a hairy walking rug with moths haven't seen that buffalo all winter
this is this is just gonna end mid yeah wait wait okay all right uh i think jason will add the
button yeah okay here we go so um i haven't seen that buffalo all winter maybe it died
uh a buffalo tsk tsk i think my visit is long overdue thank you for your assistance
anytime i don't know what the bank trustees will say about a buffalo and then in comes alva
uh
he comes hello dumb there's the big applause and blackout almost the end of the show or the
most free portion yeah of the so show thanks for listening to this and thanks for listening to
what the fuck is the play called crazy camp uh i hope they've updated some of the camp names on
it camp looky loo also the disrespect to call a character officer dumb i was humiliated to play
officer dumb and i shan't be doing it again i was hoping you would do a great gizzou voice at the
end hello dumb hello dumb dumb i had a little gizzou on it well now you always do you will now
say say goodbye dumb that's just a good to dumbs plural all our listeners oh goodbye dumb dumbs
forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced by brett
bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep
up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team
and liking our page on facebook