Forever.
Dogs.
Hot dogs, get your hot dogs here.
Join the good boys as they search for the finest hot dog at the Disneyland Resort.
Featuring hot dog sharing hijinks, open table shenanigans, and just whose idea was this anyway?
The answer may surprise you.
It's the Hot Dog Hula Baloo on Podcast The Wrap.
Welcome to a very special Podcast The Ride that is sure to change the face of hot dog
related entertainment forever.
This ladies and gentlemen is the Podcast The Ride Hot Dog Hula Baloo.
Hello everyone, I'm Scott Gardner joined by fellow Hula Balooers, Mike Carlson, hi.
I am a Hula Balooer, hello.
Yes, this is the debut of a new exciting event.
I think I said yesterday a new PTR franchise.
I think so, yeah.
I feel good about it.
There's possibilities and it's certainly open ended because we didn't, I mean we'll talk
about how the rules that we set made it so we can do more of these quite readily, maybe
leading up to some big grand championship.
Well we'll explain what we're doing here exactly, but first a guy who's really going to be thriving
today, his name is Jason Sheridan.
Noblest of all dogs is the hot dog.
It feeds the hand that bites it.
That's a quote from Dr. Lawrence J. Peter that kept coming up as I searched the Google,
I googled the phrase hot dog quotes.
Should you do it again?
No, no, the ambulance you just heard is waiting for us because we've recently completed hot
dog eating day and we just wanted to make sure.
They're circling the block.
Yeah, yeah, they've got the word and if you need us, we know you guys ate more hot dogs
and in two of our cases had more hot dogs in a day than you've had in two years.
Yeah, the streets have been cleared, the police have cleared the streets just in case
we need to be beautiful quote.
Yeah, I have another one too that kept coming out.
Oh, great.
So I always look for a hot dog wherever I go.
That's Martha Stewart said that on her episode about hot dogs.
Wow.
Our shows wherever she goes, wherever she goes and he just out on a walk in the ocean.
Well let's not forget the famous line from the start of the Patty Duke show, the show
that aired 70 years ago.
A hot dog makes her lose control and who can't relate to that?
Yes, you know, I mean, because that could have any number of meanings.
That's what's in the theme song of the show.
It's like a hot dog makes you lose control.
It's about cuz identical cousins.
She was.
Yeah.
But yeah, for some reason, I don't know.
I don't think there was a common thing in the show where she would just eat hot dogs
like she was Jughead or something, but that's in the last in the song.
I know that.
Nobody correct me.
I know it's in there.
That's a fact.
Something tells me that the Patty Duke heads are not so, there's not so many of them out
in the fan base, but you never know.
There's got to be one or two.
Probably hot.
I think we're all going to lose control due to hot dogs today.
And let me just quickly explain what is going on.
What is the hot dog hullabaloo?
Yesterday, as we record this, the three of us, Mike, Jason and I went to the Disneyland
Resort with one very specific goal to consume every hot dog available on the property and
the entire resort.
We're talking Disneyland, California Adventure, downtown Disney, the hotels anywhere where
hot dogs are available.
We tried every variety of hot dog.
I mean, maybe not every, you know, we had some rules.
We had to like, you know, save ourselves in certain ways, but we certainly went to every
location where hot dogs are available.
We split them all into three so as to for it to still be a tasting situation, a sampling
situation.
So we three grown men kept going to places, cutting up hot dogs into three parts.
Right.
There was a lot of high jinks yesterday.
Yeah, definitely.
Very high jinky day, I guess, bound to happen with what we're trying to do here.
But all of this in service of trying to figure out if you go to Disneyland with a hankering
for hot dogs.
Yeah.
If you want a hot dog to make you lose control, what hot dog will make you lose control?
What's going to help you get your patty Duke on?
And we're going to determine that today.
We don't know the answer right now, but by the end of this episode, we will determine
what we are declaring the best hot dog at the Disneyland Resort.
Yeah, very exciting.
I, yeah, I it's interesting yesterday.
I went in with no expectations and the day was both easier and a little harder than I
expected.
And I don't want to say exactly why yet, but it'll come out during the.
I know what you mean.
Yes, I think.
Yeah, there's the shape of it played out differently for me, I guess, primarily being that I did
not vomit or diarrhea.
Yes, either of those happen.
I guess none of us did.
I think, although I don't know how the evenings went for you.
I will reveal here now exclusively.
I did not diarrhea in the last 12 hours.
Jason, would you like to give us an exclusive?
I have not vomited or diarrhea per se.
Per se.
We're a dicey territory.
I thought we would talk about our diarrhea later, but I guess we're going to start it
off hot on this.
I know.
Look, I'm not at 100 percent.
No, nor am I.
I don't feel good.
I feel a little logy.
This was exacerbated by the fact that I kind of I stated.
Let me explain one of my hijinks.
Jane found this T-shirt for me at a thrift store that just says the phrase hot dog mountain.
We don't know what it I mean to look up, look it up and see if I can find anything about
it.
I'm assuming it's a snowboarding thing or something like that, because I think you can
go hot dog or hot regardless.
So I was like, well, I'm going to wear hot dog mountain.
Oh, wait, I'm looking at Google.
What is it?
And there's somebody in the shirt.
Oh, good.
I believe this is an urban outfitters.
It does seem like the official urban outfitters.
OK, yeah.
So you were getting a sale at a Goodwill of of this hot dog mountain.
And it's very comfortable.
And I am also wearing it today because I stayed over at Jane's.
It did not dawn on me until this morning that like, oh, I don't have another shirt and I
have to go.
Like, yeah, I know I did.
As we started, it occurred to me the shirt we were looking at all day yesterday about
hot dogs.
Unfortunately, like it was just a black t-shirt yesterday and I came in wearing a black t-shirt
today.
Like no one would have paid any mind.
I got a million black t-shirts, you know, but it says hot dog mountain.
Like I don't have two of these.
I wouldn't look.
I wouldn't put a patch to have multiple shirts that say hot dog mountain on them.
Yeah.
I mean, I could have gone home and thrown it in the wash and put it back on instead.
The reality is.
So you made the walk of shame over the hot dog walk of shame.
Yeah.
I think you're right.
Also in your first guess that I'm because I'm seeing a patch that hot dog mountain is
part of Lake Geneva in Wisconsin.
Oh, and there is in this patch.
In fact, you might enjoy this patch that it is a little hot dog in a little hat to keep
him warm and skis.
And he's heading down hot dog mountain.
I love that.
There's also a little Playboy bunny logo.
So maybe it was there.
That's stranger club there.
I guess the Playboy bunny's friends with the hot dog.
Hmm.
Well, this raises more questions than answers.
Lake Geneva in the Finger Lakes region of New York, too.
I didn't realize there was one in Wisconsin.
So we'll learn everything we can about.
Wow.
There's 13 slopes of fun at hot dog mountain.
Really?
Okay.
Well, we're going to have to cover hot dog mountain, but that's not dog mountain.
We're going to cover it in the episode.
This is hot dog.
Excited to learn about it.
This is one of the things I was going to ask about is how everybody feels today because,
okay, so some total of it and this you might be imagining jaw dropping stats and I don't
quite have those to give, but I believe that the full count is that we went to five establishments
and all split seven hot dogs, which adds up to I guess only a little more than two free
ships.
When you're adding some of the crazier ingredients and that it is pretty much all we had for
lunch and dinner.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
I thought I was going to be feeling it more as the day went on and I kept all day.
I felt like I am surprised I am not worn down.
And then this morning I felt so bad.
I slept bad.
My body just, I could feel my body being mad about lack of nourishment and things that
it needs.
Yeah.
I also, I mean, I was drinking throughout the day too.
So that combo, I think.
You know, while we were, you know, you, it's a, we did a B it's fairly big day, not, not
opening to closing or anything, but what 10, 45, nine something.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I made some, I think I really only made one miscalculation, but I was feeling
it for a while and then got a second wind.
Is that your, your Liberty to say, are you about to throw up?
No, I'm still just having, um, the vapers, the vapers.
Um, the hot dogs are okay.
Ambulance, even the ambulance over.
Also the longer the episode go, we might do it.
We're like, we're fine now, but we aren't at the end of a two hour episode.
By the end of this, we might, yeah, we might not make it out.
This, this floor might get puked stained by the end.
Full of diarrhea by the end.
Yep.
So listeners are going to get binaural vomit in their ears.
I'll bring it up.
I'll bring it up when, um, when we get to it.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
It might make sense as a progression to go chronologically with the hot dogs that we,
I think that might be a good order and kind of take, take everybody through our day.
Um, but, um, before we get into it, let's talk, uh, rules and odds and ends.
Uh, well, first of all, I want to thank Aaron Gardner for, uh, not just the logo for the
hot dog hullabaloo, but for naming the hot dog hullabaloo.
Great name.
Thank you.
Um, let's talk about rules, rules that we put forth before trying all of these hot dogs.
Um, one ruling, I think no kids hot dogs.
This is going to be embarrassing enough as it is.
Yeah.
Eating hot dogs and splitting them up all day, splitting children's dogs didn't feel good
to me.
And I don't think a kid's dog was going to take it all the way.
Likely not.
Right.
Um, we didn't go to any buffets.
I think we found all the hot dogs on property, but if there were a bunch of hot dogs set
out, um, at a hotel buffet or something, we don't know about that.
We're not going to pay 28 bucks to only get to the hot dog.
I'm sure Goofy's kitchen storytellers probably have some child hot dog option.
Also seems unlikely to me that if we, if we don't think a kid's hot dog is going to take
it all the way, then kids hot dogs at a buffet, almost certainly you're not going to take
it all the way.
You never know though.
Maybe there's an odd meaty gym in there.
Yeah.
Who knows?
Um, I took, uh, I said we should take Ronto wraps.
Out of the equation.
We did the, the, the star wars, galaxy's edge food that we're very fond of.
Um, that is the ultimate hot dog.
We called it a space hot dog before it came out.
Um, I don't like a competition where we know the winner and I don't think any of the, now
we've had all of these hot dogs.
Would you say any of them?
No, go up, it could go toe to toe with the Ronto.
It would have been a clean sweep.
Yeah.
Too easy.
Little too, don't get ahead of yourself.
Don't get full of yourselves Ronto reps.
Yeah.
You had a rule that I think turned out to be correct that I initially argued.
Are we sure about this?
And you were a little intimidated by the day and by the notion of doing this until I put
this rule forth and I think this is crucial.
Um, and this might not be, look, this, this is my judgment for this competition.
Maybe this isn't true in general, but for the purposes of this, I said corn dogs are
not hot dogs.
Off the table.
Now I don't agree with corn dogs are not hot dogs, but off the table for this.
It doesn't even sound right to me, but yeah.
Yeah.
I think for, because imagine how we would have felt if on top of it we are eating those
big thick breaded corn dogs.
That's the day that destroys us.
Now I think corn dog batter would, is like, you know, when you take a fall on screen into
a crash pad.
I think that corn dog batter would have lined your stomach a little.
Oh, you think it would have been a better day if we had corn dog.
I think the batter might have helped.
I also think the batter might have helped.
The batter might have helped.
But it could have also like packing peanuts in a box.
It might've puffed up and it probably would have puffed up and filled it up.
I also think in my mind, the hot link corn dog at corn dog castle is one of the best
small meals or snacks on property.
And I think that would have weighed it.
I would have had trouble being unbiased and because I think it's delicious.
I didn't want that either.
I think I, cause I was such a latecomer to the Disneyland corn dog.
I didn't realize how solid they were.
And I think they are genuinely pretty great.
And again, too easy.
You don't want to just like set up a competition because you know what the winner is going
to be.
And then hooray, we got the winner there.
Where we stand right now, these, just putting it in the hot dog category.
I don't know what's.
I genuinely don't know what's going to take it.
And I think that's exciting.
Yeah.
We should also say sides, sides.
We did have sides, but we are trying to separate them.
Well the, from almost the only side, the majority of the sides were cuties oranges.
I kept ordering cuties as the side, not the chips, not the fries.
Cuties, single cuties.
Massive L at one of the locations.
In what way?
What do you mean L?
Well I'll get to it.
I'll get to it.
I don't want to, we'll get there.
Massive L. Massive L.
But not all the locations.
Not all the locations.
Did you eat a bad cutie?
No, no.
The cuties were delicious.
And the cuties are much more preferable.
Oh I know what you're upset with.
I know what he's upset with me.
We'll get to it.
It's okay.
I agree.
That's yeah, yeah.
Something happens in translation to in the process to those apple slices.
I feel this way at McDonald's as well.
There's a weird like film on those apple slices now I feel like.
Yeah.
To keep them, to keep apple slices fresher I think.
I do think they're putting something on them.
Because if you open up, if you do an apple and you cut it into slices, leave it on a
plate for an hour, it's going to start to get weird.
Yes.
The color is going to start to go to sort of, I do feel like there's some sort of.
Out of those slices.
Yeah.
I feel like there's some coating or some shit on there that makes it like feel like fake.
And some of them de-skinned.
And most of the nutrients are in the skin.
Is that right?
In apples?
Yeah, a lot of the nutrients.
But most?
I believe so.
I don't know.
Honestly, I don't know.
I can see that.
I'm not seeing it wrong.
Yeah, that's not a, I feel like it's only the most picky kid I feel like is like, no,
no peel on this apple for me.
Yeah.
That's unnecessary.
I don't know.
Yeah, weird.
But the cuties, I gotta give it up for the cuties.
I mean if it was cuties or bananas, like they come with their own package.
They come with peel.
Like it's.
They don't know what we're talking about real quick.
That's a tiny orange.
Little orange.
Seedless, easy to peel.
Yes.
In some cases, in one case serving as the stands for the hot dogs.
Like we stick a cutie on either end, thus it does not tip over and spill the many ingredients.
So now, and that's good.
That's environmentally conscious we're using.
For instead of putting some plastic piece in there to hold the hot dogs up.
So I like that.
And probably prevented us from scurvy, getting scurvy, you know.
That's a good point.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Those the cuties were doing a lot of work for us all day.
So thank you cuties.
Thank you cuties.
One other thing with Toontown closed at the moment, one location was off the table and
that is Pluto's dog house.
And I don't know the quality of the hot dogs at Pluto's dog house.
If quietly that is the best place.
I don't know what to say.
I've had one there.
I've eaten a hot dog there.
Yes.
And I don't think it was anything special.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
Which kind of kept happening.
If we ever heard for sure one is not something special, maybe it got pulled from the competition.
And when we talk about hot dogs and what makes them special, I feel like we have to throw
the ball to Jason.
I think you're the obviously the hot dog expert among the three of us.
The entire hot dog fascination on the show comes from you and the just the notion that
you have them ever at your house, which still I find interesting.
Yeah.
Do you have them right now?
I don't have any right now, but I did just finish some deli ham.
Great.
Ham and no longer ham and no longer ham in the house because Pam was in the house.
Because it was on sale at Pavilions.
Wonderful.
So, well, I don't even know what to ask.
I guess maybe one question is what you're looking for in a quality hot dog.
Sure.
First off, I think interesting to note, this episode was not my idea.
This was you, Scott.
So I appreciate your innovation in this.
I appreciate.
You know, we have to set each other up to succeed.
If I think of a hot dog vehicle for you to shine.
Yeah.
Bumps that spike.
You know, you got to work together to win the volleyball game.
You know, I think overall, the very first thing you're looking for is taste.
I mean, if it doesn't taste good, why bother?
You know, after that, I think you start to get into like a presentation, you know, and
then I guess similar to taste, like elements, like do the parts of the whole, are they good
together?
Are they good separately?
Temperature is this, are these toppings making this slightly warm thing ice cold?
Oh, sure.
I don't know that hot was the strong suit of any of the entrees yesterday in terms of
food temperature.
I don't think anything came out.
I don't think anything was undercooked, but I think by the time we sat down to cut them
up hot dog is cooked by definition.
It is already cooked kind of just again.
Well, it is cooked.
You can eat a hot dog straight out of the package.
For the most part, I think you can get raw Franks.
I don't think we're winners.
Whatever you want to call them.
I'd like to call them winners, but I feel like most of the stuff you get at the store,
you could eat it raw.
It'll taste like baloney and if it's cold.
Yeah.
And if you fry baloney, it tastes like a hot dog.
Sure.
In most cases.
So I'm just saying everything I think we ate yesterday, I'm sure came out of a package
cooked.
Cold beer quotes.
It just needed to be warmer.
It just needed to be heated up.
Have you been satisfied with the quality of hot dogs at Disneyland before?
Has Disneyland's hot dog game met your needs and expectations?
No.
Interesting.
Okay.
Explain.
Well, for a long time, the hot dogs were pretty bland and they were served on very bland,
often approaching stale, like wheat rolls.
Yeah.
Okay.
And so like, yeah.
And I think the like topping packets yesterday were pretty on point.
Like you know.
They were a little diverse, I feel like.
Yeah.
Better in the past.
So those have gotten, some stuff has gotten better.
I don't think, I mean, LA still has a lot of like burger and hot dog places.
So I think we're, we do, we do pretty well, especially here in the beautiful San Fernando
Valley.
There's a lot of places that have been here for decades that are still doing the same,
you know, cooking burgers and franks the same way they have for a long time.
Well, which if, if what you're getting at is the stuff that you can get locally within
two miles of where you live, that you're going to find a better hot dog in your vicinity
than at Disneyland.
That's how I feel.
I'm like, I would say none of these, nothing that we had, I would describe as being one
of the top 10 or 20 hot dogs I've ever beaten.
I don't think so.
And I'm not even looking for like fancy.
I like some of the stuff at Weiner, the local chain Weiner Schnitzel.
Oh, but if you drive by some of the buildings, some of them still look like the cool funky
like A-frame architecture.
And some of them look like they opened in the nineties and immediately got in a fight.
Like the building got beat up somehow.
It's an all over the map franchise.
It's an all over the map franchise, but occasionally very solid.
That said, Disneyland strong suit is the corn dog.
I think in general, that is, I think we're bringing the heat.
Because it has the cushion, because it's got to be the same hot.
It's got to be the same thing inside.
It might be everything we had.
I think everything we had is the same actual hot dog.
That is what I figured out, very smartly figured out by the end of the day.
With one, maybe two exceptions.
Maybe.
One of them just by their definition, I think, can be different.
Yeah, that's right.
That's yes.
Yeah.
But it's actually the same one still.
It's just got a little extra.
Yes, possibly.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, huh.
Okay.
So we're so measured expectations already.
This is a guy with this is already let's let everybody know this is a competition between
mediocre hot dogs.
I think it has gotten better, which is not.
It's not saying a lot.
I think one place that used to be worse is actually better.
I mean, look, I don't want to tip.
I don't want to tip.
I let's I think we should just start getting into it.
Yeah, I well, I agree that we should start getting into it.
But I think as just a little short for the feature, there is one thing that happened
yesterday that we need to talk about before we head into the bulk of the hull of balloon.
And that is what happened right before we left Disneyland.
Right.
Let's explain.
So a fun day, high jink filled day in general.
I think the best high jinks were saved for the very end.
I was waiting for you guys outside of the California Adventure location trolley treats
where you were mobile ordering snacks to treats to take home.
Yes.
For the what?
Have you consumed those, by the way?
No, those are sitting in a bag.
OK.
Yeah, I was not your treats.
What did you get?
I got like a rainbow Mickey like Rice Krispie treat with like rainbow like not sprinkles,
rainbow like what do you call those that are not sprinkles, but they're different
decorative like cupcake things, you know, like it's like shavings, like colored shavings,
but they're not sprinkles.
Hmm.
OK, I'm not sure.
Yeah, I don't know what the name is.
Jason Treat.
Yeah, I got what we each first off, you can mobile order treats at the candy stores now.
Which is actually interesting that you can mobile order at more of a take home or something.
It could be a take home situation.
Yes.
Something you got to eat right then.
I already have a grievances about it because the walk up menu is much more detail.
There's many more options than it was on the mobile order.
Like you were I was a little like doing it on the fly, doing it pretty quickly because
you were in line and Mike had already placed his and I was just trying to pick something
to bring back for me and something to bring back for Jane.
I brought her like a Rice Krispie treat on a stick that had peanut butter and chocolate
on it.
And then for myself, I mostly ate this.
I couldn't find the exact one on the app, but it's a more the strawberry shortcake marshmallow
wand.
It was a bunch of marshmallows dipped in white chocolate and then covered in strawberry flavored
confectioners coating crushed cookies and dried strawberry pieces.
Wow.
It tasted like a strawberry shortcake ice cream bar, but marshmallows instead of an
ice cream base.
I thought it was delicious.
Oh, great.
So that was good at night or in the morning?
Little right before I came here.
Just a coating to cool your stomach.
Just a coating, you know.
There's also, I don't think it played out this way, but we were talking about, all right,
we're heading into the hot dog hall of blue.
We're saying like, we got to like make sure, okay, we got it.
We need sustenance and things that our body needs before we get there.
Like make sure to have a healthy breakfast.
And then I think we did, we said that did an episode and then on the way out from doing
the episode, you said, oh, maybe we can grab one of those cornbread donuts from Duncan.
It's Duncan's seasonal donut.
I did not eat it yesterday.
I ate it the day before.
I just had like a granola bar and some peanut butter before.
And then I showed up at Mike's.
We all carpooled and he offered me a donut and had presented us each with a bottle of
Coca-Cola Starlight.
Oh, yes.
Waiting in our chariot.
That's right.
It was my first experience with Coke Starlight.
Yes.
And your last, I assume.
Yeah.
It was one sip.
Not only would it be one sip, he wouldn't let his taste buds experience it and create
the antibodies that he needed to enjoy it.
Like our bodies have, Jason.
And I have Coca-Cola Starlight cans at home and I meant to throw some in my bag to present
and forgot it going out the door.
So I whipped it because we could have had a car full of zero sugar Coca-Cola Starlight
in various bottles, cans, you know.
It made the day better, I think, if we had had more.
Which you were talking about, like, if the corndog lining might help.
You said during the day, well, yeah, this hot dog thing is going to be grueling, but
I am armed with Coke Starlight.
That was going to offset.
I also had, and I didn't go for either of them, I had a travel thing of Tums and I had
a can of Perrier, just in case.
Little bubble water.
Soothe the stomach.
Yeah, Coke Starlight, I did not spit it out.
It was not a bizarre taste to me and not so different than other, especially like zero
sugar sodas.
But that, boy, that aftertaste just lingered and lingered.
It got worse and worse.
It's making me thirsty just thinking about the aftertaste.
Why do you want that?
Is this just like, because you don't really like, in the way that you, I don't think you
will drink just straight whiskey probably usually.
You need to load it up with shit like Coke Starlight.
No, no, no, no.
I will drink a straight whiskey.
Okay, okay.
Got it.
All right.
But either way.
Direct assumption on my part.
I can handle it.
I'm tough.
I'm a man.
I'm a traditional masculine man.
But no, my body cannot, it just did not recognize Coke Starlight as a desirable taste to have.
My tongue was so upset.
You know what?
I had a mini can because it's so, I poured a mini can in like a highball glass, like
a tall glass, and it only filled it like halfway.
I took a few sips.
It's mostly gone.
You drank a Coke Starlight in like a night, like a cocktail, like, well, just a regular
glass, like regular tumbler, like big piece of ice, clink, clink, clink.
Yeah.
Hello, darling.
I'm drinking my Starlight.
I've only seen it like the 16 ounce bottles or the 7.5 ounce can.
And you're a fan.
I do like it.
I do.
Okay.
Don't.
All right.
More power to you.
I didn't understand.
But so anyway, you guys are ordering your treats.
I was not getting a treat for myself.
So my attention is wandering and I realized there is a, there is a character line not
that far from us.
Yes.
It is a line for Mickey Mouse.
And I thought, well, we did this episode about how hugs are back.
If you didn't hear that on the Patreon, this is a news.
This is a recent thing that one of the last little things unlocked about pre pandemic
parks is that you can hug the characters again and get up close and interact with your favorite
Disney characters.
So I see Mickey.
I'm like, well, we got to do, this is a tweet.
We got to like, we got to post this.
Maybe we posted it by now.
If you're listening to this, we all got to hug Mickey and do some kind of hugs are back
post.
That'll be nice.
Right.
I'm sort of saying that out loud to you, Mike.
Maybe you're thinking about treats a little bit.
I would call you like half interested in this at best.
You're kind of a little glazed over your man.
Like, okay.
Then I look over and see another character line and that line is for Minnie Mouse.
Minnie Mouse.
Yes.
I said, oh, or there's a Minnie Mouse line.
And you said, oh, Minnie, like spark, like lit up color in your face now.
Flapper Minnie at that.
Flapper Minnie.
Your posture like shut, like you were like hunched over and then you grew a few inches.
Yes, that is true.
All a hundred percent correct.
And also I said, oh, and I know this sounds like some sort of excuse just for my pervert
ness to get in line to take a picture with Minnie.
But I said, oh, Minnie is the one who always hugs me because this is going to be an important
part of the story because I've never ever gone and be like, I'm going to get my hands
on me.
Like that's not so many always hugs me.
So I said, let's do Minnie, especially because Minnie is so much more.
Hello.
She's always got her arms outstretched welcoming you in.
And I said, that's going to be an easier slam done because I don't think all the characters
are necessarily like that.
They're not like Chewbacca.
So that's also another reason why.
Cruel irony coming to the.
Yeah, well, yes.
So I so my because what we're about to reveal my expectations of what happened is the thing
that completely threw me off and completely ruined this bit that we were talking about.
Oh, I don't know.
I the opposite.
Well, I love how this played out.
It's not fair.
I think it's played out.
No, I think it's good, too.
So we get in a we get in line for many and we're discussing how are we going to do that?
Like, do we count as one group?
I feel like we all need separate photos.
Separate hugs.
She can't hug all of us at once.
Do we give a phone to a cast member?
Do we want them all to be on the same phone?
How do we play this?
And then we say, well, yeah, let's all go up individually.
And then, Mike, in my recollection, how you describe this was, OK, well, I'll take the
photos and you do it and then Jason do it and I'll get I'll get your pictures.
And then I'll go in with many.
And then you guys just like, keep taking them and taking them and taking them and
taking them. This is what you said out loud.
OK, just keep going, because I'm just going to keep going at it and just like I don't
think I keep going at it.
You did not say that.
But that was the attitude that I felt got it from this particular photo demand.
Sure. Sure. That camera rolling.
OK, you never cut.
You wanted a couple angles.
You didn't want to end up with just one Zapruder film.
I wanted it. I wanted a two camera shoot, two to three camera shoot.
You know, good. Yeah.
So I go up.
I ask many for a hug.
I hug many. Jason does the same.
Yeah. So we have hug photos.
We have hug photo and you went in pretty fast.
And then I was like, oh, I'll go in for a hug.
And it felt like they were the cast.
I was doing it grudgingly.
This is what I'm saying.
Grab my hand and did a pose.
Yes. They were.
The cast member was very good at doing, like, you know, pose, like,
you know, hands with the arm or like grab my hand and like both our hands on mine.
I sense this energy.
I was just like, oh, I don't.
Yeah, I know why I don't do this.
Now, I know I don't usually.
I said, I'm so very sorry.
This is not the mini who's hugged me in Florida.
This is not the same mini.
I said I I did a little like kind of gesture like this walking up to mini
as if like a light we may be going to the mini was not interested.
So I said put her arm through your.
Yeah. So I said, OK, I'm going to just so.
So I'm in general about hugging.
I'm not a big hugger.
You guys don't know me to hug you after every record or anything.
That's not we don't know. We did it again.
Yeah. No. We did it to him again.
Another one. I'm not anti hugger or anything, but I'm generally like I need
I need the person who's going to hug me to give me like five good signs,
five good go ahead signs and then let's hug.
I'm I'm I'm happy to do it.
This many was not giving me the the all clear sign.
So I said, I'm just going to shake many's hand for the first time.
This is the first time I've taken a photo with many in the last so many years
that many did not hug and smooch me.
You went you reverted back to your high school first date.
Yes, I did. Like, well, yes, I did.
Good luck in your future endeavors.
Yes. Great meeting you.
That is exactly what happened.
And it kind of didn't occur to me.
I think Jason was taking the pictures and until we broke off
and started leaving the park, that was the first thing I realized.
Wait, Mike did not hug me.
Did not hug me.
The entire point of us didn't doing this.
And I asked what happened.
And you said very sheepishly, I got nervous.
Well, I did. I was nervous to hug this garden grove.
I 23 year old.
I also it's also weird.
I feel like the suits used to be puffier than some of the new character stuff.
They're just wearing like a green man suit with clothes over it.
I'm a man head.
I'm also biggest Herman Munster.
I'm a Frankenstein like a very small mini.
Yeah. So I I'm aware sometimes of I'm not as tall as Chewie,
but I'm like, I don't know what this this many also had just gotten through,
like hugging somebody for like a minute and a half.
Did you see this? No.
You guys were I think your back was to me.
Many was hugging this somebody for like forever.
And I was like, I'm sure that's really sweet.
And that person really is enjoying this hug.
But like I was the performer.
I'm thinking about the logistics of the performer.
And I'm like, also, can she see me?
Can many see me?
Like she's looking up.
So all of this is getting in my head.
And I got like nervous.
And I'm like, I know it's not a huge deal.
I go. But then I all of a sudden I kind of like blacked out a little bit.
And I just like shook many's hand and then took a photo.
And she like made she put her arm through my arm to take the photo.
And then I like kind of in a daze, like left and just went, I didn't do it.
I didn't. I didn't do it.
I didn't hug. No hug.
I'll say that.
That was a great I think that was great.
There were two very little kids in front of us.
They walked up to many and many spent so much time with like signed
autographs for both hugged both of them, took a bunch of pictures.
Oh, yeah. They were.
And there is a long line, too.
I think they saw they got to us and they're like, Jesus Christ,
we have so many people.
Well, they close the we are the people who are like, OK, we got to get these.
No, no, no.
They have their hand on the.
They have a lot of family like I there are people we I actually have to.
They have their hand on the bus.
When you see us, don't were you paranoid?
Like we are the thing that until the three men came, the vibes were great.
And then it was and that we got to start gunning it and save many from the little.
Self-conscious public.
I won't lie. I'm a little self-conscious about that.
So, yeah, I don't I don't.
Yeah, I don't think that they're like, all right, get your hands on your
like every cast member has their hand on their gun, like ready to go.
If they see us, I don't think it's that severe.
But I am like, they're like, OK, buddy, what is this?
Who is who are you? What podcast?
Again, I disagree.
There is no way that we, the three of us are the creepiest.
No, I know that we're going for a hug.
That's yes, that is true.
We were efficient, though, in our movement.
We had the camera stuff laid out.
We were all boom, boom, boom.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's obviously.
What you'll probably aren't.
So our actual lingerers and especially if you're a face character princess, as we learned.
Yes, that's another thing entirely.
But yes, I all the things I'm telling you, sensing weird thing.
My general hug philosophy, my hug, the the the ghost signals I need for a hug.
All of those things were not working.
And then as I told you, I just kind of went, oh, hello, Minnie, how are you?
And then we took the photo and then I left and I went, well, I didn't do the bit.
OK, on the bright side, none of us panic fired and went, where my hug at?
One of the one of the worst phrases of the late 20th century.
Just like crime straight to jail with you.
They would have they would have put us in Disney jail.
Yeah. Hey, Minnie, where my hug at?
Goofy beating you up with a normal phone book.
They'll on us if we tell that story.
Yeah, it was everything.
The car like the Carthay area, like jazz band.
They put their weapons, their their instruments down and grab weapons.
The back of weapons in the cases still has a bunch of Anaheim
1990 phone books when they were like giant.
Just like in case they really have to teach you a lesson.
Yeah. Well, anyway, we have our photos and that's the story behind them.
Yes. Yeah. If you wonder why there was no mic hug.
No, look. Yeah.
And that's look, I'll go back to Florida where Minnie is like,
she's fighting to hug me.
She's asking for the hug.
So there you go.
She's forcing you. Right. Yes.
OK, so all of that said a sidetrack.
Now let's get into the hullabaloo. Yes.
And let's kind of step through how the day progressed.
I think especially this works because the first location we stopped
was kind of a base of a kind of just no frills set.
Like what is a basic, unadorned Disneyland hot dog like?
And that is at the downtown Disney location, Diggity Dogs,
where we ordered what was described as a Nathan's original all beef hot dog.
Yeah. Flag on the field immediately.
Right at the start.
I I don't believe those were Nathan's hot dogs.
Yeah, yeah, I'm not super familiar,
but I do recall Nathan's being an elevated brand.
And I think it's one of those where the brands gotten watered down.
I think it might be like when a place says they serve Starbucks or coffee,
bean coffee. But what does that mean? What does it read?
It does not like that can still be. It's it's hypothetical.
They've watered the brand down.
Scott, I think you're exactly right.
I think we're looking at the wholesale supplier of like the lower rung.
Nathan's wholesale because a real Nathan's hot dog.
I was yelling about this last night to Jane and anyone who would listen.
At midnight, it was late. Yeah, it was like
usually longer, skinnier, a darker color than these hot dogs.
Oh, you're right. Yes, they're recognizable.
That's like that's like Wendy's Square Patty.
They have there's things about.
Yeah, these were exactly the same as the ones in the park. Yes.
I think this this is a stand that's probably very serviceable
for families with young children who will only eat hot dogs
in the middle of downtown Disney.
A child is screaming for a hot dog.
Oh, thank God there's a little stand there that sells plain hot dogs.
Yes. So it likely serves a purpose.
I want hot dog. I only eat hot dog.
Oh, honey, what are we going to do? We're in Disney.
There's a there's a stand right there outside.
Say diggity what?
Diggity hot dogs.
That must be hot dogs.
It's not a place where you get dogs or dog supplies, is it?
No, it's hot dog. It doesn't.
It seems very utilitarian.
It's not the like impulse buy of like the different flavor churros
that aren't the Disney churros or a little macro, though, like four dollar
macaroons. Yeah, it's a it's a good it's just a basic.
We went and we got this basic, which had no which came with nothing.
That's just like in the oil and we all got our own condiments.
For me, and this is this would be my go to for hot dogs in general.
My third I put I used relish and spicy brown mustard,
which the Disney variety is goldens for spicy brown mustard.
Go with goldens. Go with gold.
How did you guys with given left to your own devices?
What do you well, what's your OK?
I did I did a couple of things.
I tried it. I tried it plain.
These are small bites, but I tried it plain.
I tried it with yes.
And I'm from Chicago. This is a no, no.
But I do eat it with ketchup sometimes.
I know people say that's wrong, but I do like it.
So I tried it with just ketchup.
And then I also tried one bite with relish and goldens.
So I tried all three. Right.
Yeah. Goldens, a Sheridan family favorite, always in the house growing up.
And I love to see the packets.
Oh, always like the packets, packets widely available at Disneyland.
You pocketed a whole like 50 of them to take home to.
That does sound like something my mother would do.
Mix them in with with Coke Starlight in your eyeball glass.
They would change in older seats.
Yeah. So I did
goldens and whatever relish I could get out of the packets.
I fucking I love relish.
I hate those fucking relish packets.
It is not an item to be in.
There's got to be a better way, like because you either open too small a hole
and you get mostly relish juice or as happened late in the day yesterday,
I opened a packet and it exploded and somehow did not explode onto me,
just exploded onto like my place setting in the table.
Yeah, yeah. They've got to be bigger if nothing else, which sometimes they are.
But yeah, relish packets cannot be the same size as ketchup and mustard.
Yeah, as tidy as that.
Yeah, it's better with this.
I know it's messier, but it's better with some sort of squirt pump mechanism,
pump mechanism to get your relish.
Yeah, absolutely. Very inefficient.
I think they've standardized like the condiment allotment,
like everywhere seem to have the same sort of setup.
Likely, I think some of them used to have more pump setups.
I think those pulled at the start of the pandemic reopening
and now have given way to just like packets of everything.
I so yeah, just like fine basic hot dog.
By the way, this one probably the most humiliating to that's incompetent.
There's two moments I think were the most humiliating split ups.
This one was tough because they did not have knives at this location,
because surely we do not need to stock knives.
Who will be splitting up hot dogs,
allah, Mickey, Donald and Goofy splitting up the one bean
check and bean stock.
Never have we resembled that trio more.
So splitting up this plain hot dog just using forks.
It's very embarrassing, but nobody is around.
And you know what? We got to sit just in the fountain at downtown Disney.
A nice little bench spot.
The family from Jason's story had not come yet to see us do this.
So we didn't get embarrassed.
Too early for breakdown. Yeah.
So, you know, it was just it was it was fine.
There's a part of me it's like, you know,
maybe just a basic on a darn hot dog oddly takes it.
But I think I didn't like the aftertaste of this.
I felt I wrote down the word soupy.
I felt like it just kind of like just kind of a weird dirty water.
I wrote I wrote juicy down.
Juicy is maybe a bit.
That's a more optimistic way to to.
I didn't hate this dog.
No, I wrote juicy, looked weird, plain.
Not that they all don't look weird, plain,
but there was something about it that was a little unappealing, I would say.
You know, a lot of stuff steamed or boiled and then just put on rollers.
I a big points across the board deducted no grilled dogs today.
I feel like much infrastructure, too much infrastructure, but easy.
Oh, yeah. Sure. Yeah. Big time.
Yeah. This you know what?
This reminded me of it was not as wet, but it's I said this before on the show.
That my favorite part of playing soccer as a little kid
was getting a hot dog and the soda afterward.
And the hot dog would be wrapped.
And it was just it was so wet by the end of the game.
Whenever they had made them and brought them over to the field,
the hot dog would be pretty like wet and juicy.
And this is it did remind me of that.
So I did have a little flashback to my favorite part of soccer.
Eating a delicious, wet hot dog.
All right. Well, something about like the classic. Yeah.
Yeah. Love it.
By the way, I think we have not established how we're going to do
the scoring on this.
And my thought was to make this mathematical and also kind of Olympic style
where we are we're going on a scale of one to ten.
Us individual judges are
tallying up.
We do our own score and then we take like a mean of the three.
Yes. That becomes the official score.
And then we lock in our scores without saying them out loud to each other.
So that is a surprise to us by the end.
Yes. We enter it into the spreadsheet.
Who won? Right.
So with that said, do we think that we would you guys be comfortable
from one to ten locking in a score? Yes.
On any dogs? Be happy to.
Then let's just we'll do that.
I think I've got been locking in my score and locking my score. OK.
Great. So just, you know, keeps an air of surprise.
This that we will find out at the at the very end. Right.
So that is our feelings about diggity dogs.
Now we move.
Well, first things first, we try to go for, you know, what might be the big dog?
The heavily anticipated dog of the day, the one that inspired this idea
a little bit, which was seeing the big junkyard, chilly dog.
Yeah. At Ballast Point and sit down.
Disney, downtown Disney location, Ballast Point,
saw that at the at some bar seating, saw somebody enjoying that big old
like massive overflowing hot dog. That thing's impressive.
We got to go try that.
We head to downtown Disney.
It's a little after 11, not open.
Ballast Point, not open.
We don't know what's going on. Yeah.
Website says it should be open by then. I don't know.
Maybe we're going to have to check back in later.
So we will check back in later with Ballast Point.
Instead, we go into the park, a very late entrance into Disneyland.
There's a lot of hot dog hijinks before we actually go into Disneyland Park.
But on the way, we mobile order from refreshment corner.
And this might be the most iconic hot dog location, I feel, in Disneyland.
I think it's been a hot dog stand forever.
Maybe one of the first.
I don't know the history of the place.
Maybe we'll do an episode down down the road.
But two hot dogs from here.
Let's talk about the first, which was the electric relish dog.
Does anyone have the description in front of them or should I go for it?
OK. Yeah. An interesting one.
An interesting one.
You know, I think electric.
This is a seasonal return of the Main Street Electrical Parade.
Oh, that's OK.
So this might not be there.
This might glow away much like the parade itself.
So then it'll be back every constantly.
Yes, whenever they need money.
Lucy will let us kick the football one day.
The electric relish dog, all beef hot dog, bacon,
mustard cheese sauce, electric relish and sport peppers.
Electric relish doesn't tell me a lot like it's an electric relish dog.
And the ingredient is electric relish.
I guess it's just there's a little more going on.
You know, there's like those little like those little pops and seeds, whatever.
Seeds from like pickles, but some peppers and kind of like a hoagie spread.
Yeah. And pickles.
Relish is already like a weird neon color.
Yeah. Which I'm sure is food coloring.
But it's not it's it's not like the Chicago like bright green relish.
It was like more like a pepper.
It was not as bright as that. You're right.
Yeah. But but it's still pretty bright.
Pretty bright. Mm hmm.
So it is it is it makes sense with the Main Street Electrical Parade.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, interesting seasonal item.
I'll just say I was a fan of this one.
I liked this. I will say I was also a fan.
And it could very well go all the way today.
This was very surprising of like, wow, this is good.
Like, I like this a lot.
I didn't get that it was a mustard cheese sauce.
I thought it was just nacho cheese. Yeah.
I didn't either. But I liked whatever.
I actually missed the the ingredient.
I was and I was like, is this mustard or is this cheese?
But it landed in this beer cheese kind of zone or at least a theme park equivalent.
And I tend to like anything in that genre.
So, yeah, that's great.
And that's just kind of slathered on the back.
And you you you really sense that flavor separate from everything else.
That really like shines through, pops through.
You get just a full piece of bacon lining the entire not wrapped,
but just like, you know, baking down the middle.
Crispy and properly cooked.
Yeah. Shocking.
Yeah. Like is it for for Disney for Disney?
I've had much better pieces of bacon.
I've had better. Yes, you're right.
I've had worse at Disney.
But if you if you buy the pre cooked bacon that you can just microwave
and you do it correctly and it gets crisp, that's sort of what this was.
Yeah. So the bar kind of low.
So they surpassed it handily.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
I think like fun textures as part of that.
Yeah. Between bacon and and that electric relish.
And then the snap of the peppers as an interesting component to have on there.
I sport peppers. Yeah.
A nice maybe one of the more unique ingredients.
I wrote disgusting in the best way.
Ah, mm hmm.
Because what you're after with hot dog, if you're after especially the Disney,
it's not going to be a classy hot dog.
If you want, like all the all the layers of like fake cheese
and artificial color, whatever.
If it all goes good, like it all goes together.
And yes, I found it very good.
I found it satisfying in in a trashy way.
Yeah. If you want an indulgent kind of like carnival theme
parky kind of lunch, this is this is a good a good one.
Yeah. Yeah.
Also noticed at this location, hot dogs.
Unless I'm wrong. I mean, it's possible these are all the same dog.
But I felt like it was a little longer.
I think you maybe got it was longer.
You're right. Yeah.
Could it have been the same ingredients in the dog?
Probably. But I don't know. Yes.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe they just they just cut them a little longer.
It could have been it could have been tasted worse, honestly.
All the ingredients were slopped on there and it didn't even matter.
Yeah. I think you got to give it up.
That's that's one way to notch up hot dog in scoring is if you feel like
you're getting some value. Yeah.
And a little bit of bonus every inch counts. Yes, that's true.
Even if it's just a little bit.
That's right. It's doing something.
It's doing something.
So then we move to the other dog from this location.
The mac and cheese dog topped with bacon bits.
That's the full description.
There's no further way to the bacon.
Bits always taste a little bit like dog treats.
Yeah. This bacon, on the other hand, sucked.
Yeah, that's not. Yeah.
No. And bits coming right after a full hearty piece.
Bits cannot hold up to a piece.
I don't know. Yeah.
It's they eat all the way.
Peace all the way.
Peace all the way. I don't know how they cook these bits.
It seemed remarkably different.
I didn't like they didn't just cook strips and pound them with a hammer.
Pound them. Jason just made a pounding motion.
It was not. They were bigger, but they were less flavorful and greasier.
These are OK. So this is this.
This is basically the same.
I will sometimes have the mac and cheese cone in Cars Land with the cone.
It's got the like bread kind of bowl that's in the shape of a cone.
And this is the exact same mac and cheese, exact same bacon bits.
And these are consistent.
I don't hate the bacon bits as much as yours as you do, but they're not.
They don't taste like they should call it something different.
So my expectations are not set for bacon.
I don't know if the meat meat bites meat.
Just make it more generic or something.
And I'm I don't have the expectation of bacon.
Then. Yeah, sure, sure.
But you OK, so you're you're OK with you like that mac and cheese.
It's separately you've been OK with.
Yeah. And OK is a good word where it's like, I got to eat something quick
and I can walk around with it and then I can eat the cone.
It's kind of nothing.
It's it's like a less it's like a less good Stouffer's mac and cheese.
Like it's not a lot of texture.
It's just really creamy.
It's it's just kind of a nonentity.
I judge mac and cheese pretty harshly because I try to not have it very often.
I want that to be like a real treat, really done well.
If I'm going to go for it,
some sort of like gastropub or indulgent restaurant setting.
So if it lets me down and it's just boring and nothing,
what a bummer, because I'm probably not going to use that slot again
for a little bit.
Scott, I'm right there with you.
I like a really nice like baked or homemade mac and cheese.
Or I want a Kraft Blue Box.
I want the the shaky the bag of powder.
Oh, sure. Milk and butter that you do to your taste.
What about Amy? Do you do Amy's ever?
I like Amy's. Yeah, I like those.
Strong one. Sure. Yeah.
Amy's good shells, I believe you can do.
I've done shells. I've done the fun rabbit shapes.
I can make shells like a licensed character shape.
Well, sure. Yeah. Or whatever.
You know, I'm one of those in a while.
At some point in my parenting journey, I'm sure I will.
Yeah. The whole thing about I think with this,
but with this dog is maybe all of this.
Something I realized about my own taste.
I think I need something to cut through.
And that can be a little bit of spice or something,
even a little bitter or just like an interesting crunch or a texture.
Like if it's all if all the components are bland
and there's not like the one ingredient, if it's all base
and then there's no there's nothing up high end
like gliding through the base, then that doesn't work for me.
And this all just felt like, you know, you need like that.
I think a snap can be that there was no snapping, I would say all day.
That's another big detriment to all of these dogs.
That's why I was also like, this is Nathan's,
like bottom of the barrel, like licensed hot dog.
This is not a real Nathan's hot dog.
The smallest screen that IMAX offers.
Even like a true poorly prepared Nathan's hot dogs still has the spices
and a little bit of snap.
Does anyone make a Nathan's around here?
I don't think I've ever had enough.
I mean, maybe I haven't just didn't realize it,
but is there a place to get a Nathan's hot dog that I've always heard
so much about?
Buy them at the store and pan fry them yourself.
All right. I want to do that, though.
I want someone to make it for me.
Some places do use Nathan's as their stock.
OK. Nathan's are Hebrew national, I think, are the high end of like
easily acquired hot dogs. Yeah.
I'm a Vienna beef guy because that's like a Portillo style,
which I late tried to float to Scott the idea that we were going to take you
and us to Portillo's last night to finish off this.
But we did not do it. You didn't tell me that.
No, I did. Would you have gone for it?
He'd have no choice. He's in the car.
Yeah, I would have gone, but I would have opted for a cake shake.
All that then a cake for all that. That's right.
Yes. God, because I don't know.
After we went to the Woodbridge mall, Mike and I went to a Portillo's drive
through. I've never had a cake.
Honestly, I demolished a cake.
The cake shake was immediately so good.
And I was I was like, as I as I picked it up, I was like,
I'm not going to drink all this.
And I think by the time I was walking to Mike's family's house, it was like
finish the cake shake.
You were you're a treat terminator.
You can't be stopped like you just treat terminate.
I do control myself because as we were walking towards the exit last night,
I was like, I might get ice cream.
And I was like, no, don't push your luck. Just get a treat to go.
It's like you see the world through the terminator eyes and like there's targets
and then like ice cream target identified.
Yeah. Rocky Road.
If there was going to be art of Jason as the treat terminator,
like are the sort of the robot parts replaced with ice cream cones and
and hot dogs and is the red is the red robot eye a big cherry?
Well, yeah, you know what? I think it's that's good.
But it's also like some of the robot parts are like an ice cream scooper
on the end of one of the arm like it would be more like two thousand rather than.
Yeah, it could be like T one thousand where he can kind of change his shape.
So it could be like his arm changes into ice cream scooper or like a cake slicer or.
Yeah. Yeah.
The pizza roller.
I was going to say, what's the thing that you make ice cream in?
Oh, just an ice cream.
Like a tumbler crank.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So imagine, yeah, Robert Patrick's arms turn into an ice cream maker with a crank.
This is really I leave that up to you.
You want to use Arnold as a base.
Do you want it to be Robert Patrick?
Well, however, I just want some version of this to exist.
I think somebody will help us out.
I think we know we're heading with these.
You want to lock in our scores for the two refreshment corner locations.
Let's see. I think I know it.
Yeah. Locking it in. OK.
And as you guys continue to lock in now, we, I believe,
move over to the hot dog that we had a sit down reservation.
We reserved a spot at the Craftsman Bar, a location
we really like in the Grand California Hotel.
One of the great recent additions, this wonderful where you get the vibe
of the hotel pool and the and the fake Sequoia
vibes as well.
This what a relaxing, what a great place.
And I was delighted to discover that they have a hot dog of the month
that rotates through their lineup.
Food there, I've always found pretty solid, great place to drink to.
So I was really looking forward to this
and kind of delighted that they had a hot dog of the month. Yes.
Do we also?
Well, here, let's I guess let's say it first.
With Jason, you had a little more Intel.
It's a little not archived, but you found a little something about.
So like on the QR code menu you had to use, it just said hot dog of the month.
But I ask your server.
Yeah, ask your server, which is always funny.
Could you? Yes.
What's your wine list and what is the hot dog of the month?
But on the regular browser website, hot dog of the month
this month, just the month of May, pretty new.
The Gordito dog beef hot dog on lightly grilled flatbread
with black bean spread, melted cheese, cream up pica de gallo
and micro cilantro served with tortilla chips.
Incorrect. We got seasoned fries.
The menu said chips and we got the fries felt strange.
But delicious.
The fries were very easily some of the best fries on Disney property.
Great batter. Yeah, boy, that is a yeah.
But I'll be looking out for fries at that location.
Now, we talked about eliminating this because it's it's kind of heading
into Rontorap territory.
I think the naming of hot dog of the month is what kept it in the competition.
It is still a hot dog.
And look, it is look, it's a wiener inside at the end of the day.
It's a wiener. That's right.
I this didn't work for me.
No, no, no, no, no.
Did Jason disagree? It was delicious.
I thought it was delicious, but with some faults.
OK, OK. All of those toppings.
This is I think all those individual toppings I liked.
But when you put them all together on flatbread
that admittedly had been cut into three portions.
Yes, we may have destroyed a lot of these with the methods.
We got like a gooey or sauce or something.
And with the goo goo is the word I was going to use.
All of these toppings kind of destroyed the texture.
It just felt like a big goo dog.
But a big goo dog.
I and the dog, I'm pretty sure it was just the same hot dog.
I think it's exactly the same hot dog everywhere else.
Yeah, this is where I would expect, if not an elevated dog,
at least a charred dog a little.
Yes. And because the like the pizzas at that spot are fantastic.
I actually really like the food at this bar.
It's not just like, you know,
theme park food, but arranged better on a plate.
Yeah. Lobster quesadilla. Very tasty.
Man, for sharing, do not eat it yourself. You will feel bad.
I learned this the hard way about two months ago. OK, OK.
I but I was trying to taste some of this stuff, like even I was trying
to get the pico de gallo alone.
If you noticed, I was eating pieces of the pico de gallo alone and I go,
I don't think this pico de gallo is very good.
Yeah, I agree. I did not like very fresh.
It was not individual ingredients.
Yeah. And it was it was gooey and like the bean sauce was OK.
And it was obscuring every other taste.
And it wasn't particularly it wasn't anything more special than a Taco Bell
bean, like which I have once a week.
So I know I know my Taco Bell beans. Come on. Once a week.
Good question. Maybe it's usually at least once.
And yeah, it's sort of I couldn't taste the hot dog at all.
You taste this kind of like non flavorful bean sauce.
Couldn't taste the pico de gallo at all.
And then the wrap was just very bland and like didn't taste like anything.
It wasn't like a delicious flour tortilla or anything.
Yeah. And it didn't have that didn't have the char that you can maybe end up with.
Yeah. Yeah.
Rontos. You can't help but compare it to Ronto.
I feel like. Oh, yeah. Get that flatbread as part of it.
This is a good idea, I guess.
But I don't the execution and the ingredients I was very disappointed in.
Excited when we asked the server.
I was looking forward to it.
Yeah. I did then feel the most shame of the day when she brought our drinks
and then said, and you guys are you're just doing the hot dog of the month.
Yes, I yes, I also felt shame there as well.
Yeah. Yeah. And we thought about ordering a second one.
Yeah, but I'm glad we didn't.
It was bad. Yeah. Probably better.
We didn't. Wow. I didn't realize you guys felt so strongly.
We were kind of pulling our punches yesterday in terms of our reaction.
We all looked down. We're all staring.
I feel like at the table.
Yeah. Some of the reaction like you couldn't help making a comment or two.
You're there. And that's facial reactions.
I feel like we all had like a oh yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Couldn't hold it back entirely.
Can I talk about my error?
My like yellow.
Oh, I know what it is now. Yes. Yeah.
So I didn't feel like ordering a cocktail.
You guys had some beautiful looking ginger margaritas.
How were they? Very good. Very fun.
A good first like drink.
A little sugary.
So that's like your first one.
And then you could change to something relaxing.
And yeah, I didn't really feel like a drink.
I cocktail cocktail.
I wanted a little sugar kick.
I noticed a lot of places are starting to add, you know, mocktails,
non-alcoholic cocktails.
I thought I would try that.
So I ordered the coconut fruit punch,
which was just essentially like a Mike style candy drink.
Simply fruit punch, coconut water, simply limeade, vitamin water,
energy, tropical citrus with a splash of Sprite.
And then there were coconut shavings on top.
This made me feel so puffy.
It was delicious.
But even more so than the multiple hot dog segments I'd eaten,
finishing this whole like tall glass of fruit punch, candy juice,
which is not surprisingly for a man who likes sweets.
Fruit punch is not often a go to.
It tasted good.
It was something different.
But I was like I was happy for the walk to California Adventure
to before we had to eat more hot dogs.
I would say any break in the hot dog eating was was crucial.
Yes. Much needed.
Yeah. Well, you know, we all had to think about how we're going to pace ourselves
and what's going to help us along.
Yes. Drinking a bunch of candy.
Maybe not a good idea.
Today, I'm feeling like having a bunch of wine and beer was not a good idea.
But, you know, hey, it made me it made it go down smoother.
Give me the energy I needed during the day.
So no regrets then.
Yeah. You know, here's what I think.
I think that this this program, the Hot Dog of the Month program
at the Craftsman Bar, I think a different craftsman
Hot Dog of the Month could take it.
I feel that they have quality in them.
But I don't know that this one or just did not work for me.
I think recently there was like a pig in the blanket style dog.
When I was there before, it was a pastrami dog.
OK, yeah, I think they're I think they're getting too full of themselves over there
and they're thinking they can do anything at that kitchen and they can't.
You can't put anything on it.
Anything doesn't work.
You know, like I think just play it a little bit more like with the with the hits.
Play it a little more with what works.
Pigs in a blanket. It works. Chicago dog. Sure.
Always rely. I don't think I've I'm sure there's bad Chicago dogs,
but I feel like just there's so many toppings.
It's a great preparation of hot dog. Yeah, yeah, I agree.
Not one of those yesterday. OK, well, we do.
We feel good. We want to.
By the way, I should put
fractions, decimals on the table.
I don't think it has to be a clean.
I'm doing point by I'm doing point five.
All right. Five. Yeah.
All right. Great. Do point to twos.
Do point nine one six, whatever you want to do.
Yeah, I think I've locked mine in.
OK, so now we keep moving to another one of the primary spots
where hot dogs can be found and expectations
should be high. Hot dogs being there, their bread and butter.
Yeah. And that is the infamous award wieners.
Well, we did something. Oh, you're totally right.
I apologize. I don't mean to cut you out.
No, no, you are correct.
Because at this point in the day, really, what we did
was go and check in again on the once closed ballast point,
because that junkyard dog I saw with my own eyes.
Yeah. And I really think this thing has what it takes to to take it all the way.
It was a very impressive looking hot dog.
We walk up to ballast point and ask if we could get a table for three.
And it is a it is an attitude.
It is a scoff is what I feel like the idea that we could be so foolish
as to think we could just waltz right up to ballast point.
It was Spago table Beverly Hills.
And we were like dressed in like the worst
like the newspaper and like we our hair was messed up.
And we were like just came from like sweeping a chimney or something.
And we were like, table now.
That was the attitude we got from the person at you.
Ballast. Well, you want to eat here.
Spago actually very accommodating.
A lot of rich people look like shit in there.
OK, fine. Like shit.
And I have been it's always a pretty utilitarian.
Like you can probably just walk into the bar, order the full menu.
Yeah. Well, Mr.
Mr. Fancy, again, trying to go better.
And anyway, let's get back to my real passion. Hot dogs.
Yeah. Yeah. And I was like, oh, yeah, I know.
I mean, who are we to think that we could just walk up here
at three thirty on a Tuesday and get a table to get a beer and a hot dog?
I mean, this place obviously is always jammed to the brim.
It's not. And by the way, and the precedent has said that like,
you know, you can check for later today,
but you kind of got to do it days in advance.
Also, already weird, because that hostess, the host stand always there.
I'd never seen anyone there before.
You have. I have.
Have you because a month ago,
I walked up during a lunch rush and said, hey, do you have a table?
I had a 10 minute wait and walked right up.
And I and the time before that and the time before that.
Ballast Point was becoming a go to.
And I never waited more than 10 minutes, sometimes walked right up
at a like a busy lunchtime and it was fine.
This new thing of you got to do it days in advance.
What do you mean on open table?
Uh huh. Not on the kids.
Do it off Disneyland dot com.
There's no way to find a way to make reservations.
Ballast Point. You fucked up.
I was so ready to give you another chance.
Yes. And if everybody doesn't know, Jason has been mad at Ballast Point
ever since he saw in a grocery store that their beer was a dollar
more than a normal beer.
They're all. And you know what?
There's so many more microbreweries available now, making just as good
for less per unit.
And another, if you if you don't remember that, I find one of the famous
catchphrases of the show was born that day.
I don't think we've referenced it in a while.
I believe it was correct me if I'm wrong.
Who gives a fuck about grapefruit?
Yeah. Who gives a shit about grapefruit?
Who gives a shit about grapefruit?
Yeah, because we were just talking about the grapefruit.
The raw anger that you were boiling, boiling like a hot dog.
And it turned out Jason was right.
I guess Ballast Point would come to bite us.
I was ready to let bygones be bygones.
I was ready like, you know what?
Let's give him another shot.
Because my experience has usually been
the other kind of annoying where it's like you walk upstairs
and it's kind of like first come first serve ever man for himself.
That kind of bar thing where you just kind of have to sit and wait.
Are you are you leaving?
Are you like indoor or outdoors?
Or you just walk into the bar.
I was and I wouldn't see. I'll just take.
Hey, what do you want?
You know, that's that's been my experience.
Yeah. What happened?
This had this had become I declared this.
This is my new favorite and Disney.
Oh, wow. And how does it suddenly within a month?
It is a line out the door.
Is this shape X fault somehow?
It's got to be. Got to be.
Got to be. Yeah.
It would be DeSantis fault somehow.
I know this is California, but this might this might be
retribution in some ways.
Fucking with Ballast Point.
So but what they didn't count on and I did.
You know, I didn't make the the hostess deal with this.
This isn't on her.
It's on the corporation. Of course.
But I say now at anyone from the corporation listening,
you didn't realize that you were shooing away people with a platform.
Unbelievable microphones and that you have just publicly, humiliatingly
been withdrawn from consideration for the hot dog hullabaloo.
You could have been had this crown like this little like trophy
now on your mantle of winning this prestigious new award from our
most beloved of all theme park slash food, all food podcasts,
any food podcasts were the obviously the most popular one.
Yes, very much.
And you could have won this award from us.
And yeah, maybe you were a little cranky when Jason put you on blast
a few years ago, but this would have redeemed you.
And now look what you've done.
Look what you've done.
No reason. When you when these faces walk up, you find a spot.
You tell some other people to scram.
Yeah. Tell some people who don't know who don't even like imagine
not having a podcast. Our photos point.
And they're letting non podcast havers eat up there.
Any mall outside a theme park, there should be three little pictures
by the podium of our three faces.
The opposite of banning people from the gates.
Yeah, exactly. Yes.
Always, always allow in because we weren't going to we're not.
We don't brag. We don't say look at our podcasts.
Let me show you the downloads.
We don't say stuff like that when we go around.
We're all but humble podcasters.
But that's just because we don't want to say it.
We want you to be able to identify us.
So we have to pretend to be likable. Right.
Pretend so anyone will listen. Exactly.
But out in. Oh, you should see.
You should see how we have to be because if we we don't come in
with an attitude, this is what happens.
And I'm looking out for them.
I don't why I didn't want Ballast Point to suffer a humiliating blow
in the hot dog hullabaloo, but they did it.
They did it to themselves.
And then to make it even worse, I said, well, maybe we should just drive
to Long Beach, which is where Ballast Point has another spot.
Right. We were thinking about and we were with any of you know, right.
And we were like, well, we're trying to help balance point out.
And we looked and we said, OK, well, it's 30 minutes away.
It's not so bad. It's inconvenient, but not so bad.
And then we looked at the menu.
There is not the word junkyard and there's not the word dog.
Junkyard dog on the long beach.
Ballast Point.
We would have made a special trip off property and still given it to the if
if it merited it, if it merited, we could have still won.
And no, they but they don't have that dog in Long Beach.
They deny they're like, you guys don't deserve cooked food,
actual cooked food today.
I even asked, do you do take out on Google?
Less than says dine in, take out what?
So lies about when they open.
So lies about take out lies about we've always been an establishment
that you must book. We that you know, that big beverage,
you know, conglomerate who owns them now.
Now, yeah, they're the ones jacking that dollar.
Slipping a few years ago.
I already saw it. Jason had it.
I thought the wind changing.
Would ultimately pay off here.
What sort of thing doesn't happen at Golden Road?
It's also owned by a massive beverage conglomerate.
That's the haven't had any bad experiences.
So, oh, well, well, yeah, is it?
Yeah, that's I think that's what I objected to in that argument is like,
yeah, imagine being part of a conglomerate.
Now let's continue our show where we talk about things put out by nothing
but conglomerates every single week.
Well, that was the big lesson of the doubt that there's a deal is that all of these
were owned by like a massive eyeglass conglomerate, a flip flop conglomerate.
Like it was just so much more sinister than city walk.
It's all conglomerates. Yeah.
So many conglomerates.
All we can do is track their boring names
and try to enjoy their product, but they wouldn't let us.
So you're out. You lose zeros all around.
And thus we we took it to a place that would never turn us away
and that takes pride in hot dogs, and that is award wieners.
Award wieners, one of the pun based Hollywood locations that has remained.
They it's keeping that DCA one point of spirit alive.
The full title, they've got the subtitle of its award wieners in a supporting role.
I might be missing part of that title.
I like that. I think that is what it is.
There's a big statue that's kind of a fake Oscar holding a hot dog.
I'll make sure I have the copy totally correct.
But fun play.
Were you were you guys previously familiar with a best wiener in a award?
Wieners best wiener in a supporting role as the full title.
Were you were you guys previously experienced with award winners?
Sure. Yeah, I've had award winners over the years.
This the menus changed a lot over the years.
I think a little better right now.
A little bit on an upswing.
This was unfortunately one of the L's we took.
Mike Mobile ordered the dogs here real quick.
We got a mountain of a lot of blame being put on Mike.
No, no, I should have been.
I should have been looking out.
This location has something they call film strip
fries, which are kind of fluffy.
I don't know, like a potato chip shaped French fry.
I don't know how to describe them. They're good.
The film strip fries are good. I recommend.
I think QDs.
Oh, yes. Well, I think QDs were good for offsetting
everything we're doing to ourselves.
So I have no regrets about the QDs.
I'm also the one time I went here before had those film strip fries.
Did not like them at all.
You did. We were on different sides of the spectrum.
Those were like chalky and hard.
And I, I, they were.
I think I got them like fresh out of the fryer a few months ago.
And and they were.
Or they've up their game.
I had this. I did the film strip fries years ago.
Are they these? Yeah.
Little curly guys. Little curly.
Kind of like fair food. Don't like that.
I've never had. I do not like these.
You're going to have to break the tie at some point.
OK, I have to get some film strip fries.
Go down tonight. I'm a sucker if I see curly fries, crinkle cut
frat like something that's not just a straight fry.
Yeah, but these didn't do it.
I OK. Yeah, I don't know.
It's fair.
Probably would have racked us just like the junkyard dog.
That's part of it. Yes.
Throwing off the equilibrium. Absolutely.
I think we needed those cuties just to the cuties like slowed us down.
Presumably gave it if nothing else, like the little like the
the water inside them was probably good for us.
Yeah, that was.
The first item that we had here, the bacon street dog.
That is an all beef hot dog dipped in a house made roasted red pepper
ketchup topped with grilled onions, bell peppers and crispy bacon
crumbles served on a toasted bun potentially with film strip fries,
but not in our case with a little cutie.
What do we think of the bacon street dog?
Good. I liked it. Yeah, I liked it.
Kind of folded Texas toast, the toasted buns.
I feel like I saw a surprise to me first time I went. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not sure I feel about the Texas toast.
I thought better.
I thought it was more of a split top bun, like a lobster roll bun.
But no, it was more like a folded piece of Texas toast.
But not buttered, not like butter.
Yes, this is the problem.
Because what's the point of having all this extra bread
if it's not going to be a big sweet piece of Texas toast?
Well, but it held together, I think, better than the stale buns everywhere else.
Well, the stale buns, yes, are bad.
But I'm just saying if you're going to get a big piece of bread,
that's you're getting more calories or, you know, than a normal roll
or a normal bun, why would you not want it to be fun then?
What's the point of having more bread if it's not a different taste or more fun?
You know what I'm saying?
Because if it's Texas toast, the fun of Texas toast is that it's buttered.
Yeah, it's indulgent. Yeah, exactly.
It's like almost a piece of French toast.
Like what's the point?
We may as well just have a regular, a smaller piece of toast.
If you want to do a different texture, that's fine.
I got to say this, though.
I I'm not craving butter to be dripping off either.
These are the heaviest dogs we had.
No, I don't want a butter.
I'm just saying there's no reason to have that much bread
if it's not some fun element.
You may as well have less bread because it's not like it's adding
some extra fun, crazy element to it.
That's all I'm saying. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
More more bread, not of the yeah. Yeah.
I don't know. I got to say I was a fan of this, though.
I agree. Yeah.
And as opposed to those previous bacon bits, these bacon crumbles,
I was scraping up, I was grabbing them off the plate, the ones that fell off.
I thought the the peppers were delicious.
And now here we get like this is stuff that's cutting through.
It's biting its spice and its texture.
Yes, that mac and cheese on top.
It's just it's cream on bread on like uniform meat.
I need little I need like little bits that are fun to,
you know, toss around in my mouth before they add down the hatch.
The red pepper ketchup.
The red pepper ketchup. Good.
I good. The best condiments of the day.
The peppers all fresh.
Are you like felt like much more fresh?
All that stuff felt much more fresh than anything in the special.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah, I yeah.
You know what? The fan, that's kind of all I got to say about it.
I liked it.
Mm hmm.
The other one from this location, the Uptown Chili Dog,
an all beef hot dog topped with homestyle chili,
pepper, jack cheese and corn chips served on toasted by Texas toast.
What do you think of Uptown Chili Dog?
All right. Well, a big thing of mine going in is that I usually avoid
chili dogs at theme parks because they have made me sick multiple times.
Now, I think both of those signs were coming out of Universal Studios Hollywood.
Looking back, maybe one Hollywood, one Florida.
So that said, I was a little hesitant about the specter of any chili.
Now, I was looking forward to the chili one because I was feeding off.
You were just so excited for Ballast Point.
Of course, that defeated us.
I was bracing myself for this chili dog.
Happy to see Fritos.
I so rarely eat Fritos.
Now, as we were eating it, I had a something come over me and I said,
I believe.
That this is Hormel chili.
I wrote down the quote, it was because there was there was
there were these pregnant pauses.
I am I am reasonably certain
this is Hormel chili.
It just felt as I said, you know,
it today's the Star Wars day as we're recording this.
I said I felt a presence I've not felt in a long time.
I am pretty sure in the way that like the the mac and cheese
or the man chees earlier, I don't necessarily think was so first.
But it was in the ballpark of Stouffer's this.
I was like, I think this was an industrial fat of Hormel.
Like, that's what I couldn't tell is if that's a good thing or bad thing.
I don't know. It was unclear.
I think I want a little something if I'm cooking it at home. Fine.
But I think I just want a little something more.
This this taste it like someone wrote down the concept of a chili.
It was just kind of nothing.
This one was kind of nothing. It didn't do it for me.
I did not know that was pepper jack cheese until you read the description.
That's yeah, I felt the same way.
I was surprised when I saw it.
You want that to be the little spice that cuts through. Did not.
I didn't hate this. Yeah, I didn't hate it.
But it was it doesn't all work together.
I feel like temperatures were off.
The chili should have been a little warmer.
I mean, I know it's impossible the way they do everything, but it just did.
And it didn't gel in the way that that street dog did, wherever you all the flavors
worked together to make one special taste.
Nothing, by the way, nothing like an actual L.A. street dog.
Well, you're a big.
I've never actually even gotten one.
But yeah, I'll turn around after we leave a wrestling show or a concert.
And Jason's right at the vendor getting one of those sizzling.
They're good. I'm not even putting.
I mean, I have some I don't like this strip of mayo on it.
But if they have like a little green salsa or a little avocado or nacho cheese,
I'll take a little.
Those grills that kind of like, you know, summon the flavors of the onions
and like the hot dogs are imbued with like anything else that hit that grill
in a good way. Yeah.
Those post Hollywood Bowl show. That's fantastic.
Yeah. It's like George Carlin's character, Jersey Girl, says,
don't pour out the grease.
I need something. I need to cook the pork roll in that.
We all remember that scene.
That's a very that's maybe the most New Jersey line ever written in a movie.
There's a George Carlin quote for everything.
George Carlin quote. Yeah.
And most of them are from Jersey.
I probably butchered it, but look it up, folks.
I also would dock the chili dog points for being so late in the day.
I think I think that's a tough one to do later.
Could have been tough at ballast point to have kind of the heaviest,
the heaviest one, because this was where I started to feel it.
Maybe I started going a little downhill.
I think around this. Yeah.
I think I said, I don't feel sick, but I am very full.
I am full now.
The chili also like the quality.
Yeah, I don't know Hormel from anything else, but even like I'm
tasting this chili and I'm like the chili at Wendy's is better than this.
Yeah. Like that's bad.
Like that's more specific or flavorful.
But you guys might be impacting.
I wrote down a score and I've notched the score down a little bit.
No, I think I agree.
Look, we don't operate and we're not in separate soundproof booths here.
That's not the idea.
We're creating a discussion, but math will determine it at the end of the day.
Do you want to lock in scores?
Yes, I would like to lock it in.
Award wieners.
Got it. Please. Great.
At this point in the day, we took a much needed hot dog break.
I had concerns about is the hot dog Hula Baloo going to prevent me
from going on Guardian's mission breakout, which I am still a little edgy about.
And I feel like such a pro now.
I was fine. Even loaded up with many hot dogs and questionable chili.
Right. Yeah. Totally fine.
Well, you got the right.
We hung out at the Pym Bar and you had a glass of wine, Mike had a beer.
I just was pounding glasses of water.
And yeah, we did guardians and web slingers said I do a very nice listener.
Thank you for saying hello.
Yeah. So we we cleansed the pallet for the walk to the Jason.
As you pointed out, all these hot dogs are oddly central in the parks.
Like they're all clustered in the middle, except for this one all the way
at the other end of California Adventure, Lonely Outpost.
And we went to the wharf first before we went to the lonely outpost.
We went to like the wharf food court.
You and I had a beer, had the blonde and that brought me back to life.
Yeah, that gave me a second wind having a drink that day.
Interesting salad, an interesting looking salad.
That's yeah, I don't know.
It was what was it even called?
It was like a Chinese chicken salad.
I came with three slices of fresh sourdough.
That's from the bread.
Yeah, it was from the bread place.
It was fine. I there was some cucumbers.
I just needed something.
Look, it was green.
That wasn't. Yeah, I maybe should have.
Though that salad did not look good to me.
I just came home and approximated in a side bowl as much as I could do.
I know a side at home, but just like cereal, almonds, banana, fruit, blueberries.
A lot of sugar, though, still.
I guess so. Yeah.
But that might have been why you were feeling it in the morning, too.
Cereal bowl, did it?
Well, there's all the there's a lot of sugar in the fruit.
I'm just saying if you had like the in the banana and the blueberries,
you think the even after a day of drinking and hot dogs,
this is this is what I face on this show.
I'm not saying it's the worst thing in the world.
I'm just saying that that's it's a little sugary.
And it's all at the end of the day.
And it's all the end of the day.
Yeah, it's possible. But it's not a lot of very plain cereal, though.
Sure. OK. Because sometimes even granola.
You have to remember, I'm me and not you.
Well, I wouldn't make a side bowl with fruity pebbles.
Although it sounds good now that I say it.
I love there were some granola in Nature Valley.
Granola bars just keeps making more and more products
that are like trying to be dessert.
And it's like, no, I want you to make like horse feet.
I want you to make a bar of just oats.
Like, I want you to make less sugar.
I know, because I even I will go in somewhere
and I want to get a little like like vegetable juice.
And even like some of the companies that make like stuff
that has more vegetables actually in it, still they have to make it sugary.
I finally did I say this already?
I finally found they have like an avocado juice at Trader Joe's,
which doesn't taste sugar.
I'm like, finally, there's a green drink
that you can just grab off the shelf that doesn't still taste
like it's trying to be some sweet juice.
I tried it after you told me about it, and I think the taste is very good.
It is refreshing.
It's got the texture of drinking Green Goddess salad dressing.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
It's a little. Yeah, but that's good.
Like that's don't don't let me off easy.
I don't. I know. I want a thin.
I want a very watery good.
I love it. I want a cold, fresh.
I love it. Very watery.
That's what I like. I'm sorry.
So this final stop, a newer one on the horizon, Angry Dogs.
This is part of the Pixar Pier expansion is one of the quick little stands.
It's very well themed.
You get a gray. You get anger from inside out.
The Lewis Black character who is who is blowing up,
who is shooting fire out of the top of his head, screaming great.
They just did a good job with that.
All those little booths I like. Oh, yeah. Senior buzz and
all well done.
So there's a regular dog here, which they wait.
The name of it's kind of slightly less annoyed dog.
Yes, I know.
I thought, yeah, the angry dog and the slightly less annoying.
Yes, I think that's right. Yeah.
But we did angry dogs.
That's the, you know, the interesting one here.
And this just came plane.
Now we're back into condiment territory, but with a couple of new friends.
You got Sriracha here since it is a spice place.
And that's a good addition. Nice to see that.
They could probably use that at a bunch of these locations.
Yeah. So I liked that.
But I'll throw it to you.
Would you how do you feel about the angry dog?
Probably the best flavored dog.
Yeah, I think because of the spice closer to that hot line corn dog.
I like. Yeah. Yeah.
Finally, something some of that is boiled.
When when Pixar beer first opened, there was like a line of condiment
dispensers like Sriracha or Buffalo, you know, spicy mustard, regular mustard.
Right. Like where you that was part of the novelty, I think.
Again, everything's kind of been standardized, everything in packets now.
This is where relish exploded.
That'd be a nice more pumps.
Less packets is what I think we should come out of this episode saying every day.
Yeah. For us to make our dog goo.
Yeah. Yeah. Just put that all in one sentence.
And that's what we say now.
It's a loaded sentence.
So I did like that.
I guess, you know, while I liked the taste, I am looking at that actual dog
and like, what are these weird streaks of red?
What am I eating?
I mean, I just not think about that all day.
I just can't.
Red pepper.
Yeah. The streaks are probably less alarming than whatever the meat is.
Yeah. I was looking at somebody.
I don't think there's any like official confirmation of what dogs,
but some I saw some message boards, people saying like Disney World
is like it's like 20 percent chicken, 80 percent beef or like something like that.
I don't think any of these are like all beef kosher.
Yeah, no, not really well seasoned dogs.
Yeah. Yeah.
But probably not pork, people think also probably no pork, but like part chicken,
part beef. Yeah.
So we pray that that's all it is.
I think was one of the kids labeled a turkey dog.
There were. Yes, there was a kid.
We did not do it because it was kids.
The dog was too tiny. Yeah.
And we also didn't do a veggie at award wieners.
Oh, right, right.
But the listeners asked about that and they were like, yeah, it's fine.
You said it was fine.
I said it was fine. Yeah.
Jane and God and I had a bite of it a few months ago and it was kind of fine.
He does this. Oh, God, this drives me nuts.
Is someone from Philadelphia where it's like a Philly dog,
like green peppers and onions, like you don't put green peppers on a cheese.
Like it's like a cheat, like vegan cheesesteak dog.
And it's like I don't the vegan part is fine.
I don't care about that.
But so many places like you see it, it went some places like real cheesesteak
sandwich, green and red pepper. It's like, no, stop it.
No, that's not interesting. OK.
I knew that I don't think I knew those were out of bounds.
I think like banana peppers or hoagie spread or like spicy pepper.
Yes. You made me so hungry with that list of ingredients of the stuff
I actually want to eat as we've been.
We spent all day dealing with hot dogs yesterday, talking about them today.
You describing any other genre of food?
I said hoagie spread and Scott burst his mouth with saliva.
Oh, he's like the easiest.
Like if you go to Jersey Mike's, their pepper spread like pepper relish
on like that kind of thing.
Vinegar, very a lot of absence of vinegar yesterday.
Yeah, no vinegar to cut off like good on top of hot dogs to cut the fat,
to cut the grease.
None of these are like.
I will find out at the end.
Are we? I'm curious if anybody's given out any nines or tens. Yes.
OK, really. All right. All right.
But is that in your in your mind, is that on the scale?
Yeah, that's or would you?
That's why I'm Veer and lower.
I left I left.
I left some room for portillo's or other things I've had that are like
top of the line in my mind. OK, OK.
Yes. Some invisible.
They're not getting ranked, but yeah.
And also for improvement for Disney, you know. Yeah.
I think so. There's nothing I would give it a 10.
I can see 10 on the scale of what we're doing.
Yeah. I think general hot.
That makes sense. That's perfectly valid.
I mean, it'll still come out.
It'll still come out in the same order of victory.
Yeah. Yes, Joey. Angry dogs.
Yeah, I think it's like this.
This would be if I had a choice between maybe the first diggity dog
or the angry dog, just like as J.
Oh, maybe. OK. Say I'm an angry dad and I've got a family and I'm mad
and I need to eat something.
And I just like my my anger will not be quelled.
And then we turn the corner and we see anger from inside out.
And my young son says, Daddy, look, it's you.
And then I said I like first I'm mad because he's insulting me
and calling me this character.
But then I go, you know what? It does look like me.
And I have a little bit of a chuckle and I say, oh, we can get a quick
hot dog here.
I think I would want that one better than I would want diggity dog.
I think that would make me that would.
What about all my move?
The kid this is too this is too complex for the kid.
You think that the scenario is too complex?
No, they had the dog. Oh, yeah.
I think they got it.
Well, you got to just do the slightly less annoyed.
Yeah, they got they got the better one.
Or some kid.
My brother, very young age, was like very in the spicy stuff, like Jack it up.
Yeah. Well, this kid you describe, though, is such a wiener,
not in the hot dog.
This is your initial description of that kid.
This I that does throw a tantrum.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, Dad was throwing a tantrum in my scenario.
Oh, there isn't the kid.
The kid was actually making roasting dad.
Me. This probably solves both because dad gets to have spicy dog.
There's a beer stand like steps away.
I think they had one beer.
They had one Firestone Walker beer.
Static. Yeah.
Yeah.
But I guess all all that to say,
if it was just between diggity dog or this, this, I think it's fun.
It's a fun little change up.
And you can you put as much sriracha or as little as you want.
You still get a little heat.
It's just yeah, it's a little bit more of a fun thing.
And if it's a quick kind of snack meal, I would go with this over regular.
I almost yeah, I would in general, I would recommend it.
I think if you're you know, grabbing a quick
but if you're grazing as we were all day, I think I know where I'm locking this in.
Yeah.
Well, have we and one more thing to cop to.
There are there were hot dogs available at Wetzel's Pretzels,
but Wetzel's Pretzels was pulled from the competition due to past sins against Jason.
I mean, you guys were welcome to do it.
I was not to kind of ruined already ruined my being present
and fully enjoying my I fly experience during the City Walk Saga.
And I was not reliving that now.
Did I?
I forget what exactly I should go back and listen
if I had like a single pretzel dog or like little mini pretzel dogs.
But I could be wrong.
And that's probably where maybe thinking back, I did it wrong at City Walk.
So it's like sitting out.
Those are just like a single pretzel dog had never done me dirty before.
So yeah, maybe this was where I should have given my second chance.
But I think we were all still in such a haze from being swerved by Ballast Point.
I also think, you know, this is the inaugural hullabaloo.
So I think we were also trying to sort of feel out like what we were trying
to strike a balance between what was doable, but also funny and pushing it
a little bit.
Maybe we didn't push it enough.
Maybe in hindsight, we should have done those.
And now next time we do some sort of hullabaloo, we will know
how to push it a little bit more than we would.
We've got to be worse to ourselves.
We should be a little worse to ourselves.
A little worse. Yeah, that's what I think.
You know, we'll make our month in advance park pass
and then we'll make our six week out of Ballast Point reservation.
It's like three guys can't run around eating hot dogs,
said several theme parks and hotels.
It's like they were trying to cut back on the most annoying guests
that were that were the least likely to spend
actual money the other all the other times they went.
I think why would we not be welcome?
The people who went to reserved a table at a sit down restaurant
and proceeded to all split a twelve dollar hot dog.
We didn't want our drinks and tip and so we did.
Yes, we weren't savages.
I had an extra that's for the couple bucks.
OK, that's good.
Well, I think we're at the point where maybe we step down for a second
and we calculate and we reveal I don't exactly know
where this is going to land,
but I think it's time for the judges to tally the scores
and we find out the winner of the inaugural hot dog hullabaloo.
All right, I have opened the digital envelope
and calculated the scores done all the tallying.
And I just want to say there's,
you know, to all of the hot dogs, it's not about winning.
It's about that you're all sort of mediocre.
And probably Disney should have some better hot dogs.
But I do think I am sure that if we were to do
if we had done the hot dog hullabaloo 25 years ago, there would have been.
I bet a lot more competitors that were all essentially the same.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
I'm sure there were so many more hot dogs at Disneyland.
This is actually it's gotten better.
Yeah, I think so.
And there were some things there.
There were there were some that I sort of wish I had had the entire thing.
Not that badly.
I am glad that we did the thirds.
And there were like two.
I was like, oh, I could have eaten the whole thing.
Yeah, yes. Yeah.
But who will take the whole thing?
Let's find out as I read the final scores.
Diggity dogs, the unadorned fake Nathans, all beef.
Mike six, Jason five, Scott four.
Median score of five right in the middle.
Right. Probably where it should be.
The electric relish dog from the refreshment stand.
Mike eight point five, Jason nine, Scott eight, eight point five.
Thus far. Wow.
The mac and cheese dog from the same establishment.
Mike seven.
Kind of surprised by that.
I said I had, but I said I've eaten.
It's kind of like that mac and cheese.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
On the opposite end of the spectrum, Jason two.
Wow.
That mac and cheese just destroyed the bun like that.
It was just like a pile.
It was the first what you I knew something was up
because you said this would be the first that I do not finish.
She didn't even finish a third.
Yeah. And I gave it a three point five.
Thus weighing it all down at four point one six.
Six, six, six, six, six. The decimals keep going.
Craftsman hot dog of the day.
The Gordita dog. The month.
Oh, if it was the day of they were a different hot dog.
You would give it a little more leeway.
Yeah, but there's also there's not three hundred sixty five types of hot.
That said, I'd like to see what they did for Christmas.
What's a good Christmas hot dog?
Oh, yeah, I would guess candy cane
on candy cane instead of beef.
I was going to say probably a interpretation of the gobbler.
A Thanksgiving dinner kind of thing.
Because I sure turkey dinner, I feel like works for either Thanksgiving or Christmas.
It's like a hot dog shaped piece of a roast. Yeah.
Meat roast. Oh, no.
Turkey dog cranberry mustard stuffing.
Maybe sounds OK.
Yeah. Well, if that's what the craftsman's doing in November,
and then I'll go check it out. Yeah.
But for now, what they're doing, they're Cinco de Mayo entry.
The Gordita dog, Mike five point five.
Jason seven point five. Oh, my God.
Scott three. Wow.
Wow. I think I was low as anyone here.
Point should have gone lower. Sorry.
OK, so now we move over to award wieners.
Will any of them be award winners today?
Let's find out the bacon street dog.
Seven point five from Mike seven point five from Jason seven point six.
Wow. Wow.
Great minds think alike, but one decimal point off of like this landing at it.
The confusing seven point five.
I was a little looking back.
I looked back on it fondly, and that's why I had to give it that score.
Because I was like, you know what?
I did like it. All the pieces were pretty good.
I think I was pretty worn out at that point in the day.
So I was trying not to let that influence my decision.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You got to remove where you're at.
The ballast point anger should not reflect on this location.
The uptown chili dog, Mike six point five.
Jason three.
Scott five point five.
Thus landing at an even five.
There's only one more that has the chance to take it.
The remaining scores for the inside out inspired angry dog.
Mike seven.
Jason seven.
Scott seven.
Wow. Wow.
Two of them. We landed exactly even more.
Exactly. That puts it at seven.
Just above that, at number two, the bacon street dog at seven point five three.
And taking the the full event
at the winner of the hot dog, Hullabaloo
is the refreshment corners electric relish dog at eight point five.
A very strong eight point five.
A strong eight point five.
I really enjoyed it.
I was a little conflicted.
It being a limited time, probably seasonal dog.
Who knows how long it'll stick around.
I'd love to have another one. I'll be honest.
I would eat another one.
I think they captured lightning in a bottle here.
Any corn dog at the Disneyland Resort?
Probably still a better bet.
But so yeah, yeah.
Well, I think that's maybe where this goes by saying that corn dogs
corn dogs are not hot dogs.
I think it sets up some future event such as this.
And I hope everyone enjoyed this.
The the you know, the winner, the electric relish dog, the losers, us
for gathering around paper plates and tearing hot dogs in three.
But hopefully the audience felt like winners hearing about our exploits.
And now I pose it to the audience.
Is there any other journey of this nature that you would like to?
Would you like us to do any other completion of a genre of food
at Disneyland, at anywhere else?
Send us on a mission.
It feels like corn dogs, probably the next one.
And the if the corn the corn dog champion taking on the hot dog champion.
I'd be interested to see.
Yeah, I mean, corn dog, a lot simpler.
There's only like three or four varietals.
Maybe more if you add in whatever weirdo downtown Disney
card is going, but I think this was a much more pleasant journey overall
than like the the Gulf of like the hamburger hullabaloo
or like the pizza party.
Like there's some the golf between the pizza in the parks and like the pizza,
like Vietnam or like the black tap burgers compared to the park burgers.
Do you like a steakhouse kind of burger?
Oh, but about a steaks on
we do this.
Would you like us all to have some nice steak show?
Tell you how delicious they were.
The steak showdown.
We're walking around to tuxedos.
John, different.
I want to remind everyone, though, if we do do the corn dog thing,
I have not had a corn dog since one made me throw up when I was like five or six.
Well, I will be returning.
I have not had a corn dog since because just it has the memory of it.
But I'm willing to your therapy like the Maury episodes where he's like shows
someone a tarantula and they run around the audience.
If I could get a minotaur to feed me a corn dog, a lot of my problems would go away.
So lump all the fears together.
That's right.
I know that.
I don't think that would freak you out more.
No, Michael.
There's more fun ones like milkshake madness.
Like there's not that many milkshake madness.
Oh, that's what you want.
Cake shake in the mix.
You were now you're begging to be sent on these.
This is like now.
What about doing one of these?
Ice cream?
Once ice cream.
I did.
What about once a month?
We do one of these.
Oh, no.
It's becoming our only fans.
Like, you know, I'll do it.
I'll I'll I'll use this toy if you want me to, just because I have to.
As the darkest thing I've ever heard.
No, as often as comes up,
the only fans thing much more dignified than us slogging through theme park
hamburgers, much more respectable.
I think we should just do getting I know where we will follow in his footsteps,
which is get the Mr.
And just review all this food and just do a whole full YouTube channel.
We just pivot to YouTube, pivot to video.
We're pivoting to video.
Yeah, yeah, it's coming.
OK, well, send us a will, you know, whatever, whatever.
What do you want us to do next?
Leave a comment below.
Send us on our next mission.
Do you want us to eat a lot of something?
Let us know.
My name's Mike.
Click here, here, here.
We're here. I'm pointing.
You can't see it because this is audio.
Like subscribe and ring the bell and light the fuse.
I I like what about it.
I don't care what they tell you to ring the bell.
You know, what did we end up there that now we have?
So, OK, for me to watch more of your videos, there are two steps.
That's not a problem of the YouTuber.
This is a problem of YouTube.
How did you possibly get it to that point?
That's notifications, right?
Is that what the balance like?
If you want an email, I think that a video has been done.
I've read some stuff on like digital detox or like simplifying your like smartphone experience.
The first step is always turn off all notifications,
except phone calls and text message, like anything immediate.
And that is, I think, the only notifications I have on on my phone.
So the idea of YouTube just telling me like, hey, there's a new video.
Hey, there's a new there's a new roller coaster video.
Like, no, YouTube, absolutely not.
As opposed to any time I've been hovering over Mike's phone
or used your phone to take a photo or whatever it is.
Your notification intake is unreal.
Yes. You hold it.
If I'm looking at your phone for 10 seconds, it is like,
Ding, ding, toy theme park news test.
Just endless. I don't know.
Monday, Monday, not texting me.
Not to know. I mean, it's an alert that he posted something.
Oh, that's fair. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A flight, a flight booker thing that's still up there.
It is like I'm getting as much information as like an air traffic controller
is getting at all times.
And that's very odd, because you once showed me a productivity thing,
like reminder hack that you do, where if you needed to remind yourself
about something, you would write it in a note, screen grab the note,
make that your lock screen background.
Oh, I know what I've actually mostly done that for is is
when I'm trying to watch Wrestle Kingdom.
Which is in Japan and it's aired at like four a.m.
And I want to remember not to check Twitter right when I wake up
in the morning and see the spoilers.
But how do you see that background if you have so many applications?
Well, you know, if you put it on sleep,
they won't show up in the morning when you click on your phone.
OK, so I see.
I haven't actually done that trick in a while.
Now the screen is the dog's face, a blown up photo of that face.
That sounds that's the way to start the day.
I mean, just just because you're just because you're talking, let's talk.
Let's see what the notification. Yeah.
What do you go? Yeah.
OK, I have Wario.
I do. I have Wario 64's tweets sent to my phone,
which are like video game deals and toy deals.
I have secret flying notifications, which I haven't done that in a long time.
I mean, we've flown, but not like, yeah, where are you going?
Yeah, I could try. You know what? You're right.
I should turn that. There we go.
Or make progress. I have Uber Eats notifications.
I have I don't know why.
I had downloaded a while ago.
Miss called Nick Monday 34 minutes ago.
I have Wendy's Biggie Bag bonus fry deal.
This is an hour ago. This was sent to me to learn it.
Do these things. You've earned a free small.
I would drop everything. These biggie bag purchase.
Get the offer in the app and even more fries.
Burger King may the fourth be with you for two hours ago.
You may a three dollar whopper or impossible whopper be in your hands
on the stellar Whopper Wednesday tap here to order.
It's always Whopper Wednesday.
That's it. You don't need that.
I have Vegas Star Wars mentioned two hours ago.
Vegas slot game that Jason turned me on to a couple of years ago.
That's telling me about collecting one million five hundred thousand chips.
It's a winning Wednesday.
We have a feeling you'll get a lot of Wednesday.
It's winning Wednesday. Monday Wednesday.
Taco Bell. I have some Zillow notifications for houses I can't afford.
That's just cruel. That's just cruel.
Oh, are you what is this all?
Are you proud as you list these neutral?
I think even five. Yeah, I think Mike, Jason and I are ranking.
Our level of alarm is at ten point one hundred. Yeah.
Walmart, for some reason, I had a classic Rafael in my cart
and it wants me to finish the purchase, but little does it know.
I already purchased it months ago.
So I am proud because these notifications have gotten me plenty.
They've they've they're worth it, is what I'm saying,
because you get notified for all sorts of interesting deals and things.
Yeah. You know what?
I can't be too hard on you because sometimes you forward me those deal.
You text me those deals all the time.
I have benefited.
That's what we say about the checking. That's right.
Mike driving himself slowly insane into full body deterioration.
Sometimes it's to our benefit.
You would think I would be more of like kind of a manic character
with all that coming in like, oh, like this guy, you know, like a cartoon.
This guy, you just we hurt a lot of stuff.
You just internalize it like a geyser.
Geyser Mountain. Yeah.
It all comes it all manifests itself in your inability to hug many.
That's right. Well, I think I'm just operating on a level
of absorbing the energy around me.
And you think you've reached enlightenment.
They exactly you've reached it.
I've gotten so many notifications.
So calm all the time.
I'm connected to so many people via tweets and app notifications.
You realize we're all one.
I'm vibrating at a different frequency than everyone else.
I can see the world sort of on a fourth plane like Neo at the end of the first.
I wasn't going to say it, but yes, you're right.
It is a lot like Neo.
I sort of unplugged in to the matrix.
The rest of us are just in Zion in the muddy party.
I already have only see our little bubble.
We can only see our little bubble attached to the greater consciousness.
Occasionally, we just jack into Twitter just so we could just get riled up at whatever
lunatics going on.
OK, all right. I'm getting out.
You know, I'm Musk's Neuralink.
I already have it, man.
I'm already I'm already getting it all.
I don't know what even you're talking about.
OK, well, after all that, now here's the part where we have to give you
instructions of what we first of all, you survived podcast, the right.
I'm going to do this little spiel and just let me know if you don't fake it,
if there's not one there.
But if a notification shows up
but that you didn't already read before the spiel is over.
So you survived podcast, the right, the hot dog hullabaloo.
Send us on our next mission through whatever media you want.
That could be our socials.
We're on everything at podcast, the right.
Merch is available in our tea public store.
And we'll throw that hot dog thing up there.
Thanks, Aaron, for the logo and the name.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast, the right,
the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the right and hit the bell
or send yourself a complicated series of notifications.
Set alarms.
I admit and wake up at eleven fifty nine when our new episodes are out.
Yeah. Wednesdays on the patron of Friday on the main thing.
Did you get anything while I was talking? 100 percent. OK.
Jimmy Iovine, that long, I stretched it a little.
Me, I have been son, Jamie, I have been has an app called Network.
We've talked about it before.
Oh, yeah. Some of the letters are missing from the word network.
This is a kind of a home shopping for millennials.
People we know of like so.
So like there'll be little likes the videos and stuff that are hosting,
basically telling you, you know, you can buy some things.
What just dropped is there's a live broadcast now,
something called Panera Day of Cravable Drops.
Me to Medi. I don't actually know how to pronounce it.
But a MediCom toy is a type of is a toy company.
And they do these things called Bear Bricks, which are like almost like
Vinyl Mation's, but they're like a big bear.
Sometimes they're smaller bears, sometimes whatever.
And then they paint like characters on them.
They're just like Vinyl Mation's basically. But they're very popular.
I have no bear bricks. I do not own bear bricks.
But this just let me know that I can purchase bear bricks like this bear
brick. 100 percent.
There's this Pinocchio basically is a Pinocchio bear brick here for one hundred
dollars that I can purchase and I can go through and see.
Wait, what does that have to do with Panera?
I don't know. But the two hosts, but the two hosts are standing
in front of a display and it's just frozen now.
They're standing in front of a display that's a giant sandwich
and in the front of the thing, it says Panera.
I don't have a lot of answers for you.
This, again, just popped up while you were doing those after show plugs.
So I am just this is what is happening.
This is what has just come in here now.
There's a Simpson Cyclops bear brick.
I don't know if that's just from, oh, Treehouse of Horror.
It's when there was a I forget which one that is.
Yeah, but you can buy that for one hundred twenty dollars.
I can buy one of these guys for you if you want.
Jason and I both turned and did Jim Halpert takes to each other.
Before you got to the word bear brick.
Yeah, you mentioned like three startup names, Panera, Bearbrick.
Here here's the here's the main screen.
This is Panera Panera Day of Cravable Drops.
Oh, man, they got these.
What's the drop?
So that's when they're dropping bear brick, like so dropping the bear brick sale.
Not food. Not food is not they aren't selling.
So they aren't selling like egg drops.
Nasty looking chicken sandwiches.
Now, Panera, get in touch. I'll fix your restaurant.
Oh, do you know about free? Do you know about free sips?
You've already. Yeah, you got to do free sips.
That always tastes terrible.
I hope you can get a you can get an iced tea for free.
You're excitedly pointing at Jason about sips.
You already told him about that. Don't taste good to him.
I know. I have no I have no palate until July 4th.
You can get a free drink of any kind at any Panera once a day until July 4th for free.
I will drink any unsweetened iced.
There you go. That a shot.
Yeah, I guess so. All right.
Sign up for free sips.
You never know if it weren't for me.
We just did. We did.
Thanks to my friend, Luke, actually told me that we just did live Jim Halpert GIFs.
And Mike, you were just a full time Michael Scott.
It's happening.
You were that about everything you just listed.
Oh, my God, it's happening.
Yeah, that's true.
This is I mean, we've all we're all there's just our brains are mostly nitrates
at this point, nitrates and sodium.
So we're all like losing it a little.
Let me ask you this question, Jason.
Did you get that Duncan on Free Coffee Wednesday?
Free Coffee Wednesday?
Wow, of course.
And he knew about that before me.
I did not turn him on to Free Coffee Wednesday, but I'm just letting everyone know.
Go in the app. Free Coffee Wednesday.
Dunkin Donuts. Yeah.
That might only be in this area.
Yeah, might only be.
Well, check your app before you go over there and demand it.
Oh, my God. It's happening.
By that, I mean me atrophying and collapsing over by.
Forever Dog.
This has been a forever dog
production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardiner, Brett Bohm, Joe S basileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcast, please visit forever dog podcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcast's Spotify
or wherever you get your podcast.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.