Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains hard pieces of spider web fluid, devil dinosaur,
train car disappointment, and three podcasters made entirely out of mutant bees.
It's Web Slingers, a Spider-Man adventure on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who were bitten
by a radioactive theme park nerd and have been dealing with it ever since.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, and the worst thing is I didn't even stop that, you know, other...
You wanted to be bitten is what you were saying?
No, no, I'm saying like after I tried to go to like a theme park convention, the robber
was running out and I could have stopped him.
I could have stopped him and told him about like...
What was he stealing?
Magic journeys.
I don't know, like maybe the recently returned Bugsy, not Bugsy, who's the...
Oh, from Epcot.
Yeah.
It's not Bugsy.
Not Busby.
It's not Busby Berkeley.
Not Busby Berkeley, no.
No, I wish.
You would have stopped if some sort of Busby Berkeley relic were being stolen from a museum.
They're stealing Busby Berkeley's body.
Yeah, that's Scott Garen talking about Busby Berkeley in the first seconds of this podcast.
Oh yeah, we're off to the...
You know, you think you're looking at an episode title that seems like something current and
relevant and relatable.
How quickly can we get to the guy who did all of the swim dance numbers.
Yes, big musical numbers.
Jimmy Cagney's tuxedo from the end of Footlight Parade.
A hundred years ago, a person named Busby Berkeley made movies with a lot of dancers.
A lot.
Practical effects, baby.
In-camera edits.
And Jason's never been the same.
I've never been the same.
Yeah, what gave me permission to be weird?
I guess I'd have to say the Busby Berkeley movies.
Well, one young Hollywood star inadvertently nodded to the song and dance routines of the
past that we'll touch upon today.
I have no idea what that refers.
Oh, it's a Tom Holland thing.
I'll get to it.
Okay, okay.
Is that when Tom did... did he do Umbrella on...
Yes, he did Umbrella, but it started as singing in the rain.
And he's also on board for a...
I believe he's playing Fred Astaire at a biopic.
Oh, right.
Oh, this is... you must be so excited.
I'm much more...
I mean...
Another 100... a person who's a dead 100 years.
I am much more excited.
I'm much more skeptical of the Chris Evans, Gene Kelly biopic.
Is that a joke?
No, that's real.
That is real?
That's real.
It should be Channing Tatum because he can really dance.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
But you don't think Chris can learn?
I don't know.
We'll see.
Michael Douglas couldn't play the piano and the Liberace movie was pretty good.
That's true.
Yeah.
I mean, Pretty Good is one of my favorite movies.
I know, yeah.
Yes, that's an understatement.
It was marvelous.
That's what it was.
Yeah, anyway, our origin story, I was trying to say, was we got bitten by a man who loved
theme parks.
Yes.
Well, and I think that what this podcast is for the listeners is if they were not bit
themselves, then we provide a special vehicle that allows them to imagine what it would
be like to have been bitten by a radio.
Very true.
Yeah, I guess you're in the Nerder vehicle.
That's good.
No second E.
Dot, dot.
We provide you the Nerder vehicle to simulate what it's like to be stuck how we're stuck
all the time.
Exactly.
So yeah, it's a good, it's a safe way for you to live out what we do with every day.
Which you know, speaking of delving deeper into this world and us and everything that
we do, we have a little announcement here at the top of the show.
So many people who are listening to this may already be subscribed to our Patreon podcast,
the Ride the Second Gate, which we thank you so much for doing that.
The Patreon subscribers quite directly keep the show running and allow us to focus on
it and make it as good as it can be.
And besides that, we have a lot of fun over there.
I think we get crazy and indulgent and obscure and off topic and get to talk about it.
The late shift and about Sebastian Jackal and you know, because we're, we contain multitudes.
They're all pointless multitudes, but we do contain them.
Dead ends.
Yeah.
So what I'm getting at is we have so much fun over there, deep diving into our crazy
interests and into this, especially into this crazy theme park world.
We've decided that it's time to go even further, push things even deeper.
It is time, ladies and gentlemen, to open the third tier of podcast, the ride, a third
gate, if you will, beyond the second gate.
But if you thought I just revealed the name, that's not exactly right.
It's not podcast, the ride, the third gate, because we think of it as a little a little
more than that.
What we want this to be is a VIP lounge, an exclusive VIP lounge for the ultimate podcast,
the ride fans.
And that is why we are cutting the ribbon on podcast, the ride club three.
Welcome to club three.
We right now are issuing you an auditory invitation.
This is it. It's a super swanky private club within the second gate.
You guys excited? I'm excited.
Sounds good. It sounds curious.
Yeah. Listeners, you can enjoy you can feel what it was like if it was the mid 80s and
you were an executive vice president at a microchip manufacturer and oil company, Boeing,
an oil company who's about to just like really fuck up Alaska.
You know, yeah, that you get like up above the ride.
There are like three couches and then free orange juice.
Yeah, there's a mini fridge full of tabs, tabs and frescoes.
That's right. This is a mini fridge full of frescoes for your mind and for your ears.
And if that doesn't sell you on it, I don't know what will.
So what happens in podcast, the ride club three?
Well, keep in mind, it is still the second gate.
So you get the perks of podcast, the ride, the second gate.
You get your three bonus episodes every month.
But you also get the main feed episodes like this one you're currently hearing right now.
Ad free. You can listen to them without ads.
I mean, we can still ask us if you want to hear our our better help.
Oh, yeah. We'll still send them to if you're craving the ads,
we can still make sure that those get to you and you can kind of like piece them off
like little little quick bites as it were.
And of course, yeah.
The nice thing about advertising is it alerts you to goods and services
you might not otherwise know about.
Yeah, we don't want to take away that privilege from you.
But if for some reason, if you just if you want to hear an unbroken conversation
instead of one where we one of us suddenly butts in with different audio quality
or a voice you've never heard before and will never hear again, but then if you want to,
if you just want unbroken pockets, right episodes, that's happening over there.
Plus only on Club Three will you get one more bonus episode each month with topics
chosen by you, the audience.
And I think we want to see how far we can go, how deep we can go, how obscure we can go.
We are going to ask you for your dream podcast, The Right Episodes, how crazy
into things that we have talked about into like if you want to hear like we're going to talk about
the 1997 Disney Vacation Club planning guy, you want to watch that and we're going to talk
about whatever is the deepest thing you want to delve into.
That's what we're going to do over there.
Yeah, maybe even just like a chapter of that guide.
If you have a specific, yeah, reason.
Oh yeah, alert us to specificity.
Yeah, we are more than willing to break things up.
As you know, yeah, as you're aware.
I can ask my mom to dig out the VHS one we surely have somewhere in a box and we can compare it to
whatever one someone ripped to YouTube.
Oh yeah.
See if there are different things.
Quality, yes.
Where does it fuzz out?
How bright are the colors?
I don't want to now give your mom extra work, but if she's going to start digging through the box
then she's got to find those school plays too.
We got to get some Jason's school, but that seems like a great thing to do over in Club 3.
Well, I've got a little bit.
I've got a little.
Oh, you don't say.
I will have to cut it up.
I started watching some of what I ripped and remembered that we actually did have microphones
and lavaliers and stuff, but the one thing to try and get people's voices to carry that
weren't particularly good at projecting because there were children, they had floor mics and
everyone is wearing adult shoes that are probably two sizes too big on plywood stage extenders.
So a lot of what I'm hearing is thunk, thunk, thunk.
People might want to hear what a 12 year old Jason stomping around in big shoes.
If you can believe it, like 10 to 12 year old Jason pretty good at raising his voice.
So I actually probably over.
I do talk over the thongs.
You can hear me over the do you have any line in your head that you might have said,
especially as even if it's just a like, Hey, or like officer, I remember very
specifically saying in a sinister German accent, very she.
Oh, wow.
Like there is the girl.
At first I was like very chic and then I realized, oh, that's a V in where.
Yes.
That was the only direction they gave me for the German accent swap,
stop the W's for V's.
And then they're like, there's a movie called IQ about Albert Einstein, his nephew fall in love.
So me and my dad and my family went to like blockbuster and found like, okay,
here's the VHS IQ and I'll watch this.
And most of the movie went right over my head, but I was just like watching the scenes with
worked well enough.
Wasn't there a movie where like Fred Astaire had a German accent you could have gotten into?
I don't know.
There's probably some.
You might not have been willing to do that for a different time.
That's true.
Yeah.
And who knows what the movie selection was like at movies.
Is that the name?
That was a chain that had a little cow and 3d glasses and the logo.
Sounds to me like a club three, the movies.
We're going to talk about your.
Oh man.
The movies cow.
The movie cow.
There's so much.
It's really up to you, except for the first one, which we, which is up right now.
If you want to hear an extra bonus episode beyond the second gate, we have picked the
first one, which I think is a good starting point because if we're going to watch, you know,
crazy old stuff that we are very nostalgic for, I think a good starting point is the
classic VHS that so many of us had Disney sing along songs, Disneyland fun.
Of course.
There were all those sing along song compilations that were clips from the movies, but I think
we all the most loved the one where you actually got to go into the park and, uh, you know,
run around with Roger Rabbit and that zippity doo da rap and all that stuff.
Yeah.
It was really fun.
I was watching it this morning and making notes, praying I had picked the right one.
And then finally towards the end, I was like, ah, there, there she is.
There's an old friend.
There is she.
There is the shiny queen.
So, uh, if you go, if you go to podcast, the ride, the second gate club three right now,
you get this episode you're listening to ad free, you get Disney sing along songs, Disneyland fun.
It's just the beginning of the monthly extra bonus episode that you'll get.
And we'll try to figure out some other fun stuff to do over there because we
appreciate you supporting the show so much.
Uh, so club three, it's the third level of the podcast and it's just an extra
three dollars a month on top of the five that you might already be paying for the second gate.
Yes.
Before that you get more us, more fun and less ads.
Sounds good to me.
Good question.
Yeah.
We're excited about this.
Please come join us and, uh, thanks Aaron for the name club three.
You're on fire with the names lately and the logo.
Go check all that out.
And the logo.
Uh, yeah, of course the $5 tier still three episodes a month.
An added benefit of club three.
What that means is that you are going to get an RSS feed where all versions of the show
show up in one place.
Oh boy.
Three logos, all fighting to the death.
All fighting.
Which will win.
Oh yeah.
How's that going to even think about that?
Yeah.
Crazy.
We want to cloud those artists.
We don't want anybody else sneaking in.
We don't want any, any choppos and Marans and Carvies and spades.
No.
Keep them out.
Us only.
That's right.
Wow.
So there you go.
Patreon.com slash podcast, the ride where the usual stuff happens and this.
And with that said, uh, let's get to today's topic.
Web slingers, a spider-man, a spider-man web singers, all caps, a spider-man adventure.
And then forget the dash in spider-man.
Of course, the dash, uh, always there for spider-man part of the weird
like fifties and sixties comic guys just making up stuff as they love.
So Batman has no hyphen.
Spider-man does have an hyphen.
Superman, no hyphen.
No hyphen.
X-men has a hyphen.
Right.
Is it a Marvel thing?
Was there, is the dash Marvel?
Is that a Stan Lee affectation?
Maybe.
Yeah.
That's a good question.
Um, did the star wars droids have hyphens or are they just.
Yeah, there's hyphen in right?
R2D2?
R2D2 does.
R2-8.
BB-8.
Yeah.
R2-8.
Okay.
Yeah.
You got your dashes in there.
C3PO.
We got, yeah, C dash 3PO.
3PO.
Okay.
Yeah.
IG-88 has a dash.
Which one?
IG-88.
The bounty hunter.
The bounty hunter, Scott.
IG-88.
He's got kind of a long pencil.
He's like gray.
He's got like a long, what would you describe his head?
He's a robot who's very tall.
He looks like a giant pencil kind of, but he's gray.
Yeah.
Very tall.
He shows up in like one shot of.
All the Empire Strikes Back.
In Empire Strikes Back.
One shot?
One shot.
And then an IG-type droid shows up in the first Mandalorian.
Yeah.
Tyka.
And quickly blows up.
YTT is his, well not quickly.
He's in there for a few.
Okay.
But then he does blow up strangely in the,
spoiler alert, in the finale.
There's a scene where Vader has brought all the bounty hunters together in Empire Strikes Back
to go get Han Solo.
That's where Boba Fett is in.
Basque is in there.
Basque is another bounty hunter.
He's not a droid.
He is a, I forget.
He's kind of reptilian, isn't he?
Yeah.
Something like that.
I'm, people are going to be mad.
I don't know what, what alien species he is.
Boss is in there.
Kelsey Grammer's.
Boss?
Yeah.
Kelsey Grammer.
Cable character.
Stars character boss.
Yeah.
He's one of the bounty hunters.
Um, so yeah, anyway.
Uh.
As we all know, like that hyphen is a bonus.
Like, uh, more punctuation in a ride title has usually been a successful thing for Disney
in recent years.
It's been a big thing.
I guess so.
We make fun of all the dashes and doodads,
but they're, they're often on pretty great attractions and successful attractions.
You're right.
Yeah.
But it is a weird new modern thing to just as much as much many words and as many other
little things.
I don't know.
It's so many qualifiers.
Yeah.
But yes, you're never getting Space Mountain.
The branding is just has to be so the brand, like it just has to go through probably like
focus groups or something.
I don't know.
Um, which to this, to that end, I don't know.
This isn't so bad.
You get your all caps web sling.
And that's an interesting, I don't know why it has to be screamed at you, but, um, you
know, I guess it's, I guess it's fine.
You know, you're, we're getting off a little easier than other attractions.
Yeah.
It's fine.
Look, it's fine.
It's just, it's funny.
That's all it is.
It's a little silly.
We just want a little, we just, we yearn for the days of a simple name like, uh, uh,
mountain, big thunder mountain or space.
Don't forget railroad though.
Disneyland railroad.
Oh yeah.
No, no, big thunder mountain railroad.
All right.
That's fine.
That's complicated.
Yeah.
Escape from the haunted mine, but zoom it would be today.
There's a, that's yeah.
With like, got some more punctuation at the end.
Exclamation point, like question mark, question mark, exclamation point.
Yeah.
Haunted mine.
I forgot already.
Jason, I happened to be in the park briefly yesterday and I was like, oh yeah, there's
ghosts on this ride.
I forgot that.
Big thunder.
Yeah.
It's a ghost.
Ghosts.
The ghosts are the reason that the train is out of control.
I was like, did we talk about that?
Yeah.
I think we did.
The spirits of the mountain are angry at all the mining.
There's a narration.
Uh, literally, uh, uh, there's on the train, the narration.
Yeah.
When you're on the train, it says big thunder and like talks about the spirits who have
made the train go out of control.
The guy, like at the beginning, the, the wildest ride in the wilderness.
We may have spent 45 minutes talking about this three years ago.
I don't remember any of them.
I don't think so.
I've never known about spirits.
He's Jason said we did talk about this.
I mean, if, hey, find me a sound bite, I could have.
Well, I think Dennis McNicholas brought it up as well because he wrote that script.
Sure.
And I think he was leaving supernatural stuff.
Okay.
Well, so anyway, so you don't see them.
They're just around.
Yeah, I know.
I guess they're like, they aren't coming out of the geysers.
It's a, again, I'm your guess is good as mine.
I was like, is there ghosts on this ride?
And Jason goes, oh yeah.
I go, oh, okay.
Anyway, I just might, maybe it's gone.
Maybe the piece of information out of my brain is gone.
I think it's the sort of thing like some of the older rides where it's like, well,
you can just enjoy this on the surface level.
But if you really dig down, we had a store, you know, we have a.
But that story of element is only available if you're on the train, which I find, I guess I like.
Cause like, if you're just on big thunder, you're just like, well, here we go.
Nah, blah, blah, blah.
And then that's it.
But if you're on the train.
Wait a minute.
Sorry, I got confused there.
You're saying that when you're taking the Disneyland railroad, they tell you about spirits.
Yes.
Yeah.
They wait.
Okay.
I missed that.
All right.
Yeah, sorry, sorry.
Not the big thunder.
Okay.
So I see that narrator.
Yes.
Weird.
No, I don't think I know about this.
I couldn't, I couldn't remember.
And again, maybe we're going to look really foolish when somebody goes back.
Well, of course you talked about it.
We're going to get John Stewart.
We're going to have a posing clip that we.
Yeah.
We're going to just such hypocrites we will be.
I'll boot up the old Marvel Unlimited and read the comic series and see what they pull.
Sure.
We know they.
Sure, they're in there.
I'm just saying.
I completely forgot.
Bartamus Bullion is in the comics.
Yeah, I know.
We talked a little bit about that on the episode for sure.
Anyway, so we're talking about who?
It's Spider-Man?
Yeah, we're talking about web slayers.
Other park, the different park across the way.
Yeah, which has been open for about a year now.
About a year?
It's kind of hard to believe.
So maybe now we can evaluate it with a little bit of, you know, greater context.
We've done it a couple times now.
I think all of us.
Yes.
And yeah, Mike and I were there a few days after it opened and Scott, you wrote.
Did you write it for the first time when we went with Griffin Newman?
I think so.
I'm trying to remember.
What's in my head is that I've done it three times, but I'm not exactly sure.
With that, let me say this.
And I don't want to put an air over this.
I don't want to chill the episode, but I might as well just be forthcoming and get the conversation
moving by saying this.
I do not like this.
I have landed there.
I'm not trying to, not trying to be negative, not trying to be an edge lord.
I have been, there were things about it that didn't sound that good to me when it was in
development.
I think we all talked about them, but I was hoping against hope that those things would
not end up bothering me in the final product.
And I think after a number of times and the three of us just did it together recently
on the hot dog canoe day, I think that's where I have to lock it in.
Okay.
You're locking it in now.
I don't want to lock mine in now.
Oh, you don't have to.
And maybe the conversation will lead us all to different opinions, but I feel like I should
just be clear and forthcoming about that.
But do you, am I, am I crazy?
Am I wrong?
Well, I think there's a lot to consider for this ride.
I mean, one, it has an uphill battle in that there is already a 20 plus year old Spider-Man
ride that you could argue is the best ride.
Maybe the best current running ride.
And I think the Tower of Terror in Orlando is giving it a run for its money.
They're tied kind of neck in neck in terms of like stuff I have loved at various ages
and still have stuck with me.
And I'm still delighted.
Tower of Terror and Spider-Man are the two best rides in the country.
Yes, in the country.
I have not been out of the United States much.
I have not seen the parks around the world, so I don't want to gauge on those.
I might have to toss all the Hagrid's in there.
I was pretty fond of Hagrid's.
Maybe time won't keep it a classic, but as far as like coming out of the gate, how much
I loved it on the day, I put that in a top of, because I was declaring it best ride in
Orlando, but I don't know.
That's just, might just be me.
Guardians is on my list.
It's better than the Orlando Tower of Terror.
So that's what I, yeah, I believe it is.
Do we talk about this?
I think so, yeah.
Okay.
And the reason it edges out is because the actual thrill part of it is more interesting
to me.
That's how it wins.
Yeah.
Wow.
I don't think that's insane.
Because it's an empty, because again, now I'm spoiled.
I'm spoiled by things to look at and enjoy while the actual drop stuff is going on.
Sure, sure.
But you're, yeah, something about this name, when that it is called a Spider-Man adventure,
it does almost feel like it is not the Spider-Man adventure.
Yes, that's in Florida and Japan.
And it is, yeah, boy, that is it.
That is awesome.
Right.
I was almost wondering if like, had we mythologized it too much to just hit us all the right way
in 99, 2000 or whatever, whenever we first did it.
And then when I was down there for that bachelor party, everybody was just like,
just blew their heads off.
It's so good.
It's really fun.
I have to say that the 90's Spider-Man cartoon, so by extension, the Spider-Man ride in Florida,
because it's pretty similar, like it's it's they've made some changes for the ride,
but that is my favorite portrayal of Spider-Man outside of the comics.
Like I think the more than any movies.
He's a little too handsome.
Yeah, he's a little too handsome, but he's he's kind of like regular kind of regular every man.
I think of the movies, I do think I like Tom Holland, the best of the actors who have played
Spider-Man.
I like Tobey Maguire as an actor.
I think he's a little too emo as as Peter Parker.
And I am excited to see Tom Holland.
The current status quo for the Tom Holland Spider-Man is a little more of down and out
as opposed to like awkward teen and down and out is kind of like when Peter Parker shines,
like he kind of the whole thing of the Spider-Man no way home.
Is that what it was called?
The newest one.
Yeah, OK.
They all have homes.
That's our day.
They're all homes.
Homes that is it kind of sold me like by the end of the movie, I'm like,
oh, yeah, suffering is it's kind of intrinsic to Spider-Man in the way that like,
yeah, Bruce Wayne is going to have dead parents, you know, like.
They have reversed engineered the origin of the original origin of Spider-Man in the movies now.
So this is spoiler alert.
If you haven't seen these home movies,
he starts out as like little Tony Stark, like mentee.
And then we get to the point at the end of the last movie where no one remembers he's
that Peter Parker is Spider-Man, including MJ, including his best friends.
And now he's like alone with no money and no one knows who he is.
Which I don't like when they did it in the comics because it was stupid.
And Scott, just so you know, when they did that storyline, this storyline in the comics,
it wasn't Dr. Strange doing magic to make everyone forgetting.
It was literally the devil.
Spider-Man made a deal with Mephisto, the devil.
Geez, so Sebastian Shackle.
So essentially made a deal with Sebastian Shackle.
Now, Scott, it's not Mr. Mastopheles, the character from Cats, right?
Yeah, that's from Cats.
It's not Mr. McPhisto.
Bono's character from the what, Pop Mart tour?
Yeah.
Or can we out that one of those live shows recently that you really wanted to come out
and say you were Mr. Mike Phisto?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jason and I were like, might be going a tad obscure there.
Vetoed.
Yeah.
Just let me say the words I want to say, guys.
You didn't say it, but you were right.
Like I inferred what you meant is that we should do the full YouTube Pop Mart tour episode
before I come out and do that bit.
Oh, boy.
That's what you said.
Part three is going to be a very fraught place for me, especially.
I have thought about Mr. Mike Phisto before.
Yeah.
There's also a kind of a dirty, sexual thing.
And then that word Mike Phisto, like I don't want a weird.
I get you're the one finding it.
You found it in eating.
And Ash is not crazy.
That's not crazy.
Eating ash.
No, but I didn't hear it right away.
But well, you're more like Phisto again.
We're just getting deep into your.
This is like, yeah, this is a name you imagine yourself having.
No.
OK, there's no I'm not thinking about fisting.
OK, that's I don't want to be too bawdy on the main feed here.
This is what they say that you get on Club Three.
That's to they say that a hero can save us and Mike Phisto is not going to stay here and wait.
Although I guess it's just like Kit Phisto, the Star Wars character.
That's true.
And that's I guess who I don't know anything about, but I assume is really good at.
Well, that's a George.
That's in George Envision.
That was the characters kind of the ultimate fister.
The opening day, we went to Galaxy's Edge.
Mike was really considering that he was very delighted by the Kit Phisto statuette.
Yeah, well, he loves all the fistos out there.
He's finally with his brethren.
Are you talking?
I think you're talking about Plo Koon.
Was it Plo Koon?
I think you're thinking of the Plo Koon statue.
I don't know.
We were going through a kid.
Fisto phase at the time.
So there might have been a kid.
Fisto toy or something.
This don't Plo Koon are Jedis.
Yeah.
So anyway, not pod racers, not pod racers.
It's not Klo Poon, which that would be sexual.
That would be sexual.
Yeah.
His name was Klo Poon.
Maybe that.
I mean, look, there's going to be a lot of streaming shows.
So maybe Plo Koon has a brother.
Well, you know, why not?
Disney wants to get as much Star Wars out there as they can.
Why not be the first corporation to embrace their own, not a triple X porn parody?
Why not start?
They allow these odd little podunk companies to make the porn parodies.
Disney should.
Yeah.
Disney plus XXX.
Imagine the announcement, like the upfronts kind of thing, where Chay Peck comes out and then
he kind of like then Tinkerbell shows up and she like stands on top of the plus and then it tips
to become an X.
And then she makes two more X's of here with the pixie dust.
That's right.
Transitions from like, and that's why we're excited about the subscriber growth of hot star
services in Asia.
And now moving on to other streaming territories.
If I could get the red lights, please.
Oh, Tink, what are you doing here?
I think they've got a Disney probably secretly owns a bunch of adult companies.
Oh, yeah.
It's just time for them to come up.
Because if the goal is 12 new Star Wars series every year, they're eventually going to run out
and have to start doing porn.
Yeah.
Porno.
They bought the rights for the James Gunn web series that is a parody of the Bang Bust,
but they just pick people up and give people rides with Craig Robinson.
We all remember this James Gunn project, right?
James Gunn directed.
I'm sure it's not a thing he would like people to forget.
I don't remember.
Well, Google it, I guess.
From the minds that brought you guardians of the galaxy.
The twisted, beautiful twisted mind, I think is what they said in the Suicide Squad trailer.
You're two descriptors of the mind.
That's what it was, if I recall correctly.
Not twisted.
Come on, give me a say something nice, too.
Yeah.
No, it is a compliment.
Yeah, but like, you know.
Twisted is cool.
Say something nice about how my mind looks.
Yeah.
I've lost my mind.
I was saying I like Tom Holland.
I hadn't seen that lip sync battle performance where he like really does some crazy dancing
and stuff, and then I found out the context of that was like years old.
He'd only been Spider-Man in one movie or so.
I think it was to promote the first like movie with Zendaya and she is on it and he's like
dancing towards her and they hadn't started dating yet.
That's the moment.
He's very like flirty and everything.
But then he fully commits to a very complicated dance routine and just does an insane flip.
He can do a lot of those flips himself.
He does flip.
I think he flips more than Garfield and McGuire, for sure.
Yeah, so my respect went way up for him in that respect.
I like Colin DeLau, too.
I think it's a good take on the character.
I think in the 2000s, I really think Gyllenhaal would have been interesting if they had gone
with that recasting.
I think Topher Grace, too, probably would have been a good Peter Parker.
I agree and instead he was Venom.
He was Eddie Brock.
Topher Grace was Venom before.
Oh, that's who that is.
Yeah, before Eminem did the Venom song.
He could come back.
Everyone can come back.
Yeah, so Spider-Man, I'm a big fan of that first.
Yeah, the original ride is unbelievable and I don't know how you...
Well, I guess I do.
There was the rumors for a while a couple years ago.
I think we all remember when we would look at patents for ride systems that never made it.
It's still happening.
They just announced the one with the vehicle damage, which is a pretty cool idea.
And there was something a couple years ago.
It was like a swinging sort of mechanism that would be like hanging from a coaster kind of
a thing that would be going through like big practical cities.
I guess that could be the ultimate Spider-Man attraction.
The one in Orlando is pretty perfect.
Well, let me say this.
This might be issue number one for me.
If you want to live out fantasies of the character, which is not necessarily what this attraction
is going for, but it is giving you...
It's creating a construct where you get to shoot webs.
And I'm like, is that...
Now, granted, I'm not really a Spider-Man kid or anything, but I think it's never occurred to me
to want to shoot webs.
Now, shooting webs up to a tree over there so I can swing really far.
Now, that's something.
And that's kind of what you get to do in the Islands of Adventure ride.
To me, the important part is the swinging around, not the shooting objects, which just sounds...
Well...
Look, if I look down at my own wrist and a weird,
gucky substance came out of it, I'd be really freaked out.
I don't think I want that at all.
So, yeah.
So, okay.
So, a couple things.
First of all, in Canon, and they just address this in the new movie,
Garfield makes his own...
A mechanical web shooter.
Does Garfield?
Garfield has it.
And the other two don't.
Tom Holland has mechanical.
They do.
This is Andrew Garfield.
The character Garfield is not...
So, the cat doesn't come out in the multiverse.
The dog sleeping at my feet does not shoot webs.
Not the dog who's here right now.
Andrew Garfield.
Andrew Garfield and Tom Holland do the...
Spider-Man has made web shooters because he's also a brilliant scientist.
That is Canon in the comics.
Tobey Maguire has organic web shooters.
He has a little hole in his wrist that they explain in the movie.
Oh, I do not want this.
Yes.
And there is a gag where they're like, wait, you just do that?
They're in the new movie.
The three of them are standing around.
Spoiler alert, they're all in the new movie.
There was two days before they started doing TV spots where they're all standing around.
A shocker.
Who could have a med?
It certainly didn't seem for eight months ahead of time.
Like, that's where it was going.
They were not constantly spotted by shooting locations.
One of them did not immediately leak it while doing press for another project.
Yeah.
I guess I'm agreeing with you that the swinging has always been the thing,
regardless of which Spider-Man it was.
That's the big thing.
That's when the first video game came out that was pretty good.
And I forget which system it was even for.
The whole big thing was, oh, wow, the swinging is the thing.
That's the transformational experience you would want to have in an attraction
or a video game or in your deepest dreams, your biggest fantasies.
Swinging and your deepest desires.
Swinging and tying guys up.
Well, I don't know.
Tying guys up, I don't.
Webbing bad guys.
I see what you're saying.
Sure, sure.
So like when we were younger.
That's what I was searching for, in your web dreams.
In your web dreams.
What is your deepest fantasy in your web dreams?
Shooting your bullies at school with your organic web shooters that come out of your
webs that come out of your wrist.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
That was number two, I think.
That was number two.
And then I guess number three would be like shooting a little web at your bully's mouth
to cover his mouth so he can't talk anymore.
So you're like, shut up, pal, or whatever.
But yes, the swinging is the thing.
So yeah, well, I want to go through the whole queue and everything.
But yes, let's just start with this.
Absolutely, that's the thing.
And I don't think you don't have to be a Spider-Man expert to think that.
That's, I'm sure, 99% of everyone who ever thought they could be Spider-Man or wanted
to be Spider-Man was like, the number one thing I want to do is fly through the air.
You've got a character with his own built-in ride mechanism.
Yes.
He has one.
And you do, you get to do it incredibly in the universal.
Right.
The webbing is concussive.
It's like blasts.
And Spider-Man has shot web bolts.
Occasionally, shoots little web bullets basically to knock guys out.
Yeah, so if you're breaking down what's going on, he's shooting a little hard piece of webbing
that can hit something.
And it's hard as a robot and blow it up.
He's not using the web.
I assume the web, when you get hit with a normal web stream, it's kind of soft.
There's a little impact.
But he is doing something.
I don't know exactly how he, you know, because he, of course, makes this motion with his
hands.
He puts the two fingers down on his web shooters or in Toby's case, on his own biology.
Biology.
In his own hand.
Goo holes.
When you shoot your soft stream goo out of your biology.
Toby uses his own biology to shoot.
So, so yeah, so basically there's got to be something different,
that you do to make the web harder, to make it a hardened piece of projectile webbing.
Why do all the shooting right?
We got so gross in Toy Story Mania.
I don't know.
Gross here in web slingers.
They had it in various video games.
They would have different kinds of webbing or different tricks and stuff, different costumes,
the armor.
He had this silvery armor for one or a handful of issues in the comics.
Right.
He specifically uses it to fight slash help.
Wilson Fisk's son, the Rose.
Did you call him Wilson Fisk?
Wilson Fisk.
Okay, good.
Wilson Fisk's son.
Thank God.
The Rose.
And then a character named Nightwatch, Marvel's Nightwatch, who is just Spawn.
They just had a character that was Spawn.
After Todd McFarland left and created Spawn, they created a character.
It's very much like wrestling comic books, where people are just like,
I'm just going to do this.
I'm just going to do Batman.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah.
So there's precedent for him using the webbing like this,
but he's almost exclusively using webbing on this ride in this way,
which is not the primary way the webbing is used.
No.
So yes, you are 100% correct that if you want the experience of Spider-Man,
you want to swing, you want to do some creative stuff with it.
You don't want to just flail your arms wildly, shooting hard pieces of web
at an onslaught of robots that just is coming at you at an insane fast rate.
Boy, oh boy.
Now you can web, if you move your hand forward and pull to the side,
you can web a spider bot and fling it at a bunch of other.
But then the onslaught of spiders, spider bots keep coming
and you start panicking going, ah, and then your hands just go.
You stop thinking of all the fun creative ways maybe you could use.
Any moment of strategy is tough to kind of stick with and keep.
You know what we might owe, and I think a lot of listeners know this,
but just like, since we haven't said spider bot before,
can we just synopsize this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're these cute little guys.
They're cute little guys.
Done, man.
I'm going to the next part of it.
Start webbing, cute little guys.
You're at an open house at Peter Parker's, at the lab.
Okay.
So this is, yeah.
It's a new creation for the theme park universe.
It's not in the movies.
It's not in the comics, which I like this.
I like the idea they've built out of mythology just for the theme park.
The thing at Avengers campus, which is a place for the Avengers to work and live and wave.
And wave.
Yeah.
And have beers.
Have beers that get poured.
Shoot up from the bottom.
Yeah, from the bottom.
Opposite pour.
Yeah.
So yes, it's an institute.
It's where the young minds of the Marvel universe, Marvel theme park universe come together.
Yes.
It's WEB, the Worldwide Engineering Brigade.
A complicated acronym, which is ironic because this attraction was delayed due to the worldwide
COVID pandemic.
What is that?
The worldwide COVID pandemic is not the Worldwide Engineering Brigade.
No, don't.
I know you were confused.
Don't be confused.
So yeah, so it's now built into the canon of Avengers campus and Peter Parker played
by Tom Holland, who's in the ride.
And it's fun now because I feel like they lock all these people into making sure they're
in the ride.
Sure they don't get any extra money, but that's the difference now that you get to see like
the most famous version at the moment of these famous version of this character at the moment
in the ride.
And he is creating spider bots that are cute as they're little guys, as Jason said, and
they're like, they look like little toys.
They sell the actual toys too, which is very smart.
And he's built these spider bots, I guess, to help build stuff.
They build and tear things down.
They can eat up something really quick.
But then scram with all its little legs, you know, put something together.
They're like 3D printers, I guess.
Yeah.
But then also the opposite of it.
They're 3D destroyers.
Yeah, break down material and then build new things with it.
And the only there's it starts with one and he's doing his presentation and focusing on
us, but he's kind of all over the map a little bit.
So he doesn't realize that the one multiplies and multiplies and multiplies.
And before you're out of that pre-showroom, there are so, so many.
And what is what was meant to be an open house at Webb becomes now a mission through
Avengers campus with high stakes, as they say, to help Spider-Man take down all these
spider bots.
Yeah.
So compliments on this ride.
Yeah, it is the most current.
It is Tom Holland.
It's the one that everyone sees in the movies at the movie theater and the big blockbusters.
All the kids like, you know, go to see the Spider-Man they know.
Also, the ride, you get to go through the locations from Avengers campus.
Yes.
A positive, very fun.
Yeah, like that.
Sure.
Together makes it a coherent little ecosystem in a very galaxy's edge way where you land
the Millennium Falcon and you see all the other stuff in B2.
I like that they're tying stuff together and making them tangible places.
Including not to jump too far ahead, the Avengers Quinjet hangar.
Take a good look and enjoy it now because you're probably not going to see it for a
while.
So yes, because that's where the building.
Yeah, right.
Yeah, that's where the ticket was going to be.
But that is not, I don't think on anyone's radar right now in the Imagineer.
I mean, it's on their radar, but it's not in the money, money side of things.
The spider bots got in there.
Yeah, destroyed the plans.
They destroyed the plans and went and filled out a bunch of pink slips for all the people
working on the ride.
Oh no, they ate all the shareholders value and turned it into pink slips.
They just, oh, and the spider bots also went to all the Imagineers in California's houses
and destroyed them.
They're going to have to move to Florida.
Made them move.
They built a new campus.
At that terrible lake.
Across the country.
Jason ate.
Hey, I think history has come around and proven me right when the governor of the state is
openly hostile to the company that is relocating here in Florida.
The issue remains, why do you hate the lake so much?
You hate that body of water.
You're so mad at Lake Nona.
That's just the name of the prefab, realtor, pseudo neighbor.
No, but it's a big, no, it isn't just where the Imagineers live because people wrote us
and said Lake Nona is cool.
It isn't the entire, it's not only the Disney.
Lake Nona, you're thinking, okay, here's what's going on.
Jason's thing of Lake Nona is an idea, is an idea, concept.
The concept of moving to Florida, Lake Nona represents to you, right?
Well, I think it's just like the idea of moving to Westwood or like if all of Westwood was
like the Americana mall.
But I don't think that's true.
I don't think it's only planned housing for Imagineers.
They may move there.
I think it exists.
I think, yeah, that is there.
But there's a greater community and I think a very nice lake.
I'm sure the lake is nice.
No, I'm sure the lake is nice.
We don't support, okay, we don't support the move to Florida.
No, but the lake visually might be nice and that's what we've heard.
Sure.
That's really what we're talking about.
It's like a real city that isn't just a place that they made a Imagineers move.
That's what I'm saying.
The Florida government.
And the end of the airplane runways that it butts up against are beautiful, really good.
Can you provide, this is, so you're saying this is like if you live there, your building will shake.
We'll need a Google map.
We gotta get a Google map.
We, I don't know.
You seem very confident that you know everything there is to know.
We wouldn't know anything about airplanes shaking the locations we're in.
But we love Burbank though.
Yeah, we do love Burbank.
So it's not a problem.
Yeah, it's not in the middle of Florida.
Lake Nona here.
I'm still, you're standing in Sofa.
You hate Lake, we gave you a chance to say you don't hate Lake Nona.
You hate Lake Nona.
There's a Nona Golf Club and Country Club right next to there.
Oh boy, I bet the members of that are nice.
This is funny.
So anyway, Lake Nona, there's still by the way planning on, again, I don't want to make it,
I want to make it clear.
I don't think that the Imagineers should have to be forced to move to Florida.
No, we're not.
I think we're very clear about that.
We're very clear about that.
I'm saying you have to remove not all of Lake Nona as an evil place.
Have we not convinced you of this?
No, I think I've come back around to my original position of like,
oh, this kind of sucks that you got to uproot.
No, that's not what we're saying.
We don't like that they had to move.
I think I've gotten an obscene amount of like YouTube ads for like,
start your tech, you know, start your tech startup in Lake Nona.
Like live, work.
You've gotten ads for Lake Nona?
I've gotten ads for Lake Nona.
Yeah.
What?
I've watched enough Florida based theme park stuff.
Oh my gosh, I got to see these ads.
Look, Lake Nona is a place that has biomedical research facilities
and a college of nursing.
You aren't mad at those, are you?
I think he is.
I think he hates the nursing school.
He hates every bit Lake Nona.
You want to wipe off the earth.
I don't know that the people going to that nursing school
are going to be able to live anywhere near that nursing school
with the current push to gentrify.
Are you familiar with what happens when areas get gentrified
like Silver Lake or Los Feliz?
Yes.
But that's what they are literally trying to do to this Lake Nona community.
You're sure that the people who work at the hospital can't?
Look, there's only one thing to do here.
Lake Nona episode has to happen.
Like everywhere else.
We're going to have to do it.
I don't understand what the problem is.
Like every other city in America, the crunch of housing costs and stuff
is getting worse and worse in central Florida.
So I think it's a net negative to force.
The forcing is not.
We don't like the forcing.
Look, I don't know what your two problem is.
You're so.
No.
Okay.
Hold on.
I feel like we've explained this 10 times.
I don't understand this bit.
The bit is funny.
Okay.
The first time we ever talked about Lake Nona,
I think what had happened is you were,
it sounded like you were just trashing whatever Lake Nona was.
Assuming that it's like a planned community
that's only a place they make people live.
Or it was just like kind of a desolate bad place to live.
Now, maybe actually what you meant really was that you were just in general upset
about them moving the imaginary people to Lake Nona,
which we don't like.
Might have been coming out, which we agree with you.
Yes.
I'm using it as shorthand to like force.
But that's what we're saying.
That's not.
Tons and tons of employees.
In the first episode, you were coming off,
like you were saying you hated that actual place
and that was a terrible place to live.
And then we got a few, just a couple messages of people saying,
well, Lake Nona is actually kind of nice and I like Lake Nona.
Like, yeah, I am sure the neighborhoods are plenty nice.
I'm saying whatever mixed use horror show of like overpriced apartments and work, live,
we work bullshit that they are forcing people to uproot their lives from Southern California,
which is great, and move to Florida,
which has now become openly hostile towards the employees
and the company they're working for.
Of course, we don't.
The Florida government, we don't.
It's a shit show over there.
Yeah, we hit.
Oh, yeah.
Florida's one of them.
But it was just funny.
The first time you were ever talking about it was just funny
because it sounded like you had been to like Nona,
knew everyone door to door was shitty
and the place was like a wasteland of like sludge and stuff.
So that's what we were joking about the first time.
And that's why people.
So I think also to justify this joke,
which I honestly I didn't want us to take a whole part of.
Sure.
No, not the.
I was just making a quick joke just to call back to it.
But the reason I think I thought that that what we were saying made sense
because people email this being like, oh, I think like Nona is pretty good.
A couple of people mentioned it.
So I think that's what how it was coming off.
I guess you just in general being mad.
No, I was using it as shorthand to refer to whatever this Disney creative campus
because that's what all the articles were just using short.
When you say like, no, no me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean the concept.
Yes.
So there so what so what I can get you to agree to is
is there are people in Lake Nona who have nothing to do with any of this and the lake itself isn't a problem.
That's that's where the disagreement came from.
And that's what was funny about it, because I think people like like Scott and I was backing up.
We were saying where you just came off like you were like saying this lake looks like shit,
like the physical lake looks like shit and it's a bad place to live that area.
I mean, yeah, sure.
I don't think this is worth the amount of ire it's getting you guys worked up in.
I'm not mad.
I just think it's funny.
The way that it played out is funny.
And then me calling it back, I think is funny.
But I didn't mean I didn't mean it to go back here.
I just thought last time we said it, it was like fun.
Like I thought it had been settled.
That's all.
Yeah, no, I think I thought it was settled as well.
I'm sorry for I just.
But OK, anyway, I think we've said our.
I guess we move on.
I think we're mostly on the same page.
That's I think it was just like I think we all mostly agree on everything.
I think so.
Yeah, I guess that's why I'm confused why you are so confused.
Because I was just making a call back to the joke about you hating the lake itself.
I said that Lake Jason hates, which is just I think I miss that bit.
That there's always there's been a lot of confusion.
I think there's been a lot of time it ever came up.
Yes.
And now we leave it to the listener to sort out.
And do parse through.
You figure out what happened.
Now we got to this point.
I remember.
OK, so right before we started into this discussion of it, I remember going,
oh, yeah, I can make a joke about like the old like donut thing, which we did to like
there were two mentions of, I think on the show.
I said, oh, this will be a funny little callback where I say, oh, Jason hates that lake.
And then here we are.
I we had the same conversation again, too.
So yeah, I just I honestly I didn't mean it.
I just we have to what we have to do is put this aside and and this has to be about teamwork.
Because that is the message of the web of this ride.
Yes.
And a web in general.
Well, and that's what web is all about is teamwork.
Yeah, we know this.
Yes, it's true.
They that is why you go on this attraction and you are thinking I got to get a better score
than everybody.
But that's not what you should be thinking.
Right.
You have to be working together.
Yes.
Which is a notion that I only understood after watching several YouTube videos and that I don't
understand based on this going on the ride.
Yeah, it's also like kind of set up idiot proof.
So you can't work against each other.
I guess you could work.
Oh, no, I was curious of what happens if you go on if you have four people in your party
and no one slings whips if you just sit.
Does it just start to Spider-Man just take care of everything because it just has to move along.
And there's certain beats of it and certain, you know, you move from up here, you move down
south and Spider-Man is in the cage and the Tavern collection and it drops like all that's
going to happen no matter what.
Yeah, it seems like there's like a base animation here that's going to happen and you just you add
you it's customized based on what you do.
And there are different things and like secrets and stuff in the same way the Toy Story has
like kind of unlock situations.
But it's like the basic the basic version of it, I think plays out like you're saying in a normal
way or what the normal way for the program is.
But yeah, I don't the ride is still too popular to like go on and have a fun like don't shoot
anything like there's not like if you're going on it like I don't know that I've seen any videos of
like look what I did.
I want to web shooters and I lied down on the seat look like look what happened.
We're not experimenting like you would be with a ride that's been there for a decade.
The line has never not been very long that I have seen.
And let me say this.
The thing that has become my the torch that I'm carrying, I guess, skippable versus unskippable
cues.
This is the most skippable cue I've ever seen.
You're standing in that you're just going around and around in that courtyard is like two like
weird gun inventions and four signs with a with a scientist on it.
And I've only done it and it's been 50 minutes.
I would know the pre show.
I like I like Tom Holland fun little routine.
I like that when they auto call Tony Stark and he goes, no, no, no, like that.
But that outside cue I would love to never do again.
It's kind of a heat trap.
Yeah, you know, we could really use another thing from universal fans everywhere.
Yeah.
Well, they've got a bunch of gizmos everywhere.
Why don't they invent some build them into the gizmos.
I like the profiles of like the other geniuses, like the other not who's in there.
Doreen Green Squirrel Girl is in there.
The character Squirrel Girl, Lunella Lafayette, Moon Girl.
She's friends with a giant dinosaur named Devil Dinosaur.
Yeah, that's good.
There's good little stuff.
OK, yeah, you're right.
The outside cue is not great.
There's little signs, at least, that show other Marvel characters, which if you know
the names like Jason, I know some of these names, you go, well, there's the name I know.
Harley.
And you get a little keener.
That is the character's name.
The character that I leaned over after the Avengers funeral scene and I went, who was that kid?
You were like, it's the kid from Iron Man 3.
I'm like, oh, yeah.
Tony Stark befriends a kid in Iron Man 3.
And he helps him rebuild the Iron Man suit.
Is that what happens?
He's kind of a boy genius, too.
There's a lot of kid geniuses in the Marvel universe.
Yeah, and this is like Mensa or the gifted program.
I see.
Webb, that's what Webb is.
Were we in programs, the three of us, as we were kids?
Because I was in the gifted program.
Yeah, there's a lot of pressure on me in the gifted program.
Oh, no, my brother was in it.
And then later on, there was like an additional, like a more broader,
gifted program that for whatever reason I was not put in, but I was allowed to go on the
field trips that they got to go in on.
I have no idea what the logic of this was.
I did get to go.
There would be like extra like the kids who were actors, like there would be workshops
or stuff that I would occasionally get to do.
Gifted, you were a gifted actor.
Thank you.
And still am.
Still remain, yeah.
Can't get arrested in this town, but I like that they guys know.
Well, look, we need, listeners need to put us in things, okay?
Podcasters only add additional.
That's all our, that's our last thing.
You said the quiet part loud, Mike.
Hey, we're getting old.
So yeah, now I've lost my train of thought on this.
There's signs with some care, but you would agree that you could have the signs and then have.
A better cue.
Anything else.
Yeah, because you're really just looping around.
You know what I don't like is that you're going into this backstage area
there's some forced perspective around there and there's a weird kind of crane piece that you're
very far away from and you think that that's a big mechanical crane that's building some new exciting
thing at Avengers campus.
And then the queue gets you right to the bottom of it and the forced perspective is ruined.
And you're like, this is just a little crane.
It's a tiny crane.
Yeah.
An ant man, maybe it was an experiment at the labs that made it tiny.
Slightly tiny.
So yeah, no, the outside, like there needs to be some more like whimsy in that outdoor line.
I don't think they're ever going to change it.
There's not much room, but it is like, I don't, we really haven't talked about like
cue patterns, the patterns of certain cues, like the way you kind of crisscross through.
And for whatever reason, this one feels very unpleasant.
I think it's like too confusing for me where I kind of like I'm going through the queue and I keep
going, well, wait, what do I have to do?
And you were kind of going looking ahead.
I agree with you completely.
There is a way that you can spread these things out where you feel like you have made progress.
It's a psychological thing.
Or you get like a big, you know, if like, if you're stuck in traffic,
and then you get a surge, oh, actually we kind of, hey, we kind of went straight away
there for a little bit and now I'm stuck again, but it felt good to go a little fast.
And the more that you're clustered and just like, wait, there's another switchback and
another switchback and another switchback.
Totally.
Yes.
And it's, yeah, there's something, it could be the same amount of time you wait,
but if the line is structured in the right way, it feels better.
And I don't know, I don't have the equation for what that looks like.
What's the good way to do it.
But this feels, this is like one of the worst ones as far as making you feel like,
oh God, where do we have?
Oh, I'm confused.
I thought we were closer.
We're not closer.
You know what I think it is is just physical footprints.
And I understand that they are working with what they had to work with.
This is built out of the shell of the, it's tough to be a bug theater and it's kind of
amazing how little changed.
I think they fit it all in that theater building.
There's not a ton of space here.
I was about to compliment the queue for rise of the resistance where you're,
there's so many rooms and you don't feel like you're doing a lot of switchback.
So it feels brisk even if you're in a long line because like new room, new thing to look at.
But that's a huge physical footprint too.
So that's some of the challenge that if you don't have a lot of space,
to put that line, it can feel like a bummer to be there for a while.
Yeah.
And they, yeah, they did their best.
There's not any, there's no room here.
So I get it that this is what they needed to do, but it is a bad line.
Yeah.
It is a bad line to wait in.
It's not great.
It did have the virtual queue for the first little bit.
It was open the day we were there.
It was before the magic keys started.
I think we bought one day tickets.
We had to all like jump on our phones to do the 7 a.m. virtual queue.
Got it.
Got in the car and the group was pretty, like the group got called when I was pulling into
the parking garage.
Oh yeah.
You were walking out of the parking garage.
So it was a little stressful.
And then like, I'm like running to get over there.
And then you were like, oh, there's, they've been doing a buffer.
This is like the third day it's been open.
Like no one knows what's going on.
Yeah.
It's like, oh, I should have double checked that before I like.
You shouldn't have like dead sprinted.
Yeah.
Tom Cruise style sprinted.
Tom Cruise with the arms, with the like very sharp arms.
Yeah.
So yeah, that we, I guess we've still waited for a while on that one, but yeah, you can
do Lightning Lane now for it, I guess, and skip.
Although people just Lightning Lane that I was with yesterday and they still felt like
they were waiting, like they went into the ride and they came out like 30 minutes later.
And I was like, that was the Lightning Lane for like.
Yeah.
Like that took forever.
I felt that with Lightning Lanes and with Rise and with this Spider-Man ride.
Yeah.
Lightning Lanes and Virtual Queues have still all made it.
You're still given this thing like an hour minimum of like, it is not like you're suddenly
just in there.
Lightning Lane should get you right on the ride.
Virtual Queue.
Okay, sure.
It's like you're waiting and there's a little extra, but like if you're paying
$15 for one ride, you should walk onto the ride.
You should be able to do as much like it shouldn't take 30 extra minutes.
You paid an extra $15.
Yeah, I know Kevin Perger has talked about this in his feature length, Defunct Land video
about Fast Passes, but I was reading like posts on Reddit because we were talking about
Lightning Lane and I was reading about Fast Pass Lightning Lane stuff where like former
cast members were talking about doing it and the different like at some point in time,
they had a red, green, yellow system and it would be based on like 10 to 1, 15 to 1,
25 to 1, which would be like 10 Fast Pass guests to one regular guest and that's why
Stand By Alliance would get so bloated because they were letting in.
They had to make the Fast Pass seem like it was worth it.
The trouble and in theory, you would want the Lightning Lane to be even more
worth it because you're shelling out money.
You're not just shelling out like the time to do the research of the Fast Pass or go
and get a little ticket or whatever.
My crazy or has Lightning Lane just made all of it much worse?
I feel like the park was so pleasant right before Lightning Lane and lately just like,
boy, everything's 45 minimum.
Well, they're still I think inflating the times to make you buy Genie Plus and Lightning Lane.
I was saying that the other day, but I was there a couple days ago and it was nothing
but sizable.
You were finding that lately the lines have been, I'll be honest, the last time I was there,
which was yesterday, I didn't go on any rides so I actually didn't.
Oh yeah, I only went on two because it was just one of those days.
Oh, you went on the train.
We went on the train and Mike got off at Toontown and I rode it back to Main Street and then rode
it all the way again.
You just raced in two loops?
Yeah, my leg was really hurting yesterday so I was just taking, I rode the train and
rode around a couple of times and went in some shops on Main Street and then got out of there.
Wow, wow.
And we were at the front to get into the queue for the train and Jason asked the cast member
there, he goes, is the Lily Bell running today?
And she's like, no, sorry.
I've been doing this for 10 years and it's never worked.
It's never.
Back in 2011, 2012, there was a lot of people online going like, if you go to City Hall
and ask about the Lily Bell and it happens to be on the tracks and there's not a private
party booked for it, you used to be able to get a certificate or a ticket that you present
it to the conductors or to the train people and they would let you in.
And I have never successfully done that.
It's one of the things.
I've happened to Mark Twain.
I have not ridden in the nice decorated train car.
It's your white whale.
We gotta make that happen.
Also yesterday we said how many trains are on the tracks because we were waiting a while
and they're like, there's only two so it's taken a while.
Yeah, I think I might be standing.
Yeah, I've been waiting a long time for this train.
So yeah, no, everything they've done lately has made guest experience worse.
Yeah, it seems like Disney World's been awful lately.
Yeah, I have not been, obviously, but yeah, Disney World seems like there's even more problems.
I will say this.
I had talked about Genie Plus.
This will be real quick, I promise.
Genie Plus.
I did use Genie Plus on a day a couple of months ago and I've conquered it.
I know how to do it.
It's basically the same as the FastPass Plus.
So it's the same checking.
I can check it all day and get an immediate time if I check well enough.
I see.
Okay, you know how to surf it.
I surfed it all day with friends who were in from out of town and we did everything.
Delivered for them.
Good.
You did that for park reservations too.
You and I were hunting to get me a park reservation because we have each other's
tickets and it is like...
I checked enough and got Jason a reservation for the next day.
Yeah.
When people cancel, they open up and if you are watching it, you can hop on it real quick.
The only thing is you can open three different web pages that give you multiple different views
and then you keep getting logged out.
Yeah.
You're constantly getting the emails saying you've logged in.
I sat on the couch for like 30 straight minutes and hit back and forward on the
calendar and then finally I saw when I clicked it, I got it.
Geez.
Well, this is a Spider-Man type.
Yeah.
A heroic action.
Web checkers.
Yeah, yeah.
Web being the internet.
I shot my organic web checking shooter, my biology at the computer.
You experienced your check dreams.
My check dreams.
So yeah, the queue outside...
I will say once you get inside though, I do think some of that stuff is cool and I like
sort of the feeling of it being lived.
Yeah.
People have their stuff there.
The Marvel characters have their...
I don't know, their civilian stuff.
There's a bike hanging inside the gate, right?
Yeah, and there's like a million...
That's Squirrel Girl's bike.
That's Squirrel Girl's bike, yeah, yeah.
Cassie Lang who is Ant-Man's daughter and then the comics becomes Ant-Man.
Ant-person?
Ant-person, yeah.
I'm not sure.
But she has a locker.
She has one of the lockers and then it's got a little door on it, like a little ant-sized
ladder and door on the bottom of it.
I like that.
The graffiti outside, there's a tag.
There's like graffiti tag and it's autographed Miles Morales.
He did the...
Yeah.
Which raises a lot of multiverse space questions.
Right.
He exists in the theme park universe but does not exist in the MCU proper yet.
That is a big gripe I have with the current state of Marvel after that Dr. Strange movie
because in this ride, there's a clock set to 616, which is...
616.
616 is the main continuity Marvel universe in the comics.
But in the Dr. Strange movie, someone says to Benedict Cumberbatch,
you're from the 616.
Your universe is 616.
And I'm like, wait a minute.
But you've been saying that the movies are their own universe and the theme park is their
own universe and the comics are their own.
So they show all different numbers by your own multiverse logic.
So you walked out.
Any times I feel like I...
I mean, I'm livid.
Look, if I feel like I'm not into this stuff anymore and then I see this stuff and I get
real gassed up, I was like, I guess I'm still invested.
Kind of makes me feel better.
That is interesting because I actually liked...
I see what you're saying though.
I didn't think about it when they said 616, which is the comic book universe,
because there's been multiverses in the comics forever and they have different names for
the different universes.
But yeah, I guess you're right.
I guess they should have made the movie something 617.
Yeah.
It's like area code, basically.
Sure.
So...
Like, artsy burser.
Or 169?
Like 16 by 9?
Like movie widescreen?
I'm not sure.
That's cute.
It's not a time.
It is cute though.
In this universe, there's a 169.
Yeah.
160...
Oh man, body-ness.
Oh no.
That isn't the Raspik ratio either, is it?
16 by 9.
16 by...
Oh, you're saying 16 by 9.
16 by 9.
169.
But when you say 169, then it's dirty.
Wait, what Jason wants is for one of these movies to have 169.
Okay, we'll solve it.
We'll call the universe 235.
Like the one...
That's a time.
Yeah, that is a style of widescreen aspect ratio.
But get a 169.
But get one of these movies, please.
I have a question about this ride.
I asked this when I was on it with you guys, and maybe I am dumb for not knowing the answer.
And I kind of get it, but I think it just speaks to the confusion of this ride.
That in the ride vehicle, it's starting, and I ask, why can't I sling webs?
Like...
Oh, what's that?
Is it the vehicles doing it?
It's the vehicle.
Yeah, it's the vehicle.
Okay, I know that it's fake, and I'm just in 3D glasses, and it's scanning my body,
which is very cool.
I like that moment.
You're looking down at your little frame that's being mo-capped live,
and that's very responsive and great.
But let's say that it really was...
Okay, if this is reality, where's the webs coming from?
Do I have metal things on my wrist that aren't...
Or are they coming out of my body?
I think they're coming out of the vehicle.
But if you're willing to dish out $35 and maybe $30 on top of that,
you can buy the Web Power Band and the other Web Tech add-ons.
And then it's coming out of your hands in the reality of the ride?
Well, then, in theory, the power-up that that gives you,
the first one gives you multi-fire webs, and then the others personalize it to other character
kind of powers.
Ghost, spider, Iron Man, rescue, other characters.
There's basically a little accessory you can buy to put on your wrist
that makes the gameplay differently, and you have different sort of powers.
But if we're talking about the reality of the ride, I think, yeah,
when you don't have one of these purchasable things, the vehicle is shooting.
Out of what?
Little holes in the front?
Little, like, rotating?
I don't know the answer is what I'm saying.
It's kind of a little screen.
Yeah, I kind of know that we know.
But if I'm looking at the vehicle, where are my webs coming from?
I think there's tiny little holes in the front of the vehicle.
A little grill.
I mean, screen like a car, a little grill.
I see.
I think there's a little grill.
I think it's like in Minority Report when Tom Cruise is moving stuff in the air,
and his hands are dictating where things are going and kind of doing things.
I'm like the Travago guy moving deals into place.
Like the Travago guy.
In the virtual space, the Travago guy.
This initially was a Travago ride, and then they sort of added the overlay.
And then they're like, oh, it's too hot.
This guy's too hot.
Now that's Travago.
Got to get him out of here.
The Travago ride is something that I would like because it's a checking and deals.
It's about checking, and a cool, swarthy guy.
You'd get on it, and like, you don't get 3D glasses,
they just ask you to unbutton your shirt a couple notches.
Yeah, so I like the original version, the Travago ride.
But yes, I think.
So the answer is I think.
And I will say a gripe I would have with this ride is they throw so much stuff at you right away,
which is a newer thing with a lot of rides.
Where like Avatar or something where it's like there's so much information you have to learn.
You have to learn that Webb exists.
You have to learn that Spider-Man has built all these things,
but they've also malfunctioned, and he's trying to get Tony.
He doesn't want to tell us Tony Stark, and this happens within so quick.
You can miss, I think, all these details if you go on five times, like whatever.
He says, get these vehicles ready.
And you're like, what are these vehicles?
And it's not just a car or something.
Oh yeah, it's like, also I invented something else.
Get in them.
Right.
It's like so much thrown at you really quickly that I think, yeah, it was just like,
we're, you should all, hey, we're here and we're going to all train like Spider-Man.
Pass through some portal and now you can shoot webs.
Go get in this car and do it.
Yeah, yeah, but they throw so much backstory to justify what you're doing.
And it's, yeah, it's similar to the Avatar pre-shows where you're just like,
it could be simpler like Big Thunder.
Woody has invented a machine that takes people.
Woody has broken the rules of reality where toys have to pretend that they aren't alive
for people and he shrunk you down to the size of a toy.
And he's also invented a special vehicle with a special string and ball.
This is too many things.
And let's just break down real quickly how the string and ball gun works.
Let's see the side view of it when it was being built.
Like so much detail and you're like, yeah, okay.
Not that all this stuff doesn't really hurt the ride experience
because it is what it is.
But it is confusing.
I just think it's weird that I don't know the clear answers to these,
I think very basic questions about what's happening on it.
I do wish they did that complicated Toy Story backstory for the old Toy Story Zoe trope
that used to be.
They would move around that the one, the old timey like.
The animation thing.
Yes, the statues that spin real fast and they're all a little different.
And then when they project strobe lights on it, it looks like they're animated.
Which I believe has ended up at the Academy Museum.
The new Oscars Museum.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
I saw somebody just told me they saw it there.
Yeah, so yeah, hey, we're all, I grant you spider powers.
Get out there.
Yeah, that'd be fine with me.
Doesn't that, they could do, it's a magic.
Anything can happen.
Yeah, Dr. Strange said.
Yeah, Dr. Strange, which, okay.
Maybe that leads me into my next little discussion point.
Because we can talk about what happens in the levels and where the spider bots get loose
and what happens.
But something that does not happen, and the listeners probably know this, is that there
is not a villain as opposed to the Spider-Man ride in Florida where you encounter many villains,
nothing but villains.
This is completely villain free.
And I understand that the plot does not necessitate it.
But again, what if you go to the Quinjet hangar and a villain got in there and then
you're gonna fight the villain?
There's a big spider bot, that's good.
But why am I, are we sure?
Are we sure no villains?
Why is it definitively, it just seems like it'd be, and again, I don't know Spider-Man
very well.
I couldn't name all the characters in that Orlando ride, but they're all cool.
And I like when they show up.
You're saying why isn't Michael Morbius, the living vampire on this ride?
And I agree with you.
Why isn't Morbius Spider-Man's nemesis?
He's more of an anti-hero than a nemesis.
Well, maybe he helps sometimes.
Scott, I'm right there with you.
I do know a little more about Spider-Man's bad guys and he's got a great rogues gallery.
Like he's got so many.
He's got a deep bench.
The bench is deep.
Deep bench.
Of these rogues.
Even beyond Sinister Six.
Of course there's a Sinister Six.
So deep.
He even just take those.
He's got Swarm, a man made of mutant bees.
Mutant bees.
Entirely out of mutant bees.
Not just partially.
He doesn't just have a bee hand.
Entirely out of mutant bees.
He's got the Rose, Wilson Fisk's son who leaves a rose as a calling card when he kills people.
Yeah, the Sinister...
Well, of course in Florida it's the Sinister Syndicate.
Because there's only five of them.
And they are off the top of my head.
Dr. Octopus.
Sandman.
Hydra Man.
No, Hydra Man.
Electro.
Shriek.
And Hobgoblin.
Not Green Goblin.
Yeah.
Hobgoblin's the pumpkin one?
It's very similar to Green Goblin.
Came along in the 80s.
But he's orange.
I see.
Cool costume.
Very good.
Good list.
Yeah, I mean, great.
Like, and I don't expect them to repeat what's in that attraction.
But something, I just like...
Again, it's one of those where we like the story.
And the way that they've missed out on a little fun maybe in Galaxy's Edge
by backing themselves into a story corner.
Yeah.
Maybe we're missing some fun here.
Yeah, I'm not sure what the rationale is for it.
Because like, Spider-Man creates the problem himself
by making these self-replicating robots.
Which, yeah, seems like a huge mistake.
Yeah, and I don't think of Spider-Man necessarily as self-defeating.
I think he gets in like tough spots because he has to make hard decisions
and balance his double lives.
You're saying Spider-Man does not self-sabotage.
He doesn't self-sabotage.
I think you're right.
Sometimes he does, but it's because something in the other part of one of his lives,
either his civilian identity or his secret identity, you know, his superhero identity,
he's usually something goes wrong because he's trying to take care of something else.
Yeah, but he is not self-defeating in that specific way like he is on this ride in a way.
He really is negligent here.
But I guess he's still just a kid and he's been given like,
just like a giant country's military budget to build whatever he wants in this new thing,
this new company, I guess.
That Tony Stark is funny because Tony Stark is still alive in the Marvel theme park universe.
Is his voice a little odd?
Yes, but he is alive.
About that, can I?
So they just announced recently that they're putting web slingers at the Disneyland,
Walt Disney Studios park, at Disneyland Paris, at their Avengers campus,
and they announced it with an Iron Man video.
And I just, what do you guys think of this Iron Man?
You're saying it started, we're hearing Iron Man right now?
Yeah.
You may know me.
You mean like, dude?
Like Dr. Evil.
How about no Scott?
Yeah, it is a little Dr. Evil.
I'm glad someone else said it too.
I was going to say it's like, you know, everyone, everyone who's ever been on Saturday Night Live
does impressions of Lorne Michaels, but that's like the worst, that's like a guy who thinks he can,
who can't.
Yeah, yes, the show goes on.
Yes, I'm Lorne.
C minus Lorne.
It's hard.
They get, look, Downey, you got, Downey had a lot of leverage because he was first.
So he didn't have to do all this stuff.
Yeah, it's also like, I believe that Iron Man, I think that's the animatronic that's going to be
in line for first flight, which is the redone, the redone rock and roller coaster.
But helpful to do Iron Man because one, you don't need to make it look like human face.
It's a little robotic already.
Do we know, are they playing like, either like Iron Man, Black Sabbath Iron Man, Oral ACDC?
On the ride? That's a good idea.
I don't know. That is a good idea, Mike.
The other question we had is, will that web slingers have footage of the events of the ride
going through their Avengers campus versus ours? Or will it be like Soarin' where-
Oh yeah, that's a good question.
For years in Florida, you were soaring over Southern California's Disney park.
I don't know.
We'll see, but I would just like to, I would like the idea that rock and roll stays in that building.
I don't like the idea that rock has left.
I don't want to lose rock.
And yes, people have sent me the Aerosmith residence.
It has been postponed because of Steven Tyler going into rehab.
That's sad.
I saw it.
Jeez.
Losing rock.
Yeah, but rock will, he'll rock again.
Nimgaloo will rock again, I believe.
So yeah, I will real quick.
I like the lockers in the queue too.
You see those lockers, they're like painted, like, you know what I'm talking about?
Well, that's what I was saying, Cassie, Ant-Man.
Oh, you were talking about those.
Yeah, the lockers.
I thought there was another thing I was missing, but yeah, there are like all these lockers
and they're all kind of painted like their outfits.
The heroes, yeah.
Like the heroes' outfits, which I think that's cool.
But yes, the ride itself, it's disorienting.
It is tiring in a way.
Like Toy Story is tiring, but this one's tiring.
And even like, maybe your arm doesn't hurt as much, but your brain
is like more tired.
It's just exhausting.
After a very hot line, and then you go flail around, you gotta flail those arms a lot.
And as a, you know, we, all right, so we just did the canoes and there was the discussion
of the physical exertion there.
I'm much more tired after web slingers because the canoes, it's this one repetitive motion
that's kind of calming as opposed to just, ah, everywhere.
How does this work?
Is this even the right way to do it?
What if I swing this way, that way, that way?
Like it's, yeah, I think it is mental and physical exhaustion.
And then to your point a little earlier is that, yeah, and then you don't even have
the satisfaction of seeing one of Spider-Man's rogues gallery like hanging from the web
at the end.
Like we did something, like really we should be more like upset by the end of the ride
because we're like, look, Tom, you did this.
We're just cleaning up your mess, Spider-Man.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
There's like some odd-
It's a little more maybe.
Right, exactly.
I mean, he thanks us a little bit, I think, but it's like we're not even helping him on
some like bigger threat.
It's like you screwed up, dude.
And now instead of us having like a leisurely training session, we had to clean up your
mess and we didn't have the leisurely time, which I think if this Spider-Bot thing wasn't
happening in the narrative of the ride, we would get to do more of what we're saying we want.
Test out the webs, use it to pull like a barrel over, use it to swing.
We get to really take our time.
But that being said, Tom Holland, Spider-Man is screwed up and now we're paying the price.
Yeah.
Wow.
I mean, I think the other thing that I, it's not as big of a deal as the rogues gallery,
but I do think Spider-Man is, I mean, it's trite to say nowadays.
New York City is a character, but Spider-Man is a New York superhero.
He lives in Queens.
That was like a big part of it.
He's a regular guy from an outer borough and that is a thing that you get in the Florida
one.
You go through New York, you swing through New York.
You're missing New York.
Would you say New York is a character?
I unfortunately did.
I miss it a little, but I do like say,
this is all taking place in the old Stark Motors factory and stuff.
Like the campus.
I think now that they filled it out, I think the thing I was skeptical about early on,
will they keep adding characters?
And they have kept that up.
It's like new movies and shows have come out.
Other characters have been showing up.
We can't say enough good things about all the amount of characters that have popped
in and out and quickly gone.
They're for like two days and then they're gone.
Loki in his prison outfit was there for like two days and then he's gone.
I think it's clever that one of the scenes in the ride, you end up in Pym Test Kitchen
and they're getting big and small and the pretzel gets big.
Well, as far as Avengers campus, I think we were a little bit in the middle on it initially.
I will say I've grown to like the campus a lot more.
I agree.
And I look forward to going there and just hanging out and chilling out there.
I think that's good about it.
I think that bar is very strong and I've had good things at that restaurant.
We said in the show, like Ant-Man walking around with the Bugs Land little thing.
That's fun.
I mean, that's terrific.
They're like adding.
It feels like they're easily able to add little ideas to it to keep it alive,
which is great.
I mean, that's what you want.
Yeah.
The nice thing about like comic book logic is like,
yeah, you can't do anything and justify it pretty easily.
Yeah.
So, yeah, as far as Avengers campus as a whole,
I certainly have a lot more fondness for that area now
and look forward to going there when I'm in the parks.
But I mean, maybe we're winding down here,
but if I have to say if I like the actual ride experience of Spider-Man,
I would have to say I don't.
Wow.
I don't.
It's too much.
You met me.
Now, is it?
I mean, I'm trying to think because basically it comes back to what we were saying earlier
about how the thing with Spider-Man is you were never imagining just shooting hard pieces of web.
That wasn't the thing that you dreamed of doing.
You wanted to swing.
Now, if it's a different character, if it's Cyclops from the X-Men
and he has his, of course, Ruby Quartz visor on,
we know he has that.
That's his thing that protects his eyes from just going out of control
shooting his optic blasts.
Which are concussive, not heat based.
Cyclops's optic blasts won't melt you, but they'll throw you into a wall at such a high speed.
It could kill you.
If that makes sense.
Do you know who Cyclops has got?
No.
James Marsden's classic performance.
He's got a yellow visor on and there's a red thing here.
Yeah, maybe.
You've seen him.
Anyway.
Or it could be Iron Man.
Iron Man shoots.
Sure.
So it's like, it almost felt like it's the wrong character to do this with.
I think you would still find it.
Oh, there's an idea.
Yeah, I think you would still find it a little bit too fast and disorienting
and like some of the same issues.
But I think that it might be more fun because at the very least you're kind of,
you're in the head space of the character that this motion makes more sense for.
So like Cyclops would like kind of, depending on what Cyclops,
like he would touch the side of his visor to like shoot a laser beam, essentially.
So say it was a Cyclops ride and you're shooting like you're,
and the thing is like tracking your eyes and you're looking up and down
and you would pretend you're hitting the side of your face or something.
That at least I would kind of be in the head space of a kid when I was little.
And I would be like, this is cool.
I'm doing what Cyclops does.
I'm shooting things and I'm shooting them fast because that's what's,
that's what I wanted to do, like to use his powers as a kid.
So there's a bunch of other characters I feel like who this ride makes more sense for.
Hmm.
Yeah, that's an interesting pitch.
Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, I mean, I don't, it's not going to happen, but it's,
I get why they ended up with this because it's a very small footprint
and they had to do something that felt action packed.
I mean, they're doing, trying to, you know, serve 10 different ideas or 10 different
mandates, maybe got to be action packed.
Got to feel like you're, you are the superhero, which is the whole big thing.
But yeah, I feel like a different character makes more sense.
Yeah.
I think, well, I was going to say kind of an inadvertent nod to the Florida ride in that the
in-between moments, there are a lot of pipes and barrels in crates, those classic theme park things.
But again, the Florida one, usually there's practical effects.
Usually there's mist something.
Sometimes there's just a pipe that explodes at the hobgoblin's bomb gets out of the way.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
There's nothing in these hallways.
And, and so you kind of see the like behind the scenes a little too much when like
you go by two screens and you settle at the first one or the second one.
Especially there's the notion that you're hopping all around Avengers campus.
Now you're in the Pym lab.
Now you're in the, the Tavon collection, the guardians.
Yeah.
But there's no way you did that travel.
There's no way you made it actually to all those places because you just went around a corner.
So you never feel like I'm, it doesn't go fast enough or simulate the idea that like
now you're whipping over to the guardians fortress and now you're over here.
And that, and the other thing about those places is they're kind of empty.
Like where are the other people?
Like I'm not even saying like it'd be cool to have Ant-Man or some of the guardians or like
rocket or going like, what are you doing?
But even just having a guy go like the classic, like, hey, Spider-Man, like just, you know,
a dock worker yelling like, Spider-Man, what are you doing?
You want those New Yorkers.
Well, she, you know, the real heroes, the citizens of New York.
You mess with one of us, you mess with all of us.
All of us.
That's what you want.
That character.
I think, and that would probably be a pain in the ass to program, you know,
the fast and furious digital people, like people running around in title safe exits or whatever.
But I think it might fill it out if you're going to keep it Spider-Bots,
like it'd be kind of cool to see people reacting.
Like what is going on?
We're calling Iron Man.
There should be, it should be almost like they're in the same way that star tours you,
there's the rebel spy and they take a picture.
They should like be face mapping people out in the park live and then throw them on the,
in the ride.
So you see like people you've actually passed by.
Right.
Yeah.
Every day.
There's just such a tiny amount of space there that, yeah, some of that stuff doesn't feel
as seamless as any of the practical transition things on Spider-Man or Transformers,
which goes from screen to screen and still gives you some feeling of like, oh yeah,
I've, I'm just sort of turning around in the world.
Yeah.
I mean, I think a lot of the, the busyness of the footage comes from like the Millennium Falcon.
It's not the same ride every time because it has to render your actions.
It has to render what's going on on screen based on your actions,
blowing up things and stuff.
Yeah.
But I've come around a little more on this ride because I figured out the easier way to do it
is you just punch, you just punch kind of like Spider-Man's black costume in the car too,
where like you would shoot and venom, which his webs shoot from the back of his hand,
top of his like wrist.
Not here.
Not here, not the underside, but the top of your hand.
And that is much more pleasant and that's how you've actually been able to get decent scores.
But it's so much less satisfying than doing the Spider-Man motion.
I really liked the black costume as a kid.
I did too.
So for me it's working.
The main thing.
Yeah, that main motion is fun.
This is what you want.
You want, you've been doing it for over, yeah.
Can we hear that?
The sound of one hand clapping.
Yeah.
I mean, I appreciate that they've color coded each rider with your webs and the scoreboard,
but it's so busy.
It's really confusing and I don't like the feeling of,
hey, I actually did okay in that one.
Well, maybe I'll keep going with the strategy I've been using.
Next round, I did way worse.
I don't like the inability to learn.
I don't know how to get better at this and maybe it is this teamwork thing.
You might have to go into it with a plan.
I watched a video that was saying, all right, just everybody go after the Spider-Bot.
As soon as you see him or try to, there's like lasers you can activate in the Quinjet
area that will just decimate all of the Spider-Bots.
But at the same time, who wants to be in that line and then be the guy going,
okay, guys, so we got to come up with a plan here.
Because all right, huddle up, stop having fun and side conversations and
playing the game with your phone.
We got to get down to business if we want to be the team that takes this for the day.
You don't think Jason and I would do that?
I mean, I guess so.
Yeah, we probably would do that.
No, I'm the problem.
Like, focus up here.
It would be nice.
It's like, hey, can you put it on tired dad mode for our screen, please?
Thank you.
Yeah, I was trying to think of something else.
Yeah, I was saying I've come around on Avengers campus.
I think I've come around on the ride more because I'm starting to figure out the tricks.
I've definitely blown up a lot of barrels.
Yeah, I think that's helped.
Yeah, I understand all of the limitations of it, but it's like,
it's still, even though it took me probably a while to figure out to get a higher score on
Toy Story, initially, just it was very satisfying pulling the cord and shooting a thing out.
Instant something happened.
Instantly, yeah, like intuitive.
It was an instantly like pleasurable experience to do that motion.
And this one is still like, I've done it maybe four times now and I'm like,
okay, one of these days, I'm really going to get it.
And it's difficult.
And I feel in a similar way, like, it makes sense.
It's been built in the same era as Millennium Falcon because it kind of feels a little over
thinky and like, oh, you have to be part of this.
Whereas some of it you go, I could just watch a video of you guys doing this.
Yeah, like, it's a little more exciting.
And it feels like, I wonder if there was any consideration to just having
just a straight up training program that was somewhat exciting.
Like, all right, I'm Spider-Man.
I'm going to show you how to web swing or whatever.
And like, we all do this and we all shoot a web and then in 3D, the car feels like it
swings and we're swinging and swinging and swinging and swinging.
And then the vulture shows up and you got to fight it.
Sure, great.
And it goes wrong.
Something goes wrong.
But I feel like if you could like, if the car like just kind of rocked itself a little bit
with a decent 3D screen, at the very least, you could kind of give everybody the sensation
that we were going and you could still have like the web appear in your 3D.
And like, I feel like there's moments like that that would stick longer in your mind.
And it's in a similar way to Millennium Falcon where your brain is just like,
I got to figure this out.
And it's not so many memorable things in the video game part of it.
The lack of just moments.
Yeah, I remember the coaxium part when you crash in Millennium Falcon, I guess, is the one I
remember.
I remember that I've been in a lot now, but it's not, as we've said before, it's not like
the stuff on Star Tours we remember.
Where you remember so many moments and big things that happen on Star Tours.
And a lot of it is because you're not just frantically doing something.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think I am.
And maybe I'm not the target for it, but like there was a moment in Doctor Strange, I feel like,
where they reference one very specific element from one of the TV shows.
And I had remembered that from the TV show.
I was like, oh, huh, that's kind of a fun little callback.
But that doesn't feel as satisfying as, yeah, like you were saying, Star Tours.
Or falling at the end of Amazing Adventures of Spider-Man, then you're caught in a big web.
Or like Transformers, where Bumblebee catches you.
That, yeah, I guess.
The finest moment in right-dom.
That was one that I am still very, that was the original maybe too busy screen ride for me.
Transformers.
Yeah.
One of those great moments.
Fine.
Watch your words.
You're going to have a big garage fight.
I mean, yeah, that'll be a big thing.
Yeah, you want moments like that, like the big drop into Bumblebee or whatever it is.
You want songs where none of us can remember when the songs play.
And it turns out we were both correct and they're different.
Both right.
But they're different parts of the-
In a way both wrong.
That's all confusing is the point.
And you want to get thanks as you were thanked by-
Yes, that's true.
You are, the solution keeps being make it more like Transformers, the ultimate ride.
It's always in life in general.
Less interactivity, more Brookheimer.
More, has Brookheimer produced those?
Transform, wait, now Michael Bay?
Michael Bay directs them.
I always got those two confused.
Brookheimer, I don't remember.
I think Brookheimer's involved in producing.
Michael Bay then.
I think that I always get those two mixed up.
But they work together.
Sure.
So, yeah, I think, I just think there was maybe even a simpler version of it.
That yeah, wouldn't have been as good as Orlando because they don't have the room or whatever.
But would have left you going, oh, that was a cool little use of space and it's a fun,
whatever, C ticket, B ticket, whatever you would call it.
And you could still have a lot of the elements that they have in there.
Oh, I remember one of the things I wanted to say that I don't think we've mentioned yet.
I like Sharon.
I like the voice assistant.
Uh-huh.
I didn't know that name.
Throughout the ride.
They say it real quick at the top and I think in the pre-show, pre-show room.
I don't know, I just like that voice.
I think it's a good performance.
I think they play off Tom Holland pretty well.
I don't know who does that voice.
Oh, I don't either.
At first, I thought it was Alison Brie, but now I don't think so.
I think it might just be a voice actor.
Is she original to the ride?
I think she's original to the ride.
So I like that.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, yeah.
And add some fun levity and giving the computerized dire stakes of what's happening,
but makes it kind of casual.
Now it's really, really bad.
Yeah.
I think that's a thing that they started in the first Iron Man movies came out and then as the
I-Five, as Siri and all the voice assistants got better and better.
I was like, well, they were kind of right about that.
I got to give them credit.
I like Jarvis.
I like Friday.
You know, a lot of AI sharing.
Yeah.
Sharon was it?
Did it stand for?
It has to stand for something.
I don't know if it stands for something.
Is it just a nod to Mrs. Ozzy Osborne herself?
I think, yeah, I think it's a nod to Sharon.
To Sharon and Ozzy or Ozzy screen Sharon.
Remember when he would just yell Sharon?
Yes, I do remember that.
Well, she should be in the universe because as I said, I want Iron Man to be playing in Paris.
So maybe they have to work on it.
They made it worked out.
I'm not sure.
Okay, I see.
Yeah.
To work out Sharon Osborne.
Welcome to the MCU.
She's in a post credit, the third post credit scene and the last one.
Whoa, can you believe it?
Well, we do it.
I think we did it.
Yeah.
And I will once again, apologize to the lake and the residents of Lake Nona.
I am going to work on finding a shorthand for the Disney mixed use boondoggle thing.
So I don't insult the whole neighborhood.
You finally understand.
You do get it.
I get it.
I get it now.
It only took me 15 months.
Sometimes I'm a little stupid.
I don't know.
I didn't know.
Say that.
Hang on.
We weren't calling you stupid.
As we were doing the last hour of the podcast upcoming,
there's a person in my brain going, hey, remember when we had that Lake Nona
argument earlier today?
And I'm like, yeah, yeah, I'm trying to finish a podcast.
Yeah.
It's really straight, just like you didn't load it.
Like all the Lake Nona feelings, all replicated like spider body.
Yes.
Took over our brains and bodies.
You were trying to clearly do one bit and I thought I was just being
frank and discussing details I had read about in various editorials and all.
I didn't think any of it was a bit.
It seemed like an earnest discussion, it felt like to me, which I hope makes any sense.
Listeners who do not, they don't remember why this came up in the first war.
Yeah, people going back, like listening.
I will find a new podcast and start with the most recent one and just go backwards.
Well, the people who do that on this, like the Marvel universe,
it's full of slight nods to things from way back in the mythology.
Oh, there's a tough to be a bug reference.
The 3D glasses are like in a pile somewhere.
Is there like a claw game?
There's a bunch of those like
capsules that you find in like vending machines or claw game kind of thing.
There's a pair of the bug 3D glasses sitting in that mix.
Yeah, I like that.
It's not, we get what it is.
I don't want to be so negative.
I think like, I didn't feel good saying, oh, that's, you know what?
You can try to think of any argument on its behalf.
I think that all ages aspect is good.
I think it's very little.
Yeah, you can be little.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Which and most, most like expensive new, especially superhero IP,
or there is a high requirement and yeah, it's cool that this is forever.
I bet this, this might be, this might, if we had a guest on the show who was five years old,
they might offer a different, they also would say, I liked, I liked when the
spider came out and they would have been gone two hours ago.
I, yeah.
And so it's not, I don't have ownership over the current Spider-Man or even the MCU,
I guess, and because also Marvel has been pumping out the 90s cartoon is on Disney Plus
and they keep putting out action figures that look like the ones that we bought as kids,
but they're much nicer and significantly more expensive.
Oh, I have them.
I do have them.
And I, I still have them on the card too.
And you know me, I'm an out of box guy, but I have not opened any of them.
I know it's getting harder and harder as the cards get nicer.
Yeah.
Especially the oversized card.
I have the kingpin.
Yeah.
Such a big card.
The only Spider-Man I feel ownership over is when any of the Muppet Babies are Spider-Man.
Just go, like I was like, I'm not is remembering this right.
If you Google image Spider-Man Muppet Babies and you can see Skeeter and Scooter and
animal is where Spider-Man swinging around and then takes his mask off and it's animal.
I think the first I ever saw Spider-Man was probably within Muppet Babies
and thought that it was like an only in Muppet Babies.
Oh my gosh.
Star Wars.
I feel like Star Wars.
Star Wars Muppet Babies is a great, I think.
Star Wars too.
Yeah.
I think Kermit is Indiana Jones at some point.
I remember.
All of them.
When I was in college, I was a PA at a comedy festival where the Henson people did that
puppet up, the puppet improv.
I was helping them load their crates the last day and I talked to Brian Henson,
not realize it was him.
I was like, oh yeah, I work on lots of Henson.
I work on lots of stuff and lots of DVD release.
I was like, do you think we'll get Muppet Babies on TV?
Like 21 year old me is asking.
Then immediately I realized who I talked to.
I'm like, do you think we'll get Muppet Babies on DVD?
I would love that.
Well, that's good.
You had the year of power.
And the answer seems to be no.
I don't believe we ever got like a definitive or even a streaming.
What did he say?
He's like, oh yeah, there's a lot to figure out.
You know, we certainly heard that, you know?
Yeah.
So, but yeah, original Muppet Babies.
That was appointment television for me at a very young age.
That's how I learned when things would be on the same time on TV.
I was like, gotta be up by 10 a.m.
Gotta be in front of the TV.
Muppet Babies is coming on.
Oh, that's another Google image.
Star Wars Muppet Babies.
And there is a Leia Miss Piggy hugging baby Kermit.
Oh yeah.
This is the cutest thing I've ever seen.
There's no cute argument here.
This is very loving.
Piggy Leia.
This is pure love right here.
That's nice.
Yeah.
You can't be mad at that.
You know what I would want to ask the listeners is,
did anyone, whether you are adult or child,
have you bought the attachments?
Have you bought the web tech add-ons or have you bought the remote control spider bots?
Because I think they thought those would be a big hit.
And they kind of got rolled out when they were doing that warehouse store.
Deep pandemic.
It was confusingly.
A very dark time for the company.
You could tell they just had everything like in crates.
They had crates ready to go with all this stuff.
And so I think it was a little anticlimactic, some of that stuff.
The web tech add-ons were announced like a month before the ride.
Yeah.
And when you're talking about this on Avengers campus where people were like,
Disney with an upcharge.
And you're like, have you ever been to Disney before?
Do you have seen Harry Potter wands?
What are you talking about here?
Are they helpful?
Are they fun?
They seem like they'd be very fun take home toys for kids.
I said at the time, if I was a kid, that would have been really cool.
And I think I even use Cyclops' visor as an example of like,
if it was like they had all your heroes stuff and as a kid,
you could get it and then take it home.
That would have been awesome.
I would have thought that was so cool.
And the idea that it would change the ride, that is a cool idea.
Yeah.
They have some little diecast web vehicles or spider bot ones.
There's a Doctor Strange one now too, isn't there?
Like a Doctor Strange thing you can buy.
Oh, maybe.
I think it's new.
So yeah, I guess, yeah.
I think that it's a cool, fun thing.
And as just a toy, it fires a little string and that's neat.
But I think it does not guarantee you to do better in the game.
That's what I seem to have caught.
But don't quote me on that ever because I'm not the person who's going to buy this wrist.
It's still very funny that they had so little room.
The massive store is in another land.
That's still pretty funny to me.
Really?
Yeah.
Cramming it in.
Well, they got something in there.
Avengers Campus has a ride.
I don't know when it will get its next ride, but at least we can say this.
It is a ride that you can go on and have opinions about as we did.
Your kids who are really good with phones and tablets and computers are going to love it.
That's, I think, the issue.
Yes.
Yeah.
Get your four to nine-year-olds there.
Your 36-year-old family members and friends will be confused.
We're tired.
My wrist hurts.
Our bodies are falling apart.
My voice is tired.
I better end the show.
You survived Podcast the Ride.
And for more of us, you can find us on the socials at Podcast the Ride.
Merch is available in our Tee Public Store for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out Podcast the Ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride,
which as said at the beginning is now home to our new Patreon tier club three,
where you get our regular episodes ad free and one more bonus episode chosen by you,
the listeners.
Eventually.
Right now we picked the first one, but it will become an interactive experience like
Web Slingers.
Exactly.
A Spider-Man adventure.
So great.
Good talking about it.
And I hope it made everyone's web dreams come true.
I hope it.
I hope it agreed with your biology.
This episode that is.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.