Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate,
which is just behind the trees from Podcast the Ride,
the main feed.
It's right over there behind that set of trees.
I'm Scott Gardner, Jason Sheridan's here, hi.
Yeah, yeah, you can kind of see it if you squint.
Not too far.
You're in the Patreon swamp, Mike Carlson, hi.
The Patreon swamp.
What a place to be.
That's a good thing, Kermit loves it.
Yeah, that's true.
Swamp's not a bad place necessarily,
you just think about it like that.
So happy there.
Disney World was built on a swamp, it's good.
Swamp is good.
Yeah, yeah, let's destigmatize swamps.
No, we're happy to be here,
very happy to be talking about this special,
one of the most delightful specials put out by Disney
or the Muppets, two wonderful entities coming together.
That's right.
Just as we are coming together with a titan of,
well not quite podcasting, but weird DIY media,
by which I mean the George Lucas talk show
and also from his New York live improv show,
Rat Scraps, it's Patrick Kotner, hi.
Hey guys, how are you?
Hello, we're fine.
The titan of weird, I like that.
Oh yeah.
That's where I stopped it, yeah.
What is the, I mean the George Lucas talk show,
it's like I wanted to call it a podcast,
but I know it's not that.
It's a live stream, it's an experience.
It sure is.
I think that's maybe the best way.
We had so much fun, I enjoyed doing that
with you guys so much.
You guys stayed a while.
Yeah, yeah, I even like, I had to go to bed,
I had a hard out to take care of my kid.
I had to bail just for pure,
like I am screwed in the morning if I don't,
but I didn't wanna go,
cause then by the end we're,
boy it gets loose, we're hanging out,
we got candles and sunglasses.
I think Mike left for like an hour.
I made a pizza, I put McGruff in the chair
and then I came back and McGruff came to life
for the last like 20 minutes.
Well we got Irishmen.
That's true.
Yeah.
Oh right, right, right, right.
Were we watching it that night?
You guys were watching, Tom Sharpling had messaged
and thrown you the curve ball
that you had to watch the Irishmen in the background.
Which he had threatened to do at some point,
like I have the right to do this to you guys at any point.
Tom had donated, we always gave the option to the viewers
that if they donated a certain amount of money
to some charity that we were doing,
that they could have an Irishman
that we would have to watch on the show
and they could, we told Tom he could use it at any time.
So I remember how much it was, but it was a lot of money
and he like held onto it for a year
and just happened to throw it all out that night.
Wow, wild.
It was crazy and fun and that's archived,
that's up on YouTube, you can watch that.
Which the quick sell of the George Lucas talk show,
I guess if people haven't seen,
I think we've got a lot of fans in common
so we're happy to have you here.
But you know, but it's you and what's his name, Watto?
Yep.
And George Lucas is a former, is a retired.
He's a filmmaker, he made a couple movies,
it's been a while though, but yeah.
And George hosts a talk show,
it's just like you're watching, you know,
Jimmy Fallon or Jimmy Kimmel or whatever,
except this happens to be hosted by a 75 year old,
retired billionaire filmmaker named George Lucas.
Who we learned knew a lot about Disney and classic animation
and the origins of Donald Duck and how he's a comic strips.
Over the years.
He loves Donald Duck.
Carl Barks, he loves Carl Barks.
His comic strips are really important.
Yeah, Clarence Duckie Nash, is that his name?
Used to be the voice of Donald.
Yeah, yeah, George, big Donald Duck guy.
Anyways, it's a talk show.
We talked to guests.
We've, you know, we've had Weird Al was on
and like John Ham's been on and Amy Mann's been on
and just a lot of insane people who, Whoopi Goldberg,
who like should not have been on the show, you know?
Like there's no reason why they should be there,
but they're there.
It's very fun.
It's very silly.
It's all on YouTube.
You guys, people can go watch if they want.
Yeah, yeah, so much fun.
We really enjoyed doing it.
And you're here in Los Angeles
doing the George Lucas talk show live,
which we're at Dynasty Typewriter
where we've been so excited for that.
It's in the future, I think, from when this is coming out,
but it's sold out, correct?
Sure.
Is it coming out this week?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes, yeah.
I mean, listen, you can buy live stream tickets still.
Wonderful.
Dynastytypewriter.com slash GLTS,
you pick up those live streams.
We're doing two shows,
two different sets of guests.
I told you guys who the guests were.
Uh-huh, yes, we know, yeah, yeah.
You can vouch pretty good.
Pretty good, yeah, yeah.
Pretty good.
Uh-huh.
So maybe, yeah, encouraged.
So yeah, go get those tickets if you want.
I wonder if you do have a, okay,
so you can't send people that way, that's great.
But we're also, we have you here
during your Los Angeles trip
for what you said was your first in-person recording.
It's crazy.
In years, I can't believe it's that.
That's great.
Yeah, first in-person, non-George Lucas,
like just podcast recording.
I haven't done one since pre-pandemic, so this is...
Geez, great.
I'm having to like stare at people.
Like you see me looking around the room right now
and it's just weird having to make eye contact.
Yeah, and we're spread out, we aren't in a window.
There's a little bit of distance between us
as opposed to between windows.
Sure, sure, sure.
It's a different deal.
I don't know if all podcasts are happening
in a garage that has occasional plane and bird
and car noise, but it's, you know, it keeps it breezy.
It's just a backyard hang.
And in this case, what could be breezier
than talking about the Muppets at Walt Disney World,
a delightful special.
Actually though, before we get to that,
which it's such a fun special to talk about,
but I really liked our back and forth about
what to discuss on the show,
because you were very clear that like
anything within either Muppets or Star Wars
and the list that you sent,
any one of them would have been fantastic
and will be in the future.
Like the topics just cut so deep.
And I guess, what am I asking here?
Do you wanna like vouch for any of them in particular
that we should do or you wanna do in the future
or just give any love to?
Let me pull up the slides.
I need to reference this out loud.
Yeah.
While you have a microphone and people-
I'm trying to remember how many I gave you,
but okay, oh my God, I gave you a lot.
Okay, so also, well it's funny,
cause you're talking to, you know,
we talk to people who love the parks
and then they give you things, you know,
attraction ideas that are great,
but they don't cut as deep as-
I love Disneyland so much.
I wanna do Space Mountain.
You're like, uh, snooze.
Yeah.
Not a real fan, we say.
You walked in the garage and you barely sat down
before you were name dropping Dexter Jester, you know.
Yeah.
I mean, let's say like Star Wars and the Muppets are my two,
those are two big things in my life, you know?
Two things that I've liked for a very long time.
So of course, MGM, Hollywood Studios was like my,
that was my place.
Like that was the place I loved the most.
God, yeah, both in their prime.
Absolutely.
And they're still, yeah, they're like-
They're still kinda there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Before everything had to be,
nothing had to be rebooted yet.
They were still pretty close to the original,
very present.
Muppet stage show, they're like,
they're all, besides Muppet Vision 3D,
they're all around in so many different ways.
Big Muppets?
Yeah, big scary Muppets, big gangly Muppets.
Those are weird.
Yeah, they're weird, but I kinda like them.
Absolutely.
It's funny seeing like Kermit with like human proportions.
You know, where you're like, there's a guy in that suit,
his arms are so wide.
It's also the juxtaposition of like celebrity hand prints
and cement, which will come up later,
and a walk around Dick Tracy and giant Muppets,
like, just delightful.
And then like the dinosaurs and,
oh my God, what an assortment.
It is like the very, very early MGM studios
is like you shook an older millennial's brain.
Like you try to read their brain signals
and you're just getting clips of memories.
And it ruled.
Yeah.
That's the best.
Absolutely.
So all right, so I said Muppets of Walt Disney World,
which is what we're here for.
I said any canceled MGM Muppet stuff.
So like the idea is that they wanted to do
the great movie ride that was gonna be Muppetized.
I said Star Wars Launch Bay, which is fine.
It's interesting.
Sure, it would be to meditate on it for a while
and you can get something out of.
I said the hand prints outside great movie ride
because I was there when R.L. Stine did his.
Wow.
Which I've never seen out.
So I imagine they just have like a store room
with a bunch of.
Yeah, I don't know that they,
yeah, I think they, to get people there
and then they'd keep them out for a couple of weeks
or if they heard the person was coming,
they'd like, get it.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, there was a very brief Goosebumps stuff
at MGM studios.
It was probably right around then.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was 98, 99, probably somewhere around there.
And he put his hands in there
and then they just like, oh great.
And then he left and they picked it up
and just put it right backstage.
Yes.
Mine was Jody Sweden from Full House.
Wow.
In print, yeah, that's pretty,
and I love Full House by that point.
Was that during Full House?
Yeah.
Oh wow.
And I forget if they had done the official TGIF trip
or not. Sure.
But right around then.
That's pretty cool.
I said the great moments in American history,
the like window show with the Muppets.
Yes.
Yeah, we never done that.
Which is a great show.
Yeah.
I said the Meet the Muppets show
which is the one with the walk around characters
that was gone pretty quick.
Yes.
It was there for like a year maybe or something.
Too many tears.
Yeah.
He screams at Big Biggie.
I said the Bunsen and Beaker mobile labs.
Oh yeah.
That was there for a little bit.
Also doing.
Is that around a little ever?
I don't think so.
I haven't seen it in a while,
but stuff has been popping up that like robot
that like roams around tomorrow in his back.
So I feel like sometimes they have stuff in storage
that just pops out once in a while.
But I don't think they've had that mobile labs in a while.
I said any Galaxy's Edge stuff really.
The Galaxy's Edge comic book, which is wild.
Have you guys read that?
No.
They like try to tie it in to the thing
and like make it feel like this is the real world.
But then, you know,
also make a lot of the background characters
just look like cast members.
It's like very, very weird.
That's strange.
The art of Galaxy's Edge comic book,
or the art of a Galaxy's Edge book
that's just going through all the concept art.
Those weird busts that were in MGM.
Yes, yes.
Of like TV legends.
And by the way, if you're just running around,
not that far from where we're recording,
you might actually enjoy this.
There are two places where those were,
because that was the thing with the TV Academy.
Oh yeah.
And we're near the TV Academy,
which is like a little courtyard with a big Emmy.
It's in North Hollywood and they have the same bus.
It's like a big courtyard with all the,
so it's like, it's, you know,
Lucy and Carol Burnett.
Yeah, yeah, that kind of people.
It's behind the Jimmy Johns.
It's not on the main drag.
And I think across the street from Vape Depot.
Yeah.
You can get, I for sure have posted a photo
of a Vape Depot through the Emmy Globe.
Yeah.
If you hit the Dave's Hot Chicken
that used to be the Arby's, keep going.
Okay, okay.
Good time, good time.
And those, and with those busts,
I don't think they put this in in Florida.
The North Hollywood one has Chuck Lorre.
Oh.
And his plaque is one of those big rants
that he goes on. Oh no.
On his like title cards.
So you can go see a Chuck Lorre.
I don't think in either one can you now see a Bill Cosby.
That makes sense.
I believe Bill has been. Yeah.
Right.
Ripped out of.
I said the Drew Carey show, the like sound thing
that was at MGM.
Oh, you have that one?
Oh wow.
Yeah.
In Prenseys I put barely remember it,
but I remember it being weird.
That was all I remembered.
Extremely weird.
Blackout by narrow audio.
Yeah.
The Figment comic book.
And then the old Star Tours pre-ride video.
Wow.
The one where they just like took the masks
from like the Ewok movies and.
Yeah.
Put it in there.
Oh, which I love the camera with the multiple.
Yeah, that's great.
Oh my God, the best.
Geez, well you cut deep.
You cut deep with Disney, MGM studios especially
with Star Wars and with Muppets.
And I think we landed at the right thing.
Which is what a, is it the, you know,
maybe not better than Muppet Vision 3D,
but it's one of the best collisions I would say
of Muppets and Disney.
Yeah.
I mean, they feel like such, they go together so well.
You know what I mean?
Like I always think of one when I think of the other
just cause they were made basically at the same time.
So like the puppets all look the same.
You know, like it's like.
Yes.
They weren't of different time period.
The vibe is right for every, it's right for the park.
It's right for the Muppets.
There's only two guest stars, but they're pretty notable.
This is again, for millennials, just put this on.
It's like a thunder shirt, not a scared dog.
Like this is just like catnip.
You just relax, you calm down.
Your friends are all here.
They sound correct.
They sound right.
They're making jokes that you would think like,
is that a weird old vaudeville reference?
But I'm allowing it because it's a bunch of puppets.
My favorite puppet friends saying it,
my favorite Muppet friends.
Yeah.
And I mean this gets dark.
This is the last time they quote sound right.
Unquote.
Right.
Well, yes.
It should be noted this aired May 6th, 1990 on NBC
on the magical world of Disney.
This is before they were fully in a relationship
and owned ABC.
May 16th, 1990, Jim Henson passes away 10 days later.
Insane.
So crazy.
So this is the last film.
Well, no, Muppet Vision 3D comes out later.
Yeah.
Right.
But like the one of the last Jim Henson pieces
also aired two days after Jim Henson was on Arsenio Hall,
which was his last appearance just as him.
And then I didn't know this, the day Jim Henson died,
so right around there, on the same day,
they aired a special called Sing Sesame Street Remembers Joe
Raposo, who's a tribute special to the Sesame Street composer.
And Jim is in it being interviewed.
So the day he died, you could watch this thing that's
about the sad premature death of another Muppet legend.
What a time.
It's also the same day Sammy Davis Jr. died.
Wow.
Isn't that crazy?
Geez.
That's a wild day.
You think that celebrities only die together now,
because people on Twitter are weird and loud about it
and make art where they're like holding hands.
Right.
Why weirdly walking into heaven together?
Or if they have figures, they do a funeral with the figures now.
That's a common thing.
It is?
Oh, yeah.
No.
Where has that been done?
On the Facebook groups I'm on?
Yeah.
I'll tie Griffin Newman and I will share them sometimes
when someone has passed away, but they have a figure.
You have to say one.
Who has been figured?
I mean, the closest one, and it's very sad,
but obviously we're making fun of the idea of the memorial
is Chadwick Boseman's Black Panther figure.
Oh, no.
Just like in a funeral.
People are like in RIP.
And I'm like, you set this up, man.
This is pretty weird.
Well, here's what I need to do is get this action
figure in a little box or whatever.
It is.
Jeez, that's weird.
Are there figures standing around them?
Yeah.
People from there, or can the Smurfs come?
Who gets to go to the funeral?
It's usually with, from what I've seen, it's usually in the universe.
I mean, there's a Stan Lee figure, and when Stan Lee died,
it was all of the Marvel heroes standing around Stan Lee,
and the people posed them perfectly.
Thanks to deep fake technology, it will be like Stan never died.
Well, that's a hole.
We could do a whole hour and a half of a new contract
that will allow Stan Lee to continue cameoing in Marvel films and TV.
I have a theory that Tom Cruise is developing the best AI
with the best deep fake so that there will never not be Tom Cruise movies.
Is that just because you got fooled by that deep fake of Tom Cruise?
I did get fooled by that deep fake.
I did.
I admittedly won that Proclinent Singer.
I'm just wondering what your rationale was for Tom being the one.
I'm thinking about Maverick, and looking at him getting old
in the Mission Impossible trailer, I'm like,
what if there are Tom Cruise movies forever?
And the Stan Lee news.
I bet my thinking would be that Tom is actually
investing in things to keep him alive.
That too.
I would think he's doing it.
He told me to be mutually exclusive.
I guess that's true.
But Tom's such a practical effects guy.
He would want to be doing the teenage blood, blood replacement,
all the different things.
Cloning himself and putting his old brain, a rejuvenated old brain
into the new body.
I think he's looking at all that stuff.
Yeah.
So yeah, perhaps part of it is the looking into if with enough G's,
if he keeps climbing and climbing, can he find heaven?
Sure.
Got a camera up there, keep filming his movies in heaven.
I found it, found the place.
All the everyone you remember and love is here.
I'm with them.
So Fred stares in my movies now.
Yeah.
Marilyn Monroe.
Sorry, Jeremy.
Heaven does come to me.
It feels like the upping from we're shooting a movie in space.
You know?
And he goes, hey, guys, guess what?
2028.
First movie ever shot in heaven.
And we're doing it.
It's not.
Everyone could have done it.
Everyone was just quitters.
Everyone who ever died was a quitter.
And then Tom Cruise figured it out.
Yeah.
And then he does a mea culpa because like, you know what?
It was a Christian god.
It's sorry.
Sorry.
That's on me.
I'm strong enough to admit when I was wrong.
I met God.
I shook his hand.
Great handshake.
Right in the eyes.
Hey, but I'm also partying with Elrond.
So I have it both ways.
Who is in heaven?
Yeah, Elrond's in heaven.
God forgave Elrond.
And if he can do that, he'll forgive all of you.
It is wild that he's now the one who comes out looking better
in that Matt Lauer interview.
Oh, yeah, right.
What are you saying?
How crazy is being?
Yeah.
You can never.
No, it can't be worse.
If it's choose your fighter, you choose Tom.
This also context.
OK, so I think everybody's very fond of the Muppets Family
Christmas special.
Mike and I talked about it with the Doughboys.
Done a couple of years before this.
I think the Muppets really shine in specials.
There's great films, of course, also.
But the specials are just it just
feels like a perfect format for them.
And just Muppets special content around this time.
The same year.
I don't think I knew this was all the same year.
This special, Muppets at Disney World.
Miss Piggy and other Muppets appear in the Disneyland 35th
anniversary special.
They're really good one that's Filmic with Ernest and C-3PO
and Tony Danza and all that.
The Muppet babies are in Cartoon All-Stars to the Rescue,
anti-drug special.
They're in the Earth Day special.
That insane thing that is what it's Ghostbusters and Doc
Brown and E.T. and Nathan Thurman.
But it's not Ghostbusters.
Yes, because it only knows Egon's brother.
That's right.
Isn't it Elon?
It might be Elon Spangler.
It's something like the head of the EPA or something like that.
There's some lawyers who bought houses off Ghostbusters.
If you guys have not talked about that, you should absolutely.
I don't know how we haven't.
Yeah, what a...
I mean, that's I don't know how we're so excited about our
multiverses.
We've already when the Earth Day special has already occurred.
Yeah, really?
Anyway, that and then well, and then horribly at the end of the year,
they ended up making the Muppets celebrate Jim Henson because he passed away.
Right. A good special as is the Joe Raposo one.
I mean, this was just a peak time.
All great stuff. All things everybody should watch.
That's a benefit of YouTube is that like, boy, these things were not
they were all like if you didn't have the tape of it off.
Yeah, really?
This might disappear forever.
I mean, that's how I saw this was I think my grandma had it on tape.
Wow. And she just taped it when it was on.
She just happened to keep the VHS.
And then I saw it when I was a kid and like stole it from her house
and like burned it to DVD so I could have it.
Like, it was just great.
Yeah. Wow.
So you really perceive you.
You have this one. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's pretty special. It's really good.
I mean, any we love any just the gangs
going to Disney World like TGIF did.
But what gang would you rather see go to Disney World?
Yeah, it's so much fun.
It's also it's fascinating how it like
the special ends in your you really feel like they're like welcome to the family.
We're here. We're all together.
Finally. And it's like, oh, guys, wait like six months.
Wait a minute. Very ominous.
Beyond the death of and the death causes everything to fall apart.
And then hearing yours, I don't think it was clear at the time.
But now Frank Oz is very much it was the deal that killed him.
So the grimace thing.
So seeing Mickey say that is like,
it's as it hits different now, as the kids say.
Pretty strange. Yeah, yeah, it is.
It like I was I haven't I've seen pieces.
I never watched all of it.
But yeah, it feels like it feels so there's so much effort into it, too,
versus just a normal like ad.
Everything we talk about as far as movie, it's all ads.
But you do go, well, there's a lot of effort here.
There's like loads of sets I've never seen before.
And then, yes, ends on an ominous note,
which I'm sure they didn't assume would be the case when they made it.
Yeah. But a visual we like casual polo Mickey.
Yes. Oh, my God.
Yes. Casual polo Mickey in his office.
When the the moment when you're building to the moment, we're at the door.
What's going to happen when the door opens?
And I watched it with Aaron had never seen it and the reveal that, oh, my God,
it's animated Mickey interacting with the puppet muppets.
And that's what I call it.
Everyone should call him that puppet.
It's more proper term.
But then also like, oh, my God, not just it's Mickey.
Oh, my God, it's casual 90s.
So let me ask you this, Scott.
We've had the debate about hyperspace hoopla when Mickey shows up at the end.
And it's shocking.
And you're very excited about this Mickey reveal, even though it's Disney World.
Would you be happier about the end of the hyperspace hoopla
if he was wearing his polo shirt and it was like 90s polo shirt Mickey?
I think so. I think that would do it for me more.
I mean, look, in this case, it's the mixing of the mediums.
This is an ongoing discussion we've had on the show.
We are you familiar with these with these Star Wars Park oddities?
Are you familiar with something they did called hyperspace hoopla?
Is that the Space Mountain overlay?
That's no, no, that's the Star Wars.
Yeah, Star Wars dance show during Star Wars weekends.
Like a few years ago. Yes, yes, yes.
I know exactly what it is. Yeah, OK, good.
Yeah. What the?
I think what's the name of the host?
There's two hosts. Sagan Ali.
So that's something. Yeah.
Same host for a few years.
And, you know, yeah, like like if you want to see Darth Maul twerk.
Yeah, this is where it would be.
And everybody do it in style. Sure.
Yeah, I knew you were troubled when you walked in stuff like that.
And then at the end of one year, which is the best year,
Mickey comes out and dances at the very end and he's in a Jedi outfit
and the audience loses their mind.
And I got I get it.
I was watching and I got excited, too.
And I think Jason and I agreed that it was good.
And Scott was like, it's not that weird. He's at Disney World. Sure.
This was my yeah, this and it was built up because you were very like,
and then wait until you see.
And then Mickey came out and I was like, so so what is it?
Like I didn't know that was. Yeah. Yeah.
If they were doing it at Circuit City, it would be there.
You go. Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
If it was a place where I don't expect to see Mickey Mouse, but I think to you
got to remember. Oh, my God.
That'd be the weirdest place of all.
Yeah. April Fool's.
Are they switching like Fallon and Kimmel?
I think it's early days of the kind of lightweight character costumes
like the Mickey. He's like, he blinks.
Oh, I don't know. Yeah, he blinks. Oh, no, it's good.
I don't like the blink in the mouth moving.
It's it's too much.
Oh, I'm pro blinking.
The costumes are just kind of like, like a green man suit now,
like their arms and legs and it's like a guy.
You can tell it's a guy. Yeah.
Which takes sometimes takes away the fun a little. Sure.
But I'm sure it makes it easier to break dance.
Probably. Yeah.
And it comes out, it's like, oh, I just want to feel this moment.
And Mickey like puts his hands up in the air and he kind of does like one of these
and his eyes keep blinking and the people are losing their minds.
Also, keep in mind that if you like the show, you are like worked up
into a lather at this point by the end of 20, 25 minutes.
You're seeing all the all the Star Wars characters dancing to pop music.
Yeah. So I guess you you would be very excited if you also just liked
the whole show, which I do.
Was that the last year?
I think I believe it was. Yeah.
So like for there's continuity through the shows, too. Yes.
So it all builds to like Mickey comes out, does a fun dance.
And it's like, anyway, you're not going to see this for a while.
I mean, here's all those songs you mentioned sound far too modern
for it not to be the last show. You know what I mean?
Like, well, that was that was the gimmick. Yeah.
It was always sort of modern.
But from a Star Wars brand perspective.
Oh, well, because they started where they're like, yeah, we're not.
No, I know. And that's that's when it was all over.
Sadly, that's when the fun was over.
It's like I it's like I threw you the ball and you ran with it
into the across the field, into the hoopla zone.
You're like, now it's a hoopla episode.
The characters were snig and hoopla.
Yeah, I was trying to remember.
It was like it because it had to be a tortured rhyme.
Yeah. Yeah. Hoopla. Snig. Snig.
Yeah. Snig. Yeah.
It's one of the ruttles, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
It does feel a piece of some of the things in the Muppets.
And I'm not talking about the Muppets dancing modern music.
I'm talking about like stuff that they would like, you know,
really nitpick on nowadays where it's like they're walking down
Hollywood Boulevard and then suddenly Miss Piki is that big Thunder Mountain.
Yeah. Geography is all over the place. Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's it's it's really insane.
The well, let me here.
Let's just let's let's go to the top because, well, there's big stars.
We got to bring into this beyond the Muppets, beyond Mickey.
And I want to go to the first one who we see,
which is that, of course, this being the magical world of Disney,
that you get an appearance from from the big dog, Michael Eisner.
Michael Eisner introduces the special.
He's in the Grand Floridian with Fozzie and another boy.
A common thing with Muppet Family Christmas.
Yeah. He's mom. I love Fozzie's mom.
I think he really used two appearances of her. Maybe.
I think so. Muppet Christmas Carol.
She's just this Fezzi wig.
OK, OK. OK.
She may have been like a runner on the Muppet show once.
Think now? I don't think so.
I don't know. I only know that from a wiki.
I don't. I have maybe a collection of it myself.
So I can vouch for it.
But the but huge roles in both of these specials.
And you know, I'm relaxed when she's around.
That's why I'm so I feel taken care of when Mrs.
Fozzie is around, yeah, because especially because of that holiday.
She makes me feel so welcome because she brought the Fraggles, Sesame Street
and the Muppets together.
And I assume she would welcome me in.
Oh, yeah, she'd love if you showed up.
Yeah, the more the more the more the merrier.
And the merrier. Watch out for the icy patch.
The her official name, Emily Bayer.
So I'm almost boy.
I mean, Emily bears around Michael Eisner's around.
Has everyone seen the outtakes?
Just yeah. OK, OK.
And I feel like probably a lot of the listeners have seen the outtakes too.
But, you know, I don't think anyone will complain about
so great standard Michael Eisner intro.
The I mean, the regular stuff is really fun that he gets like
what it's like a wardrobe fix, like in a bunch of Muppets Russian.
Yeah. Tear his suit apart.
Fozzie spills something on Fozzie.
Fozzie takes a ball, like hits him with butter on a butter night,
like rubs butter on his sleeve in there.
And really involved in there.
The way they shoot it, it makes like it makes it look like Fozzie did it on purpose.
Yeah. Which I don't think they meant to have that.
But I like the idea that Fozzie was just like, I'm going to fuck his suit up.
Yeah. Yeah. Funny.
He might have. Well, because he's like, you know, he's pranking him.
Yeah. Yeah. He's still pretty young.
It's looks real young in this.
No. Hello. Oh, not a hello.
Yes. Yeah. Having been through every hello to make the Michael Eisner
hello montage, although there's I found more.
I mean, one of these days I got to do around three.
That's how many there are.
But yeah, this one didn't work.
Not a hello.
But lots of fun stuff anyway.
Here is the the outtakes, which is a great montage in general,
because you see how much fun they're having, how much they stay in character
and keep it up and kind of needle each other.
It's the real show.
It's the edge of your show and never more clear than in this Michael Eisner sequence.
That bears in usually, but I appreciate this, Mr.
Eisner, such a beautiful room.
It's very nice. Yes.
I love it. Oh, welcome, everyone.
I'm in the lobby of the gland.
I'm sorry. Gland, gland, Floridian.
Well, we could change the name.
Could I request a room with a cave?
Oh, my God. I'm going to die right here.
Welcome, everyone.
I'm in the lobby of the gland, gland, gland, gland.
This is wonderful.
Thank you for letting us stay here. Third take.
Well, bears don't usually get to get one place like this.
Thanks a lot. Oh, great.
Welcome, everyone.
I'm in the lobby of the grand Floridian.
Oh,
OK, who else can we get?
Pazzy, you're just killing it.
Yeah, just killing it.
Do it ad libbing.
Different intro every time.
Did I? Maybe I said this once already that there's a little tonight show
where Kermit hosts a tonight show. You've seen this episode.
Can I tell you something? Sure. Go ahead.
If you go look and see who uploaded that on YouTube.
Is it you? It's Connor Ratliff.
Oh, wow.
Who I gave the video to and then he has like a million views.
And I'm like, I'm so mad.
Oh, my God.
The source of the stories.
That's crazy.
Yeah. It's of events to you.
Yeah. I watch this like less than a year ago.
It's great. But and this is going to sound like I'm shitting on Henson.
I'm not. Yeah.
Henson is fun. Yes.
But Oz is like next level improviser fast on his feet.
And like he obviously has more fun characters,
but Henson feels a little lost in places doing an hour or whatever.
It was still an hour. It was not 90 minutes.
Was it 90? Wow. That's that long ago.
Yeah. It's a 90 minutes. It's long.
And I get it that he has to be out there the whole time.
But you go, whoa, he's a next level improviser as far as like he's got
so many funny moments that are seemingly just off the cuff.
It's really a shame he doesn't he hasn't directed a movie in a long time.
I think death at a funeral maybe is the last one beyond like documentary stuff.
I also like going back and seeing stuff and like he's got a little role in like
American werewolf. Yeah. And he's funny. He's in Knives Out.
Yes. He's in Knives Out.
You go like, hey, you've been in more stuff.
I know. Like he's in so much stuff.
I was trying to remember. Yeah.
It's a lot of land of stuff. Oh, sure.
Sure. Sure. Yeah.
God, what a like magical person to be running around.
I know. Like great filmmaking of that time.
We can add this in too. Yeah.
To say nothing of Yoda. Maybe one of the best careers.
You know what I mean? Just like when you add it all up.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wow.
It's there's so many separate disparate things that like add up to.
Yes. So much of American culture.
Did he direct the score?
Yes. Marlon Brando appeared.
He could be why. Well, because he called Brando called him Miss Piggy to be disrespectful to him.
Brando refused to take any direction from him.
So they made De Niro wear an earpiece and Oz would tell him what to tell Brando through
the earpiece because Brando kept calling him Miss Piggy.
I'm sorry. And they gave us a making of show of the Godfather and not the score.
This is what I want to get actors playing old weird Brando and Frank Oz.
Who else is in the score?
Ed Norton. Ed Norton.
It was like, yeah, like three generations of the coolest dramatic actors.
Yeah. And then it was Frank Oz directing and Brando was being a weirdo.
Oh, being a Brando.
Well, yeah. In top form, they're so funny.
That's so great. Then, I mean, we'll meet star number two, but let me just go through the story
of it a little bit. The launching point being that Kermit has brought his Muppet friends to his
hometown, which is Paradise Swamp, which is full of various frogs that he knew growing up, kind of
a backwards weird place that is having a frog festival and bug fry. He thinks that this will
be a lot of fun for the gang, but they're sort of weirded out by all the froggy-ness, not the
place for that. You know, Miss Piggy is kind of sheltered and with her handyman. Who is that?
Beauregard.
Oh, Beauregard.
Yeah. He's the janitor.
He's around still.
Oh, that's okay. And then becomes in this, for these purposes.
Like her assistant.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Right-hand man. So kind of like crazy swamp frog sequence.
I like Robin too. I think I'm on record liking Robin.
Robin is a... I didn't even realize until a couple years ago that Robin was controversial
because I always liked Robin, but apparently that is not necessarily the most popular opinion.
He's kind of not to the same level, but like Bean Bunny, who I know you guys have talked about
before who's in Muppet 3D. Bean was sort of like the cute addition that they brought in.
And Robin was sort of like the proto Bean, a lot of people say, where he was also just
cute and sang cute songs and didn't have much going on beyond that.
But I was... There's some bigger Muppet fans than I that I've talked to and they go,
hate Robin. And I go, really?
Robin is Tiny Tim and he's so empathetic and charming.
I agree. I didn't realize this existed.
Now I'll say this and I want to get this on record. Muppet Christmas Carol.
My least favorite Muppet movie.
What?
Whoa.
That's Jason's favorite, right?
The bottom.
You're putting Muppet Treasure Island ahead of it?
Yeah.
It's not funny.
Muppets in space?
Muppet Christmas Carol, not funny.
It's the Christmas Carol. There are funny movies.
I'm not into Amy. That's not what I'm here for though.
I think Gonzo's... I think all that stuff, there's some of it through it.
There's a little too much sentimentality for me.
Like I like that.
But I want to laugh and I don't really laugh that much with Christmas Carol.
There's the song that's only in some of the versions that's this like heartbreaker of his mom.
Yeah.
Is that like too cloying for you or something?
Saddest song ever written. Yeah.
Fast forward through that scene on the VHS.
Well, everyone, by the way, anyone who says anything negative about anything Muppet related
is stepping in it. You're stepping in it.
That's fine.
I probably have somehow without realizing it.
I think there's any slightly negative...
Well, you know what I was about to say?
I have not actually watched Muppets in space, which we've therefore ranked ahead of.
Yes.
So and...
But also to be fair.
What do you have to say about having not seen it?
I have no previous bias against Muppets in space.
Any...
I'll say this.
Yeah.
I was seven when Muppets from space came out.
Okay. So that might be the prime age for it.
Lead it to certain ways.
Sure.
And you know, before people come for me, I have Muppet Bonafita.
I own a Beauregard bust.
So don't come for me, guys. Okay?
What is your opinion on Walter?
I don't dislike Walter.
I don't either.
I wish they figured out what to do with Walter.
Yeah.
And I think there's a very funny line in Muppets Most Wanted, which is the second
after the Seagull movie where he runs away and someone...
I think it's Pepe has a line where he says,
didn't we just spend the entire last movie making him a part of the group?
And then Robin comes in and says, at the expense of other beloved characters.
And I sort of feel that way about Walter where I'm like,
you got to find that second beat for him.
You're going to do all this.
Yeah.
And turn around.
I'm going to throw Muppet under the bus if we're doing that.
I'm curious, will I get any hate on this?
Because Sesame Street's been more present in my house with a young child.
And we really like...
Even newer Sesame Street characters we like a lot,
but there's one who's not really around anymore.
I do not care for Baby Bear.
Sure.
That might be harsh because that's a cute character.
But are there Baby Bear stands out there?
Am I wrong on Baby Bear?
What do I know about Baby Bear?
I think I know what he looks like.
Any kind of...
He puts a lot of W's in...
He has a cutesy way of speaking.
Yeah.
Just not my...
I don't know.
Doesn't do it for me.
I think that's the one thing about him that's positive is
if kids have a speech impediment.
It was a helpful thing to be like,
Oh, Baby Bear, he's like me.
No, Scott, you shouldn't.
Scott, big mistake, Scott.
Yeah.
Sounds like you're really...
I didn't say that.
And it's possible to dislike the timbre of the voice without the mispronunciation.
Sure, sure.
This is not for the register, you see.
The guy who played that does not work on the show anymore.
So that is why.
Well, and I think I've caught that he did other things like that
because I didn't really like this character, Murray.
Yeah, that's also him.
Yeah.
And that was that a...
You probably know this, that was a not a good exit.
That's a dramatic...
I believe it was a dramatic exit.
Yeah, I don't know all the details, but he was like head writer and director
and performed with it for a while.
I don't think it was as bad as some of the other exits, but I don't think it was...
Bad exit.
I mean, we're looking at with this 1990 special is teetering.
It's like right before, boy, is it nothing but drama.
It's never fully been course corrected.
And with all of these, the bad Steve Whitmire and Frank Oz doesn't feel good about anything.
Yeah.
This guy you're describing and...
Dave Goles is the one guy who's still there.
Still here.
Right, right, right.
Gonzo himself.
Who's Gonzo and who else in this is it?
Bunsen, Honeydew.
That might be...
Beauregard.
He's Beauregard.
That's him.
Who is your favorite Muppet?
Can you give us just some of your basic favorite stuff from Muppets?
I'm not really a main guy.
Like I like Gonzo, I like Fozzie.
Those are like my two main favorite guys.
But you're a deeper Muppet fan.
I'm a New Zealand guy.
Oh, interesting.
I'm a crazy hairy guy.
I'm a sweet chef guy.
I'm like a Sweetums guy, you know?
Okay, got it.
Dr. Teeth.
But like Gonzo is probably the top of the main group.
The weirdest of the...
Yeah.
Do you go hard for Sesame Street too or just Muppets in general?
I do like Sesame Street a lot.
I interned there for a year.
Oh, wow.
And I went there a couple of times when I was a kid, which was cool.
Because I wanted to work in that world for a while.
But yeah, Muppet was always more of my thing.
Sure.
But I stand the street.
Yeah, any good encounters?
Any like, oh, I got a good moment with so-and-so?
So I was there the last time as of today that Frank Oz performed on Sesame Street.
Whoa.
Not wild.
Yes.
It is wild.
He did a song with Grover.
They brought him in for like two days because he's very expensive now.
And they're not like flowing with cash over there.
It's been half an hour now with a lot of reuse.
For sure.
And they shoot like-
These sequences are in every episode.
Yeah, they shoot like two weeks a year or something like that.
Disney does not own them.
It's crazy.
Is that real?
Yeah.
It's not a lot.
But yeah, he did a Grover song and then they did like a Boardwalk Empire parody
and a Downton Abbey parody.
Wow.
And those were in him?
Yeah.
Whoa, he was in just the regular sketches?
Oh, geez.
I gotta look this up.
Geez.
I was there like right before a lot, like the guy who was playing Elmo, he left after,
like right after I was there.
The guy who played Big Bird like basically retired after I was there.
The guy who played The Count like died the year after I was there.
Like it was just like-
Oh, geez.
It was just like the end of an era.
Wow.
You know?
That's pretty wild.
Yeah.
It was, I lucked out.
Do they all have ponytails?
Not anymore.
I mean, they're all 80 now, so not anymore.
May have.
Yeah, yeah.
At the point they did.
George Carlin had a ponytail up until he was old, right?
That's true.
It's some old elderly ponytails.
Yeah.
Wow, that's wild.
Okay, so we're in the swamp.
We're hanging out with frogs.
The gang's not really feeling it.
And then a little bit of information quietly comes out, which is that just beyond a set
of trees in the swamp is Disney World.
And if they want to pop into Disney World quick, then they should probably get back
for the bug fry.
How great is this?
What a great tie together.
The Disney World is swamp and the Kermit is front.
So now, important pieces of canon.
Kermit the Frog grew up in Orlando, Florida.
Yeah.
When you're in the Muppet movie.
I guess that's Orlando.
The camera pulls out a little bit more in the Muppet movie when he's on the log.
You see the ball in the background or whatever.
You see the Florida Project.
Yeah, he's on the outskirts.
Well, and that's another thing that being next door.
Okay, because we've recently come across another bit of mythology, which is the
backstory of Mickey's Toon Town, which is that Toon Town was there first in the
fictional mythology.
In Anaheim.
And so then Walt is looking for a place to build his dream park and Mickey says,
there's a big bunch of land right next to this little town that we made.
Maybe you could build your theme park here.
So Disneyland exists because we're going next to Mickey and friends.
Maybe coincidentally, Disney World is built right next to where Kermit grew up.
So fictionally, the Disney company's habit is to move in and do a lot of building,
create a lot of hubbub around these gentle characters who are in their employ.
Ultimately, it's kind of an odd.
Yeah.
I mean, they give them a leg up, but also it can't be good for the swamp, for the pollution
levels, for the quality of life.
Oh yeah.
Oh my God.
Drives the rates up.
It's amazing they can afford it.
They must be off the grid.
They aren't plugged into the power lines or anything.
No, it's not dissimilar to In It's a Wonderful Life when George Bailey tells his old friend,
well, there's that empty factory on the outside of town.
Whole town was started out of work when that closed.
You're as a father-in-law, could get it for cheap.
Hard luck tales.
It just makes you wonder what the other...
Does the Tokyo Disney site exist because Duffy and friends had a little village?
I think that's absolutely right.
Yeah.
And if we like, all right, well, these bears, they're so nice, they'll shut up.
Even though they were coming to town and they made the work for us.
The Wuzzles were right outside of Disneyland Paris.
Oh yeah.
That's a game of the Wuzzles.
They moved down river.
They didn't want to be...
We don't want to be anywhere near any of this.
Yeah, very strange.
But I love this.
So Kermit's the Floridian, we know that now.
And the gang leaves, they all go to Disney World.
But nobody's got money.
This wasn't the plan to get in.
They have no way to get in.
The solution becomes to just break in.
Yeah.
They do break the law.
Animal buzz...
Like the animal is in the wrong here.
Yeah.
Sure.
I mean, you know, the stuffy security guard who we're about to get to, I'm not, you know,
you're not rooting for him.
Although maybe, I don't know.
Well.
But yeah, being who he is.
Jason is.
But animal, you know, yeah, there is a breaking and entering.
Can I ask a question?
And maybe I missed this now that I'm thinking about it.
Does Kermit says that he left his wallet back in the swamp or something?
Is Kermit lying to the security guard?
Or did he have a wallet?
He doesn't wear pants.
Well, right.
That's like an old get.
It's like when you pull out the pockets and a fly falls.
But I guess what I'm saying is...
I left my wallet at home.
I'm saying Kermit is usually such...
I mean, I know he sometimes gets into little things, but is Kermit being genuine?
Because it feels like Kermit would want to pay.
I think he's gotten riled up, you know, and he's so excited about going to Disney that
you're like, we're going in no matter what.
Yeah.
Maybe that's my guess.
Okay.
Because sometimes he gets a little like a raw, raw, raw, you know, sure.
Doing this.
Come on, guys, we're going to make it happen, you know.
But you don't understand what I'm saying.
I'm just wondering now that I'm thinking about the scene.
Yeah.
Well, I think he's a little dismayed because no one cared about the swamp.
Right.
But I was wondering, maybe Kermit does have 40 tickets or his money back in a wallet
somewhere and he meant to pay.
Yeah, I think so.
I can't give him his word.
I trust Kermit.
Do you think he gets the Florida state discount?
Even though he doesn't live there anymore?
His whole family does?
Yeah, I think he does.
Yeah.
Okay.
I would hope.
Yeah, yeah.
He would probably get more perks being...
Right.
He might...
They might technically be residents of the Reedy Creek improvement district.
I was going to say, I was wondering how Kermit's family is affected by what Governor DeSantis
is revoking the rights of the district.
Our taxes are going up how much?
Yeah.
There's a great joke, by the way, at the very, very top where they're walking through the
swamp and Bunsen Honeydew says that Beaker is using the Muppet Labs anti-poison ivy cream.
Makes you break out in spots and itch like the Dickens, but you don't get poison ivy.
Like that is such a good joke right at the top of the show.
That's sharp.
Geez.
I mean, it's all very funny.
It's great.
And then it's especially taken into next gear when you meet the security guard who is, of course,
Officer Quentin Fitzwaller as portrayed by Uncle Martin himself from our favorite film,
Clifford.
Charles Grodin is in this special.
Oh my God.
And something I just put together, this is actually his first interaction with the Clifford
because Clifford, the Muppet, shows up in the special.
Clifford.
So this is the first Charles Grodin Clifford collaboration.
The eventual band leader.
This is Clifford's first appearance.
He was on this show called the Jim Henson Hour, which was a year or two before this.
This is getting real in the weeds, guys, but I guess this is why we're here.
This is the only time, his whole thing was they're like, he's in the new band.
He's like the new band guy.
He's the music guy, the cool guy.
But this is the only time he plays with the Electric Mayhem is in the special.
That's what confused me was that grouping.
Yeah.
So he's sitting in with them.
I guess.
For a tour, right?
Yeah.
Interesting.
I mean, yeah, why not?
It's Michael McDonald being in Steely Dan for a little bit.
Yeah.
Before he kind of takes a behind the scenes on Muppets tonight.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh, he's the host.
Oh, he is.
No, no, no.
He's very...
Kermit goes behind the scenes.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, totally.
But oh my God, you get Grodin.
Grodin's in this with Muppets again.
And after great Muppet caper.
This is post-Muppet caper.
Yeah, that was like 81.
So his second...
What a sport to come back.
Liked the Muppet experience enough, I guess.
It's hard to imagine him liking anything, but as close as...
For sure.
I imagine they just flew his family down to Disney.
Sure.
You know what I mean?
It's probably one of those like, come on down, bring everybody, hang out for two weeks.
Well, he's also in the family by this point because I was on the IMDB.
And just looking at this, boy, any actor would be jealous of this stretch in an IMDB chronologically.
Midnight run, cranium command, Muppets in Walt Disney World.
Oh my God.
One of the great stints.
Legendary, yeah.
Geez, with probably Clifford being filmed in there at some point.
That's right.
It sat on the shelf for a while.
Yeah, might have been exactly in that zone.
Boy, and it's wonderful.
And there's fun.
This is, I think, a lot of the is a Muppet project good or not is who are those guests
who you know that they're going to have?
Are they committed in full tilt and fun?
Or are they phoning it in a little bit?
Or are they convinced this person is hot, so we'll put them in?
But Groden's exactly what you want, where he's a real actor.
He's going for it too.
He's very funny.
He had some line that made me laugh out loud and I don't remember what it was and I should have wrote it down.
He was like mugging to the camera and really going for it.
He's got a funny joke about he lost the 700 keys to Epcot, but he found 100 of them.
Oh yeah.
That's great.
So they break in, he's after them, and that's the dramatic thrust of this.
But otherwise you get to just run around Disney World with the Muppets.
Animal commits more crimes.
He steals ice cream and breaks an ice cream.
That's another thing where that would not fly now.
We cannot have our character breaking the Disney rules.
Oh yeah.
They push over a giant turnstile.
Even easier with those magic band things.
They're so skinny you could kick them right in.
A child could push those over.
It's not even a turnstile anymore.
It's not.
It's just a pole.
It's a stanchion.
Oh yeah.
It's a jump.
Another thing they wouldn't do is say the stuff wrong.
Much like what we talked about with TGIF where I'm looking at the quote,
and there's that ocean thing over there.
I think they mean the living seas, but I'm not super confident.
And a lot of pointing to, somewhere in there, Star Tours is over this way,
and they are not in the park that Star Tours is in.
They're near Big Thunder Mountain or something like that.
Like it's very far away.
They're in Magic Kingdom, and in Magic Kingdom that ride is not in that park.
However, love it.
Love it.
We're so slavish to mythologies at this point.
I love the casual slapdash nature of it.
Everybody relax.
Like we said, this breaking news of we're disrupting the galaxy's edge continuity,
and the new characters are going in.
I don't care.
I remotely break all of them.
I want Jefferson Starship playing in there.
Oh yeah.
And we have, and I don't want to get a derail,
but they mentioned Halyx in the Star Wars presentation.
That was something.
I mean, it occurred to me that that did come in a big chain of events from us.
I learned about Halyx from this executive who, and I told it to you guys,
and that documentary got made, and now Scott Trowbridge is talking about it
with Tony Baxter at a big Star Wars event.
I'm like, this is a butterfly effect.
Yeah.
And that's stemming from us, which is pretty fun to think about.
That doesn't feel, that feels like that has to go past some approvals to get on stage.
Made the slide.
It's not a Comic Con presentation.
It's an official Disney presentation.
Yeah.
So it is interesting that that's there with the head of Imagineering mentioning it.
Before they can get to it, because they're like,
we're going to step through it chronologically.
And before Star Tours, let's give a little nod to Halyx.
And it's, yeah, it's not Star Wars, so they didn't have to say it either.
No.
It's not like all this interesting part of Star Wars' history.
It's not.
I think it is now though.
I think he made it official.
But that's what I'm saying.
It's by Scott Trowbridge deigning it so.
I think it is.
It's very interesting.
So excited that this conversation is happening right now.
They're all there.
They're downloading their Patreon episodes.
They're like, oh my gosh, the best.
Yeah.
You're saying Scott is?
Hey, Scott, how are you?
They don't like to acknowledge us.
We've been waiting for the phones, Disney.
We've begged and pleaded for it to be involved.
Yeah.
No, it's radio silence.
If they call, here's a question.
Yeah.
They call you guys, right?
They say we're bringing back Halyx.
Uh huh.
Okay. Unfortunately, no one else wants to be in the band.
Will you guys do it?
What a question.
I'm saying you got to learn the instruments.
You got to learn this.
Yeah, full on.
No problem.
Okay.
I'll figure it out.
I just wanted it on the record.
Yeah.
Just, okay.
My keyboard skills are so rudimentary, but I will Tom Cruise style just like hyper dose
in three months.
I'll get there.
Give me the Marvel.
Me and Mike will do the Marvel HGH regimen.
I don't know that we have to do that, but I guess we will.
Yeah, we will.
Halyx is jacked.
Yeah.
Jason's going to do that rope route.
Jason's going to be the one swinging around on that rope.
Yeah.
Oh, because he likes heights.
Oh, I love it.
Yeah.
Yeah. It's happening.
We are Halyx 2.0.
So crazy stuff.
All right.
So we're watching, I mean, love when narrative goes away and you're just watching characters
go on rides.
And that's what you get with things like watching just Miss Piggy's going to go on Big Thunder
Mountain.
That's breezy and fun, but unlike when the full house gang goes on Big Thunder Mountain,
you're like, wait a minute.
There are logistics here.
How is this puppet going on this?
What's going on?
They are crouched down and this is not safe or they had to find a new way to make it safe.
This is logistically complex.
And do you know the behind the scenes thing about this?
No.
Frank Oz says not doing it.
Whoa.
Not doing it.
Not going on.
So Dave Goals, I guess, goes on and puppeteers Piggy for all those things.
Yeah.
I don't know how they do that.
Frank Oz doesn't want to do it because he's scared of roller coasters.
He says he gets motion sickness.
OK.
Yeah.
So it's maybe not even.
Which Ben being like, I mean, that's a horrible position.
Oh, yeah.
Super weird.
But every time I was flipping through the Muppet Wiki page for this today,
and every time they mention it, it's like in heavy quotes where they're like,
we're not really sure if he really did it or if he just didn't want to do this.
Oh, you're right.
Sure.
Yeah.
That's wild, though.
And that's maybe the most complex staging in this.
The other one probably that Gonzo and Camilla are on,
but their story is that they kind of run off and they don't care about the rides and stuff.
They're going to weird sewers.
Mm hmm.
Uh, where the laundry.
Laundry.
Yeah, the laundry.
So they are going up a conveyor belt with a bunch of loose laundry.
Great.
So they get so they're really on that thing and hidden by laundry, which is pretty fun.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
But that's a set.
Right?
Oh, yeah.
I think that's a set.
It's got to be.
Right.
Yeah.
I didn't even I hadn't even thought about it.
Yeah, totally.
That is a great get.
I mean, it starts with him sticking his head in a trash can and going like,
oh, look, it's one of Epcot's empty cup exhibit.
And yeah, they're just walking through dirty pipe rooms and the laundry.
Again, stuff Disney would never admit that there's like, oh, yeah, there's really gross.
Yeah.
It's rooms underneath all this.
It's so fun.
And it's perfect Gonzo and Camilla business.
Yeah.
Um, I want to say I like piggies eyes when she's on the roller coaster,
because they like change her eyes out, which is really funny to make them like
surprised or excited or scared.
Anything of that nature when she's full of rage running through Central Park and Muppets take me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And that's like a grown pit.
That's like a adult in a piggy.
Yeah.
Launching and strange.
So funny.
Very relatable moment with Rolf where he's like
crippled by the tyranny of too many choices.
Or he's like, there's so much here.
I don't know what to do.
We've been there were Ralph.
Another favorite moment.
Beaker gets a lot of fun stuff.
He gets a bucket stuck on his head for most of this.
They then put a wig on.
But the Swedish chef has a taco stand, which I was a big Swedish chef kid.
So then on top of that, on top of the funny, just him selling tacos,
Lutefisk tacos.
And then Buns and Honeydew walks up and says tacos in the strangest way.
He says, oh, one of your tacos, please.
Like, it's so odd.
I didn't I don't have this clip prepared, but just rather than just mentioning it,
I don't know where it's going to land exactly, but I just wanted to get a little blast of the song
that the electric mayhem does, which is rocking all over the world.
If you don't speak the same language as me, but when we rock together we will really be.
One, two, three, four.
One big family.
Rock and rollin' around the world.
So fun.
Love their logo.
I mean, it already I was almost wondering if this was a cover.
This is a similar song.
It's very ELO.
It's like a sound like of an ELO song.
Is that called rockin' all over the world?
But this song's technically no, wait, it's also sort of like ROCK in the USA a little bit.
I think the way the ELO is rocking all over this world, this is rock and rolling around the world.
There's a Springsteen song called Rockin' All Over the World.
But it's not that.
I think this is an original notion.
A lot of people want to.
Oh, and it's not.
Wait.
Then there's all over.
I think maybe think of John Fogerty rocking all over the world.
Oh, it's a Springsteen as a cover of Fogerty.
Fogerty, an ELO in Xanadu, one of my favorite films, does all over the world.
It would be so funny if they did a cover of a song from Xanadu in the special.
Oh, boy.
That's my vote.
That thing that goes around of replacing, like, give me a Xanadu, Muppet Xanadu.
I don't know the market for it.
No, it's this garage right here.
It does feel like a time where we would get like a direct to streaming series of like Xanadu.
Xanadu.
Yeah, oh, sure.
Why not?
Yes.
They made a TV show out of the man who fell.
Here's the Xanadu is back and here's the twist.
It's boring and too long.
Do you want eight hours of Xanadu?
And it looks much worse.
But then there's like one performance.
It's like, did you see Matthew Good in Xanadu?
Really great.
Xanadu Requiem.
Yeah, yeah.
Fine.
I want it.
I also really like when the weirds when almost subliminally the small world dolls
Muppetized small world dolls show up and briefly sing.
It's a small world.
Yeah, kind of demented manner.
It's like something bad happened to them.
I should say some of those shots in that song maybe don't stand the test of time.
There's Janice dressed up as a geisha.
Oh, yeah.
I just played that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think Zoot's got a full sombrero and like some odd juxtaposition of characters and yeah.
Drogues.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, World Showcase was a disaster waiting to happen for anything that filmed there.
Yeah, Disney coasted on the existence of World Showcase for 20 years.
Yeah.
Like, and everyone's welcome.
Sure.
World Showcase.
Well, our job is done.
Great.
Yes.
Set up diverse.
It is kind of crazy how everyone has like a pretty solid story in it, though.
You know what I mean?
Like everyone gets a lot to do.
For sure.
Yeah.
And doing a movie.
We haven't even talked about like Statler and Waldorf yet.
Oh boy.
They sing an old timey song to an old lady.
It's great.
To an old lady.
Human old lady.
It's yeah.
Delight.
It's really cute.
Rolf too has a really funny story.
Like he they get him into the dog.
They're like, hey, you're not supposed to be.
They like take him into the dog like hotel.
And then he does a number with a bunch of dog puppets, which I always like dog.
I don't know.
A lot of those dog puppets were cute.
The one was like snuggling Rolf during the song.
That was a cute number.
What does he say when they like catch me?
He's like, I have no owner.
I'm my own free dog or whatever.
Like that.
Yeah.
There's funny because that part is the start of Rolf's storyline is like subtle advertising
for the ability to put your dog in a place at Disney World.
Yeah.
Which I'm sure it was, but it is pretty it's pretty low key.
Like, does that still exist?
Well, you have no idea.
They have built a massive facility.
I only know about this because Beijing Mr. Morrow did a video about it,
but you can set your price point of how much comfort you want your dog.
Like $150 a night.
Your dog gets our own room with a flat screen TV.
He's walking around the park with a pocket bee and he wants to set him up somewhere safe.
It just drops him off.
Yeah.
Wow.
My jaw dropped when you said that.
That's crazy.
Yeah.
Wow.
I saw, I think there was a man, I think it was in Japan who got, who bought a life,
like a realistic Kali costume and he wants to live like a dog.
Okay.
So I wonder like if you could do that and then get for 150 bucks, that's not bad for
a hotel room at Disney.
Get a flat screen TV.
The hoaxes that go around the more insane parts of the inner.
Sure.
Is that like every elementary school is like this now?
Right. Sure.
Is that a price point to get your dog caught with a butterfly net?
There's gotta be, right?
Oh, good question.
Yeah.
It's gotta be.
The Disney dog catcher, which I assume is there too, because that's basically what.
Just look, I love my dog.
I just want to see what it would look like with a comical.
If he was on an episode of Top Cat.
I think a big change in how people like in 30 years, I think the way the comfort
that dogs can get on vacation, like, cause you can also just be staying at a Disney hotel and then
what's her twice a day.
You can go and say hi and hang out with your dog and take them on a walk on the little dog park.
And then they go back to their room and you go back to your room.
Wild.
So, yeah.
So Rolf is advertising this service, which I don't know.
They don't publicize as much anymore.
No.
So you have to like, know about it.
Yeah.
Well, some of the hotels are dog friendly.
You, I mean, a dog can stay in a room with you.
Sure.
Yeah.
A dog can rent a room by himself.
That's true.
As long as he has a credit card.
Yeah.
What else you got here?
Laundromat stuff.
We end up in, as you had to do, as all the TGIF shows did, we end up in the Indiana Jones.
Mm hmm.
It's done spectacular.
So it's exciting to see.
Muppets with guns next to swastikas.
It's very, very jarring only then.
Yeah.
Kermit is very sweet though.
Like he keeps shooting guys and they go like, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Oh, yeah.
I don't.
And very clear his discomfort with violence and confrontation.
But then Piggy comes up with, doesn't she have like the machine gun?
Yeah.
She's in the plane.
Piggy is out of her mind.
She's ready.
She's so much angrier.
Yeah.
She's the angriest of all the muppets.
There's, okay.
So there's also the Rainbow Connection performance with Raven Simone, with the young Raven Simone,
which is very sweet.
There's not much to say about it really, but it's sweet and cute.
Credited as little girl.
What was it?
She's credited as little girl.
Just little girl.
Little girl.
Wow.
That's it.
Mm hmm.
After a name like Quentin Fitzwaller, like you want a good name.
Give her a name.
Little girl.
Give the character a name.
Well, that's one of these Helen tests.
Yeah.
Disney go back and give Raven Simone a name in this.
A great performance moment where she starts singing the song and then Kermit goes,
I don't believe this.
That's so funny.
That's such a great gag.
I think the thing that people really, one of the things people really like about classic
muppet stuff is that it's self-aware, but in like a charming way or like a cute way.
And it's so low key.
It's so low key.
It's so subtle.
All the old muppet stuff, not that they're like completely playing everything over the
top now, but just there's such like letting things like really just throw it away.
And it's that it's muppets that you're saying like, yeah, that muppet really undersold that
line and it really worked.
Yeah.
It's insane.
It's nodding the camera before Deadpool did it.
Sure.
If you don't know the muppets, it was kind of Deadpool before Deadpool.
Yeah, pretty Deadpool.
Deadpool is our muppets.
Deadpool would host if they ever reboot the muppet show, right?
Yes.
You know, it feels like I'm not, and I'm not advocating for that.
Sounds like you are.
I want to be very clear.
I do not want that.
That's a bad idea.
Yeah, I know.
I would like that actually.
Yeah.
Um, you know, Hey, the kids in the hall have proven to me that you can just bring something
back without sort of like new idea.
Yeah.
Just do it again.
Maybe that's the best idea.
Just do it again and maybe have the kids do it again.
And maybe have the kids and bring back the muppet show and have the kids in the hall.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
But you know, you got Charles Gruden in this.
He's he's running around.
He's hamming it up.
He's in front of I think the best thing that he that he had to do things in front of theme park
audiences does not square with my idea of what Charles Gruden would want to do.
Yeah.
But he does it and does it great.
Just big broad, like reaching out and grabbing them.
And does he I believe he yells victory is mine.
In front of a crowd at the Indiana Jones show.
And you don't really get a lot of shots of like crowds in the background watching what's
happening, which makes me wonder how much they like blocked off, you know,
I wonder that in all these cases, what is the crowd?
Hard to know.
Because wouldn't you stop?
Like if you just saw a bunch of muppets filming something like in 1990, I feel like.
But then also there's probably plenty of people that were just like,
I must be doing that every day here.
Yeah.
It's Hollywood studios or where like.
Sure.
Maybe.
Like it's because sometimes you'll just go into Disney and it'll be like,
uh, warning, we're filming today.
Sure.
And you won't know what it is.
And then later you'll be like, oh, like Stevie Wonder played a medley in front of the castle.
Yeah.
And you'd be like, I missed it.
I was in the park though.
I was there when Gavin Newsom did the universal.
We're back with the minions.
COVID is over two years ago.
Whatever that was.
I was in the park.
That's our generation's mission accomplished.
Yes.
Yeah.
Kevin, our governor with the next to a minion and grew.
And I assume Lucille ball saying COVID is done.
Optimus prime.
Optimus prime was there.
Yeah.
Optimus prime.
So, uh.
When I was there in, uh, November, uh, we walked by the day we checked out.
Like there was someone, uh, there was a, they were filming stuff for the Christmas
specials and like from a distance we could see like, oh, wow, they're really,
I didn't know you could go that far down on like the grass next to the castle.
I hope they don't like tripping that little stream or whatever.
I think Jane was like, that's Darren Chris.
Well, whoever it is, I hope they're watching their feet.
Yeah, I hope so.
So I mean, if we missed anything along the way to the, to rounding up the Muppets
and taking them to, to Mickey's office.
Yeah.
Rizzo, Rizzo kind of manipulating Charles Groten to buy him treats.
Yes.
Is really fun.
Uh, the one handsome pig actor, Patrick, what's his name?
Link Hogthrob.
Thank you.
Wow.
What an, I didn't know the name that rules.
He has a very funny line to Groten that's like, do you know where I can buy some
masculine t-shirts featuring cute little mice?
Wow.
That's so funny.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Cause Rizzo's like, the thing about the Muppets is you got to look out for weird,
insane things.
And then he comes over and says that and he's like, just like that.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
Wait a minute.
That was a Muppet.
A delight.
I think he then, so he rounds them up and he's on the phone with Mickey.
He refers to them as the Kismet game.
And, and then Mickey runs, I'm sorry, Kermit runs interference because he's,
he's met Mickey somewhere.
Sure.
Did he say where he's met Mickey?
Well, he had to sign a lot of contracts.
Yeah.
They've been, they've been putting like work.
It's a lot of stress.
Oh, he does.
He says they're both in FASA.
Oh, what did that stand for?
Yeah.
Fictional, fictional or furry animal, furry animal society of America.
The screen actors.
Something.
Yeah.
Something like that.
I mean, all look, all the Muppets should be in FASA, you know, they got to work on.
Yeah.
It's not the first time I've heard of the Henson company having union issues.
So.
So we round, we round everybody up.
We go to Kermit's office.
It's a, a one of the finest cinematic moments ever.
I mean, it is just great seeing an animate, like animated characters with,
I think so many of my favorite Muppet scenes involve like them all meeting somebody at a desk.
Like Orson Welles.
It really is very similar to the Orson Welles scene.
Yeah.
A lot of buildup.
Sky.
And then, I mean, similar because I like the one I like in the new movie.
One of the best things in the new movie is when they all like pretend to be one guy and a big.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
So imagine if they switched the Orson and the Mickey scenes though.
So it's Mickey at the end of the Muppet movie and Orson at the end of, I don't know.
It does not make sense.
Yeah.
But.
Doesn't quite work time.
If you're no, no, no.
No.
Now imagine you switch Mickey out at the end of hyperspace hoopla for Orson Welles.
Oh, man.
Now I'm.
Now.
Now it's a surprise.
Oh, man.
Orson whipping and nae nae.
I just want to feel this moment.
Orson style.
Yes.
We know remote.
We know remote farm.
So yeah, they meet.
Mickey says, welcome to the family.
It's kind of a, it's a weird.
It's the Muppets are dancing with the devil.
Yeah.
A little bit back.
It's maybe this was a moment that shouldn't have happened.
Yeah.
Did and they all it's it really feels like, and now here we go.
We are all friends.
And instead it became very strange and spotty.
I think there's also a little bit of like Mickey Miss Piggy connection.
He kind of like gives her a look a little bit.
Hey.
Mm hmm.
It's straying on his.
Hey, he's a big star, you know, I would, I would be a little attracted to him.
You met Mickey.
Oh, if you're Piggy.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Oh, wait, you're saying it's the other way.
I don't remember who was into I have it as that Mickey was into.
I mean, maybe I just got.
That's what I mean.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
It's a reverse.
Was into.
Yeah.
I feel like Piggy's into Mickey.
I think I think it's a little about.
Mickey's happy with me.
I imagine.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
You never know who's hall passes.
Piggy and Kermit are on the outs and they've even made.
Well, I know that Mike's is Minnie.
It is.
Yeah, that's true.
So, you know, but but I'm saying Kermit and Piggy have had on and again off again.
Sure, sure, sure.
Versus Mickey and Minnie, who it always seems to be constant.
Pretty sad.
Yeah, there's never really been other than that.
Stick it up your stick it up your ass.
Fresh man.
What's that?
Wash your head.
Oh, go wash your.
Soak your head.
Fresh boy.
But what's the context of is that is that Mickey disguised as.
Fresh man.
Is not.
It is not.
Fresh man.
Freshman.
It's a fast times line.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm confusing.
Yeah, very similar.
What is the is the context of that that Mickey is disguised as Minnie and being hit on.
By Mortimer or.
Mortimer Mouse.
Yeah, I forget exactly.
It's in one of the old comics.
Wow.
I'm trying to remember.
But but that either way somebody says the phrase soak your head.
Fresh boy.
Yeah.
That was a whole confusing thing too because that was in a short that had the same name as a short
that played at the Main Street.
Where like in MJ like an exclusive thing but then there's this other thing from the 90s
that both had the same generic kind of name.
What's that name?
What's it called?
I forget what it's called.
Here's the here's the look by the way.
This kind of like closed eyebrow eyebrow.
So I think I'm I'm I'm calling this Mickey.
Is that a windbreaker?
I think it's a cardigan.
Oh, is it?
Okay.
Or maybe it's a members only.
He's he sports a members only a few times.
Patrick, yeah.
Thoughts on Denise.
Oh, oh, I mean this is now we're getting into conflict.
Oh, no, no, no, no, Denise.
I mean, for people who don't know, Denise is Kermit's new girlfriend.
When him and Piggy break up on the ABC show, I mean, they don't do anything with her.
You know what I mean?
Like she's not meant to be a full character.
A full character.
It's just like it's a joke.
It's a joke character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I haven't thought about Denise very much.
I'm I'm seeing the headline from MTV in defense of Denise, the world's most hated puppet.
I didn't know that.
I don't think that's true.
I don't know if I agree with that headline.
She can't be the most hated when Waldo exists, you know.
Oh, do people not like Waldo?
I don't think people like Waldo.
Oh, really?
I love Waldo.
I think Waldo is funny, but I don't think people like Waldo.
There wasn't a lot of Waldo.
So I guess if Waldo wasn't in Muppets 3D, I guess I could see why you would not like him.
But he's in he's in Jim Henson hour a little bit.
OK, right.
But that's it.
But I could see where you would.
But because he's so tied to my childhood.
Sure.
I do like him.
Yeah.
And I have a toy of him.
Do you?
No toys existed of him.
There's a Parkstar.
It's a Parkstar.
Yeah.
You're ruining my bank account.
Thank you.
Well, it's going to be expensive, I think, because a couple of years.
That one might not be so bad.
A few of the Parkstars are very expensive.
Wow.
There is a Waldo.
Yeah.
Waldo turns into Mickey.
That's true.
It's a trick.
That's right.
Palisades never made a Waldo.
And that's one of the greatest regrets of my life.
Yeah.
You can't blame it on yourself.
You really can't.
You can't.
So then, I don't know, welcome to the family.
And then we get one big last musical number.
And they, as you were saying, they put their hands in the handprint, in the cement.
Yes.
And there's a very funny gag where they go back to the swamp.
And then they go, oh, no, we left Miss Biggie in the cement.
And I don't know.
I still don't quite know how they do the Muppets standing.
When the Muppets are free standing, always like, that's a magic trick.
I don't understand.
It's similar to, because one of those Jim Henson hours shows you how Waldo works,
which is early motion control.
So you're looking at an unadorned Muppet.
It just looks like you put your hand into two shoes and it's picking up all of the,
I mean, it's how they operate the mouths on the Ninja Turtles or on dinosaurs.
So it's like, it's really early motion capture.
It's also same thing at the end of Muppet 3D when he's on the fire truck going through.
That's motion capture.
I guess Rizzo is on, like Charles Groten holds Rizzo in his hand at one point
and then puts him on his shoulder and he's kind of moving around.
Yeah.
I mean, it could be, like, usually now they will just, you know,
green screen the guy out from behind him.
Sometimes they do like mirrors where they'll have like forward facing mirrors.
So you just see the ground in front of you, like reflected back.
Okay.
That's kind of a shot that's far enough away where maybe that was the case.
But I don't know because she's moving a lot.
Yeah.
You know, this is probably a glorified, like RC car.
I'm sure that's what it is.
Yeah.
A remote.
Your phone has 400 more times the power than it ever had.
Yeah.
But they, I mean, they back way up.
They like truck all the way down Hollywood.
It's really funny.
And yeah, you get by the end just so small and sad down there.
It's really wonderful.
While they're saying there's a new family ties on tonight.
I think that's what
Well, Scott, you can say that.
Well, you go ahead if you have it.
I don't know.
Well, here maybe let me see if I just have the actual clip.
Yeah.
It's well, let's see.
There's different versions.
So who knows?
Might take a sec.
Look, I wish I had it.
I
Next that very aliens got a craving for a furry be like,
how is it with a kitten?
Then there's no place like home on the special season finale of two to seven tonight.
Only on NBC.
Two to seven.
Those were the two that I heard.
Oh, yeah.
So yeah, I mean, I like that.
So the story on Alf tonight is that Alf is chasing after a kitten.
Isn't that like one of the primary?
Every episode.
Yeah.
How do we hook them?
How do we make sure we watch this sweeps episode of Alf?
But it really sounds like that episode is Alf has a crush on a cat and maybe he doesn't
want to eat it.
Mm.
It says he's smitten with a cat.
Right.
We got to like, also guys that ended up being the series finale of two to seven of Marla
Gibson Jackie Harry's two to seven.
Wow.
I also own an elf puppet now.
Whoa.
Puppet?
Yeah.
A new elf puppet.
Wow.
I pre-ordered the action figure.
Oh, yeah.
Me too.
Okay, great.
Just make it sure.
Yeah.
It was almost the series finale of Alf.
If not, wait a minute.
I'm not seeing it though.
Just command F smitten.
Well, I'm just seeing it in my...
I'm seeing it as the...
Maybe it might've been a rerun actually.
I don't know.
I'll sort out this Alf specifics.
I'll just share.
Wait, it was a rerun because Alf finished on March 24th.
Oh.
1990.
Another tragedy in early 1990.
How did anyone go on?
That is also a different world.
Could you imagine a network nowadays like this show is ended.
So we're going to show a few months of reruns.
Mm.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That is weird.
Oh wait, I found it.
The episode is called Live and Let Die.
Wow.
bride stops a group of kittens for a meal.
This is funny.
That's good.
However, after one kitten grows fond of Alf, he begins to question his personal view.
Whoa.
Wow.
Next is actually...
We're writing it off as like, yeah, calm.
All right.
Big breaking news.
Alf wants to eat a cat.
No, no, no.
We wanted to eat a bunch of kittens.
And perdrevamping the entire...
Are you a vegetarian?
Question everything.
Very special Alf is what it sounds like.
Does he still like to put on sunglasses and play guitar?
Who is this Alf?
Man.
Oh, a line real quick that is another...
Again, I hate to keep bringing these up.
Things that don't happen anymore.
When Kermit is and Miss Piggy are doing the Indiana Jones stunt show
and she's just firing the giant gun in the plane,
Kermit yells, Miss Piggy, how are we going to explain this to Big Bird?
Whoa.
It's so fast.
It almost gets clipped.
But I'm pretty sure he says, how are we going to explain this to Big Bird?
Like, how are we going to explain this violence we're committing to Big Bird?
Who is the mind of a child.
What if he's just talking about the Nazis in general?
Well, that's true.
That's a big conversation.
I mean, how do you explain World War II to a six-year-old bird?
It's tough enough to explain death in general to Big Bird.
That was very moving.
So it shouldn't be...
All the Muppets should share this burden together.
Yeah.
The last Waldo Park Star that sold on March 23rd for $24.99 was $6 shipping.
That being said, I don't see one on eBay.
Wow.
Okay.
Hopefully if one pops up, it'll be around there.
I guess I'll set up an alert like everything else in my life.
That's what you got to do.
They won't let me set up any more alerts.
They say, you have 200, you can't do anymore.
We just discovered the sheer volume of alerts on Mike's phone.
Oh, yeah.
This is meant to be.
This is bringing the Muppets and Mickey together.
I got a lot of Twitter alerts for deals and Wario 64 and Wario 64, I assume.
Yeah.
So yeah, there's a lot going on.
Okay.
Wonderful special.
Good time to talk about it.
Also, Charles Groton, he gets demoted and has to clean up a bunch of gum under a bench at the end.
A lot of blasts.
Great performers, great performances.
So much fun.
You think Groton's still working there?
That fictional.
Quentin Fitzwaller.
Did he get hired back after the furloughs?
Good question.
That's a great question.
Yeah.
Or did he seem edgy?
I imagine they fire him for losing all those keys.
That's like.
I mean, that's probably, yeah.
And for ledges, I don't know if they ever charged the Muppets for admission for that.
They lost a lot of money.
Do you think that's why the deal didn't go through?
Oh, they made people mad.
Yeah, it's actually all there.
They planted the seeds.
Due to the bumbling of Quentin.
He ruined the whole thing.
Yeah.
He's responsible for everything bad that happened to any Muppet performer after this.
Oh no.
Well, it's just his character, not Groton, the character.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
But yeah, the fictional face of evil.
Blame it all on him.
But funny to see the Disney parks acknowledge the existence of gum.
One of Walt's original nemesis.
We haven't talked about that much on the show, but you cannot buy gum in Disney parks.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, because they don't want it everywhere.
And they're right.
It would be everywhere.
Yeah, be everywhere.
That's a good call.
So I think that you could buy, for many years, you could buy cigarettes, but not gum.
They're easier to pick up.
That's true.
So you can bring gum in the park, though.
You could.
Yeah, you can bring it.
I've chewed gum on rides.
Wow, brag.
Okay.
That's a little reckless for me, Michael.
What is your mother going to say about that?
She wouldn't like it because she wouldn't want me to choke.
Yeah, she's right.
She hears that she's going to be upset.
Geez, well, what a blast.
So fun to talk about it.
Hey, I think Patrick Hunter, You Survive podcast, the ride.
Wow, we did it.
So much for giving us a lovely afternoon to spend an afternoon talking about the Muppets.
Hey, let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Oh, man.
Okay.
Yeah, George Lucas Talk Show.
You can watch any episode on YouTube.
I recommend just finding a guest that you like and then just, I mean, listen,
I see three guests right in front of me right now.
That's a good one.
That's a weird one.
That's a weird one to start with, though.
But there's a lot of good people and you can find one that you like.
You did Muppets tonight.
Yeah, you did.
We did.
Yeah, we watched all of Muppets tonight with a bunch of the performers,
the writers and the producers and everybody.
That was a fun one.
Ratscraps is an improv show in New York.
It was Ask Hat at UCB and then that changed when the theater closed.
We're doing it every Sunday.
You can stream it online or you can come watch it in person.
You can follow me on Twitter.
It's at Patrick Kottner.
And right now, trying to get more followers than the canceled NBC show about a boy.
So what are the hurdles you've already made it?
We've already gone past Animal Practice,
1600 Pen, The Blacklist Redemption, Marlin, and now we're at About a Boy.
I think that's all.
Marlin Wayans?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow. The accounts are started for all of these.
Isn't that crazy?
Are there an Alpha count?
Well, there's a new Alpha count.
There's a new one.
He's been doing a lot recently.
Alpha real.
Wait a minute.
That's not out of range.
That's 9,000.
He's actually not that close to us.
I think we're edging ahead.
But 9,715.
Yeah.
What are you at?
I'm like 86 maybe?
8600.
Oh, so it's completely in the...
Oh yeah.
That's what we could beat.
That's not bad.
Yeah. 8632.
Wow.
It feels like the prime and alpha for a comeback.
Well, he was just sold.
He was sold to the shout factory.
Yeah.
And then there's rumors he's going to be,
spoiler alert, in the Guardians of the Galaxy 3.
Really?
There's a big push.
I don't know if it's probably a cameo, if it is indeed the case.
But what happens a lot of the time, and I was just made aware of this,
there's a licensing expo that happens in Las Vegas, which all of a sudden you see,
oh, Golden Girls has every piece of merchandise.
All of a sudden there's sweatshirts and everything.
You go to this licensing thing and people make pitches based on what they own
to get characters and stuff back out there.
So all of a sudden when you go, yeah, why is there all this elf stuff?
It's because there was a guy who owns Elf or is a representative
pushing that on a lot of companies to make elf stuff.
So elf right now, NECA is making the elf toy.
This company Kid Robot makes those puppets of elf,
which is owned by the...
They're both owned by the same guy who also owns Graceland
and also owns Loot Crate.
Wow.
And owns a bunch of stuff, random stuff.
So yeah, sometimes there's a push.
So I believe you're right.
I think there's a push now for elf to get back out there again.
Now here's what I'll say.
I've tried to get elf and his friend, Paul Fusco on the Lucas show.
Yes.
And I'm going to say, let's start the campaign right now, guys.
Oh, sure.
So if you're listening, tweet at the elf official account,
say to have him come on towards Lucas Talk Show.
Because I don't follow elf because then they'll get ahead of your 90s.
Do not follow him.
Follow me.
He was on...
Okay, so this is real in the woods.
There was a Target event in conjunction with NECA and Kid Robot
a couple months ago called the Hall-a-thon,
which is a confusing thing where they just release a bunch of new stuff
they want you to buy and it's on a website.
But they were having Mark Summers do videos to host the Hall-a-thon
and he talked to his good friend, Paul Fusco.
So Fusco is down to talk to Mark Summers via video.
Okay.
He's out there.
He's he and he was on the show Duncanville.
Alf was on Duncanville and he does a little funny bit there.
All right.
So Fusco is around, seemingly game.
But yeah, maybe he's completely sold Alf off now.
I don't know.
Alf is in the Donald Trump, Funny or Die mood.
Oh, yeah.
Donald Trump.
We all remember it.
He was on the Goldbergs too.
He's been on a couple of things.
Yeah.
So yeah.
And you want him as Alf.
Get into this licensing.
Here's what I'll say.
I want him as Alf.
Oh, yeah.
I want him as Paul Fusco.
I want whatever.
I have the puppet so I can do Alf if you want.
I'm working on the voice.
Not there yet, but it's close.
There's days when it sounds like some days he goes, oh, yeah, you got it.
And then I lose it.
You just got to work on Willie.
That's your way in.
Oh, for sure.
That's it.
That helps you get into it.
Yeah.
It takes a lot of energy too, even though he's a laid back guy.
Sure.
Have you ever seen his talk show?
Yeah.
Okay, great.
There's a clip online.
I found this Alf Instagram.
There's an Alf Instagram of all the clips.
I think it's Bring Back Alf, I believe.
And it's just constant Alf stuff.
Ads, commercials, stuff.
I think there was a Scarface parody that somebody posted yesterday.
Great.
Maybe I'm wrong.
But then there was a clip from his talk show with Ed McMahon.
Yeah.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
There's a young woman on the show and she's got like a tattoo of like Alf or something.
And like Ed is going in to touch her and Alf's like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ed, you can't do this, Ed.
It's like from 2006.
Wild show.
So yes, Alf's talk show.
Then can we put you on the spot?
Can you say thanks for subscribing to the Second Gate?
All right.
I'm doing this too early, but I'll do it.
I want to say, okay, it is Scarface.
It's Alfaccino and it's Furface.
And that's the...
Alfaccino is not Duncacino played by Alfaccino.
No, yeah.
Alfaccino is Furface.
Director of photography, Kit E. Litter.
So what am I saying as Alf?
Thanks for subscribing to the Second Gate.
It's close.
It's not bad.
Just throw Willie in there and then see what happens.
Willie, I'm Alf.
Thanks for subscribing to the Second Gate.
I think you're right.
That's it.
That's a key word.
I got it closer than that second time.
Yeah.
Willie is a keystone and you know it's good impression when you say, I'm blank.
Also, he's reminding Willie who he is.
Okay.
Well, yeah, Mike keep working on it.
Alf will be back in some form.
Whether it could be Mike, could be not.
And hey, this is a great episode talking about a 1990
piece of Disney video content.
There may be another episode about a 1990 piece of Disney video content.
But where, you ask, where will our episode about such a thing be?
Well, stay tuned because big announcements coming.
We'll leave that as a mysterious tease.
It's a tease, Willie.
It's a tease.