Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains a famous nephew,
stomach acid strength, a big slug,
and hard eye contact with a barely emoting gorilla.
All that plus we tackle Skull Island, reign of Kong,
on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three people with skulls,
which are wasted, storing theme park facts.
I'm one of the skull owners.
Scott gets up with skulls is the name.
I don't know, that resonates, right?
We know it's about skulls.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
I mean, I have a lot of facts about islands of adventure.
So it all works out.
In your skull.
In my skull, yeah.
Keep your skull safe so we can get them all out.
Mike Carlson, how's your skull?
My skull is okay.
I took a nap.
I've been complaining about it ever since I got here
10 minutes ago.
So I have a dreamy skull still.
I'm still, my skull is still, I guess not my skull,
but the contents of my skull are still recovering
from the nap.
Well, I bet your skull contents are also recovering
from your activities last night,
which I wanted to wait and bring up on the show,
because I woke up to them dreamily this morning.
And I just want to say to your text, OMG.
And then before that, the screenshot of what it was,
which was that Sammy Hagar had been on Bill Maher's podcast
and web show Club Random.
That's right.
I figured I'd just wait and do it in person.
I hope it was a great episode.
It was to both of us.
I want to give Jason a chance to say anything
he wanted to.
Yeah, I might've already been like half asleep.
It might've been very early and I got up
for a couple more hours and I went back to sleep.
Well, but you're making it about you.
What do you think about Mike and the great video
he got to watch?
You know, I haven't swung by yet.
I haven't swung by the old CR, the old club, you know?
But I'm happy, happy for you.
Thank you, yes.
It was a big, I've been a big proponent of Club Random,
I guess.
Bill Maher and his bad opinions and his bad show
where he drinks and smokes weed and then people come on
and he annoys them.
It's the dimmest show, the grungiest show.
They just need to like take that saturation
and the brightness and dial it up.
It looks like, oh, so this is footage from 1968
and it needs to be restored.
Can we take it to a lab?
No, no, no, this was filmed several days ago.
But the things they're saying, the opinions,
surely this is from 1968.
Yeah. No, no, no, no.
So yeah, so Sammy Hagar appeared on the show
and I have not finished, I've watched 45 minutes of it
at this point.
Out of?
It's like an hour and something.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I was worried.
Yeah, he doesn't go like crazy.
He's in his six hour.
I'm glad you brought this up.
Mm-hmm.
Because I-
As is the audience, yes.
The audience is thrilled.
They saw the title of this, new listeners thrilled
to talk about this.
Yeah, it's show at theme parks, we'll get to it.
And all of a sudden they're in the fucking mud right now.
Like, what am I in the mud?
Why am I talking about Bill Maher?
Oh shit, what is this shit?
Do they ever start?
They skip 40 minutes in, still a tangent.
Hour 20, still a tangent.
Why does most of this guy's interests,
why is it stuff that he likes to punish himself with?
What is that about?
What's contained in his skull that makes him
wanna punish himself with stuff like this?
You're also sitting, drinking a bottle of like,
is that regular Sprite or dumb?
Regular Sprite.
You're drinking full fat Sprite,
so you're gonna have a sugar rush.
Full fat?
Full fat Sprite.
As opposed to diet Sprite, I mean.
What does anyone call it?
I don't know, what else?
Regular Sprite.
Yeah, I would say Sprite.
It's sugar, so you're gonna crash.
You're gonna get that higher.
I love full fat, there's zero total fat, no fat.
Well, I don't think of it as fat.
It's not.
How much fat is in Sprite?
But how many grams of sugar is that?
Oh, there's a decent amount of sugar, of course.
Okay, well, follow-up question.
What was your dinner and what are you gonna eat
when you get home?
Oh, I kind of skipped on dinner,
so I was eating a Nature Valley granola bar
on the drive over.
All right, all right.
I'm debating how to destroy my brain after the show
if I get a Big Mac on the way home or.
That's full fat.
Or that is full fat.
There's only one option there and it's full fat.
But I haven't eaten a lot today.
Or do I go to the 10 10 showing of Crimes of the Future
at the Burbank AMC's.
Sneak a Big Mac in there.
Oh, let's do both.
Oh, sneak a Big Mac into a Cronut Burt movie.
There are only four tickets sold so far, so.
So you'll be distant.
You don't need to work on it during the record.
You don't need to get the jump.
No, yeah, yeah.
People are listening to this show
and thinking this show should be called Club Random
with the topic switching.
They have talked about any and everything but.
So real quick, I was very excited about this
because I have often wondered if Sammy Hagar
held any sort of animus tour to Jimmy Buffett
or any of the other people who have sort of jumped on
the celebrity liquor bandwagon in the last few years
because Sammy's been doing this longer than everyone.
And he does.
Does it predate Margaritaville also?
Yes.
And Cabo Wabo was his brand, which he sold,
and now he has a new, like a hard seltzer drink
or something, I think.
He has a new drink,
but he already made his money from Cabo Wabo.
Full fat, full taste.
Full fat, full fat liquid.
That's so good.
So he does, he throws a little shade at George Clooney
and Jimmy Buffett at the start of this.
At Clooney?
Yeah, because he kind of.
Who is he, me?
Yeah, so he's obviously, he's a little resentful
that Clooney sort of came in and did the whole Casamigos
because he feels like he's the number one guy.
He didn't say that,
but that's sort of the tone of the conversation.
Wow, wow.
So I was like, okay, Sammy's getting real at Club Random
because usually he's just doing
some sort of a rock and roll interview on Access TV.
That's usually how I'm watching him
because I very often am watching him interview
one of his musician pals on Access TV.
He's doing the interview?
He's got an interview show.
Yeah.
He gets to rock and talk, talk rock with a lot of the guys.
He gets to rock and talk rock.
Yeah, he gets to do both things, talk rock and rock,
which is a good combination,
which two things I like to do as well.
So you get a little of that.
You get some, there's some bawdy talk up top with Bill
because Bill always wants to talk about ladies.
Well, that's what here, content warning, skip ahead,
because I put it on for a second
because I was curious what you were omg-ing about.
And the first thing it landed on was,
hey, settle a bet.
Do you get a lot of pussy?
Ugh.
Yeah.
That's what Bill said.
Don't say babe, but does the uh change?
If you remember that's coming from a 70 year old man.
To another 70 year old man?
To another 70 year old man.
And that they are both sweaty in the shot.
As usual on Club Random, the guests,
like Bill makes the guests seem like the easiest person
to hang out with in the world.
You're like that other guest seems nice compared to Bill.
Cause Bill is like, Sam's like, oh man,
you know he says it a little bit,
but then later, Sammy's getting uncomfortable
with the amount of times Bill has said the word pussy.
Oh boy.
So Sammy's like, oh no man, people are gonna think
we're like being like degrading.
He goes, no that's not it.
It's beautiful, everything's beautiful, man.
It's all good, everything's good.
You know, sex is a beautiful thing.
He's explaining to Bill.
He's gotten worse somehow.
Yeah, I know, yeah.
Being a beautiful thing.
He's trying to get away from Bill's body,
is what I'm saying.
I'm saying Sammy is trying to defuse.
As by the way, as we need to do.
I agree as well.
But when you open the door to Club Random.
We have to, let's cut off the people
who have already typed into their comment boxes,
oh so 20 minutes about Club Random.
Let's see if we can get them to backspace it.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
It's my fault, I brought it up.
You did bring it up, which.
Look, any time on this show,
we can open up the door to Club Random.
And then the topics will get random.
Let's just say that.
Wouldn't it be funny if Bill Maher sued us
if we stole Club Random for some sort of aspect
of our show?
I think it would.
Did he lock those words down?
I don't know, let's find out.
Anyway.
Scott, I did, I texted Mike something last night.
I texted him a link on I think the Walmart website
to a vintage, well a reproduction of a vintage
Toys R Us Ghostbusters, real Ghostbusters toy.
Fearsome flush the haunted toilet.
Okay.
I sent him this link and he replied, already got it.
So.
$12, retro, they're redoing all the old Kenner
real Ghostbusters toys.
And I have a few, I have the Venkman
because he was always my favorite obviously.
Like that was a stretch.
Every kid liked Venkman.
But then they have the toilet monster
and I had to get it, so.
They settle a bet.
Can fearsome flush hold a lot of shit?
Oh man, don't call it shit, man.
That's not a nice, let's just call it excrement.
Let's say what it is, you know?
Answer the question.
We're in.
You're making it sound bad.
It's just the thing our bodies do.
That's a natural thing.
Smoke on this loud.
Come on.
Hit this loud.
Okay, let's veer from this to what the audience is,
what they actually wanna hear, what they are begging for
and that is the beginning of Discussing the Ride,
Skull Island, Reign of Kong.
And what I say the people are waiting for
and waiting for us to do is a classic podcast, The Ride.
This is not that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I got it.
Yeah, you know exactly where we're heading.
Yes, there is breaking down to do.
Would you like to say one of the things
that this is not?
Well, maybe first of all, this is a ride in Islands
of Adventure in Universal Orlando,
which means it is not, there are Kong things
that are similarly titled such as?
It is not the 2017 movie Kong Skull Island.
Skull Island, Reign of Kong is not Kong Skull Island.
No, because this ride is set in the 1930s.
It is a prequel even to the Peter Jackson film, King Kong.
It happens before the events of that movie,
much less that movie Kong Skull Island,
which confusingly was coming out after The Ride was opened.
And that movie is set in the 70s, I think.
And like.
Yeah, Dora Nam, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because it's the first,
because it came out in 2017, remember?
Yeah, yeah.
And the first shot of it is this big protest in Washington
and then John Goodman says,
things will never get crazier in this country.
Yes, he does say that.
The audience stood and applauded for so long,
they missed the next scene and a half.
Interesting that you mentioned that.
Apparently the rights for Kong,
the legendary, I believe it was production company,
the rights jumped from Universal to Warner Brothers.
And there's a 2016 slash film article that said,
rumor has it that if this project
had gotten approved 30 days earlier,
it would have been a Jurassic Park ride instead.
Whoa.
Or a Jurassic World ride, excuse me.
Whoa, because it is in the Jurassic Park area.
Yeah.
Technically a violence of adventure.
Wait a minute, so, oh, that's wild.
Because you have to remember 2016,
that summer Jurassic World is coming out.
Mm-hmm.
Was it before, was it 2015, I wanna say?
Was it?
I could be wrong.
But.
Yeah, 2015.
But it was like, you know, it was still fresh, I think.
And there is still no Jurassic World presence in Florida.
Right.
That is sure to change now that it's Jurassic World.
Mania out there, it's Locust,
it's genetically modified Locust mania out there.
It was 2015, so they would have known it was a massive hit.
So it would have been a reliable choice
for a property for a ride.
Wait, Velocicoaster is Jurassic World?
Oh, that's, oh, wait a minute.
Yeah.
All right.
I haven't even been there.
I was like, oh, maybe I'm wrong.
Yeah, you're right.
And is there like Pratt material?
I think so.
I think Pratt has a video.
I'm trying to go clean, cold as far as the ride.
Clean and cold.
You just cut off at the pass people yelling about that.
Yeah.
I guess I was just not thinking,
cause the other one here is called Jurassic World the ride.
Right.
Which that is not, so it tricked me.
That's true, right.
So the presence is growing.
Blue is there.
We can see all our friends.
Can we see Claire Dearing?
I think she did something.
I think Claire, is Claire on the Velocicoaster?
I'm not 100% sure.
We're trying to go in clean.
Clean and cold.
Yeah. Clean and cold to the ride.
So we don't know if Claire is there.
Make sure it's both clean and cold.
Are there other things that this ride is not?
Well, I wanted to be clear that it is not King Kong 360 3D,
Right.
Which is the proto version of it
that is part of the Universal Tram Tour.
Yes.
It also obviously is not Kongfrontation,
which was the, which we did an episode about.
That one we've covered. I remember that.
Of the Kongs.
That's the one that we've done.
It's a real sticky mess here, these Kongs.
Yeah.
And if, cause there's so many sub Kong attractions to do.
Kongfrontation was the Universal Florida,
the original ride with big robotic Kongs.
Yep.
And then King Kong encounter is apparently the official name
of what it was on the tram before it burnt to the ground.
Yeah.
2007.
Yeah. Yeah.
So probably the most important of the,
this is not that is King Kong 360 3D because,
so if you haven't been on the Universal Tram Tour,
robot Kong burnt down.
They did this new thing in 2010 that is screen-based.
You drive into a building and there are two big screens
on either side of you, which they do not cover the transit into.
No.
You drive in.
Yeah. They don't cover above or below.
So it's more like, it's not even Kong 180.
It's Kong pillar boxed.
Like.
Yeah. There's no, yes.
There's no amount of degrees that have been,
it's, yeah, it is a little less than, well, no, it's,
it's 360 minus a big center sliver.
Yeah.
Right.
Plus every bar and person blocking your view.
Was there already a King Kong 3D?
Am I imagining that?
I think maybe I'm thinking of Jaws 3D.
I don't think that was a movie.
A film.
A movie.
King Kong 3D.
I don't believe.
But anyways, the,
when I heard, when this was getting announced,
I thought, oh, is this some kind of,
let's shove that in version.
As Fast and Furious ended up being,
that was a clearly designed for the Universal Tram Tour in LA.
Let's try to piece that out into its own ride in Florida.
So I thought, is this going to be one of those?
Is it kind of, let's just shove it in
and make this a custom ride vehicle and that's good.
And for the most part, I would say no,
because I would not be excited about that at all.
I don't really like that thing in the Tram Tour.
This thing, I don't know how y'all feel.
I really like this thing.
Well, I'll say this.
I like that part of the Tram Tour.
I do like, I don't, it's not amazing,
but I do like it versus obviously the Fast and Furious part.
Yeah, I like it.
I think the Islands of Adventure attraction,
I think is like a pretty solid attraction,
going back and re-watching videos and stuff.
I was like, oh, I do like this.
And they did like put a lot of attention in
and added some new stuff, like original characters
and like little nods.
I think they tried to make, they nodded to like
the essential King Kong elements,
like the island, the big wall,
like other freakish creatures on the island.
Early 20th century, mid 20th century explorers.
Yeah.
You get a more, you get a fully fleshed out experience.
But here, now I'm wondering from having to toss this out here,
am I more enthusiastic about Skull Island here
than the both of y'all?
I feel like maybe I'm a little above you
and Mike, I don't know.
Here's what I'm gonna say.
And I'm not, I swear to you, I'm not doing this to troll.
I'm not doing this to start another,
we're not gonna opening up a club random door,
but I swear to you, I'm gonna say this and it's true.
When we went to Islands of Adventure
and did this for the first time,
we got on it and we enjoyed it.
And then I heard people talking about it
and I remember going, well, what are they talking about?
What else?
I missed these elements
and the elements they were talking about were in the queue.
They were in the line.
Up, up.
And we totally missed them
because there's some cool shit in that line.
And I really feel that eases you into,
like the fast pass version of getting onto the ride
really robbed us of sort of getting in the mood for the ride.
And I do think, and again, this is not trolling,
I'm not, I'm not, this is a thought I'm having in real time
with Belmar.
No, no, the curse.
The curse of Mar.
Oh, the curse of Mar.
Think carefully about what you're gonna say next.
Don't say anything politically incorrect.
Oh no, oh, Sammy kept saying, calling his show now
politically incorrect and Bill was getting,
driving him nuts.
He hated it and it was so funny.
So yeah, so I saw it and I go,
oh yeah, the queue is really cool.
And I do feel like in the same way that Indiana Jones
really sets the mood for it.
So I think when watching the videos, I go,
oh, I think I would have liked this a little more
if I had done the queue.
All right, look, yeah, we're at the,
it occurred to me that this might,
we might head into this area because, you know,
look, I'll just, I'll dive right in.
This is as close as I could think of to an unskippable queue.
That's me saying, I think it's a very good queue
and it might be even an attraction where
the queue is half of it.
There's a lot, because you got animatronics there,
you got great sets, you got atmosphere.
You have a, I think this is a line first,
a Scarecter jumps out in the,
which I don't remember happening when I was there.
They might have been on break.
It might only be like busier times of the year
because I don't think I have seen that either.
There is, I mean, there's a lot to like about it.
I think overall, this is like a rock solid,
like attraction for Universal.
But queue wise.
Queue wise, terrific.
You did the full queue.
I, well, I think I did express too when I did it,
but it was looping it through most of the queue.
I don't know that I saw the worm animatronic.
I saw the shaman animatronic.
I don't remember that either, yeah.
I might have single writered it, I don't recall,
but I saw a lot of stuff.
Yeah, my memory of it, unless we really were out of it,
my memory is we kind of went in a real quick way,
kind of right on the ride portion of it.
But let me ask you this.
How much do you actually regret this having happened?
How many, over on my list of regrets of my life?
No, this is not in the top 100.
And that is what I'm saying, that's the argument.
That's not the argument.
It is, it is the argument.
The regret of your life.
The idea that you would like think back and go,
God, but I, that wasn't, like you're only,
you might only be there once.
You'll be there again, but.
You were just saying there's certain cues
if people had the time to spend
that you would want them to go through.
That's really what we were talking about, I think.
That's my memory of it.
But now.
We're gonna have to go back to the tape.
Having brought this up.
You're down in Florida.
Maybe you are with other people.
You get front of the line passes.
Let's do express, let's skip some stuff.
Your friends say, oh, let's use express pass
on Skull Island, Reign of Kong.
Do you now say, I'm sorry, friends.
What we need to do is experience the cue in full
because I've heard it's very good.
And even Scott.
Okay.
The villain of this argument.
Okay, okay.
I would probably be more benevolent and say,
you guys do the express.
I'll catch up with you in a little while.
I'm gonna do the full cue.
I know it sounds silly, but there's a lot of stuff.
Like for example, 150,000 square feet of rock work.
Well, that's a lot of rock work.
By the time you said that,
they would be right there with you.
Just running.
I said this in the time,
you gotta know your audience
when you're with people at the parks.
Yes.
You gotta know your audience.
So I'm a, look, I'm a crowd pleaser.
I am somebody who wants to cater to the group.
So obviously, look, if I'm with some of my rowdy guys
from my hometown and they just want those thrills,
like hit you in the face thrills,
then yeah, okay, we can skip the cues.
And I know they're not gonna.
You're roughnecks.
Yeah.
All my rowdy friends and I are going
to the theme park tonight.
They're like giving you a wedgie as you're rattling off.
12 guests per row, 72 per vehicle.
You're dying to say these facts.
You were like, we're over, we're having a little thing.
And you're like, how quickly can I get the facts, Megan?
We're having a debate and you're trying to.
But, it's 72.
So yeah, so I think it depends.
I think it depends.
Certainly if, okay, how about this?
You got some friends.
They move out to Los Angeles, California.
Maybe they're not theme park people,
but they're open-minded, okay?
Yeah.
And they go, you know what?
I would like to get.
You say let's all have sex together.
And you do and it's wonderful.
And you forget about theme parks.
Let's go to a special club with bad lighting.
Yeah, so you say, okay, we'll go to the theme parks.
And then I would start to go.
You start, I'm slow and you start to explain
the history of things.
There's certain people you know,
and especially if they have the time.
So what I'm trying to say is, in this scenario,
somebody has the time.
And you'd say, oh, have you ever walked through
the whole line of whatever ride we're talking about?
Oh, you only do single rider at Indiana Jones.
Well, did you know there's a long queue?
And then you point things out.
But they have to be that type of person
that might appreciate it.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
So.
This is, look, I appreciate.
I like both of your answers.
Jason gave a very realistic answer
of something he would say.
Yeah.
Force the group to do it.
Sure.
Where I felt like the first time this came up
is that what was expected of me
is that I veer everyone with me.
No, no, I think what.
You need to do your homework.
I think what happens when we all have debates on this show
is the same thing that happens in politics
where all of a sudden we're at the very ends
of every side of the argument.
When maybe that's not actually where the argument started.
So the argument started, I feel like,
I don't know what I'm saying,
but it somehow morphed into Scott hates lines,
hates the.
Yeah, which button.
Yeah, and look, I don't like that.
That's something people say to me
and comes up in comments and stuff.
Like, people suggest like a club three.
Like, what about lines that Scott would actually do?
I do lines all the time.
I'm just saying the argument.
But, yeah.
If you had the option to skip all of them always.
A lot of these arguments,
we would have to go back to the scene of the crime
and really suss out exactly those first like eight sentences,
eight to 15 sentences to actually figure out
what everyone's opinion is on them.
Sure.
You know?
Right, right.
So, yeah.
Which is why we're gonna get back into Lake Nona
for a long time right now.
Yeah, you ready, Jason?
Right now, and let's go.
I was just letting you guys.
Let's go.
Patch it down.
All right, you all right.
Okay, you've let us talk, say some facts, say your facts.
2,160 guests per hour with a dispatch going every two minutes.
Although there's usually four of the five vehicles
going at any given time.
Do you have the miles per hour of the ride?
I don't have the miles per hour.
What do you think?
Oh, it's not.
You get like five miles, like two miles.
It's not a fast drive.
I was trying to tie it in.
I was trying to like do the Sammy Hagar,
I can't drive 55, but whatever.
Oh, yeah.
I can't drive four.
Four miles.
He's gotta do five.
He's one of the animatronic drivers of this attraction.
Oh, man.
It was Universal's first trackless ride.
And, you know, opened in 2016,
it is interesting that then Fast and Furious came after that
because they put so much time and attention
into like plussing up a port of like a clone
of the studio tour footage.
Yeah, making it way more of a beginning,
middle, and end experience.
They re-animate, they like up-res the animation,
they added, you know, they tweaked,
like there's not a tram being thrown.
There's another, you know, Safari car.
It's not a bright blue Universal tram anymore,
which I guess I miss in a way.
Wouldn't make sense if it was there.
But I kinda like that.
Maybe just because I, you know,
because I worked there and I see those babies,
it reminds me of my wild youth.
So seeing one in peril tumbling through the jungle,
like, oh, there's my girl.
That's how I feel about the tram.
When you were riding your rowdy years,
when you would think back to that first car you owned.
Yeah, mine was.
That first place you'd go to.
You were at Mel's night or pulling up at a multi-car tram.
I do consider that, yeah, that's my first car.
Mel's diner, then we'd take that thing
for a ride over to the big fat liar set.
Oh baby, those were the years.
You wanna get really wild, see a flash flood?
My friend Al Roker has some information about it.
I know we're not at this part of the tram yet,
but why don't I hit the gasoline, sound cute.
Oh, those days.
You never forget your first car.
That's a car that you are not licensed to operate.
It is a separate union from yours.
It's way better than yours anyway.
The vehicle is cool.
I don't know, it looks cool.
The vehicle of this?
Yeah, of the Islands of Adventure version.
Yeah, I remember, this shouldn't take any points away,
but I'm somewhat active as far as being a lurker
on the inside Universal message boards.
I think this is where I read this,
where they have a lot of rumors and people speculating.
It might not actually be these boards.
It might be different boards,
but there was a lot of talk before it opened
and then after it opened of speculation
on what the Universal Creative people were gonna do.
I do think in some ways, it had built it up
because there was lots of robots maybe in between.
Do you remember the one rumor,
because I'm gonna bring this up,
that there was gonna be different tour guide characters,
which did pan out, that did come to pass,
but that Kong was going to reach into the cab
and pull the, make somehow they would do it
where the driver was pulled out of the car.
By Kong, which would have been admittedly awesome
and probably impossible, could probably pain in the ass.
Well, the thing, the rumor I had read on one of these boards
and again, who knows if that's true.
I mean, I think that one might have been a better source
even than this.
This was just like a message board,
but there's a rumor that they were gonna have
like animatronic Kong legs running behind you or something.
Yeah, they're running.
In some way, I'm not sure how they would make that look,
but there was some, yeah, very, very ambitious version
that probably would have mixed the 3D movie and robots.
How do you do that?
And then hit the ground with any.
I mean, I guess it couldn't hit the ground.
You would just make the noises
and it would kind of end up speculating.
But just like the bending of joints on a massive scale,
that seems, I could see why they threw that out.
Which is cool as that would be.
Expensive as hell, yeah.
So I remember kind of reading a lot of that
and then maybe by the time,
like you see there's a little robot
and then there's just a nice,
I guess it's Optimus Prime style ending with the character
at the end, which is a robot, spoiler alert.
You get a real moment.
But yeah, yeah.
I think in some ways, when the ride was being built,
I think I was like, whoa, this thing's gonna be nuts.
And it's just like, it's good.
I do like it.
I'm not trying to put it down.
Basic synopsis of it, just to get that out of the way,
it is 1931.
You are on a expedition
with the Eighth Wonder Expedition Company
and you're going to explore Skull Island.
People don't really know everything that's going on there,
but you're trying to find if there's any evidence
of prehistoric creatures,
because that could be an incredible finding.
And there's archeologists already there
trying to do exactly that.
And boy, do you find them.
Boy, do you find them and then some.
Yeah.
And in fact, one of the archeologists, Kate,
is kidnapped by, not a bat, not a bat.
I mean, if you polled 99% of the people coming out of this,
they'd say it's a bat.
But the name of it is somewhere in my notes.
Oh, there it is.
A terapus mordax.
A terapus mordax?
Jason, you have terapus mordax?
I did have terapus mordax.
She's, the bat does drop her and the other guy.
But you like that or a terapus?
Sorry, the terapus mordax.
You're confusing me.
Very good.
But then the giant claw that grabs her
is the giant crustacean, the deplector.
Oh, you're right.
Yeah.
The terapus mordax is just the beginning of the problem.
It's the.
Sorry, what then?
Deplector?
I don't have that.
I don't have that either.
I got a decarnate, decarnate cemex.
Oh, deplector here.
Is that the worm?
No, that's a.
That's a carnictus.
Deplector I have here is giant crustaceans
living in the cavernous crevices found along the walls
of the insect pit on the King Kong Wiki.
OK.
Yeah.
Because there's like big scorpions and big spiders.
Deplector.
And then a crab.
Deplector's a cool name.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's cool.
There's a lot of cool gross bugs and monsters and stuff.
And I like that they gave them names.
But we were pro-name.
The more names, the better.
Yeah.
It feels like they went.
They did go all out with the details and stuff.
There was also a lot of short making of videos on YouTube.
And then there was a fake web series called Myth Explorer.
Whoa, I didn't see that.
It's on the Universal Orlando account.
And it is like a fake discovery channel,
like globetrotting exploration show about a woman hunting
for the real Skull Island.
Wow.
But she acknowledges that there's been movies and TV shows.
And there's a ride coming to Universal.
It's like a thing within a thing.
And so yeah, it's 2017 or 2016.
There's also one of the behind the scenes videos.
A Universal creative person.
She goes really into the importance of STEM education,
of science and math education, which I feel like
was really big in 2016.
I feel like there was a big push about the importance
of STEM education.
It feels very much of its time.
And I'm sure that the educational thrust in that area
has remained under the firm leadership of Governor DeSantis.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Hope this on science and math is as strong as ever.
He's focused on all the right things.
All the right things.
The more books, the better, he says.
Oh yeah.
He is so mighty instead.
Fast, much like King Kong.
Much like the mighty Kong himself.
Countrywide, I feel like they're loving books.
It's a real book time.
Great time to read.
Do you know if the woman found Skull Island
in the continuity of those videos?
I only saw two clips.
I watched two episodes, and then it kind of cut off.
Oh, so maybe they didn't finish then earlier.
I don't know if they.
Well, the website mythexplorer.com is no longer active.
I think one, the Orlando Informer articles
about Kong Skull Island, I think they did redirect
their link to the archive.org page,
but it didn't seem like a ton was super functional there.
You know?
Okay.
So we'll never know.
Yeah.
Archive.org, the Skull Island of websites.
You gotta go on an expedition.
Might not ever come out.
Don't let your computer get a de Plector style bug.
Please be careful.
But yeah, I mean, generally you were,
and we'll go into details of it,
but generally you were trying to save this archeologist
and they're calling you back to the base camp.
No, it's not safe.
No, you gotta go save her, and thus you end up
in the jungle with a bunch of dinosaurs who are not,
we'll get into who they are,
but King Kong swoops in, saves the day,
and gives you a little moment where you worry
is gonna be bad news, but is more like,
remember, I'm the guy.
Yeah.
It's me.
Yeah, there's one king.
He kinda mad dogs you.
Yeah.
Yeah, he shows his authority.
Which is nice.
As you have to.
So, well, I mean, we could kinda,
look, we could talk about the queue.
We can.
It's a good queue.
It's really good, yeah.
And it's got, yeah, it's got so much,
as we talked about a little, like a scare actor sometimes,
we think.
We're not sure of the schedule on that.
There's like, there's screen scare-ectors, essentially.
Like there is a, that's where I was like,
wow, this is pretty cool in here, where they kinda,
they kinda lure you into looking through this area
with some rocks, where there's some sparkly stuff going on.
So you crane your head, what's going on in here,
and then bah, guy jumps out at you,
who is very realistic and very bright in that way
that realistic screen people are,
but the brightness kinda adds to the,
the serenity.
You don't expect to see such a bright figure
poking out of those rocks.
That still is burned, and it did genuinely freak me out.
And I was like, well, this is, hey,
this is stuff that's only in this queue.
They gotcha.
Yeah, it's like we've heard,
we've heard tell over the years, like of those,
the Haunted Mansion lore of when they would have
an actor in the ride or hanging out, you know, like the,
I guess it was a suit of armor.
There was, they supposedly had an actor
wearing the armor on the ride,
and the legend is like a person punched,
punched the person,
because they got their face into the car.
So I've heard of this, and then like,
Knott's used to do, at Scary Farm,
they would do scare-ectors on the log ride,
or maybe it was on the mine cart ride, I forget.
Maybe both.
It was the, I think it was the log ride,
because you are going pretty fast.
So there's not a ton of spots for them to pop out.
So it was a lot of the emergency exit.
Yeah, right, right, right.
They kind of knew it was coming,
because it would be dangerous to pop out
from anywhere else, you know?
Yeah, they haven't done that.
They haven't done those, they don't think the last couple,
well, not a couple, whatever, four or five years,
I feel like since we've gone,
I don't remember them having those scare-ectors on the ride.
But I've always been, I think as a kid even,
I was always kind of unsure of like,
oh, is there a real person here in these rides?
So this is like the first time,
I guess one of the most popular,
like a big Universal or Disney ride had a full scare-ector,
correct me if I'm wrong,
that's like regularly showing up in the ride experience.
Yeah, well, don't forget the special treat
that met some Disneyland guests every once in a while
when Captain Jack himself.
Oh, okay, well sure.
But who?
That's not quite what I'm saying.
I don't even have the, I don't even want to.
There's no stamina for you left in you
to get to the end of that joke.
Rather not say the name.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look it up yourself.
So yeah, so this is cool,
and as a kid this would have scared the shit out of me,
and I wouldn't have wanted to go on it,
because I would have been like,
there's a person in that line?
No way.
I was terrified at the idea of real people
in haunted houses as a kid,
to the point of it was either in like Wildwood
or Seaside Heights,
like we went to another town one night at the Jersey Shore
that we didn't often go to,
and there was a haunted house,
and I was so excited because I loved the haunted mansion,
but there were all these warning signs,
that was very intense,
and like we went up to the teen working,
and was like, are there people in costumes in this?
He's like, yeah, oh yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
And I was like, I'm not, no, I'm not doing this one.
Early on, I remember the most like,
rinky dink carnival haunted house around Halloween,
and it was like, there was a sign outside
that like explained kind of what it was,
and I was like, no way,
and I was like seven or eight,
and then like that lasted up until, what, five years ago?
Whenever I went to, whenever I started.
Yeah.
At least it ended at some point.
Well, I mean, trick or treating in my neighborhood,
there were parents or families who would go all out,
and I remember a couple times,
like dads, because some people would have like scarecrows,
you know, on the front, like in a chair on the front yard,
and then some people would dress like scarecrows,
and sit in the thing, and then jump out at you
when you reach for the candy bowl,
and my dad always tells the story of like,
there was one house, and we were pretty sure
that like it was a person, not a scarecrow,
but I went up and got candy,
and said hi to like the people giving out the candy,
and walked away, and so I didn't get caught,
I didn't get, you know, they didn't jump out,
and we turned to walk away, and my dad looks back,
and the guy goes, hey Mike, hi,
and like it was, but he saw me coming.
Oh, so he didn't scare you.
Terrified, so he did not do it.
He went easy on you.
He was like, cool dad.
For old Jason.
Oh wow, well that's nice.
Yeah. Oh geez.
Well, a candy bowl mix,
I don't think I even said this,
because I think I did this after we recorded
our Halloween episode last year,
or where I detailed my panic attack
before going into an escape room with Eva,
of course the Minotaur,
but I tried to get right back on the horse,
like a week later, and went to a Zombie Joe show with Eva,
which is just like a little mini maze,
and then a weird show with a lot of nudity,
because that's the thing over there.
The club random.
The club.
Yeah.
But they make a maze,
they can make this very tight maze out of just like,
I don't know, maybe I have told the story.
They make just like, what am I thinking of?
You put down like a tarp or something,
they kind of make it in the lobby of this small theater.
So like you really are like,
say it's like as big as this garage,
but they've put so much tarp and stuff around.
They section it off to turn it into.
Yeah, and it's like a maze,
and you have to like go like really tightly in,
and there's people in there yelling and screaming at you.
And then at the very end,
because you go one way,
then you go into the theater,
watch the show come out the other way,
and it's a new maze with different characters
on your way out.
And in the very end, there's a candy bowl,
and you go to reach for some candy,
and of course it's a human being,
and their head has got like a candy bowl thing
is fixed to it.
You're touching their, oh no, it's not.
The candy isn't their face.
Right, no, but it's like stuck on their head,
and they're like in this like position,
like as if there's some sort of stand
for the candy bowl in them.
That's great.
So you reach in and you go, ah!
It's really one last freak fright before.
But I like that you're genuinely like,
ah, I made it, ah, now to enjoy a piece of.
I was disappointed,
because I did reach in to get the candy.
I was gonna say, they found the way to get you.
Yeah, well. Every time.
I wish the person saw me and was nice,
like when Jason was little.
Although there wasn't real candy either.
I was disappointed to look like,
I touched it and it was like fake.
Like rubber and warm,
because it was the person's head.
So your scream was less scared and more.
It's not candy!
I wanted my full fat candy.
I wanted full sugar candy.
Yeah.
You know, I think this was Universal,
Orlando's first thing with scare actors year round.
But out here, there was the Universal House of Horrors.
Yes, yes, yes, which I've talked about before.
So, I mean, I guess that's different.
That's like a full haunted house.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, you're right.
That's true.
But yeah, it is also just a haunted house.
Yeah.
But as a kid, yeah, I think we share the same,
like I hope there's not real people on this.
Because as a kid, I think you would learn
with Disney and Universal,
that you could count on the rides
to do what you knew they'd do.
There was a safety in haunted mansion,
because you knew it was gonna be the same thing every time.
Yeah, yeah.
The beach town where they were still giving out
cartons of cigarettes at the carnival games.
I knew was a little more chaotic.
Yeah, so that was unpredictable.
But the calmness that you could get from knowing
that there were not random elements
on the haunted mansion.
Yeah.
That's why, you know, hey,
that's why the haunted mansion stinks, right?
You know exactly where it's going.
Yeah.
Not like a freewheeling conversation.
That's right.
Maybe we can talk about lib tears a little.
So anyway, I mean, this queue is,
it is really fantastic.
The exterior is great.
I feel like in general,
what you can tell they're hitting over and over,
is it is a screen-based ride,
but it's a screen ride for people
who don't like screen rides.
Because that is the basis of it,
but they're doing everything else
that they can do to show you.
Like this is a full experience
that has a lot of dimensionality.
Including right before you even get in there,
the fact that you walk up
and there is this exterior loop.
Yes.
Where you watch the vehicle
drive out of its boarding area,
go up to the giant doors of the temple
with huge flames shooting out of them.
Like the scale of it is fantastic.
It's similar to, it's a little bit of that,
what's cool about Rise of the Resistance,
where they carve out these exterior zones
to be part of a mainly interior ride.
Yeah.
There's also a fail safe,
where if it's lightning, if it's pouring rain,
the car can skip that outdoor section
and continue to operate.
Wow, wow.
I'm not quite sure the mechanics of the shortcut.
I couldn't, all the videos I tried to find on YouTube,
like King Kong Rain, King Kong Shortcut.
Like I did get a few, I was surprised.
I did pick three random videos
and got three different tour guide characters.
Yeah, I got a good mix of the guides.
Which I think is another attention to detail
that adds to this ride.
Yeah, well we might as well dive into that.
Sure.
I mean, so King Kong does not reach his hand
into a vehicle and pull out a nanometronic character.
But on these vehicles, and by the way,
I bought all this hook line.
It never occurred to me that it was trackless.
I figured this was like,
Yeah, I didn't know that.
This was a real, like a vehicle with a motor
that's driving you around.
And I thought the shape up front was a human being.
So until we started prepping for this,
genuinely did not know that these are,
there's nobody on them except for you, the guests.
And that that figure up in the front
is an animatronic driver.
And I certainly did not know that there is a mix
of five animatronic drivers
that customize the experience.
I didn't know that until now.
Yeah, I'm convinced, now while it's cool,
and I think everybody who finds this out thinks it's cool,
it did occur to me, we might be the first people ever
to have a conversation about it.
You know what I mean?
Other than Universal Creative?
We're gonna say these names, right?
Has anyone ever gone into this before?
Oh, well, I think like we,
there's a lot of websites when they, again,
Yeah, you know what I mean,
but that's like a press release being handed to them.
Yeah, there's a press release.
It was part of the press release.
Yeah, yes, clearly.
It was part of like the full, the all hands media.
The fandom of, there's no like Skull Island heads,
Skull Island junkies.
You know, like a lot of things that we talk about
on this show, all of a sudden in a couple weeks,
stuff will start popping up and you go, did we do that?
Maybe it's our egos talking,
but I feel like maybe by just putting this into the world,
you know, maybe we'll start to see the people
will be stanning these characters, I don't know.
I mean, there are a lot of archetypes you see in,
you know, adventure movies and stuff,
King Kong movies, of course.
Should I just start?
Yeah, sure, yeah.
Hopefully, and you're starting lineup of.
Becky Callahan, the loose cannon cowgirl
who isn't fazed by the dangers awaiting her on Skull Island.
Archetypes, loose cannon cowgirl.
Loose cannon cowgirl.
Will Denham, the fresh face,
adventure seeking younger cousin,
famed movie director, Carl Denham.
Now, okay, this is the most interesting one to me.
So to explain what's going on here,
unless you're like, I know who Carl Denham is,
I'm not an idiot.
So this is set in 1931, the Peter Jackson, King Kong,
that Universal has done so many attractions about,
made the studio tour largely about,
was from 2005, I think.
Carl Denham is the filmmaker played by Jack Black,
who goes to find King Kong,
and then make him do a meme show.
Yeah, yes.
The one who calls him the eighth wonder of the world.
Oh, okay.
For the marketing.
Also the name of the character in the 1933 King Kong
is Carl Denham.
Oh, okay, that is consistent.
Okay, okay, cool.
So, and this is where, I think the fandom page
started to get a little spicy of like,
obviously, I mean, it's a nod to the movies,
but it seems unlikely that this would be a full prequel
to that movie, because why would there have been
an expedition and then another expedition?
Oh, right, because they're, yeah, it's unexplored.
Yeah, yeah, if the guy's nephew has already been,
but they tried to make this all tie together,
and I watched a video where I did land on Will Denham,
so, and this is all just VO.
There's kind of one big spot where the character
gets to make their mark, and it is in that opening loop
before the plot really kicks in,
but you get like one or two sentences to get to know
your animatronic driver.
It says his name, hey, I'm Will.
My uncle, Carl Denham, makes adventure movies.
That's what I wanna do someday.
I can't wait to tell him about this place.
You know the way you're always saying your uncle's name?
Yeah, uh-huh.
Sure. Yeah.
My uncle, Robert Gardner,
pretty cantankerous.
I don't know what else I wanna say about my uncle.
Yeah, it's a- But I said introduce it,
now you know his name.
Well, it is helpful that he speaks like that,
because we wouldn't know otherwise.
I just wanted to really quickly add that Carl Denham
is a character that also appeared in the 1998
The Mighty Kong animated movie, voiced by Dudley Moore.
Another actor who has played Carl Denham.
Someone mentioned, I think one of the universal
creative people was talking about like,
yeah, we've seen Baby Boomers, we've seen Kong a lot.
We know Kong.
We saw the 1966 cartoon with Kong, and I was like,
did you?
I forgot about that.
I don't know.
There's a lot of Kong that I haven't seen.
Yeah, there is a lot of Kong.
A lot of Kong, and a lot of Kong to go.
We still have to talk about all these other-
Oh, there's prequels- Oh, there's more names.
Oh yeah, yeah, we'll get to that real quick though.
I'll say that one of my memories of sitting next to
a certain tram tour once is just constantly saying,
Skull Island.
Yeah.
We're going back.
Well, that's the truly, I mean, to compare and contrast
them, the context of that tram version,
and granted, it is the tram, so things on the tram
can happen in a way of, we're gonna go see a set,
and then we'll see what happens on the set,
but they don't even really do that,
because you're just driving in,
and Peter Jackson's talking to you,
and we're gonna go back, we're going back,
and you go into a dark room, and then all of a sudden,
lights turn on, and it's very impressive,
and the experience is impressive,
but there really is something to building the story.
We are in 1931, we're fully committed.
Yeah, for sure.
The drivers of character.
There's the little set of Skull Island on the tram tour.
They're still doing that, right?
Oh, the bigature.
Yeah.
Because Peter Jackson, he wasn't happy
just using a miniature.
Of course.
He wanted to step it up, and that's why we deployed bigatures.
That's what we're about to see.
Get your camera, I remember him saying that,
like, get your cameras ready, you won't wanna miss this.
And then we would drive by quietly.
The parting of the Red Sea effect.
Yes, that became, yeah, yeah, yeah,
part of the Universal Tram Tour,
where you descend into a lake,
and then come back up out of it, but they don't,
wait, they brought it back when I was working there.
Initially, they were like,
we're cutting the parting of the seas.
Oh, yeah.
But then for a while, it was this awkward thing,
where you're talking about King Kong,
and then you have to go part the seas.
Right.
Okay, now we're gonna see a bigature.
So we're melding together, it's now the Ten Commandments,
and it's the Bible.
Yeah, yeah.
Plus the 2005 King Kong.
I mean, for a generation of filmmakers,
King Kong was kind of like the Bible.
Well, that's a very good point.
2005 one as well, of course.
As we've been told, again and again and again,
pretty much since I've had memories,
I've been told about how important King Kong is.
Yeah, so it's funny,
because the movie Skull Island came out
already five years ago,
but back then, they say Skull Island,
and that part of the Tram Tour so much.
Yeah.
And that wasn't on the tip of our tongues like it is now.
No.
The movie didn't really keep,
I find those things funny when Universal has so,
just dug their claws into,
I mean, it sort of keeps happening.
I mean, even Secret Life of Pets
does not exactly reverberate across all of our,
how many of those characters can we name?
But I also, I appreciate the risk involved,
because it feels like Disney won't get out of bed,
they won't build something for a franchise
that made less than $5 billion.
So I kind of like that Universal might,
we're probably close to getting a Beethoven dark ride.
They had it drafted up.
About from the old Beethoven, or is there a new Beethoven?
Well, the inevitable reboot.
Okay, yeah.
Oh yeah.
That feels like a Disney plus fodder, right?
Does Disney have Beethoven now?
I don't think they do.
Oh no, that's a pride of Universal.
That is Universal.
Yeah, okay.
Although it did have a strong, thank God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It would have been so embarrassing.
Beethoven and Missy and all the pups,
I don't want them to be on Disney Plus,
I want them to be on which one?
On Peacock.
Wherever Universal movies go.
Yeah, Peacock, I guess. Peacock sometimes.
With Ambulance.
Michael Bay. Ambulance.
Ambulance, LA-ance.
Ambulance, yes.
The exclusive home to Ambulance.
Ambulance, LA-ance, yeah, you have to stop the A
at the LA.
Okay, anyways.
Jason wants to say these names.
Oh no, well I was gonna say,
because King Kong, the Peter Jackson King Kong,
a movie I liked fine, and I think made a lot of money,
and did well enough.
That is kind of an early example
of what feels so common nowadays,
where a thing is coming out and it's pushed on you,
it's pushed in a way,
like Lightyear might be an example of this,
where it's pushed on you, on the audience.
You like this, and you like this.
This is a classic movie.
This new release is a classic movie.
They were trying to reverse engineer
a hit with long lasting repercussions.
It's too big to fail.
There's no way.
You don't have the option to not like.
Yeah, it's not like organic.
I feel like I'm wrong, the Kong, Peter Jackson movie,
which I do like in my memory of it,
but I feel like it wasn't as big of a hit
as they wanted it to be.
I think they wanted it to be like a Lord of the Rings hit.
Yeah, because they were coming off that.
So it was like, yeah.
Wait, that was probably the bar for him.
Yeah, yeah.
So I think it was like,
because I think they would have done more than.
Surely this man can hit the lottery a fourth time.
Sure.
Fair expectation to put on a man.
Only Cameron can do it.
Only Jimmy Cameron can do it.
Yeah.
And it's pre like internet marketing or like.
Well, we've seen the failures of organic viral sensations
with like the Morbius re-release just eating shit.
It was very funny.
But if they had, they could have jumped on.
Everyone thought the commercial for this
where that takes place with Naomi Watts
and King Kong in Central Park
with a Coldplay song playing, that was very funny.
I don't remember that.
What song?
I have zero recollection of that.
Do you remember what song it was?
It was like Clocks.
It's King Kong the song.
King Kong.
It's a thing where they're looking at each other.
Bing bong.
And it seems like it's romantic
with the Coldplay song playing.
Okay, is it Fix You?
I think it's, I think it might be Fix You.
She's trying to get them to calm down.
Well, you already have too many dangling plot threads
on podcast, right?
I will say I'm sort of a Coldplay defender.
I will say that.
Yeah, I like Coldplay.
That adds up.
Rush of Blood to the head.
Based on what has come up before.
Not shocking.
I don't mind Coldplay.
Clocks?
Yeah.
Clocks, okay, yeah.
I feel like that third album, what is that called?
I, you know what I do like, I still like, what's the song?
What's the, oh shoot, what's the real poppy song that I-
Jason, say some facts quick.
I don't know.
Get us off here.
Okay, they have this music video
where a bunch of monkeys dance on an island.
Oh damn, that's related, okay.
Monkeys, yeah.
Yeah, like King Kong.
Do you guys know, by the way,
the story that Naomi Watts tells about David Lynch?
Like she was, she had done 21 Grams,
she had done Mulholland Drive,
and she was weighing whether to do King Kong or not.
So she asked David Lynch whether she should do it.
Naomi Watts says, I remember calling up David Lynch,
who's my mentor, and he said to me,
and I've heard her tell this story
where she does the voice, so I'm gonna do the voice.
Naomi, anyone who sits in the hand of King Kong
is a movie star for life.
And he wasn't wrong, she's gone on to great success.
All because of Kong.
Jessica Lange.
Jessica Lange?
I don't know if Linda Hamilton sits in his hand
in the bad one that she's in,
but she was a movie star.
Is that the, do you know De Laurentiis,
like had to make a sequel?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
One, yeah, okay.
Where he eats like a bunch of crocodiles
and then dangles their bones around.
Oh, I think the main,
Jodie Benson, I think, is the voice of the character
in the Mighty Kong, the Judley Moore.
Movie star for life.
So this is already 1998.
Toy Story, yeah, yeah, I guess it's true.
It's true, David is right.
Think about Jodie.
Yeah, of all the Kong movies,
and I really, we should have researched this before,
which one is the weirdest in regards to the romance
between Kong and the woman?
That's my question.
I don't know the answer, but I pose it to the listener.
Well, I think in King Kong Live is my favorite.
It's a romance with another Kong.
Yeah, well that, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that's good, that's appropriate.
Yeah, yeah, finally.
Yeah.
Yeah, they fixed that.
Like we finally, we got that one part out of it.
So this King Kong will finally be the most successful
ever made, certainly not a thing that no one remembers
except for Scott when Scott brings it up
every two and a half years.
The thing is though, people don't want that.
They learned that people want a giant gorilla
and a woman to be falling in love.
That's what they want.
That movie, that 86 one, I just saw.
That's the heart one?
Yeah, yeah, that's what the heart transplant.
Yeah, I saw a clip of Siskel and Ebert talking about it,
and they were like, this is the part of the show
where we normally show a clip, but we don't have one.
Because the studio said, we'll let you play a clip
on your local show in Chicago, but not the national.
And they said, no dice, if this movie,
if you want us to sell your movie,
why wouldn't you send us a clip for us to show everywhere?
Is it not good or something?
And then it went to shit, and then they just yelled at it
on their show without a clip.
See now, now here, now as far as YouTube rabbit holes,
I've been watching a lot of Siskel and Ebert lately.
That's a good rabbit hole.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's healing.
It's healing the gray matter in your brain.
Ebert, dead wrong about kids in the hall brain candy.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Was up his butt that day.
Ebert has a few big misses.
Yeah, he's usually.
He did Wet Hot American Summer wrong, incorrect.
Oh yeah.
He just didn't get it.
You can tell he just didn't understand
what I'm trying to be.
Yeah, I feel like he's more right than he's wrong,
but yeah, he has some big ones where he's wrong.
But yeah, you can't bat a thousand.
Except for us.
Except for us in our opinion.
Every opinion right.
Every take. Transformers.
Correct, celebrated.
Transformers better than Rize.
Unlike the folly prone Jinx Costanza.
Jinx Costanza.
Frank, his name is revealed as Frank later on.
But Frank Costanza. Frank Costanza.
Frank Costanza.
Is Jerry Stiller.
Yes.
On Seinfeld.
Is that, so it's Jerry Stiller of a con connection.
Is that, do you think that's a nod?
Does he fall in love with that con?
It has to be a nod.
Also, somebody in the building must have said,
hey, that's the name.
Yeah.
Yeah, cause that's weird.
You can't just take that name.
That's one of the great characters.
It's kind of not said together.
Hardin New York City ex-con,
it was wary of the island's mysteries.
And they say he's prone to like, you know,
my name's Jinx cause I find myself in scraps a lot.
You think he said what I wrote it that,
most people just call me Jinx and the voice is like this.
Cause I've had my share of bum luck.
Bum luck.
Before you ask, yeah, I heard about it,
but I ain't seen no giant ape.
Let's keep it that way.
Like he's threatening him.
Yeah.
Yeah, whatever.
Couldn't they have just gotten,
they should have gotten Jerry Stiller to do it.
He may as well.
Yeah.
I guess he was still, yeah.
There's a big monkey.
I can't do Jerry, sorry.
I mean, it would have been,
like what a thrilling cameo you get on.
Oh my God.
Oh, this is like, well the character they own, you know.
Wait, no, no, they don't know the knife.
No, the knife broke away.
Yeah. Yeah.
And we're careful about it.
Broke out like Kong.
Yeah, you can still get Jerry though.
And you can like wink, wink, play the character.
Yep.
Anymore deadly games got him.
This ride did not.
It's too bad.
The final two.
Kalana, a mystical descendant of the natives
who first settled on the island.
The video where Kalana is narrating
immediately goes, my people worship Kong.
Like, I feel like that,
as soon as you were pulling away,
it's like gonna be straight with you.
So we're gonna go see my god.
I'm pretty excited because we're gonna meet God today.
Yeah.
Charles Doc Jordan, a PhD student in paleontology
who took time off from his studies to explore the world.
I don't know if you could take time off.
I mean, you could probably finagle some credit hours
to exploring the world for paleontology.
Still applies.
Yeah.
I think so.
They should have overlapped him.
But he got the PhD.
Especially if you're hanging out
doing on location studies at Skull Island.
Part of Skull Island study abroad program.
Yeah.
There's only about a 10% return rate.
You know, you're getting into it a lot.
The least they could get is like six credits, you know?
They try to send your bones back to your parents
if they are not mangled.
It's too thoroughly.
I would have gone to Skull.
No, I wouldn't.
That's too scary.
My mom would not allow.
It's pretty bad.
You know, you get any of these drivers pull you in.
I like that they customize it to where the archeologist,
Kate, says the name of all of these.
But like they change that dialogue.
So, you know, she'll say hey to jinx.
Are you talking about Kate McCaffrey?
Kate McCaffrey.
I guess I am.
Just make sure there wasn't another Kate.
No, no, no.
It's archeologist Kate McCaffrey.
But the way their little adventure starts
where she just gets kind of pleasantries.
Like, oh, hey, what's up?
Hey, all right, well, we're gonna go back to the base camp.
And then I forget why the guy,
they're trying to get more light on something.
And then I think Joe is the guy that she's with
who just says, here, I got it.
And then fires a couple of flares
and instantly a bunch of not bats, not bats.
No, no.
It's a bunch of, god damn it, terrapas mordaxes.
But it's just a flood.
It's the dumbest move in history.
You're all lighted up, bang, bang,
terrapas mordax swarm instantly.
He gets picked up by one, starts to carry him away.
She reaches up, pulls him down.
Then she gets picked up and he makes no effort to save her.
No.
He gets in a van and gets out of there.
What a coward.
Yeah, Joe sucks.
Fuck you, Joe.
You should really be encouraged to get back
to where everyone survived, spoiler.
Even Kate made it despite a lot of monster encounters.
You should really boo Joe.
Yeah, Joe should be, or Kong should eat Joe.
Yes.
Just at the end.
Yeah, should get punished for what they, you know.
Like that Jurassic World babysitter got punished
for slightly poor babysitting.
He should at least put him in his mouth for a while.
Give him a good scare.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Give him a stench he can't wash off for a couple weeks.
Roll him around on his tongue with a closed Kong mouth.
Like how far back in the throat can he get Joe
without fully swallowing him?
Like really make him see some shit.
What, he could get him down.
Okay, would Kong's stomach acid
immediately dissolve Joe's skin
or could he hit the stomach acid
and Kong could put his fingers down his throat
to make himself vomit again and puke Joe back up?
If he's got flares, he could maybe like electrify
the stomach acid.
Maybe there's like a Diet Coke Mentos effect.
Oh, maybe.
Oh yeah.
And then he flies up on flares right out of the,
which then makes King Kong cough
and spits him right back out to safety.
Okay, yeah, that would work perfectly
as long as the acid isn't too strong
to completely immediately like destroy him.
It's a quick, yeah, is King Kong's stomach acid
stronger than ours or is that part about him
not particularly notable?
That's a good question.
Or powerful.
I don't know if they address that
in any of the Kong movies.
Jason literally looked at his watch.
Huh?
You checked your watch?
Oh, it's just a habit.
I have the tick I have.
Well, no, that's a good indicator for the listener.
I was trying to go like how long have we been going?
Try to remember.
Something about that made you start thinking about the time.
Hey, it's a good indicator.
I look at my watch all the time when I record.
It's a good indicator.
Oh, you do?
Yeah.
Every now and then I often don't remember when we started
so it's a useless gesture.
Okay, well, we got time for about two and a half more hours,
right?
Yeah, sure.
Two and a half more hours about Kong's stomach acid.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I want to talk about.
Then we'll get, and then we'll wrap up.
So Joe should get punished.
He doesn't get punished.
She gets picked up and then kind of hacks her way free.
And then starts blasting everyone.
Bugs up, yeah.
And those are the carnictises, the carnicti,
and they give you a splash out of those.
You get that, you get your universal trademark,
which I've come around to now,
because we've said before, oh, universal, same old trick.
No, I think that's now, that's the trademark.
That's the director cameo in their work.
They wrote it out.
It's like the Tarantino foot shots.
Exactly.
We know you're getting them.
So buckle up.
How good are they gonna be?
The little splashes you get at universal.
So yes, I like these.
They're good in this, and you know what?
It's good atmosphere throughout too.
Good reminder of Doug Jones' rule
that watching a video is not going on it,
because a lot of my memory of it is atmosphere.
It's like there's temperature changes and wind blasts.
Like there's a feeling to these rooms.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's true.
So yeah, they are doing all of that extra stuff
that the tram tour obviously doesn't have room to do.
You get a splash on there, but it's a little more,
and it's less clever, I would say,
than feeling the innards of a big slug.
Yeah.
It's like, this is so insane,
where there's mouths within mouths within mouths.
Oh yeah, there's a very, it's a really gross,
are we talking about, what's the phallic looking thing?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is flesh, it is human flesh.
It's really phallic, and it's not, again,
it's not my twisted, dirty mind
that everyone talks about from the show.
It's not that.
It looks like a giant penis with teeth.
Yeah, a pretty flaccid penis.
Sure.
Yeah, I'm not commenting on the flaccidity.
Probably.
But yeah, no, that's very,
I did not remember it from riding,
but when I was watching the video,
I went, oh, that's a big penis.
And you see one of those big penises in the queue, too.
Which really wakes up, apparently,
that thing really comes to life.
Yeah, that's just, there's an animatronic of that.
There's animatronics at the very start
of the ride of the firmus.
Got it.
Yeah, of course, there's the big guy at the end.
I think the cave stuff,
the cave stuff filmed for this ride, too.
I have to say, I-
Everything till the main event.
Yeah.
You see it like two big,
wait, am I missing one?
Is there more than one?
Or like two big film screen sequences before the big show.
Yeah, I think that's right.
I remember thinking there were a ton of scenes
when I rode it the first time, too.
But yeah, I think that's right.
It is a long, it's in the,
it's like 630 or something is the run time.
Yeah, yeah.
It is a sizable, yeah, it is longer.
I have to say, I think I really like
the first two film scenes
more than the racing stuff.
More than the driving fast,
the fake out where you're driving faster,
the stuff from the studio tour.
Yeah, yeah.
I like the new stuff in this more.
I bet it's more like, it's kinda easier to track,
I would say, moments you remember.
Yeah, for sure.
A little more, it's so,
you're not sure where to look maybe in the main show.
Yeah, and I think,
I guess I just always wish they finished the,
and then they'd have to be a full 360,
but to something on the roof of the car.
I don't know, I can see the edges.
Yeah, you can.
I feel like I shouldn't be able to see the edges.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, it's tricky.
I mean, with even Soarin',
it's like you can, depending on where you're sitting,
you can easily, obviously if you're at the bottom,
you see the edge.
It's always a little bit of,
couldn't you have done a little more
so I don't have to see these edges sometimes?
It feels like they could.
That's just, maybe that's just because
we've been on these things a lot,
and people aren't actually registering that.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
I feel really guilty for saying anything in this area.
I think we're being ungrateful
to the people who give us so much great material.
Well, I wanna be hashtag grateful,
so I don't wanna come off like that,
but sometimes when you see the edges,
you go, couldn't you, come on.
A little more, make this screen a little bigger.
When things are, when transitions in screen rides
are seamless, where you really don't,
which I think of Transformers, I think of Spider-Man,
Harry Potter, it is pretty unbelievable.
You're like, I really can't, there's no,
how crazily did they put us in a physical position
to never really see?
I didn't, I don't remember exactly when,
but I didn't even know there was that elevator thing
in Transformers until fairly recently,
which was the last couple years,
but I had to watch a YouTube video
that points out the elevator that happens.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, I guess so, yeah, yeah.
Like in Spider-Man.
Yeah, in the middle of the ride,
all of a sudden you literally just go up on an elevator,
which is crazy, because I never noticed that,
and then in the video on YouTube,
somebody specifically took their phone
and took a shot to show you
the actual physical movement of it,
and I was like, I've never noticed that.
I've ridden this so many times.
Your favorite ride just is the best ride, yeah.
The gift that keeps on giving.
Yeah. So amazing, isn't it?
So yeah, so yeah, I see what you're saying, Jason.
The edges.
Yeah.
But I think if I had to choose,
I'd rather do this than Kong on the studio tour,
but I'd rather do Fast and Furious on the studio tour
than in Florida.
Yeah, it's over quicker.
Does that make sense?
Yes.
Yeah, it's over quicker.
Mercifully, there's no separate line to wait in.
Yeah, I kind of love the insane cumbersome setups
throughout the studio tour,
where they have to go like, hey, that's a strange car.
Like security.
Do they still do that?
Oh my God, like they have to seat it the whole time?
I've been on it a while,
but I feel like there's little differences.
I have an annual pass now, and I never go to that.
You haven't tried to get a two-year-old
on that 45-minute studio tour?
Oh my God, oh yeah, absolutely not.
Oh my God.
There's a rumor.
And if there was any stall, if there was a one-minute stall.
Oh yeah.
Sweating and sweating.
Son, look, Mr. Mayor has been canceled,
but they're trying to film the finale, okay?
They still owe it.
It's a legal thing.
Finish the story.
The rumor is Fast and Furious Coaster coming.
This ghost.
Coming here, right?
That's the rumor, yeah.
We'll see.
There's been many rumors that haven't panned out, so.
But that sounds like they might like.
Where do you think?
Well, there's a lot of speculation about where.
They were talking about getting rid of like animal actors
and just putting it up on the upper lot.
Gasping.
Yeah.
So in that section there, and some even people,
people were like speculating,
you could kind of like loop it around on the side
of the mountain a little bit in a way, which sounds awesome.
Yeah, jeez.
But I don't know, then other people were saying,
I don't know, it could go anywhere on the lower lot.
Go through the big minion's eye.
That would be amazing.
They really should do something like that.
But yeah, so hopefully they'll correct
the Fast and Furious problem, you know?
Because I think Velocicoaster as well gave,
people love Velocicoaster.
Yeah.
So I think they're like, they're high on coasters
right now.
Yeah, and that takes up,
it's not a huge footprint either.
Right, because a lot of that's vertical.
Yeah.
So yeah, we'll see.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
On this thing, I mean, like the sequence,
the main sequence, I mean, so it's a lot of dinosaurs.
Who in the, oh fuck.
They're not T-Rexes.
Not T-Rexes.
They're evolved.
They're V-Rexes.
V-Rexes, yeah.
Vastodosaurus.
Vasta?
Vast, I mean I.
You want it, you're really looking at it like Vastasaurus,
but I'm seeing an extra Tato, like Tato Park.
Vastasaurus.
It's like what.
It's Craig Healy.
Craig Healy would say.
Take it to Vastasaurus.
Yeah.
Headed to Skull and Island.
And we're in the back.
Vastasaurus seems like it's bigger or something,
like vast, like that's a descriptor for a land.
Are they bigger or more.
Doesn't look like they're bigger.
Violent.
Yeah, they're more violent.
I do not like when Kong rips their skull.
Oh, you don't like when.
I always found that very unnerving.
The moment he bends their,
he like has both ends of the dinosaur's jaw
and just rips it like.
It's the most violent.
Cracks it like a nut.
Outside of Horror Nights,
like most gruesome, violent death
in all of theme parks maybe.
I think maybe.
Of a creature.
I think so.
It's pretty crazy.
Yeah.
He snaps this thing's jaw.
You don't really see the aftermath of it,
but you certainly see the beginning.
You snap the thing and it lies.
You get a good.
It just flops.
Half second of limp.
And you're like, oh my God, Kong.
Yeah.
Gee, you couldn't get to kick him away?
Yeah, there's no,
this isn't a Batman doesn't kill situation.
Right, I get.
More than willing to violently kill.
The law of the jungle, I understand it.
I know it.
This is a Zack Snyder Superman.
That's a real crack.
Yeah, it's the quick.
It's a murderous hero.
Yeah.
You know.
Yeah, it's, no, that's shocking.
You really.
Yeah.
Yeah, I watched.
I was watching it and I was like,
whoa, I forgot about that.
Yeah.
Kong, my goodness, I have to cover a child's eyes.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's see what Kong did to the Vastidosaurus.
Miami, the Vastidosaurus, what happened?
Is it okay?
Is he going to Vastidosaurus heaven?
Honey, no, he's just, they're doing a joke.
They're having fun.
Anyway, get him off the ride.
He'll put, he knows how to put him back together.
He wouldn't do it if he didn't know how to put him back
together.
Yeah, so very shocking violence, but it does save us.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess that's what.
Kate is saved off screen, so I don't know what.
Yeah.
Kate just made it separately, so good, good for her.
But then you get, the big thing that the tram portion
does not give you and has not given you since a fatal fire
a number of years ago, that you do get a big animatronic
King Kong.
Love this, love that they knew that that's part of the
experience.
They were probably hearing the thing about screen rides.
Yeah.
They know, look, there's just, there's no conversation to me
in terms of the tram tour used to have a big robot
that you could see and now you go sit between some screens
and then leave.
Right.
It's just not the same.
Like you want to see that big robot.
You want to, you want that banana breath.
And it's cool that they maybe did that calculation
and realized we got to give them something.
We owe a robot.
We got to give them something, yeah.
It would have been, yeah, the only thing is like the old
Kong, both Kongs, both coasts, there was like the
existing in a large scale environment.
That's the only note I would give it.
Cause like this Kong is like, he's in a building
perfectly built to his size.
It feels like I see there's no sense of scale as opposed to
when he was messing with the bridge, you know, right?
He's big.
And obviously he's a big Kong and it's really awesome to see
him. But yeah, the difference that that, the only thing I
would say, yeah, the scale and the other rides is, is kind of
important to my love of big robot Kong.
It's kind of weird that he just like looks at you.
I mean, I don't love that.
I could, that would be, I guess, be a plus up is just do
something.
The budget, it feels like they just like begged the money
people, like we need this Kong.
And they're like, okay, you know how you want him to like do
something or give a thumbs up or put some sunglasses on?
No way. Too much movement.
We need him cheaper, cheaper, cheaper.
We don't want him breaking down.
And they're like, all right, well, can he do, can he give him
like a winker? Can he? No, no, no, no, no.
He just kind of has to breathe at them.
He can exist.
He can exist there and he can move a little bit.
Like it feels that's what it feels like to me.
Cause I, again, we've said it a million times, obviously the
people making all this stuff, I'm sure came up with the
coolest ideas possible.
Yeah.
And then this was probably, yeah, the compromise.
So yeah, it's better than nothing.
Of course.
Smoke a big cigarette.
Fantastic.
Oh man.
Who will that be?
Oh, fantastic.
Oh, can I complain about a cigarette thing real quick?
It's unrelated.
I just have to cause they're super seven is a company makes
toys and they're making a crusty, the clown toy.
And when they first showed the pictures of crusty, the clown,
he came with a cigarette and he handed out a cigarette and
Mr. Teeny who has smoking a cigarette as well.
And I was like, holy shit, this is the greatest thing ever.
Disney stepped in and said no cigarettes.
And now they've had to revise the toy.
No cigar.
Disney stepped in.
Well, that's going to crusty.
Oh, yeah.
Cause I was shocked that they let it.
Cause I remember we were, I was texting people texting
Justin Michael, look at this crusty, the clown cigarette.
We're like, yeah, we want to see it.
We want to get it.
And then no, Disney stepped in and they, it sucks.
Can't have good things.
That's really like, yeah, they're going to,
I think they're going to change some minds with the people
with the 30 somethings buying some adult collectors.
Yeah.
Kids are going to be like Mr. Teeny is smoking with my dad's
$45 adult collectible toy.
And now I'm going to smoke.
I want to be like that minor character monkey.
Yeah. Oh gosh.
So annoying to me.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Anyway, the robot Kong.
I mean, I, this is where I will be grateful.
I'm happy to see my friend King Kong.
I feel warmly to King Kong.
I'm happy to see a giant animatronic.
I am happy too.
I am grateful for Kong as well.
I don't want you to think I'm not.
I am grateful so, and he does look emotive.
He does.
He's, I'm glad he's there.
Oh, that's great.
I think they, they did a good job.
It was, you know, I, I, one article was pointing out,
article from the time this came out,
that this was Universal's first big attraction,
like in the Florida parks since they built Diagon Alley.
So I'm sure there were unreasonable expectations.
Oh yeah.
That it's like, well, you build a massive giant land.
Surely you're going to hit it out in the park with this one.
And I think it's a solid B plus A minus.
Yeah.
I think it's a rock solid ride.
Like, I think it's fun.
It's like a ride they didn't need to have,
but they, they did it.
Look, I don't know.
This is, it's where Universal is at as opposed to Disney.
I don't think Disney's building rides
that they don't need to be, like,
it feels like a blockbuster, nothing.
And then you go years between things and boy,
what they've added, what they've added,
especially lately to Universal Orlando in terms of
mid level, not even mid level, they're all like blockbuster,
but they, it's like somewhere between D and E ticket.
There's just a like, I just, I think all the time
about how much they are winning the war.
D pluses.
Yeah.
Yeah. It doesn't sound great.
Disney pluses.
They're doing a lot of Disney pluses.
But they had a run there where it's like Cabana Bay opens,
the water park.
Volcano Bay.
You can easily name the hotel.
Well, they're two bays.
I know one of them's a water theme park.
I know that for a fact.
The third park.
The third park, the water theme park.
That's the only thing I don't like about it.
I know.
Hate it.
Not a third gate.
Volcano Bay.
So, I mean, they also opened Jimmy Fallon after,
but yeah, no, what are you gonna do?
But they allowed.
Okay.
Yeah, it doesn't make them not be winning the war.
When's their fourth park opening?
Is it in a couple of years?
2025?
Makes me wish it wouldn't be built.
That's how awful that is.
To hear that it's the fourth?
No.
You have yet to see the volcano up close though.
Yeah.
So you'll sign off on it.
Good enough.
This is good enough that it's the third park.
The volcano itself is good enough for the third park.
The water slide's not as much.
But the volcano is third park worthy.
But the theming around it is not as good
or existent at all.
Because as you're standing on the slides,
you can just see the houses on the street
over across the street.
Yeah, it is right along the freeway.
Yeah.
Because that volcano's incredible.
You go inside it, you're like,
I was just sitting in that wave pool looking up
and going, this thing is incredible, wow.
And then you go on the slides and you're just like,
there's some houses over there.
Yeah.
That breaks the immersion a little bit.
Yeah, I remember, I saw that when I was down
for that Batch the Party last summer,
which is when I did this attraction.
I broke off from the group to do it.
I chickened out of Hulk.
I'm not quite there on a haul.
That seems like exactly above the line for me.
But it was also a good excuse to go do this.
I wanted to see this.
Over the course of that is the first time that I had
the best beer in theme parks, the Island New Bar IPA.
Oh yeah.
So great, oh my God.
And it kinda like, we'd like,
there were shots before we got in the car.
So I was already a little hazy.
That Island New Bar IPA kinda fucked me up.
And it's like, sort of a, I don't know,
pretty high alcohol content, I think.
And something between that and the atmosphere of this queue,
it was like, there was just a lot,
it is scary, it's so misty and dark.
We didn't even talk about that animatronic,
the creepy lady.
Oh yeah, the shaw woman.
The shaw woman, they even say.
And that she was warning you to not, you know,
to get out of there.
And just like, I just remember, I was in such a mood
and I also was trying to hook back up with them
and failing to do so.
I didn't know if they just weren't checking their phones
or if it was a reception issue.
But so, it's all, I'm kinda in a haze.
The line is scary.
I'm starting to genuinely think,
am I gonna lose the group?
What if I have to go home by myself?
And what if my phone runs out of battery
and I don't remember how to get back to the house
with Iron Man on the wall?
And on top of it, it was becoming very clear
how much Delta was a big real threat.
So I was also thinking, I'm getting Delta right now
in this line.
This is the most claustrophobic line.
I think I even waited out a breakdown.
I think it was like, it's gonna be down for a minute
if you want and I did stay in there.
But then over the course of that,
oh, but that means I'm getting Delta.
So I'm getting, there was so much hitting me all at once
and it probably wouldn't have all been freaking me out
as much without the atmosphere of the queue.
It really did put me in a mood and transport me.
So again, it's as close as I can come
to saying an unskippable.
Because it really gave you the fear.
It gave me the fear.
Yes, and it sparked my actual, my other fears.
Buoyed by real life fears of disease and loneliness
and abandonment.
Yes, abandonment, yeah, indeed.
I know, it was a very dramatic situation.
I felt like Kate.
I worried they were all gonna be Joes
and leave me in the lurch.
You tried to explain that too to Jinx Costanza
and he's like, Delta, I've heard of some great music
coming out of the Mississippi Delta,
but I don't know what you're talking about, pal.
I don't want, I've never seen no Delta around here.
Let's keep it that way.
But the mighty Kong rescued you.
Yeah, he rescued all of us in a lot of ways.
We all fell in love with him.
We all sat in his hand in a certain way.
Yeah, he made us all stars.
We were all Kong stars that day.
If I could plus it up, because that's what I would do.
Like it's a good ride if I plus it up.
If we could somehow touch his hand or sit in his hand.
I know you're not supposed to touch stuff on rides, but.
Well, that plus up is an experience you can have
outside of a lot of wax museums.
Well, that's true.
So you could, so you got that, you could go do that.
But like, what if he put his hand up against the tram
or put up against the car and you could kind of like touch it?
Oh boy, yeah, that'd be great.
Yeah, I guess you would still like snag clothing
and somebody be ripped out accidentally maybe, but.
Yeah.
You just gotta keep it there for a while
and you're supposed to immediately understand
that this is so that you can touch him.
Well, he would say it, I think.
Touch me.
Thrill me.
Hold me, thrill me.
Kiss me, kill me.
Yeah, plus it ups, but yeah, I don't know.
It's hard to plus this up because I think, yeah,
my gripes that I've already shared is like open,
like a bigger space to see the Kong robot and.
Yeah.
And you, oh, okay.
I was gonna say, I think I have a plus up,
which is that I really like in the redone Jurassic Park
boat ride at Universal Hollywood,
the Jurassic World ride, there was like an indoor habitat.
Like.
Up at the top.
Yeah, there's kind of a jungle at night.
I would say 86, the studio tour footage,
86 that and just build a habitat in there
and use some of those screens.
Like they have some practical dinosaurs
and maybe like a small Kong in the distance.
Use some of those screens, like area screens they have
in like the Navi River journey that kind of like blend
into the practical scenery.
And I guess it's hard to be, do a big dramatic climax,
like a big fight scene, but they did something interesting
with practical stuff in a limited space.
And I just think you could do that here.
So you want to see what they actually,
now I understand what you're asking for.
You want to see a robot Kong kill the robot Vastodosaurus.
I wouldn't see the crack in real life.
You want to see the robot have its jaw come unhinged.
You want that sound to be coming from the robot.
Yeah, that's the tough, it is tough
because so much of this stuff when you like action wise,
it's so hard to do that with the robots, almost impossible.
So it is tricky.
I mean, what you're saying, I think you could do it,
but I feel like you'd have to do it the whole time.
You'd have to get, you have to like get the audience used
to the reality of the ride with like screens and robots.
So like if the climax, I like the idea.
It's just, yeah, it would be like a little jarring maybe,
but maybe not.
My plus up isn't for this, it's for volcano bay.
It's you make it Skull Island.
Oh wow.
You reshape the volcano and it's,
then it's you're in King Kong's stomach
and the water on all the sides is his stomach.
Also he's the, it's not, the volcano is not on Skull Island.
He is the volcano.
Yeah, yeah.
You turn him into the volcano.
I guess you have to, you give him a head or something,
but yeah, you're crawling, you're,
any slide that you're going on, you're lost in his innards.
So he-
Sure, it's still more feasible
than when they were gonna try to build a King Kong
that you would board and then would climb the stratosphere.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, that's such a cool idea.
That is great.
So the volcano, I just wanna go back to the volcano
real quick, cause like they do a little show
where the volcano erupts every so often.
So Kong would have some sort of acid reflux
every 45 minutes and like throw up bile
to the people in the wave pool.
That's him vomiting, yeah.
But it's good, you know, it's good
cause it adds more acid to the wave pool.
Add more acid to the wave pool.
And then every, you know, there's only,
you start up there at the top of his body,
there's only so many ways out.
So you're trying to, every slide is trying to get out
of King Kong's dick or butt.
Okay, that's good.
Yeah.
If you, as long as you can touch his hand,
in that instance, I think I would be fine with it.
Definitely, because yeah, look, I'm here thinking dirty.
You want soft intimacy.
I want soft intimacy.
I think there's room for both
at this new improved Skull Island Park.
Okay, so Skull Island is the official
third park of Universal.
Yes, now that I would, yeah.
Once they do this.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Ride the movies, slide the stomach acid.
You survived podcast the right, I think.
You've survived.
If you've been listening, you were just like,
tumbling around inside of our stomach acid,
our guts, our brain, our brain acid, I really should say,
inside of our skulls.
And you lighting up a couple flares
is when I go like, oh, my stomach, my stomach hurts.
Let us out of this Bill Maher heavy episode.
What have I done?
And yet I'm gonna encourage people to go back in
and slosh around some more because you can find us
on all the socials at podcast the ride.
There's merch is available in our T public store.
And for three bonus episodes every month,
check out podcast the ride the second gate
or get one more monthly bonus episode
on our new tier club three.
You'll find all that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Might bear mentioning in this one, the quick programming.
But if you want a sense of what's going on
on the new tier in club three, the third,
the earned third park of podcast the ride.
So we're the one more monthly bonus episode
beyond what you already get on the second gate.
We just did our first poll of what are those topics
going to be narrowed it down to five.
We got to hundreds of great ideas from everybody.
But the the King Kong, the ults of the the one to beat
by far was the topic suggestion.
Eva Anderson talks about whatever she wants.
One by a landslide by a stomach acid slide.
And I just want to say that's common.
Eva has been, we have reached out to Eva.
We've sent up the Eva flare.
She responded like a bunch of skull island bats.
She overnighted us a box full of crocodile bones.
That could really mean anything coming from you.
It'll make sense when we do it.
So I just want to, I hype that up.
That'll be coming at some point in July.
It might even take a minute to come together.
So be patient, but that'll be coming in July
on club three that's at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
We hand hand things over to Eva,
which probably might be the best choice.
The listeners are really trying to tell us something here.
Hey, what do you want us to talk about?
Why don't you let someone else?
Someone else decide you monsters.
You vast the sources.
Yeah. So, so that's fun.
Whatever it is, is fun.
I know, I know that.
Yeah, yeah.
We're going to figure it out.
The expedition begins.
And real quick, I just want to say if, you know,
Peter Jackson talking about Peter Jackson,
and you know, we just did get back,
which was, we all watched obviously
over the Christmas break.
If you want to hear a discussion about it,
Sammy and Bill talk about it on club random
and they have some interesting takes on it.
Did the Beatles, were the Beatles important
to those guys growing up?
But not the frighteners.
They don't touch on the frighteners.
I haven't finished it yet,
but so far they have not touched on the frighteners.
It's not so much about the Peter Jackson.
No, okay.
I don't, yeah, I don't know.
But big up back, yes.
All I know is that it broke Sammy's heart
and it was hard for him to watch.
Well, he's had some band strife of his own.
Maybe we'll get a documentary about that one.
That's what he says.
Fingers crossed.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.
Thanks for watching.
We'll see you next time.