Club Three.
Welcome for the very first time to podcast the Ride and the Ride and the Ride.
Welcome for the very first time to podcast the Ride Club Three, the new exclusive VIP
club within podcast the Ride, the second gate.
I'm Scott Gartner, Mike Carlson made it.
You're still here.
I'm here and I'm in the lap of luxury in this new club of ours.
I'm loving it.
I'm loving the extra theming.
Jason Sheridan also in that lap.
By the skin of my teeth.
By the skin of your teeth, you made it.
I made it.
Because I fucked up the time.
Jason was late to our first Club Three.
I was late to Club Three.
You know, I left my house at 1 p.m. and I was like, ooh, I'm going to be early.
Nice.
I texted you.
I texted something as I was parked waiting and then you immediately texted back and I
didn't see your car here and I went, uh-oh.
Uh-oh, that's right.
I was like, you shouldn't be texting and driving.
Is everything okay?
Well, it was reading.
Siri read it to me.
Do you have Siri read your texts?
Sometimes you can say, hey, Siri read my messages.
I've done it, but I don't often do it.
Yeah.
But doesn't it?
Well, that's like a car.
That's a way to be, because otherwise it takes longer, I think.
Oh yeah.
No, it's a pain.
To say that and then have it slowly.
I could see though, Jason doing that because he gets too tired reading.
Said he'd rather have Siri read it to him.
I know.
I'll tell you, the response, the autocorrect dictation response has gotten so bad on the
iPhone.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
I found out it's because it stopped learning your behaviors and now it's sourcing it from
everyone.
The algorithm is sourcing common mistakes from a pool.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, weird.
That's why it's like you start typing I-L-O and it's like, I logged you?
Did you mean I logged?
Wait, you're saying that most of the population are not writing love you?
They're saying I log you?
I'm not saying most of the population is.
I'm saying the algorithm is somehow assuming like you start typing L-O.
They think it's logged.
I've gotten like logged as a replacement a few times recently.
Hmm.
Think this would happen to us?
I don't know.
I turn my like suggestion stuff off.
Yeah, a lot of people have it turned off nowadays.
So I don't have it to fill in there.
But L-O look, I'm not getting log.
Everyone try it at home though.
You'll know.
Maybe it's maybe there's a lot of log with I guess not me but with that because we've
talked about logs a lot.
We've talked about sopping wet logs and taking your socks off in the law.
Of course.
Sure.
You know, the phone's picked up a lot of log talk over the years.
Yeah, that's true.
I guess we thank you for logging.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for logging into.
Patreon and upping your status to be here to hear some of this log talk.
You can tell the how special this episode is already because of the log extra log talk
up top.
Yeah, that's the kind of quality you're getting from not probably not the last log talk of
today.
Of course not.
Yeah.
More log talk to be.
Did you like my voice one?
I like that.
Yeah, no, I like that.
Well, one of the one of the 10 this should be up right is that slow motion video of Mike
taking the socks off.
Yeah, log.
We did film.
We went and filmed that with like a Phantom camera.
We snuck one of the like the Top Gun IMAX cameras into a log so that we had it in really
perfect even low light in the low light of the low log.
Yeah, yeah.
The same technology used in Top Gun, the new one and escape from what tomorrow?
What's that?
The Disney gorilla?
Yeah, we made kind of a combo escape from tomorrow.
Yeah, gun, but two of the finest films ever made.
We should make our own escape from tomorrow in the park to shoot over like 10 years.
So it's not a crazy like undertaking.
Yeah, yeah.
We're all right.
Yeah, then we're not sneaking around.
Yeah, it's just 15 minutes at a time.
That's a good idea.
We're going to do.
Okay.
Well, that'll be here.
We'll release it completely here.
Anyway, the point is thanks for being here.
Thank you also, Aaron Gardner for the new logo and the name club three.
You have all made it to the deepest rung of podcasts.
The ride.
Look how deep we've all gotten.
We're all here together.
And what I like about this, what I think we could be doing here and what I think I, what
I hope that this feels like is like this is a party where everyone knows each other, where
no one has to be introduced to each other.
We don't have to sell it like, oh, you haven't met so and so.
No, we've all met.
We're very acquainted if we're all here now.
This is an Aaron suggestion was we don't even say our names at the top.
They know we just start talking.
That's pretty good.
Go straight into the show.
All right, let's get right into it.
We got to get that fluoride out of the water.
Okay.
If you're here, you agree that I need now.
I don't need that's deep.
That's too deep for me.
What's up with fluoride?
That's just a conspiracy thing.
That's not a Disney.
There wasn't a big fluoride spill in pirates.
No, no, no.
No, that's just how people think like the fluoride in the tap water.
They do put fluoride in tap water.
Yes, they do.
That is confirmed.
But some people have conspiracy theories about what it's doing to us, etc.
So yeah, Jason was getting down a conspiracy theory rabbit hole already, which is what
he's made.
He's promising from his angle of this new tier, he's going to start giving you his unfiltered
opinions.
It's spirit or raw opinions.
Yeah.
Yeah, back and forth between Disneyland sing alongs and Building 7, the truth.
You're going to find it out.
And then we'll lead a sing along at the end of an original song that's about the truth
about Building 7.
Exactly.
But so anyway, so here's, let's do a little bit of protocol here with that in mind being
that this is a, it's a swanky club where we all know each other.
I think, and we chose the topic for today's episode, which is Disney sing along songs,
the 1990 videotape.
From here on out, the topics will be selected by you, the audience.
And what we need now, this is now we're doing the top of an improv show.
What we need is a quick suggestion, but a really specific, we're going to do lots of
specific improv shows.
So what we do need everyone is a suggestion.
So in the comments below this episode, that's that this is what I'm preparing.
We haven't talked about the protocols here exactly.
Right.
But I think go into the comments of this and leave your idea of the most deep, obscure,
insane, indulgent slice, like small sliver even, like how we, you know, we like to do.
If there's one specific robots on pirate, like we already did one robots on pirates,
but honestly, one of the robots on pirates, not obscure enough for me.
That's a very famous ride.
So really get into creative, interesting, as far as your choices are concerned.
I think so.
Yes.
If you've passed, if you've been in the parks and seen a tree with a root that was weird
or that almost tripped you.
We're going to do, we want to go do an episode about that root.
That's right.
Specific trash cans.
Yes.
Specific umbrellas.
Let's talk shade.
How do you throw shade at shade providers?
Do you want us to taste the different waters on the different rides?
I'm not saying we're going to do it.
I'm just saying that's an interesting idea.
We'll see how much fluoride is in each ride.
You know, if, as we're talking about today, is there a really specific old video or special
you want to send us to watch that we can all talk about together?
You know, some weird ride that's really regional and nobody knows about.
Is it a method of, as with making us drink the water, is it a method of torturing us?
Yes.
That you could send us to do.
And I know what I'm opening myself up to here because I've provided a lot of possible ways
to torture me.
I don't want to start saying what they are, but if you want to, you know, send us on little
missions, whatever, whatever it is, things that would test the patience of even the regular
second gate subscriber.
An episode about just the sexy robot on the cover of Aerosmith's Just Push Play.
Something like that is what I'm saying.
I know what you're, yeah.
Jason knows what I mean.
This is my guy right here.
That guy right here.
Yeah.
That could be in the future Revolution X episode.
Sure.
What?
No, it's, oh no, it's own episode.
Oh, that's its own episode.
Just the robot.
No, sexy Just Push Play robot, its own episode.
I feel like we have to regulate the amount of Aerosmith specific because there's a lot,
there's a lot that could be done.
Yeah.
They can't all, we're going to, I think we're going to lose people if more than one a quarter
is Aerosmith, unless I'm wrong.
Maybe we will see.
We'll look at the comments and it will be entirely Aerosmith.
Yeah, who knows?
If you will.
We will find out.
And now I'm looking at this robot even.
Yeah, I guess, well, oh, she's, it's like a Marilyn.
Yeah, the sexy robot is like Marilyn.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a robotic Marilyn.
So that, yeah, anyway, you know what to do.
You know the runners, you know the deep specifics, and I think it's time to get down and dirty
and do all of it.
I think, you know, I think we can all agree that we would like, it's a club, it's a podcast
club.
We really want this to be our Club Random.
Yeah.
Which if we haven't, I don't, now I don't remember if we've talked about Club Random much on
the show.
I don't think we have it all.
Maybe we have.
This is just, this is just a frequent topic of conversation off the show.
You're already, I assume you're all already listening to Club Random or watching at Bill
Mars podcast done in the part of the basement, the part of his basement that's decorated,
the part that the bodies are in.
Yes.
You don't need that.
You don't need to make it look super nice.
That's the, you're only gonna, you're only attracting bugs over there.
Yeah.
It's the part where he bought a neon sign that blows out the camera and fucks the lighting
and the rest of the room.
Which is where he poorly reads ad copy in an awkwardly staged way.
Hey, none of that here.
No ads here on the, that's where you can listen again to the main feed episodes without ads.
So if you want at gunpoint ad reads, you gotta go to Club Random for that.
Yeah.
Gotta go look up Bill Mars.
Not Club Three.
No, not here.
But yeah, we're, and I think we'll share a lot of, you know, we're working on booking
everyone Bill Mars had.
So Dr. Drew will be here.
Who else is he?
Dr. Drew will be here a couple of times at least.
Who else has been on?
The woman who seemed very uncomfortable.
Was it Bella Thorne?
A woman, a woman seeming uncomfortable.
You'll have to be more specific.
Yeah.
Most of them have not been on video.
They've not been on digital video.
But anyway, yeah.
So Holly Mandel will be here.
Who's recently talked about how scared he is to be canceled.
Disgusting as, yeah.
You know, people are attacking the comedians and the logical order is Rock, Chappelle,
Mandel.
Where else, who else is going to get?
Who else?
Yeah.
And people know he doesn't like to be touched.
So that's an equal.
That's a level that's true.
That Chappelle and Rock didn't have to deal with.
That's a good point.
So yeah, they'll be here.
They'll be here buying the paywall.
They'll all be here.
But anyway, so give us your, and we'll figure out exactly how we're some here, but please
give us your episode topics.
What do you want out of out of us and out of Club 3?
I think we'll do some sort of poll as well.
So it'll all be done within this Patreon app and log in and whatever.
Sorry.
It's just the most efficient.
What was that?
Sorry you had to go to the Patreon website.
Is it that bad?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
It's just never been good.
I mean, it works.
It's solid.
I have no beef with the Patreon website.
Is it confusing, the website?
I think it's a little confusing.
Okay.
I don't realize.
I want to know your whole air, all the gripes.
I bet there's some anecdote in there.
I bet there's some anecdote in there that we're not getting at.
There was something years ago where they were going to start charging people extra fees
and stuff and then they got yelled at so much they dropped it.
Yeah, that's true.
I think you go to Patreon thinking you could subscribe to Club Random and it was not there.
Is that why you wanted to give your $20 a month to Club Random, but it wasn't available.
I think the fees ended up, I think it was sales tax, which I think a lot of states imposed.
I think you do it to pay sales tax now.
Well, it is not.
That's the government.
If we really want to get into the reality, it is not a good business for them, the Patreon.
We can't say that here on Patreon.
Sorry, sorry.
Yeah.
Don't let them know.
Anyway.
Okay.
So we'll do some sort of poll and we'll narrow it down and figure out next month's topic
that way and beyond that and beyond that.
That's the idea.
But for now, let's talk about what we're here to talk about.
The one that we've in a draconian manner imposed upon you.
The Disney sing along songs, Disneyland fun video from 1990 and which I would have to
imagine at least of people of a certain age.
I imagine this is kind of a linchpin.
This was like a big, this was a way to experience Disneyland and the comfort of your own home.
That was the appeal of this tape to me.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I'm sure I'm repeating myself to some degree because we've briefly touched on this.
This was for a Disney World family, a time that you got to see the place you'd never
go.
Oh, I hadn't even thought about that.
Yeah.
Nice.
Yes.
So you would, oh, I do, like you'd see, oh, that is the different castle.
Okay.
I'm never going to see that with my own eyes, but that there, that's what it looks like.
That's what their haunted mansion looks like.
Sure.
Okay.
Interesting.
So it was a glimpse into a forbidden world in my mind.
You assumed that your life would be, at eight years old, you assumed that your life would
be too boring to ever allow you to go to Disneyland.
It just didn't make sense.
It didn't make sense.
It didn't make sense until I moved here.
It didn't make sense until I was 23 that I would go to Disneyland.
How would that ever happen?
A lot all the time.
Yeah.
Solo for work with a laptop.
No, I would never have dreamed I would have been there over like 200 times.
Maybe it's too, it's got to be 200.
I mean, 150 I think.
To try to count.
I have no idea.
The annual passes were counting up until a certain point, but then it's, the data is
in there, but God knows, go Disney.com, whatever, go.com.
It's probably like destroyed all the information at a certain point.
Oh, we should do a deep dive on go.com.
That's an interesting one.
Yeah, that's good actually.
How in the world is it still the case that you go to Disneyland.com and then like ding,
ding, ding, and you have to dial into go.com?
From the app too, it's like, oh, it should just be in the app where you make changes.
No, it takes you then to the website, which then you have to log into go.com.
Then it takes you back to the app.
You can't do everything in app.
It's still this like mishmash of technologies from 25 years ago.
Yeah.
Yeah, it sucks.
There are situations where you're trying to book going for the day at all or book a restaurant
or whatever.
Oh, I found a time.
Oh my God.
I found a time.
Please log into Disney.
No, no, no.
You get an email.
I saw my name at the top.
It said, welcome Scott.
I don't need to do this again.
And you get an email when you log in.
Yes.
Someone has logged.
Oh, that's right.
We never localized that.
Every time you log in to Disneyland.
Someone has logged in.
Yeah, me.
Please.
Does it like every day.
I mean, it's like a real two factor authentication kind of emails.
Like there's not a code in that email.
I was just telling you.
It's just an email saying, hey, you logged in?
Yeah, of course I did.
Yeah.
I guess, that's a common thing with Patreon.
There's a lot of like, did you mean to log in?
Yes.
Yeah.
Get used to me.
I go here.
So you never could have dreamed back when you were a kid that you would have gripes
about technology that hadn't been invented yet.
Never.
I never knew.
About a park that you might never go to.
In my wildest dreams.
I would be something that I would prefer this park.
Yeah.
I am.
It's interesting to hear you guys talk about like watching this at home because Jane told
me the same thing like in her house.
They just ran this tape like all the time.
They were watching this thing.
That was not my experience.
We did not have this at home.
The music teacher at school had it.
And when there was a substitute or she just was checked out, checked out.
This was going on the TV.
Wow.
What a school victory.
Although, yeah, similar to Mike, I was sitting there going like, wow, this must be the Disneyland
Castle.
It looks so small.
Like, because just growing up in the 90s, you were just bombarded with those flyover,
you know, stock images of the castle in Florida.
Yeah.
So it's teaching you to settle.
And then you go like, oh, the Haunted Mansion looks different too.
Yeah.
They do a splash mountain.
This was educational.
Yes.
Footage for both of you.
And it was, yeah, it was, I guess it wasn't even aspirational because it wasn't a possibility.
Yeah.
It wasn't even, oh, wow.
One day.
No, it was just like, okay, cool.
This is like looking at a document from like 300 years ago or something where I go, okay,
great.
I'm glad I have a record of this.
Yeah.
When they put a montage of the Indiana Jones ride in like a parade one year, you're like,
Oh, I bet that's nice.
I bet that'd be nice.
Must be nice.
I'll never know.
So yeah, that's, that's what it was.
I mean, in addition to this is, yeah, I didn't realize what a psychological study this is.
I mean, I wasn't, I don't even want to make it.
I was not even a thought.
It wasn't even like I was so upset about it.
I was like, great.
Like, so yeah, I don't even want to make it seem like I was like, oh, I'm begging mom
to go there.
I just didn't think it made sense.
You weren't invested in yourself.
You didn't believe in yourself.
We went to Disney every three or four years.
We went to Wisconsin Dells like once and we went to like Galena in Illinois for like a
night or two.
And now I think we went to Dubuque, Iowa.
We ended up in like Dubuque, Iowa for like some small trip and it was like all club three
possibilities.
Just wanted to register if you want to put in a vote for Mike's trip to Dubuque.
If you want.
Yeah.
We took some sort of a boat trip and a lot of it was, I remember it being depressing.
I remember being sad.
So, yeah, if you want to, if you want a depressing episode, you just want it might be the episode
we need right now in these dark times.
That's a good point.
Like, so yeah, so, so it was just, yeah, it was a fun thing to see at least stuff that
looked like Disney World and to see all the favorites, the characters and then enjoy.
I would say half the songs, because some of the songs I didn't care about, but it was
enough stuff in there.
That was, I would definitely say it was the best of all the sing along song.
Oh, for sure.
Cause I had a few of these.
They definitely had a good little like, you know, round up of these sing along song tapes,
which if you didn't have them or didn't grow up with them, it's a follow the bouncing
ball situation pioneered by sing along with Mitch, I believe that was the old show that
invented this.
Am I making that up?
Sing along with Mitch.
I think that's right.
Yes.
No, that's, that's the correct name.
I think that was the first follow the bouncing ball situation on television in the fifties,
it seems like.
And if you don't know what we're talking about, like they would put the lyrics to a song on
the bottom of the screen and then a ball would bounce to basically indicate when you should
be singing the line or the word that's on happening at that moment.
I guess.
Sort of a karaoke is as popularized in America around the same time, not always a ball.
Sometimes it's the words are lighten up.
Sometimes the words are growing one by one.
Sometimes they get real creative with it.
Sometimes they're popping up all the frame.
We see a lot of creative uses of the words in this video.
Yeah, it was really exciting watching it develop.
Like it was so exciting over there, like a bowling alley footage, like strike, like if
you ever saw that, like if you bowl a strike and there's a little CG animated thing.
Oh baby.
I did a whole there's a moonbeam city, but all that shit.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
And then the local news, the local news graphics develop over time.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Well, I think I glommed on to anything of that nature and valued them more than anything
with a lot.
It's probably warped my brain, my like it being aware I've done a lot of things that
are set in the eighties and nineties.
And my biggest issue is like, we've got to get that drop shadow, right?
That thick black drop shadow at the bottom of that yellow text.
Cause I see a lot of things meant to be in that era.
And sometimes you don't sell that realism without that drop shadow.
And this thing is drop shadow aplenty.
Yeah, I know exactly what you're talking about.
What's funny now watching these tapes and especially one that's not like this one, I
think is probably easily the most budget needed video because they're shooting a lot of original
footage, but we've even watching this and then watching the other ones that are just
compilations of actual movies and TV stuff.
These are the cheapest made things in the world.
And it's so obvious to me now, cause as a kid that doesn't really register.
You can kind of tell when something has high production value as a kid, but it doesn't,
you don't, it's like not make or break for your enjoyment of something.
But to watch them now, you really feel like, Oh God, they were just, we had to get this
done.
We have to shoot this thing.
It doesn't look, I mean, it looks, I don't know, worse than like just a regular show
on ABC at the time, maybe.
Yeah, I'd say so.
It's really, yeah.
And it was kind of part of an effort.
I feel like to like throughout the seventies and eighties, there's stuff on TV that Disney's
doing that's recontextualizing the old movies, putting clips together.
Yes.
There are all these DTV specials that was their response to MTV.
Where can we, I remember watching one a lot that was based on romance was for Valentine's
Day.
So let's cut a bunch of the Disney movies and shorts into a little romance oriented.
Here's a music video for let's hear it for the boy, based on Mickey and Minnie's love.
So there was all that.
And then this seems like a next step of like, well, how do we, because we can only release
these things so much and get them out of the vault so much.
There's a lot of complication with that.
So but how do we use this library and crank a lot of shit out of it?
They came up with this and which like works like gangbusters for me because like the way
kids there's times when you're a dumb kid, you're like, I don't care about that story.
I just want the songs.
Yes.
So a video that's only songs, that's just all hits in a row.
Great.
Love it.
Yeah.
I mean, it also in the Disney war book, they go into a little, they were very confused
and scared of the VHS market.
The first Disney feature VHS's were so expensive because they were so enamored with the idea
of the Disney vault.
They're like, well, we can't just give this away.
When they didn't want it to cut into the reissue, the theatrical reissue market, which was still
big.
Yeah.
And the theatrical releases at all, just being a big moneymaker.
And then eventually they, they realized like, oh, the VHS market prints money and we can
also just cut up clips and make a new thing kind of similar to how Walt would make little
anthology movies with a little live action, a little animation, a little bit of stuff
and release that as like a theatrical release.
Yeah.
And boy, this is like one of the most successful, you know, uses of that methodology that I
would say the cheapness that you're describing, Mike, I feel like is very evident in the opening
song, which it did occur to me to way later that this, this sequence with the owl rushing
to the classroom of birds to go teach the, the sing along.
So all the wraparounds are with this character, professor owl.
Yes.
And I don't, I don't know.
It must've been way later that I realized that is this pre, that's a preexisting short.
That's something from the fifties that is just dubbed over.
Even though we all be so much more associated with this sequence, which we all watch so
many times on all these videos.
I remember that.
I don't remember the moment, but I do remember becoming aware of something was up with that
because his mouth doesn't quite move right.
And then I think maybe even in school and elementary school, someone actually showed
us the original fifties, like what they kind of like, they were not, they were not sing
alongs.
They were just like educational videos.
So I saw one of them and I went, oh, okay.
And then it made sense.
I mean, I even remember like watching Ninja Turtles and like, you would start to get,
you start to get like a hint that these were not just like, born out of the ground, that
there were errors being made.
Cause like you'd see Raphael would be talking and his headband would be purple and you'd
be like, ah, like, and I think you would ignore that.
But like when you're seven or eight or then you're starting to realize, okay, wait, there's
okay. That's a yeah, that's wrong.
Something's off with this.
A child's imagination fills in stuff like all the frames that weren't animated, where
they were standing still.
And the rest is filled in by like, you know, talking about being an average with graphics
and design. I would just stare at video game boxes like the front and the backs, the cards
that action figures came on.
Like it was an easy skip to a comic book problem.
It started as a collection.
It's now a problem.
So, yeah, the wonkiness very clear now.
I sure love that opening sequence.
And it seems like we've talked about this a little bit, but I feel like that the sing
along songs opening theme, big influence on your theme song.
Yes. Yeah.
The main theme of the show.
Like a little drum.
Yeah. Which is like that's like some Disney drum machine.
It is very 80s.
And yes, really like just like, yeah, rigid and digital clearly.
But like very, very energetic.
Yeah. Yeah. I always love that that reference point.
Really like the song in general.
I'm right.
Yes.
The dunce, the dunce cap bird.
Dumb. They had dubbed over the dunce cap bird.
Most dubbed. The most clearly dubbed.
Very dubbed. Yeah.
They could have dubbed it better, too.
Like when you watch it, you go, they could have like really matched it.
I feel like.
But again, we might be to describe they might have had a day on all this.
I'm sure they did get it out with the deal memos they were working with.
They could not have done it better.
That's a good point.
It was a miracle. It got done at all.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
That's probably correct.
I had never I looked through the credits of this specific sing along songs video.
I had never wondered or looked up who did this song.
The Disney sing along songs, main theme song, the composer, somebody named
it could be Patrick Derrimer.
It could be Patrick DeRamer.
I don't know if that's a D or a so I'm probably saying it wrong either way.
But either regardless, that composer who wrote this song
together with a guy named Roy Freeland wrote a little song called I to I
in a goofy movie.
Oh, wow.
Same guy to major.
Like where Disney got it right, where they're doing 80s drum machine.
Yeah, that's super catchy.
And then 90s New Jack.
Wow. Prince adjacent.
That's so good.
Yeah. Yeah. Never knew that was the same guy.
Yeah. Between those two songs, major Disney composer and musician.
Yeah, that's great.
I to I, you know, the best.
What do we say?
I've tried to unofficially rank Disney songs in general, but it's hard.
You have to put them in little little categories because it's like movie songs,
ride songs.
And I think I said what a certain point I declared like I to I and part of their
world are the top two.
Is it part of your world?
I always forget your part of your world.
So yeah.
So those are my top two.
And then as far as rides, it's Sinbad.
Sinbad song and and and that song.
Yeah, just Sinbad. OK, sure.
No, there's no other.
They also the same pair wrote the song Stand Out in Goofy Goofy.
Yeah. Yeah.
And also and this guy also wrote all the songs on the totally mini album,
which I was not really familiar with.
There's a song called Video Active that's pretty.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
All a different video active.
Yeah. Yeah. And I'm trying to think if they play that,
because Lindsay, right before the pandemic, we went to a retro night at Disneyland
and it was totally many was there.
And it was just we were dancing with many over by the Tomorrowland stage.
To memory to hold to get you through the pandemic.
And so and I don't think they played that one.
They definitely played the totally mini theme over and over again.
Yeah. Which is also good.
She might have done. I'm not sure.
Probably worth doing a deep dive into that.
That's true. I have one more personnel thing on this video,
which I think is interesting.
The director of it, Michael Dimich, is his name.
Longtime director for prices, right.
And Ellen, don't hold that one against him.
But I but the most interesting thing in this guy's body of work,
he directed six specials from the master of magic, David Copperfield,
including the one where he escapes from a building that implodes,
which came up in our implosion.
We have previously discussed the directorial work of Michael Dimich.
He's he is walking out David Copperfield's one shot escape
and then also directing these kids on Splash Mountain
and Roger looking scared before he's even on a ride.
Tellable moments in the body of work of this man.
So Michael Dimich, the director of everything.
There's like a hundred like the more we do this podcast, the more I'm like,
oh, there's like a hundred people that we talk about.
Yes, like a finite amount of people.
And it's all them all.
But there's like a hundred people.
Michael Jackson's involved in everything, too, somehow.
And it's a real like I was saying at one point, a real like
real building kind of like, yeah, these people were all in the same spot
and just writing these songs.
And that was their job.
And they probably clocked in and clocked out and then went home.
You know, of course. Yeah.
Mm hmm. Not knowing that people would be gripping on to these things
for the rest of their lives.
Discussing them in too much detail, as we will do now with the
sing along songs video.
I mean, we can sort of step through the through it in order if you want,
but also just throw out, you know, if there's just like, I want to get to this.
This is the highlight. Well, yeah, yeah.
Well, I'll say the first thing and I'm repeating myself to some degree
is that what I liked about this is that it gave the impression,
which I always liked, that the characters worked at Disneyland.
Sure. A kid I liked.
I didn't want any humans working there.
I wanted my favorite characters to be putting in a nine to five long shift.
Work in the rise, work in the register.
I like I like the idea was completely populated by cartoon characters.
And that's sort of what they're indicating in this opening thing
when all the characters are basically like cleaning up and preparing
Disneyland for the day.
Yeah. To whistle while you work. Right.
And they're literally sweeping,
windexing things like shining things.
Yeah. Mickey's got like kind of a lab coat on, which.
That's an interesting. Yeah. It's not standard Mickey look for sure.
Yeah. And I'm not sure.
Yeah. I guess that's like his janitorial.
He's not but he's not wearing like a one onesie or anything.
Well, he's you know, he's spiffing is what he's doing.
Spick and spanning.
He's not I feel like he's not doing the hard clean like the hard rhyme.
It's just like let me get a little less bit of polish on that.
So, yeah. So Mickey is not yeah.
Mickey is not cleaning up puke from the night before.
Mickey is just making sure there's a little like polish on the railings
or something. He's he's trying to make
these little touches.
He's trying to get that little special touch before people come in.
But yeah, all the friends are out. They're all working.
Yeah. And as a kid, it was like this is correct.
This is what I want.
I don't want humans involved in Disney, Disney World or Disneyland.
Yeah. You don't want them.
You don't want Disneyland to be a job provider.
No. You want to make you want the grandfathered in characters to be.
Yes. To be doing the partners as you if you were total immersion.
I mean, I'm sure I said it during when Star Wars and Galaxy's Edge opened
and they were saying everything was in universe and people would speak in the
in the Batuu local language and say, like, that's what I wanted.
I wanted it to be like everybody worked like they wouldn't acknowledge the real world.
So, yeah. So how would that even enter your head that you it was because
did this video create the fantasy or before this video, were you thinking,
boy, I really hope Donald did all the scrubbing of this Dumbo ride?
I don't think I was thinking janitorial work was what I wanted the characters to do.
I don't think that was part of it where I was like, I want I want to make sure
that Donald clean these toilets before I use them.
I think it was more along the lines of I want complete and total immersion
in Toonland. I want to live in tune.
Because when Toon Town was presented as a concept, that was the most
I was obsessed with any idea.
So I think it was literally just like I would like to live where Darkwing Duck
lives, get me out of this real world. Sure.
And you kind of get it at the end of the video, too, when they all like turn around
and walk towards the castle at the end of the night.
Yeah. The carousel, if you pay, if you look closely
in at least some of the shots, the carousel is moving.
So, right. Like as if they're like, well, time to hang it up for the night.
Let's go back to where we live. Right.
And I say, right.
Gepetto and Pinocchio sleep on the carousel.
Yeah. Turn the lights off and
pick a horse to lean against. Sounds good to me.
I'd love to be lulled to sleep by a carousel every night.
Set it on low. Yeah. Just a slow role.
Replace one of the benches with a bed.
Oh, I mean, I could price I could probably sleep on that bench.
Yeah, I could probably share fetal position on a bench.
But yeah, you got Chip and Dale goofing around with the popcorn machine.
Roger. Lotta Roger.
Well, that's when he was one of the core.
Yeah. When he was one of the main characters.
It's really weird. It's like the how, you know, I might have said this before,
but it's like when there was, you know, due to contractual negotiations,
that there was like an extra there was a save by the bell person
for like six episodes. Yeah. Kind of never showed up again.
It is interesting. It's weird when you just forget about a friend.
No longer around. Yeah.
And yeah, he's he is treated with just as much respect as the other main.
What? Five, six.
Yeah. The fab.
What do they call them? Six.
Is it the spectacular six?
I've never heard that.
Like there is there is a Disney wiki entry.
I have read about this because it's Mickey, Minnie, Donald, Pluto,
since the general sensation and Daisy.
But then Chip and Dale are also in the mix.
Yeah, I guess they're not in a Pluto's and we might be missing.
Yeah. Pluto's not in the mail, not in the sensational six.
So it's Mickey, Minnie, Goofy, Donald, Daisy.
And then who's the last one? Pluto.
Oh, Pluto is OK. He's on the six. OK.
And this would priorities would kind of change as the company's fortunes would
like we're pushing these right now.
Or like we bought a greeting card company.
Oh, they might buy us like, you know, like
the shifting fortunes of the 80s into the 90s.
Yeah, that's when they let that Hallmark lady into the cranky old
seven cranky old hallmark.
I mean, I believe that's right. Yeah.
Maxine was briefly in the if you did she have a show Maxine?
I think she did. I believe she did.
Or they are pilot might have been a pilot for UPN or something like that.
A lot of very interesting and like like all things forgotten or lost.
I don't mean good, but interesting.
Maxine, I think, would fall into that.
Mm hmm. Did you find three?
There was a special, it seems. OK.
Yeah. Seen's Christmas Carol. OK.
I've never seen it. She is the Scrooge in this situation.
It's like the two prime time far side specials,
which at the back of the page a day calendar, they were like,
you can buy VHS of these forty dollars, like forty dollars each.
Weird. Yeah.
I think maybe I think Tress McNeil may have been.
Oh, wow. Great.
Of course. The best of the best, you know.
It's on YouTube. We'll figure it out.
We'll check that out. Could be a club three.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So so, yeah, I like this.
Oh, this is one of my favorite parts as a kid.
This opening here, I would say.
And ready. They do a great job.
They do a great job.
They're goofing around to they're having some fun doing doing what they're doing.
Well, many setting out a lot of Mickey dolls.
Yes. Donald comes in and pushes them all out of the way.
It puts a lot of Donald dolls in there.
Yeah. I mean, if we're really going to follow the logic,
is this something Donald is doing every day because that is exhausting?
It would be exhausting if he's constantly every single day,
every single day, and he's like, oh, damn it.
Yeah. Come on, man. We have the numbers.
We have the quarterly numbers.
So this guy's so well, but you don't sell. OK.
You know what else is nice to see and especially here a little bit,
but throughout the special is the 35th anniversary logo.
Yeah. Some wonderful neon, some wonderful colors.
You can feel the 35th anniversary spirit. Oh, yeah.
In the air. Just nice to see.
You like to see it after this.
You go to the song walking right down the middle of Main Street, USA.
Now, even as a kid, minus the profanity,
I think my thought was, what the fuck is this song?
I also agree with you. Yeah.
I was like, huh?
I don't know this one.
I know whistle while you work.
And then later I know this was written in ghosts.
But what is this?
This was maybe fast forward for me.
It's always going to hear something from Jason here.
Oh, this was a song I totally memory hold until a few years ago.
And I was going through some boxes and I found
from like 2004, 2005, a two CD set of the soundtrack of Walt Disney World.
And that song is on there.
And I was like, I was,
you know, putting putting the CD, the files on my computer.
I was like listening through them.
And I was like, what the fuck is this song?
And we're all but everyone's mad at this.
So then I had no recollection of this song.
Jane was like, yeah, she's like, I have friends who they used to do that.
Like they would do that and show or they would do that on Main Street.
There'd be singers on Main Street or so or the dapper dance do it.
But this is this is one of the songs and I made a note of this
when I was watching it earlier.
This is a perfect song to tap to.
And they're like there's tapping going on in the sort of like tap dancing.
I'm talking about. Yeah.
And sort of they got the penguins from Mary Poppins involved in this.
And I thought if you had seen this as a kid, Jason,
this would have been your favorite because of the tap potential.
Mary Poppins was a movie I knew almost entirely
from specials and videos like this and stuff.
OK, so you were not Mary Poppins.
I was not a Mary Poppins kid.
I didn't really know what Burt's deal was.
I knew the penguins, the penguins were clipped.
You know, they were in a lot of stuff.
They'd be in. Did you care for that?
I mean, what Burt's deal was?
I didn't know who I didn't know his name.
I didn't know what his significance was to the movie. Wow.
I know. I I guess I knew a little.
I knew he was a chimney sweep from the great movie ride.
And I probably knew more that it was Dick Van Dyke
because I watched a lot of Dick Van Dyke show on Nick at Night growing up.
That's interesting that you didn't manage to remain hidden with all this.
You're interested from every angle.
And he has like he's got the stuff you like the straw hat.
They like suit. Yeah. Like you with any taps and stuff.
Yeah, that's interesting.
I know. I think I was also confused as a kid of like,
why does Mary Poppins in the park?
She's always like in this all white ensemble.
But like in clips, sometimes she's in the more like utilitarian garb.
You didn't. But you didn't.
She's wearing that when she's in the side when they're in the sidewalk.
Yeah, because he's got the full like kind of colorful outfit.
But I just kind of knew the broad strokes.
I didn't really know why. How she knows the penguins.
I didn't know what the kids deal was.
You were like, if only there was a way to learn any of the way.
But I wasn't interested enough.
I didn't care. No, I didn't.
I think because I would in the early days of the Disney Channel,
which we caught a lot, eventually my family paid for it.
But we would watch a lot of it when it's like free Disney Channel weekend.
Like the cable provider would give it to you for a few days.
And I would watch some of the live action Disney movies and go like,
Oh, what is this? I don't like this.
Now, now you say this, I do remember because I remember you said
I didn't get Mary Poppins until I saw the top scene from Mary Poppins.
I do remember this now. Yes.
You said that.
Now I now I get Mary Poppins, I believe is what you said.
Now we're not I'm not in the business of taking topics away
from the Club 3 possibility, but well, I'm not.
I'm also not going to encourage any further content about tops
or turning turtle the song Topsy sings.
I would put that in the umbrella of what I'm not going to advocate for.
But I think it's you know, while we are leaving this to the audience,
I think there is I think we should be able to sort of like
campaign for. Yeah, yeah.
Things that were, you know, we were like, we can.
We can endorse, right?
Now we can put out our our voting guide.
Oh, right. Right. Right.
Interesting. A lot of righted votes for Pinocchio 2022.
Oh, no, no.
So so, Jason, if you're assessing it now
with your current love of old timey song and dance,
do you like this song?
Did you like the number that happens?
Yeah, yeah, I did like it. OK.
I mean, I watched Mary Poppins in its completion as an adult,
like in its full runtime.
And I liked it.
You didn't you didn't bail with three minutes to know I didn't bail.
I didn't split it up like the value was still like bracing myself
for the two or three sittings to watch the Batman.
Oh, yeah. It's long. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Very long.
I think I might have tried one and then falling asleep.
Well, I also someone I forget maybe it was Paul of Tonkin's posted a photo
trying to watch it at like noon, like with daylight.
And it's just you can't.
Oh, yes. Any reflection in your. Yeah.
Too hard. Unless you live in a cave. Yeah. Like Batman.
So so, yeah, yeah, there's there's tapping penguins.
And I I appreciate it more now as an adult.
But for me as a kid, I was like, if I was getting the like a bridged version
of this tape, I would kind of go, oh, right.
Fast forward. Yeah. Yeah.
Because I want to see some rides, first of all, which you don't get to see.
I know. OK. To answer the question, what the fuck is this song?
I looked it up. Oh, yeah.
This is according to the credits.
It's written by somebody named Stu Nunnery, one of the great names.
And it was written for initially for, I guess, a 30th anniversary
special in 1985 and originally performed by Marie Osmond.
So you could sort of feel the Osmond ishness.
Yeah. In it, I would say she's kind of a sort of a real life
Mary Poppins in Vibe and Ash.
In the three seconds that I watched of the
of the Marie Osmond version before realizing no one has asked me to do this.
Yeah, you don't need to stop watching whenever I want.
I am free will. That's a good point.
Goofy is a cop in this sequence.
Goofy has changed into a bobby.
I don't know why he's a bobby, like an English.
Well, the British, because they're on main.
They're on Main Street USA.
Yeah. But Mary and Bert are British, I guess.
Bert's not well British.
Well, no, I guess they're both British.
So you're saying that that's the logic.
I think because of them.
So that's why Goofy, they they're forcing Goofy to dress as a policeman
from their land. I don't really know.
I don't know. Yeah, I know.
They're dressing up.
They're all having fun.
Yeah, they're all forced to do anything.
They threaten Goofy into dressing up like a policeman from their time.
But I think Mary Poppins Bert did.
I don't know. I mean, that's what Jason's that's Jason's
theory. I'm saying me.
Goofy might just be playing on now.
The penguins might be forced.
I don't think the penguins are not indigenous to the British Isles, I think.
So God knows what they're on the sidewalk.
Yeah, they're kind of made up.
Yeah, they're forced to exist like Forky by being drawn.
Right. So I guess there's, you know, free will is in question.
Yeah. In general.
So they would prefer.
So Goofy is just having fun in their universe, I guess.
I think so. Goofy, if you're in trouble,
you're being made to put on clothes you don't want to wear.
And if you're listening, if one of the inaugural subscribers
to Club Three is Goofy, let us know if you're OK.
Send us a DM. Yeah, who knows?
But yeah, that struck me is a little odd.
Also, Pluto is wearing a mustache, wearing a big curly mustache.
Yeah. He looks like a like a barber or something, like an old timey barber.
Yeah. In that sequence.
Mm hmm. So I hope he wasn't for, you know, it's tough to get a
I have to get a dog to wear anything.
Yeah. Really a lot of some dogs are perfectly willing.
But right. Putting a mustache on your dog, I imagine is tough.
I'd like every to wear fake mustaches as often as possible.
But I think they're going to shake those things off.
Yeah, no, for sure.
So Pluto seems to be enjoying himself.
Mm hmm. Yeah, as far as I can tell.
I stopped enjoying myself after this because it went into a song
called Follow the Leader, which is from not my favorite of the movies.
There's there's there's a little bit of face character pan in this tape.
Yeah. And I forget exactly sparingly, thankfully.
But he looks very old.
Mm hmm. The pan actor they have here in this looks like he's
he's probably not 40, but he looks 40 because usually they find somebody
who is a very boyish young look for pan.
But whoever the pan actor in this was definitely like pushing for it.
I think maybe, you know, maybe I prefer that in a way because.
All right. So a lot of people sent me the pan,
the villain in Chip and Dale movie and like, wonder what Scott thinks is.
My reaction is blotless scared of him than the than the regular pan.
I'm creeped out by the forever boy.
I'm glad he grew up.
I'm rooting for this pan.
Not maybe not against Chip and Dale, but I like it.
So, all right, he's finally age appropriate.
I don't know. I as long as he's not a forever boy.
Again, I've said I think I've said hook.
I like because I like hook before he went on the adventure.
I say stay on that big cell phone.
Peter Banning, you have a good job.
So yeah, yeah.
So you like the 40 year old pan and now somebody's going to.
It's not it's not go with like, but I yeah, but may prefer.
Prefer to the there's nothing he says to Chip and Dale that is worse than like,
you're just a damn girl.
And that real pan, yeah.
Frightening, cloying stuff.
Yeah. Did you, Scott, let me ask, did you see hook in theaters?
I did. Remember funny story, but this might actually be this might unlock
a little something genetically about my my predisposal to to not liking pan.
But it might run in the family because we were sitting in the movie theater
watching it and then my dad got violently ill.
Oh, my. And like, we got to go. I got to go.
And I think it was blamed that he really he stopped drinking soda
at some point in time, realized it gave him a horrible migraines.
And he pinned it on that.
But for a long time and to this day, I have the theory
that he faked this in order to not have to watch hook anymore.
Wow. He may have snapped at some point.
Because I remember the intermission.
I remember mission of hook hook was long enough that at least at the AMC
by the mall that my family went to, there was a timid intermission.
Well, halfway through, so everyone could get more snacks or use the bathroom.
I also remember being very excited, going through toy stores
and seeing a lot of hook toys.
So that was a real hook Christmas.
I had a raft. I had pan and hook. Wow.
My brother had Rufio.
Is that his name? Yes.
Yeah, we were we were all in on the pan.
Wow. A very hook Christmas.
I never saw it in the theater.
I didn't see it a couple of years ago.
I think I may have completed a viewing ultimately with a different parent
or someone else's parent.
But I really do think my dad is like, I can't.
Wow. I cannot do this anymore.
Honey, I wonder.
I feel like I've asked and he's denied it.
He's not that bad.
No. It's OK.
Yes. Great actors like a great great actors for sure. Yes.
Hey, there is a there are people out there who find hook unpleasant.
Yeah, I would still I would call myself one of those.
Yeah, I really like that might be my first memory of like, you know,
a movie where like at the very end, the character gets the suit
and the powers and the sword like gets all the stuff. Yeah.
And I remember seeing like movies marketed at like the whole family
or more adult audience where I'm like, let's get to the
let's get Spider-Man in the suit.
You know, let's get to business. You know? Yeah.
So, yeah, when I saw it, I didn't have any nostalgia for it
other than just seeing commercials.
And I remember being unnerved by the idea of the food, the colored food fight,
like the brightly colored whatever group goop they throw at each other.
I love the all the big food and then it's nothing.
And then, you know, it's all in their mind. Sure.
I mean, I guess I appreciate that now.
But yeah, watching it as adults and do it.
I like I like going back and watching some of this stuff that as a kid.
And I've said this about horror movies and stuff where you go back
and you remember like, I'm not going to see that.
I'll never see it. And then I go back and watch it.
And I wanted to like it.
I just watched Bram Stoker's Dracula for the first time ever.
Oh, really, really good. That's awesome.
So much good stuff.
That's a that's an awesome.
Yeah, you really it's like, oh, it's a movie.
It's like sets.
Is it a thing meant to terrify me?
This is there's like a ridiculous ridiculous.
And it's like it may as well just be like a bad Tim Burton
Batman movie or something like it's just every actor is chewing the scenery.
I really like it.
That does that count?
Do we talk about follow the leader?
I think so. Hey, great. Yes.
He really did.
He really do.
He like I didn't know I couldn't figure out what it was at first
because they sing so much of the like just nonsense.
Then he says following the lead.
I was like, oh, right. This song. Yeah. Yeah.
I was a pan kid, a Peter Pan kid.
So I was a little pan boy.
But now you're a pan man.
Oh, no, no.
I wouldn't say I'm a pan man, but I certainly was a little pan boy.
I loved Peter Pan and it was right.
Look, I'm not I can't start censoring here, but a few times
we could say little blank boy
love this phrase to be eliminated across all the gates.
Really? All right.
I remember being a little unnerved by the Tinkerbell stuff.
Like there's a Tinkerbell like I'm dying or like, why did you leave me behind?
Like the Julia Roberts stuff? Yes.
I think she's watching it as an adult.
I'm like, this is really upset.
Yes. Yeah.
That's the core of my dislike.
And when he's looking at his his reflection of like, well, that's the.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I don't disagree with a lot of the things you're saying
about pan, but as a kid, I didn't notice any of that.
And I like the idea of flying
and I like the idea of sword fighting Captain Hook. Mm hmm.
So, yeah.
So that's that.
I guess that we can.
So that summarizes the fatherly.
The thing we all like to the great outdoors.
Right. The country bears from vacation.
Hoedown, right.
Which, yeah, great afterwards, I didn't know this song.
Yeah, we talked about how we thought this.
I was like, this is the primary hit of the country bears, as far as I knew,
from this tape, didn't realize it was just in the seasonal one. Right.
Yeah, I didn't know. I couldn't have explained any of that.
Now, as a kid, I've said this before, I was not.
I like the country bears.
I was not way, way into them as a kid.
But this part actually unnerved me a little bit because of the bizarre costumes
where there appears to be holes in the country bears necks.
Yes. And I do remember to.
I remember that being weird, like they had like a trach ring or whatever.
Like they smoked too much.
Yeah. The woman in the scary smoking commercial.
Yeah. And it just it's odd.
And I remember it sticking out to me as a kid and not like I like the sequence.
I like the running around.
But the bears were a little scary to me as a kid.
Yeah. And they're like they're already kind of crazy eyed and have
sharp teeth. And yeah.
And I don't think those.
So yeah, to describe what we're talking about, if you haven't seen this, is that
the bears are the two bears, I guess there's three of them, two of them are tall.
So there's like kind of a, I guess, a spot for the performative see out of.
This is a very this is definitely a format of costume that I feel like they've gotten
better at doing is like they need to be taller than a person is probably going to be.
We can get in this suit. Yeah.
We hide where the eyes are.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, sort of like Big Bird.
Yes. In a way, Big Bird much taller than Carol Spinney.
Yes. So so yeah, there's like this weird hole in the bears necks.
Like a scrim. Right.
And it looks weird. Yeah.
It's it's very unnerving.
So whenever there's a close up on them, that's that's.
I was like having the memory of like, oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
What is that? Like as a kid being really preoccupied,
because that's that's the funny thing about being kid, as you know,
a certain age, obviously, you know, it's not real.
But then you start to notice the like the logistics of it.
You would notice like if somebody was getting to see you through
like the snout of the character and not the eyes, you could start to pick up on that.
But this is a glaring example of seeing the reality of what's going on.
And I didn't want to deal with that.
I don't want to deal with that reality.
Scary. They should just framed it out if they could have or blurred it.
Give them the neckerchief necker.
Like they were already wearing like bandanas.
That's the issue. So they can see.
Well, what's the they got to fix CGI or some early CGI?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, they didn't. They're there and they're there.
And they look scary.
They they run around and kind of bump into real guests, it seems like.
Because they get their go.
They're running around Tom Sawyer Island and they go run around the fort
and go up the stairs and down the stairs.
And they bump into people who genuinely look like the hell is that?
I don't. It seems like they like certainly they brought in a group of here's the kids
and here's the older couple that we follow throughout the tape.
But they definitely film just regular folks in the park.
Yeah. Throughout this video.
I think what happened is the newer like Shaker outfit.
I think it's you can see out of his mouth
because he doesn't have the hole anymore.
I see there's no hole in the neck.
So I think they figured that figured that that was unnerving, too.
So it looks like the performer inside the costume now
can probably just see maybe out of his mouth.
Hmm. Well, good.
So they fixed that issue.
Here's something I will admit.
We did all those country bear episodes now that it's it's been about six months.
Almost since we did it, I was like, could I name these bears?
Not one don't know that information is out of my really.
Yep. I don't. Who are the three? Who are these bears?
The one Wendell one is when the shorter one is Wendell Shaker.
Oh, because the kids all say, ah, Shaker.
Yeah. And then liver lips is the other one.
So there's those there are the three.
OK, gotcha. But you didn't know any of them.
Nope. Interesting that it I equate it to like
I'm traveling to Italy.
Maybe I should learn a little bit of Italian a couple of months later.
Gone. All out of there.
No, I cannot retain information as an adult.
The five bear rugs, I would understand you maybe not knowing,
but these are three of the most iconic bears.
Don't know. Didn't know.
How many can you name other than these three?
I mean, you walked into this.
I'm just curious what you retained.
I forgot most of the stuff we talked about on the show.
I'm just curious. Yeah.
Can Zeb. That's in the song. Yeah.
And do I know the kids name?
The little one, the Daniel Tiger.
That's good. That's the tiger.
OK. All right. Just bear bear one of them.
No, no, no. There's a bear from the edge.
The bear. There's one. The bear bear.
Anthony Hopkins with the part, the bear.
All right. It's out of your head.
I mean, I got believe me, we're 100 percent.
We could all be quizzed on a lot of stuff from this podcast and fail miserably.
Yeah. Forgotten more than I ever knew.
But I even later, you know, at the start of adolescence,
when most of me and my friends spent most of our time quoting The Simpsons,
I could never get the lines were perfect.
I could never like some kids could nail like Simpsons references.
And I always just got like just enough.
Or just the gist.
Like, I just can't like there's stuff in my.
And really, when they got they started to lean harder on like the way
the episode starts is not the meat of the episode.
You know, it's not the main event of the episode.
Uh huh. So that I could never remember.
I could never remember like stuff unless it was like Homer was going to get a free
boat, like unless it was funny in itself that Homer had to go get a free one,
a free boat. He has to report to the police station.
So you're you have like a distinctive memory of not being able to be able to like
explain Simpson plots.
Um, yeah, I can't on the plots.
I have a pretty visual memory.
Like sometimes when I have to memorize scripts and stuff,
like as I'm doing the scenes, I can picture the script almost like a teleprompter
in my head.
What color are the Simpsons?
Huh? What color are the Simpsons?
Yellow like my highlighters.
You got it.
Nice. My highlighters.
See, that's super visual.
Yeah.
Marge's hair quick.
Uh, shit.
Now you blow it to clock 10.
Depends on if it was licensed or unlicensed.
Marge blue was specifically owned.
Yeah.
Um, but yeah, look, this is a delightful sequence though.
And it's nice to hear.
I wanted to, cause I wanted to hear those park specifics later.
You get grip in and goes, there's not a lot of park specific songs or ones that
like, you know, will work for a mass audience, uh, on this tape for kids.
So nice to hear a country bear original in here.
And a place I remember, like I could run around that fort for like hours.
Yeah.
Which I'm sure drove my parents.
That was a moment of like, we've paid a lot of money.
We got to go on some rides.
So, you know, and also it was a pain in the ass to ride a raft over here.
Yeah, that's the biggest stop.
So I know I want to get the kiddo over there, but like that, yeah, that raft is
going to be the bit like, he's not going to wait for the raft and then
you're going on the raft.
And you know, what's funny is I'm watching, I was watching the sequence and then I
was like, I had just been on the grizzly challenge trail a few days prior and, uh,
with a friend and his child, uh, his young child and, uh, the employee
encouraged all of us to go down the slide and we did.
Oh yeah.
And I was like, hell yeah.
An excuse to go down the slide.
I may have said, I don't know if I said on the show, maybe one of the top
five happiest I've ever seen my son.
He just exploded.
True, true magic.
It was really nice to see.
Yes, that's what happened with a friend's kid as well.
So it happened with, and it happened with a older kid.
That's what it's, that's Walt's dream in action.
That's right.
Um, well then we go to the, uh, now look, we don't like the, what this song is
from, but it's sure fun though.
And this isn't it with the rap.
We can retain the rap.
Can't we?
The rap rap is the rap only.
Yes.
All right.
Just, just get rid of Zippity doo da, but the rap portion, I think you can reclaim.
Yeah.
Well, you know, in a different era.
So it is a thrill when you go downhill.
So yeah, if you don't want to talk about, yeah, Zippity doo da, uh, on the
on splash mountain from the song of the South.
Uh, yes, this ride opened in the eighties with Roger Abbott.
They got their, their new leading man.
They got the song from their brand spanking new ride.
They're super immediately popular ride.
Yes.
And then, and then it's just a like blitz through the park.
Honestly, you see a lot of rides very quickly.
It's kind of the thrill rides section is the, is the idea here.
And I liked this as a kid because it was my assumption that I would not ever
go on any of these rides.
And quite frankly, I felt brave just for watching this sequence.
Oh, sure.
I had to get the grid up to even look at a simulation of going on.
Yes.
Yeah.
I took, it took me, I would be interested.
I don't know.
I don't know the answer to this.
I don't know when I went on this for the first time, cause it certainly wasn't
when it was first opened.
It took me a long time in my mind to go on this.
I don't, it might've been when I was like, whatever, 13 or might've been like
96, maybe it was 12 or 13 splash.
My excuse me.
Yeah.
So, so, but I didn't, we were definitely there when it had opened and I was like,
no way, not a chance.
Why would I do this?
So yeah, seeing, seeing this, yeah, I think I had a similar feeling of like,
okay, but this like maybe didn't even enjoy it because it stressed me out.
The idea of going down it, because when you're a kid, you're just like, Oh, that
log is going to tip over.
Like you were believing the reality of it where you're like, I'm the logs and
tip over into those like thorns that was the thorn bush.
You thought it was just going to roll.
Yeah.
Of course I did.
Like I bought the reality that you were going over a waterfall and that you were
going to wrap it, that you go splish splash.
Exactly.
So, so the, even though cool rap version didn't sway me into thinking, ease you
into this idea.
Yeah.
This was something I was going to do until when I was older.
Roger only ramps up the fear because this is, this is an indelible part of it.
Yeah.
It's a tight on Roger going, no, slow down, slow down.
I remember that too.
He's not even on the ride yet.
Yeah.
He's and he has a stressful voice.
So he's only adding to the anxiety as he watching this as a kid going, Oh, yeah.
Cause just, I'm sure it was my first time seeing what would be a, a very
steep drop on a ride.
And as you, when you're a kid, you're imagining that's a night, like that's
completely straight down.
It's not.
It's how it was portrayed.
But that's how it's portrayed.
Sure.
Yeah.
So yeah, this, I'm sure this video did more harm as far as keeping me off of
thrill rides than good.
Yeah.
I mean, I think this is one where the marketing just worked on me.
Like I saw so much about splash mountain.
Well, you're like, I can't wait till I'm big enough and brave enough to see what
this is all about, but you were the bravest of the three, according to stories.
I was terrified.
I was unreasonably terrified of going upside down.
I finally did it on some like smaller coaster, the Jersey shore.
And then I was like, okay, well, I didn't die.
I didn't fall out.
We get stuck upside down.
Maybe that was one of the fears that I would see local news stories every
time then of like roller coaster stuck upside down for two hours.
But yeah, I mean, I'm a lot like even with scary movies and stuff, it was like
the marketing that, that was like, Oh, come and do this cool, scary thing.
No way.
Yeah.
You need to make this thing seem so nice and pleasant.
You need to trick me and he's to go the other way.
So it was like, now as an adult, I understand that like, Oh, you get to
watch a scary movie and you like wince and you cover your eyes for part.
I get that.
That makes sense to me.
Horror nights.
Now it makes sense to me.
But as a kid that didn't, that didn't even occur to me that that was the fun part.
Don't don't be scared.
Why?
Why would you ever put yourself in that position?
Do you think if they had made like a little short where the professor.
Bird explains all the numerous safety features at the Disney parks,
I would have been normal.
I think it would have been just like actually like accountants.
I think he's right now or something.
I think if he truly broke down and he goes, all right, look, here's the deal.
You think this thing's going straight down.
It ain't it's an angle.
Look at the angle.
I'll show you exactly what the angle is.
And they go, okay.
Now you like, you're going to feel like you're falling.
You're not really falling.
First of all, those thorns that bush that you think you're going to look
how far it is from the log and I go, okay.
Like they need would need to do like explain.
It's feels like you're going 150 miles.
You're going 15 miles an hour.
Yeah.
It's not a big deal.
Okay.
We know a lot of your children's entertainment starts with the parents dying.
Look, here's the likelihood of that happening.
This is what three act structure is in a movie where we need something big to
happen at the top, you know, et cetera, et cetera.
So very weirdo.
Unlikely that your uncle is going to murder your father.
What happens?
It seems like it happens a lot.
Mark in the movie, in the four movies you watch the most, they should have had a
two prong marketing approach to rides and scary movies for certain kids like me.
Yeah.
Where it was like demystifying it.
Hey kid, here's okay.
This is Hamlet.
Most of the thing, most entertainment pulls something from this.
Okay.
Well, that's for you.
That was for you as a kid.
Hey little kid, you know, Hamlet, I do know Hamlet.
I have Jason.
Put everything in the context of Hamlet.
How does this ride relate to Hamlet?
I'm Jason.
Now, Mary Poppins I've never looked into, but I'm right.
Fraggled.
How does Mary Poppins relate to Hamlet?
Oh man.
I really could have driven up my, my, uh, uh, my family up a wall.
If I've been like, mom, let's read from Joseph Campbell's hero with a thousand
faces again.
Yeah.
So, so.
So the, I mean, yeah.
So it's this kind of blitz through the thrill rides, especially.
Um, I knew that this to me was the use of this, this zippity doo da middle rap.
Yes.
Um, because rap has, uh, just been popularized, uh, in a suburban sense.
Disney has decided to take the trend and.
Right.
I guess we will, it seems like this will be around for a couple more years.
We might as well acknowledge it.
Use it to trick children.
Make it as uncool as we can.
And, uh, you know, it is a thrill.
Let's say we're going to stiffen this up.
Yeah.
Uh, but I did love that rap zip very much.
And I didn't know that there was this other use of, I guess this, this video
is a second use of a lot of these weird stray songs because it got really popular.
That weird, what was kind of regarded as a horny version of it from that one
special, all the girls are rapping it to the guys with folded arms.
Yes.
But I didn't know about that.
I didn't know about all that horniness.
I just, I knew it from this nice video.
Thanks.
Mm hmm.
Um, so yeah, I, I like that, but I definitely watching it again.
I feel like I have a little bit of that when you said you described the earnest
special with just the seeing splash mountain and seeing a drop.
Yeah.
Um, just assumed you never would, or you would assume that never would forced if
you did, uh, another fun little flash memory of this is this is the sequence
where you get a little bit of star tours and why is it a, a flash
back to see the sign that says star tours presented by Eminem.
Eminem.
Yeah.
Really big too.
I feel like really big Eminem.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Just very, very of its era.
I mean, was there, there was no tie in inside as far as we know, right?
Who couldn't have been, I don't think.
There were a picture of the characters hadn't been, um, you know, red and
yellow had yet been invented.
So there weren't like droids that were stand ins for red and yellow.
C3PO did not have a red arm yet.
So it didn't, this was years before it.
Similar.
Yes.
Similar though.
And that there's the tall one is yellow.
That's true.
But then I guess from there it's because he's also though, yellow is the dumb one.
And he's the right.
He's the JK Simmons.
Although maybe, although is, is our 2d2 smarter than C3PO, I guess.
Oh yeah.
I think so.
That's maybe what's implied.
He's that he's like course correcting and C3PO was not dumb, but he is a
little oblivious, I would say.
I wouldn't say either of them are dumb.
Yeah.
Too worried.
But he's, yeah, he's too stressed out and he's a little bit, he has like
blind spots and our two kind of sees everything I think even killed.
Yeah.
And more are too obviously way more resourceful and can take care of
problems easier than C3PO can.
Yeah, for sure.
Uh, rumbly in my tumbling.
Let's go.
The one that I popped for the heart.
As soon as I saw what this was going to be, I was like, no way.
And it is a treat song.
It's a treat song.
It's a song about poo looking for treats.
Pooh kind of being a little creep, like creeping out all the kids, creeping
on the kids eating because he wants to eat their food and it's made better.
I made creepier, I guess, by the fact that it is five o'clock shadow poo.
Oh yeah.
He's got the sort of like light brown snout and the light brown snoot, if you
will.
Uh, and it makes them look a little bit more, uh, lessive, not lascivious, but
like a little bit more like shady, I guess it's the same thing creeping
outside of windows.
I don't know why it's not, it's less.
I don't know why it's not easy for him to attain food.
Yeah, no, it shouldn't be no money.
Maybe, but he works.
He, he, uh, works at the parks.
Who should be comped?
Come on.
He should get a crew meal.
Yeah.
Very least.
Sure.
So, uh, it's yeah, there's some like gross looking food that kids are eating.
I'll say this.
And I don't know if it's just the photography, if it's just the way that the
VHS has captured it, but like kids eating pan Mickey pancakes and the pancakes
look as pale as unappealing as possible.
There's like a stop motion shot of the plate of the worst tortillas you've ever
seen.
Yeah.
If they retired this, is there anywhere where you can get Mickey shaped tortilla
chips?
That's a good question.
I haven't seen those because I like I've been, I like that idea, but then boy, are
they the driest?
Yeah.
Looking just sand.
And this is back.
I mean, when, like, I think it's fairly, uh, settled that Disneyland's food has
been a little bit ahead of Disney worlds still to this day, as far as like a
variety and quality, it's still not gourmet, but back then I think they were
still both probably in the same, in the same boat where it was like, we're going
to give you slop and you're going to like it.
We're going to give you some trash and enjoy it.
It's Mickey's face.
Eat it.
Except for treats.
I feel like treats looking good.
I think like that's true.
They never were wrong in that neck of the woods.
I don't think it kind of takes the same amount to phone in confectionary as it.
I feel like it does to do it correctly.
You know?
Yeah.
Like we like it's like bad pizza is almost tough to achieve in a way.
Cause then everyone has like, well, I had cafeteria pizza in school.
I kind of like a frozen pizza now and then.
Yeah.
We all had pizza in a bad place that was kind of satisfying.
Yeah, sure.
But harder with these other items.
Right.
I mean, yeah, the sweets look, a mini at the start of the special puts a big lolly
in the like, what are the stand?
And that looked good.
That was a, I always wanted the big lolly and then I had it once and it's too much.
It's way too much.
And then you try to save it and it's a disaster.
Zip lock bag gets residue and you can't put it on a napkin because it gets
stuck and it's weird.
We should though do an episode where it almost doesn't matter what it's about,
but where Jason has to eat a big lolly.
At the start of the episode and see how much I get done by the end.
I mean, we might have to film that one.
Pick an arbitrary, if we keep doing video ones.
Oh yeah.
Just make you have a lolly.
If I could have, can I have a bottle of water?
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
No, it's, it's like a hot dog eating contest rules.
Sure.
And we can all have big lot like different lollies.
We could, there's like the kind of skinny, like long skinny ones.
There's a big round ones.
And I'm sure there's new innovative lollies.
I mean, is it, well, I was going to say, is that an episode about lollies,
but I think maybe not.
It's just an episode about something else.
And then coincidentally we're eating big lolly.
I can see the argument for both sides.
Yeah.
Uh, we'll, we'll figure out the logic of it, but I'm in for it.
You might need to go to the hospital.
That might be one where it's like, you might have to go to the hospital.
Oh yeah.
I'm going to have some trouble.
Yeah.
I know I'm, I'm as we've established, I'm not up to your, your guys standards.
That's true.
Um, what else?
Oh, uh, just the lyrics.
I just got to read hum dee dum dum.
I'm so rumbly in my tumbley time to munch on early lunch and time for something
sweet.
Uncle Jason's going to teach us to your child.
You know that, right?
That's coming.
Um, he's already big.
He's big into poo and he does the, the up down, touch the ground.
That's good.
I, what a dream.
Oh my God.
I have always loved way pre child.
I love up down, touch the ground.
Oh yeah.
Does it in like, I took photos of it and everyone, he was exactly on the right.
Like if I was like analyzing video of an athlete, that's great.
Exactly aligned with Winnie the Pooh.
That's the reason to have a child.
Yeah.
Just to see them do this, do the thing.
Go.
I have a couple beers.
Do the song.
Do it for daddy.
Pooh bear now.
Stout and round.
Uh, uh, yeah.
Pooh.
Yeah.
Pooh really is still great.
And I've said this before we watched Pooh not long ago and he's lazy and he falls
asleep when rabbits trying to tell him stuff and it's just like Homer.
Yeah.
The same.
And you catch certain frames where that belly's so big and the look is so
vacant or he's falling asleep.
I it's real good.
Uh, recently public domain.
Oh yes.
Because they're making that weird horror movie.
There's a weird Pooh bear horror movie happening now.
So we can make a legally make a Pooh bear anything.
Yeah.
So I don't know something to think about too.
Um, porn snuff.
The horror movie looks like it's not, I mean, they've done a great job at making
all the characters look horrific for that.
That's true.
Yeah.
Wait.
I mean, what you could, maybe the thing to do is kind of like a 10th tier sort
of boondocks saints type prime movie.
It's real boring.
They would end up in red box and Eric Roberts is in it, but just the it's, you
know, jazz, pulmonary, Winnie the Pooh and Frank Grillo.
Yeah.
Vinnie Jones.
I saw a movie pop up on one of the streaming services and the billing was
like Bruce Willis, Kevin Dillon, Frank Grillo.
And I was like together for the first time, like perfect, perfect
director streaming produced by Doug.
Ellen.
Perfume.
Dream cast.
True.
Um, I mean, there's an, it's a small world.
I don't have much to say about that.
Yeah, that's just, you know, that's, you know, the sky buckets,
Pinocchio on the carousel.
Yeah.
You get a little sky bucket.
Which, yeah, that's fun to see.
Miss him.
Absolutely.
Um, there's this weird song called making memories.
Yeah.
This is another one of the, what is this?
This is another fast forward for young Michael.
Yeah.
Uh, I looked this up this and rumbly in my tumbling, both Sherman brother songs.
Did they do rumbly in my, really?
Yeah.
Uh, this song was for the pre-show of magic journeys, which we haven't talked
about yet precursor to captain EO.
Yeah.
Um, sponsored by Kodak.
So the song is about taking pictures.
That is why the song is about taking pictures.
Yeah.
Cause it's very, yeah.
Pushing cameras and snapping.
You can feel the agenda in the song.
Yeah.
I was wondering what was, what was taking pictures is making
memories and you're like, Oh yeah, taking pictures is making memories.
Okay.
That's what I should do.
There's this way that these, especially like the male singers, you might be one
singer doubled up, but they just, it's, I relate to it cause it's just the, uh,
very stiff, clear voice.
And in this song, it's that they, when they sing candid shots and then in the
end, I forgot in, uh, it's been in my head for ever since I saw this when I was a
kid in the main street song, when they sing down the middle, down the middle.
Like I could be one of these singers as long as that, cause I can't be like cool
and chill, but I can enunciate that.
It feels like shots an Osmond delivery.
Right.
Yeah.
The, well, the, the whitest of white is, is what it is.
Um, the original lyrics to that song, I think I snapped some
screenshots on my phone.
Okay.
The real lyrics to it are all about like old timey.
The real is are long before the old model T round about the turn of the century.
Folks discovered a barrel of fun taking pictures behind the light of the sun.
So it was about the new invention of cameras.
And then this other one, then, then the, then the flappers appeared on the scene.
Rumble seats and 20 cent gasoline.
Let's go.
Brandon radios and radios.
So here's, here's, here's, here's a lyric radios and diesel and jazz.
Disl Jason.
Is that diesel?
Disl maybe.
I mean, what I'm reading is that is not a Snoop Dogg thing where he like says
isle on the end of that was invented the, the fushizzle.
It's like, would it be great?
As a little diesel.
The, the next line is round your cameras and Raza Mataz, but diesel.
It's diesel.
Looking that up.
It's known.
If you look it up at some startup, diesel connects qualified home service providers
with real estate professional.
Oh my God.
This is not what it is.
Oh, the urban dictionary.
Yeah.
Did you see that?
It's third gate.
Say it in a brief.
Well, this one is an abbreviation of the drug MDMA.
Okay.
Yeah.
And then the example they get is I was fucked last night.
I ended up taking two grams of diesel out with me.
Yeah.
Hey, just a reminder.
Uh, I know this is club three, so there are no ads, but we do have a diesel.
Wait, there's another one.
There's another, there's another, sorry, Jason.
I know.
That's okay.
Oh, I know what you want to say to this one.
Is it the, the, in the car?
Yeah.
How's that?
A diesel is a skip ahead.
A diesel is an actor in where the person in the passenger seat in a car orders
the driver to slow down, winds down his window, wanks, and yet skillfully comes
into the face of an innocent pedestrian.
Oh my God.
That's just assault.
No, that's awful.
That's a diesel.
That's not what the Sherman brothers.
That's it was big in the twenties.
Walt can.
What was big?
That's all right.
Robert, what was big in the twenties?
Let's see.
Radios jazz.
Well, what about resume?
Taz?
Oh yes.
Good one.
Thanks for adding it.
And, uh, oh, you know what we do?
Remember what we used to do is brothers all the time in our model T go out for a
diesel, a rash of diesel incidents solely led to prohibition.
They got young people running around driving and disaling.
We know more disland and driving.
Henry Ford is too powerful at that point.
So they can't be on the cars.
And I can't ban the body parts.
Walt would, and now we remember Walt would come into the office and he'd say,
boys play that song with Dizzle.
I want to remember the good old days.
Yeah.
And he would live.
Then he would literally come into the office.
That's right.
So that's that.
Um, Hey, why don't let's go from that into the, uh, the song with the, the
stopping wet Maleficent.
Oh, yeah.
It is now.
The highlight we talked about before in the Haunted Mansion highlight in the
weirdest thing, but this is the thing everybody who saw this remembers.
This is the unifying memory we all have.
So there's a routine with all the villains outside of the haunted mansion and
the, the, the queen baddie is Maleficent.
Yeah.
She's painted green.
It is the wettest, the wettest face you've ever seen.
It is so, yeah, it's so memorable.
Anybody?
Yeah.
Uh, uh, this I think was the highlight of the
video too, which also like adds to the memory of it.
Yeah.
Well, some of us were delighted by the great shot of the keel boats in
action in the previous number.
That's fair, but you weren't watching as a kid.
So this is more of a recent thing where you love the keel boats.
Huh?
I loved all, even as a kid, I was like boats, trains, car.
I buy, I buy that.
Sure.
No, you're right.
You're right.
Mommy, I'm Mike Fink.
But anyway, yeah, wet Maleficent.
It's so strange.
What happened?
Why is it this way?
Did they not have really trying to rationalize it?
Did they not have a way to dry Maleficent down?
Uh, did they decide to do, to keep it on purpose?
Did they, like, if, if we try to dampen it, is the makeup just going to come off?
Well, there was still, obviously there were still things that they were
perfecting, even like the country bears necks.
So perhaps this is just the way it kind of looked in the park and it just didn't
look like they had never put it on video before.
So they didn't know.
And again, we've talked about this is made very fast and cheap.
So there was like, I guess we got to shoot it.
Well, they're also pumping fog around the man.
So you think maybe the fog is making the fog and the fact that they were probably
shooting this at four or five in the morning, I don't think it's sweat.
I don't think she's sweating.
No, I don't think it's just a makeup.
It's like shiny.
But between the fog and like the morning do of like, we got to be out of here by
six 30, the park opens at seven or eight.
Yeah.
And that much do is it really?
How much do you could you accumulate on your face?
Well, yeah, I just got to move around a lot.
It seems like there's a number of setups, you know?
Yeah.
I don't think it's doing, I think it's literally just the makeup and I think they
didn't know how it was going to look on camera, but it's possible it's fog.
It's possible it's do it's possible.
Somebody to spray her with water.
I don't know.
It's anything possible.
Scarier.
If what if it is scarier?
Yes.
Scary.
Yeah, frankly, it is scary with combine that with the scary tree costumes and all
the other one I find that I found the movements very abrasive.
I think I might've said when we talked about this within a haunted mansion that I
was so scared of that big bad wolf costume and then I imagined my bedroom was
at the end of a long hallway and I would the little thing that they do where they
kind of double turn, I would imagine them like the characters doing that one by
one down the hall in my bedroom.
And like, what if the big bad wolf's long tongue reached all the way down the
hallway and like, I don't know what lapped me up, pulled me into his mouth.
I hated that big bad wolf so much.
Well, and the editing trick where they all like, yeah, they're all dancing before
they do the double take, they're going from pillar to pillar, but disappear,
but then disappear.
And it looks pretty good.
Night style where they ever, how are they all going into the one tree?
This is the most sophisticated shot in the whole thing.
It is the best done portion.
Yeah.
For sure.
It has an effect.
It is eerie.
It's scary.
The sound effects are what that specific Creek at the end is the gate closes for
me at the actress is good looking at the little girl thinking like, I wonder what
goes on in there is genuinely poltergeist.
Oh yeah.
This is a great sequence.
This is a highlight of the whole thing.
This one, they knew they knew it.
It's a toward the end of the tape.
This was my favorite thing in the tape, even though yes, scared by some of it,
um, which I guess contradicts, I still didn't put it together that I like to be
scared even though I was saying earlier, but it was my favorite thing on the tape.
I'm looking through some just pictures of Maleficent walk around characters in
the, the shininess of the face varies, but there are some that look pretty shiny.
So I think maybe it was just whatever makeup they were using at the time.
Oh yeah.
It might just be, um, what did they spray to make you fake?
Look sweaty.
It's like a mixture of water and glycerin.
Maybe they just went too heavy on the glycerin.
They didn't have time to adjust.
Yeah.
There's some, some people.
It looks like the recent Maleficent's have a much more subtle green going.
And some of the older pictures I see like a real thick green with a sheen on it.
What was their policy?
So I don't know.
They chatted.
They ebb and flow the, uh, it was like, you know, uh, like being in Los Angeles
with monitoring of water levels, right?
They, they shifted their policy of how much water to unleash on the Maleficent's
and then by the time we get to the Angelina Jolie Maleficent, they perfected it.
They didn't have, she didn't have.
Says you, I, um, you know, I think that I don't think nearly as scary, nearly as
affecting as this actress whose name I don't know in this Grim Grin and Ghost
Sequence.
Did that movie come out three years ago or 15 years ago?
Which one?
Both of them.
Maleficent.
Are there two of them?
Was there two?
There were two.
There were two Maleficent's.
Yeah.
The sequel did come out.
I think that came out three years ago.
Okay.
Yeah.
And did they make a, like a third one over zoom, like father of the bride?
We'd never know.
There might've been a zoom Maleficent.
That's possible.
Maleficent two came out three years ago.
2019.
The hardest time to remember.
I would say Maleficent two mistress of evil.
2019.
We're recording this three years ago was opening day of galaxy's edge.
Today?
Today.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Really?
Wow.
Three years ago, we saw the brushing of the teeth of of monstros teeth.
Yeah.
Oh, the best.
That was the greatest.
Yeah.
Wow.
Um, well, yep.
It feels like 30.
This tape feels more recent somehow.
That's so insane.
Ooh boy.
Well, I'll try.
I'm going to try to grapple with that and also keep talking as difficult as that will be.
And now they've ruined galaxy's edge by putting characters people know and like in
this is the end.
Burn it to the ground as far as I'm concerned.
Four walk around characters.
How dare you when when I go and I see phoenix shand, I'm going to cover my eyes.
Stop the shand.
Yeah.
Till we're taken back.
We're it's time to start.
There's steps anywhere in galaxy's.
Yeah, we'll go.
No, no, no.
We'll get up on the next to that start of the Trevor designed starship.
That's right.
We'll take it back and we'll say we aren't leaving until you promise not to put this
cute baby alien in here.
No, it ruins the history.
Ruins the integrity of the land.
There's a character parade song.
Again, like what the hell is this?
I don't care about it.
Really party ground inflatables in there.
That's fun.
Is that like those?
But when you wish upon a star, unless I'm missing one, but when you wish upon a star
is is a kind of a it's a fun way to go out.
Again, I see what you're saying, Jason, where there's the vibe of like they're
there, you know, it's saying good night to everybody before you feel like your
pedos hit in the hay real quick.
But one last let's everybody hug with the strangest one is that it's all done in
slow motion, kind of these nice end of day moments for the last kids, the
stragglers, including one where Pluto gives a big lick to a child's face in slow
motion.
And I have been licked by Pluto.
I think we've talked about this before.
I think we have a photo somewhere of me getting that weird tongue and it was weird
as a kid because I know it's like the end concept.
It's fun.
It's just rubbery.
It's not wet, right?
It's just kind of slick.
I have a limp piece of vinyl.
Yeah, it's hitting me in the head as a kid and like maybe the performer in the same
way that Minnie sometimes makes a smooch sound effect, the Pluto performer will go
like, make a noise while you get hit with this limp piece of vinyl.
Very funny moment in this ending sequence where Mickey and Minnie push their snoots
together to kiss like their snoots kind of bend upwards and then Mickey steps
forward and it's very clearly supposed to be a match cut so they can like put the
Mickey in the same outfit but with the gloves that shoot fireworks.
Probably a different performer, like probably the guy who's cleared for the fireworks.
Oh yeah, that's a special skill.
He's got a little more.
Yeah, he gets an extra 50 cents on the hour.
Yeah.
Because he's got stunts, basically a stunt.
And it does look fun.
It does look fun.
They shoot off the fireworks.
It is, I don't know, I'm still a sucker for when Mickey just has like finger guns and
shoots fireworks out of them.
Well, yeah, yeah, that's great.
I mean, I like that.
I still am more of a fan and I actually forgot to mention this.
I'm still a fan of when Mickey is doing something like more of a human thing.
Like he's playing piano in the in the second street walking down the main street,
which I don't think he's actually playing, which kind of bums me out because I, you
know, I love Mickey playing.
I don't.
Yeah, probably not.
But maybe with the gloves.
But Mickey plays drums in parades and I love it.
I love seeing the guy.
Mickey, I love when he dances with the band.
I can never remember.
Yeah.
As you know, I like when Mickey shows up and does something, obviously at the end of
the hyperspace hoopla.
That's a big surprise though.
Uh, not necessarily rattling the insane twist drama history.
So, so I, I agree.
I like him shooting fireworks, but I, I would rather like have Mickey just like
making a turkey sandwich also.
I love Mickey doing kind of huge normal human things too.
You want the special to end with they say good night to everybody.
And then Mickey walks over to a little station and puts a sandwich together.
He puts a sandwich together.
Yeah.
And he cuts everything very precisely.
His end of day sandwich before he goes to bed.
Oh, who's on Carson tonight?
Yeah.
Oh, it's Monday.
Oh, Jay's hosting.
It's Monday.
Get the hippie bands on.
Yeah.
Oh, Divo.
If he like does some knitting or something, something where his hands have to be very
human-like while he's watching.
That's all better to you than the fireworks.
Delights me more.
That's better.
Yeah.
Mickey's sweeping up while like Burt Lancaster tells an old story.
That's good.
Yeah.
I just like him moving fast.
Like a human, like maybe a sandwich is too slow.
And now that I think about it, I see it's been knitting.
It has to be like he's playing like roulette or something.
He's playing.
No, no, he's playing.
Roll that boat.
Yeah.
He's shaking dice.
Like something where Mickey has to be human in his motions.
Putting together a model train.
No, that's got to be slow, though, because that's so precise.
Like a ship in a bottle.
I mean, I still would like to see that.
You need it to be.
Sorry.
What speed do you need your Mickey close up shots to be?
I'm working this out as I say it, but I realize now when he's playing piano and he's
playing drums, he's being he's he's moving like a human and he's moving pretty fast.
I think that's what I like about it.
So he has to make the sandwich fast to fit your qualifications.
Yeah, I think he has to make the sandwich fast for me to like watching what Mickey.
So, yeah, when he's dancing, when he's break dancing, when he's playing drums,
when he's doing a fast sandwich, when he's might not get that mustard mayo on
evenly, but fine.
Right.
So you don't want to see him like, oh, I walked in here for the day for the life
of me, I can't figure out why I came in this room.
Isn't that the damnedest thing?
Yeah, no, I don't want to know none of that.
I want to see him.
Yeah, I want to see him like knitting a Christmas tree scarf, but very fast or skirt.
Excuse me.
Not scarf or scarf skirt.
What do you mean?
A Christmas tree skirt.
Like, oh, like what goes on the tree?
Knitting on these really fast knitting.
It's fast.
Well, I think some people knit fast.
Jason, what do you how do you best?
You would.
I think people are get pretty good at it.
Can knit pretty fast.
I think most people buy their Christmas tree skirts if they use them at all, though.
My mom knitted one when we were younger.
Yeah.
Oh, it took forever, though.
All the things to be done quickly.
And you want to quickly or you want it done right?
Yeah, that's not rush.
Mickey Mickey very busy and I'm sure really tired at the end of the day.
It's probably true.
Anything that he does fast, I like fast and human.
That's what I want.
My criteria is hand with his hands, with his hands properly.
But if he dances like I miss that era in this country where a mouse would work with his hands.
Yeah, that's true.
Down and dirty.
And that's from make something that's and fast, not slow.
That's like that.
That's from a Bill Maher stand up.
That's right. We're just repeating club random stuff.
Yeah.
Big NAFTA episode of Club Random.
Well, closing thoughts on Disney sing along.
So, I mean, it's a delightful watch.
If we didn't say the user Disney Dan will post a link, but he posted a pretty clean video of this.
I think there's a few of them, but an easy like twenty nine minutes, right?
Oh, yeah.
And it's 30 seconds.
Oh, that goes down so smooth.
I didn't sing along myself, but you know what?
You should.
If you know, it's difficult maybe to sing some of these songs that again, were only released in, you know, you don't know the lyrics.
Yeah.
Right down the middle of the U.S.A.
But, you know, learn them.
Watch it.
Listen to this episode.
Go back, then sing along.
And if you want us, that's a suggestion.
If you want to hear us just to sing along track with, if you want to hear us sing along.
Yeah.
We're willing to do so.
If you want us to provide a sing along track or like a talk along track to all of our episodes where there's a screen and you say the riffs and like, I didn't watch Mary Poppins until I was.
Yeah.
Until I was an adult and then I did the full run link.
Sexy just push play robot.
If you want.
Yeah.
You repeat.
It's fun to say it with us.
Talk along with classic episodes like Six Flags Sucks and I love it.
Yeah.
To see famous, famous quotes.
And what we were thinking, like, are these crows that have descended upon our recording location going to kill us?
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
If you like the crows, we'll try to keep them around.
If you heard the crows again, this the club three is your club here in lives, fond memories of the past.
And here in lies where you can make us do bullshit in the future.
You survived the very first podcast, the ride club three.
And guess what, guys?
I have an idea of an extra sign off.
Oh, wow.
This because the people who have made it here are the super hard cores, right?
These are the people really making the show happen.
You know, the truest of the true fans.
And I feel like we owe a big thank you to the people who made it this far.
And, you know, beyond that, what we owe is like a nice moment at the end, a nice, intimate moment.
I agree.
I have just texted something.
See if you got that, Mike.
I want to give this to you to say, because this is based on your favorite ride.
The best ride moment.
And so this is something I want to say just to the only the club three members get at the end of the end of the episodes.
And I'm going to leave it to you to.
I'm going to be able to say this alone.
Yeah, you know, it's up to you.
We can we can certainly trade it, but I want to give you the inaugural.
OK, thank you.
Yeah, I appreciate this.
All right.
I really want to make sure first take here.
I'm going to do this.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
Wow, it's really photo voce.
Really? I mean, you made that intimate is what you did.
Thank you.
I could actually let me try it again.
OK, I'm more.
Yeah. Hey, you know, they made it here.
So they deserve it.
One more moment.
ASMR a little more.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
You're making an ASMR.
Wow. Yeah.
Optimus Prime doesn't whisper that in your ear.
Boot up the noise canceling headphones for that one, folks.
Well, I think he look in my dreams.
He does it right in my little ear.
In my not my dreams, but my memory.
I've turned that I had to look up what the line was because I've turned it into.
I'm proud of you. I'm so proud of you.
I am so proud of you.
I was kind of shocked to learn that it's well done freedom.
Yeah, he doesn't say anything about being proud.
Yeah. But hey, we are.
We're proud of you for making it to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
You are the freedom fighters.
Make Club 3 possible.
Please give us what you want us to do next month.
We'll throw up a poll and we will figure it out.
And we're excited to go on this journey together.