Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate where today we are talking about the best dinosaur
themed coaster in the history of Orlando theme parks. That is of course
primeval world. I'm Scott Gardner. Hi Jason Sheridan. Hi. And Mike Carlson. Hello. Yes, the best dino
but dino coaster, dino themed coaster. Dino, well in which can you even dino related, dino
adjacent? Yeah, that's adjacent's good, I think. Mm-hmm. Yeah, that makes sense. There are
depictions of dinosaurs, technically. But this is the same issue then you run into with DC Six Flags
coasters. Can you really say that the new whatever Wonder Woman coaster is a Wonder Woman themed
coaster? Is it a more Wonder Woman adjacent? Look, it's, I watched a video of it last night,
it is a flight of courage and that's all I need to know. All right. It takes courage to do it and it
tributes the courage of Wonder Woman and it took courage to build it. So I'm just all about the
courage. I apologize to Wonder Woman and her coaster and the courage that it took. But there's
other DC coasters. I looked at it and I was like, man, imagine all the people and their courage.
Do they play imagine on their coaster? That would be the toonless celebrity imagine all the people.
They couldn't get the rights to John Lennon's version so they got the early pandemic imagine.
That's right, because it's Wonder Woman because Gal Gadot is Wonder Woman. Oh, that's right. And
that took courage to do. Everyone made fun of her but imagine the courage to email all of those
people only for them to be publicly mocked. And now you can go on the ride and experience that courage
yourself at which Six Flags? Is it here? It's here. Okay. You'd feel getting on that coaster
feels like answering an email without really knowing what's ahead pandemic wide. The courage
of not we don't know that this is going for three years and counting. Yeah. We don't know that
celebrity videos are going to be roundly mocked. Right. Yeah. Unlike celebrity reunions, which are
celebrated and we love them, keep them coming since we're never leaving Zoom world. Exactly.
Many reunions but seeing along as we mock those we don't like. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Does Wonder Woman
open soon? Open the other day. I mean, I don't know when the hell this is coming out. Can we not get
an invite to a press event? I think we did get an invite but I don't think there were clear
directions of what to do in it. There was info and there was a link to media elements where you
were prompted for a password I did not have. Oh, so you tried to register for a press event
and we were confused and you gave up? I yeah. Well, I thought someone else was in the email. I thought
I was like, oh, well, we'll get on this and then, you know, life got in the way. We forgot. We didn't
have a chance to go to Six Flags for free. We didn't take it. We had a chance to go to Santa Clarita during a heat wave.
Oh man. Yes, where it's like 10 degrees hotter. Yes. Man. Yeah. Now I'm upset. And to a theme park with
no shade. I don't know if there's a tree. That's right. I guess I know there's trees in Magic Mountain,
but there's not a lot of trees featuring cracked asphalt that is not carefully constructed and
painted cement to create an illusion featuring authentic cracked asphalt. I like it more for that
reason. It's the real deal. Yeah. Now, and Scott, at the top, you were saying this is the best dinosaur
themed roller coaster because Velocicoaster is about Blue, who you just consider a friend.
Yeah, I think Blue transcends its species and their relationship transcends
a time and its own franchise. Do you ever think, because I was the other day at a nice
sit up on Jurassic patio with Aaron as we like to do and we had a great seat where we had full view
from way up above of not just the boats landing, but also the little Raptor show with Blue. Yes.
And you ever think about, maybe we don't appreciate enough that back when we did get invited to stuff,
if we can remember those days, that we got invited to the Jurassic World ride opening and we got to
watch Pratt himself control Blue, not control, that's not the way they view it. What? Like what
is he, when he's working with his hands, it's just like. Team, work with, communicate. Yeah,
I don't think he would be so severe with the language because it's his friend. It's, yeah,
it's communicated. Summon, no, halt, summon. Connect, work with, work with, work with,
work with, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Make a breakthrough with, I think he would put it in like
psychology terms. Good, good, good go to, if you do have to respond to an email that you don't know
anything about, like great to connect with you. Exciting to loop back on this. That's what you
should have sent right back to Six Flags. And that you hear that is played through speakers as you
do the first drop on Wonder Woman. I bet we could, we'll still get a, we'll see, we'll do, oh yeah,
you're invited. We missed it. Yeah, I completely missed that. July 4th we were invited on. I saw
this, I thought it was just. Media day was yesterday. Oh man. I thought there was an update
coming. I thought there was like an update with instructions. Guys, imagine the sunburn we could
have gotten. I have a feeling we could email and still go for free. Yeah, possibly. Yeah.
I don't think we save it. Would you do with Wonder Woman Coaster? It would look kind of fun. I have
to eyeball it. I have to see it with my eyes and see if I have the courage. If you had done like,
if you would have like a beer at the, it's, I know they don't have the full throttle lounge right now,
but if, if, you know, a couple of beers. This was the issue when I, when I went,
cause I wanted to try a coaster. I wanted to maybe do Batman the ride when I went with a friend of
the show, Buzz Buzz and they, the beer line was so bonkers that like, all right, that's out. That's
not happening today. It was like clearly going to be, it was so much worse than any of the ride lines.
Like clearly it was going to be an hour to get a not good beer. Like what's that? Get a pen beer,
you drink it a pen. Oh yeah. That is, yeah. You can't walk around. Oh, we discovered that too. Oh,
bomber. All right. Yeah. Yeah. It is a pen. Yeah. You have, there's a beer drinking pen at six flags.
Like you're a sheep or something. You cannot, yeah. It's really to prevent the rowdiness, I guess.
Yeah. The chaos from happening. So yeah, you, you can eat at the Johnny Rockets pen. I think you
can have a drink there, but there are multiple drinking pens for the local, uh, souses.
They pour beer from the end of the troughs. They pour them out of the feeds. You and like the
Santa Clarita town drunk, there's drinking up at six flags. I'm thrilled to meet such a, I mean,
that's a prestigious company to, for him to have been, or her have been elected that imagine it's
stiff competition. Yeah. Yeah. So I walk here. I work in that office building that just says
scorpion off the highway. You don't know how much of your data I have. There's an,
there is an Andy Griffith style town drunk in Santa Clarita. We know that. Uh, uh, so yeah,
we'll see, we'll investigate. Maybe we'll just end up there at fright Fest. Who knows? That might be
it. Yeah. Yeah. We'll always try to do that obviously, but today is about a dearly departed,
a departed animal kingdom attraction called primeval world. Um, this was okay. So just,
just basics here. This is a wild mouse coaster. We know how do you basically describe a wild
mouse coaster? It's one of those it's, it's, it's a goofy sky school at Disneyland. It's, it was
considered an off the shelf kind of ride. I remember when I rode one when I was kid,
I was kind of delighted by the concept because it's a lot of, you feel like you're going to go
off the edge of the track. Yeah. Yeah. It's those really tight turns and kind of severe
quick sudden that you might whip around the corner and there's a drop there. You didn't even see,
it seems like some of these wild mouse rides are successful if done in the dark, if you can put
them in an indoor, like we ran into a Batman one, like a joker thing that was done that way.
It seems like that'd be a good format, but out in the open, out in the sunlight, it's a weird genre,
especially for Disney where you expect theming because it just is an industrial looking
format. If you know, goofy sky school, or if you got to do primeval world, it's just, it's like all
pipes and supports and beams. It looks like something inside a factory. Like if you were
watching a Mr. Rogers video on like some instructional thing, how you would learn how
bolts are made and transported from one side of the factory to the other side with the truck,
like where the truck would take them to the stores. Yeah. And some other confusing, there's
two of them facing opposite directions. Yes. So while it could eat up a fair amount of people,
something like 1400 people an hour, if operating a full capacity, it does look odd to see two
identical coasters facing different ways. Some other things about it. The cars spin, the cars
do rotate. You cannot control that. So some videos I watched, people spun once and then not at all.
And so the one big element of this that's kind of unique is the, the cars spin,
you cannot control the spin. It just happens. So sometimes you might spend a lot. Sometimes you
might not spend very much at all. And it's not, this is what, because I was starting to go,
okay, okay, let's get this out of the way too. I don't, I don't think it's not my belief that
this was the worst ride on Disney world property, but some people positive that that was definitely
said. But then I also saw a lot of, I don't know, it was charming and people were, were hard on it.
So just to put that out there, that it's a candidate and I didn't get to go on it. So I
didn't know what the deal was, but when I heard spinning wild mouse, because I find wild mouse
coasters to be a little insane or stomach churning or something. A little unnerving. Sure. Yeah. So
I'm like spinning the whole time. That sounds not good. Then I realized not spinning the whole time
you do your drops and then towards the end, when it's just about kind of getting back to the
station, then it's like, all right, well, we got nothing else going on. How about we spin them?
It's like a late into the ride. Am I incorrect? That's, I watched a couple of videos and that
seemed to be as it was coming towards the last third of the ride. People started to spin more,
but sometimes just once. Sometimes you didn't get a lot of spinning.
I have not ridden this either. When I was there last fall, I peeked through some chain link fence
and I saw the ruins of it. I saw piles of scrap metal and like a bulldozer. It will admit this very
inglorious end, right? It just became a seasonal attraction in 2019. Maybe the intent to start
running it more in 2020. Of course, and then 2021 park reopens and they, oh wait,
or Disney world was sooner, right? I don't know. Disney world reopened after the NBA bubble,
uh, I believe so summer of 2020. Okay. But whenever they just, but this did not,
they did not. And then they just started quietly demolishing it. Yeah. I mean, the carnival games
were there, uh, still that's where I won Jane. The, uh, I thought I won her a stuffed animal
based on the ride vehicle for primeval world, but it's the, it's the triceratops ride vehicle
of triceratops spin, which does seem to still be active. Yeah. Okay. So well, let's,
let's talk about this area in general because okay, animal kingdom opens big grand park,
huge scale to the thing we've reproduced just so much nature and there's so much acreage to it.
But you got that problem of like, there's the big grand elements and then there's not just a bunch
of little things for little kids to do problem. They kept having around this time. We got to just
up the numbers up capacity, give, uh, families places to go. And there had been this little
gift shop called Chester and Hester's, uh, treasurers. Okay. And they are Chester and
Hester are a married, an old married couple who are presumably dead today as we find,
I think they're gone, right? I think it's their, their relatives who are keeping the name alive.
I think so. Although that said Chester does do the safety warning of this
roller coaster. Oh, it's chest. He says, Hey, it's Chester.
I did not see that in a video. Wow. Wow. So Chester is characterized. What do you think? What, uh,
would you, could you ascribe a quality to Chester? Well, here's the, the reading the backstory of
this whole land that was at the dinosaur Dino land USA takes place in a place called Deeks County.
Dinosaur bones were discovered. All the paleontologist and grad students came.
They established the dinosaur Institute as they're digging stuff up.
And the dinosaur Institute is where you go on dinosaurs, which was initially countdown to
extinction. That's that's correct. So when you're on this attraction, we're talking about today,
you are at the same time in animal kingdom, Dino land USA, Diggs County,
yes. And Chester and Hester's Dino Rama. Yeah. You're in four places when you're on this ride.
Yes. Because the backstory, which I do appreciate this backstory, but there are some trouble
difficulties with it. So Chester and Hester owned a gas station near where this was all happening.
They converted to a general store and then they turn an empty lot into like carnival attractions,
fun, fun attraction. Because there's a bunch of activity around the facility where they have a
time machine now and they're sending people back to rescue baby allodars. So that is gathering so
much tourist attention. Yeah, right. They basically assembled like the Flintstones
shitty campsite thing outside of some legitimate interesting discoveries. Yes. It's so much like
that. And that Flintstones episode we did that there in Arizona, there's the bad little camp
grounds with really plastic looking dinosaurs. And they so they did that. So we now have Disney
contributing, not just like Disney has done the pier and old and Coney Island, but now they're
doing like rides just two people built. Disney is nodding to kitschy roadside attractions
of like the mid 20th century that theme Disney theme parks and such essentially put out of
business as did interstates. But Chester and Hester are basically doing what Walter and Cordelia not
did. But it's for dinosaur bones, not fried chicken and pie, you know? Yes. Yeah. So they,
yeah, if you're going to come to see dinosaur bones and the and meet, uh, what are those doctors names?
Oh yeah. I don't remember who any of them are. Yeah. Yeah. Right. Dr. Seeker. If you're going to
go to hang out with Dr. Seeker at the Dino Institute while you're here, you might as well
play our scam carnival games and go on our, uh, flimsy rides. We may as well take advantage of you.
These are like, these are Huckster. Chester and Hester are Hucksters. Yeah. That's the name of
Hucksters too. They, they slick slick people. Uh, yeah. Yeah. Trying to fool. Yeah. It's like, uh,
entrepreneurs, Michael. Okay. Sorry. Small business heroes. Sorry. Sorry. You won't allow us to
like Chester and Hester. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, so I'm surprised they don't have more like kind of
Wisconsin Dell style, like tour, like the fake sifting for gemstones and stuff. Like there should
be even more kind of like, there should be an old West photo opportunity or a dinosaur photo
opportunity. There should be more of those like standard. Wasn't there a thing like that? Wasn't
there a, and I don't remember where it was that I want to say is in the, it could be, it's either in
the Sabrina, the teenage witch episode that there's like a digging for bones. Oh, maybe.
Attraction. Or is it in like one of those kind of less good, like a Caroline Ray host to either
way it's Sabrina, the teenage witch relate someone from Sabrina Doug for fake bones.
Interesting. We got to find that any, which I think is a little bit of a trick where it's like,
yeah, that makes sense in this area. Also, if you go to any, uh, zoo or aquarium gift shop,
there's a little table with some bones and some sand and a little brush and you can brush the
sand off the plastic bones. Which look, it is, it is stuff. It eats up time. It's stuff to distract
kids for half an hour to get the line down for dinosaur or the safari. So these things. Yes.
And it's funny. It's just, it's also funny in this, it happens a lot with, I guess, any sort of
creative endeavor is trying to figure out ways that intellectually makes sense for you not to spend
much money in the park. So you have to figure out, okay, how do we just throw a bunch of rides that
are already made? Okay. It's a, an old time pier or it's a shitty roadside attraction. Like this is
the imagineers have to solve this problem often where it's like, how do you dress up a very little
budget compared to other things at Disney? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Excuses for attractions to be cheap
because then, then they have to gussy it up. Like, well, storyline wise, it's like a kitschy roadside
attraction, but the line between kitsch and sheep is so thin. And I watched the one video from like
2012, uh, ride through this, uh, already crazy, uh, what HD from 2012 looks like compared to HD from
2019. Uh, but the 2019 one, uh, the, the more detail you could see, you could notice how
so many of the signs of this attraction are very dirty. And I don't think that's kitsch. I think
that is the elements. Just let it happen. That's the, we have a narrative excuse. I think something
that bugs me is that it's just like, okay, a thing or two like this where like it's hokey and it's
supposed to be, and we invented a fun little narrative to sure, but they were doing a lot of
that around this time. Oh yeah. This opened in 2002. So we're within the year of early California
adventure where that was all like, yeah, it's look, it's a cheap dinosaur with sunglasses. Yeah. It's
all tacky and like, okay, hang on, but you can't pull this on every, like you can't do this over
and over again. Yeah. I saw a thing in September of 2000. Uh, they, they announced that new
attractions will be coming to magic kingdom and animal kingdom. Uh, animal kingdom would be
getting Chester and Hester's Dinarama. The magic kingdom would be getting the magic carpets of
Aladdin. So that's a grim press conference day. That's like a, like, oh fuck that. If you don't
know that ride, that's just, that's a spinner and you're on carpets instead of elephants.
It is so tacky and does not fit into adventure land and Disney world. Uh, that is just awful
looking. And then the other attraction in this area is Triteratops, Triceratops spin,
right? Which is the same, which is another one of those too. So they're just adding these
left and right. Okay. I was, I was doing some, cause when I, once I finally watched a video
of this and saw it aesthetically and then was thinking about the opening, I was just like,
this is a, this is a 2002 ass ride. This is so where they're just leaning into the tacky
and the kooky. And I associate this with being kind of a weird cheapo time for Disney.
And then I was like, I had to figure out everything that happened in the, the surrounding
year. This is Disney's ride output in 2002. They do this in just a little over two months
journey into imagination with figment. Now, if you don't call primeval world, the worst
attraction at Disney world, you would almost definitely, I think that is the thing edging it
out as worst ride. If we're always talking rides, right? So maybe we take stitches, great escape
out of it, which is technically not a ride. You have to be sitting on something and it has to move.
Yes. Yeah. So the things that move that take you to the worst places and sites, it is probably
this, that figment ride open the same year. So same, same year. And then let's go globally.
What did Disney put up ride wise in 2002 journey into imagination with figment,
Armageddon, all everything. This is, this was open the same month as Disney studios, Paris,
wow. Gone over worst park they've ever built, which means Armageddon. It means the Paris
back lot tour where you see the sets of rain of fire and eaten ash. Bug's land is this year,
which is more charming than the other stuff. However, I'm looks choo choo train would never
be on the list of best Disney attractions. And then you got this primeval world. That's the 2002.
Yep. That's insane. That is so, that is a rough, is this there? It might be their worst year. This
could be Disney's. That's an interesting question. It's in general for us to explore once. What is
the best year and what's the worst year? Well, a couple of thoughts. One, if I, I'm going,
if I give them the barest minimum, the, uh, uh, very bare benefit of the doubt, okay. Uh, outside
of Armageddon and a lot of Disney, sewage, Paris park, the commonality and a lot of these attractions
is little kids. A friend of mine recently just took their four year old down there.
Kid loved the current journey into imagination. What? They, cause it's figment. They like a four
year old. It's a four. He's got his little jacket on. Yeah. And figment, they bought it, stopped
figments. They didn't find it unpleasant with the like lights out and the skunk in the toilet.
I don't think so. I think I, I, and James family too, liked it like both versions, like growing up
and stuff. And so I was with you on, I was like, okay, that makes sense. Cause I feel the same way
I go, I take my boy to universal studios and we go on the little minion spinner. So I like that kind
of stuff more now, but I did not think the end of that sentence was going to be the new figment.
Right. I did not, it had never occurred to me that kids might like that.
I think there is some like slapsticky stuff. It's cool when the room is dark and then it's suddenly
like a big imagination thing. I think, I think it could just be every room could be a toilet room
as long as there's still a figment there. Yeah. Cute dragon. I think there'll be a decent amount
of kids that like it. Yes. And you don't want to have what we have, which is that we like the
previous figment better. If this is the only figment, you know, and he does look the same.
They didn't redo him. Other than the bad CGI, the 2002 CGI depiction of him. They should,
every room could be figment just testing out a different like Toto toilet.
Yeah. Well, there's a Toto room. There's a Cola room. There's an American standard room,
you know, and it could just be like, I'm flushing this one. And then it's like another one. And I'm
flushing this one. And then kids would be like, that was pretty good. Oh man. If he flushes one
and then he comes out of it too. Too expensive. Oh, okay. You can put just a head, you can hide
just a head and you don't even have to build the full body. What about it's just pay, it's like a
cardboard. It's cut out. It's not a three-dimensional. Just save some money here.
If he's reaching around the corner to flush it. So you only have an arm and then you only have
a head coming out of it. So that's, that's good. Yeah. That's how you spend smart. It's clock. Oh,
it's clocked. And then, Nope, just false alarm. And then he flushes it. I'm flushing this one.
Oh, it happens to the best of them folks. How is all the best toilets, figments, toilet rooms.
My poops are rainbow colored. Yeah. Eric Eitel still on the ride in that version.
So that's been a bit of a doubt is that little, little kids will like a lot of this stuff.
Animal kingdom was hurting for stuff for kids to do. We saw my cousin and his family when they
were down there, when we were down there and just talked to them for a few minutes and we were at
animal kingdom and they're like, is there anything for a four year old and a five year old to do here?
And I was like, there might be something over in dino land still. And they're like, we're going to
see if the older one can fit on flight of passage. And I'm like, he's not going to, he's not going to
be able to stand on his tip toes. You can do the slow boat ride. Yeah. Yeah. I understand. I guess
are they just trapped by that? Like Disneyland doesn't have this problem because they started
with the, with little kid rides. And that was a lot of the initial appeal of it. And those have
some caked in charm and you forget, you would never say Mr. Toad, it's just flat characters.
Look how cheap. Yes. Like that's just not the lens with which you view that. Right. You're charmed
by those. There's just in hand, this charm and history. So you aren't running them through the
same microscope as like if a new kid's thing is built and kids like big cartoony stuff. So you
might make it look that way, but then it could end up not charming at all. Here's what I would
say to that though. And maybe somebody would tell me that the budget on these things are more than
I think. But Toy Story Land to me feels like a good version of this. It's not the most expensive
rides in the world. Slinky dog is a coaster. It's got an animatronic on it and the cars are slinky,
but they're like slightly better versions. There are another letter grade up from these. Well,
and all of those, because Toy Story Land also has one of those, it's like a little engine and then
you're in the supporting car and it whips you around. Here it's the Mater ride. I forget,
it's like an alien, it's a flying saucer. It's Little Green Men and it's so fun. Those rides are
so fun. Deceptively fun. Yeah. You completely can take a group of adults on those and they'll be
laughing and smiling when you start whippin' around. So these are all the good versions of,
I assume these are much cheaper than a crazy e-ticket ride, but the theming on these and the
ride system itself is much better than just sort of a generic wild coaster with some flat cardboard
dinosaurs on the entrance sign. Well, the environment is really fun. There's a lot of big toys everywhere,
a lot of big stuff. You're little. And then the lighting and sound and stuff at night is really
fun. Yeah, but it is the budget version. Yeah. It's not Star Wars land budget at all. There's a way
it's expensive, but. Right. And it certainly helps if you're dealing with characters who people have
affinity for and not like Hucksters we made up and generic cutout scientists. Can I also say just
before we move on from my theory that 2002 is Disney's worst year, I also, okay, also
things are not getting better because the next year is mission space. Oh yeah. Well, and it's
funny you say that because I was going to say in the Disney war book, it's like,
there is, everyone is ecstatic when mission space opens and it's not like we did it. We knocked out
of the park. It's like a prize fighter on his last legs who gets a good shot in right as he's just
been getting his ass kicked for so long and he does not win the fight, but because it's just like,
the movies are kind of duds. They're still recovering from Euro Disney. They're recovering
from California adventure. So it's like, and we're probably our post nine 11, which when you talk
Disney's worst year, it's possible that it's not 2002 with all these bad rides. It's a,
it's one of the many years where they didn't do anything. Yeah. Well, yeah, you're considering
mission space though, a victory when it was, I'm saying in the book, it was like, I see that
context sucked it up, like even, which is pretty crazy because the ride killed people. Like that's
the big success. We are talking these, the boy in a dark time, uh, within the same two years,
2002, primeval world, 2003 mission space, both rides killed two people. And I think, I think
believe these are tied for a highest death count on an attraction insane. And they were both built
at the same time. And it's weird. It's, isn't it bizarre how often the rides that are dangerous,
that kill people are also the rides that separately from that are not good rides.
Don't like them also. There's a couple of exceptions, but yeah, that does often.
Yes. Let's be clear. Good attractions kill people too. Any attraction can kill people, but.
Well, a thing about, I knew about this. I did know about this going in. Uh, I knew about Chester and
Hester's Dinerama. Uh, I was curious if everyone else knew about Chester and Hester, but the other
thing I knew about this is that the ride manufacturer declared bankruptcy in 2008. And
I always heard part of the reason for seasonal operation was it was so hard to get parts. It
was so hard to get replacement parts and do upkeep when the manufacturer no longer exists.
God. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense. Rocking a hard place. Yeah. So just kind of a mercy killing. It
seemed like for this thing ultimately, um, yeah, weird, just a grant. And then, okay, well, should
we maybe talk about the story? Sure. Yes. Well, okay. So we've established Chester and Hester and
you're in this, um, this purposefully janky environment. Yeah. But then the, okay. So what's
this within the story? Well, the queue tells a very slim story about being sent back in time,
right before the asteroid hits to the time of the dinosaurs. And if you think, Hey, isn't that the
storyline for, uh, the dinosaur attraction, you are correct. That is the same storyline. But this one
is told in the art style of kids, educational toys from the nineties and two thousands,
like the book cover you get for free at school that kind of has like,
it's yes, it's, it's in the style of, uh, Sunday funnies that you ignore.
Well, hold on a second. Jason and I, there's, we don't ignore any of the Sunday funnies.
You know, those weird Sunday funnies that aren't on the comics page, they're kind of like in another
section for some reason. And they're underneath a word puzzle next to classifieds. Yeah. They're
not as good as crankshaft or that, or that like, it's a new board game and it combines four board
games and you build, you use clay, like all these kinds of things. Use clay for a board game. There
was like a board game, like a knowledge board game that had like different tasks and stuff. And it's
like, and there's clay and there's puzzle boxes and there's trivia, you know? Yeah. I don't, I think
I know what you're talking about. Or like flash card, those flash cards, those long flash cards
that people would have. I know the long flash card. Yeah. Like that, that is the aesthetic of the queue.
Yeah. It's not, I don't love the art style here. You know, it's funny. I was trying to remember
anytime that primeval world had come up and we tweeted a joke about it when it closed and somebody
commented, when are you going to do a second gate about the original characters in the queue? Which
I, they're not wrong. Like there are characters to talk about. At the end of the ride, you run into a,
like a, he's like got big coke rim, coke bottle glasses. He's a scientist who's bald and with a
white mustache and he's holding up a sign that says, yeah. And this is this guy, there's yeah sign
guy. And there's kind of like Nickelodeon 90s style horn rim glasses. There's all kinds of glasses.
With these characters that are our friends, the kooky scientists. We don't have a lot of other
info to ascribe to them, but I guess this is technically that episode where we discuss our
friends. Yeah. Do you, do you, do we like any individuals within this unpleasant art? No,
is the answer no. I find all pretty unpleasant. I'd like to, I'd like to be a contrarian and be
like, no, you know what? Actually these pictures suggest an interesting person and an interesting
character. Here's what I'm going to say. I don't think I care for the scientists. I don't wish them
ill. They say they all seem like nice people, but you know, I kind of like are some of the dinosaurs.
Yeah, sure. Throughout the attraction, because remember we're going back to right before the
asteroid hit. And so it's not in this ride, a scene of horror and screaming that's for dinosaur.
You go on the dinosaur ride. If you want to hear screams front to back, along with loud
thunder claps and a, a like distorted audio on your Jeep. Here it's kind of like,
it's all dinosaurs going like, I'm getting out of this joint. There are like, there's thought
bubbles and signs that indicate like, Ooh, yikes. Guess the, uh, Hey, one ticket to, uh, next
available planet. Right. It's a very cute extinction event. The event is very cute.
You know what? Yes. The cutest that an extinction event could be like the picture on the top,
like the sign on the top of the ride is, is kind of cute. Yeah. Oh, and the Whirly gig,
there's like little gear, dinosaurs, dinosaurs moving a little above the entrance. Oh,
are there legs kicking like it's probably a gear, but it looks like it could be the wind doing it.
Just kind of like a simple machine, a little bit kind of cute. I think, uh, one thing I think they
maybe considered when they're like, we don't have a lot of money. What can we get away with here?
Someone might've chimed in, Hey, you know, um, kids just love dinosaurs. A lot of them,
they're either terrified of them or they love them. So if we play to the ones that love them,
we probably don't need to do a lot, you know? Yeah, that's true. Just show dinosaurs at all.
Um, include it. So this is the one I'm just fully on board with. I fully support this dinosaur who
is ducking a, like a pretty hokey comet is going by above his head and he has a quote bubble. It
says, yikes. I like yikes dinosaur, which is so being that I like any element of this, I think
notches, I think there's no way it's worst Disney world attraction just by shared virtue of yikes
dinosaur for me. That's my, yeah, that's the, that's the kitsch at least. That's at least,
I think fairly successful kitsch that you could point to in the whole dino land where it is like
the thing I was holding up is a dinosaur. That's like, he's getting hit with like a, like a,
an asteroid, like it's a beach ball or something. Like he's getting hit from behind on the beach
or something. He's like, Oh, like, well, that's going to be a problem versus like, Oh, my whole
species is going to be wiped out now. Maybe that's a yes. They don't know the extent of it,
much like humans in many ways. Well, that's, you can say, figured it out, figured it out to make
that point as well about certain things that are happening. Um, but yes, it is a very ridiculous
way to present this thing that happened to that wiped out all the dinosaurs. Yeah, look, you end
up with, I think it'd be, boy, we would be cold hearted, the three of us to not enjoy the depiction
of any cartoon character holding a bindle. We got a bindle. Yeah. Yeah. No, you're right. You're
running away and looking, but I really like any of them given side eye to the com comets. Well,
you're saying Mike, like we take all the drama as opposed to this screeching ride next door
that it's all these dinosaurs go, Oh, and they got suitcases. And one of them said, there's a quote
bubble of one. It's really, it's small. It's easy to miss. And it says this really extinct.
Yeah, that's horrible, but I kind of like how clunky it is. I'm dry. I hadn't even thought
about this pre the episode. I'm discovering the joy of these slightly worried dinosaurs who were
about to die in the moment. I think this is, uh, I actually like them. You know what? I don't mind
this at all. You've, you've convinced me. Yeah, you're right. You're right. It is kind of a fun
commentary on the dinosaur ride where it's like deadly serious. And then here it's more like,
it's a living. Well, here's what, uh, because this, I was, I feel like I had run into defense
of this attraction from Mr. Animal Kingdom himself, Joe roadie, who, you know, will go on massive,
many paragraph tears, uh, in defense of like a piece of sheet metal or whatever. Yeah. Which
am I, I've said this before, around the show. My dream is to get him to assess like the inside of
an Applebee's in that way, right? Like 12 paragraphs about the design of an Applebee's, uh,
you know, and Apple, Applebee's is great. I, I, I would only, uh, I, I recently became fond of,
of red Robin. We just talked to that and I would love to hear his thoughts about what I, the,
one of the things I found the American flag made of baseballs. I think there's a thesis to be,
I think he would like, enjoy the symbolism of that and find something profound about it. Um,
I found the board game I was talking about, if you were to call cranium,
Hmm.
It's kind of a different, that I think had like,
confusing to me the clay.
I think that was like, um, kind of a version of charades or, um, what's the one where you draw
it and you guess, try to guess like what you're like, Pictionary. I think that was like,
you get a word and you have to shape it in the clay and they have to guess what the shape,
what the item is that you've constructed.
Good enough at clay make maybe only a roadie would be good at this.
Yeah.
It wasn't like a pottery. You didn't get a pottery wheel with the game.
No, you got a pristine thing of clay that eventually probably became disgusting after like,
Quickly, right?
Quickly.
Yeah.
Yeah. So cranium, I mean, they, uh, I forget this artist name. There's a certain artist or
illustrator style it has, but just in the juxtaposition of styles. This is very much of
the cranium era of kids education.
We did have poopy loaf. We had cranium, I think.
What I was heading for with roadie, he Instagrammed about this in 2018. It is perhaps
lost on many guests that the primeval world ride is supposed to be a down home parody of dinosaur.
So he justifies this. It is a parody of another ride. Again, I think it's, it's,
it's a little bit of a stretch. I see that now and I appreciate it. I don't think it's a well
done enough. I think we're doing a lot of like excuse making.
Yeah. The ride itself is not a parody.
No, the ride is not that good rides. Just like it's a roller coaster with three drops and the
drops seem kind of unpleasant and then the spinning. See it's, I don't recommend watching
ride throughs of this. They're kind of nauseating.
Yeah, right. No, I completely agree. Uh, if it was like a Mr. Toad style dark ride with like flats
and like, Oh, here it comes. Guess we're all going to die. Like if that was the idea, then
that's a full parody, but just a wild mouse coaster and then some fun signs.
Yeah. Yeah. Not quite, but yeah, yeah. I hate to disagree with Joe, but I, I at least appreciate
they, this is all imagineers trying to have some fun in a not great situation, much like the
dinosaurs running away with their bindles and suitcases. They are trying to make light of a
dark era in time. And in this case in the Walt Disney company. And I appreciate the backstory.
And I guess that combined with, well, this coaster, uh, it's probably very fun for little kids and
families and it's not super intimidating looking. No, but it's scarier than it is scary. It's scary.
But after the first one or two times, I'm almost going off the edge. You laugh a little. Yeah,
but I don't, I don't want to do it. Well, let's talk a little about that. And some of this can be
say, you know, we'll talk about some of these other ones, goofy sky school someday, but I,
I don't ever do these. And when I'm on them, I, if I do it, I am regretting it. And when that,
when I see that first drop and I see how severe it is, what is it? It's like I've done bigger drops,
but on everything too slow. Everything with coasters for with me is that the stuff that's
slow, that's the stuff that's designed to chill. I don't like the stuff that's designed to thrill.
I'm on board for it. So I am anti chill when it comes to coasters. What about spill?
Well, spill seems like it's an accident. So no, I'm anti spill. And what about kill? Well,
it's a ride designed to kill. I don't think any of this. Well, if it's, if it's used in the,
in the way that you're just going to guess, they'll have a perfect experience than yes.
But like, like hang time at knots, the chill part that's straight up 90 degrees and the dangles,
you know, I don't need that. I don't think that's very chill. I think that's meh too.
I mean chill like chill. Oh, I thought you meant thrill and chill. Thrills and chills. I think in
the context of thrills and chills means chills like this. You were saying all these words and
it's honestly making me feel like I'm at a marking meeting for Dairy Queen. Like, all right. And this
entree thrills and then this chills. Jason, that's grill and chill. Well, that is grill and chill.
So that's there. The DKs that are branded, so they have food and additional ice cream are
DK, a Brazil grill and chills. That's the actual name of it. It's a DQ express. Then there's no
grill. I believe so. And I don't know if the grill and chill, at least in Rockford, Illinois,
that was the branding on the DQ that had like a much bigger expanded menu. Yes. It was grill and
chill. So no, I'm not talking about grills. I'm talking about thrills and chills. Chills meaning
like you're a little scared. You're chattering. You're chattering. Not chill like you're cool.
Everything's groovy. So yeah. So like on, yeah, the wild mouse coasters are all chills to me.
There's no thrills. I'm not having any thrills. Yeah. I'm glad you mapped this out further.
Cause yeah, all chills. It's all chills. And I, yeah, with, with being up that high, I'll,
I'll even say this. All the spinner rides at California Adventure are chills to me. I don't
get much thrill on them. I feel scared. And then like swings on the silly symphony swings or that
other Zephyr thing. Does this help explain some of the, the haunt desires and changes in attitude?
Like maybe none of us and some of the changes in latitude, which happened in this, this attraction,
have you, maybe you don't, maybe in haunts, you want thrills, not chills.
Well, thrills, I, I'm, I love thrills. The rules are really great. Sometimes they're a little too
extreme, like on twisted Colossus at six flags, cause they're so fast and so out of control.
But I think if I do that again, I'll get a little more used to the speed and the velocity.
But yes, I've, I've never been a big fan of chills. So I'm still trying to get into chills
in general. Mike likes thrill. Mike loves thrills. Mike hates chills. Yeah. And would you say we're
all anti chill and in some, some way, I guess so. I have not thought about, I've never thought of
anything an attraction does to you is giving you chills. But like, so I have to really, I got to
wrap my head around it one ride at a time. That's true. You're, you're describing unease.
Yeah, it's like in credit coaster is a great coaster because you never really get,
there's never a chill on it because it's, it's mostly all fast. No chill. There's the big drop
that happens that you can, I guess you could get a little chill cause it's pretty steep if you have
don't go on a lot of coasters, but not really. It's, it doesn't give you the time for your brain
to interpret things as a chill. Isn't it a chill at the beginning before the thrill?
Yeah, but it's so quick. Just a little, it's a tiny chill. It's a tiny five, four, three, two,
one. What's, what is a kid's name? Dash. Dash. Yeah. Dash and Neil Patrick Harris.
Yeah. So it's like quick. It's so quick. That's my, that's my dream. And that's when I started
going on coasters, like rock and roller coaster as a kid. And I was like, Oh good. You don't have to
do the whole, like you're ascending slowly. Cause that would stress me out as a kid. So,
so nervous anticipation equals chills. Yes. And while it can chills happen within the body of a
ride or is it only absolutely they can. Cause like for instance, twisted colossus does have
an ascending part. It's not that steep, which isn't a problem, but it does send a chill up my
spine again. Cause it's the thrills have stopped. So the twisted colossus basically there's two
tracks. You go up, up, up, up slowly, then you go nuts. And as Geo says, it releases the chemical
in your brain that just like is supposed to numb you. And then you drop, you go through the whole
thing and then you go up again, you do the ascent again. So there's a chill in there where, I mean,
I guess you could also call it a catch your breath moment as well. Cause you're just so relieved.
The first part's over. Is it okay. Let's go elsewhere in animal kingdom expedition Everest.
I, is it, is it considered a chill when you get to the top of the mountain? Yes. Okay. That's a
chill. Maybe kind of a chill in the Yeti beat because things sort of stop again. So any moment
of anticipation and right, I would say those are minor chills for me. Can a drop be a chill
or is a drop always a thrill? I think a drop is 90% a thrill. Cause like the drop again, it's,
and there's some people that don't like thrills. So they could have the total opposite feeling is
that they don't like that part. Would it an all chill experience might be walking a tight rope
and the only thrill would happen if you fell and it would be your last thrill.
A hundred percent. A tight rope is all chill unless you're like your brain is wired differently
and you think it's confusing because chill does sound like chill. I think you have to pluralize
it. I think the only way it works for me chills is different than chills. Okay. Cause usually,
yeah, you're right. The expression is usually like thrills and chills. Yeah. It has to be
pluralized. It has to be singular is chilling. Right. Okay. Right. That is calming. Okay. So
when we're talking about chills, we're talking about plural chills, but I think, I think most
people are more anti-chills than thrills. Okay. Yeah. I think so. This is fascinating to me. This
is a new, your brain has been working with this rubric the whole time. Yeah. We've never heard
it broken down this way. Yeah. How does this work for like Halloween Horror Nights houses?
Like it's all chills. It's all, it's not thrills. It's not, no, it's, it's all chills. And you're
trying to, what has been the recalibration for me going through the haunted houses is recalibrating
my brain to get the same excitement from a chill that it gets from a thrill. Because like you've
talked about like different, it's a different feeling. Yeah. But isn't when something jumps out,
doesn't that feels more like a thrill to me than a chill from how you've characterized it chills
are something's going to happen and I'm nervous about the thing. There's a lot of anticipation.
It's almost all anticipation. Like the Us house, you talked about how unnerving it was to just
walk into an empty living room. Like dark, empty living room from the movie Us and just kind of
standing there. So much of it is chill. So much of it's chills that you're right, that you're right.
The jumping out does give you a little jolt and I guess you could, it's like in a sub genre of
thrills, but by and large you're going in there and you're tense and it's all, it's, I feel like
it's 80% chills. It's 80% anticipation of what is going to happen. And the change is getting to the
point where you enjoy that. And that is where I'm, I'm still struggling a little bit with it in that
different aspects, like a Minotaur based escape rooms. Well, what was the percentage there?
How did chills and thrills factor into that experience? It was all chills.
It was nothing but chills. It was a COVID mask wearing chills.
Real world chills. In addition to my sort of whatever you would call it, claustrophobia fear
or I don't know, some sort of anxiety that just popped up. But when Lindsay went with me
two years ago, whatever, however long this goddamn pandemic has been going, three years ago,
the first house she was experiencing total chills and hated it. She was just pure. It was pure
chills, no thrills. And then the second house, her, she did admit her brain recalibrated a little bit
to start enjoying some of the chills more. I think you've helped elucidate if anyone can
track any of this, if you can successfully recalibrate your brain to understand the
difference between thrills and chills. I now see that your haunt journey has been shifting.
Your body has to become a machine that converts chills into thrills. You have to do alchemy,
chill based alchemy to convert the chills. So after the first house, you might be saying,
nope. You might be saying Jordan Peele's, nope. But then at the second house, you'll be saying,
yes. You might be wishing to get out. Then you say, nope. So much. You want to get out until you
say, it feels like they're out to get us. Yes, exactly. Yes. Perfect. Yes. Well, yeah, I think,
I feel like I have, I feel like we've mapped your brain by breaking down this chills and thrills.
I think your brain's worked the same way. I think you've just never thought about it like this.
Yeah, I haven't done. I mean, we've both talked about, I think we've both been doing a little
exposure therapy of like watching the horror movies we didn't watch as children. Yes. Or in
my case, like there's images just glued in my brain from like VHS boxes or Fangoria magazine covers.
Big ups to Rob Zombie for apparently recreating a Fangoria magazine photo spread in movie form in
that monster's trailer. I'm giving in the vet of the doubt. But yeah, like I'm fascinated. I am
fascinated by the world of horror because it's like a whole world with its own movies and TV
and fandom and magazines. And yeah, it's comic book adjacent. And I wish I was into it. But it's very
alien to me. You got to watch Bram Stoker's Dracula though. Oh, I've seen Bram Stoker. Oh, you have.
Yeah, that's great. So great. Have you seen Scott? Have we talked about this in the show before? Yes.
Yeah, okay. Five timers. I think this is a second. I was going to say it's a two. But a two is always
a candidate for a five. Yeah, for sure. I think I'll remember this though and not bring it up
until you see it and you go, oh my God, it's the greatest. Yeah. Okay. What else about this?
Let's talk about that asphalt, Jason. This is one of these defenses, every article about this ride.
Do you want to break down this asphalt thing? Well, I just saw it a little and like I looked
at the pictures and I was kind of like, I get like even even they're losing me with this, which is
that they painted this quote unquote lot, which it's not really a facsimile of a lot. It is a lot.
Yes. It's the rides in this area are just on a parking lot. It feels like a carnival built in a
church parking lot. And it looks a little fucked up. There's big cracks in the concrete. But if also
if you've got people walking on it for 20 years on the Florida elements, it gets more fucked up too.
So they have an excuse. But what the defense of it is that no, no, no, the cracked concrete was a
choice. It was a carefully because there wasn't a lot there. So we made a choice in the style of
concrete lot that we built. We wanted it to feel like just a janky place and not a manufactured
Disneyland type environment. So the concrete cracks were on purpose. Does that shut everyone
up? Well, I not Mike, I appreciate this. I appreciate the thought exercise, but what's
the perception? What do regular people, even people like us who do the extra mile of looking
into it or paying attention to details, like what is the perception? You know, because I don't think
most people that go into this dino land or went into this were like, oh, I understand exactly what
this is. All they know is they just went by like much more highly themed buildings and experiences.
And now they're in a place and they're not articulating this because dad doesn't give a
shit. Dad's just tired. He wants to get into American dishing. But it's not like, it's not
like you hear that and you go, oh, what a great thing. Like, oh, what a, because there's plenty of
stupid nerd stuff that we go, oh, wow, that's a really cool little detail. But I don't know.
This is just, I don't know. In animal kingdom. Yeah. Any little details were like, oh, that's great.
Yeah. And like wear and tear that is on purpose, like, like a collapsing roof or structure that
was designed that way. This doesn't count as that. And this is not, it would be, you know what, it'd
be really funny if it was like they did build like the front of a church and that's where you go into
like use of the bathroom because it was like, we set this up in a parking lot, like a carnival.
Like you could do something like that and really like flesh out that idea that this is like a
temporary little thing. People love church gags. Yeah. People love church guys. Why are there more
fake churches in the Disney parks? I have the faithful, a lot of them famously love to laugh.
That's true. I love that. I guess really why would you build a fake church inside a real church?
If you know what I'm saying, the Disney parks are a church. They're our church.
If you're comparing wild mouse coasters, I mean, I think that I don't like to go on it that much,
but I think that sky school is more charming. I think there's, I watched a video of that and like,
okay, every little goofy billboard is fun and there's a little bit of animation to it.
Uh, I'm, and so I was like, is this the worst one of these they did? And, and, and to make sure I
watched a video of the California adventure, original wild mouse coaster Mulholland madness.
Yes. Well, Holland madness is worse because this lift hill that you're doing on primeval world,
it's silly. It's all like misshapen clocks and doodads and swirls. And I showed up the errand.
She said the same thing I thought, which is this just looks like Seuss landing. It's extremely
Dr. Susie. Yeah. Several years after that was built. So that's the, how the colors look. So I
don't like that. You're like, why are we in Dr. Seuss aesthetic? However, and the colors are tacky
again, very 2002 S ride. Um, but then I watched them all Holland madness, which is worse than I
remember. That's just all like, uh, pipes and, uh, and then structures and then yellow road signs.
It's like going to the storage facility for Caltrans. It's, it's so nothing. It is like,
it's absolutely worse than I remember. There's one little doodle of a dip shit going like,
can I get a cappuccino? Just like the shittiest looking guy. I think I went on Mulholland,
Mulholland madness once and goofy sky school once. And yeah, my memory is yeah, Mulholland
madness. They did it, but there's more like it's, it's aesthetically more pleasant now. I,
I couldn't believe how much worse Mulholland madness was just true indefensible garbage.
Yeah. I was trying to figure out if no, and I feel stupid for even bringing this up. Now I was
looking it up. The raging spirits coaster in Disney sea is not a wild mouse. It's not, it's
it feels like a super version version. Like a cool, cool. It's really cool. And it's a short
ride, but it's really cool. But yeah, I don't think it's, it feels similar in that it's like,
it's all packed into a very little space. That's kind of a fun thing about this attraction that
you're like, that it is just like, it's, it's all right on top of each other and cars are zipping
by you and then you go under this one and through this one. Yeah. Um, but that's like the ultimate
version of it. There are thrills, legit thrills on that. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. And that's the one where
that's one where they scared me that I was too tall to ride it, that I was barely
under how much you needed to be. What happens to me? I don't want, and they look scared.
It brought me to this point. I, and maybe this, we could start winding it down, but the, I had
the thought of, could we invent a 2002 S Disney ride? Like, can we invent a Disney cheap on purpose
wild mouse coaster from this where it has a built in? No, no, no. It's supposed to be not.
And I have just a starting point for one, which is again, and think about what else is going on with
Disney 2002. Cause I looked up what movies they put out that year. Let's go. Let's fucking go.
Snow dogs, treasure planet, the hot chick.
Wow. That's a pretty funny shitty, really?
Early Rachel McAdams, uh, doing as best she can in a shitty. I like her. Um, what, who is that?
A dimension release or a touchstone? Yeah. Yeah. Uh, rain of fire, eight Nash, um, country bears.
So things are looking up. Okay. It wasn't so good of a list, but now country bears, which we all agree
that we like very much. And then, um, and, and, uh, hunchback two was that year.
Delighted talking about when Shane was here. So I'm like, Oh, this is peak. Oh, this is straight
to DVD times. That's another thing of the darkness of this era for Disney. But so they're big into
the DVD market and pumping out that shit. Maybe that's an attraction is the Disney DVD factory.
It's the plan where they're putting out lady in the tramp six, right? And aristocats for like,
so there DVDs are fly. So you are, are you a crate of DVDs? Are you, are you a DVD?
And then there's like something above you that's going to stamp a label on you.
How will we start with this? We just, since it's gotta be as cheap as possible, it's just a
repurposed version of the Aerosmith French, uh, sign that has CDs on it. Yeah. Oh yeah. They've
already made that big CD also made in this same year. That's also a 2002. Yeah. So we know they,
they can print that for, they can print us a big CD. Okay. Yeah. So, so you're, uh,
you're going through, yeah. Are you, are you the actual like laser that's printing? I think you're
the, I think you're a, a DVD. You're, you're, you're, you're fresh out of the, the DVD oven
and now a movie has to get encoded on it. So you're avoiding lasers and avoid, no, you can't avoid
them. Cause yeah, you'd be pro. You want it. You'd want like to be, or you, maybe you're in a DVD
factory. So this conveyor belts next to you are just dumping. And this actually is where they're,
cause they got so many of these. Yeah. They have, they're making sequels to everything. Uh, so it's
like, like here's, here's a, like, here's an adventure. That's just the penguin. It's where
the penguins and Mary Poppins go to outer space. It has, it has three frames a second. So they
got to get all these DVDs out for penguin space adventure. Um, so, but, so they are making them
practically in the facility and maybe you're like an employee going to check on the machine,
but then you get caught in the crazy gears of it. So you're, so you're now avoiding a laser that's
going to encode aristocat seven onto your forehead. So it's a quality control. You're a quality control
sort of officer. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. There's a problem in the DVD factory. You have to go fix it.
Okay. It's all going haywire. Maybe at some point you go through, you know, you always accidentally
go like an address or a Cove or like you go down the closed path and it's like, oh no,
they're going down the path that slides the DVDs into little paper envelopes that are sold for
$2 at seven 11. And this I never see those like at a gas station or stuff. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
There's surplus DVDs that have somehow been removed from their boxes and put in like weird
little shitty cardboard boxes or paper envelopes. Oh yeah. Yeah. That's how you can get the
transporter three for like $3. And that's paper Cove down there. We got to avoid paper code. And
this all has to be indicated with like six flat signs. Yeah. Yeah. We are nothing that, you know,
these have to be made in a day. Yeah. And not, and not even by like an artist, but by like more of
a stencil or like somebody who would like make a stencil on a crate to say there's ball bearings
in it. The pre show is a guy coming in like, oh good, you're all here. Sorry. We were just coming
up with different slogans for the front of the boxes, like bigger, louder and uncouth, you know,
like all that, like, uh, well there's little like, like cutout guys and like this ride, but they
aren't scientists. They are people on the computer looking for like a podunk movie reviewers at local
outlets willing to give these movies good reviews. Like is somebody in Omaha willing to say that
Pocahontas four isn't dog shit? Right. Well, I have to say that the hot chick boy edition was
actually a lot. It was better than just the regular theatrical version. Can we find a room
for a character named Dick Van Diske DVD? Oh, he does a little soft. He does a little. It's not Dick Van Dyke.
It's too expensive to get him, but it's like a, it doesn't even have to be a sound to like.
It could just be. Maybe he stamps the labels on with, he puts labels on his feet and then does a
soft shoe. It's drawn. That's a picture of somebody indicates and it's confusing, but you're right.
Yeah. That's what he does. He dances the title on a disc. Which with a, with a cardboard flat,
he's just like holding up a straw boater and he's like, one foot is in the air in a weird way. So
it's like, Oh, I guess he's dancing. He looks like he's tripping.
And at the very end, maybe there's let's, let's really go for broke and get a big,
wooden Michael Eisner in there. And he's got a big rubber stamp that says approved,
which he will of course put on anything as long as the production cost is less than 50 grand.
And just cause I've said it now, this is a second timer, as I'm about to say, but there's a,
I'm part of the, like the charter or whatever he's signing or the proposal, it just says,
sell a grilled cheese in a Disney store. And he said, yes, Michael, you already did this 10 years
ago. The gift shop speaks for itself. It looks like a fucking Sam goody. It's just walls of these.
Hey, I hate to blow up this concept, but here, hear me out. There's another version of this
where DVDs, I know it's a little too early for 2002, but maybe it's a couple of years later.
DVDs are becoming extinct because streaming is coming. So streaming is streaming out of the sky.
Oh, it's like big scary lights in every Marvel movie where a big light is shooting.
And DVDs are saying, Oh, time to go.
They're just like trying to run the money printer. Like it's like, Oh,
we got a couple more dollars out of this thing. Yeah. Nowhere I can find a good clearance sale.
Yes. Point me to the nearest fries electronics. We're going to all be in the landfill soon. And
like ones like kind of got the Cathy expression. Like making these with little eyes. Yeah. DVD.
Yeah. So it's a mass extinction events with DVDs. And yeah, streaming is represented by,
I guess, like the light of God coming out of the clouds or something.
Wow. Wow. This, this extents. Yeah. So you could have DVDs of dinosaur.
Yes, exactly. And they are going extinct. Is there a dinosaur too? Is there a
directed DVD dinosaur? Or was it just too expensive? Yeah. Yeah. They were, I don't know.
They were going to have to do it with puppets maybe, or like with unsold Aladar toys. Yeah.
No matter round up all these guys like are still in the garage. Thanks Griffin. Yeah.
Just pop it. Yeah. The, the, the Buzz Lightyear. Yeah. The animated show that I,
I will watch on UPN, which we later on found out after we did the Buzz Lightyear episode,
it's like they weren't Pixar did not enjoy that. They weren't happy with that. That was happening.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that was in the era of Disney. That was another dark thing is like,
maybe they're going to lose Pixar. Like, yeah, you're in our machine now. We're going to do
whatever bullshit with Buzz Lightyear. Yes. Is there's like make Toy Story 2 and make it bad.
We want it bad. We want to punish them. We need your approval stamp on Toy Story 2. Um, is it bad?
If it's bad, I'm going to do it. And imagine Pixar Pixar is newest co-release with Paramat.
Like, like whose fortunes would have been buoyed by Pixar had they left? Yeah. Yeah. Very good.
Yeah. Good point. Weird. Well, this, I think that's a, that's, that doesn't blow it up. That's a punch
up. Yeah. Do we have a name for it though? Countdown to DVD extinction. Um, what, what does it call
when there's like a big, when there's a change of format media chain? Uh, yeah. Meteor. Meteor.
Meteor. Oh, that's good. Yeah. The meteor, the, the media, the meteor, meteorites.
Meteoric shift. It's a meat. It's so it's like, um, it, it is a, the change that's coming is
meteoric for the industry, but for the physical media. Yeah. Sure. DVDs. Meteoric shift colon.
Huh. Guess I gotta buy this thing now. Which the dads are like, oh, are you right? Right. How many
more, how many different versions are we going to have of Aladdin? What Cinderella so many times.
VHS DVD, blue ray, Disney plus. And then there's a little, at the end, there's a little like,
I don't know how it would be best represented, but it's like somebody being like, hold on to
your physical media. Hold on. You know, you're going to get priced out of everything. Eventually.
Hold on. One little, one little cracked DVD in the corner, whispering to you. We're not gone yet.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Rebecca. He's owning physical copies. Um, every movie will cost
a hundred dollars and I'm going to be Googling your whole life. What movie is where on what
streamer and I've got the episodes. Peacock won't put up. She's naughty. Disney plus isn't going to
put up those Simpson commentary tricks. Hold onto your DVDs. All the streamers are going to be called
like goopy or two blip or you're not going to know which is which. Something is vandalizing.
I've got the asses. No asses on Disney plus. I have the only I have Darrell Hannah's double's
butt from splats. Right. I think it's a great ride. That's a great ride. Oh my God. Well,
you survived the discussion of a lesser ride than this admittedly primeval world, but boy,
you know, I didn't know if we were going to enter into a miserable episode. We're talking about,
oh, it's just a bummer and a boy, a bunch of crap. I think we had a lot of fun. I think we found some
stuff to like about this thing. I would say you guys tell me, I would say definitively not the worst
ride ever at Disney. Hey, it's colorful. It's got a lot of colors. Just that is something. Yes. Do
we? Did we? Are we going to officially name what the best ride is? Are we going to save that for a
different episode? You say the best. I meant the worst. Okay. I'm very tired. That doesn't sound
like us. Just talk about the best ride. It just, you know, that's true. Well, we would have to
shit. Um, is it those magic carpets are a little pretty rough.
Solid can't. Well, let's not over to, we won't, we won't discuss it. We'll, we'll like, what's,
what's your knee jerk? Mine's journey into imagination with Figman. Well, that's the
problem is that if I'm, if I'm a four year old, there's still a little dragon. So I can't say
that even though you're right. That's the biggest travesty there. Absolutely. But it's not the
worst time. It could be a right. It's gone like this. I really don't like mission space.
Could be mission space. I think mission space sucks. And I know some people like it and I,
yeah, it's just, I find it unpleasant. I mean, physically, obviously the one thing is unpleasant,
but also just like, I know this is how it's like spaces travel is done, but like, I don't,
I don't care. Like I don't, you're in a little claustrophobic thing and it's like,
I appreciate what they were trying to do, but I, but he's not playing the blues. So what good,
well, that's my biggest problem with it is that for me, uh, that's my biggest problem with it.
Oh yeah. I just bought a speaking of the blues friend of mine texted me a photo of a little
matchbox blues brothers car. And I said, buy that for me. It sounds okay. Yeah. Yeah. So I have that
Jason, you want to lock in and just knee jerk. I think I, yeah, I think I gotta go with that
magic carpets. I think, you know, some of these, I know it would be the antithetical to Disney's
vibe, but if it was just built and unveiled and they're like, Hey, new, uh, spin a ride, new ride
with like, without the fanfare of like announcing, we're building a carnival ride that looks a little
nicer for like one month before the sun and the rain just sat the color out of it.
That's solid and solid trick. Um, let us know what you think because if it's in, if it's in contention
for worst ride ever at Disney world or any park, there's an episode about it for sure. There's
rides that are perfectly pleasant that we might never do an episode about. But if it's worst,
for sure. Where if it's in bottom 20, yeah, that's true. If there's meat on the bone, we need to pick
at the meat. We need to just devour and tear the meat apart. Like volt, like the vultures we are.
Yeah, yeah. Well, we'll get there. I don't know that my mission space is definitively my worst ride
at Disney world, but it's the knee jerk though. We haven't done any of these. That's true. Yeah.
It'd be a tip that that's what that feels to me, like a depressing episode of flying carpets.
No way. Let's do it right now. Let's do it right into it. Yeah. The ones where we're always like,
it's too dry or there's not that. Then there is a huge birth, like a huge amount of room for madness.
We get them. We come in edgy. We come in just like, you know, like we drink 12 coffees. I wanted to
feed this thing. I'm going to kill this motherfucker. I have found the record in the morning. I fucked
up once or twice recently where I had just been drinking coffee and I came in on an empty stomach,
but filled with caffeine. I just felt so insane leaving them or like at the end of them.
And so now I have to force myself to eat at least a light breakfast before recording. And
wouldn't you know, I feel miles better feeding myself. Makes sense.
I didn't eat anything this morning. Oh, you guys. I feel weird. You got a big coffee.
Yeah. I got it last night. I actually drove through McDonald's last night, got the big coffee
and put it in the fridge. I don't understand these overnight McDonald's for both of you.
What do you mean? I don't think the food quality at McDonald's can survive the night. I didn't get
any food. Yeah, but no, the coffee Jason and his overnight milkshake. The milkshake is tougher.
The coffee is fine. The coffee tastes exactly the same. Yeah. It's an ice coffee. Especially if you,
I mean, I guess you can get a little milk in it if you're just going to drink it the next morning,
but like sometimes I'll get a black and add my own like soy milk or oat milk or something.
Yeah. Okay. That holds up. I'm not talking about like putting two cheeseburgers in the fridge.
That would be madness. Did you, I milkshake sat odd with me. They didn't sit out with you oddly
in your body. Well, okay. Not those because I drank them the next day, but I drank a freezer
one a few days later and I felt like shit. Oh, freezer milkshake. A freezer milkshake. What was
the over? What were the stats there? How long did it sit? Kinds? That was a Shake Shack churro
milkshake that sat for a few days. You look so bashful. A few days. I wasn't going to bring it
up, but I was like, I gotta bring this up. Cause like. Yeah, I know. We're wine at night, I swear.
But yeah, it keeps, wait, wait. So you give me the stats. Give me the, how long did it sit? What was
the like, like from when to when? Four days, like a Saturday to a Thursday. That's wild. I would never
do that. And then how do you, do you just leave it out to melt? A thought for a little while.
Like in the fridge or just out at room temperature. Just out at room temperature because it's a rock.
It's hard as a rock. I wouldn't do that. But it worked with the McDonald's one because I did
it the next day. Cause milkshakes are. Yeah, the next four days. You free. I rolled the dice.
You can afford it. A milkshake. You're a theme park professional. I am a foghead. Get a new.
Cause like if ice cream, like milkshake, I know there's the, the chemical makeup is different,
but like milkshake is almost like it's in the perfect state of not being fully ice cream
and not being fully melted. And you really like, there's a perfect sweet spot there to drink it.
So freeze it. Like it would be as if ice cream, like you let it melt and then you went and put it
in the freezer again to freeze. It wouldn't maintain the magic. The magic would be gone.
And that's the way I feel about freezing a milkshake is like, well, yeah, that what's easier is
there's this place around here called the baked bear and they do like kooky, big ice cream.
And if you just eat half of one of these massive ice cream sandwiches, which you, yeah, that's
probably what you should eat. You can freeze that and then just take it right out of the freezer
and eat it. It's like a chip, which basically change in that time, but it's the change in temp.
So if there's any real milk component, which is obviously a big question with any of these,
but you do not want to fuck around with temperature and milk. You do not want to
have that milk go all the way down to chilling cold and then all the way. This is more thrills
and chills than I could give you. My theory is that what did me in was the churro piece. So you've
got a fried chewable thing. It's not just a milkshake. It was hot and then got cold and then it got
really cold and then got room temp. I think that's why I want to do it again. I'll finish
my milkshakes like a good boy. Like a good boy. Do them all in one sitting. But I will freeze my
ice cream sandwiches and I will freeze my pints of ice. I don't eat, I'm not in college anymore. I
don't need a pint of ice cream in one sitting. Do it in two. All right, let's get out of here.
You survived Five Guys to the Red. Thanks for subscribing to the second game. If you want to
dig even deeper, like those bone sifting machines, you can join us on our new Patreon tier, Club Three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free. Boy, thrills,
chills, and thankfully not in the case of Jason and his many overnights milkshake, no kills.
Glad you survived. Glad you made it here. I thought you were going to say spills from his mouth,
from his stomach. I guess it could be anywhere. Four days, it's like wine. It only gets better
with age.