Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to podcast the ride the second gate where it is of course the dog days of summer.
My name is Michael Carlson.
My name is always Jason Sheridan.
I think we're pre summer on the calendar though.
Is this the first day?
Oh, will it be the first day when this comes out?
I know it will be summer when this comes out.
All I know is I went to a summer of fun concert tour and they don't have those in the spring.
So I listened to what the big mice tell me.
That's right.
And according to them, it is the ultimate summer.
Yeah.
So look, I'm podcast the ride.
We don't do a ton of concert reviews where we go and see musicians perform.
No, it's not so much about checking out the local rock scene as much as we consider ourselves
part of it.
We are part of it.
But yeah, you know, this is a very special episode because sort of a bit of a trip report
where we got to see some of our favorite musicians perform live.
Boy, yeah.
Mike and I went to the ultimate concert and which, you know, the bar is high because we've
I've declared that my favorite concert I've ever been to was with you.
It was a desert trip.
We're rolling stones where we broke through the barricade in several ways and we're really
close to the stones.
But we were even closer to today's act.
So close.
Blew them out of the water because they're, you know, these guys have been around for
a while too.
Keith Richards can do all of his blood changing out as much as he wants.
But what he doesn't do is literally take a new shape and form every 15 years or so.
Right.
As do these and then slim way down.
They get skinny.
This band gets skinnier and skinnier as the years go on.
I think there's a decent chance, though, that like in the next Rolling Stones tour, they're
like, and Keith Richards and it's just a young man and no one explains it.
You're about to witness a great becoming.
And it's there. Maybe they're all young, like just like the technology was just invented.
This isn't the Rolling Stones as much as it is a legacy.
Cool to the Rolling Stones.
Well, that's that's the torch to a new generation.
No joke about that. That's going to happen.
We will totally start your theory on the Beach Boys where it's like they'll just hand it
off. And yeah, I mean, I think this has already happened.
The ones that you can't track as well, like the, you know, the the temptations who is
probably not probably the the temptations all showed up around 2002.
Yeah, right. Nobody's nobody's looking up who these guys are.
They sing the songs great. They were.
They kind of like twirl around each other.
Great. Done. No one asks any questions like those.
Those guys look young.
John, the temptations in the 60s.
These guys all look like they're in their 50s.
I don't know. And I don't care.
I am drunk and my girl is on.
Oh, I know this song.
Uh huh. Yeah.
So so most people won't even question it when you go see the Rolling Stones and they're
21. Yeah, I know.
We'll we'll start getting the episode nines of bands soon enough.
Oh, yeah. It's on the way.
Right. Not this. This is there's more of this is a direct continuity here.
And not all of the members were able to be there.
But the core ones were, hey, look, we're talking about Munch's Make Believe band.
Yeah. And you hear this and you're like, yeah, I know you guys talk about them all the
time. They play in different Chuck E.
Cheese settings.
And what are you going to bust out to surprise me here?
Well, psych, this was not in a Chuck E.
Cheese. They're on tour.
They are on tour.
They're stopping all across America in Chicago, Miami, Fort Worth, L.A.
The end is a multi city.
And by multi, I mean, four to and we saw them not boxed into their box.
We saw them at the world famous Santa Monica Pier.
Here's why. Yes. And we were at the Santa Monica Pier.
They had set up a stage on the pier by the rides on the Santa Monica Pier.
And I thought a couple of people had tweeted this at us and I was mulling it over.
Should we go do this? And then I thought our chance to see the performers live is
dwindling. Our chances are dwindling because of, as you know, full Munch.
Yeah, they're going away. We don't have a lot of full Munch's.
So by that, I mean, because I was set a long time ago, that's where it is.
That is a full robot set and not just one Chuck E.
Cheese robot, which is what a lot of these places have landed on.
And in some cases, in many cases, zero robots at all.
I did. I did get a little tip that there is one closest by here is a full much.
I have to I forget which which town.
Sunland. It's not Sunland, but I'll look it up.
West Hills, close to where I'm from.
That might still have full much. I will look at the rock.
I'm getting a lot here.
Don't think they're all.
No, I don't think they're full much.
It's not too far. Hold on. Let me look it up.
Full Munch is a weird.
It does sound like it's some like it's like we're like
it's like we're pornographers, like in a rush
where we have to just have a shorthand of what kind of movies we're making tomorrow.
And then that will be full Munch. Great.
Torrance. Torrance.
There's a full Munch in Torrance.
Wow. All right.
Yeah, I think so.
We're going to head out of Torrance to a full Munch.
Bing bang. Boom. Done.
Then gang bang.
Then towards I think. Yeah.
Also home to a location of Brewster's Ice Cream,
which is a a local establishment that started near where like right where I'm from
and like has suddenly franchised to Southern California.
And this is like the second time it happened or third time, I guess, too,
because Rita's Italian ice franchise out here.
And then in Anaheim, I was down there once and I found that Joe's Italian ice,
which is another like Philly.
You know, Joe, I don't know Joe personally, but they used to be everywhere.
Did you have but you sampled Joe's ice?
I sampled Joe's ice both in Southern California and back in Pennsylvania.
So Torrance could see a full Munch and then go get some fresh made
Joe's ice cream.
Not from there was one crucial name in there that was missing, though,
and that's Mike Gambuza.
And that's the name Mike Gambuza is around.
I don't know if I care about this Italian ice.
I well, no, no, the Torrance has a Brewster's ice cream.
The Italian ice is in Anaheim.
Oh, sorry. I got confused.
Oh, I see. So you get a little Brewster and then a full Munch.
Yes. OK. OK.
You munch on Brewster's and see a full Munch.
Yes. OK. It's your day in Torrance.
Nice. Sounds nice.
Mm hmm. So so that's why I thought, OK, we really do have to see them
because our opportunities to see this band live are going away.
Just like the Rolling Stones.
Members, one of them just got covid.
I don't that much as make with man hasn't been very forthcoming with this.
We don't know if Jasper ever had about if he's got long covid.
I'd spoil or alert. They say Pasquale is not there.
He's back home.
So he may have had a positive covid test.
Oh, was that a euphemism? Might have been. Yeah.
Yeah. They're like, oh, Pasquale is back home.
He's in the pizza kitchen.
Wink, wink. I got negative.
I hope I get the back on tour.
What are we supposed to tell Jasper?
What are we supposed to tell everybody?
We can't we can't.
But these kids don't even know what covid is.
We can't say they're going to be begging to see Pasquale.
Just get the session guy, you know, just get there.
There's so many good people out there these days.
You know, they know you, Pasquale.
They don't they're we can't just shove a mustache on any idiot.
I know they're lapping me on SoundCloud and Bandcamp.
I don't know. These kids are doing in their house in their bedrooms.
No way.
I'm the greatest musician of your generation, of any generation.
I am mainlining Pex Floyd drug to take so I can get back on the tour super fast.
Now I've got it.
We'll tell him you're at home making pizzas.
It's a foolproof excuse.
Chuckie, you already got me
sick feeding me the horse eye for Becton.
What are you doing?
That's that's I didn't take enough of it.
And at the right temperature, that brings up an actual interesting idea.
You doing sort of classic Chuck's voice is maybe classic Chuckie is still alive.
Oh, he's actually the sort of behind the scenes guy.
And this new mouse Chuckie is like a young actor kind of a guy.
Oh, he hired some energetic guy with kind of like
like glee youthful energy behind the candelabra.
They say they don't like me anymore.
Behind the pizza pie.
Get one of the new kids, the new kids with the talent and the maxi.
Yeah. So he's back there calling shots.
Chuck, Chuck, I'm going to call you Chuck.
You're going to get plastic surgery to look like me
or not look less like me to look more family friendly.
Look, these suckers will buy anything.
Blippi did it. We can do it.
That ain't even the real Blippi.
They don't know their kids. They're dumb.
Chuckie is also like we haven't seen him in so many years.
So he's like old and like let himself go.
Like he looks crazy.
His hair's grown out like he's just sitting on a desk.
He's like he's got like the crazy.
He's got the Bill Cosby's eyes.
Crazy. We don't.
He's yeah, there's a lot going on with what Chuck with Chuck behind the scenes.
Chuck, he's like Howard Hughes type.
He's like like Perlmutter.
Yeah. CEO of Marvel.
There only is like three pictures, like one of which from the set,
one of which with Donald Trump, one of which him in the 80s or 70s.
Don't look at me. Don't look at me.
My neighbors are trying to steal my DNA.
Chuck's lost his mind.
He's eating his own shit more than usual.
Yeah. Baking into a pizza.
I would love that.
Now that you're saying this, I would love to see a classic Chuck E.
Cheese just acting out the script to Robert Altman's Secret Honor,
which was the the late film maker.
Hall. Yeah.
Playing Richard Nixon, just monologuing for like 90 minutes, two hours.
Yeah. Sure.
Let's make it happen.
We find any quotes from that movie.
I think we're here. OK, hang on.
There's not like her. OK, here we go.
Uh, I am America.
I'm a winner who lost every battle up to and including the war.
I am not the American nightmare.
I'm the American dream period.
That's why the system works, because I am the system.
Oh, period. It's powerful.
Folks.
He has to be. Yeah.
Something like if the concert we saw went wrong, like,
and like everything was like going to shit and kids were rioting
and people were like trying to rush the stage like that.
Chuck would have been forced to come up on the behind the scenes
and make a speech like that to try to calm everybody down.
But he was making worse.
I've come too far to work too hard for this.
Do you want you want to look me in the eye and say I'm not America?
I dare you. I got bugs all over my face.
So what?
He's yelling this to my son.
Yeah. Yeah.
You there with the kid.
You know, me.
Let me entertain him.
I prove I still got it.
Charles and a cheese.
Don't cry.
You're crying because you're a quitter.
Together, we got it.
We got it together with me and these bugs.
We got it.
You'll have them to get used to them.
All you kids have bugs for once.
All you kids will have bugs one day.
Grow some hair on your chest.
Getting bugs is a rite of passage for a young man.
I'm still hung up on Mike.
Oh, you said, let me entertain him.
So so unexpected.
I can do it.
I'm just channeling.
I can entertain him.
The greatest entertainer on the planet.
You're a star. You're a fucking star.
Oh, I don't want to talk about the show.
Let's just do it.
Let me dive off the pier.
I'll do it.
I'll die. I got nothing left.
I'd be I'd be a coward if I didn't.
Eight dollars for funnel cake.
What is this price?
This guy in the hell.
I know who is here.
No more.
The horse leave the pier.
Yeah.
This used to be good and fun.
Now the corporations came in and ruined it.
The mob used to run this appear.
So he was so much better when the mob ran.
You and you are getting.
Chuck E. Cheese.
You were.
You were a part of them.
Everything was better.
Anyway, we saw a concert for babies at the Santa Monica Pier.
Is what we did.
It was a little too loud for babies.
It was too loud for me.
It was. We got there.
It was far too loud.
Yeah, we had a hole up in the.
My brain is so broken, I can't produce the word arcade.
There it is.
Yeah, casino, the baby casino.
I almost just said the word baby casino because I couldn't think of what arcade
was. People, people online I've seen refer to Chuck E.
Cheese as a child casino, which makes sense.
But yeah, you know, even better.
It's it's.
Prices and ships.
And so I was I was I was I was pretty much on time, but I was like, oh, I hope I
hope I'm able to find the concert.
Yeah, we didn't know where at the Santa Monica.
Yeah, because it doesn't really specify.
And I was I was just getting to the coast.
If you've ever been there, like you can pretty much see there's an amusement park
and it's on a long point, like a long pier.
And then immediately I heard, are you ready for Chuck E.
Cheese? Like school?
I was so I was like blocks away.
I was like a mile away and I could hear somebody screaming about Chuck E.
Cheese. And I was like, well, OK, I should be able to find this pretty easily.
And then Scott had texted me.
It was by the roller coaster, which made it even easier.
But I could have just followed the like young person screaming screams.
The script web, my young person.
You mean the DJ from Coast 103.5?
Yes. Easy listening.
You mean the morning host of the easy listening station in L.A.?
I might have been older than me.
That might have been a decent chance.
He was older than me.
The young ish for the young acting person.
I just think of everyone on radio as being so hip and young,
even though I don't get to radio unless you've got Moxie like the cool kids.
Yeah, I guess I should.
I actually don't think that I think of Rodney on the Rock.
I think of Little Stevens underground.
I think of some ancient men who on the radio.
So, yeah, it was all it was very loud,
which was upsetting for this.
Yeah, it's loud yelling before the concert and loud just pop songs
to get the energy up.
And then this was my son had never been to the Santa Monica Pier.
So it inspired that, which was nice and mostly pretty nice to do.
But there's another one of the things that my son is pretty scared of is
hand dry, like air dryers outside of bathrooms.
Those are those are like guns going off to understaff.
You never do are new on this planet and then
you don't know where it's coming from and why.
And there's so many of those.
So we made it down an alley.
There was just nothing but those going off.
And he's gotten calmer.
But it still is like he's he's literally shell shocked.
Not literally. There's no shells.
He is acting shell shocked.
And then we get down this corridor to where a man is screaming at us.
So I'm like, oh, this is maybe not the best.
And I think this will turn a corner and it'll be fun.
Yeah. But that's yeah.
So you were you had mentioned this, Mike.
You were going to go seemingly no matter what you had your heart set.
Probably. Yes. The 11 a.m. show.
There were two shows, 11 a.m. and 1 p.m.
Yes. Yeah.
And I wanted to go early at the pier on a Saturday.
And I kept changing my answer.
I think I was it was like, oh, Aaron, a morning.
I really got to take him for the day.
So do I really want to go do that?
And then I looked it up and like from the video that I watched.
OK, this is clearly a concert for babies.
This is like plush.
This is suited characters dancing around.
And I went, well, do I really want to go down there for a concert for babies?
And then I went, wait a minute.
He's a baby.
Baby would like a concert for babies.
Actually, this makes more sense than I was going to go solo or Mike.
What you do, which was to go solo.
Well, I was essentially you ended up with it with a kid.
I was so glad you brought a child with.
So I wasn't alone there.
Would have been.
Yeah, I don't know that there's a lot of solo.
I mean, here's the thing.
It's in such a wide open spot.
It's not so crazy.
There were folks wandering.
Yes. And plenty of well, yeah, it was not exactly.
It wasn't a seated situation.
It was still it was open.
G.A. Pitt. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Literally, but fucking.
Pit. Yeah.
Love someone.
That's what it was open.
People were kind of coming and going.
A lot of parents around.
So it's not like you.
It wasn't just like, here are 100 children who are this height
and then you who are my kite.
Yeah. So it was there was no issue there.
And there were like drift, like drifter to wandering into the like, it's not like
I would have been arrested.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mm hmm.
So but I still.
One question that I had is what you were imagining you were going to get,
because once I saw a video of it and it's people in suits going like that,
I like that adds up and maybe I'll only go if it entertains my son for
for 10 minutes. Yep.
I'm not sure. Did you think you were going to get
because obviously you were saying we want to see the band and they're taking out.
There's no full munch.
But like this was never going to be.
They bring some robots out.
No, I knew there weren't hauling robots around the country.
I thought I didn't actually know I didn't want I went in pretty cold, cold and clean.
I thought maybe there was a chance we were going to see the puppets from the videos.
I thought perhaps it would be a puppet show, which kind of seemed fun to me.
Yeah. In a way, seem maybe even more fun than just the suit of characters.
Oh, I like we obviously like suited characters.
So I didn't know.
So so the draw for me kind of was thinking, oh, maybe it'll be puppets and
we'll hear the songs from the albums we've played over the years.
From the Chucky, the newer Chucky cheese and maybe even together, we got it,
which they've I've seen recently they've posted on Apple Music.
So I think the new band does together.
We got it sometimes. Right. Interesting. OK.
So I would have that would have hit you like as if you got to see.
Wow, I got to see the like when we got to see Neil Young and Paul McCartney do.
Why don't we do it in the road?
A song Paul doesn't do a lot.
And Neil was having a ball like you go.
It's a special performance.
Paul doesn't do this song a lot or ever.
So these touring 19 year olds dancing to
we've got it together, we've got it.
We've had a similar effect, similar effect or yeah, or a nice.
What are what are the two ones?
Another Chucky Day, which we've talked about before.
That is the Snoop Esk.
And then me and my friends.
And then me and my friends is the
bird, my friend, which is much, much, much.
Is that the that's the Bruno Mars Esk?
I think that's I got the name right.
Let me look just together.
We got it. The first track off the album Songs in the Key of E.
Uh huh. Is it?
Is it a new version of it or is it?
Let's let's let's see. Let's explore it.
So this way, so if you're following along with us,
if you're a Billy, I believe on Apple Music or Spotify.
Yeah. Chuck E.
Cheese is on there.
New songs coming out.
So I'm shorter.
Sometimes E.P.'s, you know, you want to check in and get quick hits
from your favorite artists. Chuck's doing it on there.
Yeah. So this is me and my friends.
Mm hmm.
It's time again.
All right.
Got brand new news and they're easy to do.
And they're all about me and my friends.
It's telling me and she like.
So they kind of go through all the kind of Bruno Mars.
They very well.
You know, very exactly. Yes.
Yeah. Which is a thing they do often.
And there's a question I have.
Is that allowed of like, you know, what is this parody?
Law?
Did you did we want to hear what their version?
I would like to hear whether they're.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How similar is this to the original?
Do they bring some new life to it?
OK, I think I think it sounded like the old one to me.
Ladies and gentlemen, we are proud to present to you.
Oh, yeah.
Munchies and Chilter.
Oh, classic.
Chuck E.
Cheese.
Hi, everybody.
That's me. Chuck E.
Cheese.
And even though this is going for super guy, I am not a star of the show.
You are because the magic only happens when.
Just make money and we're going to make you.
We've got it together.
We got it.
We've got it together with you.
We got it together forever.
They just begun.
This man is number one.
Maybe they've like re recorded over the Chucky voice
with the bowling for soup guy who now does if you're just catching up
the lead singer of the band bowling for soup, does Chucky
Cheese's singing and speaking voice?
Yeah.
Jared Reddick, Jared Reddick.
So it sounds like, yeah, he's on that track, but it sounds like the classic.
I don't know. I'm not sure if they recorded it.
Is it is it a situation where they didn't have the masters
where they had to be record?
Oh, like Taylor's version, like Taylor's version, right?
Chucky is Chucky's version.
Well, that might be it is Chucky himself is the stand in for
awful guy who's the shooter brawn.
Scooter brawn. Yeah.
Yeah.
I guess you can't do it.
I'm giving you my name, but not the masters.
I own the masters kid.
I own you.
I got a 360 deal on you.
No, no, that's that
eviscerating new 10 minute version of
I love pepperoni really tore me a new asshole.
Who knew the new check would elevate the form by remaking all the old songs?
Yeah, it's been coming.
I eat it, Scooter piece of shit.
So, yeah, so so there's some classics on the Apple Music.
And then there's a lot on Spotify.
There's a lot of music, a lot on YouTube.
There's so many songs.
We've played them on our previous Chuck E.
Cheese episodes.
So, yeah, I was going down, yeah, for the idea that maybe it was puppets.
Still happy about seeing people in suits.
But then to hear some of those classic songs we've talked about.
And I was a little bit sad and to learn those songs are not in the setlist.
Yeah, none of the songs I was hoping to hear are in the setlist.
So you brought I need to hear the hits energy
to this show of a cartoon mouse and bird.
That's right. You were like, can I guess?
I'll go to the bathroom.
And here's the deal.
I normally do not like this behavior at a concert.
Usually when I not all the time, but I'll go to a concert and I'm a snooty
concert goer.
If they do just all the hits, I go, OK, we know.
We know this is your like Vegas setlist.
Give us a little bit of the obscure.
Give us a little. That's usually how I am.
You're the guy going, play the new album.
Well, not always that depending on who the band is.
Not always that buffetters Sammy Hagar.
Well, the new puppet album, I would be on that actually.
And the last one was good because it has the song Cousin Island,
which is one of my favorites.
What's what happens?
Wait, sorry. Is that Cousin Island or Cousin?
No, no, not Cousin Island.
That's a dozen album.
Hang out with your cousins on an island.
Yeah, hang out with cousin on island.
Thanks for the song. Oh, it's written.
I finished it.
Cousin Island, which is about like parents on a road trip with kids.
It's very confused.
The song is very confusing.
And we presented this before you introduced what Cousin Island was.
You presented this as a good album and a good song.
Now you can continue to explain.
It's a classic Buffett song that doesn't make much sense
and is really odd.
Fruitcakes is obviously the king of that is that's the top one
where you're like, what is this song?
And Cousin Island is in that tradition of kind of confusing narrative
that he is.
That's a long song.
I feel like maybe it's like five minutes, six minutes.
Cruising down the coast of Panama with my kids, snorkeling with the stingrays,
kudos and the squids, kudos, of course, shortening of barracuda.
Yeah, got it. Jimmy, no need to explain.
Uh, there's a song he has on an album called like Who Gets...
Oh, yeah, go ahead with the young lady.
Did I just hear you call your brother a stupid little shit?
Yeah, right. Exactly. This is what I'm saying.
You know, you're not allowed to use those words now.
Apologize, lickety split.
Like what? Like, huh?
I feel like he used to have more of an angle of like, well, parents
just don't understand.
Well, then now he's like, parents do understand and they're right.
Kids are saying shit.
And I know I'm saying it too, but it's to prove a point.
You send your daughter to goddamn NYU and she's like, I can do social media.
That's like, I guess I'm giving her a job.
Uh, it doesn't say shitless.
Like he said something about like that's some shit list.
He says shit like twice, I think, in that song.
Jimmy. So he's cursing up a storm.
It's very confusing. And the song is called Cussin Island.
And then, yeah, there's other songs on that album like,
who gets to live like this?
Like, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk, blunk.
Let me think.
Oh, now that you now that you mention it.
Don't do, don't do, don't do.
I mean, I guess we got to play a little bit of it now,
Cussin Island, now that you've called for it.
There's a song called Who Who Gets to Live Like This?
We were like, is this really like appropriate for a billionaire
to be writing a song like this? Yeah.
Like, we know you do.
The answer is you.
You're not like like 25 anymore.
Do they think they do?
I think.
Oh, no, it's a world of difference.
No, Mr. Rogers.
It's Jimmy.
With the little tail.
Oh, maybe you like this.
I know I never should have written this song.
I know I'm in trouble if you can't sing along.
This is my heart goes out to Lindsey so hard right now.
I just really want to give her my sympathy.
And I know the same thing like for the times that you have said,
have you heard Cussin Island?
And she said yes. And then you still play it.
She does. She does not like Cussin Island.
I don't think I'm saying something out of school here.
She does like the lead singer down at the lot.
The lead single down at the Lottie.
She does like that one.
Jason likes it too.
Yeah.
The Devil I Know, also a good song from that album.
OK. I feel like Eva was not pro down at the Lottie.
I feel like she didn't have teeth.
I'm this is early pandemic.
Hey, it came out early in the pandemic.
And it was a it was an oasis.
We were discussing down at the Lottie.
Yeah. It's you know what it's about.
It's about drinking a margarita at a bar.
Jimmy Explorers and clap like the monkey.
I clap like the audience at the Chucky show.
So your point was that the Chucky band did Cussin Island.
So so you were disappointed you didn't know it.
But when you realized there's a full cover of Cussin Island,
I'll give you my full concert.
Yeah, yeah. My my concert opinions in general are like I like the band.
Did not just give you the the greatest hits album.
But I was I mean, it's a short first of all, short show.
I was thinking they playing for an hour at least.
They only gave us like 20 minutes.
Thank God it was free because I give Chuck my money.
I want triple encore.
But but yeah, I thought at least we get one of these.
And it was mostly new stuff.
And you really you genuinely.
Yeah, it's not under the hits.
You know, yeah, you know, so I said it to you.
I go, I hope they play me and my friend, me and my friends.
I said it to you.
So it wasn't it was an active thought I had.
Well, my other favorite thing that was said before the concert began
is that you were still kind of trying to make heads or tails of of what this was.
And at some point you said, God, it's so like, well, like,
what's this going to be like? Who's going to be here?
What like Chuck fans?
It's like I think what it is is babies for a baby concert.
It is a baby. You're not wrong.
It is a baby concert.
We went to a baby concert.
But I was like, are there like Chuck E.
Cheeseheads that are coming out for this?
Because how many people do you think were actually
standing there had come with purpose to see it?
Couple families, you guys.
And did you run into Jamie Loftus or did you go to the one?
I thought about a messaging or about this, but I feel like
that's too much of a weird thing to say to somebody.
Do you want to go to the Chuck E.
Cheese show?
Do you want to see Chuck at the pier?
Like maybe if all three of us were going for sure.
But it was like, hey, do you want to go to the Chuck E.
Cheese show? Like, I'm not going to.
That's not well.
She will do Chuck E.
Cheese three proper eventually.
Yeah. But this is a concert review.
So check out her podcast, Ghost Church.
It's really good. Oh, sure.
I like to listen to it. Yep.
So, yeah. So, no, there were a couple of families.
Unclear. I didn't go up and pull them.
Did you come here on purpose or were you here already?
Why are you here? Why are you here?
Excuse me. Why are you here?
Hey, can I take an informal poll?
I try to get on stage and wrestle that morning DJ out of the way.
Can I take a quick, informal poll?
I really want to get a microphone. It's a emergency.
I have a Patreon exclusive podcast that I need to I need to fill with content.
I need to know the level of irony with these four year olds.
Do you like this version of Chuck or the old one?
Let me show you a photo on my phone.
I know it's bright out here, but you have to squint.
So so, yeah. So there were.
But people were I will say the people there were psyched.
I think they were in the joint.
I mean, the music gave you no choice but to be psyched.
It was so loud.
It was not as loud as when I saw the Yeezus tour,
which I think I brought up before, where the Yeezus tour base,
which was at the now crypto dot com, then the Staples Center, the Yeezus tour base.
My heart felt like it could stop it.
Like the base felt like it could stop my heart.
It was so like crazy loud and resonating.
And I remember, like, finally, like after five or 10 minutes,
getting used to my heart now going along with whatever the rhythm of
the Yeezus songs were.
So the so the current popular rapper,
Kanye West, had a louder bass than the concert for babies.
Yes. But I'm just saying the concert for babies was very loud.
Louder than concert for babies.
I'm seeing a lot of anything that I take my boy to see.
I was I was worried.
I was like, oh, God, like these kids are going to like their hearing
is going to be affected.
I can't get earplugs into those little ears.
Right. If they make so.
So, yeah. So people there were psyched.
There were there were tents out.
They had a lot of Chucky representatives.
There were just there were two tents out. Yes.
My memory is there were 50.
But I guess two, I guess two is right.
I'm still a little hung up on you saying you had to find the venue,
which if you've never been at the Santa Monica Pier,
you just keep walking towards the ocean until you hit a railing.
Right. But there's like a little bit behind.
It was they essentially took over the parking lot.
Like, I figured I'd find it.
I wasn't too concerned, but it was tucked behind some stuff.
They took over the parking lot where Rockford would park his Winnebago
and the Rockford files. That sounds right. Yes.
Yeah, thereabouts. Thereabouts.
It might be another beach town. You'd be wrong.
So, yeah, no. So I found it.
I found it by following the voice.
I found it by following the hype.
And, you know, we went over there and we waited a little bit.
I got there like 10 minutes before the show started.
But so they had two tents.
One was selling shirts.
One was giving out, Jason, you'll like this and you're going to kick yourself.
You didn't go. Free sunglasses, free waters.
Oh, well. And I know you like a free water.
I love a free water, especially in this heat.
I know I needed it. I actually did not come prepared.
No, I needed it too. It helped dad out.
And they were helping.
They were walking around with the waters, too.
So like they were.
And I saw like Chucky team representatives down by the pier,
like trying to get people in.
Like there were a lot of his street team out.
I think there were more people working it than attending it.
Yes, absolutely.
So there were shirts.
I looked at the shirts.
Nothing was retro enough to justify it.
But not bad.
I think they were only like 12 or 15 bucks, which, you know, that's good
because, you know, concert shirts now 30, 35 bucks, 40 bucks.
Sure. So the baby concert has not followed the trends of the general concert.
Exactly. Yes.
So this free concert, free baby concert was not trying to milk us
if we wanted a free shirt.
I mean, babies are smaller also, so you don't need as much shirt.
The shirts looked big, though.
The shirts looked for adult like they were from big shirts to.
Yeah, sunglasses of all sizes, which is, you know.
Yeah, I have my sunglasses.
I have them in. I think I left them in the car.
But I've been wearing them on when I walked in or you had them on your head.
I thought somewhere they're in the bag or something because I had them.
Yeah. So we got free sunglasses.
And at that point, I thought, is it winter ready? Yeah.
I'm out in the sun. I haven't been on the pier in years.
Free sunglasses, free water. Great.
You're doing great.
So so the the whole show starts pretty quickly.
They do some banter up top and they go into the show right away.
Now, I was happy to learn, especially for the purposes of this episode,
the entire show verbatim is on Apple Music and Spotify's and Spotify.
Yes. So if you want, you can experience this.
This is already a perfect live.
You can experience this when we play it through the microphones right now.
That's right. Or you could go and do it.
You do it yourself.
Well, they can't because it's the last show, I think, is in Fort Worth.
And it's in the past. Oh, I mean, this is coming up.
I mean, they sort of could do it on their own speaker.
And then they could take it on a run or a date.
Which album they put on the summer fun album,
summer concert tour, parentheses live exclamation point,
which you did, you're texting about logistics of this episode.
You said, well, the live album is up on you did refer to it as a live album.
Oh, did I? Mm hmm.
OK. I remember that, by the way, it is it's called live.
So, yeah, yes, yes.
So guess I guess it's not a studio.
It's not a studio.
So but if you hear it, though, that yeah, what this album is, is a lot of
it is it's all the things that happen, including all of the narration of the
it is the full soundtrack of the show mixed with some very optimistic ideas
of what applause would or could be, because there's parts where the
cheering is very loud, there's parts where jokes kill.
There's even parts where there is a full audience.
Oh, which again, when you're looking at a crowd of three year olds,
probably you're not getting a perfect sound, perfect full house level.
Oh, right.
So, yeah, they they the ideal reception is was the way they sweetened this.
I imagined it. Yeah.
And the show is basically the suited characters.
And then there's a human named Jesse that is sort of like helped to wrangle them.
I mean, I guess we can play a little similar to the little shows
that I like at Knott's Berry Farm, where there is one human and then all peanuts.
Yeah. And the human helps the peanuts to dance and get in the spirit,
but also to see and know where they're landing and standing.
Yeah. Jesse, nice gender neutral name.
Right. Could be changed by. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So just I mean, this you probably get the picture, but it's like.
Hi, everyone.
Thanks for joining us for the Chuck E.
Cheese Summer of Fun concert.
My name is Jesse and I'll be your host today.
And now what do you guys say we get this party started?
So they bring out Chuck E.
and Munch at that point.
Yeah, that's kind of the minimal much like stop making sense.
The band comes out in waves and the concert experience builds before your very eyes.
And yes, it's it's it's because of that, and it's not because they need to give
the performers breaks from being in 90 degree heat in these suits.
So they stagger all beach side.
They stagger everyone doing it.
They have tents. You can see they're changing tents very obviously behind.
Right behind that. Yeah. Yeah.
But Munch is the bare minimum you need for a concert because he is the DJ.
So he's doing his DJ act like like when we talked about that one Halloween.
With the head. Yeah, he's not in the head.
He's not in the dead mouse.
Not in the dead mouse. Which would be very awful in the heat.
I would have gone nuts for that.
You're called upon in many cases to say hit it.
DJ Munch, which is far bigger, certain things.
You would have liked that, Jason.
OK, you would have liked it.
What would have been nice.
So they do. They do.
It sounded like a threat the way you said you would have liked it.
You would have liked it.
Like you would have liked it.
Ren for Ren.
You idiot.
So so they do it.
So they do it. The first song, I think the song starts playing and I go,
Scott must be in heaven here because it is called.
What I'm supposed to think is very bad, particularly
a sort of early Beach Boys sound like song.
So it's not exactly outside.
So it's not because it was way too many things to be happy about.
Wait, I missed it. I missed it.
Wait, wait, wait. What's happening?
To talk to the beach ball.
Dive in the ocean.
Let's get your way.
So.
I'm sorry, since when do I do the show with a couple of angels
because I ended up in heaven?
But I thought I go, OK, good.
They're not going to lose, Scott.
They got Scott right away.
His beach party stuff.
He loves the surf and the sun.
Oh, boy. And they started off with a bang.
Don't leave the sand in the sand, of course.
So so that's a quicker.
Got my got my boy going to he's so he's been to Chuck E.
Cheese just in an organic way.
He'll go and then like press every arcade button,
but not actually play the game and then get bored after 20 minutes.
But he's familiar.
I felt the recognition of Chuck E.
Cheese when he came out and being impressed by the Chuck E.
Cheese was very close to him.
And and the dad had muscled his way up and secured some roughly fourth row seats.
So he definitely was like, whoa, like he got it.
The Chuck E.
Cheese is not usually right in front of his face. Right.
So I felt I felt good about it.
This will work for for baby means.
Well, that's good. Yeah, I wasn't sure.
I wasn't sure how he was was was receiving his you and you guys rushed
the front of the stage, which is what I which I did not do because I'm a tall guy.
A lot of kids there.
I thought maybe that would be improper for me to just start pushing kids out of the way
to get to the front of the stage.
Why you have a kid so right in front of you at a room.
Yeah, no, no problem.
So I hung back to be a good spectator.
Good, good. But I was wondering Chuck.
All to pass it off as a baby.
Right. I didn't pull a Billy Zane.
I didn't pull out a child.
I didn't pull a Rex Harrison, Dr.
Doolittle and grab a seal, put a wig on it.
Let me through.
Let me front row center.
Your old your old instincts from like those black flag concerts didn't kick.
Kick in. You didn't get in the pit and start kicking people.
Nope, it didn't happen.
So so yeah, I'm glad that he was enjoying it.
They do some like narrative stuff, which always happened like what happened?
You were supposed to pick Pasquale and Helen Henny up.
And yeah, well, this is OK.
We talked about this a little bit.
This is my favorite part of the show is that for a minute
I wondered, is this going to only be Chuck E.
Cheese and Munch? And then there is some well, here's the big runner is
Jesse, the human encouraging Chuck E.
and being so excited to hear Chuck E.'s song of the summer.
Yes. Yes. And a lot of requests to hear this song.
And he denies her. Yeah. Over and over again.
Each time. And then in this first case, he doesn't feel up to it
because all of his friends aren't there.
And you start to wonder, are they just not here at all?
And we're going through them one by one.
Well, I know Pasquale had to stay back and make pizzas.
So Pasquale has been written out of the show.
He's got to work.
Look, he set up that ghost kitchen.
He knew what he was.
He was he knew he was shooting himself in the foot.
The Earls are on his ass every day.
Robert and Robbie.
He's losing ground in the breakfast club.
And Bella is on vacation with her family.
And you so I can't. And that, yeah, I think.
I got to me and he goes, who's Bella?
Bella. I do. You know, Bella.
I think we learned about Bella.
I don't think it was on the microphone.
I have died on have Bella in my brain.
We may have learned about her off, Mike.
Bella is a new character who depends on the source.
I think some people consider Bella a member of the Make Believe band.
Right. Bella is.
Wait, I had the info about Bella.
Bella is a bunny.
But also known as Bella B.
And so and that's it's a diverse
pick and she's bilingual.
OK, things things in Spanish.
So this is a good there.
There hasn't been a new edition, I would say, in a long time.
So Bella's around.
But it's an odd way for this is only since twenty twenty.
Right. And something new.
Yes. Something new.
Somebody new showed up in a band in twenty twenty.
I don't even know that it happened.
There's an odd way to get this information.
I don't know.
This would have been a great way to introduce the world to Bella.
So that's maybe a complaint.
Don't just mention Bella and make me take me out of the concert
to have to look it up.
Is Bella trying to like.
Yeah, I got to look up Bella.
Don't leave.
Like when the Rolling Stones added Ron Wood, I mean, they they didn't say like,
oh, yeah, he's playing on the album, but he's not on tour with us.
A bit of fanfare.
Yeah. And so you're both in the crowd going, what's the continuity of this?
Like, what are we?
Sorry, Bella.
I know. I know these.
I know everything you're saying was recorded two months ago, but
can you answer me this?
Bella is kind of like Linda McCartney and that she was a member of Wings.
But on the McCartney solo record, she's credited on some of the tracks,
but not everything. Yeah.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
So keyboardists. Yeah.
So we welcome Bella, but Bella's not there.
So you're starting to go, oh, my God, none of Chuck's friends are here.
We're never going to hear the song of the summer. Right.
But luckily, there's two of the heavy hitters roll up.
Thank goodness. All is lost.
Jasper and dog and Helen Helen.
So yeah, she's a bird hen.
Yes, they're out.
So now this concert can really kick into gear and they can do a song.
What did they do? There's a song that's kind of in that like,
like, like, did it?
It didn't. It didn't.
And I play did it. It did.
It's like a little like I don't even know what genre it is.
I'm trying to call this is.
They kept saying play in that really.
Yeah, it's it's it's let's let me let me pull it up here.
It is a modern I'm trying to think what modern song it is.
And I can't I can't place it like Cardi B a little maybe a little bit.
Yeah. I mean, I think there's a couple of songs that's like in the style of
it's a popular style of music these days.
That's the way I believe.
So hold on. Let me see.
I have to gear. I don't know why I shut it off.
But yeah, Chuckie does look.
We know he can. We know he can rap.
Yeah. Well, one of his great strengths.
Yeah. You got to bring to the live venue.
All you can play.
Play all you can play.
As much as you can make time every day to get into playing and make it a plan.
Plan on it.
We're banishing boredom.
Before it's begun.
We'll chase it away because you'll find a way to make anything fun when you play.
Play. All you can play.
Play. Just look for the game.
Find it and you'll find right away that you're working.
One of the same plays important in playtime is gold.
Now more than ever.
So we got it.
We got it.
We didn't get to Chuckie's verse.
That is that is another one where it's just like the music is another song.
And I apologize. People are yelling it, I'm sure.
What that modern song is.
But yes, Chuck has a verse and it's do I like it is what I'm trying to figure out
right now as we're talking about it.
I think I do like it, but it is funny.
I kind of like it.
I still was like amused by it.
I was still like I wish this was, I don't know, another Chuckie day or something.
But I still was OK.
I can get into this. OK.
So they do that.
And then then they have to get Chuckie a munch off the stage before they overheat,
before they collapse.
Chuckie needs a break because Chuckie's been out there a long time.
So they leave Jasper and Helen up there to do a song.
Oh, at this point, I think you were around me.
And I look and I kind of peeked over and I saw Jasper had a guitar strapped.
Yeah. And I was like, oh, baby, here we go.
For a second, I thought, oh, maybe the performer will play it live.
And then I went, what are you going to suddenly?
I said, for a second, any of human hands, the rest of the show?
No, I know.
Of course, it's wrong. I said a half second.
I went, I wonder if I wonder if.
And I went, no, of course, he's not going to do it.
What do you. But it was it was, you know, it was because you were you're reacting.
You were watching this through the eyes of a three year.
You were thinking everything a three year old would think.
But here's the thing. He it was a real guitar.
Why not get like a fake guitar?
Why not just like a. Yeah. Really?
It had strings and I believe so.
It was a real guitar. It was heavy.
I was like, why did they just get a fake guitar?
Like when you get the wooden guitar and pretend fake guitar,
the Chuck E. Cheese Corporation has access to fake instruments.
You're waiting for him to come out on stage and just start going.
There is a house in New York.
Like you're at a Jeremy Renner show.
Driving house on the rise.
Something you I guarantee you will be at at some point in your life.
Oh, I'll go to a Jeremy Renner concert.
Oh, man. The medicine.
That's been definitely delayed since 2020.
I will go see Jeremy Renner any day of the week.
We got to hit you got to hit Johnny Depp and Jeff Beckford.
She Johnny Depp concert.
This is the was this song.
The song about the first time we're going to hear it.
Johnny Depp.
It was it's a shit show.
Johnny Depp is doing an album with 77 year old Jeff Beck.
And the first single is called A Song for Hedy Lamar.
Hedy Lamar, which is a fucking Bowie ripoff song.
It's about her inventions.
Right. But it's actually about Johnny.
OK, like that's really what it's about.
He didn't help win the war.
Lindsay does not like Lindsay's like, I can't deal with this.
I can't deal with this.
No, no.
This vampire was killed when the viper room died.
Also, I figured out somebody's going to be mad at me for saying this,
but this is my take. Jeff Beck stinks.
I don't think I'm just saying this because he's doing this.
I don't know what he thinks.
He's noodle. He's like they're all those guys.
He's their boring friend.
We have to be nice to because he's around.
I am dead yet.
So Jeff's here.
Look, he's got poor self-esteem because he hasn't done anything.
I think good like I only know him.
I only know him from being 14 at used record shops looking for Beck albums.
And I would always hit those first.
And I'm like, who is this isn't right?
This is like a there's like a dragster on the cover.
There should be a little dog hopping over something.
Yeah, it's a weird, furry mush.
Whatever is on the cover.
Yeah. So let's go back to more pleasant topics.
Jasper T.
Jowell's getting a time to shine.
My favorite song of this whole this whole set,
the dog days of summer, which is a well, I like this song.
I like that. Yeah.
OK, I'll give you a little bit of it.
You can hear it's a lot of modern country, you know, it's a little mad.
The summer days growing up at home.
Some of the best times that I've ever known.
Leading with sticks and skipping stones.
What could be better?
I have a list in your country.
I mean, it will get to the course in a second.
Jasper, I think honestly, just put like
Alan Jackson's voice on that and like we're having a party.
That's perfectly like no, no difference needs to be made.
No lyrics need to change.
He's not like talking about like sniffing his own butt or anything like
there's not even really many dog specifics in it.
As part of summer's having a weird dick.
So I feel like a little lipstick and fleas and ticks.
Like it's it's not far.
Don't forget the back medicine on the eighth
the flea medicine on the eighth every month.
Put it in your phone between the show.
I need my pill.
So between the shoulder blades, don't do a glob.
Do the whole neck.
Wipe it off when it was slapped down my sides.
It's going to be 90 dollars.
So, yeah, no, there's not many even dog specifics,
but this is also one where they tell you in the same way when you go
see Ben Folds in college and he'd explain to you how to do the horn part on army.
You know, you'd explain which one side is going to do this part.
But you know, everyone knows, you've seen him.
That's fun.
So they explain to us there's going to be a na na na part,
which they're going to call upon us to do.
And I was very like, army, like when Ben Folds does the army.
You when he's doing it so certain some of the older parents here know
you, sir, with the gray hair.
Yeah, you remember kids oddly late, you know, and only you know.
The one whose better days are far behind him.
You there.
I know.
But remember, but so so.
Summer nights sleeping out underneath the stars so bright.
I wish I may wish I might lick my own ass.
So then I have a lunch and grab a cold.
And we head on down to the home.
Without fear and wonder,
it was a dog day.
It's a hanging out with all my friends.
We'll get to the non-us.
What is the magic spell we're under?
It was a dog day.
It's a na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
Jason, you would like this.
Jason, you would love this.
You would love this.
I love a good na na na na.
Yeah, you would love that.
You know, I got the one thing we had to clap.
And that's one of the things my boy knows how to do.
Yeah, he gets a command that he can fulfill.
So good. So that was good.
Yeah, he he liked this one, I would say.
So I don't want to jump too far ahead.
But since you were there, did you give him like the first time
experience of going to a bubble gum shrimp?
I did not.
That's a stressful location is what I recall.
I think I gave him experience of passing by one and pointing and laughing at it.
Yeah, but now baby's first shrimp did not.
Baby's first overpriced popcorn.
Now, Uncle Michael was drinking an ice cream smoothie
that turned out to not have any alcohol.
Yeah, this is a place where you and Uncle Mike can have the same beverage.
And it's legal.
But only they'll like it more than you.
He'll yeah.
You will only drink a few sips and he'll go, I'll take that off your hands.
I'll finish that for you, my man.
Can I finish that bottle?
I got a headache after the concert, I'll be honest.
Why? I don't know.
Too much sun.
Not enough of the water.
I almost went to the bubble gum, but then I went to forget the name of the place
and I had to tune him out and drink.
Wow. It was nice.
Which was the dog days.
Dog days of summer.
So then right after this, this is my favorite version of the plot coming up.
Yeah.
She's like, all right, so we've done this and that.
And now, Chuckie, it's time for you to sing the song of the summer.
And he's like, no, it's just really flat.
No.
And then you get further.
Finally, he kind of opens up.
He is withholding.
And then they hit a therapy breakthrough.
And what Chuckie thinks is that when the song of the summer has ended
and this concert has ended, that that means that summer has ended.
And Jesse needs to teach him that summer is only just beginning.
And even though this moment has passed, we've got so much summer left
and so many summers left, and that moves him enough to actually to do his fucking job.
Open his trap and start singing the song.
Contract said that he would be there to play.
They did. Yes.
And they did like they did like some happy birthday bullshit
because they're Chuckie Cheese and they have to do that.
It's OK. I mean, it's just like their happy version.
I'll play a second of it, but it's not.
There's nothing to talk about too much.
And it's like the traditional birthday song.
Don't have stage fright.
And then they sort of are the oh, excuse me.
Here's the here's the.
All right.
You win them right now, you freeze.
Can you place this ripoff, Jason?
We say happy birthday.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Happy.
You'll stop your feet.
You're going to kick yourself.
We're not in the ripoff part, I guess.
But it's still the chord progression.
I can go back here. Here. I'll start.
I'll start.
Birthday. Happy birthday.
Birthday. Clap your hands.
He'll stop your feet.
It's time to dance.
Turn to dance. Play your guitar.
It's right there.
I can't play.
Happy birthday.
Sunshine in my pocket.
No, no, no.
It's Timberlake.
The Troll song.
It's the Troll song, which is not the song from Secret Life of Pets,
which is a different, very similar party song at the end of the ride.
Yeah.
Yeah. OK.
Different, different generic.
So, yeah, they do that.
And then, yes, finally, the song of summer is here.
And then at this point, I went, oh, shit, that's it.
We're not getting the songs.
Yeah.
Because obviously that has to be the climax.
So, I mean, he doesn't know what the meaning of the word climax, I guess.
Well, did you take pictures?
Did you get some pictures?
Yeah, I got video. I got pictures.
I'll play the song this summer a little bit for, or unless we want to play that on the way out.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, seems like appropriate exit music.
But, yeah, we're...
Exit music for a podcast episode.
As you file out.
Yeah.
Yeah, so we're reviewing this.
You're not going to be able to see it.
It's done.
It's over.
Nope.
But you can listen to it out, listen to it along with us.
Maybe they'll do it again. Maybe they'll tour next summer.
Maybe they'll add more dates.
This is the second one, apparently.
So they might keep this up.
Yeah.
When they see how amped we all got, except for the end when this one guy got real pouty and they couldn't tell why.
They didn't poll him to find out because they didn't do the songs that he liked.
They didn't give me a free shirt or anything because they saw sad.
They saw the tears hitting the pier.
Now, another free thing, they are giving out a great autographed photo.
Wow.
Yeah, look at that.
There's all of them.
Mr. Munch, Jasper T. Gels, all with distinctive kinds of writing and a cute starfish and a cute beach ball.
Oh, the beach balls came out.
Yeah, I forgot about that too.
What a finale.
Oh, how can you say it wasn't a climax?
Yeah.
They threw beach ball.
The Chucky Street team, all 50 of them had beach balls and then they threw them out while they were doing the song.
There wasn't really like a second round of it.
Everybody just kind of pocketed those beach balls and left.
Yeah, kids got to take the beach balls.
Yeah.
So that's good, but we didn't get one.
So you weren't aggressive enough.
Yeah.
Yeah, because Mike spiked it into your child's head and it bounced into the ocean.
I'm the best at being at this concert.
I'm the best fan of Chucky.
Chucky, come out here.
You're a pretender, kid.
Well, we need to talk about, we need to talk about real quick where I made the, I had to figure out if I was going to wait in line with the children to meet Chucky.
You asked if we were, and I was like, he can't, this guy can't.
Scott said no, they're not.
You can barely keep him in the show.
He kept like, if a helicopter went by.
Yeah.
God.
There's a lot of pointing at the roller coaster.
Yeah, my favorite part of the Chucky Cheese concert was that there was a roller coaster nearby for my son to point to.
Do you do any rides?
What did you consider?
Well, we'll talk later.
Oh, okay.
About Santa Monica Pier.
Oh.
I didn't do anything else, but we wandered a bit.
It was a fun place to, I'm happy with that as like a, hey, and inspired, you know, living in LA, people in LA know, you live in Burbank.
You start thinking Santa Monica is like another state.
You think you need a passport to get over there.
You forget that it could be a quick drive or a nice drive.
And I had a very pleasant day with the boy.
Yeah, it was, I was very happy I went.
I will say the Taco Bell has gone from the Pier, which had bummed me out.
But yes, it was a fun time.
But where else are you going to find those?
Yeah, it's hard to find.
I wanted Pier Taco Bell, though, which is, it hits differently.
It's got extra salt in the air.
But yeah, I mean, more, how often is it that we get to see suited characters dance around to pre-recorded tracks?
Well, I think every day if you go to Chuck E. Cheese down the street.
Well, and we don't have time for it.
We'll discuss it in the next Chuck E. Cheese 3.
And I don't know how soon that's coming.
That's not even planned.
But I was I was looking into the Chuck E. Cheese annual pass program, which exists.
What? So we'll have to discuss this later.
It's a summer. What a tease.
Chuck E. Cheese summer annual pass program they've done the last two years.
So, you know, at Disneyland and Disney World have both shut down their annual pass programs for right now.
Like, they're not selling any new ones.
We can still go.
Well, but there's a lot of confusion.
Well, I have some confusion, which is how do you sell an annual pass for something that is free?
Well, I walk into Chuck E. Cheese and don't have zero dollars when I'm in there.
And maybe we can get to Chuck E.
3 soon, because if we were birdies are burning questions by the end of the dog days of summer.
But maybe by the end of the dog days, we'll do another Chuck E.
Cheese episode and get into this three tier Chuck E.
Cheese annual pass program. Wow.
So that's a tease. OK.
Well, one tier for each of us.
We can compare and contrast. That's right.
Yes, we should all do it.
That's for sure. So, yeah.
So all that to say, you know, go get the album.
Enjoy your summer. We're kicking it off right now.
One thing at the end in the relisting I realized is that it finished
and then everybody got their curtain call before that.
Jesse said, all right, got a hand for everybody.
We're going to remember this for the rest of our lives.
And that's true.
Very grim outlook about the current state of the global warming.
That was a hint. That was a shopping.
This is more about the rest of our lives and about the quality of the thing.
It's a good point. Yeah.
Hey, it I don't know.
I enjoyed it.
I liked it. We got more of an episode out of it than I thought.
Me having vocalized before that, I wasn't sure.
Multiple times, I was like, is there enough to talk about?
Are we sure? I have no thoughts about this place.
Yes. I said I have.
I don't think I had more than a minute to say to my wife,
whose son was a participant at it.
Look at us. We started a lot was said.
I really like the exchange where it was a lot of there was a lot of back
and forth that was like, do we think this will be enough?
And you said, I think this will be enough.
And then I said, I think it's well, maybe it's a little funny
that like you think it'll be plenty.
And I'm not so sure.
Maybe that's the dynamic for the episode. Yeah.
And you said, yes. Also, I didn't say plenty. Yeah.
Well, I wanted to make I know this isn't like a three hour country bear start.
Like, I know there's not that for this.
It was just such a it was a funny little like I wanted to be on record.
So to be said in a trial.
Now, by the way, I didn't say plenty.
Yeah, I wanted to make sure it was clear that I never said, oh, my God.
There's one show.
There is so much to talk about when it comes to this show.
Don't put in the word plenty in my mouth.
Okay. I would say plenty to us all.
It truly was another Chucky day.
Well, and now to play us out of the song we'll remember for the rest of our lives.
Yeah, let's do this here.
This lobby.
OK, now, everybody.
There's a part a little later in the song.
I forgot you survived podcast, the riot and do the guys.
Put three years up.
Also, this is clearly juice by Lizzo.
Oh, yes, that's where it is.
I couldn't figure out what was a ripoff.
All right. God, it's driving me crazy, actually.
That helps.
Chucky feels like it's over.
We've been together.
So come on out.
This is kind of a ripoff of both.
Yes, there is.
And then I'm going to go outside and play.
And it's so good to feel the sun is shining down,
down on the ground and it's so good to see all my friends are coming around.
I'm so excited now.
So turn up the radio and play my favorite song.
I don't want any other.
It's in my song.
So it's a stereo.
We can sing along.
I don't want any other.
So sing the song of summer with me.
Wow.
Sing the song of summer with me.