Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride The Second Gate, where today we're saying faith in begora, Patrick
begora that is. I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson. I am here. Is there a way we
could have your name be like Jason begora? Like a new moniker? I could certainly add it to the list,
Scott Gardner. You've been given a lot of odd nicknames. Yeah, no, I know. I think the way is
by saying it. He is today. He's Jason begora today. Uh huh. Yeah, would you would do you like it?
I like it. Okay, well, it doesn't sound like you're that into it. So never mind.
Well, I looked this up, just just to be certain. Begora is a euphemism for the phrase by God.
Sometimes you hear it in the phrase of faith in begora, which is the Irish equivalent of an
American saying by golly or by gosh. By gosh. Begora, of course, I know there's one place I've
heard it the most. I'm pretty sure. And you guys know what I'm talking about? No. Well, it was,
it's said on the Batman 60s show by the not Commissioner Gordon, but the other guy,
the other guy. Yes. His name O'Hara, Chief O'Hara. Yes. He says, Oh, but gore a lot.
And then sometimes bad, at least once Batman said begora because I just saw it. There's a Instagram
account I followed. It's just Batman 66 clips and pictures. And Batman ends one of these clips by
saying begora. It's a wonderful, stiff, and a very neat. Okay. So we're so that's the cultural
significance of that for me. Yeah. For us, I guess it's involved. It's of course, Patrick begora,
the little man of Disneyland, little man of Disneyland. This is one of those. I think I
learned about this within an episode. I didn't know about it, but I don't know why it came up
before, but this was news to me, but kind of delightful to learn more about. Yeah. I,
well, I had to go back and I pieced together how I first heard of it, which was only a few years ago.
But I do want to shout out. Thank you to Roxy Cohen and Taylor Haney, Tyler Haney, who recently
suggested this topic and a pretty, pretty good timing with how he came up for us. So now they
suggested it. So here we are, but it is, you mean because they suggested and now we're doing it.
Is there more to the time? I think it came up naturally on an episode. And then I saw these
mentioned in the comments. You were smiling though, in a way that made me think, well, it's pretty
good timing because by the way, I have the character in my pocket. Here he is. Like it was
something like you had a little secret. I was smiling more because I was proud of myself that I
wrote down, don't forget to say this at the top. And I didn't forget to say that. You were proud
of yourself. I was just proud of myself for doing the bare minimum. You were smiling so wide.
Well, I'm doing it. You're beaming. I said to say the names. I don't know how I'm saying the names.
I mean, this is a delightful topic. I mean, I agree. I am tickled by all of this. So the little man
of Disneyland, if you don't know, kind of started in 1955. There was a, oh God, what is it called?
Little golden book. Little golden book. Little golden book. Yeah. Why is it? It's the little man
of Disney. Oh, you're right. The little man of Disney. Yeah. Okay. Keeping those tees, gang.
And eventually they put in a tiny little door in Adventureland as like a little Easter egg
was removed for a while. But then in 2015, they went all in on the little man of Disneyland.
Now, yeah, they went all in. Now, correct me if I'm wrong. Did I not learn about this from John
Lasseter? I think I learned this from John Lasseter. Not personally, not one. I believe he was
involved in the presentation at D23. Yeah. There was a big coordinated efforts to bring this
bit of old mythology back in 2015. Okay. Yeah. They re-released the book in 2015. And I think
at least for the initial release, you can only get this at the publisher's booth at the D23 event.
And now it's kind of available everywhere. Okay. I borrowed a Kindle copy from the LA library. That's
how I got ahold of it. Oh, nice. Okay. Well, there we go. We got an easy way for everybody to
experience this story and follow along with us. We're not going to read it to you, but we'll go
through it. But maybe for another Patreon tier, Jason should read it to you. Oh, Jason's Tuck-ins.
Would you do a Club 3 exclusive reading to the listener? Oh, it's not a long book. Of different
voices and stuff? Well, now you're giving yourself more work. I'm all for it. But just at least one.
If I'm going all in, I'll go all in. Read the book and then I will put under it the baby
Aerosmith song, Don't Want to Miss a Thing. Like the lullaby, I Don't Want to Miss a Thing,
which is not the first time I've put that music under you. You mean from those bad Spotify albums
where they just kind of midi style turn? It's Jason Reed's Little Man of Disneyland to Your Sleep.
That's going to be, we're going to do this. This is easy. Let's put in the next round of voting.
No votes. We're doing it. They get it. Oh, people. Okay. All right. They're getting it.
That's a bonus. That's not an official. That's just a bonus. That's a bonus. That's a bonus.
I'll do that. You can do that. Why is it Aerosmith? Why are they the lullaby? Because I have the file
on my desktop. Because I don't want to rip a new file. Yeah. Well, but that's Club 3. So I guess
that's an exclusive item. Okay. Well, Donald appears in the books. You're going to have to do
some Donald dialogue. What did Jason, what he wants to do with the voice. I'm not going to edit
him at all. Well, that's a funny thing. I mean, that's a big thing I have to say about the book,
which is that there's no, I mean, it's cute. It's very funny, but there's not really an attempt,
I feel like, to make the characters like there's, it's not spelled phonetically. Like when Donald
talks, Goofy talks, it just sounds like guys. Yeah. They're just like humans. Yeah. Yeah. They're
just like humans. Like I'm just going to read a passage because this is how I heard it in my head.
Who are we? Cried Donald Duck. Don't you go to the movies? Don't you watch TV? Don't you read books
or newspapers? Don't you know Goofy and Pluto? Don't you know Donald Duck? No, said Patrick.
And he blew a smoke ring right in Donald's face. Good. Good for after that, after that entitled
rant. Yeah. So angry. Yeah. Much deserved. When I read it, I think I will try to do a voice
for Patrick, but not for anyone else. Cause everyone else is just like, yeah, man, we got
this construction project we're doing. Okay. Can I give you one more? I think don't even think about
it. Don't attempt. Don't try it ahead of time. Oh no. Good. And only one, only one take. One take
of the whole book. Yes. No, no edits. There's a lot of pressure. No, no pressure at all. You're free.
We're just going to do it or we'll do it live. We'll do it next time we record. Okay.
Jason, now Jason's clam that now you're worried about doing it at home. Yeah, I don't care.
But how are you going to know that he's not, he might be slipping other takes in there.
I'll know. You need to be watching. I'll know if you don't know. It'll be a separate file
unless he's editing it and then putting it back on the memory card.
Which I don't think he's going to do. Yeah. He'd have to like reassemble what a raw file
would look like. Okay. Okay. Yeah. So there's no way. Okay. So you'll have a, there's a fail safe.
My memory of this is around 2015 because there was a Disney parks blog post explaining
what this was and to keep an eye out for it at adventure land.
And there, the May, 2010s, I feel like at Disneyland, they redid California adventure in
2012 and then they coasted on that for a while. And so there would be little things like, oh,
there's a little theater show next to the castle now and there's Maurice's treats. And I, I feel
like I would get excited. I was like, oh, there's something new. And I would go down and he like,
well, this is kind of a nothing, but I remember it's 2015 reading about the little man of Disneyland
and looking up more what it meant. And I was like, okay, next time I get to that park,
I got to find this tiny door. This felt like enough to you. This is okay. We had cars land
and now we have a little door in the bottom of a tree, a little door and a little window and a
little smoke stack. Yep. Yep. And that's what we got. That's what this is about. So there's a book
about it's a leprechaun, just to say a book about a leprechaun who lives at Disneyland.
And then, and then there's a little bit of drama that happens, but there's an agreement that he
will continue to live at Disneyland. And now you can go to Disneyland and see his little door and
his little smoke stack and his window. Does that all, I mean, I get all three of the things. Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. He lived in an orange tree. He lived in like the orange groves and when they were
gutting it, when, when the character, the characters also being pretty hands-on with the construction
of Disneyland. Yeah. They're building the park. Which is what I obviously like to see. Yeah. That's
in line with that. They continue to this day to do all of the cleaning and manual labor, getting it
visitor ready. They, you know, in, in Cannes and Joe Rody had nothing to do with the guardians overlay.
It was a series of tunes who were conceiving of a new ride version of the ride and building it.
Who had to go meet with the people at the elevator company. Right. Figure out different,
you know, patterns that the, that the elevate. So the characters have to know a lot about
physics and engineering. Yeah. Yeah. Everything. The characters, they really, cause how many like
areas do you have to be an expert in to be an Imagineer? Many. Yeah. So they have the
Disney characters in addition to being fun and funny also know everything. Who would be a,
a dis of all the tunes who would be like lead Imagineer, like Ludwig von Drake or gyro gear loose?
Yeah, I would think you would want at least in a ceremony, at least in an oversight, like,
you know, top of the chain. But like, yeah, like are there any other like good with plan
drawing a plan type? I mean, both gyro and Ludwig kind of screwed things up a lot. Yeah.
Um, the, uh, the Etch A Sketch from Toy Story has the ability to produce a, you know, geometrically
right. Yeah. Like fine points diagram out of it. So maybe he's not leading it up, but you want
Etch A Sketch around, right? Cause he's a, he's a supercomputer essentially. The Etch A Sketch and
horse horse collar are, uh, you know, they're the ones really burning the midnight oil. Yeah. Right.
Horace is the kind of the public facing. He's like, he deals with the people in the management.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, Ludwig or gyro might be like taking the two hour lunches or like,
Oh, I, they, I'm out at five every day. Sometimes four or three, you know,
they rest on their laurels or they're a little lazy. Yeah. Well, somebody needs to do this.
Somebody needs to show this version of, of Canon where the tunes are designing rides. Yeah. And
where all the character, one thing I like about kind of tune Canon and tune town and all that
is that it implies that all of the characters that ever were and ever will be exist already.
And they, maybe they just haven't been cast in a movie. Oh, I see. Yeah. Cause I think in Roger
Rabbit, there are characters around, even though they're in the year that that movie is set,
they have not, their movie isn't out yet. I can't name who those are. I forget if like Dumbo wasn't
out. Um, but that's the, you know, so like, uh, Mirabelle from Encanto has been living in tune
town. Oh wow. And just waiting for a big break for 80 and just like, please cast me. And it took,
it just took that long. I had to rely. I relate to that. I relate to that hard. Any actor. Yeah.
The algorithms just feeding you annoying things of like, you know, uh, so and so really didn't get
their first big break until they were 45, you know, they were doing bit parts for years.
But they, at a certain point, these annoying me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She auditioned for like to be
in the background of wind in the willows. Didn't work. Yeah. So there's, so there's characters who
are around who won't be in a movie for still decades to come. Well, cause yeah, they're immortal
too. So yeah, for all the tunes that exist now are the only tunes that will ever exist. It's like,
um, energy. Let's say all the energy is it exists already. Yeah. Go away. Yeah. Yeah. It's just there
and it moves around. It's a little creepy in a way. All the characters are like, they're really,
just to put it in another simple way, they're all bicentennial men. Right.
They're all like Robin Williams, the robot who lives, who outlives his
owners many times over. Right. So that's the rules of tunes. Yeah. And I guess the rules of the little
man of. Oh yeah. You would have to be, you would have had to be hanging out. Maybe that's not
correct though, because there's something weird about like he, is it in the book that he like
outlives all his people? Isn't that in it? He's the last one. Yeah. He's the last one. It also shows up
not a lot of Patrick Bagura appearances in other things, except that Tales of Adventureland,
YA adventure series. Oh that, yeah. I know that. It came up wearing the sea stuff because like we're
trying to dig, trying to like ring the washcloth of like, where are the sea mentions? Where are the
cannon like mentions and this Tales of Adventureland? It's like, okay, the robot shows up there,
but does the robot in the sea? Like, you know, that sort of thing. What was the last thing you said?
Does the robot inging sing? I said the robot is like in the book, but is he there? Is he in sea?
Oh, okay. Is he in sea? Okay. Yeah. What robot though? I don't know. I'm just using that as an example.
Someone made like a steam punk robot, I feel like. Are you thinking of Dr. Tootsom? I'm not thinking
of Dr. Tootsom and his grotesque creations. The only thing, the only hope right now is that the
smokestacks are rising above our city walk, over City Walk Hollywood. The guitar is gone. The guitar
is rising in its place. So the famous Toothsome Emporium smokestacks. It's a great, we don't,
look, I don't think we're happy about the Olympics in LA, but this is, this is what could, this is the
torch of hope for Los Angeles. It's the only thing I'm holding out hope for. Yeah. Yeah. I've been
there a couple of times at like one in the morning. Like I've gone to the last showing at the movie
theater for like a couple movies and at 12, 30 AM, one in the morning, there is like a dozen people
and that thing is fully lit up with work lights. And they are like, working on it. I think there were
people waiting for it still. Like waiting for it to open. Oh no, banging on it. Praying, holding a vigil,
like the steampunk chocolate plates will be open. People on the top of the building.
I have been thinking about City Walk. I've been thinking since the Tim Kelpaca
episode, I've been thinking about Womp Hoppers every day. Yeah. Oh, good, good. Yeah. I apologize.
I'm so, I feel bad for Womp Hopper that we forgot him. We forgot the name Womp Hopper. I knew it was
a wagon thing. Wagon works. Wagon wheel. Wagon works. I believe wagon works. Okay. So it's a step
back in that direction that there is a character who only lives at City Walk. He's got a big sizable
campus up there. Yeah. Yeah. It's great. Womp Hoppers. It's also funny to me, I had the recent,
we got out of a movie at 9.45 at City Walk. It's really funny that like, oh, so you want to get a
drink? Uh oh. Like, just no, like who would, why should we have like a bar open at the, anywhere
at this place at 10 o'clock? Are you a maniac? It used to be, yes, because we would go to a movie
and this was years ago already at this point, I guess, because it was maybe Age of Ultron,
which is eight years ago, seven years ago. Yeah. And the only place to go was Howl at the Moon
or Saddle Ranch. All gone. After 10 or 11. Yeah. And now it's, yeah, there's nothing. Yeah. It's
gotta be a weekend and then you get midnight if you're lucky. This is a revenue stream we can do
without. We don't want a bunch of luscious vomiting on our dancing fountains. And it's not
Orlando. Just, you know, act with people late. Right. Orlando is a party spot and City Walk,
Hollywood, they do not want partying. They got Howl at the Moon. That was the nail in the coffin.
Yeah. That was, remember the, the weird thing where a security guy at Howl at the Moon had to carry
your drink six feet between the entrance. Do I remember that? What do you mean? That's a vivid,
one of the crucial memories of our lives. We brought that up a few times. I don't know,
at the last few years, who remembers anything? But that was still so strange to me. Well, yeah,
because yeah, basically, if you don't know what we're talking about, there's a section where you
can drink on a balcony at Howl at the Moon, which is on the third, the third floor, I think. Yeah,
right? Yeah. Of City Loft. In City Loft. Where the bars are. So there's the inside of Howl at the
Moon and then there's a little balcony area. But to get to the balcony area, you have to cross
the sidewalk and now you're not, it's, it's not legal to drink on that sidewalk or hold an
alcoholic beverage. Yeah. So a person, an employee has to surf your beverage from the, from the
inside of the bar to the balcony area, and then you can take it again. A licensed beverage holder.
Yes. To walk at three feet. And maybe that's why it closed. Maybe that was too expensive to hire
a person to surf your beverage. Well, just the training that they have to pay for. Well, of
course. To put them in simulators and they don't let them do it with real alcohol. They put like
sugar water in it that simulates the weight of alcohol. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So surf is probably
like the industry term for it. That makes it sound more real. Sounds cool. But I did go to a fancy
restaurant once where like, oh, your table is ready. And we were at the bar and they like put
like two wine glasses on a little stone slate and they carried that. I think, I think this guy came
up on the episode. We talked about it. Everything that we've just said the last five minutes. Again,
this is why I've brought up the five timers club. I think that we are like inducting members into
the five timers club every episode. And we don't even know. By that I mean stories that we've told.
These stories have been told. I'm saying that there's other stories that we're not even aware
of where I'm like, I'm telling this fresh anecdote for the first time. This definitely came out
because it's one of the weirdest things I've ever seen in a restaurant. And I'm sure in fine dining,
it's kind of standard. Yeah. But it was still very strange that they keep like, and this is where we
keep the little stack of slate that we use to serve beverages. Yeah. Sure. 10 feet to a two top.
Now that I don't know if we named it surfing. That could be. But who knows? Yeah. Well,
we were so blacked out on blue curacao in that episode. Oh yeah. Let's get from blue to green.
Let's head over to, let's get back. Let's get to the luck of the Irish.
So let's see other big moments that I feel like we should mention. It's kind of established early
on. So yeah, Patrick lives in a little tree. They're gutting the orchard. They're gutting it all.
We might need to explain this from the ground up a little bit. Like the, so yes,
Patrick is the last leprechaun. Right. His people have been, I don't know what.
Let your imagination run wild with what that means. Cause they're magical creatures.
I've buried 700 friends. Yeah. Or heat killed them all. Maybe he didn't want competition.
In the final book in the Tales from Adventureland series titled the doomsday device,
Patrick Magora guards the eternal tree. An enchanted date palm also referred to as the
Dominguez palm, which is a reference to the, uh, what did they say? The oldest actual tree
Disneyland. And that was part of the fine print is like, you have to keep this tree.
Walt, you can have this land. The original owners of the land. The original owners was like, you
have to keep this alive. And the Dominguez palm is still in Adventureland. It's moved once or twice.
Over the years, this stuff got built up more. So all the famous, all the notable trees of the
existing land owners, fictional or otherwise are in Adventureland. So basically if you read this
book, the Easter egg has a second Easter egg inside of it. Uh, it's like those Cadbury that
they had to take the toys out of. I like that I go to Rustin Russian nesting done. You go to
treats with prizes. Cadbury eggs had toys in them? No, those, uh, sorry, uh, kinder balls, uh,
kinder like, yeah, I know, I know. So now the toy is in the box next to the egg, not inside the
hollow egg. You don't have to shop through to get to the toy. But yeah, so this, so it's a leprechaun
who lived in an Anaheim orange Grove before Disneyland was built or being considered to be
built. Yeah. And he is like a tiny leprechaun and dressed like you are imagining. He smokes a pipe,
smokes a pipe on like every page and yeah, he blasts a smoke ring at Donald. So funny. Yeah.
So now we have some dueling mythologies, which is that we've, cause we discussed that toon town
origin story where the tunes already live toon town existed before Disneyland. And then they said
to Walt, Hey, why don't you build in our backyard? So there's that where the eternal tunes. So why
not use this orange group? Nobody lives there. What they didn't know is a leprechaun lived there.
So separate things way up at the top of the property tunes. Then this leprechaun living in
a single, a leprechaun living in a citrus tree as you do, right. That adds up to me. Um, and,
but then there's a bunch of like construction hubbub. He goes outside. What's all this racket upset
about it. Yeah. And, uh, yeah, Donald's kind of fresh to him and he gets a smoke ring in the face.
Donald kind of doubles down and then Patrick like blasts his ass with magic.
It's established that Patrick has powers, right? Yeah. But it's kind of like, it's the, the, the,
like the Twilight Zone with the kid who controls the town where it's like, you only see the powers
in action a little bit. He, um, yeah, he, he shatters Donald shovel. Is that correct? Yes.
Just like, and he puts him, knocks him right on his seat. You could destroy matter. Yeah. Which
is pretty scary. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know, this guy's somebody to be reckoned with. They could,
it's a good thing they ran into him at this point and not further into the construction
because they could have had the castle fully built ready to go. Right. And he shatters it with his
mind. Yeah. That would have been scary. Shit. Yeah. That's a book. Now, honestly, in, in, in,
you know, cause he's living in Disneyland, he could still do it at any moment. Oh yeah. If he,
if he changes his mind or doesn't like the way like you're, you're playing with like a dark
Phoenix level of power here. Yeah. This definitely an Omega mutant kind of thing. Like high class
X-Men level mutant powers displaying here. Black Tom Cassidy, Proteus, Moira, Moira McTaggart's,
son. Yeah. All of them. Yeah. All of them. Another fine Irish reality warper, Patrick Magora,
Proteus. Yeah. Yeah. Proteus. Yeah. So he could, I guess for more current reference, he could do
the snap at any moment. He could. That one I know. It's like he has the power of the Infinity Gauntlet.
The Infinity Gauntlet. The reality stone. That's the luck of the Irish baby. That's how powerful it is.
What's the reality stone? You can change reality. Yeah. There's like different, there's a Time
Stone. There's a Reality Stone. Those are all the different things. Yeah. The color. Yeah. The gauntlet.
That's right. Okay. So yeah, this guy's, don't mess with this guy. Yeah. Yeah. And then Mickey
comes in down by going like, hold on, hold on. We'll show you the plants. Let's all get in a
helicopter. That is so great. Mickey Mouse tells a three inch tall leprechaun. It's like, all right,
we understand your concerns. We need to get in a helicopter. And we'll explain everything.
Which the D23 article noted about this all coming back noted that's actually how Walt would go from
the Burbank Studios down to Anaheim. He would ride a helicopter. Well, it's also what he would
do. I mean, this is like, okay, so this is a scenario where we want to build something on
this land, but there's people on or near the land who don't want our thing built. So what do we do?
Well, once we explain what it is we're doing, it's going to be fun. This is really, it really is like
an instructional playbook. Maybe it was written for those reasons to like, okay, so in the future,
you're ever trying to build near a Civil War battlefield. Here is the need to get in there,
talk to the locals, convince that look, this is going to be good for your like, you might,
hey, you might end up with a job. Hey, Patrick, there's plenty you can do. You can go, you're
very small. You can scrub all our pipes with a little brush. You can be the busiest little
plumber in all of Disneyland. That's exactly right. Except I think Walt would have been like,
Civil War battlefield. No way. Keep that. Keep that as is. Oh, that's true. He may have not liked
that. But anything else, Native American reservation here, guys, let me show you what we're doing.
We'll make your land better. Yeah. Everything else. Yeah. Swan planned. Swan. Well, we need
to build a bunch of stuff. Arm around the gators. Don't destroy the ecosystem too much, but you can
destroy it a little. Dredge it a little. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's like, it's not shock and awe
because he's not hurting them, but it is just, it's, it's, it's awe. How about it's only awe?
It's only awe. You did, it sounds not good what I'm doing. And then I bought all this property
shady way from underneath you essentially to keep the values down. But when you see like there's,
you're going to get to ride around in an elephant. Now are you impressed? And in Patrick's case,
absolutely. He kind of just looks over the plans and got it. Cool. No, I'm, you know what, now that
I see, now that I see what you're doing and the kind of joy you're going to bring, I sign off 100%.
Now I get it. Yeah. He eats, he's like a rocket to the moon. Like this is incredible. Like everything
he's kind of overwhelmed. The, there is a, a fun page where like Mickey and Goofy and Patrick
are looking at concept art, which is based apparently on actual concept art. And the,
I have some names, the illustrator, the actual illustrator of the book, Dick Kelsey,
adapted the concept art and he was a real, like he was on staff at Disney. He joined Disney in
1940, worked as an animator, art director and writer, worked on Pinocchio, Fantasia,
and Alice in Wonderland. And then the, the writer of the Little Man from Disneyland book
was a Golden writer, Jan Warner. She wrote under the name Annie North Bedford.
Annie North Bedford. Yeah. The address of the little Golden Books headquarters was on,
it was on North Bedford Avenue. Beverly Hills. Beverly Hills. Yeah. So a pen name,
and she wrote like 400 little Golden Books. By the way, little Golden Books are very nice. These
exist in my parent ecosystem. They still do them. They do them for new movies. We just got one of
Budsatopia. It's like, I feel a nice comfort wash over me when I see that gold stripe on the side
of, cause it's not only my childhood, but I could sense that I could sense that coming from my mom's
childhood. And maybe before that, I don't remember, I don't know when Golden Books started,
but there's a, I don't know. I let, you know what? I'm just going to, I'm going to give that stripe
a little swipe next to it. Just kind of like wipe my thumb down that and see how nice I feel after.
Yeah. As a kid, that's what I, I mean, I remember the books, but I remember the spine.
I remember that. I'm like, Ooh, yeah. Look at that golden spine. Like, yeah, let's just like,
let's just take those spines. What if the book was just the spine? What was all spine?
You know, that's a little, I think there's a little smoking a cigarette feel to just like
foop, just run in your hands and that thing. It's, I'm just going to get a lot of golden book spines.
I'm going to de-spine all the golden books. That is some like adult, like relaxation technique.
Like put a big golden spine on a door in your house and then just rub it when you're feeling
stressed. It's a great fidget spinner. We just invented a fidget spinner. If you can make your
door into a big golden book, then you can rub the spine when life is getting you down.
Try it. All right. Cool. Well, I'm going to start, then I'll start stripping them with their spines
and throwing the rest of the books away. Yeah. The book gives a shit corporate trash, but that spine.
Yeah, that's good. That's good. That's comforting. I think it's kind of funny also that this is a,
with the magic involved here, Mickey Mouse meets a leprechaun and then what happens?
We put them on a helicopter and take them to look at some blueprints.
There's a really fun mix in this story of magic and practical. Yeah. Yeah. But also, but you know,
it's magical in its own way for a leprechaun to get to see a helicopter. I mean, it's so huge to
him. He could live his life in it. He's, but this could book could have gone a different way where
can this be my home now? Yeah. Is there, does the leprechaun in the movie, the horror movies,
the leprechaun, does he ever go on a helicopter? I don't think so. Hmm. I'm not a hundred percent
on that either way. Has anyone watched any of the leprechaun movies? I haven't. I was too scared as
a kid. You've never seen any of them? No. No. Even like clips? Not really. Leprechaun in the hood?
I'm aware of it. Don't know anything. Have you ever seen a clip of a leprechaun smoke a bong?
No, he does. Oh, that's great. Well, you've got to watch leprechaun in the hood at least.
Look, haven't seen that part, but that's, you know, if we're comparing leprechaun media,
that's pretty exciting. Yeah. So, so I've only seen, I have not seen all, I'm not a big leprechaun.
I've seen like the first one and I've seen leprechaun in the hood. And then there's another,
I forget what the one before that maybe I'm not seeing the greatest movies. I'm just wondering,
like, is there precedent for a leprechaun in a helicopter? Because they get sillier as they go.
So I wonder if there was any, like he was on a sightseeing tour or he was well, he doesn't,
he doesn't smoke a bong and then operate a helicopter, does he? I hope not. Dangerous
for himself in it. I'm concerned about him. I know he is a bloodthirsty leprechaun. Yeah. He's
an evil. I don't want him to hurt himself. He is not like Patrick Begora. No, Patrick doesn't,
besides like giving Donald a little ouchy. He doesn't really do anything. Deserves it. This is
not a good situation that they are just tearing up his, that Mickey at least is, you know,
he, he tries to be a mediator, right? But Donald is just like, this is a pest. We have a plan here.
We're going to build a 1800s America in your, and we, I don't care if you lived here, get the
fuck out. It's such a funny thing though, cause, cause the way you would want to present Disneyland,
I feel like in the fantastical way is that this stuff is here. You're just there. So when you see
it presented in a way that literally they have to dig holes in the middle of a thing that already
exists is funny to me. Donald Duck himself has to go in there with a shovel. But, but like the
distinction being like the way Disneyland is presented is like not that this is fake. It is
real. This is actually a real main street that was just built because there was a necessity.
There was a necessity to build the guardians, whatever, all that stuff makes sense as opposed
to just like, yeah, Mickey, Donald, if you want to make some cash. So they go into a forest cause
they're going to build like what Walt's America was like, so they can sell candy. Like that it's,
it's not really the way you would want to present it. We're milking daddy's childhood for sweet
coin. We're going to make some sweet coin. So we've got to get you out of here, Patrick. Oh,
taffy. Yeah. Sure. He loved taffy. All right. Taffy. Let's sell some glassware. $150.
We'll have a glass blower in there. 75%. I mean, they do do a handshake deal. Like you can stay
here, Patrick. And the they're like, we can help you find a place. And he's like, no, I've
picked something out. Like they eat, they, you're just like, okay, man, whatever. And Mickey says,
we'll, he just says, can I have a wee place after you've finished this Disneyland? And Mickey says,
fine. Which I am out. Fine. Fine. Oh God. We have to let you live somewhere. We can't just pop you
in the head. Don't be in the littlest ditch. Donald, it's like a tick. Donald 20 seconds to build that
ditch. This guy's got powers. We can't kill him. He could probably rise from the grave, get us in
the end. We've got to make a deal with him. Outsmarted by a damn patty again. Walt warned us.
So he says, we'll be fine. We'll build you that house. How about one of these? So they're going
to bet they do offer to build him. And in addition to everything else they have to do, they're going
to build the leprechaun a house from scratch. Which probably they were going to do it so begrudgingly.
It was going to suck. So Patrick's right to ask for his own. He's smart to make a deal here. He's
smart to make a deal. He's also like, I guess kind of a minimalist because all of his stuff fits in
like a tiny wheelbarrow proportional to him. But it seems like a reasonably easy move.
Yeah. So, so.
Where was he before do we think? Was he like, was it just kind of in the middle or, I mean,
it could have been anywhere. If it was all orange trees then.
Yeah. I think he probably had his pick. Now the original, I was trying to find, I was having
trouble finding like a picture of the original home, but apparently when you are getting off
the jungle cruise, there's like a concrete kind of tree. And that's where you would see his little
door before. Right. Okay.
And I'm not, that was removed at some point and then yeah, put back in with a fair amount of fan
fare at the 2015 D23. That's the other thing. They were selling the book. They were selling the new
printing of the book and they're also, and he might just magically appear this weekend at Disneyland,
his little home, you know, which if you go to the big sign that says the Indiana Jones adventure,
look at the bottom of a tree around there and you'll see it. I'm breaking cave. Fabe dizzy
at a whole like thing of cave. Fabe. Uh huh. Are you okay? You just seem like I'm having bad
indigestion. Oh, okay. What from what? Tell us.
I had like a bell, like breakfast biscuits, like a crispy like Belvita biscuit and a banana
and a cup of ice coffee. It was the banana. The morning banana. Jason's kryptonite. Yeah.
I'm allergic to banana too. Bananas are bad. Yeah. That is the lesson of this show because
we discovered this before the Jason, you have a banana in the morning is the worst thing you
can do to yourself. And then we had the day where I have to think about this one ever since. We had
a day where we ate hot dogs all day and then I felt bad the next day. And you said it's because
I had a bowl of cereal when I got home, you pinned it on. Well, that's, that's a lot of sugar.
Surely it is not the day's worth of hot dog. It was the confidence in the dogs.
It was not a lot of hot, but I'm just saying for sure it could not have been the hot dogs.
It definitely was a slightly sugary, but some of it natural, some of it from blueberries.
Maybe protein, straight protein. That's all. Yeah. Spoonful of peanut butter glass,
ice water, sugar to that. Depending on the peanut butter can be a little too sugary.
Yeah. I keep an eye out for it. What kind of, what kind of peanut butter? I am a, a skippy
natural guy. See I have that too, but that still tastes sugary to me, even though it claims it.
That doesn't think it's that. It's just like candy. It's delicious. But then there was also
the one where you were having the full fat Coke. Yeah. But then you and Jason, you got critical,
but then you said you were having a bit, you, I was full of that sprite, but then you said you
were having a Big Mac later than I have that bowl of cereal. This is what I'm just trying to figure
out the rubric of good eating and bad eating. I don't think when I said this show, I don't think
I was saying you were eating poorly. I was, I was suggesting that the cereal wasn't helpful versus
I wasn't saying like, Oh, you're eating poorly. And I wasn't saying like, Oh, I eat better. I'm
just saying, sure. I was saying though, I think like, you know, much like after like a workout,
you need protein, you need to replenish your electrolytes. So, you know, you did a full
Disneyland day with hot dogs. You need to like, whatever banana and blueberry and some flakes,
whatever. That was what did it. Whatever supplements Joe Rogan takes after his workout.
I don't know. I don't listen to the show, but whatever it is, I think that's what you should
have done. It's a straight protein. And then I should have just pure powder, some powder.
Maybe you should have had powder after probably should have done like a line of powder.
Yeah. Just get four, four little lines in a row snort, snort or lick.
Just hit the punching bag for a while. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Late night creatine bump, you know? Yeah.
Punching bag. That'll settle the hot dogs. That'll settle the hot dogs. Now you're doing
it. Now you're just kind of like, like kind of plot. You seem like you're plotting.
I recall the other detail that is happening with the Big Mac was that I wanted a chocolate
shake with it, but the only coupon in the McDonald's app was buy one milkshake, get one free.
And I was like, Oh no, you had two milkshakes. You can't not use the coupon. It would not be an
option. Why bother? You can do both in one. After full fat spray, you're at full fat spray. That's
going to keep you out. Then two milkshakes. Well, I had a good night's sleep the night before. I had
a great night's sleep after that. No, I ate half of a chocolate shake and a half of a vanilla shake.
And then I combined them and drank that the next day. So next morning, like lunchtime the next day.
Okay. Lunchtime. Yeah. It's a long time for milk to sit around in the freezer. That's not so bad.
It'll ice creamify too much more than a shake. The consistency won't be as good as fresh out of the
machine, but it's not so bad. Wow. Okay. Yeah. So are you recovering? Are you because you're having
a little? No, I feel great. No, right now you do? Huh? Yeah, I feel pretty good right now. Okay. You
were saying you were dealing with some indigestion just a couple of minutes ago. I don't know. I was
just burping. It was just repeating on me. The guy had a banana. Let's have some sympathy. I know.
I start coughing when I have a banana. I have like a pollen. Okay. Listeners, tell me your,
let's hear them all. Let's hear all your banana horror stories. I like Jason have present have
are making it not no longer a stigma. No, the degree to which bananas tear up your stomach.
We punish like little razors. So, so tell us your stories of banana horror. The only way I can eat
single banana or the only way I can eat bananas is when I have banana runs. That's the only way.
Oh, those are fine. Yeah. No, I have like that function. That was at midnight. Fine. But as far
as real bananas, no big problem. That's just my, that's my system. What am I? What am I going to
tell you? That's you lie. No, I understand. You were wired this way where it would be a banana
is like a, is an atom bomb in the stomach because you were, it is programmed for banana run. Are you
back on bulk candy back on bulk candy, like post COVID, like, no, I don't really about bulk candy.
Oh, germ wise germ wise. Well, Jason, we know COVID is not really spread surface wise. So I've
never really been much of a concern. I know, but it's like logically, I feel like a lot of people
were having issues coming over that. I have, have I gotten bulk candy since the pandemic? What a
question. I feel like we returned to normalcy or not. Maybe once I did, maybe once, but I, I'm not,
I think once at the most, if I have, and that's not necessarily because of, because of the pandemic,
just because I haven't been in a lot of situations where I desire. I haven't gone into a movie at
city walk in forever. So that's usually when I would get a little bag of candy as you load up
over it. It's sugar. You get a couple of candy thongs in your pocket and a bulk bag. And then
you eat the thong while you're watching age of Ultron Avengers, a Ultron is that I've never
taken a candy thong into the movie theater. And it's no never candy's not good. You're not going
to do well. It's like, you know, it's weird. The best candy is on candy thongs. I mean, I'm not
saying I won't now that I've said it, let's all do it. But I think the candy candy is like the candy
necklace candy, which is fine. It's kind of like Smarties, which all like, I feel like once you'd
be eating a candy necklace, you'd kind of get tired of it halfway through. Have you got,
have you recently gotten a candy necklace and worked your way around that? But I ate enough
candy necklaces as a child. Do you mean your share of candy necklaces? They were never my favorite.
I'll tell you my, I don't, they weren't mine either. My, my current scam is a CVS runs a lot
of buy two, get one free of movie box candy, which it's like $6 at the theater. So it's like 150 at
CVS. So if I have extra bucks, I'm like, well, guess I'm buying movie box candy. So I have, I,
any freebie like CVS, which I think is mostly a scam. I think everything's overpriced there.
And then they trick you with coupons to get it down to like, yeah, like Coles cash. So Coles
tricking me. Yeah. So you guys do, you've had, you've had enough Coles cash experience to be
damn cold. I'm not mad at Coles, but I'm just saying it is a whole big trick. Yeah. It is a big,
it is a big shell game, a three card Monte table with a shell game on it. And that's the way I
feel the shady weed table at the bottom of your Margarita. Exactly. Or, uh, you know what I,
I've, I have trying to, I tried to keep candy out of the apartment, but lately I've, I've had
cookies in there. There are cookies at sprouts and I'm surprised I haven't told you this in private,
but I'm going to do it in public. They're sure you're willing to go on the record.
So I am willing. Uh, there are berry cookies that sprouts that I will eat the fucking box
within two days of like 12. They are so good that they're soft. They have like a berry taste
and I can't get enough. I, I, I, I go, goo goo. You heard it here first. Mike is goo goo for berry
cookies for berries, for berries. So no candy, but bonkers for berries. And I have no adverse
reaction to berries on like bananas. So they're not banana cookies. So that's what, that's what
I've been indulging in lately. I think the new, all right. So on the, on club three, uh, Jason
reading this book, Jason's tuck in time, then you'd suggest it because you have the suggestion that
we should all try candy thongs. So we do, we post like a weird half hour video. That's just us
silently eating candy thongs and then sometimes like holding them over each other's mouth. Like
we're like, we're all having grapes together and like, oh yeah, some of yours are we, um, are we,
are we pacing ourselves? Like I could knock that in 10. I feel like we have to do it now with that.
Oh, no, it's a challenge. I don't know. I don't know. Jason's 10 minute candy thong challenge.
Are there sizes for the candy thongs? What's that? Are there different sizes for the candy thongs?
I'm not quite sure on the current sizing or if it's a one size fits all sort of thing.
Oh, we know one size doesn't fit all thong wise. It would be more, you know, I think thoughtful and
body positive for them to have a full range of candy thong sizes.
I'm sure the people who make candy thongs for it's sugar are very thoughtful and body positive.
Yeah. The makers of candy urine or forward thinking. They're down that aisle on the left.
They're next to the cereal box labeled dingleberries, you know, but all size of
dingle bear. We're very dingle positive. Yeah. Okay. Well, look, this is, you might've said it
accidentally and stepped in it, but I think everybody's going to want to see if you can clear
quickly and polish off a candy thong candy or in a candy. I'm taking a look at the picture.
Yeah, take a look. Okay. And I might be defeated because this isn't my favorite and sometimes
too much sugary stuff. Candy garter like Jason and I had to take off of our high school dates.
I know that wasn't a candy garter. No, it was not. Only here's what we're dealing with. I think
my only concern is that my teeth are going to hurt sugary stuff like that.
Well, you just brag that you could do this in 10 minutes. Can you estimate
an amount of sweet tarts though? Right. Jason, this is a lot.
I mean, if I can have water with it, work some Joey chestnut magic on this. There are different
are you allowed to disintegrate and then drink the melted? I'd be more concerned if it was gummy.
Like for example, I have a box of Jujyfruits on me right now. Wow.
Very good. And yeah, that I those would those take me a few a couple of settings,
dots or that sort of thing. So the gummies six in your teeth. Oh man, this next live show,
maybe we should have you do it. Good. I just like, well, let me time it. Like I let me,
I feel like it'd be artificial if we tried to squeeze it into something. Oh my God. If I just
eat it naturally throughout a live show and I have a stopwatch going there. OK, so what I
showed kind of pulling you out of like being able to talk, I get a part of the show. OK, no, no way.
I had to showed you what I believe. Yeah. Is this like the thong they have? It's it's sugar. And I
don't know if they have this, but this apparently is a new thing called the candy posing pouch,
which is a thong specifically for scrotum and testicles. Yeah. Well, testicles,
scrotum pretty much same thing. I don't know. Scrotum keeps the testicles. Excuse me. Yeah.
So I don't know if this is this is less. It's really scrotum in a way. It's like it is a
candy scrotum. So we'll take a look when we get into a chugger to see which has the more
pieces and then whatever has more will buy for Jason. It's going to be more. It's the most
we got to deal with this. Mm hmm. OK, be very funny. It'll be a first for me. Well, vomiting
on stage is vomiting. Is the sugar my I think what would likely happen is the sugar will coat
my throat too much back of my throat and I'll start to feel ill and it'll probably be worse
because I'll start to freak out. And then and then we'll we'll do some investigation into your
Kohl's cash history. And actually, you've gotten ripped off for seven dollars via Kohl's cash
second vomit. Well, vomit. If you got the Kohl's cash going and you got the capital one shopping
in your browser, you got the honey app going, you know, you can save some money. Yeah. Honey
app never works for me. Yeah, it's not really worked for me. Yeah. OK. In summary, the little
man of Disneyland. Yeah. Charming tale about what's possible when you're nice to the people who live
in your the little people who live in the grounds you bought. Mm hmm. What a yeah. What a wholesome
tale. What a pure tale. What's nice, though, is what I like about this. I don't think I'd put all
this together that like because I was like, OK, so there's a book and then they tied it together
with you can go see his house at the base of a little tree. But I didn't know the timeline on it.
I didn't know that this book I don't know if it predated Disneyland, but it's very possible. It's
same year, right? So it was like all these little marketing pushes they did. I mean,
talking about building, I mean, they've melt for decades. The footage of like walking around
Orange Grove said like backhoes, you know, digging things out, you know. And so what I'm saying is I
think that it's neat that like here's here's where they leave it in the book. So when you visit
Disneyland, keep your eyes open. Maybe you'll see a wee man in green smoking a small clay pipe.
Follow him when he goes. Follow him to his house. A nice thing to do. Follow him home.
Find out where he lives. If you do, you'll be the only one in the world who's found
Patrick Begora's home. So I kind of like what this is doing is planning this little
IRL Easter egg hunt. Like you maybe you get this book, you've read it. You're a little kid in 1955
or in 2015. You read it before you go to Disneyland and now you're like, there's a
little thing that I can try to find and they don't tell you where it is. Of course you can Google it,
but it's a fun thing to keep your eyes out for. So I guess I like that that it's a
little adventure that they're assigning you that can straddle medium. It's from a book,
but then you go to a real place and you can stalk an already kicked out of his home man to his second
home. Right. And you can hear him inside upset that he made this decision because of how loud
it is out there and how many people are just clomping around and he's probably like moving
around from the vibrations from the tourists. They're redoing the tree house again. They said
Tarzan was the last time. They don't acknowledge that it would be very noisy if he builds a new
place in Disneyland. Yeah, that he would not be, yeah, he would be living. Are you okay?
Okay. Okay.
Boxes, juice, you fruits. I'll be ready. Right. It's right. You need to be cracking
now. Yeah. You send in some runs to go attack that damn real banana. What if I had a whole
pound of runs loose, loose runs, banana runs in my bed? Are there run thongs? Can we make one?
I could. No, I mean I couldn't, but I guess you just take like dental floss
but you have to string them through a little hole. I guess. Yeah. Sounds like a very small
precise hole. That's something we can put Patrick to work doing. Okay. Yeah. Little pickaxe to make
little holes in banana runs for an all run thong. Yeah. Now we're talking. It's very,
it's funny also to look back to 2015 and go like this might be one of the things I remember most
fondly about the so-called diamond 60th anniversary. The return of the little man.
What a letdown that was. Yeah. It was kind of turfed out. I think it's kind of interesting.
You guys really glommed onto the diamond because you still bring it up. I don't know what the hell
the celebration was, but you like had hopes for the diamond. It's the diamond, you know,
here on new year's 2015. I'm just glad there's something to look forward to the diamond celebration.
Sure. To be remarkable. I had family visit twice that year and we stayed down there two times and
every piece of paper had diamonds on it. And I still find like in like boxes or stuff for like
bookmark like little diamond ticket stubs or receipts with diamonds on it, like that sort of
thing. I was there all the time in 2015. I just didn't register the diamonds. Did not care. Yeah.
They were like the little diamond logos. Yeah. They just did. There was a big, there were big
plans and then they had to pull them back because of, I think the Shanghai park was there. I think
Shanghai, similar to Paris, cost a lot more than they initially set aside. But we got the hat box
ghost. Hat box ghost is probably the highlight. Yeah. The return of the hat box ghost. And the
diamond set list of the tea party. Of course. Yeah. Thank you very much. Yes. I mean, I feel like I read
stuff online that people didn't see through at the 50th, 10 years before that either.
I don't know what that was either. Yeah. I mean, it's been down since 35. So,
how many more years till the next one? Oh, three, two or three. Yeah.
Not all the way. And it's going to be a, it's going to be a real blockbuster. She whiz,
but at least they did this. This is nice. They gave Leprechaun his false door back and you can
go see it. It seems like you can get up pretty close to it. You can knock on the door. There's
not a big line to get to this door. There will be after this episode. Obviously. And you know what?
Just go, this is what Patrick and the Disney company would want. Go up to his door, knock on
it, see if anything happens. If not, just leave a candy thong there or bring a candy thong with you.
It's sugar first. Cause that'll, that'll feed a Leprechaun for days. It's how he's good luck.
We'll rub off on you. And you know, I, I would love it. A candy rub on your private area. Buy
a candy thong and let good luck rub off on you. Let a Leprechaun rub off on you. You'll get a
sugar rash. Yeah. Sugar rash, better than a sugar rash. I think little golden should re-examine a
lot of the other little details at Disneyland. Write a book about the people on the party line
on Main Street or that you can hear down that one alley above you at the windows. You can hear like
people talking at the end of the one alley by the Starbucks and there's a party line phone in there.
Party line phone. You've listened. I picked up the phone, I guess, but outside of the phone.
Write a book about the two-tone light bulb. Our beloved, our favey. Did we talk about this on the
show? Yeah, we did. Hot dogs. We did. Yeah, in the hot dog episode. We found the two-tone light bulb.
We weren't 100% sure where it was. Uh huh. Yeah. We definitely did talk about it though.
Almost positive. Cause I think your, your whole thing was like, like you were like
annoyed with us for mentioning it. Yeah. I'm pretty sure. And we were trying, Mike and I were looking
out. They were selling, I think very briefly selling sippers. Well that was, we got, we got,
we got faked out. We got faked out with that fan made thing. A fan made cause they were selling
the light bulbs from the electrical parade. They're getting too good. Somebody made a
Photoshop of like them selling the half white, half red light bulb, but that was fake. That was
just a little joke we played on. Uh, we got tricked. Jason and I got tricked. Yeah. It's
gonna be the most obscure thing ever discussed in the corner of Disneyland. There's a light bulb
that is half red and half white and they were selling bulb sippers, but somebody did a prank
bulb sipper of half and half bulb sipper. Yes. Somebody did a prank of the bulbs fake. I got the
ultimate prank. I'm going to prank the world. That's right. Me and prank Bane.
Yeah. Yeah. So, so we were, yeah, they did not sell that, but we were excited because we were
ready, Jason already to buy it. Oh yeah. We were ready to put, put that money down. Yeah. It was
cumbersome, like pain in the ass thing we would have had to carry all day, but it wasn't worth it.
Yeah. Yeah. We would have gone next to on my bookshelf next to those Austin Powers action figures.
Have you taken those out of the packaging? No, still in box, still in box. Yeah. I got a couple
things I'm debating. Like, do I take this out? Do I leave this in? Do you have, are you, do you think,
what do you think about your collecting? You think you're an inbox guy? I, I I'm kind of splitting
different. Some of these throwback ones. Cause the, cause the retro cards. Yeah. The retro cards.
There's a retro war machine action figure that I remember the day dragging my mother to toys are us
to buy that original action figure. Yeah. So you're going to get that new one. Yeah. I don't know if
I'm going to be able to take that out of the box. Yeah. Yeah. Cause you want that hit, hit of that
adrenaline, hit that serotonin. Serotonin. When you see that thing from your child. Yeah. I hear it.
Like a tiny leprechaun lighting a fresh pipe first thing in the morning. Have they, are they, are they
still making this? And are there, is anybody contemplating taking the pipe away and editing
the pipe out? Because as we know, I've been complaining about Disney and smoking lately,
but this would seem like easily they're going to just Photoshop like a pretzel rod in his mouth
or something. Kids everywhere are going to want to be like their favorite leprechaun who is unseen
behind a door in a tree in Disneyland. So they have to get rid of his pipe. Have to get rid of his pipe.
But obviously like if this got in any Disney like standard and practices person's radar,
then they have like, there's no way they wouldn't say, take it out. Yeah. Cause they do it for
lesser things. We've already robbed this leprechaun of everything. His home was taken, his land. He
lost or killed everyone else in his clan. And then he got kicked out of his house.
And we, and his book wasn't published for many years. We cannot remove his pipe from it. If you
look up his like character Wiki, the only interest it says on there is smoking. We can't drop this
man of his only interest. Photoshop. If anyone wants to Photoshop out the pipe and put in a
candy thong in his mouth, because like, let's get ahead of it with different, you know, Disney's
going to put something in his mouth. So go wild with it. It'll be a delicious 10 minute meal.
Health. Cheers. You survived podcast, the ride. Thanks for subscribing to the second gate. If
you want to see, if you want to be tucked in with this story by Jason or see Jason eat a candy
thong in 10 minutes, this is, I mean, I hear you on eating it throughout a live show, but what I
really want is just one video, just phone on tripod running for 10 minutes. Let's see how long
you get. Let's see how much you can get through that thing. That's my, that's my pitch. Well,
we're looking into it very strongly and we're all thinking hard on it. And those are words
you can trust. Those are, that's a message of honesty. Anyway, some of that stuff and other
things will be on club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month in our regular
episodes ad free. Well, bug Gora, it was fun to talk somewhat about this book, but Gora, but Gort.