Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain devil dung,
buttermilk farts, blushing hubbies,
and bras, bras, bras.
We stroll to the turn of the century by way of 1955
as we talk weird old bullshit that used to be on Main Street
on Podcast The Ride.
["Wild Wings of the Sun"]
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks,
but also shockingly often weird old meats.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan, hello.
Meats, M-E-A-T-S?
Yeah, not meetups, no.
I wouldn't say that today is largely about weird old meats,
but we are talking about weird old stuff on Main Street,
and that includes restaurants, and restaurants in the 50s
at Disneyland had to include weird old meats.
Oh yeah.
It just didn't, doesn't count as a restaurant
unless there's something you would never
put in your mouth today.
Yeah, absolutely.
And joining us, hmm, hmm, the video watchers.
This is a video one, by the way,
and you can find that on the Forever Dog YouTube,
but the video watchers can already see an empty chair.
The listeners, you'll figure this out with us.
Mike Carlson, hello?
I did feel about like 150 pounds lighter or so.
Mm-hmm, his private is more than that.
I don't know, I have to give him,
but it's by sheer height, by sheer height.
Yeah, yeah, by sheer amount of him.
I didn't want to go too much more than that and be like,
you know.
Well, he's not here, so you don't want to start saying,
yeah, that 230 pounds, I don't believe so.
No, Mike, this is, so he's late.
This does not happen usually,
and I think normally we might just wait on it,
but we're here at the glamorous Forever Dog Studios.
We want to get moving, use the slot that we have,
he texts us that he's late and just start without him,
so this is all being done with his permission.
You know, this feels, this is interesting first of all.
I think this has, and we've done one just you and I,
but not one where we will start just you and I,
and then there will be this burst of absolute panic,
just sheer.
I love it.
The most, and we all get it together.
The listeners get it, the watchers get it
on the Forever Dog YouTube channel.
The bundle of stress that we're,
like Santa Claus is coming.
I love it.
Stress to Claus, stress to Claus.
I absolutely love a little bit of chaos,
a little bit of uncertainty,
and maybe it's just the hunger,
maybe it's just the hunger of not having done improv
in three years.
It's just like a little bit of the unknown.
Yeah, well, sure, sure, you know,
we've done our little, we've done our live shows,
but we aren't like, you know, we haven't done a ton.
You have this weekly slot
that you have not been back to,
but the people who were up live all the time,
the Chris Rocks and the Dave Chappelle's of the world,
they've had the wild cards of people trying to kill them.
You know, you haven't had that level
of something unaccountable from the audience.
No, I have not.
I mean, I guess my equivalent would be like
a hungry coyote trying to steal like the ham sandwich
I packed in a Ziploc bag in my bag.
Like, hey, get out of here, pal.
Does that, has that happened?
No, it hasn't.
No, I'm saying that would be my equivalent.
No, I'm not saying anything too incendiary
that someone would be coming after me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, just general interest
in things that people might have.
Yes.
Your weird meats.
Yeah, my weird meats.
A man-o-mole might want your weird meats.
But so, we'll just see.
We'll see when the bomb goes off.
I don't know if it will be in 10 minutes.
I don't know if it'll be later than that,
because does he remember that today
he is at the Glamorous Foreverdawg Studios?
Well, yeah, I did something similar a few weeks ago
where I was a half hour off.
And so, I was driving over when he texted me
and was like, where are you?
And I'm like, in the car, what do you mean?
And I was like, oh no, it's one, not 130, isn't it?
And so, I started using an old shared,
I have a podcast to write, like Google Calendar,
that I think I mostly used it.
You should get the listeners on that too,
so you know what's coming up.
Yeah, I'll put it on.
You know where we are, and that we are producing
the episodes, there's more going on with Club 3,
so if you wanna keep track of our iCal,
make sure we're hitting these dates.
So, I'll remind him that that is,
he can punch that into his calendar app.
The calendar is, yes, I use the calendar, yeah.
I'm on the calendar, you send me those invites.
And well, the issue that you have with Mike though,
is that you get him on those alerts,
and then you get lost in an avalanche of 100 alerts
of like, there's a new kind of Batman sticker releasing.
There's new, you can get a deal of two fries for one
at a restaurant that he doesn't like.
Right, that's right, I forgot about all his notifications,
because I said I turned all of mine off except reminders,
and text messages, and phone calls.
So, if I get a weird notification, it's like,
oh, fuck, I downloaded a new app, gotta turn that off,
fuck that up, you know?
But he's like-
Mike just, the more that he can,
he's like, through the looking glass,
every day is like the end of 2001.
Yeah, he's still somehow getting Circuit City notifications.
It's a, yeah, zombie accounts, closed stores that are,
yeah, Fry's Electronics, he's getting alerts about the deals.
He's getting the HBO Go, like,
this app is no longer supported,
please download HBO Max to continue watching HBO programming.
Well, it might come back, I mean,
the effort it would take to shut off the alert,
like in that time, you might as well just leave it on.
Yeah, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Well, we'll see when it happens.
We'll, and boy, this is a good one for video,
because the empty chair,
I'm just looking up at our monitor.
The empty chair is a very funny visual.
I'd also so think it's very funny if he comes in
totally prepared for a different episode.
That's possible too, yeah.
Yeah, if he's like, oh, god,
so what does everyone think of the King Arthur carousel?
That's fine, we can pivot, we can half and half it,
you know, we'll just, we'll leave an index for the listener.
Or, okay, so if you want King Arthur's carousel,
remember half of it is in the weird old Main Street episode.
Oh, yeah, that was a thing for a little while.
I don't think it lasts a smart podcast with chapters,
and I think the image would change as you went through.
I don't think this caught on.
Mm-hmm, it sounds exceedingly complicated.
Absolutely.
More effort than we wanna put in,
but we do like complication, so if we can create a scenario
where there's gonna be a lot of different arrows
drawn to different podcasts, I mean, we've done that.
We have a podcast series that picked up two years later
with one with a secret title.
I feel like a lot of people still haven't figured out
the secret title.
If you go to our Patreon and listen to the episode
Universal Cruise Line, you'll see that.
The cruise line.
Yes.
A little Easter egg happening in there.
Yeah, yeah, which was, I mean, that was still fall 2020.
We were all insane, and so I think we were,
oh, a little bit, we love doing little surprises.
And listeners seem to like it.
I don't think a lot of other shows do surprises.
That's well because they don't care.
They don't give a shit about you.
Yeah.
But we do, the two of us do.
The two of us do.
The two of us who cared enough to be here on time
for you and pointing in this video iteration,
again, at the Forever Dog YouTube channel,
because people seem to get confused where that is.
All right, so yeah, there's confusion with that too.
What goes where, what episodes are where.
But let's kick it off proper, and we'll allow Mike
to give any introductory thoughts.
Yeah, we'll give him the log line and yeah.
Remind him what it is.
But today's episode, I mean, look,
I don't think we've landed on the name exactly,
but in my head, at least what it is thematically
is weird old Main Street bullshit.
That's kind of what we're addressing today,
which is to say attractions, and I say that
with like the floppiest, limpest quotation marks
I could possibly do.
Things that visitors could experience
in the first five years or so in Disneyland's
beginning area of Main Street USA.
Yes, yeah, a lot more exhibits, a lot more sponsored tie-ins,
and not just like this restaurant is sponsored
by Kraft Foods.
Sure. Like an exhibitor sponsoring,
and maybe showing you the history of something,
showing you their products over the years,
and solely to cover some of the costs,
because that was what an interesting fact I found out
these leases, it was like a five-year lease,
and Walt won it the first year and the last year upfront,
so he could have a little operating money.
So the other ones you can pay like regular retailer rent.
Oh, interesting.
Well, and it was like early Disneyland
was such a weird risk and calamity
that that's sort of a big ask.
If Walt is saying, hey, I need you through 1960,
and give me some of that cash, they might be thinking,
what if there is no Disneyland in 1960?
I think that was a very real possibility.
Extremely, especially given some of the things
that we will be talking about, because if this is what,
like I think we've had some of these stray,
like oh, I heard they had this in the early days,
and this and that, and when you look into it,
you really start to go, how did Disneyland make it?
Disneyland was sort of like, this is what they had,
all the hype, they hype it on television for a year,
and then it has, well, we'll get into it,
but it's, a lot of it is extremely mundane, I would say.
Yeah, and some of it makes sense.
I'll throw out a kind of a generic one,
the book and candle shop.
Okay, sure, like candles, kind of a go-to
when you travel to tourist destinations.
That's like, oh, it's a nice thing,
it'll remind me of the trip,
I can bring it home for myself,
I can bring it home for a gift.
Makes sense, especially the idea of Main Street being,
I was telling you before we started recording,
there's so many articles just saying,
it's based on Marceline, Missouri,
and kind of, the answer is kind of.
It's more based on, like John Hench
and a lot of other Imagineers talked about,
it's based on the idea of a perfect Main Street,
in the past, there's a little bit of nostalgia here,
and memory is kind of a difficult thing.
Because you're saying that,
if it were more literally based on where Walt Disney grew up,
you said it's not a particularly glamorous place.
Yeah, I mean, I think a lot of places back then,
the Main Streets, while they were,
like everything you needed in town,
so everyone could walk there,
or take a horse and buggy, or early cars,
it was filled with mud,
and everything was painted like one or two colors,
and there were newly installed power lines everywhere,
like it's kind of gross,
it doesn't look like the World's Fair, you know?
You had to go elsewhere in Disneyland
if you wanted a bunch of mud.
There definitely was mud.
There was mud, they did get that,
but the idealized perfect Main Street,
they were trying to keep spick and span.
Sure, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're doing this, by the way,
I think this episode will be landing
kind of right around the anniversary,
that mid-July point, which is Disneyland's birthday,
I think the 67th anniversary, I believe,
if my math is not. I think that's right, yeah.
Happy 67th.
You doing anything for the 67th?
I don't know.
I think I blacked out for a little while.
We're celebrating by not going,
even though we gave them a bunch of money.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, blacked out on the past,
not blacked out on Walt Scots Mist or whatever.
I don't know, that's an idea, though.
We'll see how I feel when July 17th rolls around.
Oh, that's something to do on July 15th.
That's an episode.
Eat, drink, and smoke like Walt for a day.
Yeah, yes.
Well, you know what I discovered over the course
of this bit of research is there is a book
called Eat Like Walt.
There's a handy guide to how to do exactly this
that we've been talking about.
I have seen that book.
Is it in an official Disney book?
I don't believe so.
Oh, okay.
Because every now and then there's some very specific books
and it's like, oh wow, Hyperion Publishing.
You know, like.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Here's what I can say is that I went to the website,
eatlikewalt.com, and the mouse ears that I saw on it
seemed not standard issue.
Like the, you know, it's a circle and the two circles,
but they seemed like maybe calculatedly
like legally in the clear.
We make them a little smaller, a little asymmetrical,
then maybe Disney can't come after you.
But anyway, that's what I think like, you know,
it's opening day week.
We did this episode two years ago that I enjoyed so much
about Disneyland's opening day,
which seemed like such bedlam and such just odd wild west
where obviously there was the wet cement
and there wasn't working water and there were monkeys
with organ grinders and then the host of the broadcast
cheating on his wife live on the air
while hopped up on meth essentially.
I've just been so, that just made me go like,
wow, Disney really was, even the clips that they choose
to show you of that opening day special
can still kind of give you the man.
It's Art Linkletter and it's Ronald Reagan
and then like that's Americana right there.
But I think if you get past kind of the wall
that they've set up and see like what that park really was
for the first year or so, it was weird and sloppy
and it is kind of amazing it made it
and it's such a like tent pole of culture now.
Yeah, you know, when I, we first,
I started reading stuff about this and everything
and I was like, oh, am I just, you know,
looking at it through like 2020 eyes?
Like is it, was it stuff people actually liked at the time?
And to an extent maybe, but then also you see the like,
stores that aren't stores, you see that like,
I just need a little operating money.
Like I'm just trying to get anyone who will take it,
you know, in here and then you start to dig down
the specifics of like, no, that can't be,
I can't be right, no, that, oh my God, it is right.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, some of them are just boring.
Like, honestly, and I don't mean to like say
that this won't be a good fun episode,
but truly like the things that I don't have
a bunch of stuff prepared about,
there were things that were so boring
that I did take like a hard nap yesterday
because I was looking at a big article
about the Disneyland baby shoes store.
Like, there's gotta be something interesting
in here somewhere and then, oh my God,
I went out just like a brick.
Oh, is that grandma's baby shop?
You know, confusingly not.
It's not grandma's baby shop.
I did come across grandma's baby shop,
but separately there was something called
blue bird baby shoes.
So grandma's baby shop is not blue bird baby shoes.
Because I didn't see much on it,
but as soon as I saw, in reference to another place
we'll talk about said, it's right past grandma's baby shop.
And I was like, grandma's baby shop, let's fucking go.
Yeah, I was upset there wasn't more information
about grandma's baby shop.
Yes, I, you know, I think Yesterland,
one of them, Yesterland, a very good website
about like stuff at the Disney parks
that's not there anymore, pretty thorough,
quoted someone, another website or another article
was like, there is not a lot of documentation
on the book and candle shop.
And it is so weird to see these places
that are pretty thorough say that.
But then when they say right after grandma's baby shop,
it's like, is that the funniest phrase on Yesterland?
Right after grandma's baby shop.
It's only for like, yes, I want some things for my baby.
No, get out the door.
This is for grandma's to buy for babies.
Yes, it would be, all right, if you're a grandma
and then you also have your own new baby, that's allowed,
but no mom's buying things for babies.
No, no.
Grandma's only.
So, all right, to start getting into some of these things,
and by the way, like just the way this has played out,
is this the first episode in months
where the phrase bad boys of Boston has not been said?
So far it hasn't.
We've made it like 15, 20 minutes,
well I did it, I did it by.
You did it, let's not tell him we mentioned that.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
And let's see if it comes up organically.
Let's see if he naturally, if he comes in so guns blazing
and knowing what has been lacking in his absence,
he's just gonna come in and start shouting,
Green Day, Green Day, Green Day.
He's gotta make up for it within a 30 second span.
Yeah, and also the idea, there's not a,
I'm not gonna dox the man,
but there's not a straight shot from his place
to where we are on a freeway.
So he's on surface streets.
And this, for whatever reason, this type of year,
the San Fernando Valley has decided,
time to get some construction projects done.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And I'm checking that still now,
this is a very late mic, this is an extremely late mic.
But it doesn't matter.
Let's start talking about these old timey stores.
There's one I'm gonna save for him
because he wanted to talk about it.
I'm gonna wait.
Oh, I don't know what that one is.
I'll just sit here, I just won't do it for the time being.
But what do we do in the meantime?
Let's, okay, so one thing, all right,
so here's a general thing to say about Main Street.
You go there now and it almost feels like
just one big run of Disney Store, right?
Like there's separate store fronts,
but you kinda just walk through all of them
and there's subtle, like all right,
this one has more shirts and this one has more toys.
And then there's ice cream and candy and whatever.
But it definitely feels like,
it does not feel like 15 distinct businesses or anything.
No, with some, with a rare exception of like,
okay, that's the coffee, the current coffee shop
and it's a Starbucks now.
There's a jewelry and watch store.
That does connect to the other stores,
but it's kind of on its own.
Yeah, yeah.
But besides that, yeah, it's just sort of like,
it's all places where you buy stuff
that is cute and Disney-ish, essentially.
Not so much the case when it started,
because they knew they wanted this Main Street area
and they knew they wanted,
or we wanted to feel like an old timey town,
but then what is in these places?
I feel like they were starting to build the stores
and didn't know what was going to be in them.
And then once built, what you ended up with
was a bunch of, was literally a bunch of different businesses
that were all often competing with each other
for business of the, like restaurants specifically.
This was not a Main Street thing,
but there was a name that struck me a couple years ago
whenever it came up, that there used to be a restaurant
in Frontierland called Don DeFour's Silver Banjo Barbecue.
And that you had to learn who's Don DeFour,
just a guy could have, and not a character.
This isn't like, you know,
like Sleepy's Pillow Hut or whatever.
Yeah.
You're a real life man, Don DeFour.
And like, because those individual businesses
made money separate from Disney,
they did, they had to compete against each other.
So like, he was worried he was gonna lose people
to the chicken plantation
or whatever other old timey place there was.
So he had to like start putting spotlights
on the restaurant.
Like the park had to let him point a bunch of spotlights
at his own place, just to get people to come to his,
because it was kind of like tucked away and easy to miss.
So this is an early thing about Disney
that I think is interesting,
that all the stores were fighting each other.
Yeah, I think another distinct, and I hear keys,
could this be, nope.
Nope, false alarm.
Get in here.
Oh, here he is.
Go, and there you have it.
Well, the walk of shame begins.
Why does this have to be on video?
Why does this embarrass me?
You're not on video yet.
You can collect yourself.
The listeners have been watching an empty chair for.
There's a stain on my shirt.
It is such a shit show.
In my life right now, everything's fine,
but it's such a shit show.
If it makes you feel any better.
Look at my, oh, I look awful.
You look great.
I'm so sorry to the listener.
Sort of sorry to the listener who's just listening,
but there's video component, and I look like crap.
Look at the video to see how crappy Mike looks.
Look at this stain, look at this stain.
What is it?
It's wet.
Mike, if it makes you feel any better,
I have a small stain on my shirt,
because this is a real, I'll tell the story about this shirt.
This is a real vintage Epcot shirt.
I bought it March 10th, 2020.
We had just recorded the Islands of Adventure
preview episode. What happened March 10th, 2020?
Oh, I went to a crowded Trader Joe's.
Jason loves, you love any like,
and guess what the week was?
It may have been a March in a certain year.
And I went to a very crowded Trader Joe's
to buy canned goods like a blizzard was coming.
And sure enough.
So you got a giant bean stain on your, what's the stain?
I bought a $2 vintage Epcot shirt at a Salvation for Me,
or some sort of thrift.
There's gonna be a time when you're in like a kind of,
like a retirement home and you're gonna start,
you're gonna start like conflating that March week in 2020
with 9-Eleven.
You're gonna be, you remember March 9-Eleven, 2020?
I bought a can and a shirt.
A much more annoying Irishman hours.
But hey, let's not dunk on me.
Let's dunk on Mike a little more.
This is an opportunity.
It's not Jason, it's time to dunk on me.
And I deserve it.
I deserve it for the way I look on camera, first of all,
but also for my tardiness.
Hey look, in the interest of solidarity, there.
I just dumped water on myself.
Now I am also stained like all of you.
It's a clear stain, but you can kind of,
I am sopping wet.
So if you feel more.
Sparkling water.
Noted for removing stains.
No, Scott's making it better.
Well.
He's making his stains better.
Preventing future stains is what it's doing.
Well, I have nothing stain making on my person, so.
You okay?
How you doing?
I'm all right.
I'm a little stressed out.
A little stressed out right now.
We had the discussion of do you,
did you, we were like, well I hope he knows it's here too.
Oh, I didn't know.
Well, yes, you're right.
You're correct that I assumed the opposite.
So that was correct.
But I did have a half second to double check that
before I left.
And when all shit, it's farther.
It's farther than we oftentimes report.
You were slightly delayed because the iMessage
search feature is still this many years
and it's just absolute dog shit on Apple's part.
I did look, because yeah, I don't want to get into
the weeds of how this organization runs.
But.
We did a little.
You'll have to listen and find out.
I will have to listen.
So yeah, yeah.
I did do a quick search.
I definitely wrote it down wrong.
Look, there's secret reasons that I can't reveal yet.
What's going on in my life?
It's like Doughboys.
Like Mitch, you're also in the Twisted Metal show.
You can't talk about me yet.
I am also, there's a new character they're adding.
But it's so secret they can't talk about it.
No, it is nothing a career, well I guess acting wise,
no, it's nothing like that.
I forget, we were recording, right?
Yeah, I know you walked into it.
We were recording for half an hour.
Listen, we decided to live stream this.
Everyone's watching it live too.
Did you do any of the episode or did you just roast me?
We were just kind of getting into the generic stuff
about early Main Street and how they had to fill the space
and first to last year rent up front.
We did discuss how even if you had a calendar alerts
correctly that it would get lost in an avalanche
of alerts for restaurants you don't like
and stores that have closed for good.
Yes, that's true.
And like two dollars off like a new Marvel legend alert.
If there was a toy that was a slightly discounted toy,
I would be getting alerts and it would cover up
what I was supposed to be doing.
Yes, that's true.
So anyway, I am here.
I mean, feel free to destroy me if you'd like.
I do deserve it.
I'll take my lashing.
You already have the stain.
You bear the scarlet letter that is the stain.
Any idea what the stain's from?
I think it's just probably water.
I think it might be gone already.
Not mine.
I poured a bunch on my, which is not visible
as far as I can tell.
If you both want to throw water on me during the show,
I'll take that but there's equipment.
I guess the equipment might be hurt by it.
I don't want to mess up their equipment
and I would only do it to help people.
I would only do it if there was an ice bucket challenge.
Yeah, if there was some sort of charity events,
then yes, okay.
Would it be a viable episode to go back and do
to just cover a bunch of people's ice bucket challenges?
Because it was a great thing that like hit everybody.
Everyone did, lots of weirdos did
from Mike Love to George W. Bush.
Yes, that's true.
Everyone got to put their stamp on the ice bucket challenge.
Every once in a while, I'll go back and like,
you know what I'm watching tonight?
Ice bucket challenges.
Is that true?
Yeah, a little bit because I like the George W. Bush one
because Laura Bush has to act.
One of the worst actors up for on the Earth.
Oh sure, yeah.
She's supposed to do it and then she comes in
with that smile of nervousness
when you've never been on camera before.
And like, I didn't know how to do it.
I didn't want to mess up my hair.
I think that's viable.
Mike Love does it.
It's in a concert and it's such a gun point
and not understanding what it is.
And then it is so sad when he challenges Mick Jagger
to do it because like, dude, Mick Jagger's not watching
one of your YouTube videos.
And he didn't do it?
No, he, no, if Mick Jagger ever did an ice bucket challenge,
I don't think it was because of Mike Love's
challenge being issued.
I see.
Well, I felt like the celebrities were like doing that
in sort of conflict.
There was some sort of plan, but maybe that's wrong.
Maybe they just picked somebody they liked.
I'm not sure.
I think some of that, that's an interesting study
you could do if you were analyzing ice bucket challenges
is unanswered ice bucket challenges.
Oh, that's a good idea.
And ice bucket challenges outside of your league,
like reaching for somebody.
Somebody too high up the tier.
I know you're sort of famous,
but like Obama's not gonna do it because you said to do it.
Who, Jamie Kennedy, I don't know who.
So like if we had said like Pod Save America guys,
we challenge you, they're out of our league.
So they would not have answered us
and it would have been embarrassing.
Obviously, yeah.
I mean, we'll get to their league someday.
We're trying, but the more we're late
and the more we're, that's why, if for only that reason,
to just catch up to Pod Save.
Sure.
Yeah, we just need to vote a little harder.
And then maybe they'll dump a little ice.
Yeah.
They'll finally answer our ice bucket challenge
seven years later.
Here's what, but you know what?
This isn't about roasting and it's not about being mean
because we haven't really gotten to a specific location yet
in weird old Main Street bullshit.
And we saved the one that you wanted to talk about,
which is the bank.
We saved the bank for you.
If we really were vindictive,
we wouldn't have let you talk about the bank.
After all that, after half an hour,
all right, we're there everybody.
The bank is what we're.
I'm crying on the way over here.
I wanna talk about the bank plate and get to the bank yet.
I wanna talk about there's a bank on this.
An actual bank, a functioning bank.
Yeah, it's a functioning bank.
Just a bank.
And the first thing when you came in,
if you go into Disneyland now
and off to the right is the Disney Gallery
and maybe that corridor of bathrooms
are the first you use when you come in.
But so Disneyland's here, you're in its Disneyland,
the realm of magic, here's a bank.
Yes, it's like now, yeah.
I like, I'm trying to think of what's better.
I think it is better that you can buy a Mickey statue
where he's tugging on a firefighter's outfit
or something there now instead of it being a bank.
But if I'm thinking about Disney as a real place,
I do really like the idea that there's just a bunch
of stupid daily tasks you could take care of on Main Street.
So there's something fun about it.
You would have liked to,
you might have saved banking to do.
100% I would have saved banking for Main Street.
Don't you think you would have done it?
We would have done a little bit,
these two, we're the first guys to ever think of this
10 years ago, been like,
you wanna go down and make a deposit?
And be like, yeah, Jason and I would have two envelopes
full of cash that we were gonna deposit at Disneyland.
And be like, this is how we do all of our banking.
We would have absolutely done that if it was still there
when we first started going to Disneyland.
Because again, I do wanna emphasize
that it's an actual bank.
Because some of the places were simulations of business.
It weren't actually their businesses.
Or like, I bet there's people in Florida.
Because Florida still is a barber shop.
Really?
Yes, right, right.
A functioning barber shop.
You can get your haircut on Main Street?
You can get your haircut on Main Street.
I have heard some people like,
oh, it's time for baby's first haircut.
We're getting it done on Main Street at the Magic Kingdom.
Oh, because they're happy to be at Disney World.
It's like a first thing, it's a first time, yeah.
Yeah, and I'm sure there's Orlando locals
who it's like, time for a haircut.
I'm gonna make a reservation and make a park reservation
to get a haircut on Main Street.
Would you not do that?
I would also do it.
I would probably do that if I was close by.
Not every time.
If there was a Disneyland haircut,
I would have tried it probably by now, at least once.
I wouldn't have, and I'll tell you why.
Because it would suck and cost $250.
Well, it would suck, because it's $250,
but don't you think they'd have some sort of whimsical
80-year-old man who's cutting
and he's gonna give you the hot shave?
It's like, why don't you do it once?
You do it in...
One time.
You're in the window on Main Street
and you're kind of a display, you're kind of an attraction.
Oh, they make you a little show.
Yeah, yeah, I suppose so.
Maybe once you would do it?
Yeah, I would consider doing it next time
I was in the Magic Kingdom.
Well, yeah, well, you got it now.
Well, now we have to do it.
Now all three of us have to do it.
Ideally, at the same time in chairs next to each other.
Oh, can they do that?
I don't know.
Is it like a sport clips?
Is it like multiple chairs?
I was picturing the old couple, well, like one or two.
I feel like there's two chairs, probably.
Okay, can they do colors?
I don't know they do dye jobs.
I'll dye my hair on Main Street.
I've never dyed my hair before,
but I will dye my hair on Main Street.
In an old timey barber shop, you're gonna go bright blue.
I wanna get as much as you can get there.
Hmm.
I don't know if he has blue.
Well, I don't know.
That feels like that would take a long time to color.
Because if you're going different colors,
I think you have to bleach,
and then it would have to dye it yellow and then go blue.
And you're on vacation also,
so now you're using hours for this haircut.
But it's content for us.
That's true, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do they have the menu, what you can do?
You gotta get your eyebrows removed.
All of your arm hair.
I wanna see if there's like a menu.
How much hair will they touch?
Yeah.
Now I'm wondering, have they relegated this to the app too?
Is this now like, in theory, simpler,
but more of a pain in the ass?
Because you can't specify,
you can't talk to a human over the phone.
Yeah, that's a good question.
Child, okay, services available, child haircut,
my first haircut, adult haircut, beard trim.
So they're not gonna color your hair there.
I don't think so.
They're probably not gonna shave you either.
Well, the beard trim, yeah,
you're not getting the warm razor out.
No, but I'll get an adult haircut.
It doesn't, starting at $21.
Cheaper than Floyd's, cheaper than local chain Floyd.
Not so bad.
I guess I may.
Yes, you have to do it.
Well, let's see how those hidden fees stack up.
Aren't you suspicious of this?
At current Disney World, a service that in the real world
is usually much more expensive,
is $21.
Do you, yeah, $21 gets you the high and tight
or gets it shaved all the way off?
Sorry, that's the price.
$21 is the cost for a haircut.
We cut one hair.
Do you want us to cut the others?
That's just the going through the door fee is $21.
One hair, I cut one hair, that's a dollar.
Another hair, yet another dollar.
And like Mickey's just got a calculator next to him
and it's like, $1, $2?
You have 1,000 hairs.
Shapek approves of this, not just because of
all the hidden fees, but because he's like,
hey, make haircuts as expensive as you want.
Not a problem for me.
That is gonna, that will,
that is definitely on his to-do list.
He's got like a big board.
It's like, he says like, evil board or something.
And it's like, make haircuts cost at least $500.
What is left to make more expensive?
All right, charge per brick that you step on.
That's the new Disney and Magic ankle bands.
We track, it's a fun thing where we track
every step that you take in the park.
And it helps with fitness and you get a little sticker
at the end and Goofy says, good job.
And yes, then we charge you for all the wear and tear
that you put on bricks and cement in our park.
We're helping your heart, so pay us.
Or pay us for your heart help.
But yeah, so they had a bank.
They had a bank.
I like more mundane stuff.
I like, I would like more of it is what I'm saying.
I would like more things like that available.
I know they did have it, obviously.
We're talking about that.
Well, you say it's mundane, but here,
like here's a description I read of what you could do there.
You know, there's a vault.
You pass by the vault that is holding money and documents.
And then the branch manager, Leo Wagman,
sits in a nearby armchair behind a roll-top desk,
nodding and smiling at the visitors.
So you come back from Disneyland.
How was Walt Disney's Disneyland?
It was great.
I saw Leo Wagman.
Who's that?
Is that a character from a movie?
No, he's a guy at a bank.
You know, like a fun movie about a bank
or like the Mary Poppins bank.
Mary Poppins bank guy?
No, bank guy.
He's a real branch manager for Bank of America.
This guy is a famous Disneyland character, though.
Now, I mean, we're getting him out here now.
Yeah, we're getting the word out about Leo Wagman.
Leo Wagman.
Some of my information today came from a really strange book
that I think is called like Fifty Fivers or Class of 55,
something my parents gave me for Christmas one year.
It is a book that tracks every single human being
who worked at Disneyland in the first year.
Wow.
And like, then you read, like they tracked them all down.
There's at least a little information.
Like this, he's from Fullerton,
but then he died in La Palma.
The stories are not magical.
They aren't interesting.
It's just like, here's people.
Do they claim to have everyone?
Yeah, and there's, I mean, there's hundreds of little.
Sure.
Is Leo in there?
Yeah, yeah.
There's an entire, like I don't have it with me.
There's a whole separate, besides what I just read,
there's a separate Leo Wagman section
where you find out where he was born and I assume died.
Wow, has anybody here ever known the name of a bank employee
that they would go to a lot?
No.
Like they might've like thought I did
if I went more than once, but I didn't remember their name.
Did everyone go to the bank as like children
to open up your first savings account?
And like, it was a big deal
because you sat at the desk with your parent?
I did not have that.
You never did that, Jason?
I think, yeah, I did something like that.
I mean, we had the like, the bank was next to the post office
and they were both across the street from the high school.
Right, and you got like a little book
because it was 100 years ago when we were children.
Yeah, yeah.
You know what I'm realizing now
is that I'm potentially introducing
a new second gate character
because I believe I got a mascot character for our bank,
the Harris Lion.
Oh.
I believe I had a plush.
Let me look him up.
You got any info on Harris Lion?
Is the Harris Lion cute?
Let's see, he for sure is cute.
There's no doubt about it.
But that's like more of a Midwest, I think I've got bought.
Yeah, I got bought by BMO, BMO Harris.
BMO Lion? But they kept Harris?
I guess so.
BMO, Harris Bank, here he is with a bull's jersey.
I mean, he's not the cutest, I'll be honest.
No, no, not really.
I like him.
He's not not cute.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, there's this bank.
I mean, I've had this bank as well.
A bank, you mean a piggy bank?
A literal bank, yeah.
A lion bank.
That does look familiar.
So this is a new guy, Harris.
Oh, that's fun.
I'll do this, hold up to the...
There you go.
Mike is now here to show you banks,
a little bank that he had.
And hopefully, my biggest fear during that
was that something that's happening right now,
I wasn't gonna get a bunch of panic text messages
and show those to the camera.
But luckily those came before and will come after.
That's another thing.
No, you have full transparency to the listener.
I guess that's the bank.
So you got to do it.
The vault is still there.
Did you say that?
No, no.
The vault is still there and it's still being used
to house very expensive things you can buy
from the Disney gallery.
Oh yeah, there is that little nook.
And it's big, it's a big, thick bank vault door,
which I never questioned what it was.
I thought it was just theming.
And I was like, oh, that's fun.
They made a vault for the special things.
But I've walked by there before and they had a full...
It wasn't on an animatronic,
but it was like a recreation of the guy
in the haunted mansion with the dog.
Sometimes it's just like some sort of statue.
Sometimes it's like a one of a kind artifact.
And sometimes it looks like it's just a picture in there
and you're like, well, that's not as...
This feels like it should be some crazy expensive thing.
But sometimes maybe they...
Or people's actual financial information,
which is what used to be in there.
Yeah, sometimes it should just be like ledgers,
bank ledgers and withdrawals and deposits.
And yeah, I mean, that's gotta be in there somewhere, right?
Maybe it doesn't.
Like in the wall somewhere.
But there weren't safe deposit boxes there.
No.
That would have been amazing.
You couldn't do your escrow services.
You couldn't do that.
Right.
These surfing bank robbers from Point Break
did not try to heist the Disney World Bank.
But what a great novel for your new novel series.
Oh, yeah.
Bodhi is back.
He did not totally eat shit at the end of the movie
and die in the big wave.
Jason Sheridan presents The Main Street Files.
Disneyland, it's a Disneyland meets Point Break adventure.
Yeah, it's Disneyland meets Point Break.
They're 70 page paperback novels that Jason writes.
They're like those series of the guy
with the adventures at Main Street.
The Main Street Files.
You could write one of those.
For our patron, Jason's gonna say
he's gonna write a 70 page novel for the highest tier.
When did I say that?
Just now in my imagination.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, on the car ride over,
did you have a conversation with me?
Do I just appear when you're running late?
You are like my great kazoo.
You show up all the time in my life.
It's not 11, dumb dumb.
It's not the right time, dumb dumb.
Also, I'm going to write a novel.
There's a weird video of Jordan Peterson going around
where he's in the scare, he's in like a Jack Skellington suit
and he's doing this odd screed about.
Oh, Elliot Page?
Yeah, yeah, but the only part I saw is this weird like,
we'll see who gets canceled.
Yes, that's it.
I was like, this is like great kazoo a little bit.
He's like a big tall great kazoo.
He's like, yeah, so long, woke mob.
I forget what he says.
Woke moralist, you dumb morales.
You dumb.
Yes, it's lit because he's joining Ben Shapiro's
Daily Wire now as a contributor.
Same family as Gina Carano's movie.
That's right.
All the best content.
Terror on the Prairie, which as somebody pointed out,
sounds like a 30 Rock fake movie.
Yeah, so they've shot a video.
I don't know, I was just like,
do we have to explain to this guy
in the middle of Main Street?
Jordan Peterson is like an annoying guy
who's like mad at trans people and always crying.
And like trying to get kicked off Twitter.
And yeah, he said something derogatory about Elliot Page
and then Twitter kicked him off.
And now they made a little super villain video of him
for Daily Wire.
He came back.
We'll see who cancels who.
We'll see who cancels.
He says like, we'll see how,
yeah, like it's a weird, did somebody write it?
Did the writer of Terror on the Prairie
write this little monologue?
He came back after attempting,
his daughter tried to get him to eat an all meat diet.
And then he was addicted to Benzos.
And then I think she took him to like a weird
stay in rehab in Russia or somewhere in far Eastern Europe.
And somehow came back.
Somehow he's doing the rounds again.
And there was like the most fragile person.
Yes.
Why are we talking about this guy now?
Hold on, hold on.
We can stop.
Keep talking.
I'm sorry, this guy is insane.
He's a crazy, like he was mad.
Clock's ticking.
When the, all right.
It's 11.33 right now.
No more, 11.34, we're done.
He was mad about like the Sports Illustrated cover.
The woman didn't look like a woman
from the 90s on the cover.
And he was like, you're not fooling me with this.
I won't be tricked.
This woman is not the same weight as the woman in the 90s.
And people were like, what's wrong with you?
Well, and what's important is that anytime this guy
farts anything out of his mouth hole,
that we, Twitter needs to make it be trending.
Well, that's an issue.
There is no other choice.
We're trending it now, but it is like,
dude, what's wrong with you?
This gaunt crying man who clearly has consumption
has some thoughts, has some thoughts on light year.
And Jason summed it up.
All right, so the door slammed, vault door slammed.
We're shoving Jordan in there.
You brought up heists.
There was a heist on Main Street.
I'm gonna dive into that story.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, you ran into this at the restaurant,
the Red Wagon Inn.
This is now the Plaza Inn, I believe,
down at the end of Main Street.
And there was a heist there of some kind in 1960.
It's a really weird story where a guy at the restaurant
was taking, he was moving money from one place to,
from the back of the restaurant
to technically the backstage.
And then a guy came out, he felt something against his side
and uh-oh, and he had to give the guy
the full $10,000 that he had,
which seems like that's a lot of money
for a Disney restaurant to be moving.
And that was, so this became a matter
for the Anaheim police and they're like,
and there was, somebody had a gun in Disneyland
and this all, this seems weird and it's a lot of money.
So they talked to the employee again.
Two days later, he failed a lie detector test,
confessed and showed the police where in,
they did the women's locker room.
He hid most of $10,000 and returned it.
Why would he hide it there?
They'd never, why would a man be in the woman's room?
It's the perfect crime.
Yeah. Yeah, geez.
He just lied.
Only in Jordan Peterson's America.
I didn't say it, I didn't say it.
Doesn't mean we have to keep talking, let's go, all right,
quick.
But yeah, it's like, I would think if you would
steal a bunch of money, you'd try to not keep it
within 50 feet of, like, try to get it out of there.
Yeah, really strange story.
And the idea that like, I don't know,
I don't think we had metal detectors at that point,
but I also don't think people were bringing guns
to Disneyland.
Yeah, right.
I don't think.
It just seems like this was maybe a plan
that wasn't well thought out.
Yeah, yeah.
This was a very, this was the William H. Macy of his day.
Oh yeah.
Immediately.
Usually.
I told you the story, what do you want?
If you're gonna heist like $10,000 like that,
which is probably worth like 10 times as much in 2022 dollars.
But usually you don't just have one doofus who lies
and is very bad at lying.
Yeah, and his plan was like, himself on like,
I'll be good, I can handle this.
Me, a like, assistant manager at a theme park restaurant,
I mean, I can hold up to the police for more than two days.
Oh God, no, I'm sorry, you're dang it.
Come to the women's room with me.
That's like the three of us are probably,
if we were little and we took like an extra piece
of candy, we would have like within an hour
of been like crying and be like,
well you have to confess something, mommy.
I ate an extra piece of candy after dinner.
100%.
Yeah.
I lied about something.
Three big bucklers.
At the time, three little bucklers.
That's what we'll call ourselves from now on
because we're not three childless men in our 30s anymore.
Three little bucklers.
That could replace Cliffords too potentially.
The list, we can't put this on the listeners.
The listeners are bucklers for sure.
If they listen to us.
This is unfair, we've already put on them
that they're like the creepy little Martin Short character.
You Cliffords, you're also bucklers.
They also would not hold up against police
or parent scrutiny over a piece of candy.
Let's ask them.
Hey, tweet at us if you're a little buckler,
a nasty little coward with no integrity.
I'm glad you're in the main video
to seek for that, for asking that question.
Well, I mean, what a boy.
I mean, if they truly are bucklers,
they'll buckle because you asked that.
A nasty little coward.
Yes, I am, sir.
The podcast I listen to yelled at me, I buckled.
I think we got a lot of bucklers in the audience.
I think we have a lot of people
who could easily give us wedgies too.
Yeah, I know.
You come in late and then you insult,
then you say that everybody,
our whole audience is gonna buckle.
Who is this Mike?
I don't know.
I'm not sorry though, I'll tell you that.
I'm not sorry for what I said.
I'm like Jordan Pierce.
You won't cancel me.
You won't get an apology from me.
You won't cancel me for calling you bucklers.
That's right, bucklers.
We'll see you buckles against you.
No.
I regret nothing.
Here's some other things I have to say
about the Red Wagon Inn.
This is my intro that you missed.
It was, mainly what we did was laugh
at my opening joke for 10 minutes,
but I said that there were a lot of,
you know, like weird meats come up on the show
and it's gonna happen here
because it's original Disneyland.
Kids menu at the Red Wagon Restaurant.
A couple odd things going on.
This was a Yesterland poll.
Why Red Wagon Restaurant serves
genuine Swift's meat for babies.
For 25 cents a can, choose from strained beef,
strained veal, chopped beef, and chopped veal.
Swift's is the foremost name in meat for babies.
100% meat.
Now, Scott, you got a two year old.
What is his favorite chopped or strained meat?
And do you buy Swift's?
It's so frustrating that it's not easier
to find strained veal.
It's been my biggest complaint since becoming a parent.
Where's all that used to be on every street corner?
I took them to Disneyland.
Where's your veal?
It can be strained or chopped.
Will it slide?
He prefers chopped, but you can strain it.
You know, a fun fact that Mike found out in the app,
you can order, you know, a kid's meal of strained meats.
You don't have to have a kid.
You can just do it in the app
and it'll be ready at mobile pickup.
And can you get it a little cheaper
if you say doesn't have to be 100% meat?
Yeah, yeah.
But that's a...
A couple cents off.
They can't do that in an app though.
You gotta ask.
Yeah, you gotta stand in line to get it a la carte
or to get a little more filler, a little more sawdust.
Veal.
I want the, I'm here for, I need the baby veal,
but it doesn't have to be all veal.
Meat for babies is also just...
Really disturbing, Nate.
I guess babies have meat.
Sure.
Mine doesn't so much.
Not a lot.
You don't need a lot of meat.
No, I don't think so.
You certainly don't need veal for babies.
No, that's what's, and veal is babies.
It's babies eating babies.
Oh yeah.
This is the world that Walt wanted in the food.
This is what he was trying to...
I wanna look down the street
and see nothing but babies eating babies.
There was a whole wonderful world of Disney
about babies eating veal.
He was presenting that to the American public.
The most beautiful American sights there is.
Jason, did you eat veal when you were a little baby?
No, I don't think so.
I don't think as a baby.
I've never had veal.
Really?
Yeah, I still don't, no, yeah, I wouldn't.
I feel like chicken Parmesan and veal Parmesan
are just kind of standards at like where I grew up.
When was the last time you ate veal?
I don't know, a few years ago?
Veal piccata maybe?
Never.
No?
I don't even know that it's been offered to me.
Like I don't even know that I've seen it on a menu.
You must have been in a restaurant with veal.
Probably.
I think so.
It just wasn't, nobody offered it out loud.
Nobody pushed it on me.
Can we make you buckle?
We know that stain is veal.
Buckle now.
I was eating a little jar of baby veal,
of baby food veal on the way over here
because I haven't eaten in days
and that was the close.
That was.
Lap, lap, lap, lap with your tongue.
The closest store was a baby food store
and I just grabbed stuff off the shelf
and I was just shoveling baby food veal into my stomach
and yeah, I got some veal juice on my shirt.
The cans are mostly juice, you gotta get them.
Yeah, because it can't be big pieces for baby.
Yeah.
Yeah, baby needs.
You put juice in the bottle.
Baby needs juice.
My baby needs juice.
Baby.
We're bottle feeding him.
Veal juice.
Veal juice, of course.
No formula, no breast milk.
No, the formula shortage has not affected us at all.
Well, that's because we mainly give him veal juice.
Veal juice.
No, not beetle juice.
No.
Well, you also, then you'd have your,
you'd give baby strained veal
and then they'd wash it down with buttermilk.
It's just weird this time.
What was going on?
And then also, and then just past that,
then there's a full, okay, there's a page from,
they don't call it the kids menu,
they call it the menu for young Americans.
And then there's only five items on it
or types of meals you can order.
Two of them are problematic.
I'm not gonna say those out loud.
Oh no.
Two of them in various ways are characters
who are problematic.
Oh, got it, got it.
And then one of them is,
this, you know, like one meal is just the Casey Jr.
And then that's unrelated.
It's a sirloin patty.
But then one is Danny.
And it's a little happy black sheep,
or a black lamb, I guess, from So Dear to My Heart,
the 40s Disney movies, So Dear to My Heart.
And he looks so eager and happy
and like he's gonna go run and play.
And then his meal is broiled lamb chop.
It's like clucking chicken.
It's like a Saturday Night Live sketch.
Yes.
Weird.
Like have lamb chop, sure.
But why put this, like we have one lamb character
in the entire lineup and we're gonna have him.
That's a decades long trend, I think,
that maybe around the time of that clucking chicken sketch,
people were like, wait a minute.
Didn't wanna think about the face of what they're eating.
Yeah, it was like, oh yeah,
we'll have a cute picture of the thing you're eating.
And finally, after decades, people were like,
well, maybe that's a little weird.
Maybe that, people don't wanna see that.
Yeah, and why have that when one of them is chopped meat
and then a side of jello represented by a smiling train?
What was the smell back then in these places,
just like everyone eating the most meat possible,
just like churning out meat in the kitchen?
I mean, I guess it probably wasn't that insane, but.
Well, I have that question in general because there's,
well, there's not only that,
it's all meat and buttermilk everywhere,
but then also to transition
into the other smell making materials,
there's a tobacco store.
The tobacco is.
Right, you're just buying tobacco.
And everyone's farting too.
So I think we've talked about
how much farting was going on back then.
No, we must've discussed the degree of fart in the air
at early Disney Land.
Because everyone's eating heavy meat for every meal,
smoking like a chimney,
and that gas has to come out.
And I don't even think we've answered the question of how,
people didn't just let it rip in the 1950s or 60s, did they?
Or would they say, well, excuse me after they did it?
If they were in line for the train, would you fart
or would you have to squeeze it out?
What would it be?
What was the protocol back then?
Obviously it's not.
Was everyone just wearing so much wool material?
Did it just get absorbed?
It would muffle it.
That's why you dressed that way.
It was soundproofing.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, it was such a thick material
that you just hear like,
it wasn't like that far.
It would bounce off though.
It's as much as two hands rubbing against each other.
That's what it ends up sounding like.
Right, so you just hear that constantly.
And then this.
I'll say, just an unsettling little shuffle.
And then just the worst smell imaginable.
But you were used to it
because that's what everyone smelled like.
Well, no, but just the smell is muffled
by everyone's nasty hair products and pomade
and unfiltered lucky strikes.
So you're saying a meat fart in the 1950
was a better smell than just what was going on.
It would be overpowered by everything else.
Yeah.
Okay, that makes sense, honestly.
There were so many other smells going on.
It wasn't even a big deal.
And also, I mean, a lot of plastics nowadays still stink.
Early plastic, first few decades of plastics
probably smelled atrocious.
Maybe, yeah.
Interesting.
Well, but the tobacconist didn't help.
It's the time more than anything.
I'm not like, this wasn't perverse, I don't think,
for Disney to have a tobacco store.
But it's just weird that now you can't even smoke
in the parks in any way.
Right.
But at the time, it's cigarettes, cigars, pipe tobacco.
You just buy them on Main Street, walk right out,
and start smoking, probably on the rides.
On the rides, which is what I've said many times,
that I don't wanna smoke cigarettes,
but I will smoke a cigarette on Pirates of the Caribbean
if I was allowed.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I realized a couple times recently,
I had the thought, like, oh, I have never smoked
inside a U.S. Disney park, and I guess I never
will have that option, because it's now a smoking,
smoking areas outside.
Yeah, when did they get rid of the inside the park
smoking areas?
It was more recent than you'd think.
I think it was like 2019.
Because we went with a friend of ours.
Some article said like.
In the last decade, and he smoked.
All right, Disneyland has ceased having indoor smoking
in the year 2000.
It's like, oh no, that is much later than you would think.
Yeah, well, that's when it all changed, I guess.
Late 90s, too, yeah.
But yay.
So out of step, I guess.
You could get your hair cut and smoke a cigarette
in Disney World in 2000.
And if certain products were blown into your hair,
it would light your hair on fire.
That's true.
Yeah, is that blue sanitizing liquid
that they keep combs in, is that flammable?
Barbasol?
Seems possible.
Isn't there a light alcohol component to that?
Yeah, I think so.
No, Barbasol is the shaving cream.
It is something close to Barbasol, I think.
Are you sure?
I think so.
I mean, Barbasol could also just make that, I don't know.
Hmm, let me look.
Barbasol is a thing.
Everyone here be quiet while I do this.
That's right.
We'll wait.
Barbaside. Barbaside.
Barbaside, that's it. Barbaside.
Yes, I apologize to the listener.
Barbaside is blue and yes, alcoholic
because it's killing germs.
Here's, there's not a lot of photos of the tobacco store
and not a ton of information about it.
But I found a photo from the front door
and the front door had a little poem on it.
And just, okay, you'll be able to tell with my voice
where the text goes from just black italics
to all caps red.
I think I'll be able to signal it.
So this is what, if you want to buy a pipe at Disneyland,
here's what you read at the door.
Tobacco is a dirty weed.
It satisfies no normal need.
It makes you thin.
It makes you lean.
It's the worst darn stuff you've ever seen.
I like it.
That's what, look at this.
Look at this.
Wait, there's for the listener.
There's the watcher.
I like it.
What is this?
This wasn't Disneyland.
Wild thing to put in there.
This I would buy.
I would love to own this sign.
John Stamos probably paid like 200,000 for that.
Yeah.
Bastard.
I mean, it's funny to look at nowadays,
not just because they don't let Nick Fury
have a big cigar in the Avengers movies
or the really insane detail of,
yeah, there's photos in Carthay Circle
where it just looks like Walt's pointing at stuff
because they Photoshopped the cigarette out of his hand.
And let's not forget Krusty the Clown toy
is not allowed to have a cigarette.
These things you both have said
are like five-timers clubs in the last six weeks.
Yes, for sure.
Well, stay tuned, folks.
This is the third time for this.
There's more cigarette content coming.
That's right, that's right.
That's true.
But I think it's weird to look at the tobaccoist
because I feel like Disney, Main Street,
they have removed anything that's potentially objectionable.
Like the candle shop they wouldn't have on Main Street now
because a child could like,
can't let the idea of children being by flame.
So much is so like, well, you can't have that
because a child could use that
to stab themselves in the arm.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
But this is acknowledging that it's like bad.
Oh, yeah.
Like this is basically saying like
sometimes it's good to be bad.
Oh, that little poem?
Yeah, yeah.
It's saying it's bad,
but it's also saying smoke them if you got them.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it feels like it's like a mockery
of somebody who likes poems
might think this stupid thought.
Right.
But me, I say, I like it.
Isn't it absurd?
I like it.
Yeah, who wrote it?
Yeah, no, it's not attributed to anyone.
Did Walt just compose it one day?
He started talking like, you there, take a note.
We're putting this up on the side of the wall
or is it a fame?
Maybe it's a famous thing we don't know about.
Well, I know some of the,
I think I was saying for, if you got here,
that they asked for,
they would say to get businesses to be on Main Street,
we're gonna build a building, okay?
We're gonna take care of the decoration of the outside.
You have to do the inside or we can help you.
But yeah, who knows if that was
whoever was running the tobaccoist
or if that was like Disney's little touch.
It's outside, so I guess it would be Disney.
You would think so.
Yeah.
You know what else he said before you got here?
You stink.
Jason said it.
Roll the tape back.
He wouldn't stop saying it.
Jason said that?
We have to change the topic.
Just because he's not here doesn't mean.
I bet he's gonna come,
that stinker's gonna come in with a stain on his shirt.
Because he was eating meat and smoking
and going back in the car.
He was smoking.
He's stressed out so he's just chain smoking
in the car on the way over here.
He was pounding his Virginia Slims.
He was sipping a Nalgene bottle of veal juice.
He's a stinker and a buckler.
Let the record show.
There's a lot of ways to describe me.
And I accept all of them.
A stinkler, a buckler.
Put that on a shirt, folks.
A Clifford, a stinker, a buckler.
I like it.
And I like it.
I'm kind of mentally going from least weird to weird.
This isn't that weird to me.
But we've talked about it.
I feel like, Mike, you've noted the oddity of this,
that there is a Wurlitzer store.
It was a piano and organ location.
Right.
This doesn't make any sense for Disneyland to have this.
But it is cool.
Yes, definitely.
Well, because that's what I,
so I was like,
I was like,
do you, could you buy a piano at Disneyland?
And then they gotta load it into your car?
Like you can, you just see people moving pianos
down Main Street?
Yeah.
But no.
Yeah, it wasn't,
because there's no room to hold house,
like a piano warehouse.
Yeah, yeah.
Probably not more than a couple pianos.
So I just happened to come across this,
right when we started talking about this episode.
Twitter user, at MysticFlights,
who I believe is an artist
who has worked for Disney Imagineering before,
posted a postcard of the Wurlitzer store.
And on the back, it says,
Wurlitzer, the name that means music in Disneyland,
proudly represents the entire music industry
in the fabulous spectacle.
The Wurlitzer exhibit is located
on the quarter of Main Street USA and Disneyland.
And then it says,
you're cordially invited to visit our store today.
And see here play Wurlitzer pianos from 495 up.
So they've priced it out, by the way,
with the inflation calculation, $495 in 1955,
is worth $5,398.75 today.
It's a pricey purchase.
Yeah, so it's like go to Disneyland and stop in,
order a Mac Pro and a Retina monitor.
Well, it's the price of that Star Wars drink
on the new cruise ship.
Yes, which is like multiple cocktails,
a shot of Pappy Van Winkle bourbon,
which is very expensive on its own.
And a trip to Skywalker Ranch.
A ticket to get into Skywalker Ranch
comes with a special $5,000 drink on the Disney Wish.
Oh, so it's not icy.
A bottle of Lucas Fincher's sparkling wine
sent to your hotel room.
So it's more like another trip.
A free cameo from George Lucas.
Yeah.
He'll whisper what his episode seven through nine
were gonna be.
That's right.
All about what the Wills were gonna do.
Let's talk about the Wills, yeah.
So, yes.
There's Wills in this drink.
It's a shot of Pappy but infused with Wills.
So they do high ticket, high price items sometimes at Disney.
What is the most expensive like souvenir
you can get from Disney right now, I wonder?
Oh, is it in the vault?
Maybe it's in the vault.
It's in the vault.
I mean, there was a bunch of like $500 Marvel statues.
That's up there.
That we've looked out before.
I think that's up there.
It's gonna be something.
But there's pieces of art in there
that I'm sure are more expensive and stuff.
Yeah, Giggly Prince, is that the term?
Oh, G-I-C-L-E-E?
Yeah.
Or how do you know how to,
I don't know how that is pronounced.
You might be right.
I don't know how it's pronounced, yeah.
So yeah, you could get a piano.
Yeah, I think though it was mainly about,
in that way that we found with City Walk
that it's less about they make a lot of money
at this location.
To advertise.
And more about getting the word at, yeah, yeah.
So I think it was more about,
I think they would even give you information
about where to get pianos and organs closer to you.
Right.
But they also, they did organ concerts every night.
Like a guy would sit and demonstrate,
and they'd patch it into all of the Main Street speakers.
So I didn't know that, that in the early years,
at five o'clock, there'd be an organ concert of Disneyland.
Yeah, that's cool.
Of instrumentals of Disney songs.
It's competing with the lowering of the flag.
They're playing taps.
And someone else is playing an old time rag.
20 feet away.
Scott Joplin playing.
So that, yeah, that was organ music,
which is much more like a baseball game.
Yeah, there was a guy who used to play organ
at Disneyland every day,
and then he left that to play organ for the Dodgers,
in fact.
There you go.
And then now it's just, now there'll still be a person
that plays the piano over by the hot dog store.
Yes, there's that, yeah.
So you still got a little of that old time feel.
I just love the hubris of like,
we're like, sir, we represent the entire music industry.
Sure.
They made a deal with Walt to be presented that way.
Well, that's what a lot of these things were about,
and it's a lot of why these places were there,
is they were flexes, they were flexes of your business
and of your Walt relationship.
And due to Walt's friendship with a particular CEO,
you ended up with a pharmacy in Disneyland,
the Upajohn Pharmacy.
Walt and this guy were smoke tree ranch guys together.
Of course.
At the famous ranch where they're building Cotino now.
We all knew about smoke tree ranch
before a couple months ago.
No, smoke tree ranch's still going.
Cotino is inspired by the league.
It's not the same place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He liked the Palm Desert in general.
Can we become smoke tree ranch guys
if it's still around?
Or is that like a rich person's club?
I think it is a rich person.
I think there are vacation rentals or stuff.
Yeah, I don't think it's the most,
I don't remember the nature of the property.
But to become smoke tree ranch guys,
do we have to have a membership
or can we just go there once and call ourselves that?
We should look into that.
Look into it.
We'll hang at smoke tree ranch.
Yeah.
In an episode on location.
So this place, the Upjohn Pharmacy,
this is one, I was probably initially glossing this over
as like, that doesn't seem like anything,
but Jason, we found the same thing.
This place is weird.
So much detail, there's so much on,
specifically there's one mouse planet article
called the story of the Upjohn Pharmacy at Disneyland.
And it is so detailed both because people still had
the pamphlets they would give out.
And there's also like the internal Upjohn newsletters,
like reproduced, which sounds like,
it doesn't sound like a human being really.
So like, we are not in the entertainment business.
As you know, we are in the pharmacy business.
But this is a chance of solid,
interesting advertising opportunities.
And it's like, all right,
don't have too much fun there, buddy.
You want a pharmacy copy to be fun.
Yeah.
Pills, pills, pills.
Get them now.
Hey, they literally say at some point,
it's like, I know this may seem weird.
This might be totes random, but
we're gonna do a pharmacy and a theme park.
This was like, but the main feature of it
was that it was a turn of the century,
a recreation of a turn of the century pharmacy
with old turn of the century stuff.
So you got to see old syringes.
Yes. Yay.
It was like, it was kind of like,
it's a wonderful life pharmacy thing.
Remember he's like delivering the medicine or something.
Yeah, he delivers medicine and then
the pharmacist like smacks his pad here.
Oh yeah, that's right.
The pharmacist hits him in the head
and it's a wonderful life.
So I don't think that would happen.
Bailey is like, you filled those capsules with poison.
Right.
I know you didn't mean it.
Oh, because the pharmacist is losing his mind.
Well, yeah, because he's drunk himself into a stupor
because his son died.
Yes, that's right.
Jason knows this movie very well.
I do know.
Then what happens?
Well, in the alternate universe
where George Bailey is not born,
he's not there to stop the pharmacist
from poisoning a child with pills.
Yes, that's right.
We were living in it's a wonderful life
for a minute of what if Mike was never born?
I know.
If Mike wasn't on the show.
And thank God it was short
because what a nightmare.
What a nightmare for somebody.
There wouldn't have been that tangent about it.
It's a wonderful life if I wasn't here.
Can you imagine?
I can't.
Imagine your life without that.
So yeah, picture of an old timey pharmacy,
which again, I kind of wish they had it there
and that was just the candy store or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wish at least it was themed after it.
Yeah, yeah.
Right, where there was old time medicine
but it was just a Gobstopper.
It seems like a lot of emphasis on mortar and pestles.
Which are cool.
Also a jar of live leeches.
Yeah, we got a photo of that.
Can Brett through there?
Brett, bring up that leeches photo.
Pull up the leeches please.
Yeah, this is a really creepy situation.
This is scarier than anything in Disneyland.
Now this was not a real pharmacy.
No.
The bank was a real bank.
This was not a real pharmacy.
Oh, here we go.
There they are.
Yeah, there's a girl just staring in horror
at leeches that are very long.
These are three inchers, three inch guy.
They were bred on leech farms.
Like these medicinal leeches were bred
to be good at medical stuff.
Right, they were trained.
Yeah, yeah, they like whispered at them,
suck out bad stuff, not good.
Don't just make people bleed and that's it.
Yeah, oh yeah.
They definitely didn't stop using leeches for a reason.
Yeah, were leeches happening so much in this era?
I feel like no.
If we're saying this is turn of the century.
I feel like this is a fun thing they're using here.
Because I think they're touching on,
before pharmacies there were apothecaries.
And I think if you go back far enough,
you get to like, oh no,
leeches can take out the bad blood.
Right, but this wasn't happening
as much in the 50s and 60s.
No.
I think the, well not 50s and 60s certainly,
but if we're like tributing turn of the century.
Right, like mainstream timeline.
What I saw is that maybe,
like they were around a little
and that you'd find them at bars and barber shops
to treat black eyes.
So got punched in the face,
put a scary black worm under your eye.
Would it just suck the blood out
so it would not look as bruised?
I think that's the idea.
That's right, some dentistry.
You used to go to the barber to get your hair cut,
a shave and get some bad teeth pulled.
Whoa, that's wild.
Buy a leech.
All right, leeches gonna start,
leeches gonna yank this tooth out.
Also how often are you getting a black eye as an adult?
Well in the turn of the century probably a lot.
I guess probably a lot, yeah.
Rough and tumble time.
Bullies everywhere.
You hit a wrong note in your barbershop quartet
and they gang up on you, that's three against one.
Blue-dos, Popeye's, blue-dos everywhere.
Hey, I'm ready to, I gotta kiss ya.
I'm gonna take you out and give you a suck ya one.
I'm gonna suck ya one.
They're just mumbling constantly
and you gotta stay away from them.
Yeah, and that guy was the secretary of state.
Yeah, for many years.
Again, not a real pharmacy
but did employ two real pharmacists
whose names are Frederick August Esteem
and Philip Milton Harvey.
So they could answer your questions.
They would dress in, they were wearing
the period appropriate attire.
They would talk to guests
and they would talk about the exhibits.
Great, so you watch Leo Wagman waves at you
from an old banker desk and Frederick August
tells you how they used to grind up Sassafras.
I wonder, is there enough room in there for a real pharmacy?
Probably not, because you gotta get a lot of different,
I mean, I guess around that time,
I don't know how many different drugs they had
just being used in America.
They're limited, so be like a,
it maybe fit in more of the hotel,
where it's not a hotel store, it's like a little,
it's like one shelf of necessities.
So yeah, now you can basically just like,
you can buy Tylenol on a leave and stuff, right?
Yeah, you can get those,
yeah, you can buy those at a lot of the shops.
You can also just go to First Aid
and they'll give you most of them for free.
Oh, load up.
Good tip.
Yeah, that's their way, that's your Disney Land bargain.
Save yourself some money, folks.
You bring a little duffel bag and just say,
I have 15 children with headaches.
And then just open the bag
and then the doctor will dump it in.
Don't do it if you're a buckler.
But don't do it, yeah,
because you'll start crying in a minute,
you don't have 15. Do it for me.
I'm too cheap for a leave.
My only choice was to pay $120 to come to Disneyland.
My 15 kids don't have headaches.
They're fine.
They're thriving, okay?
Especially the quintuplets.
They're queer. Both sets.
Clear headed and fine.
I think I told this story on the trip report
when I went to Disneyland last fall.
You five timer.
A five timer.
But it was still very funny to witness someone
who had a very specific ailment
and knew exactly what they needed come into First Aid.
I think I was just in there getting an ice pack
and they went, excuse me,
I just rode the Millennium Falcon and my,
I have a stomach ache.
Do you have Dremamine?
They're like, eh, we have a generic version.
Here you go.
So that was funny?
I don't know.
They were just so, they were just so,
good day, madam.
Do you have Dremamine?
I have just ridden the Millennium Falcon Smuggler's Run.
You're saying they knew exactly what it was.
They didn't have any,
they weren't like me when I went in there
and I was like, there's something in my eye
and I needed help and they were like,
I don't know what to do.
Yeah, I wasn't sure,
I think I was just not sure if Disney First Aid,
if it was like the school nurse
where you really had to sell
that you needed a single Tylenol,
like please, I have a headache.
I just need one Tylenol
and they would act like they were giving you
like a Xanax or something.
They would act like they were giving you
a controlled substance.
I only went to the nurse once.
Did we talk about this?
Are you serious?
In all of school years?
Once.
I went like once a month when I was in elementary school.
Oh really, you were a nurse?
I was a nervous guy.
You were a nurse kid.
I was puking.
I was always seemingly dehydrated.
I didn't know you were a nurse kid.
I was a nurse kid.
Because there were kids.
Nurses' pet.
Yeah, there were kids who would always go to the nurse.
And sometimes they would just be like,
the solution was like, go in here
and lie down for 20 minutes.
Wow.
On that paper bed.
On the paper bed, yeah.
I came in there because somebody scratched my eye
in gym class and the nurse couldn't tell
what was wrong with it.
But she called my mom and she was like,
he says something's wrong with his eye.
I don't really see it.
But I think it's probably real
because I've never seen him in here before.
Like he's never come into the office
so I believe he is not lying.
Because she would see liars constantly.
Because kids are lying all day.
Jason was probably doing it when he was a kid.
Oh, we all tell a little white lies.
That's much respect to the guy who heisted that restaurant.
Yeah, you can just lie your way through things.
If he had been a little better at lying,
he could have gotten away with it.
Yeah.
10 grand from his job.
So that was the only time I ever went to the nurse once.
Hey, we were jumping in the pool
in a kid's little red shorts.
Their scratchy little red shorts.
I was saying I got a lower half injury.
Michael has a testicular trisian
due to his little red shorts.
No, no, no, it was that a kid's,
the bottom of his shorts went against your eye.
Oh, yeah.
That was high school with the little red shorts.
I did not wear little red shorts in elementary school.
Even though it would have been cute.
Ballistic, great nylon shorts.
I wasn't old enough to wear little red shorts.
I wanted, look, if I could have worn Mickey's
little red shorts when I was in elementary school,
I would have.
But it was not an option presented to me.
Yeah.
Scott, do you have what they gave away
at the Upchon Pharmacy?
Yeah.
So, well, if you have a more official description.
I have a very, very detailed description
from Mouse Planet again.
The shop gave away free postcards,
as well as a free square miniature glass bottle
of orange colored unicap vitamins.
Inside a red box, a white silhouette
of the Disneyland Castle logo containing a description,
a descriptive pamphlet stating,
a souvenir of Disneyland Upchon with a history of Upchon.
The bottle was one and a half inches tall
and contained 12 vitamins with an expiration date.
Yes, I love it.
Give me more hyper detailed descriptions
of the tiny free vitamin bottle in a box.
So how, okay, how big was the bottle?
How many vitamins were in it?
How big was the box that held the bottle?
Right.
So it was the degree of.
Specificity.
Yes, that our listeners,
I struggled to get to the word specificity.
My language has no specificity.
You were becoming so bored by what you were talking about.
You just trailed off.
Little bottles of vitamin of box of.
Is there a Jim Hale about vitamins?
Is there anybody, is anybody like,
is Kevin Perger done a big Disneyland vitamins.
An Upchon episode.
Yeah, Upchon episode.
I wanna know, were there kids who would dare each other?
Like, do you guys know about the TikTok trend,
gentle minions?
Yes, indeed.
Where like just tons of teens will go see
the new minions movie in suits and be rowdy.
I don't know this actually.
Where they are.
Aren't they like, I think they're very like, yeah, yeah.
I've seen footage of them all watching it very intently
with their arms up in this sort of.
I think it's a mix.
I think some are rowdy and I think some are, who knows?
But we're there, I'm saying we're there kids
who would go to Upchon, get the free bottle of vitamins.
Like, I dare you to take all those vitamins.
I think that being a little stinker
was not invented until the 1960s.
Oh.
Like no child had ever misbehaved until,
it was Dennis the Menace really helped kick the idea.
Just the idea, it was invented by perverse Hollywood writers.
Oh man, Jordan Peterson's right.
And that is when everything went off.
The world gets you Dennis the Menace.
It will get you Menace too.
The rowdy antics of Dennis the Menace
destroyed this America.
Dennis is lost.
He doesn't, he's looking for meaning.
He's crying out and society is ignoring him.
That's why he has to have the little slingshot
poking out of his back pocket.
We're all Mr. Wilson, aren't we?
Aren't we all trying to get the rowdy boy to behave?
Isn't this what we all feel?
You won't cancel me.
What would Walter Mathau say if he was still with us?
Even Don Rickles in the sequel, the director of the sequel.
Playing Mr. Wilson.
I was confused by it, but now I understand.
Wow, that's a pretty solid, like.
Rickles is Mr. Wilson from Mathau to Rickles.
Well I think Mathau to Rickles, that's pretty good.
Yeah, Rickles acting career, interesting.
Yeah, you're right in terms of prominence
and interesting person, but yeah, I guess,
it's an acting trade down.
Yes, 100%.
Oh yeah, and I'm sure that was the only shift in quality
in the Dennis to Menace sequel,
which started very, high bar by the way,
the Dennis to Menace Walter Mathau movie.
Dennis to Menace?
Of a great film.
Are you calling it Dennis to Menace?
I didn't, but that's a good idea.
That's what I thought I heard.
I don't know.
Did I accidentally say Dennis to Menace?
Maybe not.
It should have been that.
Well, that's maybe too, you already had Menace to society,
so two and Menace have already been in a title together.
That's right, Dennis is a Menace to society.
Dennis is a Menace, I'll tell you what, two, society.
I'll get you.
So weird play, they also, they had a weird,
the movie that's slightly less weird than The Leeches
is that they had something called asafoetida gum,
which is a type of root or spice,
or something that comes from a root or something,
and the nickname for it is Devil's Dung.
Folks would wear it in a little sack around their necks
to ward off diseases.
So go to Disneyland, go see the bank teller,
go check out the Devil's Dung, try some strained veal.
It's at this point, here's maybe a broader question
with this topic that I wanted to bring up,
that's what your main street is.
Your main street is leeches and Devil's Dung,
and your dad makes a deposit at the bank,
and there was a lock store, they had a history of locks,
you could see a lock from ancient Egypt.
So you do all that, and then you go,
and that's just your opening act, to then go to a park
which has an unthemed hill and mules that kick
and bite you and piss, and a cloth dumbo
with eyes as black as death.
Mickey and Minnie with holes in their face.
Yes, with grates.
Grates, four grates going down their lower part
of their head, yes.
I think what I'm getting at is, how did it make it?
In this first year, and I don't even mean that,
because I always said there was fun stuff
at Disneyland even to begin with,
but then there was all this, and what was it
in that first year that got them through?
Because everything we have listed is either boring
or insane, and then a lot of the rest of the park
was that too, what do you think the takeaway,
when you came back from early Disneyland,
what was like, and then they had this, a castle?
I bet the castle and the Fantasyland rides,
and I bet those went a long way.
Oh yeah, Jungle Cruise was almost what it was,
because that was roughly the same,
just with less animation and the figures,
and the trees hadn't grown out yet.
But that's pretty, yeah, in 1955,
that's pretty crazy and immersive.
Yeah, and that's kitschy and fun.
No jokes yet though, don't forget.
No jokes, serious.
We're just saying serious facts about tigers.
Yes, very serious.
So I bet it's that, I do think probably
having it be turn of the century Main Street
felt novel to people and reminded them of their childhood,
or some of them, depending where they lived.
So that was a nice nostalgia hit for them.
I mean, I guess, look, I'm somebody who goes
to the saddest malls I can find,
because they feel like 1983, so that's roughly,
that's like a 50s person trying to visit a weird town
from 1902.
Well, it's like me when I drove through the Taco Bell
a couple weeks ago, near where I live,
and I was like, oh, they repainted it,
and it's the 90s purple.
Like they're using 90s purple on a lot of Taco Bells again,
which is very exciting.
It still doesn't look like the same
as 90s Taco Bell inside, but it made me feel good
seeing 90s purple on the outside of the building.
That does sound nice.
Yeah.
I love Taco Bell.
Yeah, it's fun.
Yeah, it's like the preserved Burger King
that was going around Twitter.
Oh yeah, they uncovered the Burger King.
From the Concord Mall in Wilmington, Delaware,
which I used to go to all the time,
and I was like, yeah, I recognize that Burger King.
I recognize that Burger King.
Like.
It was just like sealed up, and they never.
Sealed up?
Yes.
It's a woman posted, she's like,
I worked at that mall one summer,
and this was our overflow store room,
and there were just boxes and boxes
among the booths and stuff.
It reminded me of when the turtles
find that untouched subway station in Secret of the Ooze.
And make it their home?
And they make it their home
because it's been abandoned, no one knows it's there.
Yeah, so they just found.
Oh, oh yeah.
Perfectly preserved.
Yes, yes, yes.
Like I was like, I think I was sitting there
after Toy Story, I think we bought extra toys.
A little toy, whatever.
For Toy Story. Google it.
Yeah, yeah, oh boy, oh I will.
So.
I'll try to find like a VR helmet
that'll let me just wrap myself in those.
So yeah, so if we were imagining what,
like the version for us, if there was a new theme park
and Main Street looked like just a mundane mall
that we went to when we were little,
with like a retro Burger King, a retro McDonald, like.
Yeah.
If a.
Like.
No, it's an old circuit city.
Babbage's, what is that?
Oh, Babbage's, yeah.
The old electronics store.
I don't know if Babbage's.
Babbage's and electronics boutique.
Electronics boutique.
An old hot topic.
An Aladdin's Palace arcade.
Oh, Aladdin's Palace, fantastic.
Yeah, so if it was like all of that,
I'm going back every weekend.
Yeah, yeah.
If it's like that hardcore.
They have, they have a Mervins, wait for it, California.
A Mervins California, who would care about a Mervins, but.
So yeah, cause like even our parents who like Disneyland,
that's still, like they didn't live
during the time of Main Street.
They're maybe fascinated by.
And yeah, so I think, you know,
when you were going in the 50s,
there was a much higher percentage of people
that had lived through the time period it was representing.
Yeah, yeah.
For sure.
And it's like the most like clean, idealized version of it.
Yes, there's no problems there.
Well, and also, all right, so in asking that question,
what were the hits?
What were getting people to leave Disneyland
and talk about Disneyland?
I think that brings us to the big dog.
I was wondering like, oh, are we wrapping up?
No, no, no.
Are we just building up this?
No, no, no, no, no.
Is this its own?
No, no, no.
Is the wizard?
Look, it should be its own, but it will do it here.
It should be its own.
We'll do it here.
Let's do it.
If we can, if we can contain ourselves.
We're gonna get really nervous.
And that is, okay, we're gonna buckle.
We're gonna buckle even talking about it.
Well, we'll ease ourselves in
because we're talking about a store
called the Intimate Apparel Shop.
It's not the Intimate Apparel Shop contain,
but the incredible, the immortal,
the wonderful Wizard of Braz.
Is there a way to turn these studio lights red?
Oh.
Turn up the heat on us in here?
The table red is a red table talk.
We're getting real.
We're getting real about bras.
So yeah, Disneyland had a bra store.
I mean, what it said, okay, so outside of the store says,
if you can pull it up, the outside,
there's like people standing on the steps or something.
And the, well, here we go.
There's, well, there's the wizard.
There's the wizard, C.V. Wood in front of him,
an early, important figure in early Disneyland,
who I later went on to other projects outside of Disney.
And I have heard described alternately
as an interesting character and kind of a con man.
But I haven't really dug into.
Yeah, me neither.
Yeah, I need to learn the show.
Oh, that, yeah.
Yeah, that's a good tease.
We'll figure out what's up with C.V. Wood.
But okay, so this exhibit was sponsored
by the Hollywood Maxwell Bra Company.
And they had the tagline, the Wizard of Braz.
The viewers can see that here.
Included, and with this odd piece of art,
where we are looking at two women,
one is in a bra and one is in,
the outside of the store says,
"'Torsolette,' a word I have never heard in my life."
I guess that is a corset.
I believe that's what I would think it is.
That's an old-timey way.
But a lovely torsolette.
And these, it's very bridal.
It says, the bride chooses bras for beauty's sake.
The whisper wardrobe, lavished in lace,
wooing a wide world of fashion with straps to,
blah, blah, blah.
But anyway, the headline of what we're looking at right now
is these two women kind of demure and looking down
and changing into their beautiful torsolettes.
But then there's a fucking creep behind him.
Look out, one of the it follows creatures is behind you.
There is a murderer.
Pressed against foggy glass?
I don't know exactly.
It looks sort of like Eric Idle making a goofy face.
Big wide eyes.
And is that the Wizard of Bras?
Is this the Wizard of Bras?
Yes, that's the Wizard of Bras.
There's the Yesterland posts on this
have a little illustration of him.
It's not much better.
He's like a weird little, not quite a jester.
Yeah, he's like Zoltar.
He's like a dude.
There you go.
He's like a little Zoltar-y.
He's a little like the person in the medieval movie
who it's like, oh, they're a total liar.
They're snake oil salesmen.
And they're trying to weasel their way into becoming king.
I wouldn't trust this man to sell you a brassiere.
Yeah.
Creepy attitude.
I mean, if anything, he should be selling neck doilies,
whatever the hell those are called.
Yeah.
You know, what Shakespeare wore.
What are neck, I mean, is it neck doilies?
Why not?
Oh, I know that thing.
Yeah, you know those puffy's that people wore
because they were dumb in old dumb times.
That is a very good question.
But then what's he holding in this picture?
Is it a key?
Is it a leech?
Is he trying to make these women have leeches?
Is it like, you're not beautiful enough.
Let the leech suck more beauty.
Suck the ugly out of you.
I will remain young forever.
Well, in the illustrated one,
he has a, like, it looks like he's holding a needle.
Like a weird little.
A needle.
Like stringing it through his ears.
Yeah, I don't know what this.
What's he doing?
Oh yeah, he's pulling a needle through his ears.
Why?
It's like an old circus trick.
What are you doing, wizard of bronze?
Does one of the torso let,
does it like unlock like some sort of chastity belt?
Maybe from the back?
And he's like, I've locked you in.
A knot will unlock until your wedding night.
Your groom's in for a nasty surprise.
Certainly I have the key.
I will be there at all your important moments.
I am the wizard.
He's really a great Disney villain.
He should be up there with a Chernobog, quite frankly.
He's one of, yeah, he is a scary,
I mean, yeah, they should be using him in Phantasmac.
Why not?
We should have seen the wizard of bronze fight Mickey.
He's in Phantasmac.
An evil champion of women's chastity.
Yeah.
He's really strange.
Nick, can we go back to that other photo
where he's on the steps?
There's some stuff to analyze here.
So I guess this is the same guy,
but now he's got like a big cartoon head.
And oh, there's the needle.
Okay, we're doing some sleuthing here.
He's holding that same needle.
So that's an important.
Yeah, and of course there's Hernan J. Norris.
Herndan.
J. Norris.
And they're both staring at a bug going by.
I don't know what they're doing.
President of the Hollywood Maxwell Brazier Company.
Also should be noted,
the designer at the Hollywood Maxwell's company
who would often go to Paris fashion shows and stuff
was named Theo Devo.
Wow, yeah, that's a cool name.
Ooh, neat.
I mean, without a picture of the wizard of bronze
putting the needle through his head,
I think it's like it's a knitting needle, right?
I guess so.
He's sewing the torso in.
Yeah.
Right, but I mean it would help
if it was some string attached to it
and there were like two knitting needles,
but I assume that's what's going on.
Now we're getting to a more fun territory
with the full picture of this character
because he's like wearing fish nets, right?
So that's fun.
He's wearing the products.
Like stockings?
Yeah.
Is this the same character as the character
from the other picture though?
Yeah, I think this,
well, this looks like a walk around one,
but there was like a mechanized one, right?
I think we're looking at the mechanized one.
We are looking at.
I don't know because it's the best photo that exists.
Yeah.
Of that.
And by the way, just in your question, Michael,
who is the real wizard of bras?
I also saw one that's just like a cone
and who's just like a little cute cartoon guy.
He's a cute, like a left breast of a bra?
I wouldn't say that.
Even though this company did sell the 50s pointy bras,
I wouldn't say that because he was longer
than those would probably be.
He was just a cone.
He looked like a big wizard's hat,
but then the top part of him
was his own little wizard's hat.
Okay, so it wasn't like a Madonna cone bra.
I don't think he was one breast of a cone bra, no.
So there's a lot of ways to represent,
like Mickey, there's a lot of different wizards of bras.
Yeah.
Now, while this picture is up for people viewing this,
that man on the right who's looking at an ant infestation,
the one in the darkest suit,
he is the voice of the wizard of bras.
So I don't know this for sure,
but my best guess is that there was a mechanized figure
that looks like, or that it is,
this stocking-clad vizier, whatever you want to say he is.
Who would tell you about the history
of underwear and intimate apparel?
Mm-hmm.
And with this guy's voice,
which you can only imagine is like,
I don't wear bras, like how else is he gonna sound?
And a couple things here.
First of all, there's info about this
on the Ripley's Believe It or Not website.
Because then, by the way, wizard bras is one of these things,
if there's ever a list of the weirdest things
ever at Disneyland, wizard bras is in there, definitely.
It's not number one.
So you see it a lot, but still not a lot of info
to pull from it.
But it was enough that Ripley's Believe It or Not
talked about it, and they called the little show
that you watched an underwear history lesson.
Ha ha!
And let's see.
So there was a couple bits to this.
It was a store where you could buy bras and torsillettes.
So you could do that.
But there was also a demonstration aspect to it.
One bit seems to be that you would look into
3D illusion boxes, and you would turn your head
in the illusion box, or one of those pens you would get
that makes ladies clothes disappear.
Of course.
So you would look one way, and it was a woman fully clothed.
And then you'd look another way,
and she was just in a corset and pantaloons.
Okay.
So it was a place in early Disneyland,
an opening day Disneyland, where you put your head
in a box and watched a woman undress.
It was a peep show.
It was a little peep show.
There you go.
And you'd think they'd lean into,
and this stuff is utilitarian, and society's opinions
have changed on it from here to there, and that's it.
But they are a little bawdy about it all.
They are a little bawdy.
And Jason's getting emotional and upset about it.
I don't understand.
How could they, they're grooming.
It's grooming.
It seems like there were some interviews,
websites would note it, that they would talk to people
who worked there, talk to cast members at the time,
and they'd be like, okay, yeah, the parents and the kids
didn't really care.
The grandmothers would giggle, and the older,
the grandpas would be scandalized that this was here.
And I guess that's just a side, that's progress for you.
That seems to be the...
Grandpas were scandalized?
They were like, I'm so upset with this.
They weren't upset, they were just like,
oh, I can't be in here, I have to get out of here.
Well, you're discussing, you're describing passages
from a Disney-produced article from an internal newspaper
called Disneyland News with the headline,
If Hubby is Shy, Watch Him at Main Street Corset Shop.
Hubby is so shy.
Hubby is shy in the corsetaria.
It's just a weird article in general,
but it's the older generation of men
who are the most polite.
They invariably remove their hats upon entering the store.
Oh, there's pantaloons nearby, I best remove my hat.
I mean, people would remove their hat
anytime they went in anywhere.
That's old, for people's favorite thing to enforce,
is hats on or hats off.
And they loved getting apoplectic at like,
the guy hasn't taken his hat off in this diner,
in this 24-hour diner.
Meals ruined, birthdays ruined, any occasion destroyed
because a guy like 100 feet away had a hat on.
If you could have monitored everyone's blood pressure
as they walked in there,
I bet it would have jumped 30 points.
I need to calm down, I need to go get some tobacco,
three doors up. Some baby veal.
Yeah.
I need to calm down with some baby veal.
You can't eat baby veal in the store,
you're spilling it on the torsolettes.
It is crazy, I mean, I'm sure people have said this,
and maybe we've like, Walt famously didn't want
Annette Funicello to wear a two-piece bathing suit
because she would show her mid-drift in movies.
But he had a bra store where you could see,
I mean, maybe they weren't showing their belly.
He was upset with the belly.
You put your head in a box,
he would have happily had Annette wear whatever,
but you have to have a special box to view it.
But if it's a room open to anyone,
and a grandpa or a hubby might walk in and be scandalized.
Was it some sort of a box that would protect you from Jesus?
Like Jesus is scorned?
Like how Magneto has a helmet to protect him
from Professor X?
So if you put yourself in this box
that would protect you from religious or God's scorn,
you could gawk at a woman's bare belly.
Yeah, I think so.
Well, you can make Jesus sort of magically appear
in items when you want to.
So yes, by virtue of that,
you could make him disappear from a box.
So Walt could have like a priest like bless a box,
a reverse blessing or something,
or have like a church of Satan guy bless the box
to prevent Jesus from getting into the box.
So whatever hubby does in that box,
Jesus doesn't find out about.
Yeah, I think so, yeah.
We're opening in three days.
We haven't had the Church of Satan
chase Jesus out of the boxes yet out of the bra box.
Now, I don't go for you, you characters a lot of the time,
but there's one thing I need you to do.
You're good at chasing Christ away.
Protect hubbies when they're getting a peek.
We don't want Jesus here in the bra store.
So please put us put a first put a spell on them
to ensure that their hats get removed.
Because if they don't, their hats are going to fly off.
It's going to blow off their heads.
Steam will come out their ears.
We need a satanic draft in the entrance of the store.
And he'll blow hats back then.
Yeah, so this is stuff Walt had to deal with.
He apparently was against having this store.
He did not want this to be here,
but he had to flesh out the street.
There had to be things in the street.
Sure, he was against it.
He's the guy in charge.
Hollywood is the story.
Hollywood makeup even Max Factor,
the actual Max Factor, told him to fuck off.
And it's like, OK, guess we can't have a makeup shop.
What else do mom, grandma, and little Sally like?
Pantaloons.
I don't know, underwear.
They need dresses and underwear.
Laces, toilets.
Undergarments.
They smoke cigarettes.
Oh, fuck, we already have that.
Women in the park should smoke cigarettes
with little bits of lace at the end.
The cigsigalettes.
Fire again at Disneyland due to the lace cigarette trend.
Like, there should have been...
There were other things he could have done.
If you really like pudding, like pudding works.
Someone's like a pudding store on Main Street.
They didn't have to put this here.
He was pretending he didn't want this here.
Second candy store.
Sure.
Or so to fowl.
You know what, between the carnation and the candy,
the carnation ice cream and the pharmacy,
there wasn't, I'm sure there was regular fountain soda,
but there wasn't an old timey, you know, sarsaparilla soda.
I still think pudding works is a good choice.
If they had just a full-time pudding radio,
a good Disneyland pudding place.
J.L. Pudding's pudding works or something.
There are a couple pudding places in Los Angeles.
Really?
I think, yeah.
Where, do you know?
Santa Monica?
I don't know.
Is it like hipster pudding?
I think it's like, yeah, it's like a paper version of pudding.
So you load it with toppings and stuff.
Yeah.
Interesting.
High-end Silver Lake hipster pudding.
Yeah.
You heard it.
I did not know about this, Trevor.
We gotta go.
The thing that's like $2 at the grocery store, guess what?
They found a way to make it $10.
Man, I wonder, is there like a Mike Gambusa of pudding?
Or is that maybe you?
Could be, yeah, yeah, the door's open.
Yeah.
J.M. Sheridan's pudding works.
J.M. Sheridan's trifle world.
Puddins and trifles.
The Wizard of Trifles.
Before we wind it down, there's a clip that we have,
if we could play that, because there's no audio of the,
what then the Wizard of Braz did,
which is very upsetting that we can't look at that character
and then know how Gruff and William Frawley is.
Yes.
But what if there was some even weirder audio
that people cannot seem to find,
or it seems like the most I found was,
this may have been at a print-on-demand kiosks.
This was possibly part of when they did,
I guess, the 50th anniversary or around then,
you could burn a CD.
You could pick what tracks you wanted on a CD and burn it,
and this might have been one of them.
Which could have been like a song from a ride
or it's Groom Grinning Ghost or something,
but then it could also be this odd 90-second snippet
of the Wizard of Braz show.
So this isn't the wizard, let's be clear.
She's setting up the wizard.
So I don't remember a lot of what this is,
but let's just experience it together.
Look in the mirror and see the story of fashion.
Like all stories, it has two sides,
but since fashion is a lady,
the world can only know half of it.
The truth is that even in Granny's day,
being a doll required a lot of pull.
Those 90s were supposed to be gay,
but it took a lot of work to be stylish,
and most of it was undercover, as this makes clear.
Needless to say, Granny's secrets were well hidden.
Why, she turned green with envy if she could see the lift
today's girl gets from our low-cut Viet.
I want you to pause between every third word.
Cheeky pauses.
Then for a change of mood,
there's the new and intoxicating pink champagne
that lends its own sweet shape to you.
You see, modern girls have so many fashions to choose from,
it takes a wizard to keep them in shape.
That's why Hollywood Maxwell designs a bra for every fashion.
To see them all, just ask at your favorite store
for Hollywood Maxwell, the Wizard of Bras.
My favorite store?
Favorite store, yeah.
My favorite store is Fry's Electronics.
I don't think I could ask them for Hollywood Maxwell bras.
I went into the Woolworths and said,
do you have Hollywood Maxwell's bras?
And they're like, no.
One thing that's striking me from that is that music.
I was going to say the music is so...
Vrooom.
Doot doot doot doot doot doot.
That's still used as lazy comedy music in certain movies.
Yeah.
You're like, oh god, the comedy music.
Yeah, good old sneak around.
Sneak around music, yeah, it is sneak around music,
but it is trying to lighten the mood.
It's trying to lighten the mood of this like, dolekit.
It's uncomfortable.
Well, the hijinks that, you know, like,
Steve Martin might get into,
try to get his way at the wedding and father of the bride.
Yes.
But in this case, it's the hijinks of a woman
hiding her... giving herself some pull for hubby.
A woman, but you can only know how a woman is this.
Just clothes, I don't know.
Humans are so fucked, like, it starts to close.
Come on.
I mean, I'm not saying like when I was younger
and you'd like walk into a Victoria's Secret,
I wouldn't be like, what am I?
I can't look at anything.
Like, I was like that, but like, this is society I live in.
This is the society.
What do you need to do, ladies?
Spend an hour and a half getting little hooks and pulleys
to jam around your body,
make you very uncomfortable all day
so that you can sort of look like you are half a pound lighter.
I wonder if Hollywood Exile had the reputation
that I have heard women talk about Victoria's Secret,
go like, it fucking sucks.
Like, none of the sizes are correct.
They don't measure you right.
Like, an actual apparel, like, women's apparel store,
actual, like, bra shop, they're like,
you've been wearing the wrong size bra for two decades.
You're saying like, teen mall employees that work there
might not be measuring people correctly?
Yeah, it might not be totally correct, yeah.
Well, the Hollywood Maxwell bras from these pictures,
if I'm gathering things correctly,
they were the perfect size and shape
for women's pyramid-shaped breasts,
which I assume that they had until the year 1959 or so,
until they evolved to be less pointy.
Until the 60s when they started burning bras.
Like, they were burning...
They started over as the Great Revolution.
We had to reinvent what they were even like.
Yeah, yeah.
What a strange place and show.
Oh, but here, just before we wrap up,
one thing that's interesting about this,
this odd, creepy show with that V.O.
Oh, buh-buh-buh, and I don't know.
And then whatever the wizard sounded like.
And I don't know what the wizard did,
but he at least probably like turned
or shook around violently.
But he was mechanized.
And keep in mind, in 1955,
there were not mechanized characters at Disneyland.
Lincoln was almost a decade to go,
no Enchantiqui room.
So it's possible, possible that technically
the first audio animatronic was the Wizard of Bras.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's pretty wild.
Again, don't know what he did.
Probably just like his ears steamed.
Yeah.
At the mere thought of like a, you know,
of a half inch of skin revealing itself.
If he rotated, it made the sound of like an ax being sharpened.
Like, it was just horrifying.
He sparked, he would spark.
Again, if those sparks tumbled into the barber shop,
into the barberside.
He's the first ever robot that could get horny.
That's what we're trying to say.
He's the first.
Now we have many robots like that,
but back then that was very rare.
Yeah, look, and if you played that like tinkling little music,
you were allowed to be a little horny.
Disneyland could have a little horny as a treat
if you had that.
Because it would make it comfortable.
Without the soundtrack, it would go right to hell.
Society would fall apart.
But unless you play the Mickey and Goofy sneaking around the haunted house music.
Walt came into Matching Ring one day and he goes,
here's what I need you to do.
We need to make a robot who's a little horny.
Not a lot.
A little horny.
Can we do it?
All right, see you later.
And he walked out and he went to see Hazel George
and get his polo injury worked on.
His laugh in place.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, ladies, that's the presentation.
Now all eyes on the wizard who's about to get hard.
What a wall person.
I said a little.
I didn't say anything about an erection.
I'll allow a 20 degree angle.
He can go 20 degrees up, not a full 90.
Not a full one.
No full 90s, not on my watch.
If I say a 90, we're shutting the store down.
Roy comes in.
He's like, this is too expensive to give a robot a boner.
Walt, we're going broke here.
The Bank of America won't allow this.
I'll ask him for 50 grand more.
No problem.
Here's what I'll do.
I'll stage a robbery.
All fake robbing the bank so we can pay for this wizard robot boner.
If the chicken of the sea people can cut the amount of tuna used on sandwiches in half,
we'll save ourselves a bundle.
Have a scoop, fellas.
We got rusty robotic erections to pay for.
Well, I think that's a little window into what Main Street was like back in the early.
It was exactly like that.
And if you manage to not get sparks in your eyes that flew off of the Wizard of Braz,
you could have yourself a pretty nifty day.
You survived Podcast The Ride.
And thank you for putting up with an episode that did not have full host content,
much like a chicken of the sea sandwich.
It was thin on host for a little bit, but I hope it was an assumptuous meal anyway.
I want to apologize to everyone for my little secrets.
I will be on all the episodes going forward unless other little secrets get in the way.
Little secrets, sorry.
Little secrets.
Well, while we wait to see if he makes good on that or buckles,
you can find us on all the socials at Podcast The Ride.
Merch is available in our T-Public store.
This video will be up on the Forever Dog YouTube.
We've got a YouTube and I'll put on a playlist there.
You'll find it.
You'll figure it out.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out Podcast The Ride,
the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
We've also got our new tier club three where you get one more bonus episode every month.
Well, what a wonderful trip into the past.
I hope that it was an entertaining look at things that were largely not entertaining.
But did keep the lights on.
That's right.
And leeches.
Forever.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.