Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may be teaming
with five-legged goats, honey booths, and duck tambou.
People have got to know whether or not
their podcast is a crook.
Well, we're not a crook.
We're covering the Contemporary Hotel
and we're Podcast The Ride.
In-house noises
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
a podcast that's like a monorail of information
running right through the middle of your brain atrium.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
My brain atrium is one of the most pleasant places to be.
I just want to say that now.
Mm-hmm, beautiful interior decorating.
Beautiful old murals,
but my atrium and the hotel's atrium,
both equally pleasant, I want to say.
Right, and- And I'm very excited.
Yeah, that metaphor makes a lot of sense.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
And my atrium is more like the layout of the building
or design of the building, I guess I should say,
which is to say brutalist.
Mm-hmm.
Whoa, a hot take.
Hot take early in the podcast.
Dark thoughts, I guess.
Brutalist brain of Jason Sheridan.
Maybe that's what we just abandoned the episode
about the hotel and get in, dig in deep.
What is so brutal?
What is he talking about, folks?
Please, Michael, I have 17 pages about the contemporary.
Yeah, a lot to get.
There's a lot of pictures, granted.
The fuel of that brutalist brain of yours
with that apricot LaCroix. With the apricot, yeah.
It's delicious, I saw it in the fridge,
I was like, oh, I gotta try the apricot.
Brutalist brain fuel.
Today's episode is about Disney's contemporary resort,
one of the original two Disney World hotels
that opened in 1971.
Of course, the big, grand, futuristic hotel
that the monorail actually runs through.
And this is a video one, so if you're watching this,
or if you go to the Forever Dog YouTube,
you can see that I've brought my pride and joy,
which you can just hear.
You can hear that, that's all you get if you're listening,
is me pounding on it.
But if you're watching, I brought in my contemporary toy,
which I'm very proud of.
I lit it up from the inside, it doesn't come that way.
All you have to do is have a wire running not hidden
through the part where the monorail goes through.
I love this, this is one of my favorite items that I have.
I'm so excited that there is a big physical contemporary
that you can own.
Like a toy for the dorkiest child.
Oh yeah.
It could ever be.
It is, I've seen this, you've had this for a long time,
obviously, and it's something that I am jealous of,
and I haven't yet, until now, thought,
oh, I should buy this on eBay.
There's nothing stopping you.
It's not a rare item, you looked it up,
you can get it in a bundle with the other.
200 bucks, I think, for the monorail, the contemporary,
and maybe a spaceship Earth toy as well.
You're talking vintage,
because they still sell the contemporary.
Oh, you can get this thing?
I think you can get a newer version of this.
Oh, interesting.
And I'm on top of this.
Mine is just fine the way it is,
it doesn't need to be newer.
Well, you've got the real deal,
you've got the real deal vintage one.
I don't know, this might be from like four years ago,
I have no idea.
I like it, is the point.
It's dusty as a motherfucker,
but there's so many nooks and crannies,
every little hotel, oh, my fingers get in,
everybody else's frame, the contemporary's in,
I don't know, this is a very strange gesture I'm doing.
Look, look at the rooms.
They get very dusty in these little sleeves,
so the upkeep is difficult,
and I might start sneezing a lot during this episode,
not COVID, as far as I know, yet.
This is like great sort of play sets,
great play sets and toys,
and I don't wanna get off on a tangent here,
I don't wanna get off on a rant.
You about toys and play sets?
Just quickly, yeah.
This company, NECA, that makes the turtle toys I buy,
they're gonna make a turtle sewer,
that's the big rumor, we've seen pictures of it.
But I feel like contemporary,
as far as Disney World locations,
that's kind of number one, maybe,
as far as you want a play set of,
because it's so iconic.
Obviously, the castle's cool, but Disneyland got a castle.
This is so unique to Disney World.
I feel like maybe it is my main play set
from Disney World that I would want.
It's so Disney World specific,
so specific to that early, it's the Vacation Kingdom.
It's an emblem of the Vacation Kingdom,
but it's still iconic to this day.
This has ended up being in the background
of kind of all my Zooms for the seven years
that this all has been going on,
and let me tell you, it is a conversation starter.
The conversation goes, oh, yes, the Disney Hotel
is one of the hotels that used to be there,
and then that keeps going for two minutes,
and then the second part of the conversation,
the other person says, oh.
So if you wanna start that conversation,
get one of these and get it into the background of your Zoom.
If you wanna befuddle someone.
Yeah, yeah, if you wanna make them wish
they hadn't asked the question.
If you had just a collection of different hotels,
maybe that would actually make more,
you're like, well, I collect models of hotels.
That I've stayed at.
Yeah, I mean, I sort of do.
There's just not that many of them,
because I have a little mug of the Bonaventure Hotel,
which is the futuristic, the John Portman Hotel
with the elevator pods in downtown LA.
I have a ceramic mug of it, essentially,
that I use to hold pencils.
But that's, as far as I know, it's not like a big area.
Is brutalist architecture in little forms
you can put on your desk.
If we put it out there, I mean, we have a lot of listeners,
some that work in toy companies,
I assume people that obviously have made doll,
Michael Eisner doll for us.
I'm not calling for a custom built hotel or anything.
I'm just saying, maybe if we put that out there,
people, we could realize that there's a market
for hotels that we like,
that you wanna display a miniature version of.
So look, if somebody wanted to,
there's so many buildings to choose from
in the Peachtree District in Atlanta.
I would take any of them.
It doesn't need to be the Westin or the Sheraton,
whatever you want.
This is like your Ninja Turtle level fandom.
I need every cartoon character
that they made in the original cartoon.
I'm like, I gotta get all these,
because I never dreamed it would happen.
If there was a line of hotels,
you would have to get it all.
You would have as crazy a display as I have.
Actually, yeah, if there truly was,
I'm trying to think of other ones.
I mean, this wouldn't be in the line.
This is in the 10th release.
But we stayed in a Hyatt Regency near Disney
in Garden Grove that had a really good atrium.
And I'd love to have that in the current color
and in the original peach.
Exactly, that's how you do the toys.
You do a variant that has the different colors.
And then they could have a Comic-Con exclusive hotel.
Maybe it was only painted a certain color for a year.
Not only the hardcore hotel fans know.
And that's the one you get at Comic-Con,
because it's only they made 500 of them.
I'm finally in your world.
I'm locked in.
I just want to point out that the presence
of a customized toy has Mike immediately gassed up.
You're saying that my energy rose.
My energy rose naturally.
Scott perked up a little at the talk
of brutalist architectural hotel designs.
You perked up a little bit, but Mike, he's got the juice.
I like to toyify things.
So sometimes when I'm talking to people about toys,
I try to figure out exactly what their completest collector,
what would unlock their completest in them.
Because a lot of people like toys
and some have just a few of them.
And only a few people I know are like kind of completists.
But I believe everyone has something
they would be a completist about.
Oh yeah.
That's interesting.
Think about that at home.
What is the, you think you're not a toy person,
but if they made toys of that.
Exactly.
And tell us in the comments, what would you want?
What deep obscure thing?
Exactly.
So yeah, Jason, you collect some toys.
I collect some toys.
Will there be a specific, like islands of adventure,
high level toys based on just like the rides
and the iconography of islands of adventure?
I think if they had like, you know,
were Christmas villages big where you grew up,
like a tabletop Christmas,
like your parents would pull out the pieces and stuff.
If they had a full islands of adventure
with like each piece sold individually
of each like a landmark and you could,
you know, put them on a table with like fake snow,
with like cotton snow and light it up.
Oh, that sounds nice.
Yeah.
So, so yeah, as we said, yeah.
What would be your completest thing?
I have four or five completest things.
They're reissuing.
They make yours.
Yeah, in the last few years they are.
Yeah, this is, I'm all on my lonesome here.
It's just me and you contemporary.
See on the video, I can kind of nuzzle it.
I think there are, there are more,
we're getting, the only thing standing in the way of this
is that plastic prices and things are rising.
Shipping is rising, but price wise,
that's the only thing because they're a company
that's more obscure and more obscure
as far as what collectibles people are making.
So I don't think this is out of the realm of possibility
that someone would make a hotel, a model line.
Yeah.
Start cranking them out.
I, exactly one person is your customer.
I know on Yelp, I have seen crafters make
like desktop organizers or lamps
that are replicas of the lamps that some of these,
like craftsman style lamps in the style of the ones
in the Grand California or lamps in the style
of what you would see at the Animal Kingdom Lodge.
Would you be completest if you could purchase
all of the sort of light fixtures in an old Pizza Hut?
Oh yeah.
Tiffany lamps.
Oh absolutely, yeah.
If I could recreate the Canaan Road Pizza Hut
where I was having a Batley from Eureka's Castle
and then I spilled it everywhere,
but I still have very fond memories.
I'm drinking your soda.
It's my Batley.
That's your Batley.
Sounds like Lovitz.
Or Chuck E. Cheese.
Oh yeah.
That was Batley, I don't recall.
I don't remember what Batley sounded like.
He would say, I meant to do that, I believe.
I think that's what he would say.
Let's see, that again sounds very Lovitz to me.
Was Lovitz the voice of Batley?
I think I did say I meant to do that.
Didn't Batley say I meant to do that?
I don't remember a single other fact about Eureka's Castle
besides that the puppet spilled my soda
in the Agurah Hills Pizza Hut.
Yes, Batley would say.
Sit down Pizza Hut.
He would say, I meant to do that.
Yeah, Batley.
We haven't talked about Batley on the show yet.
No, yeah, Eureka's Castle could be.
There's plenty of opportunities in Eureka's Castle.
Yeah, play sets, all that.
I just bought, because we were on sale,
for like $4 each, I bought these little pieces
to connect and make a little Seinfeld apartment.
Okay.
It cost like 25 bucks.
Is it an empty apartment?
No, well they have little like peg pieces of the characters,
which I'm not, that's fine,
but I wanted just the apartment.
Okay.
You're more about the space, you want that?
Yeah, I was excited to have this space displayed.
Does it have the bike back there?
I actually haven't put it together,
so it might be painted on.
Okay, does it have, so you don't know,
it doesn't have his wall of VHSs, or you have to check?
I'll check, I'll check.
Let me know, let me know.
I haven't put it together yet, yeah.
Or do an unboxing.
Let the audience in on it.
We haven't done a lot of hotels.
We did a hotel sector in the City Walk saga.
We covered Sloppy Telly's Sheraton and Hilton,
but this is the first of the Disney's, I believe,
right in front of us now.
Right.
And I feel like there's a whole year on hotels, probably.
Oh yeah.
If we wanted to entertain ourselves
and perhaps bore some percentage of the audience.
Not this one though,
because this, there's a ton going on here.
There's entertainment, a ride goes through it.
We're almost talking about rides.
A ride goes through what we're talking about today.
I mean, that made a very, very clear impression.
Maybe even before I went,
was the pictures of the monorail
going through the Contemporary.
Yeah, which still seemed very futuristic at the time.
It feels futuristic now.
You don't see this all the time.
This is one of the great feats of man.
To have a monorail.
Eighth, ninth, tenth wonder of the world.
Yeah.
At this point.
I don't know how many they're up to.
Well, they're really only seven, right?
And Andre the Giant is the eighth
and China is the ninth, wrestler-wise.
But I think technically eight.
Okay, okay.
I don't think there's been an official declaration
of an eighth wonder of the world.
We have to decide if people are allowed in the list or not.
But the seven, yeah, the seven,
I think the seven was set in stone before.
No, iconic part of the early Disney world skyline,
because they didn't have all those other areas yet.
Primarily it was that Magic Kingdom zone
and you only had two hotels at the time.
Grand Floridian came later.
So when you went there, this is what you saw.
You saw the future.
It was nothing. And later spirits.
Yeah, and this was, by the way,
supposed to be a massive hotel district.
The unbuilt, the Persian hotel,
we eventually, there is a hotel called the Venetian,
but Disney had plans for a hotel called the Venetian Hotel.
Oh, really?
There are all these unbuilt hotels
that were gonna be themed after world destinations.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
So yeah, it was a much more,
usual the blue sky is very ambitious
and then we end up with less.
I mean, there's still talk that they'll,
there's been talk that they'll,
because right now there's only-
There's still room.
There are apparently a lot of sinkholes in this area
and that scuttled some progress.
Yeah, that's true.
Florida is swampy and maybe long-term,
not the best building area.
Love to eat steel girders.
Just the earth takes them back.
But they finally connected, right?
We talked about this before on the show.
They finally connected the Magic Kingdom to Grand Floridian.
Grand Floridian, it only took 50 years
to get that project done.
It feels like that was probably supposed
to happen much sooner.
Yeah.
But they really took their time.
It took a half of a century to do that.
Priorities.
They also in the last decade have made it much more clear
and safe that you can walk from the contemporary
to the Magic Kingdom.
Yeah, but yeah, I would say like,
when I think about, oh yeah, it would be awesome
if there was like 10 hotels or something around this,
but I don't know.
I kind of like that it takes a couple minutes for you
to see that you're like a big picture of the next hotel.
I like that there's three.
The space makes it feel, especially when I was a kid,
much more like kind of magical.
When you get little lengths of monorail ride in between
if you were stopping every minute, it might get annoying.
Right, so yeah, I'm sure they could build cool stuff
around it, but I kind of like there's only three.
I kind of think it's cool and it gives like,
yeah, the space gives it a little bit more
of a anticipation.
I keep saying especially as a child,
but we all know what I'm talking about,
especially as now an adult.
Continually, but as a kid, I remember being like,
you're peering out and you're like, oh, it's over there
and I can see it in just a little.
That feels like if you were stopping every two seconds
and it felt like you were just going in a big mall
or something like that, that would be less fun.
All three deluxe hotels, because they say,
I think the view and they justify it being close
to the Magic Kingdom.
Does anyone want a hazard guess on a nightly rate
a month from now in August?
Oh, from now?
Yeah, I'll guess.
So.
$565.
Okay.
I looked up the price of what it is
if you want a theme park room, so I'll refrain.
This is an expensive hotel.
What are you seeing?
So what I was seeing for middle of August,
so a month out, for a main tower, this guy
that we're looking at, main tower theme park view,
$741 a night.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Main tower lake view, $680, garden wing, $493.
So getting closer to reasonable in those garden wing rooms.
Closer.
Technically.
I spoke with my mother before doing this episode
and she said that they pay, what, $60 in the 70s,
I believe, for a night.
And I believe we stayed there when I was little
and it was more than that, but Lindsey and I stayed there
like eight years ago, or maybe I guess 10 years ago
at this point, and it was half what you're saying.
It was like 300, the Luxo hotels were all kind of like
$300 at that point.
You have a park view, where'd you stay?
Point on the.
Well the problem is it was one of the other towers
and I was stupid and I didn't realize it wasn't even that.
They probably confused you in all the text.
They did confuse me.
Now I wouldn't be confused, now I'm savvy,
but at the time it was the first time back
going to Disney World and I said, let's splurge a little,
let's do two at Grand Floridian, two at Contemporary,
it's a little expensive, not that expensive.
But then we got there and I was like,
oh shit, it's in one of the extra towers.
What's the point, that's stupid,
we may as well have been in an All-Star.
Gotcha.
One of the wings demolished around 2007, 2008
to build the Bay Lake Tower, then opened in 2009.
Yeah, so that was a little bit of a bummer.
Here's the other bummer about the price of it also,
and you find this at a lot of Disney hotels,
is like, oh it looks cool, like they say,
they make a toy of it, it looks good on the outside.
You get into the room and it is like
the most basic-ass hotel room you've ever seen.
These seem like just really, it's just a box.
These are not extraordinary.
Yeah, the one in the main tower.
Now a great view obviously if you get on that balcony.
Yeah, and I think the other ones are probably nicer,
the ones in the, what are you saying?
The Garden Way.
Yeah, they're built in the 70s
and clearly not like super rehabbed
other than putting the pictures of the Incredibles in there.
I'm sure we know about the way that this was built,
the way that the rooms were installed,
which is like drawers and a dresser,
that a crane, that the rooms were all built off-site,
fully built, like with wallpaper and tubs and everything.
Beds, furnishing, all fully built,
that this was built in conjunction
with the United States Steel Corporation.
The architect Walter Beckett is credited
with a lot of the design.
Welton Beckett is the guy actually, the first.
Welton?
Not Walter.
I don't believe so.
You might be getting close to Walter Becker from Steely Man.
I think it's Welton Beckett.
Here's Scott's architect corner
because what this guy designed and built,
these are like, especially LA, major icons of LA,
the Capitol Records building was this guy
the Cinerama Dome, the dearly currently departed,
but coming back with a lot of gross sounding food.
You're right.
Cinerama Dome, the Pan Pacific Auditorium,
which was this old LA landmark, this old theater
that now is just, there's a park and a gymnasium there,
but it used to be this like grand theater.
It's what the gates at Hollywood Studios
and California Adventure are based on,
those like big art deco with the stripes going around them
and a big setting in the film Xanadu,
also important for that reason.
Wow.
So iconic imagery from the sky, contemporary included.
Also the Reunion Tower in Dallas, which is the big,
one of my other favorites,
I would collect every one of these.
I was gonna say, they should do a line of just this guy.
Yeah.
Oh my, just start here.
Oh, if I can have a little Capitol Records,
someone must have made.
They have to have made a little Capitol Records.
Yeah, the Capitol Records building.
Yeah.
I mean, if you haven't seen it in LA,
driving down the 101, yeah, incredible piece of art
that looks like a stack of 45 records.
Now you're getting gassed up.
Now you're getting, yeah.
Oh yeah, look at this.
Can I get a miniature Capitol Records building?
I, it looks like, unless these are one-offs,
it looks like you can get.
Oh. Wow.
Why have I not done this?
You can for sure get that.
Oh yeah, that's a toy set.
Yes.
And there's like a Lego-y version.
I'm doing this.
I'm getting, I don't want Congress.
Get out of there.
Congress, not the building.
That's a defiled building.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't want anybody ever storming the Capitol Records,
but don't ever storm a Weldon Beckett building, damn it.
Oh, I was gonna say, I also want a set of the,
if it's an orb on a pole, that's,
any of the like observation towers,
Space Needle is kind of one of them.
The, what's the Knoxville, the Sun Sphere,
the Wigsphere from the Sixth Sense.
Oh yeah, okay, not like the orb
that the salty prince and Donald Trump,
everyone was touching the little orb.
No, a bigger orb, yeah.
I'd love to, no, I'd have that orb too.
You'd have the orb.
Kind of any, yeah, any of history's great orbs.
You'd ponder that orb.
I would, yeah, yeah, if we could all,
they should make it available for us to touch.
Sure.
I agree.
We could all take a trip to Saudi Arabia
and touch the orb.
Give us the orb, let us touch the orb.
A fact I always liked about the constructing of this area
is that they built a factory on what is now the,
like, the Port Orleans Resort area.
They built a factory to construct all these rooms.
Okay.
And, yes, Orlando has a very interesting interview
with a historian named Jim Corvus,
and they were trying to debunk the idea
that Disney's plan was when they needed to redo these rooms,
they'd pull them out of the contemporary
and put them back in.
Mm-hmm.
And.
Wait, do we finish saying that that was how,
that they, like, they were all airlifted on a crane.
They're modular.
And slid into the space where,
that a hotel room was carved out for.
Yeah.
So that in theory, if you wanted to update them,
you just do it in reverse.
Or if you had an unruly guest,
you could just pull them out in the middle of the night.
Yoink.
Dump them somewhere,
or, like, airlift them into, like, Disney jail,
which also should have been a modular building like this.
Because you could also see with different lighting,
this looks like some sort of mega jail,
or, like, the Marvel Universe Villains Fortress,
like, the Raft.
Oh, yeah.
Which is where they put the supervillains in.
Yes, yes.
So it's, like, the greatest hotel ever,
and it would also be the greatest prison of all time.
And you could, yeah, if there were, like, you know,
like, upper right corner ain't so bad,
but you really punish people
if you put them down in the basement.
So, yeah, you should, like, pluck people out.
Like, a big War of the Worlds machine.
Right, so, like-
Yeah, you're here now.
So, like, if you're going through it,
it's like, Baron Zemo is in one of the rooms, and then-
And he's talking to the lizard in another room.
The lizard's next door, right, and then,
I don't know, the rest of the bad guys are there, too.
It's important to have friends.
Oh, that's the Joker.
Sorry, that's the Joker in the red.
Joker's in there, too.
It's Joker and Catwoman.
They're all in the contemporary jail.
But, yeah, that was another, like, blue sky, I feel like, idea.
Well, I don't know that they ever,
because the thing is, once they put them in
to the contemporary,
they settled into the structure of the building,
and then they were pointing out in this interview, like,
yeah, they weren't gonna ever take them back out.
They built balconies.
Like, they built things around it.
They built support. It would be very hard to do it.
It'd be impossible.
You know, it's easier just sending
a couple of wallpaper installers up with rolls of wallpaper.
I like wallpaper installers.
That was the example they gave.
Like, you know, it's easier just sending, like,
carpet guys up.
Well, that's what I mean, like, a blue sky idea of, like,
oh, yeah, then it'll be cool.
Like, we'll be renovating half of the rooms or whatever
by pulling them out, and then we'll just do it offsite.
But, like, that's, who knows how far along
that actually got?
Because it does seem crazy and practical.
Yeah, to yank entire rooms out,
like you're, like, picking something,
you're grabbing a booger out of your nose.
Yeah, no, it seems insane to do that.
So, yeah, I don't know.
So they didn't do it. It didn't work.
They also, like, this whole, it was intended as this project
with US Steel to prove the efficiency and cost-effectiveness
of US Steel, and it was estimated, US Steel said
each room will cost $17,000, and then each room
only cost $100,000.
Wow, yeah.
So that's more than five times in 1971 dollars,
so that's a lot.
So they're still, so the prices now are still paying off,
though, probably.
That's right.
They're still paying off. How much does a hotel cost?
It was awful, like, when all the furniture
was made of asbestos, you know?
Yeah, so I get it now.
You a stealer liar, you can't trust the word of US Steel.
Can't trust US Steel.
US Steel, I think I read something once that Disney
had to take over getting this done,
because US Steel was so far behind,
and there was a fact somewhere that by, like, 1970,
they had all the convention space booked for 1972.
So it's like, we can't open late, okay?
There were rooms for the people to stay in.
It's like the version of the Jimmy Fallon sketch
where he says move, and he's the IT guy.
That's what Disney said to US Steel.
They were like, okay, I'm tracking this, hang on.
Okay, Disney is Nick Burns, your company's computer guy.
Exactly, so Disney is, yeah, they would say, like, move,
because we have to finish, well, I'll do it.
I'll do it myself, basically, is what the Disney company
would have to say to US Steel.
I don't know, this makes it much clearer to me, at least.
I don't know if the listener likes this.
Somebody later, like, so when driving with their husband
or wife who does not listen to the show,
half hour into a long drive, like,
what do I have to talk about?
Oh, you know what I found out is that US Steel is like,
the guy bungling the computer,
and Disney is like Nick Burns.
Nick Burns, Jimmy Fallon character.
Makes sense to me.
Three more hours of silence.
Why did we take this trip?
Let's just turn around.
How many people break up?
How many people, honestly, in the audience,
have broken up after trying to explain this dumb podcast
to whoever they were dating or whoever they were married to
and they were like, I can't do it anymore.
I understand, they went to City Walk.
I get it, it's funny, ha ha, 19 episodes, really good.
When you like it.
What a bit.
Maybe I would laugh at the punchline
if I understood any of the subjects in the setup.
That might help.
Maybe we should be together then.
That's great.
Thanks for telling me all those facts.
You didn't make eye contact once, you fuck.
So we apologize if that happened,
but honestly, I don't know.
Somebody exactly this.
You may recall, I listened to the show to escape.
Remember the dark days.
Not a mirror held up to me in my life.
Now I'm praying a fucking crane
dumps a modular hotel room ahead.
I wish my room right now was removable by crane.
That's also so funny to think about.
We gotta redo these rooms.
I've called the crane people.
What are you fucking talking about?
Just buy some new couches and put them on a truck.
Or you go down to the lobby and you're like,
oh, my son actually threw up in the closet
and I just wanna, is it possible to get somebody,
oh yeah, hold on one second.
They hit something on the button
and all of a sudden the room is just plucked
out of the hotel to be cleaned.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's great.
That's a fun cartoon idea.
If it was that efficient, yeah.
This is what a god could do.
Yeah.
So I mean, I'd like to see it, but I'm practical.
Not terribly practical. Doesn't make sense.
Luckily, across this hotel wide,
they chose aesthetics that would surely last
beyond 1974 or so.
They showed the name contemporary,
which requires you to stay contemporary.
And they kind of made the entire hotel look like the,
speaking of Seinfeld sets and constructing them,
the Merv Griffin set that was pulled out of the dumpster
and assembled in Kramer's apartment.
Yeah.
The whole hotel looks like that.
Where like, I obviously love old color schemes
and retro vibes, but boy was this an aggressively
just like early 70s, just like steeped really hard.
Like it's not one teabag of 70s aesthetic.
No.
It's a thousand all in one little cup.
Well, interesting and comes back around
in like cycles of design, fashion and taste.
Feels dated, I could only imagine back then,
this feels dated immediately.
Yeah.
In the way that mid-century modern is kind of,
I don't know, I will say timeless.
It feels like it's always in fashion.
It's like converse all-stars.
You mean you're talking like more 60s?
Yeah, like more like 60s style.
That never seems to fully go away.
Yeah, that I'm sure that had ebbs and flows
as far as people like recognizing it as cool probably,
but nothing like the inside of the contemporary,
like his age.
I can't think of a thing in Disney
that's aged worse maybe than the inside.
I'm trying to think, I mean, obviously stuff
has been redone, Disneyland Hotel has been redone,
but it still has its kind of 50s-y
or whatever year it was built in vibe.
Yeah.
But yeah, I can't think of anything.
If I could read a little, there's a big article,
several big articles on a website called Passport to Dreams
if you want to see a lot of contemporary
and read a lot of history of it.
And they really broke it down nicely, the early vibe.
A bizarre amalgamation of 70s pop and Mexican hacienda
where dramatic reds, oranges, yellows, and browns
overflowed from every nook and cranny.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the vibe.
Interesting, I didn't even think about it like that.
Which is a play that I would love to go walk around.
I'd for sure love, I would love if it existed
and if they'd never changed it,
but just like for regular people.
And it does, this Southwest vibe is really fascinating
because you look at this hotel,
you look at the outside of it, what makes them think,
make it feel like a future Pueblo?
Like, how did they land there?
Well, I actually found the answer for that
because I'm staring at the Mary Blair murals
and like, how did this get here?
Like, what is the thinking?
And there was thinking.
There's an article, there was.
They weren't sure.
They had a justification
and I don't know if I fully agree with it,
but there's an article in Design Observer.
And the idea was that Mary Blair's whimsical art style
and unique color palettes are very warm and friendly
and inviting and the characters in those murals,
which they are in a lot more early day stuff.
The restaurants have them, the do not disturb sign,
the soaps, they're kind of everywhere.
So very cute.
Cute Mary Blair, big eyed.
So that is meant to counterbalance
the kind of intense, brutalist architecture.
Sure, soften it up.
The balance, yeah.
Warm it up, yeah.
Right.
Yeah, I mean, it's interesting.
It's very bold for sure.
It's still good.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't let my negativity make you think I don't like it
because I do like it.
But it's the idea of something that is contemporary.
I mean, the restaurants and some of the amenities
have kept pace with changing taste, I think.
But I did have to laugh because it's like,
we're updating the rooms to the Incredibles.
Our hotel called The Contemporary will now have rooms
based on a movie from 2004 with an art style
from decades before that.
And then they redid the downstairs lobby
and that is all concept art and design stuff
from the development of The Contemporary.
So that contemporary is the past.
Right, right.
So we've kind of given up on the present and the future,
much like much of our culture.
Like, yeah, you don't want to think about the future
too much.
It's old stuff now.
Yeah, yeah.
Which now, I don't mind that stuff.
I mean, I like anything anytime they turn to it.
No, I think it looks great.
The lobby looks great.
The Steakhouse 71, new in the last few months,
it also looks great.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
There is a bone to pick and it's not my bone I'm picking.
I guess it's a past guest of the show, Dennis McNicholas,
who talked about Frontierland with us a little while ago.
He loves The Contemporary, loves to stay there,
and is a big fan of how they have redone the lobby recently
with this kind of nod to their 70s,
the original aesthetic.
But if we could pull up a photo called Rock Pillows,
Rock Pillows is the photo,
and this is one detail that Dennis liked a lot
if you're watching the video version.
So yeah, it's very, it's kooky cut out art
in Southwest colors on the wallpaper in the back,
and then big long sectionals.
And then along the couch,
there are these kind of odd, angular-shaped pillows.
They look hard, they look like rocks,
but they are quite soft.
If we show the close-up,
can we show Rock Pillow 2, beautiful, thank you, Margot.
I mean, that's fun, right?
You know, that adds some life to the couches.
We like our fake rocks.
I don't think we knew that they came in pillow form,
so we like this.
However, Dennis was there several weeks ago,
and the general style of the room remains,
but the Rock Pillows are gone.
No!
Why, Disney, why?
What?
You've taken so many nice things from us.
Why must the Rock Pillows, gotta be Chay Peck.
Chay Peck didn't understand it.
Well, my gosh, are there different pillows there,
or the pillows have been removed altogether?
There are no pillows, it's just blank.
Imagine that long couch with not a single pillow
causing distinct marks in between.
I think I have an explanation for that.
I believe these pillows,
I think something was going around when this opened.
Bugs?
I think those were chained to the couch.
Yeah, you pointed that out, yes.
And I think they were getting roasted.
Even Mr. Morrow pointed out that a bunch of new
Vacation Club stuff opened at the Contemporary,
and he went through a lob, and he's like,
oh, the pillows aren't chained down like in the Contemporary.
And I was like, what the fuck does that mean?
And Jane's like, oh, they chained pillows to the couches
so they wouldn't get stolen.
Yeah, I'd steal it, I'd be the first to steal it.
I understand, I'm the perpetrator.
Maybe somebody got past the chained system
and took all the Rock Pillows.
Chay Peck has sort of a Minority Report style console,
like technology console, and he knew you were about
to heist this thing in a couple months or whenever we go.
Probably.
And he was like, you know what,
let's just take them off the table.
So next time I go, I'm gonna be arrested for mind crimes.
That's right.
It's the future Chay Peck.
That's right, yeah, he's gonna arrest you for that.
Chay Peck, did you know this was coming?
A middle finger?
Did you know I was gonna commit this profanity
on a web broadcast?
He did know.
What do you think of that, huh?
He did know you were going to Disney Jail.
Banging on the Contemporary with my finger.
Now I'm just imagining Scott pulling a pre-cock
out of a vat, pulling up.
That was, you dirty rat, who was that?
Was it Bryce Dallas House?
It was someone's first big role.
Was a pre-cock?
Was a pre-cock.
I gotta look this up.
Oh yeah, I forget.
But no, that's gonna happen in Orlando with Scott.
Gonna pull someone out of a tank.
Mind crimes, this is ridiculous.
This world of arrests for things that haven't even been done
and no change.
Well, it's real.
Bring back the rock pillows.
We want our rock pillows.
We do want the rock pillows back.
Couldn't they at least put them
in like a little glass display case?
Okay, she had already been in stuff by this point.
It's Samantha Morton is the quote,
most talented of the three pre-cocks.
Oh okay.
I don't recall them having differences.
I can't remember the movie.
I just know about the main premise.
So there is a best pre-cock.
Agatha.
It's Agatha.
We gotta get Agatha out of here.
Okay, gotcha.
So if you start buying pre-cock action figures,
Agatha's the one.
I don't know if they've done Minority Report.
I would probably get, again,
I don't get a lot of Toys and Things,
and it's not like I've seen that movie a zillion times,
but to have pre-cock action figures would be pretty sweet.
Yeah, that would be cool.
I think they should just do a full cruise collection.
I don't know if he's into those action figures,
but like the eyes wide shut.
They make light of what I do.
This isn't for children.
This isn't for laughs and frivolity.
This is serious.
We're saving the planet one film at a time.
But come on, Tom.
Eyes wide shut figures?
Come on.
At least one sixth scale, hot toy style.
Masks to put on, all of them.
I just watched it for the first time.
Oh boy.
It's good.
It's something else.
It's a good movie.
Keeps you up at night.
It's weird.
Don't watch that right before you go to bed.
It is a weird one, but it's great.
You could have the note, like the note he gets about
to do an investigation. Oh yeah, cease your inquiries.
Yeah.
Cease your investigation.
Oh yeah.
So yeah, Southwest Vibe that they have continued
to stick to a little bit.
And one thing that has never disappeared
is that huge Mary Blair mural.
I don't know what you call it exactly.
The Grand Canyon Concourse mural.
It's what I've seen it referred to as.
If you don't recall, Mary Blair,
the artist mainly associated with It's a Small World
and the kooky perennially 60s design of It's a Small World.
And this is one of the other big places
where you see Mary Blair in the parks.
It's one of her last projects I think
for the Disney company.
And it's really nice.
It's all these cute villagers and a goat.
I didn't know about the goat.
Yeah, the five legged goat.
The five legged goat.
Yeah, he's another kind of nerdy reference, I feel like.
The real ones know.
Yeah.
So tired dynamite goat, wired.
Yeah, exactly.
The dynamite goat, everybody knows that.
I have a lot of them listening to this.
No, go to the grocery store
and ask about the dynamite goat.
They'll know, anybody.
What's the dynamite goat?
And they'll go like a big thunder.
Everyone will say in unison,
big thunder mountain on the lift hills.
Turn and face it while you go around the bend
and the thrill will be a little more intense.
Did you read the justification?
I did, yes.
Yeah, I thought that was really interesting
that it was a purposeful quote unquote mistake
and it's meant to represent the idea
that nothing man makes is perfect.
The Southwest Native American drives
that she was studying and being inspired by,
she was paying homage to that idea.
Pretty cool.
Yeah.
I did not know that.
She's wrong, they made the exterior
of the contemporary hotel, which is perfect.
Yes, so that's the one, yeah, perfect thing.
I mean, it makes sense
that that would be inside of a perfect structure.
Yeah, yes.
It's perfect to ironing.
It's very ironic that in a perfect place.
You know what else I like about,
here's something to say if we're,
if just to move, if we're moving fully on
from the outside of the contemporary.
We don't have to.
Yeah, absolutely.
We can just have this episode be the outside.
The outside of the contemporary is the name.
I have thought about that as the way
to tackle Spaceship Earth, that it is exterior.
Yeah, yeah, I hear that.
Like talking about it as an icon.
And the mural as well.
Oh, sure, yes, yeah, everything on the outside.
And then inside is a whole other thing.
The inside is five more episodes.
That is a great idea.
Great, great.
You guys, I know you guys are proud of me
when I am pitching the topic, Microdivisions.
Another relationship just ended
because somebody realized that they were gonna have
to listen to that in the car with somebody.
They're like, well, that's enough.
I'm getting out before they do that.
I'm sorry, the Epcot ball is getting
an inside and outside episode.
It's not the Epcot ball.
I know if you're riding shotgun,
you're supposed to get control of the iPhone.
I can't abide by that rule anymore.
There's too much content.
These maniacs put out too much content.
I have to keep up.
I'll get behind it, I'll get spoiled.
You think I want to, you think I wanna hear all this?
No, it's a chore at this point.
Compulsion.
It's a chore at this point.
I have a problem.
They promised that Scott would eat a bowl
of fruity pebbles and I've been waiting.
I want him to eat the fruity pebbles.
When is it gonna happen?
I'm begging to hear Weiger and Mitch talk about their cum.
I'm begging for that and it's awful.
I hate it.
Well, we have nothing to say after that, Jason.
You made us, yeah, you threw.
Too far, my friend.
We're gonna have to take a five minute break
while we think about their cum.
Yeah, sure.
Too far.
To talk about something as pleasant as those guys cum,
again, the outside of the building,
which you know what's great is any perspective that you get,
any view that you get where Space Mountain is also in it.
This almost, if you're in the Magic Kingdom
or you're in their Tomorrowland,
it almost feels like this building, the Contemporary,
is elsewhere in Tomorrowland or on the horizon.
It almost feels like the back wall facade of Tomorrowland.
It blends so well.
Space Mountain looks so beautiful
and is kind of a good pair,
a good match with the Contemporary.
I like to think of them as being married.
I like to think of them as partners.
They're a little far away.
I guess in the right perspective.
Not from their, they're big buildings.
They're as far away from each other
as I am far away from you and you.
I guess that's a good point.
I just would, if they were married.
They're not close enough to kiss.
I want them kissing is what I'm saying.
If I picture the two buildings married,
I think they should be able to reach over
and give each other a little kiss.
So maybe they're married but they have separate bedrooms.
They're one of those couples.
Yes, like Disney would want in the early 70s.
There's a little moat, I think,
that makes sure that's like having a privacy curtain
like you'd have in a hospital
or in a married couple bedroom in 1971.
That's good.
They've never consummated.
The two buildings have never consummated their love
but they are married.
And now again, it makes perfect sense.
Now it's a perfect way to describe it.
Unless you want to think of the monorail.
Think of the monorail as Space Mountain's sperm.
Okay, what about this?
Entering the contemporary.
What about this?
Space Mountain and the contemporary are married
but Space Mountain is unable to have a physical relationship
for whatever reason.
I don't want to say why
but Space Mountain cannot be physical.
So Space Mountain has allowed the contemporary
to be physical with the monorail.
Oh, I see.
And Space Mountain gets to watch the contemporary.
You're describing some sort of agoraphobic open marriage.
Well, well, well, now who are the filth mongers?
I'm being very tasteful in the way I'm describing this.
In a way, Mike has presented the most.
Well, although, is that dirty or is it clean?
What I'm describing is very-
Well, if it keeps everyone happy,
if everyone abides by the boundaries set up.
I think that they're all very on board with the rules
because it's been going for 50 years at this point.
The relationship's been this way for so many years.
The scene where they land,
if these are people and not hotels we're talking about,
so it's a scene where a woman is walking through the park
and then you go wider and see her bow
and he's in a bubble.
He's in a big plastic bubble
and they're having a nice stroll together.
I'm beginning to think about marriage,
but you are aware, obviously, of my condition.
What if I were to propose an arrangement?
I stay in the bubble and you get railed
by a man of my choosing.
Well, this is a relationship people have.
It's the only way it works.
No judgment, this is a relationship people have.
If it works for everyone, I think it's fine.
Those early contemporary vacation kingdom marketing materials
really looks like they're trying to get the money
of traveling couples who have quote, arrangements.
You're saying it's appealing to swingers?
I'm saying if you look at the pictures in these brochures,
and also there's the Magic Kingdom.
The characters and the attractions are so small
compared to parasailing, compared to putt-putt boat.
I'm still, okay, I'm confused.
Can you show us a photo?
That parasailing and putt-putt golf
are being advertised as a...
Well, look at this.
These are young couple, these are people on vacation
at a resort.
Hot singles.
Hot singles in your area.
Hot swingers, hot singles.
I don't know if they're necessarily courting
the swinger demographic, but I see what you're saying.
These might be monogamous couples.
I think you're putting a lot on them to say that...
Let me see the thing again, Jason.
Yeah, sure.
Could I hold it in my little hand?
My little hand?
Yeah, you can see there's small shots of each part.
First of all, there's two pictures of families
in this picture.
Oh no, three pictures of families.
Wait, how many children are in what Jason just took?
But what's the biggest photo?
There are four children in this picture
that Jason's talking about.
In the montage you're describing, there's four children,
and you're saying that this is an ad
to come and get a third at a Disney World Hotel.
This is a later.
It's starting to fade away.
The attractions, all the parks are in this one.
All you're responding to is the fact
that very prominently there's a man
who is in very good shape with his shirt off
on whatever this parasailing thing with a woman.
Who he may be completely monogamous with.
One piece bathing suit also.
It's not even scandalous by Disney standards,
Waltz standards.
And then the other pictures are of the parks.
So basically it's advertising parasailing
for hot young couples.
That's what I would say.
I don't know that there's any sort of swinging subtext.
Well, it's just there used to be so much emphasis
on the former, what is now California Grill,
the former Top of the World Lounge,
where it's like, come, eat a nice meal,
get hammered, see some singers.
Put your keys in the bowl.
They're open till 2 a.m.
Nothing at Disney World is open.
I wanna see if you can find the most swinger's energy ad.
And you don't have to do it now,
but for the future, I wanna see if there is one
that really gives it off,
because I don't know that that's the one.
It has parasailing in it.
It doesn't parasailing in it. Sexy as sport.
Jason, are you sort of like,
you have a parasailing fetish?
I have a parasailing?
Like, yeah, someone sails up, hello there.
We saw you across the beach.
We like your vibe.
Oh no, the boat's motors are crossing.
Blah, entire arrangement falls apart, fires.
But even just in the text of those early, early,
Disney World is now open,
the vacation kingdom of the world,
they're emphasizing the vacation element.
Come take a vacation, not come to the theme park.
It's almost an afterthought, and especially back then,
the parks closed so early.
My family was all, we took my grandparents down.
They're still close to early.
In 91, and like in November of 1991,
the parks are closing at like 6 p.m.
Yeah, but they still, I still find that,
I'm like, why isn't it open later?
Anytime I'm there, I go, what?
Well, in the late 90s,
the Magic Kingdom was open until like midnight.
Like Disney Land is.
Yeah, I think that's still, maybe that happens in the summer,
but all the parks should be open till midnight all the time.
It's really strange.
Yeah, that's what I want.
What a hassle it is to book reservations and everything.
Yeah, because then you go,
well, if I'm gonna split the day,
I like staying till midnight.
That's the fun, so.
I do still take Umbridge with the idea
that advertising that you can have a drink there
equals everybody come fuck.
Well, no, they counteracted that
by making the most disgusting cocktails you have ever heard.
Yeah, yeah, let's talk about the cocktails.
Can we talk about the gross food?
This is the gross food section of the show,
and I have a lot.
No, everything in this list is horrendous.
Now, I don't know if,
I don't even remember where mine are pulled from,
which restaurant, I guess it doesn't matter.
I pulled a lot, the website RetroWDW
had scans of a cookbook series called
Thought You Would Never Ask
and Thought You Would Never Ask Part Two,
which collected recipes from restaurants in Central Florida,
which included Walt Disney World.
Okay, well, it's all Central Florida old recipes?
Oh, who collects these things
and talks about them, these freaks?
Oh, I don't even wanna meet the person
who put this on the web.
Strange.
Anyway, let's talk about it for now.
Let's talk about everything in them.
Tomato stuffed with fiddle leaf fern.
Yeah, I don't know, fiddle, what is that?
Okay, I looked it up.
Fiddle leaf fern is kind of like a spiral shaped fern growth
that you can use in cooking.
I have never ever seen food with fiddle leaf fern.
Eating a fern?
Hey, I might eat a fern.
It did include, what else is it?
I'm not a brontosaurus.
No.
Onion, two sticks.
Never will be.
Six tomatoes, two sticks of butter, nutmeg.
Everything on it back then had nutmeg in it.
Like, a lot of the cocktails involved nutmeg.
Drinks do too, yes.
I mean, I like a nutmeg in a drink.
I'm not against that.
But wait until you hear some of these combinations.
All right, go ahead.
I think the grossest one I found was called French 75.
Which is a drink that is not always like this.
Yeah.
This is a specific French 75.
I think I've had a French 75
and these are not the ingredients as far as I know.
However, how much money we wanna put on Mike
thinking this sounds like French 75.
Mike will love this.
And this isn't even the one with sherbet in it.
French 75 from the cookbook.
One and a quarter ounce gin, two ounce sour mix.
Okay, normal.
Two and a half ounces champagne.
Okay, still pretty normal.
Dash of rock candy syrup.
Great.
The suggestion of how to acquire rock candy syrup
is melt down rock candy with a little water.
That's so you have to make your own rock candy syrup.
I've never had rock candy syrup.
I like an occasional piece of rock candy.
I don't know how you guys feel about rock candy.
Can't recall having rock candy.
I know I have.
Jason?
I like it okay.
Yeah, it's a little bit of a chore.
Yeah.
You've gotta suck on it for a while.
It's a vacation treat.
I feel like it's a thing that candy shops on vacations.
They have it in its sugar.
Once in a while, if I was getting bulk,
I'd have a little piece of it.
But it's a little bit like,
yeah, it's just like a little crystal.
So I guess you would melt it down.
I don't know.
It's a sugar.
I don't know what's the.
I guess it does just end up being a syrup
at the end of the day.
It's strange to see in a recipe.
Scott, do you have the monorail drinks in front of you?
Yeah, you got four colors of monorail pink.
Gin, pineapple and orange juice,
grenadine syrup and heavy cream.
Heavy cream.
No, fuck.
No.
Heavy.
Monorail red, tequila, galliano, grenadine,
pineapple juice and lemon bar mix.
I bet that's good.
Yeah, well, yes, you.
I bet that, but which part of it is bad?
Well, for you, the tequila.
Yeah, no, I know that.
You can get away from that with all this sugar.
But I mean.
It'll be like there's none.
Which part of it do you guys not like about that drink?
Look, I don't want any of the.
I don't want the sour mix in the French 75, much less.
So you don't like a whiskey sour?
Not so much.
I try to get as little of, and margaritas,
if we can get down to it's like a, it's juice.
It's a splash.
Yeah.
Not sour mix.
Okay, cause sour, yeah, okay.
But I'll have a whiskey sour.
I don't like it too sour.
But I guess that depends on the strength of the mix.
Lemon bar mix is fascinating.
Is that like a powder?
I don't know.
I can't picture how that comes.
And grenadine is God's nectar.
I love it.
Grenadine is the greatest.
Grenadine is like the Shirley Temple.
Yeah.
Yeah, the greatest drink.
The greatest drink known to man.
I'm sorry.
Are you still a Shirley Temple drinker?
God's juice, God's juice I call it.
I double checked.
Galeano is a sweet liqueur.
So this is like the sweetest.
That's the issue.
I think pick one of the.
I would never have a drink with more than one of these.
A sweet liqueur added to all of that
I think does seem like it's a little crazy.
Cause grenadine goes a long way in the drink.
But grenadine is so.
Lemon bar mix goes the longest way.
Yeah, maybe.
Monterey yellow has coconut cream.
That's the weird one in there.
And then Monterey purple.
Yeah.
I like to eat wine and grape juice.
What are we doing here?
For Andy and wine.
Wine and grape juice?
Wine is unspecified.
Don't worry about it, wine.
Cause wine is made from grapes.
Why do we need more grapes?
And just grape.
I don't, I'm not drinking grape juice for any reason.
I like grape juice, Jason.
Yes, I do like grape juice.
I like the grape juice that's called wine.
Okay, I like wine too.
It seems like a lot of grapes.
I have some non-alcoholic drinks.
Did you pull these?
Maybe not, what do we got?
Okay, let's see.
Bay Lake Thirst Quencher, a refreshing intermission
featuring lime sherbet garnished with pineapple,
fresh mint leaves, and topped with delicious lemonade.
Just think there's a lot going on there.
Yes.
But not as much as an orange sunshine.
A delightful combination of freshly squeezed
Florida orange juice, blended with an egg yolk,
sweetened with a spoonful of orange blossom honey,
seasoned with a hint of lime,
and a touch of grated nutmeg.
These folks. I bet that's good.
I bet that's good.
They love nutmeg.
I bet that drink's good though.
And zero alcohol content.
Zero alcohol so you don't get that stupid buzz
that we don't want.
You get all the sugar and none of the buzz.
You just wanna feel a little bit of sugar,
little bits and blaps in our brain.
Yeah, you just wanna have fun.
Do you think that one sounds bad?
I don't, I just think there's just too much going on.
I mean, egg yolk. Egg yolk?
Egg whites, if you froth, it becomes meringue.
Egg yolk, I don't know, it might be interesting.
Cause egg yolk isn't like it's sugar thing.
It isn't.
So it's four different forms of sugar
and then egg yolk.
And no alcohol.
I bet it's interesting.
I'll make that one.
Can I make that one?
You should make it.
Yeah, I'll drink it if you make it.
It's probably as an episode.
And now a guy's in the car and he's been like,
oh, I gotta keep listening
so they can make that dumb drink.
Now I'm into, that's the significant other.
They come back.
Fine, okay.
I do wanna hear this guy in his 30s drink egg yolk.
I also, I'm giving them the benefit of the doubt
that that is like real honey, like fresh honey.
I hate artificial honey or like honey in packets.
I just don't like it.
The lowest I will go will be the bear shaped bottle.
Oh, so you don't think that's high quality?
I will descend to the bear.
Well, it can be either.
I've seen like raw from the farm honey in those bottles,
but I've also seen just like the Kroger crap brand.
So there's multiple bears.
There's different bear bottles
for different qualities of honey.
Yeah, the bear bottle will trick me.
I'm saying like the nasty little lemon honey tea
and the tea bag already has honey flavoring in it.
That's gross to me.
Can we look into how many different bear bottles
there are for honey and severe?
Well, I'll take any of them.
I'll take any of them.
I know that, but I'm saying for our purposes,
figure out mascot wise,
figure out what the different bottles are,
the plastic or the glass.
Oh, the skew numbers.
Yeah.
Yeah, and figure out like what's the high quality bear
and what's the brand and.
Sure.
Yeah.
I think we can do that.
All right.
Which one of their little honey spigot hats is the cutest?
That's right.
Yeah, there's a lot here.
There's multiple episodes here.
A Burbank farmers market usually has a honey booth.
That's where I've bought honey in the past.
You've been to the honey booth.
Honey booth.
I mean, I could, we could dig into what the honey booth is.
I know that, okay, that is a funny phrase,
but that's kind of a standard farmers market stall.
I don't think that's that.
I have no doubt it is.
Does it consist of you dipping your entire.
I just want us.
Into open pots.
Look, did I have a long conversation with the guy of like,
well, what do you think the differences
between the poppy honey and the buckwheat honey?
He's like, well, the buckwheat honey
is gonna have more of an interesting flavor, I think.
I was like, oh, okay, well,
I'll try the buckwheat honey, I guess.
Like it's, language is so important, folks.
Cause like, if you think about this, it's like,
if you just said I bought honey at the farmers market,
we move on, we go back to the hotel.
But Jason says, I went to the honey booth
at the farmers market and I could talk about it
for 10 more minutes, but I mean, we won't.
I'm just saying the language is so important.
He said full fat Sprite
and I've brought it up in every episode.
Every episode.
You five-timered it like immediately.
I'm knowingly five-timered it.
And that one, of course, Sprite,
they for years advertised as fat free.
I fucked that one up.
Full sugar Sprite, full calories Sprite.
I don't know about it.
Too late, it's full fat Sprite.
Why are you, don't know, we love full fat Sprite.
You know, it's short and sweet.
You get what I'm saying.
It's not diet, you know?
Not diet, yeah.
So anyway, honey booth, honey bears coming soon.
Honey bears episode.
There's some other, I was looking at just food
that you could get in 70s contemporary.
I mean, they're all pretty bad,
but let me just cut to the chase
and bring up ham and rice salad.
These are three characters from different universes.
They don't belong in the same multiverse.
Ham, rice, and salad, it's not a fun mix.
Ham salad, though, is something
that has been around for a long time.
Ham can be in salads, or it's in combo.
I don't like it.
No, I don't.
Not a big fan of it.
I'm not a big ham guy in general.
Wait, are you talking about like a chef salad,
or are you talking about chopped up ham with mayonnaise,
AKA ham salad?
Oh, ham salads like chicken salad?
Ham salad, tuna salad, chicken salad.
They're all in the same family.
I've never had ham salad.
No, oh god.
That, yours, what was yours, the full title again?
Oh, the full title was ham and rice salad.
That could really go in any possible direction.
Could, I don't know if there's any results.
There's things on here that, like, duck tambu.
That sparked my interest.
Well, what's duck tambu?
There are almost no results for duck tambu.
Duck tambu.
Nobody bothered to save the recipes for any of this.
No.
Let this die in the 70s.
Let the past die, kill it.
What's the last Jedi line?
Kill it.
Yeah.
They burned all the books.
Yoda burned all the ancient contemporary cookbooks.
Great ham and rice salad, it was not.
Now no one will ask.
You'd never ask, now no one will ask.
And no one missed them.
Also spaghetti salad.
What do you mean?
There is a very funny, there is one menu for the contemporary,
I believe that listed as Italian spaghetti.
I was just like, oh, maybe there is something to that idea
that food didn't taste good until the 1980s in America.
Or it's just so much salt and lard.
That was the stuff that tasted good, you know?
Which by the way, so the restaurant up here in the video,
here I'll pop off the little, up here in the floating,
the top portion and I'll lock it back in, bang.
At the top of the contemporary of course
is the California Grill, which opened in the 90s
and remains a really fantastic restaurant
and a great place to have some drinks.
And that feels like a, that is staying contemporary.
That is like, people are eating avocado now.
There's this thing, sushi.
Flat bread pizza.
Flat bread.
Yes.
But I think of bread as being a big puffy loaf.
What do you mean?
It's thin.
Someone who, whatever culinary mind at Disneyland
discovered flat breads and just distributed them wide,
bought a massive, like they got a huge bonus.
Like you're saving us so much fucking money on bread costs.
It seems fancy to them.
They bought it.
These fucking suckers, these fucking rubes.
I do love the, I will pay, I don't even look at the price.
If it's a flat bread and it's at Disneyland
and it's next to wine, I'm like, oh shit, that was $84.
It wasn't good.
I've probably been suckered.
I'm a sucker for deep dish of course,
because I'm from the Chicago area.
But flat bread is so manageable pizza-wise.
So if you're not, you don't want to spill.
Appetizer, it doesn't have to be your main.
Yeah, it doesn't have to be your main.
It could be your side.
So it could be anything.
And it is a, depending on what you're doing,
it's very desirable.
I feel flat bread.
I think, I am a sucker if the flat bread has like
Goat Cheese or Manchego and or Figs, I'm like, well,
I am pulling out my monocle and my ascot for this
and we must have it.
Some honey, some balsamic, something going on.
Yeah, absolutely.
I'll do a once a year anchovy, honestly.
On a flat bread?
Sure.
They do at Disney?
I don't know they do that at Disney,
but I'm just saying, like I'll go crazy on a flat bread.
That's what I'm saying.
Sure, anything goes.
Yeah, you can put honey on it and I don't care.
It could be the cheap shit.
It could be the good stuff that Jason got at the honey bar.
You're the most bulbous bear.
But so that's the top of the contemporary now,
which is great.
I got a last minute time there when we were all down
together a couple years ago.
Oh my God, like top of the world.
The former name of the establishment.
If you're watching fireworks up there
and they're piping in the music
and you got yourself a great drink
and you got yourself a great gal,
which I had and a baby on the way.
I was really just like, wow, life is,
I was like, absolutely effervescent up at the time.
I am anytime.
Was that the telephone girl?
You were having a great time.
She got to drink shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She's drinking club soda.
Why is she less.
Another lemonade.
Solitary than me.
I feel like that was a day we had,
we went to that lounge that just opened at Grand Floridian
and then I think, was it the same day
or am I mixing up my days?
I don't think it was.
We may have done it that same day.
So we got to go to that Grand Floridian lounge
on the balcony and then went to top of the world
later that night.
That's a day, right?
They're just touring the.
That's all you need to do.
You don't even.
Trader Sam's there.
Yeah, Monorail Bar Crawl.
If you're like Disney World's too expensive,
it is too expensive, but you can go to the hotels.
And not stay there.
Not stay there.
You can leave.
And you can get the magic.
You can get a little piece of magic.
You can get so much magic.
We felt all the magic.
And this building glistening in the night as you leave,
wonderful.
I felt the magic back in my hotel room
where I was napping while you all were doing that.
And then I got up and got dressed and went,
think I'm gonna eat chicken guy a second time.
That's Jason's own calendar when we're on vacation.
I'm a wild man, folks.
Jason does his own thing when you're on vacation with him.
I just want to make that clear.
If you ever go on vacation with Jason,
do not expect him to be with you 70% of the time.
Wait, no.
We did a lot of stuff together.
We have done a lot of stuff together.
We all broke off a lot.
Yeah, but I think that you are more than most people
just end up doing your own, you're on your own thing.
Depending on what the vacation is.
Sometimes, yeah, yeah.
Comic Con, I think we're a little bit more together.
Yeah.
There's lines to stand in.
There was lines to stand in, which we like doing.
Well, yeah, that's true.
And Comic Con, if you try to say,
I'll meet up with you later,
that's like the biggest pain in the ass.
It's impossible.
I never saw them again for the rest of my life.
But if I tell Jason, oh, we're going to the wire,
we have a passes to the wire lounge
where you get free little tacos and a free,
what's the T-shirt?
Oh, wait, I have multiple freebie Mr. Mercedes T-shirts.
Mr. Mercedes T-shirts.
Jason got it at the wire lounge multiple times,
which is a, there's all these parties at Comic Con
and some are easier to get into than others.
And this one is like sort of hard to get into,
but not that hard because it's got free stuff in it.
And a couple of years in a row, we went there
and Jason each year got a free Mr. Mercedes T-shirt,
a show I've never seen.
What the hell is Mr. Mercedes?
Okay, Mr. Mercedes was a Stephen King novel
that was turned into a TV show.
I believed for the short-lived,
either AT&T or DirecTV Channel, and now it lives elsewhere.
I think it lives on Peacock or something.
Whatever confusingly named channel has Louder Milk,
which is also confusingly named.
Right.
And they don't explain it.
Their posters were just like, AT&T Network,
what's that, never heard of it,
Mr. Mercedes and Louder Milk.
Then it's a picture of a guy and a picture of another guy.
Why aren't you watching it?
They told you everything you needed to know.
Right, and then there's a picture of Jason with the shirt on,
wearing it to bed, I assume.
Yes.
But yeah, no, we would do that.
But yeah, I feel like on theme park vacations,
we do a lot of stuff, but then yeah,
you're on your own timetable often.
Napping, napping.
Well, we all would have gathered, I think,
previous time to check out some great entertainment
up at the top of the,
we all would have made a point of getting the table,
getting some big plates of ham and rice salad,
some rock candy and gin drinks, and enjoying,
this is a quote from Imagineerding.com
about the former top of the world bar.
Where else could you enjoy roast duck with orange sauce,
veal Romanoff and rose petal salad,
while being entertained by the likes of Carol Lawrence,
Jack Jones, and Phyllis Diller?
Amen, I cannot answer that question.
I don't know where else you could eat literal rose petals
and watch Jack Jones, who I Googled
and is the singer of the love boat theme, apparently.
Which seems like that would have been a guy on your radar.
It does, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, why am I passionate about,
oh, now I'm not gonna produce the name,
the Believe It or Not Joey Scarberry, I wanna say.
Believe it or not, I'm walking on air.
I'll get into Jack Jones, but yeah,
lots of, you know, you can see Sherry Lewis and Lamb Chop.
I mean, God bless her.
Oh, man.
I would have loved to have seen.
Nothing but adults, because it's a bar.
So adults at a bar drink rock candy and watch Lamb Chop.
That's the ad stuff Jason's talking about.
You're getting adults there.
And was Sherry Lewis just doing
her Lamb Chop show for adults?
I don't know if it was a blue Lamb Chop.
I don't know if it was a profanity laden Lamb Chop ad.
Have I talked about seeing Sherry Lewis in person?
I don't think so.
Well, she opened, the first Target in our area
that opened in the mid-90s.
Sherry Lewis and Lamb Chop were at the opening,
and we made a point to go see Sherry on Barrington Road.
Miss Chop.
Miss Chop, we were big Lamb Chop fans in the house,
and we saw her, and really all we did
was stand in the parking lot and saw her
maybe cut her ribbon, I don't know.
She didn't really do a ton.
It wasn't amplified?
My memory is that it was not.
Which is like, oh yeah, I can see the little
red hair lady.
So yeah, we were big Lamb Chop.
My parents are moving, and I was just sent a photo
of the three Lamb Chop puppets that we had as kids.
My mom wanted to throw them away and said they're dirty,
and I said, no way.
You are not throwing these away.
You put those dirty puppets in the trunk
and you drive them out of here.
That's right, so I said, I want those dirty puppets.
Bring me my dirty chops.
Dirty chops, and they're on the way,
so I will get the Lamb Chop puppets to add to my collection.
So then we all have one and we can all do
a funny, a bawdy Lamb Chop nightclub act.
That's right.
Jason, who do you call?
What's that?
I thought they were all Lamb Chop.
No, no, it's Lamb Chop, Hush Puppy, and Charlie Horse
are the three main Lamb Chop characters.
I thought it was three Lamb Chops, okay.
No, no, no, no, three, yes, the three characters.
The big three.
I guess Hush Puppy.
The triumph.
Hush Puppy or Charlie Horse.
The holy trinity of Louis verse.
Yeah, the names I kept coming across, Mel Torme,
I saw mentioned as like doing 10 days or eight days there.
The other.
Sold out for 10 days.
10 nights.
Torme.
Okay, the other name I saw,
I saw people saying Phyllis Diller,
but then I saw like a, you know, events guide
of what was going on at the Contemporary at the time,
and they mentioned Phyllis McGuire,
and I was like, who is Phyllis McGuire?
Phyllis McGuire was part of a three sister group
called the McGuire Sisters.
She only died in 2020.
She was the longest living McGuire Sister,
and I pulled up some of her music on Spotify,
and I just wanna, Margot, can you play
that McGuire Sisters song,
because it's shocking revelation
about where we know this song from.
Interesting.
A couple of pretty gals.
Pizza at suppertime.
When pizza's on a bagel,
you can have pizza anytime.
All right, you can cut it, Mark.
Thank you.
Wow, what a revelation.
What a revelation.
I had no idea the Bagel Bites song
was based on an ancient, old-timey hit.
Wow, did they pay royalties?
I'm assuming they had to pay the McGuire Sisters.
It's a parody song, essentially.
It is a parody song, so maybe they didn't.
Oh yeah, maybe parody law.
You could hear, you could go to the Contemporary Hotel
and hear an un-pizza bagelified version
of the pizza bagel song.
Oh man, you could hear Phyllis McGuire sing that song
in a haze of cigarette smoke.
Wow, that's interesting.
So obviously they were not performing that
after the pizza, they probably stopped performing
many years ago, I assume.
I don't know.
They weren't like 80 years old doing that?
I don't know if they were all alive
when the pizza bagel started.
They didn't get to enjoy pizza bagel mania.
Yeah, they didn't get to go on tour to do the song,
is what I'm saying.
They should have been able to go into the...
Contacting the McGuire estate.
Hey, did any of these wonderful singers
get a chance to sample a pizza bagel?
When they walked God's green earth,
when they were all still around,
did they get God's bounty, that being a pizza bagel?
Also, when they were writing the jingle,
they were like, I can't crack this.
There's no way we can write an original song
about eating pizza on a bagel.
We must take an old song and rewrite it.
Like, I guess it's...
Maybe it was just there was a deadline
and it was like Elton John's candle in the wind
and he was like, let's just rewrite an old one.
And they're like, let's rewrite the old honey
on whatever the hell they were saying.
This could also be a thing where older people would go like,
yeah, you fucking idiot, it's that Sugar song.
Oh yeah, sure.
It was a classic, yeah.
Well, if you're old in the audience
and you know the Sugar song
and that's something that was obvious to you, let us know.
Yeah, also, Margo, could you bring up
that picture label, Jimmy Rogers?
I couldn't find anything on Jimmy Rogers
besides this one old photo.
And this kind of sums up early contemporary,
like the early five. What a wonderful photo that is.
Thickest mustache I've ever seen.
The thickest hair.
Both hair and mustache are three inches deep.
Thickest eyebrows.
That logo on the back wall though
is my favorite thing I've ever seen.
It's a bunch of cascading octagons.
I haven't counted the sides.
From red to yellow.
It goes through all the colors
that were available in the early 70s.
From dark red to lighter red to orange to yellowish orange.
And then there's just a big circle
that looks like a weird Petri dish
made out of carpeting or something.
Like a little like.
Those are all microbes in there.
Microbes or I guess sperm, I'm sorry, apologize.
But yeah, it's so weird the whole image
but it's such a great, I don't know.
It looks like carpeting on the wall.
It's a vibe.
That's a vibe in there for sure.
And world class entertainment.
And you know, Connie Stevens, Vic de Mone.
Those are names that I may have heard before.
I couldn't tell you for sure.
Everybody just, all entertainers around that time.
It was just kind of trust.
That is a name.
That's somebody, right?
Yeah, no it is.
No, for no I ever.
Oh come on, Vic de Mone.
He did, whatever.
I'm not gonna look it up.
It's Vic de Mone.
Vic de Mone sounds like a person that does.
You know Vic de Mone.
If there's somebody named Vic de Mone,
they're a singer and they're a good singer.
Of course.
That's all there is to it.
And they're in the Contemporary.
First 10 sold out shows.
Yeah, this is stuff we've talked about.
Like we're Disneyland and Disney World.
Like it was, I don't know that Vic de Mone
was like the hippest thing in that year.
Like he might have been hipper things going on
in the 70s music wise.
I just guess, but.
So like Woodstock.
Did Woodstock have any effect on the career of.
No, well Vic de Mone, no.
I don't think it was like,
Steven Stills wasn't playing at the top of the Contemporary,
but they were certainly trying to draw a certain crowd
that they're not courting as much anymore.
Well, if you wanted to rock,
there was still a place for you.
And that place is called the Teen Pool.
Unlike other, sometimes kids go to their own pool,
separate from the adults or the adults have their own pool.
The Contemporary, a rare scenario
where teens are cast off have their own pool
because there they can play rock music.
Because it would be too jarring to hear a bunch of bread.
Imagine if you're just a good American Vic de Mone
loving man and then you get blasted by bread.
Ah!
What is this?
Well, you're a kid, look, you might not be ready for this,
but your kids are gonna love it.
Your teens are gonna love it while they're swimming.
Those teens at that Teen Pool are up to no good.
They're smoking cigarettes, unlike us at the adult pool
who are also smoking cigarettes, but it's good when we do it.
They're better cigarettes.
We do it with class.
Yeah.
Also just the Teen Pool just seems like a real
pervert trap.
It's that if you were trying to run a Chris Hansen operation.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, yeah.
We put up a Craigslist ad saying
there was the opening of a Teen Pool.
Hey, half of the top 10 Billboard charts
are over at the Teen Pool
with people they've crossed state lines with.
Oh yeah, the 70s with a Teen Pool
that played rock music, oh my God.
Get every rock and roll artist away from there.
Jesus, I didn't even think about it.
Show us the logs.
Show us the Teen Pool logs, folks.
Who went to the Teen Pool?
There was more wholesome stuff going on for kids to do.
It seems like people were very fond.
If you were a kid who went to the Contemporary,
while your parents went upstairs to swing, to swap keys,
you could stay in the Fiesta Fun Center.
The arcade was kept at the Southwest theme.
The Fiesta Fun Center, which had,
there was a movie theater for just a dollar.
You could see classics like Love Bug,
Mary Poppins, or Song of the South.
Oh good.
Whoops, moving on.
There was also a big shooting gallery
that seemed legit and imagineered.
I mean, Disney building a shooting gallery.
That was gone by the time I went for the first time.
Yeah, well you just had an arcade
and the Southwest of it is gone.
I went in 80, 89 or 90 for the first time.
Yeah, so that was gone.
There also, there was a big mural on the wall
that had representation of the three caballeros
in keeping with the theme.
And the caballeros had girlfriends who were only,
that's the only media in which these three caballero
girlfriends appear.
Yeah, like Chipette caballeros.
Yes.
Of whatever their names are.
Do you have a photo of that?
I don't with me.
Just a note, okay.
Yeah.
We'll find them.
Maybe there's some, yeah, record of like
what those characters' names were.
They just, actually I do have a photo
and they just look exactly like them,
but you know, the way you try to find
just your exact equivalent.
Right, like the Chipettes.
I mean the Chipettes are mirror images of the Chipmunks.
Yeah.
Yeah, that arcade, my memory of the arcade
is basically one thing.
Yeah.
And it's one of the most exciting things ever
as far as Disney World memories,
is they had, and let me find it,
I have the picture with me here,
the only time I have ever seen
the real Ghostbusters arcade game.
Okay, that was not, what's the deal with that?
It was not a common?
I never, I guess not.
That's one of those things as a kid
where you walk in and you go,
this is a complete, like I've never seen this before
and I would never see it again.
I have a similar memory of an arcade
like in another beach town where I was like,
holy shit, what's this Ghostbusters machine?
Never saw it again.
Really, interesting.
Because the same, the only other arcade cabinet
that I've never seen again
was a Bucky O'Hare arcade cabinet.
And that was at the Little Caesars,
which became the Caesar Land,
which is still a topic we need to get into one day
when we can find somebody from corporate
that has the materials.
We don't, this is just nothing to go on.
Because there's very little, as far as
pictures, there's just some people from the Chalmers,
only Little Caesars that was like a Chuck E. Cheese,
essentially.
So yeah, Ghostbusters, I wonder if it was not
widely available, which is crazy
because it was such a popular cartoon and movies.
It could have just been overtaken.
Like they made it when the show was wrapping up.
Maybe. And it's like the Turtles game
and the Simpsons game and the X-Men game
just like overtook.
I guess, but you would think,
Ghostbusters, you know,
did you ever, you played like Simpsons and Turtles,
the main arcade games.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
X-Men was around, whether you played it or not.
But Ghostbusters was, do you ever recall seeing this?
No, no. No.
Yeah, not a common one.
I guess you're saying, yeah.
Once.
So I wonder what happened with it.
So, but that's like, that's almost as powerful
a memory as like going on any of the rides
for the first time.
It's to me.
It's going like, oh my God, Ghostbusters arcade.
Did you not know that the game existed?
No, you didn't know anything.
This is the old, you remember the old days of everything.
Toy wise, like you didn't know what toys were available.
You'd go into Toys R Us and go,
I hope they have Sonic the Hedgehog toys.
I mean, unless you saw a commercial, you wouldn't know.
So when you'd go into a new arcade,
you would find games you never saw before
and it would blow your little mind.
Wow.
So.
So was it great?
I remember it being really fun.
I think it was a side scroller where you would shoot
your proton pack stuff at Ghosts,
which is what a game like that would be.
Yeah.
But my memory was it did live up to it,
but I think I didn't get to spend too much time there.
My parents probably were like,
we should go to Disney World.
The thing we paid for and have been planning to do.
We shouldn't sit here.
For some time.
Although I think maybe timing wise it was bad,
because I did end up beating the X-Men arcade
with some kids because it was broken
and that was at Grand Floridian.
Okay.
So a bunch of strangers and I one night
teamed up to beat Magneto and it was a wonderful moment
and we never saw each other again.
Geez, wow.
And this wasn't immortalized in some kind of Washington
crossing the Delaware type thing.
Not as far as I know.
It is in my mind.
When the heroes stood up to injustice.
Yeah.
Did what was right.
Great moments in Disney World arcade,
or arcade moment, I guess.
Disney World, great Disney World arcade moments,
which I bet a lot of kids have a certain age.
I don't know if kids are still as excited
about arcade games as they are,
or they were when we were kids, but I could be wrong.
Because it's still there.
Arcade is still there.
Do they have tickets now?
Some places have tickets, some places have real cards.
Right, I think they have some sort of
like Chuck E. Cheese style thing there.
I could be wrong.
At the contemporary, I'm not sure.
To redeem.
Let's start, let's get our remaining details that we like
because there's a big thing that we haven't gotten to
and I can only assume it will be the closer.
Yeah.
So toss out anything else.
Can you bring up that concept art picture, Margot?
I had never seen this before.
I think this is early what the contemporary
could have looked like.
It's very different.
Well, is this from, because the idea of this type
of building was in the original Epcot plans,
and I don't mean the park Epcot, I mean the city Epcot.
Like there was this idea of a general building vibe
that I believe was supposed to be a mall.
Like it was the shopping center in Walt's Future City,
which it does continue to have this extremely mall vibe,
which probably speaks to why I dig it.
This looks like part of a city, this art.
This might be Epcot design and this also may have been
when the original name was in play, which I really like.
Tempo Bay.
Tempo Bay is a.
Tempo Bay's a great name.
I maybe would have, I maybe like it more, I don't know.
Tempo Bay.
Do you think it fits?
I mean it fits with a place with lots of young couples
who are looking for new experiences on a vacation
they'll never forget.
Hey, get on my tempo, baby.
Press against my chest and feel my tempo.
Oh God.
I don't think there's anything gross about it.
That's a heartbeat is what I mean.
I said the same thing as you did,
but you saying it made me recoil.
Yeah, Tempo Bay is a cool name.
This looks much more like a Marvel prison or something,
this art.
This looks a lot less inviting, but it is cool.
I'll give this back for a prison.
Avengers.
If you're out there about to build a prison
and you listen to this show.
Yeah, if you're a part of the prison industrial complex
in America and you're looking for fresh, innovative ways
to make some money and build new prisons,
listen to podcast the ride
and then just steal an old Disney concept.
If you're part of the prison industrial complex
and you subscribe to our Patreon,
then we think you're great.
Yes, we're against the prison industrial complex
unless you were paying us $8 a month, then we're on board.
They could build the Marvel super villain
holding pen somewhere.
That would be fun.
That'd be a fun ride.
Yeah.
Everybody gets out and they just use old contemporary,
old Tempo Bay concept art.
Yeah.
Why not?
Tempo Bay.
Margot, will you pull out that matchbook image?
It's a very Jason request.
Pull up the matchbook, please.
This little simplified version of the contemporary
shows up on a lot of stuff.
Oh, yeah.
And it's still used.
Can you switch to the menu too?
They will tile it too.
Oh.
I mean, this looks like the Overlook and the Shining.
Oh, yeah.
God, that'd be great as wallpaper,
as computer wallpaper, anywhere you want it.
Yeah.
So I think-
As a shirt, as a kooky Lasseter shirt.
They did hit on some stuff that it's like,
yeah, this works for a place called the Contemporary.
This is kind of timeless.
Works in a lot of eras.
There was also an era though
where it was unmistakably 80s.
There's a picture 80s contemporary.
And there is an inherent maulness to it,
that it is a big open atrium.
And then look at the-
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
I mean, this is what I see in my dreams.
This is a neon sign in kind of cursive
that says Contemporary Woman.
And then all those pipes up there,
that's what the Space Mountain is like in Tokyo.
This is still there.
I think so.
This gift shop.
And it's pretty much in the same-
I think the pipes are still there too.
Yes, I believe the pipes are.
The lighting is absolutely different,
but the gift shop is still there.
I don't think they're selling the same things.
They're not selling like big thick denim shirts.
I don't, it looks like-
Big cloth flowers for ladies to wear.
They aren't selling like bizarre, a top that's very long.
And the skirt doesn't start until like past your hips.
Right.
Bizarre proportions.
But the last time I was in there,
I remember being like,
oh, where's all the merchandise that says contemporary?
And they're like, we don't have any.
And I went, what?
Yeah. Oh, shit.
Bring back the rock pillows.
Give us something to buy.
Maybe that's different in the last couple years.
But that was a while ago. I also don't think
that you can rent, I believe these,
there was also Contemporary Man
and you could rent tuxedos there.
You walk into a store, it looks like this
and rent a tuxedo.
Oh my gosh.
We would have done that for a show.
Imagine how weird that tuxedo is
and there's probably like a little coke vial
deep in the pocket. Oh, right.
Cause top of the world lounge, the detail, it says,
somewhere it said like jackets required for men.
Like that's, it was a nice place.
So you go rent it from the contemporary for contemporary men.
Potentially go rent it when you're getting
your shipped box of oranges.
The ultimate.
That's a 15 timer.
Well, it's the big thing we're waiting for,
the ultimate 15 timer about the contemporary.
Well, I don't know that we fully addressed it,
but you want, let's get to it.
Let's do it.
Richard Nixon.
Richard Nixon. Richard.
No house, Nixon.
You might know this already,
but this is the contemporary hotel
and the, specifically the adjoining convention center
is where Nixon said, I am not a crook.
That is right.
That is the ultimate little piece of trivia.
That is a good one.
People love that.
Normal people like that.
Yes. That one won't put them to sleep.
Right. You say that to people.
Say it and then stop.
Then don't say anything else that you've heard today.
Yes. Regular folks that don't give a shit
about any of this go, wait, what?
Yeah. It's a thing.
Like every president has a couple of phrases
you can just say, you know,
ask not what your country can do for you.
Tear down this wall.
Like I am not a crook quickly became Richard Dixons.
It would be like, you'd be like, yeah,
did you know when Bill Clinton said
that he didn't have sexual relations with that woman,
that was at Knott's Berry Farm.
You'd be like, what?
He was?
Boysenberry Festival.
Yeah, Boysenberry.
He had some Boysenberry on his shirt if you look.
If you look close, yeah, it was a purple tie
so you couldn't tell that much, luckily.
He planned for that because, you know, he was smart.
Say what you want about the guy, he was smart.
He was smart.
Boysenberry tie.
Sloppy boy, but he was smart.
Read my lips, no taxes, Cedar Farm, George H.W. Bush.
Yeah, it happened.
Another notorious quote, you ever think about
how we are in our lives very often
near where one of the most notorious,
this was probably, I am not a crook,
one of the most notorious until the great presidential quote,
grabbed him by the pussy, that is the NBC studio.
That was mere steps from Jay Leno's Tonight Show studio.
We so often, like I'm getting off the freeway
and pass right by that.
Yes, right where the Billy Bush situation happened.
If you watch the full video, it happens,
they leave the bus and they walk into the building
they're going into and they pass by an old timey car
that is at the entrance of Jay Leno's Tonight Show studio.
This can only be a Jay Leno.
Oh, I never realized that.
Duesenberg or something.
Watch the tape, watch the tape.
Not the part that, that happened
and he still got elected, but if you wanna see
an old Duesenberg, the real point of the tape.
Wow, Jay's car is in the tape?
It is, it's complicit.
If the car had said a big ah-oo-ga,
if Jay had honked his horn at the right time,
it might have startled Trump and Billy
and it wouldn't have happened.
And then he would have gotten elected even more easily.
I was just gonna say there would have been no difference.
What future am I describing?
Yeah, the thing you're describing isn't even
that big of a deal after the fact
that it didn't do anything and he still became president.
As opposed to I'm Not a Crook, which is,
it's not like it hurt him, but it's certainly
like synonymous with the.
Yeah, the whole thing.
The collapse, because it happened
within the year of him stepping down.
Let's say some, all right, so the full picture here.
Sure.
November 17th, 1973, Jason, you were talking about
like what this was, the specific event
that was happening in the convention center.
It was a one hour press conference
with the Associated Press Managing Editors Association.
Now think about that.
What president, after Nixon, is going like,
I'm going to go talk to the Associated Press Editors
for an hour.
Yeah, I mean, only during an hour.
Trump can improvise six.
That's true, yeah.
Sure, no problem.
As long as it's a bunch of hooting and hollering.
Yeah.
He's actively giving COVID to.
That's right.
But he was being asked about making money
in public service and the full quote,
I've earned every cent and in all my years
of public service, I've never obstructed justice.
People have got to know whether or not
their president is a crook.
Well, I am not a crook.
I've earned everything I've got.
Anyway, he said that November 73,
stepped down in August in 1974,
so turned out he was a crook.
He was a crook.
Now this plays into the observation
that I wanted to make about this.
I don't have the clip of it,
but here, you kind of did a Nixon-y thing there.
If I was going to try to do what I think
kind of accurately it was and how he said it,
this is my best attempt.
They've got to know whether or not
their president is a crook.
Well, I'm not a crook.
I've earned everything I've got.
That's maybe kind of a dry.
And then over the years, probably within the year,
but what it's become in pop culture,
and I invite you guys to all do this together.
I think you know where I'm going with it.
Here is what the world has turned the quote into.
Yeah.
I am brother crook.
He does that.
Yes, it's this.
The people think this.
They picture him on.
He's always, it's a priest side.
That's my thing.
It's priest side.
And then I shake on my jowls.
I am not a crook.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Suck it to me.
It's always, I'm not a crook.
Shakers.
This is like, but this happens all the time.
Luke, I am your father, isn't the quote.
Yes, yeah.
These things get changed.
The fact that people so really confidently
and probably to entertain people at a party,
look what I can do.
Luke.
He doesn't say Luke.
No, he doesn't say it.
He says I.
Do you want some more gin and nutmeg special?
But yes, there's no M.
Well, I'm not a crook, but it's.
I am brother crook.
I am not a crook.
I mean, how many times did Rich Little say,
I am not a crook at one of his sold out shows in Las Vegas?
Still, I think.
Still doing it.
As with our episode, it's what he builds to.
The opener and the closer for Rich Little,
I think, at this point.
Some bands open and close with their hit song
and Rich Little, I'm sure does Nixon or Johnny.
He does either Johnny Carson or Nixon first and last.
What if Nixon hosted the Tonight Show?
He absolutely does that.
Nixon was Carnac.
That's actually a little heady maybe for the.
Yeah, too many things.
And it's a little disrespectful
because honestly, Johnny, that's Johnny's show, so.
You know, he was the king.
Nobody ever did it better.
We'd do the golf swing and.
You know what?
Everybody would watch it.
It doesn't matter where you walk life,
you're from, what politics you are.
People love.
Piscopo.
People die mid talking about Johnny Carson all the time.
They're just in the middle of the sentence.
Do the listen.
Okay.
Wait, go ahead.
No, I don't think I'm gonna.
You probably have some funnier thought than I do.
My thought isn't that funny.
I just like, do the listeners know,
do they watch enough interviews with old band
that have this reverence for Johnny Carson?
Do they know even what we're talking about?
That's my question.
That's what you're questioning in this episode?
I'm just wondering.
Once in a while I step out of my body
and I go, wait a minute here.
People tuned in for Mickey Mouse.
And they're like, what is this?
Johnny Carson put off you for 40 years.
I think either you have to not have those moments
or you need to have them 70 times an episode.
That's true.
That's how to proceed.
Today I'm stepping away.
I'm floating above myself.
I'll give you credit.
I think that is a valid question to answer.
I'm just wondering.
I think at a certain point it just became so ubiquitous
if they may have heard it and just tuned it out.
It's just like.
Weird wild stuff.
CNN documentaries or time life compilation commercials
or whatever.
I was gonna ask in 20 years or 30 years
are people gonna be like, oh man,
the thing you gotta remember.
When Corden said he was stepping away,
I mean the music stopped, the car bowl carrier was over.
Everyone gasped when they heard there's not gonna be
another crosswalk dance-a-thon off.
Yeah, I think.
When the Foo Fighters,
because remember there was seven of those guys.
They all fit into one car.
You couldn't believe it.
And the spin-off shows when it would just be celebrities
and they weren't singing their songs.
Who could have thought of that?
Wait, I mean you got Quantico
and then you got Quantico in the field?
Ariana Grande and Seth MacFarlane together
singing Little Shop?
Get out of town.
Hold on.
Wait a minute, they had Arrow and then they had Supergirl
and then you're telling me there's these legends of tomorrow
I gotta know now?
And it really blew people away.
And all these guys knew each other.
The characters all knew each other
and that was revolutionary.
It's gonna happen.
I don't know what you were referencing
with Seth MacFarlane and Ariana Grande.
Well, Scott.
I shouldn't have asked.
Well, there is a spin-off of course.
Carpool Karaoke is not just limited
to the James Corden show.
It is also its own show on Apple TV I believe.
In one of the episodes, Seth MacFarlane is driving
and Ariana Grande is sitting shotgun
and they sing like Sud and Les Seymour.
And Les Seymour.
Yeah, and they sing it together.
Wait, no spoilers.
Well, they have the plant, there's like a plant.
Big reveal in season two.
Plant in the backseat I think.
You're either gonna sing Little Shop of Horrors
like the girl group does
or you're gonna sing Sun Les Seymour.
If you're talking Little Shop
and you gotta condense it to a show.
I've been reading interviews with Seth MacFarlane
talking about the state of musicals these days.
And I do wonder Jason, if you concur with his feeling.
He feels like we're really not in a good spot musical wise.
He believes like Rodgers and Hammerstein.
Like that's the top of the level.
And we still, the songwriting is not there
as far as the last couple of decades of musicals.
Yeah, I mean, I think, yeah, I don't know.
There's some good ones, there's some bad ones.
I did like watching the Tonys.
I was kind of like, yeah, I don't know any.
There's some stuff where it feels like there's musical
the speed run, like quick where you can just have someone go
something is going to happen.
That's all you have to do.
But he's saying the best stuff is still in the past
and we have to get back to more traditional songwriting.
It certainly seems like the Broadway and the West End,
the way they book stuff,
it is just like a lot of the same stuff comes up.
Scott, do you have an opinion about this?
I think it's interesting that Jason's just earnestly
answering Seth MacFarlane's question through you.
I'd love to get, you know, get back to fourth grade.
That's a pretty interesting point.
Let's get Seth on and talk about it.
And only that.
Yep.
Okay, here's a Nixon thing I found out.
Do you know what might have brought him
to the Florida area?
Oh, actually I don't.
Why did this thing happen here and why did he go there?
He was fresh from a vacation because he,
much like Trump, had a Florida White House.
He had a place where he went like 50 times
during the presidency.
And this was three and a half hours south
in Key Biscayne, Florida.
Beachfront property.
He got it really cheap from like mob hookups
and Jimmy Hoffa affiliated people.
And he was in a neighborhood of like other crooks,
including, he was really good friends.
Nixon's Florida neighbor was a guy named Robert Abplanalp.
One of the most complicated names I've ever seen.
Robert Abplanalp, who was the inventor
of aerosol spray can tops.
Wow.
And that made him enough money to be Nixon's neighbor
in Florida.
And in fact, so okay, this is 73, I'm not a crook.
Oh wait, oh, this would have been the beginning, I'm sorry.
When the Watergate break-in became a story
and leaked to the press, where was Nixon?
As it broke, Nixon was on Robert Abplanalp's private island
in the Bahamas called Walker's Cay.
The air, not Moosha Cay.
Not Moosha Cay, which is what I'm saying.
So like, there's a lot of notorious Cays at this point.
Yeah, really.
There's Fire Festival Cay.
There's David Copperfield Monkey Cay.
Now we know there's Watergate aerosol spray can Nixon Cay.
I wonder if it's still in the family.
I don't know.
That's an interesting question.
Is it still owned by the Abplanalps?
I think it may have been slowly desiccated by hurricanes,
which is the fate of a lot of these Cays.
But anyway, it could be a future ordeal
is stepping through every Cay.
All the Cays, yeah.
And discovering how many crimes
and which crimes every Cay is associated with.
All the crimes.
By the way, usually pronounced key, C-A-Y, key.
Like the Florida Keys.
But sometimes spelled K.
Yeah.
Did I say it right or wrong?
So you're saying it should be,
actually we've been calling it Moosha Cay this whole time.
It should be Moosha Key.
Yeah, I only learned this recently.
A lot of times pronounced key in that area.
Interesting.
Moosha Key.
I'm not 100% on which is and is not pronounced key.
Well, people have been confused now.
They always knew Moosha Key is David Copperfield's
private island that had monkey butlers or whatever.
Keys or Cays?
I don't know.
I don't know either.
I don't know if it's a key or a Cay.
And anyway, so that's the,
wait, there was something else.
So he was down there.
And that property in Florida had a helipad
that was built by the Department of Defense.
So America paid for Nixon to have a helipad.
And then he sold the property and made a profit on it.
So that's iffy, right, to sell the helipad
that the government built.
And it looks so Florida shady and criminal
that this property was used in both Miami Vice
and Scarface.
Great.
The place where Nixon used to live.
And I assume Nixon associate G. Gordon-Lytte
was on a Miami Vice episode, I think,
because he was a celebrity.
Oh, okay.
G. Gordon-Lytte did the break in.
Got the acting bug.
Yeah, and he, you know, there's a,
I was gonna say great, I don't know, it's great.
But there's a Conan O'Brien with Conan,
Don Rickles, and G. Gordon-Lytte.
I don't know if you've ever seen that.
No, no.
But G. Gordon-Lytte was a crazy person
that got put in prison for the break in.
But worth investigating for many reasons
because he became a celebrity, had his own radio show.
Al Franken always bragged about being friends with him.
Al Franken, you'd be like, I am friends with G.
We call him G.
What?
That's what we call him.
I swear to God, he'd always talk about this
when I was listening to the Al Franken show in college
on Air America.
The clues have always been there
of your ability to stomach hours worth of.
Oh yeah, I would listen to all of Air America
when I was around.
People you disagree with.
Well, I always, I mean, the SNL connection with Al
was a good line into politics.
A good straight line into, I guess I'll listen to Al
talk about G. Gordon-Lytte for an hour and a half in college.
I guess I could have done,
been doing better things with my time.
But we've talked about before the G. Gordon-Lytte calendar
of women in bathing suits holding guns.
We have, on this show we've talked about that.
I think we have, Jason, you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, we have talked about that.
I mean, nowadays those people are just congressmen, so.
Yeah, yeah, no, it's not so, G. Gordon-Lytte
seemed like a sort of a freak show at the time,
but now it's just, everyone's like that.
But anyway, I've lost the, G. Gordon-Lytte
was on Miami Vice and shows like that.
I don't know that he was on that show specifically.
Johnny Carson reference audience might be at G. Gordon-Lytte.
I was back in my brain.
That's what I'm saying, keep it that way.
Zip it up.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
Just keep it, don't even.
You're right.
You'll only freak yourself out.
If you look at the whole picture.
They're all getting, everyone's getting ready for this,
for the Plumbers, for that new Prestige mini series
coming up about Watergate.
So they're gonna be talking about, is it out?
The Julia Roberts one.
No, that's Gaslit, isn't it?
Oh yeah, yeah, but that's out now.
But that has that one guy playing G. Gordon-Lytte.
Okay, so there's Lydie in the air.
Lydie is back in the zeitgeist.
We're getting our lids blown off.
The man passed away a few years ago at like 100.
Which is, of course that guy got to live to 100.
But yeah, yeah, Lydie is in the zeitgeist.
He's around.
I believe you.
I believe both of you, it's Lydie Mayne out there.
There are a lot of weird, it's so weird
that people were like, yeah, he's a celebrity now.
Isn't it fun?
Well, it was, cause look,
Watergate was hot.
Nixon made it hot with great catchphrases like this.
And there's one more observation I have about this,
which is that if he was at the Contemporary,
and I think he was in and out,
I think he did that hour, got grilled, and then he left.
He did not use the Contemporary
in its vacation kingdom amenities.
But this was the first scenario of a president
being very near his own robot in the Hall of Prejudice.
Oh, very good point.
Very good point.
He was the first sitting president when that was built.
And I don't think he went into the park,
but he was within a mile.
He could have taken a 15 minute walk
and been with his own robot,
which is something I wonder about all of the presidents.
Do they ever think about what's up with their robot?
Do they ever ask, can I go check out my robot?
Or are they over it, cause they're the president?
Of course there's a robot of me.
Yeah, I mean there was Reagan, what do we have?
Reagan was in Epcot.
There's footage of Reagan in Epcot, I believe.
Nixon at Epcot too.
Nixon at Epcot.
Yeah, but Reagan gave a speech at the.
Was Clinton at Epcot too?
Clinton was at the Disney Institute for some reason.
Carter, I looked this up, sitting presidents at Disney World.
Carter and Obama both did speeches in front of the castle.
But I don't know, so they were the closest.
So I don't know if they ever took the stroll.
You would think they would wanna get that photo.
Disney would have always wanted to get that photo up
with the robot and the president.
They still haven't done, I mean now I get it
why they're trying to like, they're not publicizing
the Hall of Presidents anymore, really.
That's not like at the front of the pamphlets
to go to Disney World.
It might have been in the past.
Yeah, they're bringing the parasailors back.
Yeah, the parasailors front and center.
By the way also you can go see Cheer-Boo
depending on what your preference is.
I'm just saying, if there was a robot of me somewhere,
I would just see it.
I would be there every day.
I would hammer around with it.
Yeah, yeah.
You put your arm around it.
You do the photo with like, hey, how you doing?
And maybe, maybe if nobody's looking
or if people are looking, you give a little kiss.
Yes, I would kiss my robot.
You would kiss your robot every day.
How often would you kiss your robot?
Probably twice a day.
Twice a day, up in the stakes.
I mean I'd ask the Imagineer to make sure
that it wasn't gonna like, like the oil wouldn't get on me
or it wouldn't spark.
I would like to think that they don't have a bunch
of oil at the ready at their lips.
Yeah, but don't you think the oil's leaking
in the pores of the rubber, of the face skin rubber?
Could be.
It would be an exciting day
if you were watching the Hall of Presidents
and then one of them, and then James Polk started just
black biling, like as if he had like an alien
about to burst through his chest.
Oh yes, Penguin, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Because you would think, because it has to be lubricated
because the rubber on the face is moving so much.
It has to be some level of lubrication, I would think.
But we don't know if it's black or if it's clear.
We don't know if it could be clear.
We don't know how the presidents are lubricated.
That's true.
I would guess it's probably clear.
That would make sense.
I would think, because it would start exploding.
It should be red, I mean.
Sure.
Because if something goes wrong,
at least you got an interesting show.
Are there less fluids now with the electronic ones
that aren't hydraulic, because they're not hydraulic anymore
than newer ones.
That's a good question.
I mean, you still have to, I don't know, by the way,
anything I'm talking about, you still have to get
big pieces of rubber that get moved, changed out
because they get worn out.
So they still have to move.
So I don't know, maybe not.
I'm not sure. Send the face.
Send the face to the flea market.
We're done with this one.
I told you when I went to D23, like in 2017,
they showed, in the Imagineering section,
there was this giant mater mouth from the Cars ride.
Just the rubber from his mouth that moves,
that has to be changed every couple months or something
because it gets worn out.
And it was crazy.
And I was like, oh yeah, everyone's face has to be replaced.
Everyone has to have new rubber faces, I think.
If they do want to get rid of the Hall of Presidents,
just go all out and pump tons of red hydraulic fluid.
Don't say that it's going to happen,
but just go out with a viral event.
Kill the presidents off is what you're saying
in a blaze of glory instead of just quietly shutting it down,
which is what I think will happen eventually.
Reservoir dogs just blow out.
They all dot, like weaken their knees,
program them all to just collapse.
Give us a show.
And red pours out of them.
And program screams.
Get acu...
I'll do it.
I'll give you as many...
What do you think Franklin Pierce would have screamed like?
Ah!
I'll try to do 46 different screams.
And then some of this kid lighten off fireworks in there.
Some kid gets some Florida fireworks
and he's just in the background,
lighten them off while this whole spectacle's going down.
And then that'll be the big deal.
You could sell it as a ticketed event,
the final hall of presidents,
and then build Jason's sleepy hollow ride
that he keeps talking about.
That's a five timers at this point.
Even though it was a real blue sky.
Yeah.
You brought it up this time.
That's true.
Yeah.
It can be, we all share the times.
We all share the times.
Okay, final thoughts about Contemporary,
which we wanted to sink down.
I love it.
Yeah, I mean, getting off, we didn't even say like...
It's so comforting having it in front of me.
I could just sit and describe sitting on the monorail
and going into the station.
And the warm memories I have
of just stepping on the carpeting,
feeling the air conditioning in there.
These are some of the most pleasant memories I have
from the first 18 years of my life.
There's something about,
there was nothing like stepping out inside the hotel
and the feeling you got when you would do it.
It's the most sincere I've ever been on the podcast.
It's the best.
Truly, and I still feel that way.
I'm not sure if it's for sure tied to nostalgia,
but I do wonder if you were an adult and you've never been,
if you still have this kind of feeling of like,
whoa, this is awesome.
Yeah.
Scott, do you know about the...
The Top of the World Lounge is what they started to call
at the top of Bay Lake Tower.
That's the DVC only.
I tried to go, we couldn't go
because we had just booked the room.
It was only for DVC members.
And now it is called Top of the World Lounge,
M-Dash, a Villain's Lair.
No, I don't know about that.
Because it's got villain themed drinks and snacks and stuff.
Oh, I like that.
There were guys, I don't know if this was permanent or what,
but there were actors, improv actors walking around.
As if it was a Villain's Night Off.
What villains? Who was there?
You know, the Kang, the crew.
Maybe?
Maybe Hades?
But I think they were more Disney-bounded dressed.
They were more like, they were doing bits and all.
Interesting.
Oh, okay.
You can hang with villains there?
I like that they...
Was there anyone named Vic singing?
Vic?
Vic.
Vic de Mone.
Vic de Mone, yeah.
Remember?
From earlier.
Vic from earlier.
Vic de Mone.
Oh, and Vic de Mone.
I have lost track of the old time,
we said so many old timey singer names.
Vic Jason did that.
And I was back thinking,
does everyone on these blogs mean Phyllis McGuire
when they keep saying Phyllis Diller?
Another gotcha moment from Michael to Jason.
The gotcha press has added again.
Can we, Marco, can we just pull up,
it's just called, I think it's just 70s contemporary.
Can we just look at a nice photo here as we,
cause this is the, I mean, look at that just twinkling.
Oh yeah.
It's early Disney World's dusk.
A glow inside, severe on the outside,
but warm and glowing on the inside.
And to pull up in the monorail,
like such comfort, such great then modern technology.
I mean, it's a beautiful place, a calming place.
Yeah, it is, I mean, everything is so expensive,
but you can still, right,
you can just get on the monorail still, yes?
Yeah.
Yes, so I just like, if you're like,
ah, Disney's too expensive,
a big pain in the ass right now,
get on that monorail and take it in at dusk.
Drive over there.
Do it, go get something in the lobby.
You can go to Mickey,
we didn't even talk about Mickey's Kitchen.
It's a great show, it's where I got kissed.
What?
I got kissed by Minnie at the buffet,
at the character buffet, yeah.
I have a picture of it.
It's on my Instagram.
I have a picture.
Well, you got it, all right, we'll tweet that out.
I was trying to go out on like a nice idyllic image here,
but you have-
I was kissed by Minnie Mouse.
Much more of one.
The contemporary, that has nothing to do
with my affection for the place though, I swear to you.
It's a nice thing, it's good, I liked it.
You aren't just recalling, you hated it.
You would have done a negative,
like looks like shit stained on the outside,
the 70s relic, what a garbage place
is what you would have said
until this magical kiss happened.
Yep, and the performer made the smooch sound.
That's the important thing,
is that the person inside the suit made that noise.
Can you add, can you do a Nixon
and then add a smooch to the end of it?
Would you- The time hole episode.
Real Nixon or the caricature?
Whatever way you wanna go with it.
Hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr, hurr,
I am not a crook, mwah.
Beautiful. Perfect.
And that's the entire history of the contemporary,
condensed, what a wonderful place, so fun to talk about it.
You survived podcast, The Ride.
You can find us on the socials at podcast the ride.
I assume there'll be a photo of a mini mid-kiss
or just in the general vicinity of when it happened.
I believe she's got her snoot on my head.
I think so, I'm looking, trying to find it.
Oh yeah, here it is.
I mean, take a look.
This is for the sheepish face that you're-
Well, because I didn't really-
Well, well. Believe it or not,
I didn't really want the performer to kiss me
getting rid of the kayfabe of the podcast.
She also isn't, it's a little false nose.
But she didn't turn sideways with her mouse mouth
and go like, woo.
So you didn't want it, is what your reality.
No, I was sheepish.
This photo, I look sheepish
because the performers shoving their plastic nose
on my face when they block.
Get it in front of, put it in front of my camera.
You have mouthful of eggs Benedict during this.
Gee, I don't know.
Do I look like a little stinker?
Do I look like a little stinker in that photo?
Yes.
What's the caption also?
I said, they're not allowed to talk,
but they are allowed to make a loud kiss sound effect.
That's what I wrote.
May 9th, 2013.
Who knew?
You'd be talking about it for years.
A snoot you'd never forget.
That's true.
Merch is available in our T-Public store.
Perhaps a shirt that says a snoot you'll never forget.
And for three bonus episodes every month,
check out podcast the ride the second gate
at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
You can also get one more bonus episode
on our new tier club three,
where I believe by now we will have the results
of the audience requesting to have Eva Anderson
talk about whatever she wants.
Do you wanna know how that panned out and what it was?
Oh, and you know what, Eva gave us postcards.
Oh yeah.
Marco, can you pull up that image?
I took a screenshot of it to put it on the screen.
It's the one last image.
This is the most contemporary,
we got presents in this episode with Eva.
Why did we get them?
What did we do to deserve them?
Oh, you'll have to go to club three to find out.
Beautiful.
Both garden wings.
What an ending.
Oh, I didn't realize, I thought you were still going.
Both garden wings.
Ended in a fifth turn.
That's gonna be our send off from now on.
Jason yelling both garden wings.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehme,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.