Club Three.
Okay, it's Club Three, you know who we are,
let's fucking go.
We have time, no introductions here,
although I should let Mike and Jason,
you should say something.
No, I don't give a shit.
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No time to go.
Club Three.
We gotta dive in.
There is one introduction to give, however,
and that is just to lift up and celebrate the winner
of our first, we didn't know that people could be chosen
as winners of this, but we threw it out to the audience.
What do you want as a Club Three topic
and the first thing chosen,
very clearly landslide was suggested by Ben Hicks.
Just let Eva come on and talk about whatever obscure,
insane pop culture things she wants.
So here to do exactly that, Eva Anderson, hi.
Oh, thank you, I wanna congratulate Ben Hicks
and the Club Three listeners for their intelligence,
emotional intelligence and foresight
in knowing that obviously I should win this.
There was only one way to go on this
and before we dig in and give the floor to you,
there was a runner up that I thought was pretty worthy.
The runner up, this is from JF Co.
They're suggesting, quote,
the original crypto Disney dollars.
Ooh.
Great idea, was a very solid number two,
got way ahead of the pack,
but obviously Eva was the winner.
Here's how this is going to work in future months
because we'll ask you for your suggestions
for Club Three topics below.
If you're on Patreon, just list them below this episode.
The runner up's always gonna get another go.
So number two always advances to the next round.
That is their consolation prize.
So Disney dollars will get another chance,
but will there be a more exciting topic?
We will see.
There will be four more chosen.
Give us your ideas and also,
if you're looking at other people's ideas,
click like on those things.
Put hearts on it so we know that's what
you're excited about.
So get in those comments and let us know
what you wanna hear in August.
But for right now, Eva's here.
You presented a number of ideas.
This was no draconian.
You made a demand of us.
You gave us agency in this discussion and we appreciate it.
But are you happy with where things land?
Are you secretly pining for one of the other topics
or would you like to throw anything out there
as, well, I would like to do this at some point?
No, I mean, I feel like we had
a really interesting discussion.
I threw a lot of stuff at you guys.
There was some weird celebrity auctions coming up.
There was a very bad sounding immersive play
that I was gonna maybe force you to go to.
There was talk about you kidnapping us,
which I'm assuming would be like,
you pick us up from a location in your car
and you take us somewhere without telling us.
I think it might've been this immersive play
that I was reading about.
Probably the immersive play.
Any details about the immersive play?
I don't remember that one, no.
It was called Club Babaloo.
Oh, that was good.
Wait a minute, I thought Club Babaloo
was more of a themed bar rest.
I keep getting hands for Club Babaloo.
I know, I mean, I was getting ads for it.
I was like, maybe we should all,
I mean, we could still go to Club Babaloo, you guys.
Is Club Babaloo the haunted tiki bar?
No. The horror tiki bar?
Think about the name.
What else could the name be, Jason?
I don't know.
I've gotten so many, like, it's a tiki bar, but it's haunted.
It's a tiki bar, but it's sci-fi.
I just keep getting fed these.
This is like a show.
It's like a burlesque show, I think,
but you're backstage at a 50s sitcom or something.
And it seems like there's a lot of actors who are like,
well, I don't know.
And I don't know.
It's like, there's like,
you could get a special table with like a sandwich.
They bring you like a sandwich,
but the sandwiches all look like pre-wrapped,
kind of like 7-Eleven sandwiches.
I have not been to this, but I was like,
man, this could be real rough.
Yeah.
Because Club Babaloo is the name of Ricky Ricardo's club
that he starts on, I Love Lucy,
after he leaves the Tropicana.
This seems like it had some I Love Lucy crossovers.
Yeah.
The other thing I suggested was possibly,
and I don't want to like blow too many ideas out,
but like some of the Buena Park entertainment district.
Yeah.
Sure.
Places that you guys have never touched.
There's the potential for a mini saga
just in going down Beach Boulevard and hitting all of the,
cause there's a lot.
Right.
We've never done Medieval Times.
We did Pirates of the Intervention,
but we haven't done the burlesque body.
Teatite version.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Teatro Martini.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, Teatro Martini.
You did Teatro Martini?
I did not do Teatro Martini,
but I'm sad to say I believe Teatro Martini has closed.
What?
Oh, man.
I think maybe there's another show
or maybe it never came back.
I will look into it.
I'm not a hundred percent on this,
but I feel like there has been some developments.
Will you please announce the right way
that Teatro Martini has been closed,
that it's been compromised to a permanent end.
Teatro Martini has been compromised to a permanent end.
And the rings, the long sheet
that someone was spinning off of on the roof
just ripped and the whole cast fell down.
Yeah.
Fell ten stories onto a hardwood floor.
They can't all hang on it at once.
They were asking for trouble.
Well, that, you know.
This was never an option,
but I was texting Eva separately
about this weird thing called Elro a couple weeks ago,
which are like themed raves.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, those look really cool.
There's like a Navi themed rave.
It's in Vegas, right?
Monkey pox super spreader event.
Navi avatar themed rave.
It's really funny how any text I get from any of you guys,
like really quickly devolved to like, I would do this.
I think I would do this.
I think we would, well, I would do this, yeah.
There's a lot of daring going on,
which comes up in this episode, I would say.
I mean, that's really the whole endeavor here,
but you gave, I guess,
what you landed on the official dare for today's topic.
So would you like to give in the prompts,
let Eva do whatever she wants?
What are we talking about today?
We are talking about a thing that's very specific
to the West Coast, it turns out, themed car washes.
Yeah.
Themed car washes.
It's a thing I discovered during COVID by accident
when I was driving around the South Bay.
And I just thought about it every day for years.
And so I decided, what I presented to you
is that we all go to a different themed car wash
and report back on our experience.
Yay.
And you guys, we did it, right?
We did it, yes.
And we legitimately don't know anyone's results.
Yeah.
So there'll be a lot of surprise for each other
and for the listeners.
What a blat.
This is a great assignment and a great discovery.
I truly did not know this area whatsoever.
Did anybody, have you guys ever stumbled upon
themed car washes out in the wild?
I mean, not seen, there's one in Burbank
that has a crazy, I don't know if it's googie architecture.
It just has a lot of ornate metalwork.
It looks very much like it's been there since the 50s.
There's one on Ventura Boulevard that's just hand car wash
and it just has a giant grotesque hand statue outside.
Yes.
With these horrible hands.
Which that's great.
That's like a Valley perennial item.
And that's what I love about this area in general
is that it feels very, cars are new.
How do we get people to our thing?
Well, we have to put like a big dumb item
or we have to shape our building
like a basketball or whatever.
It feels like such a 60s or even like a route 66
kind of thing.
But a lot of these are new.
I think the one that you ran into
that I think other people did,
that it's an entire chain of them.
And I think they're pretty new.
This isn't like some 50s thing.
This is in the last decade or so.
Yeah, they're a new but rapidly decaying company.
The same way Joe roadie made Animal Kingdom
to look like it was falling apart.
It feels like the same type of imagineering was going on.
That sort of care to detail has been put in these.
I mean, it is fun to add a little bit of
not Disney level theming,
but like miniature golf course level theming
into a daily errand.
Yes, yeah.
I want those everywhere.
I mean, this certainly relates to my love
of Fry's Electronics.
So people have really talked up these regional grocery chains
that have animatronics or weird little shows or what.
I mean, this is what I want out of any business.
I want it out of banks,
just any like borough out of like loan place.
I want it out of anywhere that you have to go.
You want a pre-show video before you go into any business.
Yes, yeah.
I agree.
Give me a little show.
Give me something to laugh at.
Educate me.
My wallet will open up wide
if you give me a little bit of entertainment.
Like that's more fun.
That's more fun than some of the banks
have like coffee bars in them now.
I remember there was one.
The Capital One Cafe.
Well, the Capital One Cafe is one,
but there was another one, I think it was a Chase
that Jane went into once
and they had gotten rid of all the tellers.
But there was coffee available and she went,
can I get a roll of quarters?
And they said, we don't do that here.
No quarters, no tellers set up,
but there is some probably awful coffee.
That's weird.
So you only go into like take out a loan or something?
Like what is this bank for?
I guess there's an ATM and you can get a macchiato.
I mean, I know the Capital One Cafe.
I haven't tried it yet.
There's one by the Americano where the coffee is discounted
if I pay with my Capital One credit card.
Haven't you not been there?
I know.
Is this automatically added to the Club Three
Votable Topics for next week?
Oh, maybe.
For Capital One Cafe, I've been to Capital One Cafe.
Julia Prescott and I went there at a nice time.
Yeah, absolutely.
But I like, I mean, I do like Bank Mask.
There was a chain, Commerce Bank,
which I think eventually got absorbed
into the Wells Fargo system.
And they just had a very specific C logo.
And I think there was a walk around C?
A big C?
Like it's a big ornate C?
Okay, that's in there too.
I gotta find it.
They were definitely Bank C.
They got a lot of mileage out of that big C.
And I'm like, I'm pretty sure there was a walk around C.
That feels like a punishment
for the opposite of employee of the month.
You would have to slide into that C.
It would be really uncomfortable.
Yeah, your body's at like a weird scoliosis position.
Create an impossible yoga pose.
You have to walk around in for an hour.
It's a torture.
I would love if all of next month's suggestions
came from this episode.
If we can manage to produce enough.
Oh wow.
That's two right there.
But we also, we gotta leave it up to listeners.
Yeah, I mean, even one of your suggestions
was just like an interesting looking swap meet, I think.
Oh yeah.
A swap meet with a bakery
or some sort of like Pennsylvania touch.
Is it the one that's like east of, let me.
And then there was a motel with constructed teepees.
The Wigwon Motel.
The Wigwon Motel where it's like,
we might get murdered if we could have.
Oh, in San Bernardino.
Yeah, there's like a whole, there's a whole Route 66,
like just weird, bunch of weirdness
that you could experience
if you guys really wanted to take a road trip.
I mean, it's a road for, it's a car, it's for cars.
It's just supposed to delight and enchant you.
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I love about what we're doing here.
It's kind of like car entertainment.
Why leave it in the past?
I also, okay, so just thing one about any car
or even a non-themed car wash,
I don't wanna speak for everybody,
but I really enjoy and have always really enjoyed
driving into the car wash
and the little show happening around you
of your car being cleaned.
Sitting in the drive-through, that is great.
That is like a little ride, I think.
When I was a kid, when I learned
that was a thing you could do the first time I died,
oh my God, I lit it.
That's like a, that's a little like 45 second Disneyland
in your neighborhood, right there.
Oh man, yeah.
Early days of the pandemic, I was like,
I think this is a safe activity I can do.
Go to the drive-through Shell car wash.
Yeah.
But you weren't sure, exactly.
No one was sure, but there was a lot of people there.
I was not the only one who had that idea, so.
Oh man, I just watched, I just went to the,
the American Cinematheque is doing a
like depressing movies series they just wrapped up
called Bleak Week.
And they showed Adam McGuynes, the sweet hereafter.
Anyway, the opening of that movie,
which is about a school bus going through the ice
and everyone drowning,
is Ian Holm getting stuck in a drive-through car wash.
Oh wow.
And having to get out of his car and walk through it
cause nobody is like manning the car wash.
And it's really, it's really triggering and crazy.
It's like a thing you never think about.
What if the car washes stop going?
I think about it.
Oh you do?
Well you can see Bill Bo Baggins himself have to,
looks like get shot in the face with the hoses and stuff.
That also, that happens in other very moving,
affecting scene in an affecting film, The Country Bears.
Yes it does.
Country Bears is one of the most extended people.
Diedrich Bader is running around,
and he's stuck in a car wash.
Their hair gets crazy.
Their hair gets so crazy.
Wait.
Did that stress you out?
So Mike, hold on.
I just want to confirm.
You have worried about being in the middle of it
and getting stuck and you have to walk out.
Or just like, or like,
I think that happens in A Final Destination.
I have worried like, oh what if like this thing
kind of like breaks or something and like smashes the window?
Oh, it comes through the window and the,
like something.
The big rolly brush like takes your head off.
Cause it is impressive.
Like it is like a big machine.
You're in a big like machine and machines break sometimes.
See I have had the opposite.
I've had a fan, like not a.
A fantasy of like,
what if I could walk through a car wash
and then I get it all.
Like cause that.
That's a different.
Okay.
I hear, I think I've thought that before.
I don't know if I ever described it as a fantasy.
I didn't say an erotic fantasy.
I just said a fantasy.
You did now.
I think, well I think there was a lot of water parks grow.
There would be like a play area where it's like,
oh, it's like you're walking through a car wash.
Isn't that funny?
And I was like, oh yeah, that would be fun.
Okay. Yeah.
So it's not like a foam fetish or something.
No, no.
Getting nice and sexy.
I would like to get brushed with a big brush though.
I just like put my arms up and turn in a circle.
It's like.
It'd be like a double dare.
Yeah. That feels better to me.
Being in the car is the thing that's scary.
Cause you're trapped in the car.
Oh, and it can be like a,
what if we came like a car compactor
and the car got smaller and smaller.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
Secret car compactor.
Yeah.
And then you're in the cube.
Right.
Like a top secret.
Is that happening top secret or,
or is there a naked gun where that happens to somebody?
Possibly.
I feel like there's one eighties movie where a guy gets like
packed into a car and then he's walking around
and the car's on him.
That's funny. Yeah.
A little cube walking around with arms.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's not, that's not how I pictured it going wrong.
I didn't think.
Well now you can add that to your list of things.
Maybe I will think about that.
And just, this might bear mentioning that,
you guys are, I think this might be in the Imagineering
story, that Tony Baxter mentions the drive through car
washes as an influence on the finale of the Indiana Jones
adventure.
Whoa.
That's what gave him the idea because you get that odd
little feeling when it's like the mood,
the room is moving around you and you can,
I do it every time I go like,
oh wait, did the car start moving?
Oh God. Yeah.
No, it's just that you're surrounded by walls and the walls
are moving, which is what happens.
I didn't, honestly, I,
I've been underselling how I don't think I realized what was
really happening in the boulder scene of Indiana Jones
adventure, where it's massive wall, all the cave walls.
Oh yeah.
And the boulder does not move.
It like, I stare at the diagram for a while to even get it.
That's one of those things where I've heard that explanation
and I still, when I'm on it, I don't get it.
I don't understand.
Like it doesn't, I still am like,
the boulder is coming at me though.
Well it's so dark.
I heard what he said.
It's so pitch black around you.
Right.
I love that part of-
The boulder that you can watch night vision POVs
of the ride that kind of show you.
Like that's a way to see through the mystery a little bit.
But hey, if this, if it's good enough for Tony Baxter,
then it's good enough for us.
Yeah.
And we all went and had various thrills in the world of
themed car washes.
I, where do we, where do we start?
Anybody want to dive in?
Well, I believe Mike, you did the OG
and I feel like maybe you should start.
Sure.
Mine is of course the green forest car wash.
Is that the first one?
And is that, is that the entire brand is green forest?
Yes.
But they have the, which theme of green forest did you?
The jungle.
You did jungle.
Yeah.
Which is in Hawthorne.
It's in Hawthorne, California.
All of these are in the South Bay.
So none of them are near where we live, except for Eva.
So it was, it was a little expedition for everybody.
Definitely.
Right.
So I just, to give you a little, the listener,
a little understanding of what a day was like.
Scott and I went to see a concert for babies,
Chuck E. Cheese live.
Same day.
She's on the pier.
And then I ate a tuna melt and then I drove to Hawthorne
to get my car washed.
So I missed the turn to get there
and I ended up in a target and.
You sighed, you crashed in.
Yeah, I blew, I crashed my car into a target.
And then I went to this jungle themed car wash.
The line was long.
Ooh.
People were.
It's a Saturday.
It was a Saturday.
I tried to turn left in there,
but there were so many cars backing up the street,
turning in right that I went around.
Cause I was like, it just, like not a good situation
to be putting my car in.
So I turned around, I turned,
I made like a U-turn at a certain point safely.
And I got in line for the cars and it took like 10 minutes
to get in there, to like pay before I started
getting the wash.
So you're immediately like there's the graphics everywhere
are like graphics you would see in some sort of like auto
store.
If that makes like here, let me show you what I'm,
I don't know that I even I'm describing them correctly.
Like this is enter.
They look like decals, like big,
like sticker decals that you could put.
The jungle theme is not evident in what you're showing us.
Well, right.
But it is evident in the different tiers
of car wash you can buy.
So the, I would say the graphic design is a little tacky.
Would that be fair to say, I mean,
I don't know what your experience is,
but it's a little bit tacky.
It looks, I don't know.
I guess I'm being a little snooty.
They gotta attract you to the different deals
and price ups.
Right.
So there are three options at this point.
Okay.
So there are two like drive through lanes essentially.
And that's where you pay for the car wash.
And again, they were both packed
and it took me a little bit to get in there.
So there are three tiers.
Lowest is jungle.
Second, the middle one is bubble Kano
and the highest is volcano.
Vol is better than volcano.
I'm not sure.
Yes.
Does volcano at your location come
with a free towel or air freshener?
Whoa.
No.
So this is only some of them.
Because you also went to a green forest.
You went to one within the family.
Yes.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah.
So no, I did not get anything for free, but so, so yeah.
Do you want me, I'll read what it comes with.
Yes, sure.
Okay. Well, we need to do a thorough investigation of this.
What level did you go for?
Volcano.
I did too.
Yeah. I think at that point, yeah, just go all out.
Turbo day, turbo day.
I don't know.
So you get turbo day with it.
Wheels cleaned, foam bath, clear coat polish,
the shine rain shields.
And they're all like kind of sort of icon graphics
to describe what these things are,
but I still don't really know.
And then it just says premium car wash.
So, okay.
So what I thought was interesting here is that
there are single prices
and there are monthly unlimited prices.
So you can get like a monthly pass.
There's a magic key program.
There's a magic key program for the car washes.
And it's only like double the price of a single car wash.
Yeah.
So did you do it?
If you lived in Hawthorne, you'd be home by now.
You'd be washing your car every night.
Yeah.
If I lived in Hawthorne, I would have gotten it, yes.
Although it was only $24 versus $13 for the volcano.
So I guess I should have.
Unlimited, if you were near one of these
and you could time it where you weren't,
there wasn't a big line of cars.
Getting your car washed every day would be pretty sweet.
If you guys had a little kid
and they liked going through the car wash,
I mean, you'd be wasting so much water,
but it was pandemic and there's nothing else to do.
You just drive the kid through the car wash
like every two days.
You could even, yeah.
And you could tell like the people,
hey, turn the water off.
We just want to go in and see the big wheels
and the machines.
The rollers.
If there's lights, make the lights go.
Yeah.
So I got that.
I will say this, the consoles that you buy,
the car wash were kind of cool.
Like I like it, it's a big blue console.
I believe they have Apple Pay available.
This isn't some like rinky dink operation.
This is like a real.
Was yours in a gas station?
No.
Behind a gas station?
Okay, that's interesting
because I went through the Bell Gardens one
and it was attached to a 76.
And it seemed like they were separate businesses,
but they weren't like, you kind of had to work.
You had to go in 76 to get your free air freshener towel.
Okay, so there was some sort of cooperation
between the two businesses.
What you're saying.
Yeah, because you're like,
after you went through the car wash,
you were in like a gated parking lot
for the, all the vacuum stations.
Well, maybe a deal has been worked.
I guess so.
Or reached between the two parties, you know,
cause there's nothing like that going on here.
This is just a pure jungle themed car wash.
So yeah, there's big like, everything is green.
So like a big green fence outside.
Where like the, you park your car after
if you're going to get it blow dry
or you're going to get it vacuumed.
So I went through and immediately you see a big fake place
plastic lion looking at you through some, you know,
like trees or shrubs or whatever.
If you can see this guy here.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Looking sharp.
And there's a big, there's a big picture of a lion
on the side of the building that says,
and there's a big thing above it that says,
get ready for an adventure.
And the lion is like, or excuse me,
the tiger is staring at you with his like eyes,
his evil tiger eyes.
I mean tigers aren't evil, but they scare me.
So I'm saying they're evil tiger eyes.
And then you basically like, it's again,
everything is slow.
This is busy, it's a busy day.
So I got a lot of time to look
at the different static figures.
There's something of like a, I don't know,
like a snow leopard, not a leopard,
but like a, some sort of a cat,
some sort of a big white cat.
Sure. Sure.
Which one scared you?
Does, did that one scare you?
No, that one didn't scare me.
There's a giraffe here.
Great.
There are some fake rocks sitting here.
Yeah.
And then there's like a toucan as well.
Let me tell you something.
I'm reacting as if I don't know a little of this.
I did go to this car wash as well.
I also, I went, this is not my main one
that I'm reporting on.
However, this episode was in the air.
For a different episode,
I went down to Redondo beach and then ended up in Hawthorne
with the friend of the show, Buzz Buzz.
And we of course had to go pay homage to the spot
where the beach boys house was
before it was demolished to build a freeway.
There's a monument there.
So we went and paid our respects.
And then I'm like, well, I'm 10 minutes away
from the jungle car wash.
So I got to do it too.
So I've experienced the things that you're just going to.
Yeah.
I've been to the jungle.
I also, I mean, this is how I discovered the idea.
That you went to the jungle first.
I just found the jungle and I laughed like a maniac
for like the entire, there was no line when I went.
And I just was like, what the, what the fuck is this?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So three, three Colonel Kurtz's who have gone up river
and are in the jungle.
The horror.
When you're alone, you're like looking over,
you're like, you can't explain this to anybody.
It was that feeling to be like, what?
Yeah. And you wonder.
I feel bad about your weekend visit now too,
because mine was like Wednesday at 4 p.m.
It definitely, I'm sure took a lot of time than mine.
Cause I definitely felt like I was in this line forever.
I was waiting for this forever.
And there's just, yeah, there's a bunch of like old,
again, old looking stuff.
I don't know that it's that old,
but it looks like it's been decaying rapidly.
Great. Yes.
Rody level.
Yes.
I mean, moisture must not be good for statues
not meant to be in moisture, right?
Yeah, no.
These aren't, they are not like car wash brand
of animal statue, like meant to withstand
the insane elements.
Right.
Like whatever the tire polishing material,
they can't absorb it.
The plastic can't deal with it.
The humidity of an actual rainforest, basically.
Right.
So just constant moisture
and then unrelenting sunlight, Southern California.
The light that they talk of drawing people here
but also playing on people's mind and driving them insane.
Curing their tuberculosis, but also...
Yeah.
Also, maybe I should start a cult.
We should get a cult going out here.
So the building itself is painted.
And it's interesting because the painting on the building
that is supposed to represent a forest,
if you look at it, it looks kind of cool.
But when you're driving by it,
it looks dirty and looks like shit
at the same time.
Do you know what I mean?
This is kind of cool, not Mary Blair-ish,
but maybe a little bit adjacent.
They did a mural.
It's a mural.
It's a big mural on the side of this car wash building.
And you can appreciate it for what it is,
but also, yeah, it just is coated in a cover,
like a thin, thick layer of dirt.
That's what it feels like.
It is, yeah.
It's exposed to dirt and chemicals all day.
I mean, that would be the problem, I think,
with Jason's fantasy of running through,
I think the chemical exposure is gonna be bad news.
Yeah, I think the chemical exposure, the turtle,
yeah, you're probably not supposed to get blasted
by turtle wax.
Blasted by a turtle wax cannon.
Only one way to find out.
Yeah.
What would be the worst?
Would it be the clear coat polish?
Would it be the foam bath?
I'm worried about the shine.
I don't think we have enough information about the shine.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's like the logo of the shine
looks like a sitcom logo.
The shine.
Featuring the shine.
So, yeah, so I'm getting very excited in line.
It's taking a while, but I am excited.
I'm like, oh, wow, okay, here we go.
So there's like, yeah, there's like a monkey figure
hanging from a fake, dirty palm tree.
And then there is a, I guess, is it a llama?
Like this is like a llama,
and then there's just a rusty old chain
hanging in front of it, and it is not on purpose.
I thought it was a screaming deer.
No, you're probably, yeah, you're right.
It is a screaming deer.
Its eyes look like it's been cut out.
Like the front of its eyes have been sliced
and it's screaming in pain.
So it's not even slaughtered,
because you're not slaughtering it
like you're going to eat its meat.
You're maiming it.
This is torture.
You're maiming a deer, yeah.
And then there's just a big rusty chain
hanging in front of its head
as if it's about to be like wrapped in it.
Could be part of the torture.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that might be the next step.
Some unfortunate deer.
Yeah, and then at that point,
you're about to go into the main event,
and you get like a fun little portal thing
that again explains to you the different levels,
even though you've already paid.
So I'm not exactly sure what the point of that is.
And then there is music, right?
Hold on, like I have a video here.
Oh.
I forget if there was music or not before that.
Maybe there wasn't.
I didn't get any.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I was trying to soundtrack it myself.
So you had steel drums in the car.
Well, yeah.
They were piping it in.
I have a boombox in the back with the.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
Jungle car wash.
Nothing more fun than that.
That's as long as it takes him to write a song.
So yeah, so you go in there.
Now, I don't know why I was thinking
that there would be some sort of plastic figures
in the actual car wash.
I was thinking that.
This is maybe, this is a tough area
for a lot of what we're talking about today
is that it is tough to theme the wash part itself.
And I think we should all give bonus points
to any of these where the wash components are also themed.
Yes.
It's tough to do.
I give them credit, anybody credit for,
you trying or not trying and failing?
Right, but I will give them credit for lights.
There are lights going on here that are very fun.
And when, so there's red, orange and green lights.
Did you guys have both of those?
Yes.
And I felt like the orange lights
are supposed to represent lava.
Oh, volcano.
Wait, maybe I didn't get the lights
because I didn't do volcano.
Oh, you get better, like a better light show.
I think you maybe get a better light show.
I should have turned around and tried it again.
The line was very long.
Yeah.
And I was very,
I ate a lot of Chuck E. Cheese already that day.
The concert, not the restaurant.
I wasn't eating cheese pizza.
They weren't serving Chuck E. Cheese food
at the Chuck E. Cheese concert.
So you get red, orange and then green.
And I think that, yeah, I think,
I don't know what the red is.
The red is maybe, I don't know, hell.
Like I'm not sure exactly what the red is,
but the orange felt.
It's been a deforestation in the jungle.
I guess lava's a red light.
It's eerie red light.
Bolsonaro's burning down the forest.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
He's got COVID again and he's enraged.
Given his sad little thumbs up from a hospital bed.
They just have a hospital bed in the presidential office
in Brazil at this point.
Yeah, yeah.
I thought the Bolsonaro statue in the,
in the floor wash was kind of important.
Yeah, yeah, it was odd.
But at least some theming.
So yeah, maybe the red and the orange are both lava.
And I thought the orange is,
I've mentioned this recently that my,
one of my favorite things is,
I think it was Disney's America that I like
when they do like steam and orange light
to make it look like fire.
Like they added a big thunder.
And what they would have had
in the industrial revolution ride at Disney's America
when you were escaping.
Smelting.
Smelting, yeah.
Molten steel.
The idea of smelting.
So I was like, okay, this is, I'm a big fan of this.
Yeah, did you guys?
Whoa, that's cool.
No, I did not get this.
Okay, well volcano is the way to go.
No question about that.
Yeah, and then at that point,
do you remember the colors you got?
I may have not gotten a lot of colors.
Really?
I didn't say a lot of colors, I did the easiest one.
So then yeah, so then it goes to green.
I wanna show you guys this.
Let me see.
This is a whole world of colors.
So yeah, so like red is flashing here.
This is cool.
Which I, yeah, it was very cool.
And then at a certain point,
so like my windshield is getting scraped now.
And then it turns into the orange here.
Oh, great.
You're in the gates of hell.
That's right.
And I'm now dueling with Satan.
Those are his teeth.
They're rubbing against your windshield.
And then of course, he's realizing that I'm a pure soul
and he releases me back into the kingdom.
He doesn't belong here.
Into the kingdom of heaven.
And it's green now.
Green means go.
Lush forest.
Green means go to heaven.
Wow.
And then there's story.
So yeah, so I was excited about the colors.
And then I was like, okay,
there's gotta be like a triumphant animal.
But the first thing you see is a dirty barrel.
Not a barrel of monkeys.
And then you got, so the,
what do you call the big floppy things
that get on your windshield to try to get the water off?
You know what I'm talking about?
Like the big rags kind of.
Yeah.
Like big rubber rags that are like getting the stuff.
Oh yeah, so there's a blue,
there's a big flashing blue one too at the end here.
So I think that that's what you're paying for.
I think you're paying for the light show.
Yeah.
That happens.
Should have taken some LSD, my man.
You gotta really time that.
That's a tough time though.
From what I understand about LSD.
LSD lasts 12 hours.
That's why the line was so long.
People are like, I'm waiting for it to kick in.
Go around me.
And the trippers.
And then you come out and then yeah,
you see a whole menagerie of animals.
Lion.
Yeah, oh, they're all waiting for you.
I got out and went back and revisited.
I spent a lot of time with my friends.
A couple of parrots, a really big one,
a really big bird, like an eight year old kid
sized bird.
Cool, like you'd find a Jumanji walking in the jungle.
Yeah, exactly.
And then there's two anthropomorphic flower characters.
Oh.
Cute.
Oh, cute.
Love them.
And one of them has on the leaves or the petals,
wait, wait, and then the other one says go, go, go.
So I believe they light up when you're supposed to wait
and when you're supposed to go.
I believe that's what happens.
So you take a hard left into a regular parking lot
and you can get your car vacuumed.
But all of the vacuum stations all have
an individual dirty palm tree with the top
of the dirty coconut.
Right.
Those are my favorite parts, I think.
Did you see it, wait, about the elephant.
Did you not see an elephant?
Oh, did I mention, I saw an elephant.
Did I, I guess I forgot to mention him.
Did he have a little Hulk statue
standing on his head when he was on?
What?
Wait, I don't think you did for me either.
I remember you sent me this picture.
I have it, hold on.
Hold on.
You keep talking, I'll pull it up.
Okay, okay, well what else?
I'm gonna, let me find that.
I have a photo of the elephant.
Did you go to the bathroom?
Because the bathroom had tropical plants inside.
Oh, I didn't go to the bathroom.
Yeah, you had to walk through the office
of the people who work there and they look at you weird.
But then.
You guys didn't see this?
That was not on my elephant's head.
There was a tiny triumphant Hulk standing
on top of the elephant's head.
I think he got rid of it.
Yeah, I would have.
Wow.
You got a minus point.
Hulk is proud of you.
This photo is, yeah.
Car wash flash green, color of Hulk.
2021.
Clean windshields are good.
Wait, so you went over a year ago.
So this is a.
Wow, that's an old one.
I went in like, yeah, mid 2021.
Wow, wow.
Oh, that Hulk's long gone.
Some nasty little kid hopped out of the car
and was like, mine now.
It's next to, it was next to the parrots.
That's well, I hate to say.
I remember you sent that photo and I'm like,
oh, we gotta do the car wash episode now.
But minus points for getting rid of Hulk.
Well, we'll make sure everyone gets to see the Hulk.
Yeah, yeah, he lives in photographic memory.
They could have gotten sued by Disney for that.
Yeah.
They just had to get rid of it for legal reasons.
So what do you think, just judged as a themed experience,
how did this compare against some of the other things
we talk about like the haunted mansion?
Well, if we're comparing this to haunted mansion.
If I had to rank this against the Disney rides or okay,
I would say it's, or all the rides, Transformers,
this car wash, Rise of the Resistance third.
Yes, of course.
Yeah, good answer.
That's very fair.
That's what I would say.
Wow, geez, wonderful.
Okay, where are we moving next?
Are we going, are we sticking with the chain
and going to Jason?
Yeah, I will go.
My experience was a little more different
because the setup was different.
So they did have big clear signs of like,
cheap car wash here so you could see it from the road.
Does it say cheap car wash?
It says $5 express Monday through Sunday.
But there was also a themed sign.
If you can see this,
dinosaurs are the theme of the Belle Garden.
Dinosaurs, hell yeah.
And there's, so as soon as I saw the list,
I was like, since I was a little kid, I loved dinosaurs.
I still like dinosaurs a lot.
So I was like, well, I'm gonna go to the dinosaur one.
Great, you picked, you're based on your interest.
Yeah, and if you can see,
like this one was kind of hard to get a shot of,
but there is a dinosaur statue pretty quickly
when you go in.
And there's one you can see when you go out
and the rest is kind of just painting.
Oh, there's another guy.
There's a like spitter kind of dinosaur.
Oh, cool.
So a similar setup, as Mike said,
you pull into the credit card thing.
And I went last Sunday morning
and I was like, okay, it's a beautiful day outside.
It's Sunday morning.
I was preparing myself for a line.
And so I go down.
What does that look like
when you're preparing yourself for a line?
I was like, oh, I bet.
Do you like get a drink?
It's, I make sure you go to the bathroom
before you leave the house
but you also have a cold bottle of water
cause it could be waiting a while.
So-
No milkshakes though.
No milkshakes.
I got a little treat, but so this-
For the line?
No, after where everything was done.
So this is in Belle Gardens, California,
which I hadn't really been through before.
And there is like residential neighborhoods
around this gas station,
but leading up to the gas station,
it was mostly empty office parks.
And when I was getting back on the freeway to leave,
I saw the bicycle casino hotel.
Have you ever seen?
I've never been there.
Really not.
I walked in there once
and took a picture right before I came in
and immediately like, what are you doing?
Why did you do that?
And then I walk in and it's just nothing but joyless game.
Like, and everyone looking at you,
like get out of this place.
It is not a place you're supposed to go.
Yeah.
Sorry to take away from this real quick.
The gambling in there is like, is it just table stuff?
Is it slots?
I forget.
Some things miss say it is one of those,
where like a type of gambling is not there.
There's that hotel that's on the way down to Disneyland
and I forget that has like gambling in it.
And we stopped in there
because it says something about casino.
And we're like, oh, this might be-
Commerce?
Is it commerce?
It's on the five.
I think that's-
And you go in-
It's just look like you could like jump out the window
and land on the five if you wanted to kill yourself.
Yes, it's perfect for that.
But yeah, you go inside and you're like,
the gambling looks like it's just a temporary,
it looks like just a bunch of people set up tables
and people like it's packed in there.
And it doesn't even like, you wouldn't recognize it
as gambling.
You would think that everybody's like having a meal
if you weren't looking.
Oh.
Really it's an odd vibe in there is what I'm saying.
Yeah.
And it's not like-
These straight California casinos are weird.
You can't have slot machines in certain places.
Right.
No, I worked on this reality show like a long time ago
called Driving Force, which was about a drag racer
named John Force and his three sexy daughters
who also were drag racers.
And he's like-
Driving Force?
John Force?
John Force.
Yes.
Wow.
He's a famous drag racer.
He is, wow.
It's like he drives nitro cars
that have like the parachute and stuff.
But they lived in like Yorba Linda
and his daughters, like he was a terrible father
and he would scream at the daughters all the time
in the footage.
And the main thing he would scream at them about
is that he grew up in a trailer in Belle Gardens
and they're so spoiled.
And he would just say, it was like,
so the only association I have with Belle Gardens
is like John Force's traumatic backstory.
And I think we made him take the daughters
to the trailer at some point.
And the daughters just cried
because like Belle Gardens was so bad.
Oh my God.
That show ended because one of the cast members exploded.
Whoa.
Did you explain?
No, you like-
In a car.
He crashed to the nitro car and exploded.
And-
Not John Force though.
No, one of the other teammates.
It was very sad.
It was like the first one of those accidents
that happened a long time.
Oh my God.
And my boss, the show runner,
who went on to run Intervention,
went to the network and was like,
hey, we can still do the show
even though the guy exploded.
We'll just make the show about how the guy exploded.
And the network was like, no.
You canceled immediately.
Did a season come out or?
Yeah, there's like two seasons.
They made us do like really, really elaborate
Kentucky fried chicken integrations into scenes
where John Force would come home with a bucket of chicken
and be like, hey kids,
I just got this great new product
from Kentucky Fried Chicken
and treat it like it was like a reality TV scene.
Bell Gardens, I couldn't eat this good.
Really? Seriously?
Yes.
Anyway, Bell Gardens.
That's John Force.
I'm hanging up John Force.
Wow, the footsteps of Force.
Yeah.
Wow, his real name was John Force.
Wow, John Force.
John Harold Force.
Yeah.
That's like not as, well it is.
It's Schwarzenegger's name in Commando is John Matrix.
Yeah.
Cool.
Okay, so you're in the footsteps of Force.
Yeah, so I'm walking in the footsteps
of fucking legends, of giants, okay?
Not just the dinosaurs, not the footprints.
I mean the Force footprint.
And here was my impression of Bell Gardens
as I'm a few blocks away from this car wash.
It was on a Sunday morning, mostly deserted office parks
and those giant, you know, giant like five story
office buildings that say like Chase or Bank of America.
And you think, if you think long enough, you're like,
why does this bank chain need, why do they have so many
of these weird little office parks in the middle of nowhere?
Can't be the whole building, right?
Good question.
Yeah.
What's the rest of it?
I guess you just pay, you pay a little extra in your rent
to have your name on the side.
Sign, you see it on the freeway.
So until I came up on the area, which was a lot of gas
stations and some strip malls and fast food and stuff,
I was like, what is this neighborhood?
And so then it opens up and it's gas stations and all.
And I looked up the, on the website, it says,
located behind the 76, turn in off this street.
So I follow the instructions, I see the car wash
and there's the big signs, he can't miss it.
And there's no line.
I pull right up to the gate.
I don't wait at all.
And another car pulls into the other pull in spot,
starts to go in.
And so I'm looking, okay, there's a couple dinosaur statues.
And then there is a guy with a mop, just mopping.
And he like just points, like pull up there,
this way more, this way more.
And I see all these instructions, like,
take your, turn your antenna off, take your antenna down,
put your car in neutral, take your hands off the wheel.
And I'm like, what?
It's okay.
And I'm glad he was there because you have to,
and I was talking to my mom about,
I went to this car wash and I hadn't done one
where you had to like put your car in neutral
and it pulls you through in a while.
And she's like, yeah, I think I like hit something
on one of those.
She's like, I don't like those anymore.
Cause like, I, usually they don't direct you how to do it
and you can fuck up your car.
And so I was.
I'm stressed out by that section
where they tell you that stuff.
But all the, all the car washes around,
or a lot of the car washes are in,
that are in the gas stations are the ones
where you just pull in and sit.
I think it was a kid, we did do the ones
where it would pull you along.
So I haven't done that in two decades or more.
And I loved those as a kid too.
So I was very excited to be one,
cause there's a bunch in the Valley where it's like,
you pull up and it does go through one of those car washes,
but you get out and the guy takes it through
and then they, you know, wipe it down afterwards.
I want to be a little boring.
Give me a ride.
And also one of those ones on a nice day at LA,
I was like, oh, I have an hour before we have to record.
I'll go get a car wash.
And I am just sitting there waiting,
just watching the clock.
And I text you guys like 15 minutes
before we're supposed to record.
Hey, can we push half an hour?
I'm still at a car.
I've been at this car wash for 50 minutes
and my car hasn't gone through.
So in the end that ended up being a 90 minute ordeal.
Oh no.
And so I was very happy that this was very fast.
Too fast almost.
Cause I was like, the car got hooked in.
I started going through, I got the $10 volcano wash
and I was like, here comes the light show.
And immediately my car is coated in so much bubbles.
I can't see anything.
Oh no.
It is like a,
have you ever been in a whiteout snowstorm?
No, yes.
I have driven in a whiteout a handful of times in my life
in Ithaca.
It's terrifying.
Yeah, very scary.
And that is what this car wash was like.
I think there was a flash of colored light at the beginning
and then it was just soap bubbles.
Multiple times.
Cause the volcano wash,
you get three different levels of polish and soap.
Could you tell like hints of light coming through?
No, I couldn't really see.
So I don't think there really was.
That's what I was getting.
Yeah.
Cause like, it was a thick,
I had a thick layer of bubbles as well,
but you could tell there was lights there.
Yeah.
You had intro dinosaurs?
Yeah, I had intro dinosaurs.
And then when I'm, you know,
you're coming out of the car wash and it blasts you
with just water.
And then it like hair dryer blasts.
And then there is at the end,
you get, there was a light saying like, stop, don't go,
don't go, it's green.
Now you can put the car in drive.
And then there was a 25 foot mural of dinosaurs.
Oh yeah.
That's a great mural.
That was great.
That's so long.
That was so exciting.
I was so excited to come out of the whiteout conditions
and see dinosaurs.
It's like seeing the brontosaurus for the first time.
Yeah, like Jurassic Park.
Yeah.
And then there was,
there is a brontosaurus on top of the building.
This is what it looks like from after.
And there is just so many,
there was like 10 vacuum spots.
And I was happy cause I had a bunch of fucking shit
in my car, you know, crunched leaves or whatever
to vacuum up.
Leaves?
Like, yeah, leaves.
Like from hiking?
I park under trees.
There's trees next to where I park.
So sometimes stuff gets in there.
Yeah, you're tracking it.
I guess that's.
And so I was also like pulling into this parking spot
and I was like, all right, let's see how this,
did this work?
Like how, how did, like, I was like, is my car look,
cause I just got blasted with so much soap bubbles.
I was like, did this do any, and I get out
and I was like, Jesus Christ, the car looks brand new.
This is like maybe the best car crash I've ever gotten.
Good job, Bell Gardens.
I guess I didn't talk about mine.
Mine looked fine.
It looks good.
Yeah, I know complaints here.
It looked great.
I, it looked better than like the $20 wash.
Like I've gone in Burbank where people, you know,
wipe it down.
And so then I have to take the receipt inside
because at this location,
you get either a free air freshener or a free chamois towel.
Wow.
I guess.
So I go inside and I'm like,
hi, I just got the volcano wash.
And they're like, okay, do you want the towel
or do you want the air fresheners?
And I was like, oh, do I pick one off this rack?
And they're like, no, you can have vanilla or,
I think it was vanilla, new car smell.
I forget the other ones, berries.
Like there was like five and they had
shootier, shootier air fresheners.
But they were still the official little trees,
air fresheners.
My favorite discovery about a year ago,
the air fresheners you see at every car wash
made in the USA.
And the brand name is Little Trees.
Oh, trees.
And I think that's cute.
Oh, that's great.
I got the vanilla one.
And they must've thought I was crazy
because I went back into the car wash a couple of times
because I went in to get the thing.
And then I was like, oh, you know what?
It's a long drive back.
I should use the bathroom.
And I go in to, I saw the bathroom door.
I go up and it's a door with no handle.
And it just says, cashier will open the bathroom for you.
And they like buzz the bathroom door.
And then inside there was a button
to get out of the bathroom.
And I was like, okay, so this is how they keep crazy people
out of this bathroom trap for too long.
Yeah, John Force ain't getting in that bathroom.
And John Force, no, he cannot camp out there.
Scott, I mean, this was a pretty big,
this was the 76 and pretty big convenience store in it.
Scott, I thought you'd appreciate the wine section
partially hidden by the planters, peanut mixes,
and also the most industrial looking closet next to it.
Wow.
And a fun little wine sign up top.
That's a great swirly dubbing.
Yeah, this belongs in your garage.
Yeah, you should get the wine sign.
Soon as this place is out of business.
But you just puffed them up with your good review.
Yeah, the only thing about the bathroom
I was a little put off by was this handwritten sign
that said, please don't flush toilet paper down the toilet.
And I was like, oh, I don't.
Let me take a look at that.
You're in Greece.
Please don't.
You're in a foreign country.
I looked at it a number of times just to make sure
I wasn't misreading paper towels, but it for sure says,
please don't flush toilet paper down the toilet
with a smiley face.
And it is like, yeah, so I was just trying to,
yeah, it is a piece of paper that's posted.
Could it be a prank from a car wash user?
No, it sounds like their pipes can't handle anything.
Yeah, can't handle half ply, Scott toilet paper.
Was there a garbage can in the stall next to the toilet
full of shitty paper?
I did not, there was a massive garbage can in there.
So I guess, I guess they found a working ground.
I kind of feel like you dropped the ball here.
You could wash your butt in the car wash.
Yeah.
You stick your butt out the window.
Bend over and shine please.
Moon the dinosaurs.
Yeah, pick your level of whole wash.
Volcano.
Bubble, bubble cano.
V-Wax, yeah.
So got the Manila air freshener.
I was like, you know what?
I haven't gotten a big fountain soda in a while.
And they say like 99 cents outside
for a massive jug of soda.
I got Coke Zero, so that's zero calories anyway.
But there was definitely.
It's good for you.
It's healthy.
Yeah, yeah, full fat.
And then I saw something where I was like,
oh, an interactive element for the show.
A little treat that I can share with everyone.
Something that's come up multiple times,
but I rarely see in California.
I got this big bag of IndyCaps.
Hot Fries.
IndyCaps Hot Fries.
Oh man.
From my childhood.
So in the interest of, I bought them.
And in the interest of making Scott,
turning Scott into a little junk food freak,
like me and Mike.
I see.
We can all enjoy it.
Well, we learned while eating Mariah's cookies
that people love when we eat next to Mike.
Yeah, they want that Mike sound.
Yeah, so.
Nom, nom, nom.
You go that way, go the right way.
Why don't you stop the recording as we all sample it.
Oh, that's a good idea.
And then you can start it again.
Okay, sure, yeah.
Let's try it.
All right.
So we've all had a few of IndyCaps delicious hot fries.
Thank you, IndyCap.
Thank you.
You know what?
I liked them.
That's pretty good.
Maybe I shouldn't be so afraid of eating like Jason.
Yeah.
Or any of you.
I think. That's solid.
Three or four are probably what you're supposed to eat.
This bag was like a $1.25.
Oh no.
It was unseasonably cheap.
It has three servings.
This whole bag is 400 calories.
Oh, they have barbecue fries now.
I was gonna say, what are the other options for IndyCap?
Cheddar fries and barbecue fries.
And so like they would sell little mini bags of this
at like all the schools I went to growing up.
They did not.
I did not have that growing up.
I don't think they cared any of IndyCap's food
or where I'm from.
Sorry, go ahead.
I was just gonna ask if you felt like it embodies
the spirit of IndyCap particularly.
I think so.
I mean, IndyCap's whole thing is he's a lush,
he's a bum and his wife is always mad at him.
So I think, yeah, he likes these snacks.
They probably go good with a pint.
Cause I feel like he's always at the pub.
The bitter drinking.
Yeah.
What were you saying, Eva?
I'm reading an interview with John Force's chef
of what he likes to eat.
So there's a recipe here
for speedy Southwestern potato salad.
Whoa.
And so a drink-
We've been talking a lot lately about eating like Walt,
but now we can eat like John Force.
He has a drink called a whole shot win,
which I don't know what that means,
but it's like frozen raspberries, lemonade,
raspberry vodka and cranberry juice.
I guess Mr. Force drinks that.
Although he only, when I was working on the show,
his favorite thing to say was coffee up, beer down.
Anyway.
Coffee up, beer down.
All right, now take a shot of raspberry vodka
and get in that car.
It ain't my fault if it explodes.
Turbocharged tenderloin.
All the food has to be speed and force.
What does John Force look like?
Oh boy.
Oh yeah, take a look.
Oh yeah, you're gonna love it.
Does anyone feel like describing him?
I mean, I'm gonna look it up, but do you have a-
He looks like, he kind of looks like the Kennedy
that Cheryl Hines is married to.
Yeah, Google him.
Yes, yeah, totally.
But like more like a racer version.
Oh yes, very, yeah.
Like the way when Biden was still keeping the fake teeth up.
Yeah.
He looks like, yeah, he's like 2012 Biden.
He's like he's got George Washington's dentures
in his mouth.
Wow, yeah.
Okay, well, which makes him look kind of Busey-esque.
He looks like a Busey.
Right, right.
He's extremely Busey-esque in the way he talks
and his mannerisms and stuff.
He looks like, I've seen people mention,
use this phrase that like, he looks like he put his face
through the face app to put the smile on it,
but that's just his regular face.
Yes.
Well, we have another option if anyone wants to hear
a full John Force episode.
We might- Oh wow.
It's very possible that even-
It's a foregone conclusion at this point.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Even you're gonna get called into service
on every Club 3 if we're not carrying,
you're gonna get a permanent spot.
I could talk about funny car racing all day.
Sure.
Jason, do you know, is Andy Cap owned
by King Feature Syndicate?
He might be a King Feature Syndicate.
I don't know, he's not on one of the-
I'm trying to find the answer to that.
He's not on Toon Lagoon anyway.
He might not be.
That's, I'm kind of feeling he's not
in the King Feature Syndicate family.
I feel like Andy Cap would sometimes,
in certain newspapers, I mentioned this recently,
there were weird extra comics under the word puzzles
and the chess puzzle, the chess game.
But yeah, so yeah, I got myself a big Coke Zero too
because all the signs everywhere were like,
our cups stay colder for longer.
And I'm like, well, good, hey,
there's some accidents on the freeway, long drive back.
I'll be able to enjoy a cold beverage the whole time.
And I'm like, I wonder what makes them colder longer.
And the revelation was just,
oh, these cups are just massive styrofoam jugs.
These are just, I-
Oh, just bring the styrofoam back?
Yeah, it's just styrofoam, that's the trick.
Only in Foley Gardens.
Yeah.
Well, let's boil it down.
How do you rate this purely in the theming department,
as a themed experience?
Sure, as a themed experience, I mean, I had a walk-on,
so that always makes it a little better.
No queue.
Well, no, he got through the queue fast.
I got through the queue fast.
Okay, that's cute.
Yeah, that's fast.
And there were dinosaur statues in the queue.
Like I said, if there was a light show,
it was so much soap, I could not tell.
Like I think, yeah, the impression of lights,
like as Mike was mentioning, would have shown up a little.
Yeah.
Yeah, the service was good.
The people at the gas station were very nice.
It was a busy day.
Gas in Bell Gardens is much cheaper than the Valley.
Okay.
That was my worst experience.
I tried to go to the ARCO across, like down the block.
It was so cheap there.
And everyone was just coming from every door.
There were cars pointing every which way.
And I was like, I am going back to the gas station
with the car wash to get there.
Oh, you left in return.
I left in return.
So those people must've thought I was insane
coming in and out of the,
making that many transactions at the gas station.
But you wanna put it next to a ride.
Is there a ride that you think is not as good as?
Well, I think like in terms of like not a huge weight,
but still a reasonably good experience,
the vacuums kind of worked.
But overall pretty pleasant.
I'll put it, I would maybe like Mike and Sully
to the rescue, the Monsters Inc ride.
Wow.
So solid, but like, could use a little more,
oomph, he could plus it up a little more, you know?
It doesn't seem like,
you're talking like 10 dinosaurs ultimately.
Like it's not fully immersive,
but that mural looks solid.
Yeah, the mural was cool.
And I had a pleasant experience.
Great, great.
Wow.
Amazing.
Eva?
All right, so just jump right to it.
I went on the Green Forest website
and I picked the farthest one away, San Pedro,
which has a big squid and appears to be ocean themed.
Ocean, okay.
Big squid, there's a little octopus is hanging from it.
There's a dolphin, you see like,
and I had to get to,
I had to go to a comedy show in Irvine.
So I was like, I'll go to San Pedro,
wash my car and then I'll go to Irvine.
Not actually in the same direction at all.
Okay, yeah, you feel like it is.
Yeah, but then I had to go way back north again
to go south again, to go to the Spectrum Center,
which is, I don't know if you guys have been
to the Irvine Spectrum Center.
I have, yeah.
It's a, hell.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, really confusing and super packed.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I would go to the ends of the earth
to see Sebastian Maniscalco like you did.
I mean, I did go to the comedy laugh factory
in the Irvines.
In the mall.
Yeah.
Oh, Maniscalco's playing the pond.
He's playing the pond for seven nights probably.
Oh, I think he was like coming to Vegas
right after I had been there,
was playing the T-Mobile Arena or something.
I think he's all arenas all the time.
I did see a good show.
I'll tell you guys who it was off air
because it's a secret.
Just casting secret.
Anyway, okay, squid, squid, squid.
Very excited to see the squid.
Drive for like an hour plus.
Get there.
It's not, it's no longer.
What?
No.
No, it looks regular.
The squid has been painted red, but keeps its squid.
Wow.
Oh, the sign is like a squid,
but now it just looks like bulbous.
Oh my God.
Bulbous sign.
But I'm like, I still got to wash my car.
So I put it up and there is a slight theme.
Volcano.
Still volcano.
Yeah.
So you can get a lava luster wash.
That's it.
What's the price?
What's the price looking like there for the volcano wash?
20 for the top one's 20.
Oh, it's a much higher.
32.95.
That's a good price in Bogart.
Yeah.
Touch up, light clean only seven.
You can get monthly wheel blasters though for 1995.
That sounds good to me, John Force.
I love my wheel blasters.
This fucking crazy volcano that's like shooting
lightning down onto the car washes.
Yeah, that's pretty fun.
That's like an L Ron Hubbard book cover.
And when you drive in,
you see the volcano kind of above it.
And then there's red lights.
There are red lights flashing.
So they got rid of the squid
and it looked like there was like cute dolphins and stuff.
No explanation.
It's just gone.
So, but anyway, I got my car wash.
It was totally fine.
I think I did get a free little towel
they threw into my car, whatever.
And I was like, that's not good enough.
Yeah, no theme.
You got screwed.
So this week after work, I drove to Hermosa beach
and I went to the rock and roll car wash.
Oh yeah.
I was like, we need to do this again.
And there's only, it was one of the only remaining
themed car washes that nobody had done.
So the rock and roll car wash
is in like the heart of Hermosa beach, right off the one.
It has this big guitar on the sign.
And when you get up there,
these are the package menus you can have.
Wash package menu.
It starts in vocals for $22.99.
Then it goes to vocals and guitar.
That's cause you see, when you're recording a song,
you always start with vocals.
You start with vocals.
Number two is vocals and guitar.
Three is vocals, guitar and bass.
Number four is vocals, guitar, bass and drums,
the quote whole band.
And that's $34.99.
Wow, $34.99 is expensive.
And so there's a sign
about all the things they're not responsible for.
And then there's musical notes on it.
Stamps.
And fire.
Yeah.
So you get inside.
So this is one of those where they wash your car for you,
but the entire interior is full of signs for bands.
Yes.
So it's like, it'll both be like a big, you know,
like just a picture of the Rolling Stones.
But then I liked the like,
the specific signed poster for the birthday massacre
or the band infected rain.
What's the birthday massacre?
I don't know any of these bands.
And they might be South Bay specific.
Wait, and I'm sorry, who signed infected rain?
Infected rain signed their poster.
Infected, the rain is infected.
Infected with what?
Infected with bees wax to give your car that shine.
Oh, it's just like the Beatles walking across Abbey Road,
but then it's also just like,
oh, they had just,
they had t-shirts for sale of the Beatles and ACDC
in the little shop where you could buy like a drink
or an air fryer.
Whoa.
Infected rain is from Moldova.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
So they're probably like a crazy metal math.
Yes.
Infected, yeah, they're on.
That's like the manager's cousin sent them their poster
and they hung it up.
I think the owner is into rock and roll.
There's this weird picture of him with this band
and the main guy is like a skeleton face with a Pope hat.
And I think this is the guy that owns the car wash.
Because-
This is like a satanic church or something.
That's really crazy looking.
The thing that was interesting, oh yeah.
So two more things that are very important is
there's this huge fat Elvis statue in the corner.
Okay.
The suffering Elvis.
Yeah, and there's also like the sign on it that says,
please respect the king for your own safety.
Do not climb on Elvis, thank you.
And then there's like one of these you could sit in.
Like one of those-
Oh wow.
A car seat.
Like the back of a car, like the back of a T-bird.
Yeah.
But it's a bench.
So that's what you sit, this is where you're at
while you wait for your car to get washed.
Neck with your special lady while you're waiting for us
to do four coats of turtle wax.
And it was like, everyone seemed very nice there.
It was like, I appreciated the Elvis statue.
Here's something that's really interesting though.
There was a framed article on the wall where I was like,
oh, this explains a lot.
It's from Car Wash Magazine.
And it was an article in 2014.
And it's called, it's California's themed car washes.
And it was breaking down the new trend of themed car washes
starting with Green Forest, which had just opened
and won a bunch of awards.
Wow.
So most of what's interesting about this is it's the guy
explaining why he opened the rock and roll car wash.
But sidebar, it's like, he keeps getting compared
to Green Forest, which is winning all the awards.
And then at one point in the article, he's like,
I'm opening another one and it's gonna be, he says, wait.
He's like, I'm opening a future project
in the Rondobo beach area, like after the rock
and roll car wash.
And we will also have a popular theme there,
but you'll have to wait and see what the theme is
for that location.
It'll be something right out of the movies.
And it will also coincide with the beach and the pier vibe
in anticipation of a new waterfront project.
Even if the waterfront project is held up,
our theme will still work well.
This never was built.
Like this stuff never happened.
What does it mean?
What do you think that is?
I don't know.
Is it like a net beach blanket bingo type?
That could be cool.
Straight out of the movies.
Yeah.
I think it's an avatar.
It's probably avatar.
The way of water.
He knew way of water was coming.
My buddies with James Cameron,
my buddies with the infected rain and also with James Cameron.
One thing they do say is that,
like this is about car crazy Angelenos
who demand entertainment.
And also they also say that,
That's Jay Leno.
That the Green Forest washes won a lot of awards
for conserving water.
Oh, interesting.
They're a bit more environmentally friendly
than other washes.
Okay.
Which is kind of nice.
It's a nice thing about the brand.
I have heard of that.
Like, oh, if the options are like wash your car yourself
in your driveway with a hose or go to car wash,
the car wash is more water efficient
than you just running a hose for 30 minutes.
Good to know.
Also Paul's boutique was playing on screens in the room.
Okay.
But also watch music videos while you wait for your car
while you stop by the Elvis,
but you don't climb on him.
Did you go up to the cashier and go like,
Hey, I saw you had a couple of T-shirts.
Do you have any T-shirts for this place?
Oh, I should have.
Do you have any infected rain shirts?
Or infected rain.
I'll take either.
I just went, another thing that was just interesting
was there are posters all over for this movie called Butter.
So I went on the website and started reading about Butter.
It's a independent film came out in 2020.
And this is the plot summary.
A lonely obese boy, everyone calls Butter,
is about to make history.
He's going to eat himself to death, live on the internet.
And everyone is invited to watch.
Oh my God.
What?
Christ.
Butter, no.
So much more to live for.
You can eat a lot, but not to death, Butter.
I almost went as far as to like watch all of Butter,
but I just watched the trailer.
This is unrelated to the 2011 movie Butter.
With a carving Butter.
Yeah, with a carving Butter.
No, this is about a boy named Butter.
When he first makes the announcement online
to his classmates, Butter expects pity, insults,
and possibly sheer indifference.
When he gets our morbid cheerleaders
rallying around his deadly plan,
yet as their dark encouragement grows,
it begins to feel a lot like popularity and that feels good.
But what happens when Butter reaches his suicide deadline?
Can he live with the fallout
if he doesn't go through with his plans?
And there's one thing that's important to know
from the trailer is that Butter plays jazz saxophone
very well.
And that's something he gets a lot of attention for.
Also his mom is. Maybe it's a salvation.
Mirosirvino.
Mirosirvino, wow.
Geez, wait, Oscar winner, right?
Oscar winner, Mirosirvino.
This movie, it sounds like a male insensitive precious.
Yes.
Also.
Weird name of a character,
except it's really odd and abrasive and mean.
I read a, sorry guys, skip ahead
if you don't want to know what happens at the end of Butter.
Cause I was reading all the user reviews on IMDB
and somebody spoiled the end of Butter,
which is that he kills himself.
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
No.
Butter, no.
Butter.
Oh my God.
So anyway, that was my experience.
Because he listened to too much infected rain.
I have a, I'm guessing the audience,
I'm guessing the audience will not vote for Butter
in the next club three.
No, but we look at the results and say, no, Butter.
They voted for Butter.
No audience.
Yeah, usually like if you find a movie poster
or information about a movie,
it's sometimes good to just like get as much
as you know, Scott.
There's something, something,
there's sometimes something at the end of the clue trail.
You have to at least try.
The one that's been driving me crazy for a long time
is that I assume we've all at some point
been to the nearby Burbank restaurant
across from the Warner Brothers lot, the Smokehouse.
Oh yeah.
Old school restaurant, fun vibes in there.
Great vibes.
In the lobby.
I once saw Tony Baxter in that restaurant
actually before we got to meet him.
And it's, yeah, old school, you know, wood paneling.
And then there's been a poster there for so long now
for what seems to be a short film filmed at the Smokehouse
called Martinis at the Smokehouse.
And I cannot figure out how to,
it's one of those like, it was in festivals
and I'm like, what do you mean it's only in festivals
and you don't just put it on a Vimeo later.
I'm dying to see Martinis at the Smokehouse.
From what I can tell, it's like two lonely guys
that are like closing down the Smokehouse
and then there's through some magic,
they go back in time and they're there in the 50s.
Oh, when it's like cool and like, yeah.
When men was men.
Men was men.
Sinatra.
Listeners, if you have any connection
to Martinis at the Smokehouse, please.
It's like Burbank, midnight in Burbank.
What's midnight in Burbank?
Like midnight in Paris.
Oh yeah, I guess so, yeah.
We thought of it before, Woody.
You know, it's okay though, he's a good guy.
I'll let it slide, he's Woody.
Sorry, the trailer's available.
I think you saw the trailer, yeah.
But I look, if you watch it, you will only be,
you'll be just thirsting for more,
like a delicious martini.
Can I, so the butter carving movie with Ty Burrell.
Feel free to suggest, listeners,
if you're gonna give us the votes,
either to specify the year,
because if you want us to watch the butter carving movie
with Ty Burrell, we will.
It won the blacklist, I mean, it was like,
the government liked that script.
Yeah, yeah, people liked it,
there's a bunch of people in it.
The budget was 10.8 million.
Does anyone wanna guess what the box office was?
500,000.
Mike, any guess?
70,000.
175,706 dollars.
Whoa.
Yikes.
Mike cleans that up.
Oh no, what happened to butter?
So kind of a hard hit for the producing company,
the Weinstein company.
Okay.
Oh.
We tried to get the Weinstein's to produce martinis
in the smokehouse, they didn't do it,
but they're good guys,
it was nice to grab a drink with them.
We went back in time and got Robert Evans to produce it.
Oh.
Kid Robert Evans, teen Robert Evans.
Okay, so that's the end of my journey.
Geez, I mean, so you got exposed to a lot
of the great pop culture the last 70 years.
Yes.
How do you rank it as a themed experience?
I mean, it'd have to be like a walkthrough experience,
or something like the mystery house,
I would put it with the mystery house
maybe at Knott's or something,
something you walk through.
I guess you had to show,
but it's like, what's something you walk through?
Yeah, yeah, because it wasn't a ride.
Like a walkthrough fun house at a county fair, maybe.
Yeah.
Sure, sure.
And then for Butter, I would compare Butter
to the, what is that, Martin Short movie
where his parents have sex.
Oh, Making of Me?
Making of Me, yeah.
Put those up next to each other probably.
Equally horrible.
The Butter trailer and the Making of Me are the same.
But I had a great time.
I spaced out my car, watched this guy's by a few weeks,
my car got dirty again, I'm not a monster.
Okay, was that, did either one do a better job?
I mean, they were both fine.
I think I'm with y'all, drive through car wash all the way.
I'm sick of having, like the manual labor
of making somebody wipe down my car is not necessary
and I like to be in control of my own schedule.
And I like to see the jets.
I like to see, I'm like, Brian, you know,
like here come the warm jets.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm like that too, yeah.
Right when you get in there, oh cool.
Yeah, yeah.
I do, again, if you need to put the car in neutral,
I want a guy there to say like pull forward, pull forward.
Yeah.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
I will say if you go on an off hour
and you close the loop and you do jungle,
if you're ever in that part of town,
they are very, there's a lot of guys in charge of jungle.
Oh, that's good.
You got some help.
It's well-manned.
A lot of the green forest ones had good,
of like very helpful, attentive work, you know.
I think it's a good brand.
Yeah, I think so.
I recommend it besides the-
I'm sad they dumped San Pedro to make it a fake volcano.
That's a real bummer.
Don't go, don't, listeners don't drive all the way
to San Pedro from like another state you live in.
But you drive to Hawthorne.
People are already on the way when they heard.
The last one is there might be one,
there's one on Martin Luther King Jr. Boulevard,
which also looks to be a dinos.
And I think there's a dinos in Vegas.
Oh, wow.
So next Vegas trip, Nick and Chris does a third show.
Yeah.
You'll get your rental car washed.
Hopefully it's on the way to Kaplip.
All right, Scott.
Well, yeah, before I get to mine,
because I was trying to, we were discussing these
in general throughout the country,
other interesting ones that exist.
And there's also, I noticed another dinosaur one
that's in Austin, Texas, the Jurassic car wash.
And that one has spitting dinosaurs apparently.
Whoa.
I don't know if that's like for kids to play with.
Or if it's in the actual, in the car wash.
Cause that's what I'm looking for is like,
can somebody make the car wash itself?
Integrate.
I think that's hard though.
It's tough.
Yeah, I only, I had one idea of how you could do it,
which is that if the whole thing is like a Godzilla
Gamera type monster and you drive in through his mouth,
and then it's like you're being digested
and maybe you paint everything kind of red and fleshy.
So like everything you're going through are like his organs
and you're being swallowed.
Ooh, what about like a monstro?
Oh, that would work.
Well, and it's, yeah, it's water oriented.
And if they can make you feel like the end is you getting
spit up into the air out of the blowhole.
You could make it biblical too.
It could be, you could do it in like, you know,
the Heartland and have it be Jonah.
And you get swallowed by a whale.
Or Moby Dick, make it like, you know, East coast
and do Moby Dick.
Just anything whale related.
I just really missed having that squid.
Yeah, yeah.
That is a bummer.
What is the point possibly in replacing that?
Why did they have to do it?
Just paint it red.
What the fuck are you doing?
It's still a squid.
Yeah, now he has a half a squid.
I also discovered the phenomenon of haunted car washes,
of car wash haunts, which I imagine that Mike would love.
I hope so.
And these might happen around here.
I found one in Anaheim.
So be on the lookout.
This could, because maybe we could maybe return to this
in Haunt Cast the Fright season.
Is that a year round haunt?
No, I think there's a lot of,
these might be anywhere near the listener
throughout the country.
And it's not necessarily otherwise in theme,
in otherwise themed car washes.
Like a regular car wash might turn haunted.
And the video I watched of the Anaheim one
looks pretty good.
Like they get it's characters.
And the characters are in the wash.
Are they?
So you might pass by like kind of a scary exorcist girl
whose hair in the video was blowing,
like she was near enough to the dryers
that her hair is blowing creepily in the wind.
So this is a real,
this isn't just like when a miniature golf course goes,
this is haunted golf course.
And it's like, there's one skeleton hole,
one tiny psycho household,
one creature from the Black Lagoon hole, you know?
No, there's like fully like scary clowns
walk up to your car and like try to get in.
I saw a video of like shaking the handle,
like let me in.
You saw a video of one of those, right?
Yeah, yeah, we were sending them.
I, and like, you know, the fake chainsaws
that give you the jump scare.
I want this. So that's the whole area.
Yeah, I think for sure we can find
and listeners can find one of those.
But you're saying they're in the actual washing portion?
Like I watched videos where there were like a lot of people
like in every possible area.
They're just like adjusting the polishing chemicals?
I hope it's dangerous.
See, that was the thing with some of the drive-through haunts
where it's like, I would hope this one would be one
where you put your car in neutral.
Cause I was concerned,
I saw some of these drive-through haunts and I'm like,
I don't know that you want to be having the like gas
at your disposal, the gas pedal at your disposal
when you're going through these things
and someone starts banging on your car window.
You get crushed somebody,
you get crushed a scary clown against the side of the wall.
Yeah, yeah. Oh no, I crushed Jeeks.
I crushed Jeeks from Saul.
He was on his little tricycle. I didn't see him.
Oh man.
So haunted car washes for sure.
We got to figure out. I think that's so exciting.
But then my favorite one that I found out about,
maybe the weirdest themed car wash in the country
is that there is a car wash that is themed
after an old 19th century river boats.
This is a car wash. Wow.
Yeah. Jason, take a look at that.
This is, it is the Mark Twain, but you can drive.
The bottom floor is the car wash part.
Yeah.
And then otherwise it like it, there's a dock next to it,
kind of like a boardwalk.
And it says there's like a little like lagoon
and like with a, you know, with a fountain shooting up
and coy and all this stuff.
So you get to like, I like, you get to just like
have a little like Mississippi experience essentially.
Yeah. This looks fantastic.
That looks very fun.
And that, that is a different way to draw people than
I'm thinking there, there's a gas station in Sherman Oaks
and a lot of gas station I went to growing up
have like the biggest goddamn convenience store
you've ever seen.
Cause they just build a store, the length of the car wash.
And sometimes there's new windows where you can watch.
I was like that.
You watched your car go through
and then they need to fill those shelves.
So then you get the strangest assortment of like, you know,
mats for your car, air fresheners.
There's for some reason, a rack of candles.
There's weird like, you know,
Oh yeah. What other bullshit?
Doodads or gadgets or
CDs and DVDs and all that.
Yeah. Like fidget spinners.
And then just a wall of stuff to animal
just cause they just need stock to keep people entertained.
Yeah. While they sit around for
a while.
And you have to justify the length you're right.
Yeah.
This I think is like a great use of,
cause a river boat is long and like,
what a great like place to put that kind of thing.
So I started thinking like, okay, I was like, where is this?
I would be awesome to go to this.
And it is in California I saw,
but it was a town name that I didn't recognize,
which is Campbell.
Like where is Campbell?
Let me look up Campbell.
Campbell is in NorCal.
It's 333 miles away.
Okay.
Probably not.
Probably doesn't make sense to do it.
Probably a big asshole to do it.
And anyway, I went.
Wow.
Eva knew.
How far is it?
Whoa.
333.
Okay.
Miles away.
Wow.
So that's a long drive, right?
That's a crazy drive.
I didn't do a crazy drive.
Here's what I did.
So I mean, I was feeling you out about it all Eva.
Like, does this make sense?
But you were traveling, you're working.
And I brought it up to Erin.
Like, this is a little in my head and she got like possessed.
Like, I want to do this so badly.
For whatever reason, this just like called to her so hard.
And we figured out a plan and here was the plan.
We went from where we are right now
to the Burbank airport, which is 10 minutes away.
Yes.
A very cheap Southwest flight to the San Jose airport,
which is 10 minutes away from this.
The Campbell is right next to San Jose.
So that's pretty fast.
Rent a car specifically to get it washed.
For the only reason you're renting it.
Wow.
Return the car, fly back to Burbank,
and then still get home in time to put our boy down for bed.
This was the plan.
Wow.
This is what we hatched.
And this is exactly what we did last Wednesday.
Last Wednesday.
Wow.
Just about a week and a half ago,
we took a day trip to San Jose just to go to a car wash.
Wow. How long round trip?
Okay. We were, we left the house at a little after 9 a.m.
We had landed back in Burbank at 6.15, I believe.
Wow.
But we took our time a little bit,
but yeah, all like just within the window of the day.
Wow.
Tempted to stay overnight, but like, oh my God, if we don't,
then it's just a day trip.
We don't have any luggage.
So we breezed through security on both easy airports anyway,
deployed both grandmas to take care of the kiddo.
Thanks, grandma.
My next question is, what did grandmas say?
Yeah.
Cause I, I talked to, I talked to my parents like the day of
and the day after I went to the car wash and I was just like,
I was just like, you know what?
I don't want to open a can of words.
So I just went, yeah, I got a car wash yesterday.
Sat at the grocery store just for a couple of things,
you know?
Right. I had no way to, I mean, look,
they're used to at this point to just kind of a grinning
and bearing it on what are they up to?
I don't, okay.
Hey, if it gets this time with the kiddo,
then we're happy.
So Erin's mom might be listening.
Thanks so much for helping us.
Right. Erin's mom will listen so she knows.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That we're out of our minds.
Made our dreams come true.
Made Erin's dream come true.
Yeah.
Looks like a charming town, Campbell, California.
Well, let me tell you, I, my report is glowing.
I don't want to spoil it,
but there is no turn where this becomes bad news.
Oh wow. We made a mistake.
That was in our heads is like,
oh, but if we tempt fate here and then we don't return,
would that not be the worst thing that could happen?
That was my, my mom's reaction was just like,
okay, well tell me where the first aid kit is
in case you're, in case you get delayed for a while.
Yeah. Uh huh.
Oh, they have a water tower.
In Campbell?
Yeah, they have like a Warner Brothers lot.
They passed by the Campbell water tower.
I mean, I loved Campbell.
Okay. So, uh, lightest security lines and flights ever.
We were, went from inside our house
to inside a San Jose rental car in two, two hours,
10 minutes.
Wow.
So efficient.
When you're not even worried, when you got no luggage
and you're not, there's nothing to do on the other end
that you're stressed about.
It was, this is maybe the first time ever in my life.
I felt like I'm taking a flight.
Like when do you ever enjoy being on a plane?
But this felt like, wow, we're in the sky.
It's only a short, like Burbank, if you could do it
like to Vegas or something,
and if you're only there for a day or two,
that breezy feeling, which is rare at an airport of like.
Similar length to Las Vegas, where you have that,
where they have to get the beverage service out.
It's so fast.
But then it happens when you're like,
wait any time, if you're on a plane
and they say we're beginning our descent
and you laugh at how early you're starting the descent.
Yeah, you have not finished an episode
of the West Wing or whatever.
Whatever's on demand.
The Vegas experience is really fun to go fly to Vegas.
You get into the Vegas airport
and if you stay like South Strip,
you're like, I was in my house 90 minutes ago
and now I'm 10 stories up in a hotel room in Vegas.
Oh yeah.
It's wild.
I took my Italy leftovers last time.
Yes.
Less than two hours.
Walked them back home, put them in the fridge.
Yeah.
Okay, so we get to the rental car.
When we find the rental car, it is sopping wet.
It has just been washed five minutes prior
and now we are just taking it straight into another car wash.
Was there a discussion of dirtying it up?
Throw mud at it?
We don't know the area well enough to know where,
we don't know where to like, you know,
we don't know where to go drag this.
Where the?
This isn't like John Ford's car.
We don't know the lay of the land.
Excuse me, sir, where are our big piles of soot?
We need to dirty this car up.
Big farm around these parts.
You each constructed a Chipotle burrito ball,
walked in the parking lot, just nailed the car.
Take that.
We have to, to justify the cleaning.
It's a great breezy drive.
It's only 10 minutes away.
We get off at the exit.
What is the exit facing?
But it's like direct line of sight into the parking lot
of a former Fry's electronics.
Oh wow.
Right there, same exit as the car wash.
Do you know what was the theme of that one?
It was Egyptian, I believe.
So it was kind of tan, not a pyramid, but very, you know,
tan and tall, big austere ramps.
So now much like a hundred years ago or so,
it is just like the pyramids.
It's just an unopened tomb.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Except I care about them.
But Chip is blessed your journey.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Knowing that Chip was, I was in the footsteps of Chip.
Yeah.
Or Charlie. Charlie, you went from Charlie to Charlie.
Like airport to airport.
Cause you- Oh yeah, cause we're right, yes.
The Burbank airport right next to the former FIAS
where I've been, where I got Charlie to bring home.
So anyway, I didn't say the name.
This is the Delta Queen car wash.
That's the name of the ship.
But I think now it just goes by classic car wash.
Jaw dropped as we pulled up to it.
It is legit great looking.
It is not run down.
The place is packed.
There's so many people doing just the exterior wash
where you just drive through,
but so many people waiting for the full deal as well.
It is hopping, but not a lot of line
for just the exterior wash.
So we drove right in and you drive past
like a little ship wreck and all of the-
Wow. It's like very main street style lanterns
and American flags everywhere.
And you pass by like a cutout of a sea captain
in a yellow slicker who just like caught a big one.
And he's also holding the sign that says,
put your antenna down.
Oh wow.
It's very, the whole campus kind of is like,
it's so Knott's Berry farm.
It's really charming wooden hand carved signs
and like 1900s Americana by way of 1960s.
I think that's when it was built.
So just aesthetically love it, love the place.
The wash itself, look, you just drive through.
There is no, you're not, there's no like bells
and there's no like ragtime music.
I wouldn't note that if there is a way to jazz up that,
literally jazz up that part of the experience, I'd be happy.
But who cares?
You're in an old state,
the moment where you're driving onto the riverboat
is so exciting.
Wow. Is it in the interior?
I mean, does the interior seem like,
I know it's hard to see because of the suds,
but is the interior at all different than just the normal?
Like, could you see the walls?
Does it look a little bit more like a riverboat or anything?
Or does it just, when you were in there,
would you mistake it for a different car wash?
No, it was completely average.
So I guess I have to give it minus points for that.
But I still, I don't have it in me to give any minus point
to this delightful experience
because everything on the outside was so great.
So we went and did the car wash
and that was nothing to speak of,
but felt fun to wash the rental car.
And then we parked it down the street,
walked past what used to be a Hooters.
That was one of the things that really pulled me in too,
was like, and there's a Hooters next door,
but not anymore, unfortunately.
But not a riverboat Hooters?
No, no, no, no, just regular Hooters.
Okay.
With the bright orange of Hooters,
like in the same periphery as the brown of the riverboat,
would have been great to see, but no.
That's too bad.
But there's so much stuff.
There's a little mini-mart that sells coffee and hot dogs,
like on the little spinners.
In general, Jason, this is just, this is so up your alley.
Time to uproot your whole life and move.
To Campbell.
On to the ship to get a little room
at the top of the ship.
Oh, you could captain it.
Do you get a certificate for driving the ship,
like the Mark Twain?
I don't know that.
And if visitors cannot go up onto the top levels,
which is also disappointing,
but I really liked seeing that the manager's office
is where the captain would be.
Oh, it is.
Oh, wow.
The manager.
And I think that, like, I don't think it's all the employees,
but I think the top tier people wear, like,
kind of a naval uniform.
Oh, like Captain Stubing type, like loveboat outfits?
I think so, yes, yeah.
Oh.
So it's so great.
And then there's like, even in the little mini-mart,
there's nautical gear everywhere,
like navigational panels and old stoves
and that kind of thing, and there's flags waving
on a big mast.
And then you go into a gift shop.
So if you are getting the full wash,
there is so much to do,
because then you can go into the Queen's Chest,
which is a very Knott's Berry Farm-style,
old knickknacks kind of store,
where they're selling postcards and cards
and like big brim picnic hats and a huge wine selection.
And it's like good wines,
because you're up closer to Napa or S.R.O.L.S. or whatever.
There is a huge fish tank full of like beautiful carp.
And there's like a plaque telling you about the carp
and the history of carp.
Wow.
There's spectacular fish in this really nice,
like a lot of wood surrounding it.
And then for some reason, up on top of the fish tank,
off to the right, not centered,
is a framed sepia-toned photo of Jessica Chastain.
And there's not anything else like that.
There's no other celebrity presence.
She didn't sign it.
I don't think she's been there.
They just want to pay tribute to a great lady.
What?
That's like when people would frame the picture
of the president and hang it in their home.
Or like government offices still have that,
where it's like they rotate the-
Or like Elvis in a Thai restaurant.
This is our favorite celebrity in Campbell.
Is she from Campbell?
Oh, maybe.
I don't know.
She is from, she was born in Sacramento.
How close to Campbell is that?
What if she works there or something?
It's on the way.
There was a mini sock market, like a novelty.
Wow, really?
Oh yeah.
Area, so much stuff to look at.
But then the best part of it was that this felt like,
because we did this with a little bit of,
this wasn't like go do the car wash
and turn around immediately.
We left ourselves a free afternoon in San Jose
with absolutely no plans.
So we found, this basically felt like a scavenger hunt
where you go to location number one
and then you get a clue that takes you
to location number two.
Because we picked up a book about San Jose oddities.
And I'm flipping through the book
and I'm stopped cold by the dead eyes of Chuck E. Cheese.
There's a big Chuck E. Cheese picture
and it's pointing out how, I've totally forgot about this,
Chuck E. Cheese started in San Jose.
That's where no one started the whole thing.
So I'm like, oh, could we go to the first Chuck E. Cheese?
The answer is no, but there is this other one
that was considered the flagship Chuck E. Cheese.
And this, like everything else in the day
is only 10 minutes away.
Wow.
And the book also says that this particular
Chuck E. Cheese location is haunted
by the ghosts of two children who fell to their deaths
on the site. Oh my God.
Oh no.
Jesus.
What are you talking about?
The book says this?
The book says, yes, this is verified in writing.
Did they fall from the ball pit tunnel?
Like the top ball pit tunnel?
Oh yeah.
That's why they don't have these things anymore.
Right. Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, I mean, what I found out is that,
so then we went to it, there was no sign of the haunting.
I didn't discover really anything there.
You didn't see the bones of the children?
They didn't just leave them untouched
so as to not anger the spirits.
This is, I could see why there'd be rumors
of a falling situation because it is a three story
Chuck E. Cheese.
Wow.
This is massive.
I believe that the story of the kids who died
is leftover from the previous tenants
because this was a 70s toy store,
a massive 70s toy store that had like big kind of cages
on the outside and there was a different wooden soldier,
like a giant wooden soldier in every one of them.
I've seen pictures of it now.
This place looked incredible.
But now it's the Chuck E. Cheese,
the flagship location for a long time.
The children, the accident happened at the toy store
or the Chuck E. Cheese?
I think it's unclear.
You can Google this.
There's discussion of these rumors, but no concrete proof.
We got no names on these kids.
So I don't know.
And did you find the San Jose Audities book
at the car wash or you bought it in advance of your trip?
No, no, that was at the car wash.
So we had no idea.
We'd never heard of this gigantic Chuck E. Cheese.
Yes.
So like a movie you pick up, oh, this is interesting.
Take it right to the cash register.
Well, look, I didn't buy it.
I just got what I needed.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, I ripped off the-
Jason can appreciate that.
Yeah, you gotta appreciate that.
And you got a few minutes while that's going
through that car wash.
We paid for the car wash.
So what do you want?
So anyway, it's a, it is a three story Chuck E. Cheese.
The visitors can only access the bottom two floors.
And it is extremely impressive.
It is the biggest Chuck E. Cheese I've ever seen by far.
I think it was, I think the biggest in the country at least.
The top story used to be Chuck E. Cheese University.
This is where they would train general managers.
So if you were running a Chuck E. Cheese
anywhere in the country, at some point you had to make
the sojourn to San Jose to get your training
and probably watch all those great videos
that are all up on YouTube.
Cause we, there's hours of these Chuck E. Cheese training.
And it's not there anymore.
I don't, I know, I believe it is now storage.
So we can get up there somehow.
I think there are like old Chucks and Munches
all rusting away.
Oh, there have to be.
I will go back to do my masters at Chuck E. Cheese University.
I-
PhD.
I will fly up to Campbell to do that.
There's a McDonald's University in Pasadena
that I've, there's an art gallery next to it.
I've heard of McDonald's University.
It smells like french fries in the art gallery.
Cause it's next door to the McDonald's University.
Jason will get his doctorate.
Sure, yeah.
A lot of people go back to school in their late 20s, 30s,
you know, and we're going to McDonald's University,
Chuck E. Cheese University.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, adult education should be celebrated.
Sure.
I agree.
Lifelong learning.
So the Chuck E. Cheese itself,
fantastic, huge sprawling, no robots, no full-
I was going to say no full-munch.
That sucks.
No full-munch unfortunately.
But, and no sign of the, the haunt.
I couldn't find evidence of that,
but I was haunted by what I found on the outside,
which is what I just said about how there's the three cages
with the soldiers.
There's now, there's still those three big cages,
but only one of them is filled.
And it is filled by a 20 foot tall plaster Chuck E. Cheese
that you can see from the freeway.
Whoa.
It is huge.
We took pictures of us next to it, just for proportion,
gigantic Chuck E. Cheese.
And he is, he's sitting and he is crossing his legs
and he is pantsless.
So you can just stare into the giant unspecified crotch
of a huge like dying in the sun Chuck E. Cheese.
It's like a basic instinct Chuck E. Cheese.
Yeah, I was going to say,
can someone edit like the Chuck E. Cheese photo
and then a shot of the sweaty, wavy night?
Like, ah.
What are you gonna do?
Is it?
You're smoking?
You had sex, Helen and I had sex.
Yeah.
And she gave me pleasure.
You ever fucked on cocaine?
It's nice.
It's very entertaining.
Is it old Chuck or is it new Chuck?
It's old Chuck.
Yeah.
Good, good.
Yes, they went, we can't change that one.
No.
And he's just chipping away, like flecks of the paint,
falling off.
Wow.
I saw a Reddit comment from somebody who said,
like their friend's dad built that.
Wow.
In the early 80s.
So it's such classic early 80s Chuck E. Cheese.
And we would have never, I never knew about this.
This is perfect podcast.
My God.
That we stumbled into just thanks to heading up
to check out the old riverboat, the Delta Queen.
Still, because this all happened so quickly,
still hours to kill.
So we went to a bizarre mall, the Eastridge Mall.
We went to, we had a drink at a airport hotel lobby
right nearby that happened to be one that I had watched
a video of from the early 90s on YouTube.
Like I have like, oh boy, I'd really like to go
to that San Jose hotel someday.
Like it was a bar called Maxi's.
Whoa.
If I could ever be in Maxi's, and it's not Maxi's anymore,
but it's the space where Maxi's used to be.
We had a great drink there.
What's it called?
Ooh, it was, it's some just like, what I want to say
is it's like 360 olives or something.
Perfect.
Okay, all right.
I don't recall, but some bizarre hotel bar name.
I feel like you're about to say you like renewed your vows.
Like this is like such a great day.
I know it felt pretty much, I think it did.
I mean like, if I could just cut to the chase and say,
this was absolutely the best date that Aaron and I have had
since becoming parents, since COVID.
It was like, we were just so juiced the whole day.
It was spectacular.
We have the Delta Queen to thank for.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my God.
Thank you, themed car washes.
Yay.
Wow, yeah.
Not only, which is one more thing also.
Then we like, okay, so then we're back,
we return the car, like we only had it for five hours total.
Get back to the airport early
so that we can spend ample time, just have a relaxing drink
at Trader Vic's in the San Jose airport.
One of only three Trader Vic's in America.
Oh my God.
And it happens to be there.
So we took our sweet time,
and this wasn't even like an imitation of a tiki bar.
This was like just a legit great, really good Mai Tai,
really good drink made specifically for the San Jose airport.
And we relaxed so much in fact,
that we had a first in our lives,
which is the PA calling us to the plane.
Oh wow.
The airport is like not a big security line,
but we had to sprint across it essentially
after downing Mai Tai's.
Because look, the planes up there are just like,
like a Wednesday 520 flight from San Jose
is like a bus essentially.
Yeah, yeah.
Everybody, let's get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, they'll wait.
They'll wait for you.
Go check the Trader Vic's.
We got another, we got another couple of dirt bags.
Trying to finish their juice drinks.
We know where the dirt bags land.
Wow, you know, you always hear couples counselors
or marriage counselors go like,
you gotta keep it interesting, you know,
especially when you've been together for a long time.
This is what they talking about.
You guys took the ball around with the,
you understood the assignment.
Absolutely.
I mean, look, this entire, it was such a thrill.
Like it, and it felt like a day, you know,
Eva, you set the bar so high.
I mean, this day was like undeniably a spiritual sequel
to what you did with the Doughboys going to Chili's 2
and returning immediately.
So you opened us up to the possibility
that there could be a great day from going to an airport
for an inconveniently, an odd short amount of time.
Oh yeah.
I mean, I mentioned this in the Doughboys podcast
for Chili's 2, but the fact that Nick Weigert
walked on the plane with only his little suitcase
that held his Nintendo Switch.
His tiny Switch it is.
I was like, this is so cool.
And he just like, that's all he carried the whole day.
Yeah.
It's so fun.
It feels so great to just walk on and off of it.
And then like just walk out.
We just walked out of Burbank, parked really close,
got back early in fact.
So we were like, let's just keep this train rolling.
So we went to the Burbank airport Marriott.
Oh yeah.
Home of BugCon, get your tickets.
If you haven't already.
It's the final BugCon.
The last BugCon, you gotta go.
If you haven't, if you've been thinking about it,
clock's ticking.
Another drink there at the weird bar with all the bees.
It's only the aware of the bees.
Buzz, there are bees at this.
But anyway, this was like, this was the greatest day.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you Eva for inspiring it.
Thank you for, thank you to everyone at Delta Car Wash,
Delta Queen Car Wash for all you do.
Boy, incredible.
There's still magic in the world.
I think so, yes.
And you know what?
You know you're gonna find it at a theme park or something.
That's what you expect.
But little touches of it just in Hawthorne
or in Campbell, California,
that's surprises around the corner.
That is how it feels.
It was like the most magical thing since COVID.
It was great.
Oh man, I'm so happy.
There you go.
So, yes.
I have a little surprise for you guys.
Speaking of surprises.
Wow, wow, still bombs getting thrown.
But if you wanna rank.
Pulls out a gun and just kills us.
Oh my God.
Pam, pam, pam.
Doesn't get better than this.
Yeah.
Just Scott.
We'll never top that.
Someone, someone get the SD.
I'm going out high.
Someone get the SD card.
Someone preserve a legacy.
Get this to the Club 3 subscribers.
Oh, rank, I mean, look, I enjoy,
this day was better.
This absolute, the whole day was so much better than like,
if you get to Disneyland and it's so crowded
that you know you're not really gonna get on anything
and it's hot as hell.
We've had worse days at Disneyland than this day
to San Jose, to the car wash and back.
Absolutely.
So this is an A plus plus.
This is the ultimate volcano erupting all over our minds
as highly as I could rank it.
I was, I looked at the map and I was like,
oh man, I wish I had known.
I did drive by this area when we went up to Napa Valley.
And then I realized there's this long stretch
of California where the five and the 101
are miles and miles apart,
but they run parallel to each other.
Yeah.
And a bunch of, we took the five
and a bunch of interesting stuff was like either direction.
And I had a weird moment where I was like,
oh my God, we've been driving forever
and we've only passed P. Soup Anderson's.
And then I discovered, I think there's two P. Soup Anderson's.
There are, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so I, in lieu of this,
for most of the drive, I listened,
I listened to half of Jamie Loftus's Ghost Town,
which is very good.
And then I listened to the cycle of Doughboy's live episodes
with Gabris and Carl Tart,
but I went backwards so they get less fucked up
as it goes along, which was an experience.
That's so fun.
What's going on?
What do you have store for us?
Well, you just gotta, do you compare it to a ride?
Oh, well, it's, I mean, it's easy to say
it's like the Mark Twain, but better.
They finally improved on it
because I can drive my car onto it.
Okay, so this is a surprise for you guys
via my brother Dash, who you guys have met.
Also the person who located the missing Dick Tracy book
and brought one copy of it to Griffin Newman.
Oh my God, wonderful.
Solid dude, listen to the show.
Call my brother Solid Dude, he is.
That's nice, not everybody feels that way
about their brother.
The best.
He, so he was in town last week.
My mom and aunt grew up in a house in,
off Coldwater Canyon that my grandparents bought,
like way, way, way back when.
And they, it's being sold.
And so the fam, we're having to like go through
and clear out all these rooms of things
that have been there forever.
So Dash moved a file cabinet in a back bedroom
and opened a closet that hasn't been opened
for several decades.
Wow.
Oh wow.
And inside he brought, he found this bag,
which is full of gifts for you guys.
What?
Whoa.
The bag itself.
The bag itself is a Living Seas bag.
With the big, with the logo, with the icon of it,
presented by, what is it presented by?
Presented by United Technologies.
United Technologies, cause guys,
this bag is untouched from 1989.
Oh wow.
Do you guys know what happened in 1989?
Yes.
Well, I don't know.
I know some things that happened in 89.
Is that what?
MGM Studios grand opening.
Whoa, cool.
This is stuff from the grand opening of MGM Studios.
Oh my God.
That has been in a closet this whole time.
Sorry.
This.
From the grand opening, wow.
So first of all, you guys all get Mickey toiletry kit.
Whoa.
They all have, they have a, you could.
A comb, a very visible comb.
Yes.
The old, the craziest like chipping plastic.
A comb, wait, this is like a.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, it's a travel toothbrush that says Mickey Mouse
on the side.
And he's in a little sailor suit.
And there's an actual tube of crest as well.
And then there's like a little weird,
it's like a little pill container.
It looks like it's for drugs.
Wow.
There's a face on it.
Oh my gosh.
We're just talking about pill bottles
in that Main Street episode.
Disney pill bottles.
We gotta line up all this to take a picture at the end.
You were there in 89, right?
Yeah, my dad was part of the opening ceremony.
Geez, wow.
Which is, it's all on the video on YouTube.
Like there's a YouTube video of the opening
that I was looking at that has like,
Kevin Costner's here.
Like they just introduce all the people.
Oh, he's in the roll call of like the limos going up.
Were you in the limo?
I must've been, yeah.
I was little.
Wow.
My brother and I were both there.
And yeah.
Oh my God.
Untouched Disney pens.
With every, wow.
These were, I do remember these.
With the variety of Mickey's and that 1986 Mickey.
Oh my God.
That's our guy, yeah.
What a winner, that's our Mickey.
There's three of everything, it's so great.
Three buttons.
How is there the NJM thing?
Wow.
Three of everything.
Jason Hamme.
Geez, this is all, I've never seen a picture
of one of these items.
This is all so legit.
Wow. Wow.
Some crazy postcards.
I remember these pens.
Including a really cool postcard
of the contemporary from the era.
Yeah, wow.
There's just like a bunch of cool postcards.
There's also just like a flower and a Mickey.
Ceramics?
Ceramics. Ceramics.
Ceramics for us.
Yes.
Jeez.
I don't watch these.
But then this is, oh yeah.
And then there's a letter from,
to my three year old brother from Mickey saying,
hi Dash, I'll have a safe trip home, your pal Mickey.
Wow.
But then here's the absolute.
We get this.
He should keep that one from Mickey.
There's a third ceramic.
It's a sleepy.
All right, get it here.
Jason has claimed the sleepy ceramic,
which I think we're not gonna argue with.
No, it's next to me.
And then this is like the craziest thing.
Wait, there's a, before I do the crazy thing,
this is not from that era, but,
I'll do this last.
So this is, whoever's spouse can handle this,
gets to have the Mickey Mouse Club musical mug.
Scott, will you open this package and take the mug out?
Whoa.
But while seated.
So yeah, it's an old school little box
that says Mickey Mouse on the magical,
or musical mug.
With some name on finger on the name.
Yeah, okay.
Mickey Mouse's Club.
Open the box and lift the mug out.
Is he gonna get blasted in the face with something?
Snakes.
Music, I guess.
Real snakes.
Okay.
It still works.
Christ, it still works.
When you lift it up, it plays automatically?
Yeah.
And when you put it down, it stops.
So if you're drinking coffee, it's playing.
And when you set the coffee down, it stops.
The merch was so much stronger
when Michael Eisner was around.
I know, it's like such Eisner stuff.
Jeez.
Oh my God, Eva.
Wow.
I, thank you so much.
This is like a time capsule was.
It really felt like a time,
it was like a 1989 time capsule, it's crazy.
Oh my God.
And Dashill, thank you so much.
Yeah, thank you sir.
I was like, you have to take this to the pub.
Solid dude, that Dashill is.
He's a solid dude.
Solid dude.
And then I just felt like Jason has to have this
even though it's not for a 1989.
What do we got, what do we got?
Here, it's a 50th.
It's an Annie mug from Oval Teen's golden Annieversary.
Oh my God, Oval Teen is celebrating the anniversary of Annie?
Yeah.
You mean Orphan Annie?
Yeah, the comic strip doodle.
Oval Teen, the like milk, the chocolate milk.
I think that's older.
Oval Teen is, you mix it into chocolate,
we look to make chocolate milk.
Yes, no, no, no, I know Oval Teen,
but this is why are they celebrating an Annieversary?
Oh yeah, it's in the bag too.
Yeah, was Oval Teen an original sponsor of Annie
or something, do we know?
I mean, Oval Teen is like the sponsor,
isn't it the sponsor in the Christmas story?
Like it's like don't you ever have to drink your Oval Teen.
They sponsor a lot.
Yeah, just chocolate milk.
Yeah. Wow.
So guys, that was my surprise for y'all.
Oh my God.
Thank you so much.
How was there three of everything?
That's amazing.
This is insane.
It was like, this is so crazy.
The past gave a gift to us.
Yeah, that is.
This is so nuts.
That's some weird time traveler shit.
Yeah.
Oh my God, okay.
Sealed in a hoarder closet.
Well, as if there was any question
about the right decision being made
for the first audience selected Club 3 episode.
Oh my God, what an epic celebration.
Eva Anderson, you survived.
You survived Club 3.
You made it all the way down.
So nice and committed to this podcast.
You made it all the way to the lowest rung.
You've come all the way with like,
spend more time on the second gate than any other guest.
Now you're club, you're maybe the only guest in Club 3.
Oh man.
This is wonderful.
I'm so grateful. Thank you very much.
Grateful to the fans, the listeners.
Thanks so much for having me.
Thank you guys for participating in themed car washes.
Of course, yeah.
Thank you for bringing us.
I can't, then you gave present.
Look, you saved my marriage.
Obviously, obviously on the fritz.
Yeah, but nothing, but that mug is gonna test it.
I know, I was like, whoever gets the mug,
it's gonna be wild.
Good thing you guys got all that energy
from that little jaunt.
The mug's gonna break it.
This is gonna test all of it.
That gave it another six months.
It's either the mug or the assorted items of plastic
that are breaking down.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh yeah, no, they're, yeah, they're.
Will Jason brush with the crest tonight?
Oh, we do brush.
I hear someone's gonna open the crest.
It's so good.
30 year old crest.
I don't know what consistency that ends up with.
Maybe better.
Well, we're the ones exiting through the gift shop,
but would you like to as well?
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
I got no plugs.
Go to a themed car wash, live your life.
Okay. Yeah.
Well, you know, Wee Crash is still up,
and I don't think I've gotten to say to you,
I liked Wee Crash so much.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, check out, it was great work on Wee Crash.
So I'll plug that for you.
Thanks, man.
And audience, you survived the first Club 3
that you selected, the moment of intimacy,
your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
And truly thank you for subscribing to Club 3.
You're keeping this old Delta Queen river boat afloat.
So thank you so much.
Don't forget to vote in the comments
for next month's episode.
And if you just say, do this again with Eva,
we would totally understand.
Watch Butter on streaming services.
Watch Butter.
And I just want to throw out there's a YouTube video.
You don't have to suggest it for next month,
but just Google search YouTube Liberace,
send in the clowns medley.
That's all I'll say.
I think we are allowed to, we can juice the,
we can try to like get our plugs in for what we want.
We can campaign for sure.
I mean, just seeing that the video of the MGM grand opening
with just a parade of stars coming out of limos
certainly sounds intriguing.
But it's up to you, the listener.
It's up to you.
You decide and we, yeah, we will so willingly watch Butter.
Yes.
I'm sorry, spoiled Butter dies.