joints
Born with Northfort
Upbeat music
Started with a complete blues
Alright, nice leisurely Club 3 beginning. None of that pressure, you know?
We get to just like ease into the pool here. Yeah, I like it. This is none of the pressure of having to remember your guys names
We can just start and it's no one needs to know our names
Just like just easing into it like we're all just unclothed easing into a jacuzzi together to hang for two hours
We are recording this at the Los Angeles Los Angeles famous we spa
The spa in Koreatown would someone I think suggested we do as an episode topic
I was confused by that suggestion. Yes a spa is a as a themed experience
It is a themed experience. I think there's some tropical ish rooms
Yeah, I know I think that's actually a good idea. I don't want to do it maybe right now, but eventually I mean
I'm not just the bar with themed car washes of what yeah
Yeah, I don't you'd answered it with their tropical stuff
Yeah
Cuz I when I I was in a I went and got a massage years ago with the Planet Hollywood
casino in
Las Vegas and I remember going into sort of the room with the showers and everything and it felt like I was like
It was with my friend Luke I was like it feels like we're on planet like Vulcan
We're in like some kind of like futuristic kind of otherworldly place in here. I really like this. So okay
Yeah, I think I place making and yeah, so what you're saying is partial nudity feels alien to you
Full nudity feels
Yeah, I was like look at all the dicks around here. This feels like planet Vulcan. This is like the Vulcan
This was a spa not just some particular this wasn't some this wasn't a Star Trek convention after hours
And this was in the Las Vegas Star Trek convention at like 11 p.m
One of the bunch of guys naked wearing the Spock ears
And some some people who decorated their penises the way that they think maybe
Like a Klingons penis would look right what does Klingon circumcision would look like with the war blade that they do it
It's not it's a ritual that we all know
Sure, right
Yeah, yeah
Well, well, okay
Well, there's an idea right there because we have to talk about I don't mean to start these episodes and immediately go to what we're
Doing in the future. No
Yes, how do you decorate your penis properly at a Star Trek convention is a viable topic?
But to talk about a couple other
Topics that came up in this month's poll. There's one I want to say really fast
I'm really excited that people want to hear me do the universal tour
I'm very flattered by that, but I will just say there's bigger plans for the tour down the road
This has been talked about for a while. I don't know when it's gonna happen. I don't know. That's the next year thing
So don't worry. That's that's coming. We don't got a club three it but there is another
thing and
Before we get to Disney dollars, which is which is today Disney dollars was the winner
But we established the rule that the runner-up
Lives to fight another day that they're up in the next round and I just want to say a quick word about
Let me read the full
suggestion from Shane Cannon
Show your penises to each other at Los Angeles is famous. We spa
All right, thank you Shane for that thought and yeah, we're absolutely down and
showing if you want
No, no, no, that's not wait a minute. We're reading the wrong Shane Cannon
Suggested this please discuss the failed Canadian Garfield restaurant
Garfield eats the failed Canadian Scooby-Doo frozen food brand Scooby-Doo eats and the founder of both of them
Archetypal guy quote-unquote and noted hyper narcissist Nathan Masri now
It was too much to put that all I don't know. Maybe we could have put that full text into the poll
I'm not sure but I just left it at failed Canadian restaurant
Garfield eats
never has a
Suggestion called to me so strongly. This is a this is a true siren song
I'd go across the ocean to to discover to learn more about
Garfield this were this really this just this just hit me
I don't know how you guys feel but I wanted to take a second to vouch for
And and look I'll just say I and endorse the idea
Failed Canadian restaurant Garfield eats the reason it's so attractive now on its own Garfield eats Scooby-Doo eats, whatever that sounds great
We would love to look into that when you add in a guy a new guy
Guy using the term guy
Happy makes me so happy to cake. Yeah, so that's why yeah, it sounds so intriguing
We are dying to learn about guys
Yeah
Dying to go into spas and dying to learn about guys
Yeah, and then he that he kept going is what I like. I think there was a minute where I'm I'm loving the polls
I'm fascinated by the moment. I start to watch them and like, okay, this one's breaking ahead
But these two are neck and neck like this
Failed Canadian restaurant Garfield eats was neck and neck with the Universal Studios GameCube game where you have to pick up trash
And I love both of these
I know I didn't want to be fighting for one over the other but then Shane gets in the comments and starts
Campaigning further and I'm gonna read his full quote
But just to again just be I in to further his campaign because this I saw it turn literally he wrote this and then there
Were more votes after it sure way out of the pack
People listen to me. This guy is fucking insane Nathan Masri
He's at fashion cafe levels of insane if not more this story's got everything copyright disputes
Bizarre original characters weird one-off attempts at doing a reality TV thing insane corporate
terminology self-help books
Entergaging digital content that is some of the corporate terminology
He invented the acquibius term of entergaging Wow the deification of Jim Davis
Garfield creator very intense anti-boomer sentiment and more so please please please vote
Garfield my gosh, what a list got more tantalizing than lasagna is the Garfield. Mm-hmm. Yeah. No that sells it pretty well
Yeah, yeah, so we're not gonna tell you what to do
No, you got a pretty big Disney theme park
Pretty pretty bit. It's kind of like a blockbuster like with Netflix
You know surprise it's the Super Bowl and when the game's over you get a new Cloverfield movie on Netflix
You know, I think that's how that release panned out. I may be conflating
I think you're right. I think it was a new color when there's just a big
unavoidable thing in culture like the gray man when there's something that each and every one of us is talking about that's
Dominating every conversation we're having like the gray man is right
Yeah, we run into on the street with our family and friends our parents the milkman
Yeah, the milkman as well tips his cap. We're all little red notice boys
And now we're all little gray men boys and where the boys go now. Where do we go? I think maybe we go to
Orange, I mean I guess we're red. We were little and now we're orange
I guess we backtrack and we've become spider head boys, you know
You guys know spider head spider head is the big budget blockbuster starring Miles Teller
Yeah, and the Hemsworth that play store
It's based on a yes. This is the came from the director of
Mission of top Tom Capric that came out right after and yet. No one was talking about that
Yeah based on a George Saunders short story
I think from right around when he went one of MacArthur genius grant acclaimed author George Saunders and it just
Dropped right as Maverick was in the middle of like demolishing the box office and I have not heard any
Mention of it Wow. Well people are look we we flew with miles
we watched him make the offer we watched him and
Very accurate Al Pacino
Go through all the steps of making the godfather. So maybe people just ready
I can't believe I'm saying this
Maybe people are ready for a little miles break and I just mean for like three weeks
Like it was just weird to do with that. Sure. Yeah, absolutely
We'll be back. Yeah, you know, hey, that'll be one of the topics next time to just talk about Miles Teller
No notes. You don't get notes
You just get to just talk on the top of your heart about your love of Miles Teller free associate
Anyway, are we just like condemning other topics? Yes to the yes. This is oh boy
It is this that maybe this is collusion is this what would you call it? What is I don't think we said any rules
I don't think there's a constitution that we have to abide by no. No, I think we're okay
I think we're not breaking any I don't think so, but do maybe people want to try maybe that will like
Turn against it fight
Again, like maybe people want to try to take it down to slay the beast, right?
I mean, maybe I can just yeah, I mean obviously I threw out the idea that Liberace puppet
ventriloquist performance
Yeah, throw that in so stuff so so yeah, I don't know maybe either people could rally around this or people would feel like you
Can't tell us what to do and then they'll vote that we need to review
Everclear songs from an American movie part two or something. I don't know
That seems like the strategy is gonna be such a grand swell for Everclear songs from American movie party. Yeah
we will see
but I just I just wanted to give that some some time and
And boy, I don't know I when there's a guy calling to you there's a guy
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so leave your comments below what you want to hear if you want to try to if we want to try to take on
Garfield eats. Mm-hmm
But I don't know babe best of luck to you're gonna be you could be the spider head going up against the top gun
It's gonna be like a midnight and like a patreon club 3 subscriber
Well, their phone will ring and it'll be an unknown number and it'll be a muffled voice
And go look I just need you to do the right thing here
I need you to vote for the right thing and like Scott is that you and then the hang up and then that'll happen with
Everyone and I know we're very loyal. I know we're very smart
50 extra looking for all I'm looking for is
200 extra votes for Garfield eats and if it doesn't work, you know what you're gonna do you have to send Rudy out
And he'll find him
Crack team that's right
It's done somehow and if not, we'll get our revenge in four years
Damn it you pay him and Rudy will go and try to get people to vote for Garfield
He doesn't give a shit as long as he's good thinks he's getting money. Oh, that's true. Yes
All right, if somebody sends this to Rudy Giuliani, yeah
Your starting rate will be three thousand dollars an hour right money that you will definitely receive and Rudy if you don't take it
You know Robert Davi will that's true
What did Robert Davi do for I don't know. He's just kind of a Trump guy. Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, he's a sleaze
I didn't but I was like, babe. Was he actually deployed along with the sit down?
I don't even really believe it. Yeah, I don't he might have been working pro bono, you know trying to get in the yeah
Well for you working for exposure
He's working for exposure to get in the like whatever the Hollywood version of like pure flicks. Whatever you call their
the Kirk Cameron movies
The Gina Carano ex-kirk Cameron movies
He'd be in as the king of the heavies if he's already doing stuff like that. I forgot. What is he famous for him again?
Why do we know Robert Davi like old like he was just I think he was a supporting actor in some movies
There's like a big one. It's like under siege or something like that big action. I don't remember
Has a license to kill. Yeah
Okay
Records probably goonies. Yeah, that's what I yeah because he did a he did a funnier die video and part of the
stipulation was that he
Get to it some like turn to camera and say and buy my album Davi does Sinatra
Always in die hard. No first I heard. Yeah. Oh, yeah. That's like a number one. I think
I believe that's either funnier and I'm remembering season music if you can believe that something that a very Trumpy guy is also
Is it?
Okay, threat Trump fan and creep. Can you do you believe it's possible?
I hard believe
Okay, we are here to talk about the today's time. Let's focus on today's topic
Which was which one after the previous round?
It came back and got it
Suggestion from JF co the original crypto Disney dollars company script
Corporate script as Wikipedia points out. This is company money
Yeah, yes. This is a private company in the world making their own money
For you the the consumer to spend because there's another I think there's a tie
I don't know the ins and outs of script. I remember this idea existing at school
But there's like script that you give to your employees
Yes, that's now what's happening here because we are the customers and we can choose to get their script the
like like
miners
Mining companies would pay their you know, it's kind of stranded in homestead like kind of can't leave the wilderness
miners in company script that you could use at the company store. Oh
I see so it's like if Amazon paid in Amazon bucks their employees which we're not that far off, you know
No, well, wasn't this the Elon Musk's revolutionary plan is that you get you go to Mars and you get paid in Mars bucks
Well, I yes you get paid a Mars bucks and you work off your trip to Mars. Yes
Yeah, everyone on Mars is an indentured servant. Mm-hmm
Yeah to their well-toned boss God Elon Musk
Yeah, he had the many secret babies
That's most either people reinventing the concept of buses or reinventing like slavery
Mm-hmm. They all figure it out. They'll crack it. He had to bring it into the 21st century, right?
Yeah, just with a spacey futuristic twist and it made sense that they would be the whitest man
The you know, the literal whitest man you've ever seen a white South African who could have foreseen
Who could have foreseen that coming?
Look, this is not malicious like that. I don't know think Disney dollars
I was like I was waiting for in look I'm we're gonna learn about Disney dollars
I think I was waiting for the malicious turn and I don't think I found it other than it's like a way for Disney to
Make lots of money by making money literally
But that's isn't this what they do?
All the time and now they do it in these ways that are dull and not ways where you get
Fun looking money. I think it looks fun, right? I always liked it. Oh, I loved it. I definitely had some Disney dollars
It was a fun like little souvenir
It was a fun like way of like, okay, you have five Disney dollars to use on souvenirs. Like how are you gonna use it?
It was a good it's a good little
practice money
Situation for kids. Yeah, and I would always say I mean I definitely have some at my mom's house of the the blue and pink
$1 one the early generation ones
But I researching this I saw somewhere I was like I had no idea about some of these designs
Well, yeah, I was shocked as well. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they went into what 2014
2016 Wow. Yeah, that's pretty far. So that's time to incorporate
Lots of characters into the fold. Oh, yeah does not have to stay at Mickey goofy many
No, a lot how many friends started to appear? Yeah, it could be Iron Man at that point and all his his friends
And I found a page there is still a page on the Disney World website of how to use Disney dollars
Because while they do not print them anymore
They still accept them as legal tender at the domestic parks in America
Okay, Disney Cruise Line some locations at Castaway Key
You can be a swimmer. You're on the private island
You're swimming around and you can have Disney dollars with you to bartender and Disney dollars and Castaway Key
That is my one one of my questions I had was there a high roller
You know people if they're playing blackjack or or poker and they they throw a chip when they're leaving for to tip the dealer
You always got to tip your dealer. Yeah, we're there where their Disney lounge lizards
Who would like tip the bartender and Disney? I'm sure there's no way there weren't right? Yeah, no way there weren't
I don't not good. That's not good. Now. We're in this now. We're in this I mean, I think well you could you could redeem the dollars at least
Seemingly pretty easily for regular American currency
Yes, I think you I think completely the the extent of your Disney dollar day could be hey
I have these can I get money for them? Yeah, so you could do that
But it's just with the somebody you're tipping you're just adding another step they have to do but maybe they had it in the register
I don't know that's so maybe they don't make the exchange themselves. So who knows? Yes, but yes, there's got to be like
Weirdo Disney people that keep the keep a keep a Mickey for yourself
Did anyone bribe someone with Disney dollars now that's a question
Oh boy, like can you get us to the front of this? Can you get us the front of phantasmag? If you know what I'm saying?
There's a Captain Jack Sparrow in it for you
Or there's a pirate skull whatever it was. There's like a skull logo
Disney dollar. Did you see those the pirates? Yeah, the movie one. Yeah, I read the movie parts of the Caribbean
Yeah, a Disney dollar. Yeah, I bet somebody did
Try to bribe someone with that before did anyone I know this is a thing in Vegas
I've never tried it. I want to try it. Do you know about the $20 trick?
when you put the $20 in like your
Slide use a slide trick. We're trying to bribe somebody right? It's even easier
It's when they say can I just need to when you're checking into hotel?
Yeah, they say I need to see an ID and your credit card
You put the 20 between them and you ask are there any upgrades available?
Okay, but there's mixed reviews some people
Works others say like if you're staying at like win or
Win or encore or like a Bellagio or something
There's high role like those are high-end places. You might have to try a 50 or a hundred
Too rich for my blood, but I do want to try you've never tried the 20 trick
No, I want to I do want I want to and I wonder if people try it at Disney
I've never tried it Disney, but I did try to tip the person was really nice who checked me in when I stayed at
pop century and
They were with the college program and I asked them about it and I tried say I said thank you
And I tried to tip them they're like, oh front desk. We can't take tips
I was like, come on. You're in the college for come on. I know they don't pay you a lot like I and she's like no
I'm sorry. I can't interesting. So that 21
$20 a trick won't work probably Disney. Yeah, I don't know about that
But if you're gonna do you're gonna try this and they you're going to Vegas. I am going to Vegas
I am going to try it. What tell right? Huh? What hotel? I don't know when this episode is coming out. That's after that
park MGM
Make sure it goes out tonight now. Yeah, I'm gonna put this episode
No, it's not not the month yet. It's not the right month yet. You're fine
Are you seeing so so in or get in a car get to Vegas and this is your chance to see Jason
Yeah, are you seeing soul sonic? What are you doing? What are you doing there? Sole son? Oh the
Yeah, yeah
It's great. Yeah, I bet it is great. I think it's 250 at least you're in for 250 if you want to sit anywhere good
But it's probably awesome. Oh sure
So try the tree this is wild. Not bad. Yeah, we'll try that night. No, but it'll be in September
Yeah, the Aerosmith will be back
So, okay to try the 20 trick
Yeah, see if you can get into our show back
I I have heard people say like if they're not down for it
They'll just say thank you, but I there's nothing available right now and give you the 20 back. Okay. Yeah
I think it would be really funny if they kept the 20
Said there's nothing available. I would be laughing the whole trip
Yeah, sure not like
Furious months later, I'll be furious
It's like gambling you know, you only gamble with money you're willing to lose sure, you know, of course, yeah, yeah
But this money this not this
Sort of fake money except not I guess it's not I mean like that
I mean, I think that the thing that makes this stand apart
Where it's not just a fancy way of doing gift cards is that the legal tender nature of it?
Yeah
And it is that they went all these steps to make it like real money to print it in a fancy
Manner that there are the security measures. Yeah, they really did this up like cereal numbers
What yeah serial numbers here on the various raised the paper is raised
So it's like you can tell if it's fake or not I recall the the texture of it
I remember it feeling you know, it's yeah, it's elevated. It's better
It's better than just a piece of paper. Oh, yeah was I don't I think my this is my memory of it
That I always wanted Disney dollars, but my mom was like why we just use our money. Let's use our money
Very good question. You're like extremely good quiz like we don't want to get stuck with a bunch of Disney dollars
So I was just like, oh, come on. I want fun money. I want characters
I know I don't want yeah fucking presidents who gives a shit but Mickey. Yeah, Mickey on my money makes sense
but but the more I think about it like
When you had it, do you remember like where you know money is dirty and gross was who are Disney dollars
Do you remember were they like fresh crisp or were they like?
Oh, yeah, this has been in somebody's pocket for six months. Maybe they didn't I don't think they were giving them out as chain
I think they maybe had one turn around the horn. Okay, cuz I wasn't sure about that up
I just don't remember seeing a dirty Disney dog
It makes sense that they didn't give you a dirty Disney dollar
But I don't think that yeah, I don't think they're handing you and the one and two and three
But I didn't see it when I was was looking through this stuff
I was like, I'm not sure cuz I
Imagine yes, they would be like if some Disney dollar looked like it had been to the mill like there no way
They're handing out to a guest. Yeah
No, I think they're keeping it crisp it's like the parks themselves like they've always got a look spick and span right?
Make sense. Yeah, you don't want you don't want to start getting it's like phone numbers
Written on it and like, you know
Crude objects or body parts pointed into our favorite characters. No, that's true. No, we don't want that mommy my my
Disney dollar says
Clinton crime family on it. What does that mean?
Yeah, no, so so I don't know I
Wonder I'm sure they would have to yeah, Disney would have to take a dirty Disney dollar
But they would not ever hand up a dirty thing. So and they're brighter. They're brighter than dollars
They were also slightly larger than us
Okay, more difficult to fit in your wallet. Yes. I kind of remember that I remember the envelopes
I remember the envelopes are very reminiscent of the old Disney store with kind of the like the very like 80s pink stripes
Yeah, and I remember them existing. There's you ever seen an original in there. Oh, there's the envelope
Yeah, someone is selling on eBay this one which comes with the envelope and this I had never seen before this is a
2000 it's got the 2000 Epcot ball on it. Okay. Yeah, they would do like anniversary
Batches, which I know I don't remember seeing any of these like these other ones. I just remember
Classics. Yeah. Well, it's if this was happening now
Jason I think especially would be on the blogs being like, oh my god
Did you see what they're putting out like you got to see this like lightning McQueen has his own Disney dollar
We got to go down and get the new dollar. Yes
Yeah, if it was happening now, even though it was happening while we were still obsessed with other stuff
But we just weren't it wasn't on our radar. It didn't occur to me. I think that it was still going
In the 2010s and it also didn't occur to me that like it was over until they're like yes done
We're not doing it anymore. I do think if he wants a cheap win a cheap pop Bob Bob
Chay Peck if Bob Chay Peck was like we're bringing back Disney dollars. I think people would go like yes
I think so. I think yeah, even though it's just a literal like financial exchange. Yeah
It's something about I don't know it's just more friendly and
Silly than a lot of the other stuff lately
The one dollar bill has the big red panda from turning red and the five dollar bill has Grogu baby Yoda
And people are just like oh my god
I'm carrying a wallet. I'm using cash again and then ten dollars has George Clooney from Tomorrowland on it. Oh, yeah
beloved three beloved characters what else would it
Starts in May 1987 we start with Mickey on the one goofy on the five
1990 mini joins on the ten and I think other denominations
Showed up after so maybe talk about the the starting
Of it. J.C. You were alluding to there's there's a couple versions of the story of why they started doing this
Yeah, you were saying one of them. I
The name I kept coming across was Harry Bryce who was credited as the silhouette cutter on Main Street and
He went to a Disney Anna convention, you know collectibles and tchotchkes and stuff
And he was like man people are spending money hand over fist on this stuff
What if they just what if we had what if Disney just had their own money?
Mm-hmm people would probably and he is probably it this story is probably, you know apocryphal
But like he is right and I'm sure there was the thought of and then people are gonna collect those dollars
In addition to using them as dollars and he's right because I have been to there's a Disney on a convention every now
And then I'd like the Anaheim Wyndham and there are vendors gone to that. I went to one of these a few years ago
I haven't been back but I get their postcards every few months
and
One or two of the vendors just has binders and binders of brochures napkins Disney dollars
There's like all paper product vendors. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Well and then just also as far as
the idea of gift cards alone
Gift cards are I believe a very big moneymaker because there's some percentage of gift cards that just go unused
So it's a really good way for businesses to make money in general because if you
Force people to have to spend the money at a business
Oftentimes people will forget or they will lose the gift card and I don't know what the percentage is
But it's a very good moneymaker for for a lot of businesses because they will not have to redeem all of the money
That people are putting into their gift cards
I saw a number a guess from a Disney executive about how much money there is in unspent
Disney dollars
Disney dollars that were never put back into so that are sitting somebody's drawer
20% I don't think or not a percentage just a number
How much money did Disney make on Disney dollars that were never given back to them one million dollars?
25 million dollars two hundred
Two hundred
Millions and millions of bill of literal bills. Yeah. Yeah, we probably had it seems very positive
I thought before this I should probably go check my my childhood bedroom
Yeah, because some of the intent of it was like I'm not gonna sell this and this is like
If we keep it crisp, that'll look nice later
I feel like there was the intent to oh, let's see if it accrues value
Which I they have but not to like I still don't know how you're like
I don't but there are probably people who've made good money
Well, if you the Disney dollar collecting if you look on eBay, I feel like it's like maybe three times
What the currency says around that?
I think even well, I mean I kept seeing like there's depending on what it is for sure
So the the 2001 that comes with an envelope
I think that was going for like 30 bucks on eBay. They go for even more on
Hold on. I gotta find these website names. They're so good
Those are like Disney collectible specific. No, no the bank note collecting websites
So they go for even more on bank note world calm and they're really high on boolean sharks
And I gotta say once I started digging in it reminded me I love little peaks into niche areas of
collecting
That I I I just get the gist of it and it's like there is a whole other world
He little terminology little terminology
Damages and little like nicknames for things and it's joyless
It's not they have not had fun doing this for decades some of them
But some of them are probably slogging through it. Yeah
Yeah
The what is it their departure website our departure board calm?
I think is the website I found and they talk about like you want to buy a bank note album
Okay, and you'll either get like a three slot
Pages or two slot pages now that Disney dollars are a little bigger
So you probably want a two slot page and you don't want steer clear of PVC
Polyvinyl chloride because it can degrade the notes the album below is made of
Museum quality PVC free acid free material and you got a new mess. It's a new miss brand
So, you know, you're not willing to pay for new miss then don't then stay out of the game
Yeah, just throw it in a garbage can light it on fire. You know, why bother?
Do you have one of those in your bag here that you're gonna show us?
I started I was gonna say and they couldn't bring a new miss out in the elements. Yeah, you're right
That's to the human
Yeah, you want to keep that room completely perfectly climate controlled. Yeah. Yeah, give it its own room get it
Yeah rent an apartment with a bedroom that you only put your new missus in no PVC a mile mile nearer
That's restraining order against
Absolutely
Yeah, no, it's this very specific word, but it's I clearly like patience required to
Get it up to the point where it's making you
Because that this is one of the things I wanted to I was wondering about is this initiative this premise from
JF co who suggested the original crypto is there is there any truth to this?
How does it compare contrast to crypto now?
Here we have it
There is a very literal people have it as a crew like I kept it and then in the years since now
I'm able to sell it for this on eBay. So there's growth there. So here's what it is
Here's what I would say comparing it to even of any currency
The big thing with Bitcoin that people say is good is that there's a finite amount
You can never print you can never make more
so
Mm-hmm
so it will accrue value because because the like, you know when inflation happens stuff oftentimes is because
We've printed a lot of money in like American currency
so I feel like Disney dollars became more like Bitcoin once they stopped making them because there is a finite amount now that's
processed like
So the real they made that shift exactly
Yeah
So now it is a little bit more like that when there is a fun unless they start printing again
Which I guess always possible right now. There is a certain fixed supply now. We don't know what it is
I'd be interested to know how many dollars exactly were printed. Do we know that I don't okay?
Somebody might and if somebody should know it if they go through the records, but so again, I cite our departure board.com
As a full list of Disney dollars that are like the letter are
Our departure board
Pirates oh
You are departure board. They have a list. I don't know if it's I'm sure it's not everyone in circulation
I think it's all the serial now all the varieties. Yeah, and you can have that document for 750
Seven dollars fifty cents. Oh, okay, and it says all the varieties that have ever been made
I believe that's what it is, but it doesn't say how many of each have been made or does it?
Well, if it's got the serial number ranges, I guess you could then
Do the math. Oh
I see. Yes, that's you're right. If it does have the serial number we could figure it out
We have to get our hands on this document those go from zero zero one two
Yeah
Number things I know okay, so there's this the serial numbers sequence of numbers
There is a letter at the beginning and at the end the one at the end doesn't seem to mean anything
the
Prefix which is the letter at the beginning?
Tells you where this dollar is made for
ABE was for Disneyland D F is for Disney World
T was for the Disney Store
This is similar to if you look at a dollar bill
There's a letter on the serial number that tells you what meant that dollar bill comes from there's like a dozen
Or no, I think there's seven or eight big mints across the country
So on the letters the letters on a dollar bill go through like a through
Whatever it is J or K. Maybe it's 12 so you can get a full set of like eleven dollars
One from each of the mints does that make sense?
If you're a money collector you look at the serial numbers and you can tell like oh I want to have
Yeah, something from this bill for me a year from every mint. Yes, uh-huh, right and then you put it in your thing
What is it called?
banknote no, but the book the book the
Was it cold? Oh
Forgot already new miss new miss. Thank you. Okay. I need to write these things new man for future
Everything new miss the phrase I was trying to remember was philatist which is stamp collector stamp collecting
Wait is a philatist philatist
Ph it does sound probably saying it wrong
Phil at e li st
Mm-hmm
Philat I mean, how would you sure are we sure on that pronunciation?
I was reading the dictionary calm
the
phonetic
The philatist. Yes, that's not can that be real Israel? I mean, I know that's the word
fully
flately lately specialty in flately. Yeah
for lately for lately
Wow
Yeah, how else are you gonna pronounce that word?
I had like two losses a little kid where I went maybe I'll collect stamps
I am going to be a flattest mother
They put out the Elvis stamp and I was like, maybe I'll collect stamps. I just started taking them off
Letters that had been sent like birthday cards
Only like a quarter of them were new stamps and then a bunch of them were just to use stamps
I was like, yeah, I think I'm done with this and then every few years I'm like, oh, I gotta get the Pixar stamps
I gotta get the Bugs Bunny stamps and then they sit on my desk and then I go like why I need to use
Stan I need to mail thing like I'm not gonna save the wall
You've made attempts at being a philatist. Yeah, but then it's like well, I gotta pay my tax
So Bugs Bunny and the mermaid Bugs Bunny is going to the government. So he drafted in. Yeah
latest I mean for a for a
Hobby that you would get made fun of for for it to have that name is pretty insane
A hobby that you would get picked on for being like a nerd is pretty crazy that that's that's the word to describe
Yeah, that's one you only use among, you know fellow travelers
So, you know, that's you don't use that you don't tell your kids at school that you know
Are we we're missing an L guys, isn't it?
philatelist
Philly which I think helps it
Philatelist is what I'm seeing unless that's a different. Okay. I guess yeah, here we go
I think that I think the L does a lot of heavy lifting. We're not it. We're not in the fellatio realm
Of course it has an L
That's madness
Do it how to pronounce sing on and it's
From it we just wasted
Philatelist here's the thing from the latest to philatelist in the course of a few minutes
My god, I love this
No, did you wait a minute? Did you have the L in your notes or to bail?
No, I mean I was looking at the like upside down letters spaced out
Pronunciation and I just kind of was a typeface. Yeah
Yeah, that list is in there philatelist
Yeah, philatelist now here's a quick now
We say a lot the people are screaming into their phones the right thing on this now
I would be shocked if there's more than one person listen when I look at the philatest philatelist it says for lately
so
Dam collectively, so it's philatelie. So that's where I thought
So it's fuzz. It's a pH. So I don't think we're not even pH is fair. Yeah, it's pernet
Yeah out loud. It works better than written. Yeah, I'm looking I'm staring at the written word philatelist and I see no issues here
No, you're right now that when I'm looking at the actual word, it's not that's if I scroll lower. Yeah. Yeah, you're correct
I don't think we're gonna have stamp collectors mad at us
I think we're gonna have trivia experts mad at us to like know this term because it was his jeopardy answer
It was a bar trivia scrabble. Oh scrabble is a good one
A lot of points on that only you don't if you won a game with philatelist that might be the only way
This is in your head. I've looked up philatelists
And I don't think that's actually a word so we'll be okay. All right
There's something that says diary of a voracious philatist
But I'm not
A film
What media are we talking? It's a live journal I think oh
Jesus that could go any direction. I'm not gonna read it. I don't want to just think this is called three
I understand but then that club random, okay, we're not gonna get that saucy
But
Let's how let's let's get back into the realm of dry and talk about an old man who used to run the
Disney Jack, no, not Jack
Here we go an hour but now we're gaining steam where they were going down the roller coaster Jack Lindquist everyone's saying this was a
I always liked the vibe of this guy
This is like this seems like a nice old man who was the it wasn't always old I guess but he was part of Disneyland
From like just a few months in he was working for another company
And then he visited Disneyland while I was getting built and he said he fell in love with the place
So then somebody from Disney called him asking for somebody who's good at marketing and he said what about me?
And he was there just a few months later
And then that led to a career that ended in him being the president of Disneyland the first
President of Disneyland there was no such thing as this. He's like kind of like that winky old man
Does he do what I'm saying? Like he kind of has that little wink charm
Does it make sense? I need a little more context. Are you saying?
Winking or a wink Martindale? No, not wink Martindale. I'm saying like, you know kind of that like I'm an older man
Hey, how are you doing there slugger winking when you say that?
Yeah, wink mean he's a folksy kind of guy. There's nothing malicious about no. No, I think it's a pure
It's a way it's like a sparkle in his eye. He's like an old st. Nick like
He has a st. Nick
We're saying refresh my memory
When we did the Toontown episode was he the one at the ground break the older guy at the groundbreaking saying this is a very exciting
Endeavor yes. Yeah
You seem to think someone was weird about I think you didn't like him is what I remember
Oh, it was weird about that speech
I forget there was something about the speech that might have bumped for me and I but I don't remember what it was now
Mm-hmm. I think maybe it was
the like
Background guys the guys dressed as like costume construction guys and like
They were sweeping or they did his intro really weird. I don't know if it was him
I think so. I think that's right. He would have been open. He like is he still there, you know
They look like probably retired right before Indiana Jones open
But he was there when they started building it was pushing ties nerd
You got to do a second park and was still alive
To say and then that led to California adventure, which I didn't think was very good
Yeah, then he's been said but I liked the you know when then cars land and they figured it out
But he was still as there's a lot of the old Disney hands we're gonna run for a while. Yeah, sure
Yeah, he got out cut out on top. I feel like feeling period
He didn't like yes, unlike, you know people in the Senate. He enjoyed some retirement
He didn't just like well, yeah, like drive his brain into them into mush and oh, yeah better
Like what if I leave when I'm happy and everybody's happy to see me?
Your golden years like chewing down warm corner bakery salads like
What a way to go
This guy brought a lot of things to the park grad nights. He's attributed to having invented
Wait, did I not say this is Disney dollars are associated with him?
This is like we considered one of their things that he yeah, there was some brought some there was some I was a video
Which video does so but like this I've heard that the guy talked about that story about the silhouette painter
But also then like some people think it was just Jack who did it. It was Jack's idea
I really listen to the recall on or this part was intense on Mouse Planet where
The writer and his Jim Cork has said
He says he thought of it not the silhouette guy and this wouldn't this is not a man who I think would lie
He's a straight shooter and I take him at his work. So they're calling out maybe silhouette guys alive
So so I don't be a liar quirk is still he digs deep
I mean he seats has done a lot of Disney history stuff. He came up on the contemporary episode. Mm-hmm
Mm-hmm. So he might know I
If you looked him in the eye with Santa lie to you would old st. Nick tell you a fib
I don't think so. I don't know somebody who's winking all the time. That's fine. That's true
I'm waiting for me in a lot of things. I suppose not sure like oh, yeah, I invented did he Disney dollars wink
I
Guess that's a different right there all those winks. Yeah
He invent, you know, he did like any of those anniversaries the 30th and 35th where they're given cars away
That was all this doing they didn't really celebrate anniversaries. That was something that occurred to him
Why don't we we need little reasons to like that's such a funny thing that they didn't and that's the one guy thought of it
Yeah, now everybody does that every place every part excuse any yes. Yeah. Yeah feels like something
Alright, right. He even was like he said like people don't really celebrate 30th
Anniversaries and whatever who cares. Let's try it and we're great. All those were really fun. Yeah
Disney dollar anniversary anniversary Disney dollars specifically. Oh, that's right. It all tied together because he did
Yeah, here's a print for the 35th or for the 50th or whatever. Yeah
Another weird thing I found out about Jacqueline quest is from theme park insider
something that he was doing in the 70s was
spearheading the initiative to get different countries to participate in
World showcase to have a little pavilion version of the country in Epcot and
The interviewer asked what was your favorite thing you got to do as part of that and he said well
I'd have to be when I spent those five weeks in Iran. I
When I spent so much time with the Shah with the Shah of Iran
meaning Muhammad Reza who was the
The last Shah of Iran because when so Jacqueline quest is hanging out with him
And they're talking business about the little theme park that maybe they'll do and then a year later
He is deposed in this huge crazy
Revolution. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah the shop famously a brutal man
famously brutal ruler installed by the
United States
intelligence agencies helping along
He I think are
Probably when jet when old Jack is talking to him about and then there'll be maybe a boat ride about the history of
Persia and the heat they had that ball ago interesting. I like that
Maybe I don't want to get wet. This is happening and he has like
50,000 prisoners of war like political prisoners
He's torturing also as in this year because it's okay. So all these meetings are a year with a year to go
Before he's
Exiled and then he dies a year later
Cancer is ravaging is by horrible horrible cancer is ravaging his body and he's still taking the time to like
Maybe a restaurant would you know, we're gonna have a Ben Franklin animatronic. You should see it sometime
His idea is kind of cross-boundary, you know borders and you know, it's styles of government
Everyone could learn a thing from mr. Franklin
It's called future worlds and you'll be able to see it
Yeah, okay. Well, what sorts of hats do you like here where I could see our way into putting Donald in one?
Sounds good. Hang on. I'm being called to the other room
Grenades who is this ayatollah character?
Jack
The ayatollah is asking for me one second
I have been putting off this call for weeks
Jack's just like sitting there like not paying attention. What's going on the back room?
You eating it like a Mickey ice cream bar and like just like smiling
Exit from
Iran was very much like Argo sort of situation, but it was more mr. McGooey
Yeah, I was just enjoying it's like I really come come to like rosewater and in food
For those usual sounds on the plane and it was like it's like the entire city is exploding behind. Yeah
Great big beautiful tomorrow. I love that song. Don't you? Yeah, then weeks later what happened in Iran?
I guess we won't be putting that in the ride. Oh good golly. I had no idea
That was the nicest looking hotel we had drawn up shame
You know that too. He's trying to figure out the Persian Hotel. Oh, yeah
Really weird so look Jack was was everywhere and coming up with great ideas and hanging with great people
And that kind of came he traveled so much and he said I was flying back from a trip to Europe
And I was going through my change and there's there's Franks and Deutschmarks and pounds and I thought you know some of these countries
We just visited they you know, we do more people per year than their population. So why can't we have a currency?
It is it is right it is funny it is also like we are
Very powerful and we should have our own money there is that's also part of it
I suppose it's that you could now it's this is the other if now shape back did it
Then like the the Santa's faction would all be so enraged
Oh, yeah, yeah as if this hadn't happened in the 80s. All right, right
This would be used as the sign of their out of their mind
Well, you know, they'll be saying, you know, this is the great reset Disney is gonna accelerate the great resets of the word New World Order and
That's what is the great reset
Believe it's like where you like everyone's currency goes to see I could I really actually don't know
but it's like a full reset of the like worldwide economy and and global politics and yes, it's sort of a I
Guess it's a fringe idea, but I wouldn't be shocked if it was like 15% of people in America are worried about it
Yeah, I mean there's also along the same lines. I bet some of the same there's some crossover with the people who
Do you guys know about the denar the Iraqi denar?
So this was this was a currency in Iraq
and
It essentially became worthless after Saddam, I think was deposed
Or maybe it's the current currency in Iraq. I forget very low exchange rate, but
People were buying it up in droves because they thought Donald Trump was going to
Go like one Iraqi denars now worth one US dollar so they would have stacks and stacks of denars. Oh
That would were worth people were doing this
Trump judge Trump people like the same people Americans are buying people who are complaining about the gold standard
Okay, and just tweeting at Donald Trump every day. Mr. Trump, please
RV I feel like they would say RV the denar and that was some term of like reset it
Reset and make it worthwhile
It's some of them may have been soldiers in Iraq and just got out with a lot of denars and they're like I know
They've got a lot of work. It's like Confederate money. It's worthless
Yeah, it says Donald Trump supporters think the president will make them rich if they buy Iraqi money. Yes, 2018
So, you know
So there's a couple yeah a couple things going on. So yeah, if Disney all of a sudden today did their own currency
Yeah, they would think that they were like this is part of it. This is book and speed. Yeah
This is money for pedophiles only or something. This is pedophile money that if we don't have the you need the right kind of
Blacklight you bright you get through if you get a lot like you have to switch it between
Three different types of black light really fast and then you'll see like the secret symbols
Right the American dollar and the American dollar will be worthless in five years
But the the money with Mickey will be that will be the one that will be the world currency in five to ten years
It's a Disney dollars. So we'll have to go to their parks and yeah learn their agenda. Yeah, they're fascist pedophile agenda, right?
Yes, that's right. It's both of those things. Yep. Same time. So yeah
Yeah, it would be interesting if they try if they did it
They bring it back because people yeah people will go nuts
But I honestly the stuff we're saying there will be article people will be Alex Jones will be saying the things we're saying about
Disney dollars. Yeah, that's not crazy
That will go on
The the way that Disney dollars arrived on scene
There is some like odd kind of real-world intensity
To it. Yeah, anybody see the video Scrooge maybe
Yes, because this is important the Disney dollars are signed by the treasurer Scrooge McDuck. Yes, that's so everyone
No matter what character is on it. Scrooge McDuck is considered the official Disney. Yes
And so and Tinkerbell usually is on the front
Uh-huh kind of like, you know symbols their symbols on our US dollars Tinkerbell is the symbol
If Mickey even Mickey's not on it
There's some sort of character or landmark on it and there's a Scrooge McDuck signature, which is pretty funny
That's a pretty good detail. Yeah. Yeah, I do like that
And not only that but on this particular day on the launch in May 1987
He showed up in person
In duck to make the first handoff
Earlier today an armored truck arrived
Scrooge McDuck McDuck is the Disney dollar treasurer and after he made the drop-off
The Magic Kingdom money became available to every Disneyland guest
including Tom DeArcey who came to Disneyland all the way from Pennsylvania to buy over
$2,000 worth of Disney dollars
This guy's getting huge stack
But the point that why I wanted to show that and I'll post that somewhere is that that it's a that an armature that a Brinks
Truck arrives pulls up into the end of the hub or not the whole whatever the plaza
Scrooge McDuck gets out has a big sack and just kind of smacks it onto a ticket counter
really aggressively and follows that up with just kind of like a smack of the just pounds the
Really like aggro a real aggro move from this old duck. Yes. It's very
Violent I love any especially funny because he's four feet tall. He's very barely gets above that counter
And he's a giant old duck. Yes
And then there's a man who appears to have backpacks from Pennsylvania like that's a hiking backpack
Yeah, he's got a he's got a funny vibe. Yeah, he looks like when Mark Parosh was the yo-yo guy
Talking about yes for any old backpack. Yeah
stack of
Two grants somebody I think bought
Ten grand the first day some people were saying this is my kids college fun
This is like there were there were high you know for what which you never I don't know
Maybe if they held out and are these the people who were making these eBay transactions or these
Our financial ladder I forget the name forgetting all the specifics if you can imagine I would yeah
I would love to hear their plan at the time because obviously like I
When you go to the airport or when you fly overseas, there's always you know conversion rates between currencies between so like were they hoping?
That that would have what something would happen. We're like Disney dollars would decouple from the US dollar
Like what was their long-term plan here for this being?
What's the man in that like the dollar would have to weaken?
Yeah, the Disney dollar is so strong right then you just you say you can live like a king, right?
But I don't think in America. It's possible. I don't think that's possible unless
Disney was using Disney dollars for everything they were doing they were paying the government and Disney dot like yeah
You would have to be yes all of their money would have to be and you couldn't like cuz you all the exchanges happen in
Disneyland or Disney Disney stores so you would have to
Like they you have to be like the cashier is like crying or don't make me hand you this cat
We can't afford this. Yeah, so we're just we're hemorrhaging money if uh, uh, yeah
Cuz I would know to go back to the crypto Disney dollars when they were printing them
I think were pegged to the that's the phrase pegged to the US dollar
So if the US dollar appreciated or depreciated Disney dollars would go up or down
So I think the only time that they would have ever
Gained value would be now when they were years ago when they stopped printing them when it's speculators when now space
Are selling them on the secondary market?
Right and it's mostly for kitschy weirdos who want to do that. I guess but
Money isn't real anyway
So you're saying not just not since they got rid of the gold standard. That's a good gold standard. That's right
Well, so I don't know how it worked out for the ten grand
I don't see they they they made more than two million dollars worth in the in the first round
The the first run the first run of it was it was a guy who just bought
$75 worth a
Buena Park hairdresser and he left with and Mickey came out and shook his hand and I mean that makes it work
He's and he got a plaque and the first Disney dollar was
Embedded in it. So I think he won because he spent less money
It's not like they gave the plaque to the ten grand guy spent 75 bucks and he got to meet Mickey and get a plaque
That's pretty good. Yeah, it's pretty good. I I'm realizing a flaw as we talked about
Change that if you have a $10 Disney dollar and you bought a $5 toy
Or let's say a five
That cost five dollars and sixty cents with tax
You are getting coins back
Yeah, American currency are getting probably American regular currency. I guess you could get four Disney dollars and forty cents
That's probably if you wanted it, they probably give you the option
Depending on if they had the the change
This is something that occurred to me as a weakness in this whole thing. This is fun
We got ones and fives and then tens and twenties. Where are the coins?
Where the Disney we like our tokens we we liked the coin from
Zalem from a lead of battle. Oh, yeah. Remember the coin from Zalem. Yeah
I still have my coin yet. It's worth the money. Yes
I probably had anybody with 80 bucks. I think she's really at least a year or two ago
Who's the kings of silly money now?
It should have been coins though, obviously like well and I maybe this is this might be worth a little thought
If these are just equivalent is it penny nickel?
dime well, so
Here's what I was they supposedly they were floating the idea of doing three dollar bills and seven dollar bills initially
Yes, I love that. That's so funny. It's so funny and they should have done it because well why though because of
character yeah little pigs
Seven chores Wow, right. Yes, so but if you start
That I think that's so fun that it's these insane amounts, but I started going like, okay if I alright
I'm gonna exchange I have $60 and I want
Sevens how?
Like you're in the you're in a theme park in the heat. You're trying to divide seven into
60 or whatever it is. Uh-huh. That's a brain breaker
Yeah, it's not it's not as that the five C ones fives and tens simple it's very simple easier to yes even numbers
I think that being said
Everybody has to learn a little advanced math for the sake of fun
Yeah, you know, that's your belief in Jenna. That's because that's why you like
Everything that Disney World is instituted because it requires advanced math
To get on a ride. Well, yeah, I don't like the thing that's been happening apparently where you have to what is it?
Like stay up till midnight and then get up at six o'clock
To like complete like whatever the reservations you need the next day. Whatever it is
Has it gotten worse? What are you talking about?
You're now locked into you have to stay up insanely late and get up insanely early
I pray if you want to get like your full like to get to be able to like get the fastpass or to get the
The genie plus what's the midnight? What do you get it?
I'm trying to remember there is some if you want to get I should look it up
But it's like look it up because when I was down there it was just setting my alarm for like
655 to just constantly refresh an app first off get off the Wi-Fi to refresh an app
It's so funny because that I'm like I must be crazy, right? It can't still be this bad and then trying it
I'm like, okay the Wi-Fi still this bad and all of the blogs of like how to do this thing get off any Wi-Fi
Use why do not be on Disney Wi-Fi, but do be on the app. Yeah, do keep refreshing
This is madness. How have we ended up here and that it's just like, okay, there's a new ride if you think okay
I'll just wait for it. Not an option fuck off
Buy it or you had to be really good at refreshing our notoriously bad software apps
It's just I saw somebody
Saying like I don't know if I agree with Scott and reheam that he's recently saying how Universal's winning the war and I don't
Know if that's across the board, you know
Universal Hollywood has its issues and lacks of magic here and there despite having the definitive greatest ride in the world
but I'm more mean the like
For I cannot wait to stay at Universal Orlando
Next time there is a Florida trip and not deal with any of this fucking horse shit. This is insane
What are you taught every new detail that gets added is crazier and crazy
So it looks even so relaxing and there's so many rides, you know, I got to do any of this and universal
Yes, okay. Here's what it is
So at midnight is when you can then purchase the genie plus for the next day, but you cannot start reserving
Reservations until 7 a.m. So you're if you want to do it all you're at you're fucked because
You have to sleep for six hours on your vacation
So wait, so can you you can't buy individual lightning lights at midnight you say you are buying Disney plus for the park
Jeannie plus yes, so it's like 1201 or whenever it rolls or 12 o'clock you that's when Jeannie plus and Jeannie plus does run out
Apparently, okay. That's why you have to do it at midnight
Oh god, but you can't make your first reservation of the day until well, but it is it's hotel guests
I think it's seven and regular guests at night something like that
That's why it's like they're forcing you to like get six hours of sleep or seven hours of sleep
Which is just a very bad system on a vacation on your
I mean you're in a hotel and now you have to yeah
Get up early and ostensibly you have entered this property past giant sign some of which I know they're deconstructing and rebuilding
That say the word resort on them
Which I have mentioned this before that does have certain
Connotations to it what that dude's gonna be pleasure
Relaxation I don't forget that some of the hotels take like an hour to get to
Via complicated transportation means so let's add that to it as well, right?
Yeah, but again the math of universal it's like, okay, we got three hotels that are more expensive granted, but
You could just show your room key at the park and walk on any ride basically. Yes
Yeah, it's working if it's working a lot and a lot of the rides have been so good lately
Yes, like the best so
Yeah, yeah, and you might not be able to do that at the brand new rides
You'll just have to wait in line, but then it's equal. It's an equalizer. Everyone just has to wait in line. Mm-hmm. You know, yeah
Insane
Here's one thing that universal didn't do
Better is the money I didn't know until today that there was a time when they tried
It starts it starts off bad Disney dollars. Oh neat alliteration
Universal dollars does those don't you didn't do anything there. You try to make that fun in any way
I don't know what you call them
Yeah bucks. Well bucks. Yeah, it's dollars or bucks, right? You're only the two options
Well, I got one now. I got one for modern minion money
No, that's great
It's all the difference Bob and right right right. Oh, that's great. Yeah, that is good
Yeah, although I get maybe you need more distinctly different characters
too because you'd be confused by you'd have to branch out to the girls and grew and
That would help. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I need grew to be okay. Okay, but minion money is very good. Yeah, minion money is good
Yeah, but this was there was McDonald land bucks
You know there was a lot there were a lot of places doing stuff similar to this yeah, yeah
This definitely existed out there
I think Disney did it the best with the like high quality of printing and that it was really committed to the Universal ones seem
Just like yeah coupons essentially. That's what McDonald no recollection. I didn't need I've been the idea zero
This was like early 2000s. It seems like other parks didn't start doing this still a little bit later
Can anyone guess a character who was on the Universal money in the early 2000s
Let's think about their well of IP. That's some of the other it's like Mickey and Donald and goofy and then a universal you got
Woody woodpecker. Yes, what he would put Woody woodpecker is their Mickey
That's their one. I guess a lot of ways we find that Woody woodpecker is their Mickey
Can you really say universal is winning in general when that is what's happened a character who who's only
Presence in the last 60 years has been an unpleasant straight to Netflix movie
Well, I I did watch that video series
Recently and it did shock me that Woody woodpecker's kid zone
Was a late 90s edition because that's when they're like, this is our guy. This is gonna be our Mickey Mouse
There were probably yeah, there must have been big animated movie plans that build on when would epic universe
When will the Woody woodpecker mega land to be built? That's my question
Is that in the first four or we have to wait for the expansion for that?
He's were will find a world to his birdhouse
Detail do people this people we met do people like Woody woodpecker that much
No, have you ever met anyone? No, not when chilly Willie is on the table
I do like chilly Willie. I don't agree with that. But I was never like a kid is
Like yeah, Woody woodpecker. He's annoying. Yeah, he's awful
But yeah, does anyone like him out there somebody go? Oh, yeah, that's that was my favorite character as a kid say what you haven't seen
You haven't seen the other good Woody woodpecker novels that were written in 1951
Okay on the inside universal
Message board someone says I still have my mummy returns five dollar universal
That's pretty good like rotting mummy. Yeah, is there an islands of adventure currency?
Like is there anything that has like the the light tower or anything? It's all general resort. I believe
Which they like I they don't even own that no
Using to zone by Warner Brothers. You don't even think of scooby-doo being in the parks
You know what I
Mickey and boop is there any mini and maybe the answer for them is teaming up with a half interest in these two characters
Maybe nobody really cares about boop. People really care about woody people care about boop
I'm not sure why exactly but people fucking go nuts for boop. The people do love boop $10 $10 Spider-Man bill
Oh, that's pretty good. You should get that. Yeah, you should buy that but boop. Yeah, we should do a full boop
Episode cuz I honestly I don't I don't know a lot about but I don't know anything about boop
I don't know why but she's around super popular still to this day and I'm always shocked at how popular it's a license like any
if you if you would go to like a souvenir shop or like
Like a mall like go to the Grove
Go to the Grove and go to one of those like just kind of souvenir shops and boop is everywhere every way
Yeah, and but especially like towns that have like
Small malls and then there's just a store selling Elvis and I love Lucy lunchboxes
You're gonna get some boop there. Yeah, she's every she's everywhere and it's for some reason still selling
I think if you watch the Charles Fleischer cartoons, they're weird. I have
Great, but I was so strange. We should what we should do some boop. Yeah, we'll do it. Let's try to figure out why I mean
There's a why and a lot. Yeah, almost all the universal main states
We got a kind of an angle why we should do Woody too, but I'm less interested in that. Yeah, that sounds annoying
It sounds we don't have to do it. Yeah, do it don't don't
Don't tell us they're on
Woody when Garfield eats the main thing we know about Woody is the ha ha ha ha ha ha like the noise the noise
Yeah, of course would I don't think I was about to say people willingly watch this I don't think they did I think was a short
Before other stuff they're probably like god dammit of all the characters
I'm gonna go to try to force some pee out and I hope that this cartoon is over before the movie
I came here to see I mean I kind of like I think the the walk around costume solid like walk around Woody
That was kind of without his personality. It's fine. Yeah
Visually, yeah
but as far as
I'm trying to think if there's a cartoon that I like less that I watched as a kid or just like again
Woody was like on and I would see it and I wouldn't have said like oh I hate this but I'm trying to think
Of anything that I thought like found more unpleasant
Boop bucks if they called them boop box is good. Sure. That's true
But then you're a little then you're limited and like so that's so wait what it's but it's I can spend this anywhere
I could but yeah, it's boop bucks. What about Lucille ball and calm ball bucks ball bucks pretty good
Ten dollar. Yeah mummy returns for ten dollars
Jurassic Park gets ten and ten note. Yeah dinosaur burst and dinosaur that's
That's what I thought I had a dollar bill. I thought that was normal and then a tiny t-rex
ripped through the paper
Jurassic points that doesn't sound as good. No
That's I'm trying to think. Yeah, I don't know
Fred Mertz money
Ethel Mertz money. No, they don't have Fred and Ethel in the parks, which I've written written letters about but
They still haven't they haven't done there are no yeah, there is no Fred Mertz no walk around Fred Mertz
No walk around like you with a cane
JK Simmons
Oh, is it Mertz or is it the JK Simmons Mertz? Well, it's Frawley. He's Frawley. He's Frawley
They can all they can both coexist. I guess that's all is a different Captain America's right different
Yeah, the people are gonna want to see both
Encourages you to stick around all day, of course
Anyway, they they messed up that's not good
But you know what is good and and I'm gonna go ahead and say well
No, I don't want to say did you guys run into the other theme park that did this that had money?
No, I don't think I did Dolly dollars
All right, that's pretty Hollywood
I don't mean to shit on the topic that we're doing and that was chosen for us
But Dolly dollars are better. Look at these
Glamorous person who has ever been on money. Look at all the the gold and the frills
Look at the beautiful like it's her it's her on the front. You get to see every type of wig and every area
Oh, yeah, oh my god treasurer Dolly Parton. She's all of it
There's only one character at Dollywood
So she just has to be everything and then here's a count country fair on the back and here's Dollywood
Boulevard and oh it just gets me guy
We got to figure out how to get down there that'll really be the great colors great colors
So they're so vibrant the hair is better in each one than the previous
Each wig better than the last. Yes. Yeah
These these are joy. I don't know if they're still doing these good question. Yeah wonder
Yeah, Dollywood rules
why in the Disney has to
Desperately invent all of these these lame excuses for characters when Dollywood had it is just they retired at one
There's a 2010 Dolly dollar
So yeah, they're recently at least
Huh? Yeah. Wow, these are years like decades of them at least these Universal Studios dollars are going for a lot on eBay
So these are we maybe we're the fools. Maybe these are all doing great
I mean, this was a great thing to invest in and we all messed up or wait a minute
We were children our parents messed up
That's their parents should have been like these people there on the first day when Scrooge pounded his money bag into the onto the counter
My boy, I'm gonna next time I see my parents. I'm gonna say why didn't you spend ten thousand dollars on Disney dollars in?
1987 yeah, I could have a life then I went to the I gotta say though
I went to Universal Studios a good amount in the early
2000s and I have only the famous recollection not even of doll of these images
No, these aren't for this didn't take at all. Yeah, usually there was always standee signs of like
Your photos get all your photos in one place or like there was always the
Fucking internet cap like print out all your photos of the day on a CD and take that home with you
Universal's just getting around to some of the good ideas that Disney did 30 years ago as much as Merch is concerned and obviously back then
Anything that we're gonna do is half-assed by and large
So that means in 30 years Universal Orlando is gonna be perfect super
Unpleasant complicated. No, I'm so they're gonna be the whole thing. They're gonna figure out a way like alright
So you go to bed at 2 15 wake up at 2 30 we're doing it prison style and we make you do it
We start banging on the doors get up get up
Do you want to go on men and black alien attack or not? Uh-huh. Yes, they'll catch up then
I feel like I did see like there's a survey going around among annual pass holders
Would you like to reserve the day you're coming to Universal and everyone's like fuck you? No
Good yeah off
There is the rumor is that there's an original
Universal Hollywood horror Halloween horror nights maze called prison this year
Yeah, yeah once that's also the weekend is getting his own maze. I'm so excited about this
Weekend music blasting loud in a horror maze. This is awesome. I'm so excited
I'm sure they're in the liner notes or something. There's an explanation with the bandage gimmick. I've no idea what it is
See in the maze. Yeah, we'll learn you said you're going to this year. I mean, we'll see we'll see wait a minute
I don't sound like doing it
Wait, what is this? What are the quote? What are the what are you gonna decide? You know what this time?
We cannot make that judgment
We're talking by the way here we're about a month out from haunt season, so you're gonna decide quickly
Oh, yeah, because that you have to reserve in advance
This is the opening day the opening day of of Hollywood Halloween horror nights here is the 8th of September
Hmm or the 6th you got to be sure but you got to make these decisions
I'm gonna make mine right now. Am I gonna go? No, it's easy done. You never promised that you never you never
Simple but frightfest maybe
I hated six flags in the regular day so much
Oh
Or not. If you want to go to nuts, we'll go to nuts. Not nuts is the best one
Not says the coolest seemingly but hornets awesome to most passionate. Yes, you got you got a variety
I've said this before but you get you get those teams. You're right. You've got a lot of been locked down
There's a lot of sliders at knots though. So you don't like those
Can we just talk about
Disney dollars we came across that we liked that's a good get out of here
I gotta say I do appreciate I think this was a pretty canny move
They made a $50 note. There was only two thousand of them made and they only sold them on one day
1955 you can see 1955 to
50th anniversary of Disneyland. Okay, I think that's pretty smart. Mm-hmm thinking
Yeah, is that like when you when we're saying this these are the ones we would have wanted if we were into this
Like what what struck your yeah, like here's a $5 with goofy on the front
And I think it's the Liberty Bell riverboat on the back
Yeah, I used this I looked at the serial number and saw it was for Disney World
So I don't think it's the Mark Twain use the Shazam that you have for river boats
Look the first angel investors seed money is not coming in
There is not interest in don't need this apparently. Mm-hmm. Yeah, there's a lot of good
There's like them. There's the space Mountain one. That's that's on one of the first
Images there was a little run towards the end looks like 2014. There was the Mountain series
Yeah, where it's the the ride on the front and Mickey riding it on the bat, those are pretty sharp
I think by the way the style of all of these I mean my favorite is just the classic
basic Mickey wave in and it's a really
picturesque castle as is the the Liberty Bell the steamboat on the back I
the riverboat rather on the back the
I don't know. I the basic style of them stayed pretty great
Yeah, goofy the goofy $5 bill is funny because he's like snooty. He's like got his nose turned up
Which is not a choice. Yeah, not how Mickey and Minnie are they're like their normal happy selves
But goofy looks like he's like full of me stuck up or something. Yeah, here's a mixy Mickey 60th
65th
birthday
It's a Disneyland one because it's got the a and here's his house and the weird car. Mmm, the weird car. Yeah
Bulbas car with eyes the cars alive. We don't know its name. Mm-hmm. It's uh, what there's so many
There's like big. Yeah, you were saying there's the other rides. There's big thunder and yeah
That's a very Fleischer studios thing like an inanimate object with eyes and it's a lot like I feel like every guy
Mickey's on the ride in these he's not it's not like a ride car with eyes that I'm looking at. Yes
Yeah, this face man one. He's just in the space mountain
But yeah, there's so many there were some opening California adventure
Ones which I don't always love that DCA 1.0 aesthetic, but I kind of like it
Mixed with the stately aesthetic of currency like here's I do really like Mickey
Climbing the the mountain like like with the bear mountain behind with grizzly peak behind him
Seeing that bright yellow kind of annoying original logo
On a dollar bill I sort of like well, there's the Disneyland. Oh, no, sorry. It's just a regular resort
But I was gonna say these are I guess from around the same time, but it's got Mickey and Minnie with sunglasses on
Yeah, like tourists. Yeah vacationing Mickey and Minnie, but it is the Disney. Sorry. It's a Disneyland resort, but it's got the bear
It's the it's the castle and then the bear. Yeah, so obviously California venture was there at that point
Is the bear still are they still pushing the bear?
Is the we were all we talked about on the grizzly river rapids we were all kind of confused about the
Years, yeah, which is great. I really think it's cool, but we all didn't quite know what it was
Yeah, we had questions icon if you grew up out here and you're looking at the state flag with the cool bear on it
Maybe you'd make the can I'm a you're more thing about? Yeah, that's true
But it is yeah, there's just so many Disney dollars that they made
Well, you got a Pirates of the Caribbean one and maybe here's a quick
souvenir smackdown
What do you think is the top?
This is the on stranger tides bill a one dollar on stranger tides bill
It's got the skull keep in mind. It's got the skull and
Swords and then the ship the black pearl the black would not cherish this want this
What do you think the top version is going for on eBay and these have not sold yet
This is the what somebody's trying to get somebody's trying to get I know if they're more rare
And this is like a you know tie-in to a movie. So there probably was not as many made. It's just
Regular Mickey or regular goofy. Mm-hmm. So that might put it in more rare. So
I like I said, I think the millennial one with the Millennium logo and the Epcot
You know the wand and the 2000 that was going for 30 with an envelope
I'm gonna say like 75 for this one. Mm-hmm to 50
Again, this is the top right the most
Okay
$10,000. Okay. Okay most expensive
That somebody thinks they could get he's saying what was yours to 50 and 10,000
You're saying 10,000 now I am yeah cuz he said that's the that's the highest one somebody's trying to ask somebody's asking for
I'm gonna go lower. I'll say 1000
somebody's trying to get
$500,000 for
Stranger Tide go to sold and or click on sold and completed on the left and see what it is selling for
On the left you should see if you scroll it should do you mean like if somebody
That'll show you what the recent stuff is sold for basically
Okay, if you see sold I'd have sold or completed and then it'll show you what's what the actual total people
I'm not as eBay if I'm not seeing that on here
Disney doll see if my before my phone dies here. I'll look for it strange. Did you look up stranger tides Disney dollars?
I think I think it's just Disney dollars and most expensive. I see Disney
I'm gonna look up stranger tides and they have an IC the listing you're talking about for five hundred thousand dollars
And completed sold let's see here in edge keep it's the user elite coin one Disney dollar
Has sold with the logo for 1499
before that
One
Let's see. Was there something spot? Yeah, it doesn't it seems like all these are like 50 or lower
This is you try to find the biggest rube paper money guarantee. It looks like it's been assessed
It looks like it's it says exceptional paper quality
So they're there. Yeah, that's gonna get you up into the 300 thousand dollars produced. They are out of production, but still accepted
Elite coinage company is proud to offer the largest selection of certified Disney dollars
Yes, because there's graded and ungraded Disney dollars
This is like comic books in the sense that certain comic books are more once they've been graded by the official
I forget the company that does it that grades them. So if you have an action comics, that's like a
9.2 that's gonna be a lot more money than action comics
4.9. Yeah, you slab it you put in a giant plastic case so no one can touch it
Okay, and those are worth more just like the guys have here the two most reputable
reputable Disney dollar grading companies in the world are
PMG and legacy grading previously known as PC GS
So if you got some Disney dollars and you want to get a grade it you got to give it to one of these companies
I'm sure the people at Bank Note world or billion shark a bullion sharks
But keep it keep in mind that PN PNC and the I don't know what you said
Well, they've changed names, but I mean the quality the quality work is still there
I just want to know where a philatist goes to get their stamps assessed. I
Mean there's all again. These are whole other worlds
I know we have just we haven't even cracked the book on we're just seeing the cover
Burgeoning philatist and I'm wondering should I be putting my stamps in a new miss?
Yeah, I guess great question, thank you for coming to the seminar you'd be tough to go wrong with the new miss
You know, it's a great starting. I use them quite a bit. They're very standard, you know
I oh wait one more that the let the bill
The I as I was saying I find a lot of these aesthetically pleasant and I miss seeing them out in the wild
It's only one there's only one that where they fucked up and it's this an area where they fucked up putting this anywhere
Chicken little get the fuck out and I hate you chicken little
Look bad at this movie. Am I being harsh?
This movie looks like shit everything they ever put up in the parks that big balloon that looked like shit chicken little you met Disney
You fucked up over and over again. I get it. I keep swearing chicken little makes me angry
You've seen a little character. No, I've never seen it. Oh well now folks the sky is falling I guess
What am I am I gonna watch it and fall in love with with little you know?
All that stuff it's so much weight is on dizzy plus now and I got a I've been meaning to watch bolt chicken
Little brother bear home on the range like I just there is a to you want to I'm just so curious
I want you I want you to watch it
The only thing the thing I like about chicken little is that there is an original bare naked lady song on the soundtrack
Okay, called one little slip. I've never seen the movie
Mm-hmm, but the song is like kind of a ripoff of it's all been done
They kind of like did the same they just maybe turned in a demo
I think the Disney were like give us a new it's all been done and they did
Yeah, it's like Mickey Mouse Minnie Mouse for sparks. They're like, yeah, we'll just fuck it. Hey, no get out of here
That one those are both great. I just mean the thought process we tied the band
Cynically thought of but they still have a good thing. No, it's got a web address. It says summer 2005 on it
www.disney.com slash chicken little hit your web address out of here
I don't am I wrong everyone that bit there was a big inflatable chicken little thing somewhere
A couple of right there was a dog in the pole big chicken little hitting the pole change my mind
I'm sure you little chicken have the new have like everything now the cycles of nostalgia
Are happened so quickly has the chicken little nostalgia come yet online. Have we seen it?
I think we're gonna find out and either it'll be one person or it'll be
Definite. Yeah, I don't know. We're in where am I one little slip fans at the bare naked ladies song
Maybe they remember it for that reason too
I don't know. Well Zach Braff's the main voice. I see her to guess that this movie will change my life. I swear
I think that's fair. Yeah
so
Besides the chicken little buck besides the
Flawless except for chicken little in your eyes. Yeah, otherwise they did great idle. These are nice
I think maybe they could do it again
You know, what's interesting is that these were they stopped making them Disney dollars died just a few months after their creator
Jack Lindquist died and
Mouse planet said it was nice that the father of Disney dollars died before he saw his creation eliminated
Was it? Yeah, that's I'm like
if I invented some fake money and
I could get six more months on this earth, but I had to learn that they stopped making my fake money
I think I'd vote for the the more time months. Yeah, I think that's right on store
Yeah, I think that's right. I mean who knows maybe that was like every morning Jack would go like my is my money still around
And they go yes, Jack. I'm already so maybe it was important to him. Maybe I'm crazy
You need to go. Okay, and he give you the wink and then he'd go down about his day
But I don't know any winked his final wink right and there or did he did he up to heaven?
Did he find out like there was like oh, yeah, they're thinking about getting rid of the dollars and goes
Oh, no, and that was it and when your wife dies and then you go, right? It's like
Padme a Queen Amidala dies of the broken heart at the end of Revenge of the Sith
She couldn't go on because of what happened Anakin they could now do
Star Wars money and that's you know, that's great. They have all that like they you're supposed to do that double speak in the gift shops
And yet they don't they don't have is you're walking around with Star Wars money
Well, they did though they and I they have the gift certificate
There was a little piece of metal a gift certificate like opening day or the first couple months you could have bought
That was like worth I forget if it was a specific
Denomination or if it was you could just add it like I think you had to add a yeah
I don't know it almost bring this back kind of yeah
But there wasn't a full like system like credits and you couldn't play the Lando card game or anything
You could flip one of those bad boys on eBay easy, right? Oh, yeah, those are sold out those are sold out quickly
I believe at least I don't know forks. I don't you write the for the spork things were selling they don't do those anymore
But yeah, they should have done a full credit system. They should have gone all the way
That would have been awesome and confusing and
Extremely quickly. All right, never mind
And they shouldn't bring it back cuz everyone will be think it's a conspiracy and that's true resetting there
Okay, so you know what? Does he actually does he know is perfect. It happened and it's gone dad dad trying to use Star Wars credits
To buy overnight oats and he's mad because it's cold. He's like when is opium cold
look
digital Disney dollars
Mm-hmm crypto Disney dollars and if Disney dollars have they gotten into that that game?
Yeah, no, but don't view you're crazy. I don't think there are people right now working on it
I believe Marvel had some truly atrocious golden
Things. Oh NFTs you mean or yeah. No there everyone's figuring it out
I just tried to do like hey, it's an NFT of amazing fantasy 15 and it's like come on man
That's like free on it. Come on. Well, that's a whole thing. Yeah, but but Disney I would be I would I would bet they're investigating
Yeah, I mean probably this digital Disney dollars at the very least with the metaverse
Wasn't that a thing that well I Iger's on his own track with that
But I feel like before he fully left Disney's like gotta look into the metaverse. Iger is looking into the metaverse
He invested in Funko
He's done a lot John Stewart is try to get him to start his own news network
There's a lot going on with mr. Iger
Yeah, metaverse metaverse possible. I mean there's
it'll be it'll be interesting to see what they try on all these avenues because I feel like they're
Traditionally kind of a conservative company and they will get into it later
There's a question. Let's go back to this crypto point. Yeah, if you had ten thousand dollars
Do you put it into Bitcoin or do you put it into?
I
Guess now Disney chicken little bucks. Do you buy nothing?
Do you buy as many chicken little bucks as you can for ten thousand dollars? Yeah, why not today now?
Okay. Yes, what I would say to that. Uh-huh. I would say
The probably Bitcoin is the answer but I would say look into
How many chicken little bucks were made? Okay, that's what to figure out how scarce chicken little bucks are
I think it's probably not so desirable because of the property is not so desirable property is not desirable
But the rare ones either like certainly the misprinted ones are very
Expensive, but I think like the shorter run smaller run
Disney dollars are the ones that really sell yes exactly. So
It depends it depends what what they're going for
Well some money they are in the range of
$500 so that's how much they've accrued in what 17 years
So by that logic if it goes from one if these trends continue
We could we could probably do a full. Okay, I see a pre-owned it looks kind of dirty this Disney dollar this chicken little Disney dollar
$15 I think it's a buy it now. It's probably more I do it
And then you can best offer it because you can wash currency there there are well, yeah
You get another business and you wash it that way. No, I mean like
Okay, yes, I think you can wash currency. Yeah, I do wonder yes was their money laundering done with Disney dollars
Well, did they how did anyone get that did a stripper get tipped with Disney dollars?
This is a question I had to is anyone ever made in Orlando. Of course they did. Did people make I'm living
I'm on vacation. I'm on top of the world. Yes, I'm making it rain Goofy's there's no doubt it happened
It didn't happen. Did anyone do the you know Snow White?
Railroad
Okay, with it, yeah, Michael Eisner did
Let's be honest
Think about it. Just think we have money now. I see. All right
I'll be right back. I'm gonna this Walt's laughing place office still preserved. I'll be right back
What are you talking about
I want to get out of skates right now. I'm playing you and hockey. Let's get on the roof
What if Mickey me you a bad club sandwich?
I just saw clerks one. I want to play a roller hockey on the roof
We're making a school and we're making a movie of the character
Well, I think we just solved something we never put together Disney made their own money in the 80s right then my class
Craziest spree. All right, we figured it out
Even though we're on to you, please still come on the show
Yeah
Wolf of Wall Street cut the Disney dollar scene number one question
If we ever talked to Bob Gurran here is did you do cocaine the Disney dollar?
He's cool Roley has talked about doing psychedelics
So there if one guy did a mushroom then for sure the CEO of the Disney Company did a talk with
Yes. Yes. No question. Yes. So
Now we figured all that out you survived podcast the red club three your bravery saved the podcast. Well done freedom fighters and
You know, I guess let us know what you want to happen next month
Extravaganza
Nor the other coverage. You're the other proof. I'm not that cuff first cough cough the brush you pop