Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to podcast the ride, the second gate.
We're here today to discuss a very important album about a character trait that
everyone knows about the legend Donald Duck.
He loves gadgets. My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan. Hi.
Scott Garner here today also to talk about this thing that we all know already,
but is, you know, is something that's explored in the album we're discussing today.
He's a digital duck. That's right.
Which manifests not in apps because that's not the era that we're dealing with yet.
It's more like the sharper image kind of,
he likes a lot of do dads with digital components. Right.
We are of course talking about the 1983 album Splash Dance.
Mickey Mouse Splash Dance.
I think fully officially it's kind of presented as if Mickey Mouse is the artist
of the album Splash Dance, but he's on it very rarely.
It's kind of a little like laugh into it.
And then you're kind of on your own with anonymous singers.
Yeah. He presents it, I guess, in a way, I guess you kind of would say.
And he is on the presence in it.
A lot of the songs are about him or mention him and his friends, his good friends.
I wanted to start real quick.
You know, we always talk about the album art and I say we, I mean, like
record heads, vinyl collectors, music fans.
And this has a fantastic cover.
Let's just start there. Love this cover. Yeah, absolutely.
Mickey hitting a big wave.
Mickey is hitting a big wave. The curl.
The angle is fantastic.
There's a cool wave going the way that is rendered.
I don't know if it's early CGI
or just drawn from kind of a digital feeling angle, but it feels very airbrushed.
This image was really big in a book that like I had a piano in the house growing up.
And there was a book like sheet music of Disney songs.
And this took over a full page of it before I knew the album Splash Dance.
And I would I would stop and stare at it.
It felt different to me. Yes.
Even just a few years down the road, like whether it's 3D or fake 3D, it's just it's it's rad.
This is like this is what is it 13 years before Mario 64,
where you would be get behind it would be you would finally get a 3D rendering
of the worlds that you played in video games.
And this feels sort of like that to me, where it's like
you're behind Mickey, you're on his journey, you're on his wave.
Yeah, even if it maybe it was not rendered in any 3D fashion.
Right. But if it was like it does give you that it's that angle that absolutely is exciting.
Like if you I would love for this to keep going into a video or into a video game
that I'm controlling, sort of surfing with Mickey scenario.
I completely agree. And of course, I think the number one thing
we have to talk about this and we really haven't talked about this topic in a while.
But I never noticed how good of a seat Mickey has before this cover.
Are you sure we have? Are you sure we have to go down this avenue?
I'm just saying I was looking at it and I go, look at Mickey's nice seat.
It's like that seat is featured so prominently on this cover.
I mean, you noticed it, Jason.
Yeah, it's like you're saying like it's Wednesday in my neighborhood
because there's a dump truck there, you know, it's trash truck dump truck.
Look, I'm not going to be like that.
It was clever, but this isn't club random, Jason.
You can't just be vulgar like that.
Oh, how many things can we mention in the first five minutes
to make me want to run for the door?
I'll keep it. You know, I got to find I got to find a, you know,
a ball right over the plate to smack at because I admittedly this topic.
You you can pretty quickly when this topic came up in conversation, we're like,
oh, well, splash dance. Yeah, splash dance.
And I'm like, mm hmm.
Yes, because I knew the pieces of this.
I did not know the whole.
Have we ever talked to be out?
Well, yeah. What was your level of your maybe you've seen this cover?
Maybe. Yeah, I think it was the the cover, the phrase, the phrase.
Disney was really milking splash in the 80s.
So, oh, yeah, splash mountain, the movie, splash, eventually.
Yeah, that's true.
No, no splash mountain really connection.
That's that's a few years away at this point.
But yeah, I didn't really know.
So I went in pretty fresh to this album.
Was this the first time you saw the photo of Mickey's iconic seat?
I think I've seen it in passing.
I think it's been like a lot of this album has been used in
either anniversary specials, birthday specials or like music videos.
Yeah, a lot of the songs have found homes elsewhere. Yeah.
It is this I don't know how to and maybe you guys can help with this.
Actually, what if you had to explain as a first time listener?
Yeah. What is this album to you?
Is there a way to like what's going on?
OK, I kept seeing I saw one or two plays
refer to it as a spiritual sequel sequel to Mickey Mouse Disco.
And I think there's similar writers and producer or same writers
and producers, I think, or some writers.
But it's the same entity.
Yeah, it's Walt Disney Records.
Some of this has gone over in the Halyx documentary,
which we appear in and help inspire, help inspire the Walt Disney
Records made a lot of books that were just telling the story of a movie.
And they did it even for non Disney movies for Star Wars and E.T.
And that was their bread and butter.
But I think the people involved wanted to shake it up and, you know, and rock.
They wanted to get rock and make it, which prompted the album
Mickey Mouse Disco, which was a sneaker hit after a bunch of,
you know, changing their promotional strategy and advertising it on TV.
But this is like an oddly huge album.
Eventually, this Mickey Mouse Disco, which I've never heard in.
Has anybody heard Mickey Mouse Disco?
I don't think I've heard it in full, but I've heard some songs and I'm into it.
I mean, I like every gimmicky disco album.
Well, and then this is the next decade.
So this is a lot of I don't know.
I like pop songs.
There's echoes of like trends of the time.
There's some synth in here.
There was one song where I was like, this kind of sounds like ABBA.
And then there was another song where it's like there's hints of Devo.
Uh huh. Like as if someone had heard Devo once or twice on the radio
and then went in the studio and tried to reverse engineer it.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Yeah, that's a lot of it to me.
It's I've seen it.
Someone might have even suggested that we do it as an episode
and might have framed it as when Disney did a new wave album.
That's not exactly right, because it's not we definitely aren't in
Duran Duran, Flock of Seagulls territory.
It's like much.
There's like a darkness, I feel like, to new wave.
And this is all very bright and goofy.
But it's in goofy, including goofy.
Goofy is on it.
It's kind of like, I don't know.
It's just like Disney trying to do an album with the trappings of 1982,
1983, which is delightful to me because I love so much music
from then, and it has the feel of pop songs from then that I like.
It feels like it's as like it feels like Disney's doing.
Let's use all of the methods used to make an Olivia Newton
John album with Minnie and Chip and Dale and such, which.
So I've always been very fond of it.
I haven't known this album forever, but whenever I stumbled on it,
it's an interesting mix.
There's songs that there's a couple of songs on it.
They're very important to me and some that I have zero thoughts on at all.
Yeah, there's and I will lean on you guys to have any opinions all over the map.
But there's certain things where I'm like, this might be the best Disney album.
I like the like the peaks of it, I think, are wonderful.
Yeah, the peaks are high.
There are a couple of songs that are like nothing and veer much closer to
kids like kind of mindless kids songs.
There's a couple that are like more like that, where you go,
yeah, this is sort of monotonous and whatever.
Sing songy. Yeah.
But who knows? Those will be Jason's favorites.
But that could be Jason's favorite. We don't know about it.
I mean, I assume we're on a similar page about which ones are good
or which ones are very good.
We'll see. Yes.
I I'm going to try to I found out some history about this album
and I'll try to pepper it in as we go instead of front load it.
But here's the here's one thing to say about it is that most of the music
on this album is made by, I believe, a husband and wife team.
Michael and Patty Silver sure.
And I'll say a little more about them as we go.
But the main thing is
gummy bears theme is them.
Tailspin theme is them.
And a lot of the songs on this Disney afternoon album.
Do we have this?
I've heard it recently, but I have I did not have it as a kid.
Didn't have it growing up.
This was this was a like stuck in the car.
Mom and dad don't put any other tape in there.
I want I remember listening to it to go see the Disney afternoon overlay in 1990.
I loved the theme songs.
I love the main Disney afternoon theme song.
Yeah, yeah, certainly.
But there's all these other songs.
I don't even remember being on the shows.
I don't know if they're just inspired by Tailspin or gummy bears or whatever.
But I liked all of them.
I found these all to be like oddly sweet, angsty, touching songs at times.
And it makes so much sense to me that that album was like had a place in my heart.
And then everything I've heard from that, not everything,
but there's certain songs on this that have come up before that I feel odd emotion about.
I think I have to credit Michael and Patty Silvershire.
I think they did a good job.
The gummy bear song we've talked a little bit about.
And I never had any I honestly have no affection for the gummy bears.
They didn't watch the show.
But that theme is so good.
Boy, it's a it's a real it's a punch.
I don't think I knew that they wrote it.
This couple wrote it sung by Joseph Williams, son of John Williams
and often lead singer of Toto, which connects a lot of dots for me.
Like, why have I landed on Toto so hard as music?
I can't stop listening to it.
I think it's on some level.
Yeah, it is like, oh, so there's there were pop songs in this era
that essentially sound like the gummy bears song.
It'd be a little embarrassing if I'm just blasting the gummy bears song
in my car all the time.
But I can do if I, you know, I legitimize it slightly with six songs that are similar.
I play the gummy bears theme on Apple Music once every couple months, I think.
Good move. Two or three months, probably.
Yeah. Have I ever told the story of when I almost got kicked out of my dorm
because of the DuckTales theme?
No, no. Does this sound familiar?
I don't think so. If it's a five timer, I apologize.
And I don't remember here, but I don't think I've told this.
This was a discovery for like as soon as not streaming services,
but like Kazaa or audio galaxy or whatever.
Yeah, I was thinking this too.
I I feel like I didn't get to file sharing until college.
And I was like, remember a day where I was like, oh, my God,
people have TV theme, so I can get these.
I think our brains probably work the same way.
Yeah, you're like, well, here's full album stuff and that's cool.
Wait, but somebody took the time to upload Mr.
Belvedere. Whoa.
I can be interesting like that and play Mr.
Belvedere in the car on a mixed CD.
But anyways, my roommate in sophomore year,
we were very delighted to have just access to the DuckTales theme
whenever we want, because also a real like solid blat.
That's a jam. I think we're all fans of that.
And we had there had been one incident where somebody was kind of
stomping around a little bit and it bothered our our
is it already or like the guy who lives in the building?
Are a which in this case was this big brawny guy.
He kind of looked like Pete, the Disney character Pete.
I don't know how they landed on him as the guy who's going to live in the dorm
building, but he was kind of he was very mean and gruff and scary.
And he came up one day and kind of was like, I've been hearing a lot of sounds.
I don't think I like it.
And then he came up again and said, I think I know what it is.
And he had some other explanation that led us off the hook, but left it at like,
but if there's ever stomping again, I swear to God.
And then we had a kind of a late night
stomp around to the DuckTales theme as you do college. Right.
Oh, yeah. Going nuts. Blasting the DuckTales theme.
And it was literally right before we shut off the lights and went to bed.
So we did it.
And then with the main, the door had been left open.
So suddenly door, the lights are off.
Door slams open. Hey, what do I tell you?
And he's like, we this guy's screaming at us just bloody murder.
And then he calms down, gets himself together and says,
here's what's going to happen.
I'm going to write a letter.
And the recommendation of the letters that you guys fight somewhere else to live.
Whoa. Wow. We're like, oh, God. OK.
And we just kind of. All right. Well, let's forget about that.
Let's try to get some Z's and we'll see how this plays out.
But we have angered this guy, I guess, for the last time.
And then the dreaded day came in a couple of weeks
where we opened our school mailboxes and there was a letter to each of us
saying that we have been a nuisance and we need to find somewhere else to live.
And we looked at the letters and went, oh, no.
And then we thought, wait, does anyone but us have these letters?
I think this guy wrote a letter to us,
telling us to find somewhere else to live and not do any sort of board
or the school or anyone who could evict us.
So we're like, this big brawny Pete guy is so dumb.
He didn't. He wrote a letter to us.
What's that going to do?
So he stayed there and blasted ducktails and everyone.
And I come back.
No, we said we kept the stomping at a minimum and maybe we tried it.
Maybe after that, we made an effort to take ducktails out on the street.
Only in the car.
How only when only in the drop top.
We even hold up.
I'm not saying it's that weird, but how often were you playing ducktails and dancing?
This is the only time that it was ducktails, but it has really lit us up.
We for sure was, I said there was not YouTube yet.
YouTube was 18 months away or something.
So the ability to I can just pull up the ducktails theme whenever I want.
I don't have to buy a DVD to hear it.
It excited us so much.
So it was a go to to blast it.
So when you say stomping, were you like acting out the intro?
It was sort of no.
It was like truly just like stomping around like monsters.
My roommate and I both like Godzilla movies.
But what does Godzilla have to do with ducktails?
No, nothing.
No, it's just the stomping.
The spirit of Brian and I.
Did you stop? No, no.
I had a similar RA incident where my junior year
we were in the like the one dorm that was air conditioned
and everyone had their own bathroom.
And that was pretty nice.
But our room was next to the RA.
And my roommate and I were not particularly wild.
But one night, one Thursday night, I remember
he was going to his girlfriends and I we were watching like
the start of the Daily Show and we were kind of laughing at whatever.
You laugh and too loud at him going like
the classic Jon Stewart.
Yes. Yeah.
But not a cream pie dropped off the top of a ladder.
Yeah.
So we hear a knock at the door at like 11 p.m.
and we open it and it's like the RA and they start going off about like
it's so noisy, it's a Thursday night.
And I just I have study and I'm like, oh, sorry.
He was just late.
And we we we really apologize because he seemed very upset.
And then they started going into like
and I never see you guys at floor events at at the social meet.
And I'm like, we're both juniors and we're very busy.
Like we're in multiple like this school paper, the school TV station.
Like I was going to do laundry for the first time.
Yeah, I had to do my own fucking laundry.
I and I had to talk them down.
I talked to them for like an hour because I was I was like, oh, no,
they are going through something.
And and then they finally left and he was just like, what the fuck?
And I was like, I don't know.
I feel like we should tell someone.
But after that, I know they are at risk to themselves.
There's no we plan these floor events and they're for fun and for you.
And you don't even know they were they were perfectly nice.
But I don't think we were the problem.
A previous year, I remember there had to be a floor meeting once
because two guys got drunk and one of them took the fire extinguisher
off the wall and shot the other one with it.
And then the whole floor, that stuff just lingers in the air.
So everyone's eyes are burning.
And like so that seems to me more troublesome
than like a couple of guys being goofy to the DuckTales theme.
I think so like Godzilla.
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
Stomping like Godzilla to the DuckTales thing, combining IPs unnecessarily.
I had a blast is what I recall.
I do that and then lights off immediately.
But then a man comes in and yells at you.
This is one good thing that we have right now in our lives
that some man can't just bust down our door, start yelling at us.
Yeah, if not, it's if it happens, it's a man we chose to live with.
Yeah, I don't live with some mean man currently.
Luckily. Yeah.
So maybe when your son is older and you're 60 and you're stomping around,
he'll be like, what is this?
Shut up.
What is this song?
I don't want to hear the DuckTales theme again.
And actually, that probably is the most accurate way that it would go,
is that Aaron and I are blasting the DuckTales theme.
I like a symphony.
I like symphonies.
I like sophisticated music.
He does. You know, what's funny is that he does.
He's learned how to conduct because of the movie Soul.
So now I can say conduct.
And then he like, I played Beethoven on the bike today
to see if he would conduct.
So I think you're you've you've guessed something completely right about our kid.
A quick shout out. I'm not sure if he's on the Patreon.
My high school band teacher's son listens to this show.
And he reached out to me.
His father reached out to me.
Why did he ever scream at you?
You know, I don't think he ever screamed at me.
He was upset with the band a lot if we were we were being louder, whatever.
But yeah, anyway, high school bands are so pleasant to listen to.
How could that how could that put you in an agitated state?
There's there are I have albums with solos of mine on them and they're not great.
You mean Alba, the school band, Alred albums of our school band.
Well, yeah.
And what's the solo like on what?
That's a good question.
And what are you playing again?
Remind me the trumpet, of course.
OK, yeah, I'm a trumpet player.
We all know that was the word was was the audience.
I haven't played the trumpet.
You've been there for every episode.
You don't remember trumpet.
I can play.
I have not played the trumpet in many years, but I've yeah, it's
it was my first instrument.
Would you be playing it on like rock and roll part two?
Well, for the.
Yeah, for the for the basketball games, we would.
You would play.
Wait, no, we didn't play rock and roll part two.
We played like, give me some love in.
Oh, cool. And the horse.
It was fun playing and playing at basketball.
It was really fun because every like everyone would show up
I think we all had brainwashed ourselves thinking that we were helping.
Yeah, which was part of it.
You were. Yeah, they just looked into the sea of khaki pants and black t-shirts.
Yeah, we had a casual wearer.
And we had like dark red for the Saxons,
Schomburg Saxons.
So so we'll get those solos together.
We should want to hear.
I have I have I listened to it a couple of years ago and I was like,
you're not on the podcast or you're not on the Patreon.
You got to be. Well, it's cool.
They do extra topics that veer a little bit away from the first.
And you get to hear one of the hosts great trumpet solos from 20 years ago.
Freddie, he was like two decades.
He wasn't even an adult.
And he I mean, he was this guy was a true true virtuoso.
I was in. Yeah.
I wasn't in the good band, though.
I was like first chair in concert band.
Oh, I see. Which means I wasn't as good as like the symphonic band.
They go back and forth between telling nice memories and traumatic experiences
that still live with them.
That's true. Yeah. Plus years later.
One of them pretenses Godzilla.
Rarrar. Stomp, stomp, stomp.
I think we were probably shouting the woos really loud.
I love the idea of this.
This sounds like the most wholesome thing I've ever heard.
It really was.
I do. I for sure know that we were not drinking
on that particular night.
100 percent. No one assumed you were drinking.
Yeah, I know.
This is a sober dance along to DuckTales.
And I think this episode will be the equivalent of such
the only drinking going on is that the star shit.
No, it's star shit.
Cherry. So just regular full fat.
Harder to get the full fat.
Full sugar. Coca Cola.
Zero sugar. It's full.
Zero sugar. OK.
No, it's not. Yeah. Zero.
Let's start talking about these these songs.
Yeah, let's go through them.
I guess starting with the opening track.
Mike, it's really your call what you want to play.
Maybe we should hear a little of the first one, I guess.
The second music.
Well, you know what I could play really, really fast is this commercial
for Splash Dance, because this was this is apparently how they sold
a lot of Mickey Mouse disco and then they did the same strategy of kind of longer ads.
This is like a two minute ad on TV with a blue screen at the end.
From jazz and checker money order.
So here's this.
If this explains the premise of it, and I don't think it does really.
Here comes America's favorite mouse and he's splash dancing.
It's Mickey Mouse Splash Dance, the brand new record album
from Walt Disney Productions.
It's fun. It's exciting.
And it's a splash from coast to coast.
Come dance along with all your.
Well, I would say that doesn't explain it in any way.
He's very splash dancing.
Yeah. What does that mean?
Why is this?
The first song is specifically about splashing.
It is it is the title track.
They sing a lot about splashing.
Honestly, I think a more accurate name for this album would be robot dancing
because they seem to be leaning on that.
That is topical. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, here's here's some history I can unfold then.
A lot of this stuff is from a book called Mouse Tracks,
which is the history of Walt Disney Records.
And this husband and wife team, they were they sent a bunch of demos to Disney
and they got hired to put together the songs for.
OK, first off, Disney.
All right, we did disco. Now we're going to do Mickey Mouse Rock.
This is the first potential project.
And the only information I could find about that in this book is that
this same team wrote a song that said they said
we wrote a Bob Dylan type song for Donald Duck to sing.
Don't know what that means or how that could possibly work.
I would love to hear it. They wrote five songs.
The entire album was squashed.
Didn't end up happening.
But hey, we'll keep you in mind if we do anything else.
So they started working up something else, something that would use
all these synths that are in music all of a sudden.
And they started making an album called Techno Mickey.
So why are all these other songs about robots and androids and digital ducks?
Because it was it was about we're going to take synthesizers
and do a song about synthesized objects.
And then it became something called Mouse Tronics.
So we're still in that electronics area.
And then the movie Flashdance was a big hit.
And they said, sorry, guys, now it's splash dance, huh?
People are excited about Ashdance, but anything with Ashdance in it.
Doesn't matter what those first few letters are.
So we end. So it's got to be splash dance.
The people said, well, we wrote a lot of songs about robots
and we don't really have any songs about splashing.
And they said, better get writing then.
So then we ended up at we got a splash, splash, splash.
They were just handed this arbitrary phrase and had to make heads or tails of it,
to which I say, good work.
They follow the corporate mandate pretty well.
I think it's a catchy song.
If I had heard as a kid, I would definitely be like rewinding that cassette.
Yeah, yeah. Well, there's a lot of pep in a lot of these, I'd say.
You want to play the just the beginning.
I mean, we heard it in the in the ad there.
But this is kind of you can hear Mickey's appearance essentially in it.
One, two, three, four.
Hey, let's splash dance.
I want to start through the puddle.
Crash into the sea.
Dunk my head in the bubbles.
Get water all over me.
Dive like a sunrise, like a whale.
Fly up my flippers like a big fishtail.
Barely stop off the board, you bet.
Anything as long as it's land.
I'm going to splash, splash, splash.
Cause the water's cool.
Splash, splash, splash.
In the swimming pool.
Everybody get wet.
Splash, splash, splash.
That's great.
I think we got I think we got some real like Kenny Loggins
pep going on.
We got some. I think one of my favorite things about this album is all of the really
earnest singing.
It is very serious.
The vocals are just because like, you know,
what stops me with a lot of these Disney albums from really given at the time of days?
I don't know if I want to hear these characters sing.
Remember when we talked about the rap one?
I do not want to hear them rap.
I don't want to hear them sing standards.
That album that came out, I flipped through it.
Not interested.
I would rather maybe they hand the singing duties to some guy I've never heard.
If the singing is going to be superior.
Now, I saw the Mickey Mouse credit on this is Pete Rennaday.
Yes. Disney Journeyman.
Who is Henry in Country Bears?
I think you are the host of it.
He is like Lincoln, I believe, at least in some iteration.
He's Lincoln.
In some iteration, he's on the Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
And he is,
what's it Nemo?
He's doing a James Mason impression.
Oh, the narration on the subs.
OK. 20,000 leads.
Interesting. I don't know if he was Mickey a lot.
So it's not that other. It's not Jack Way.
It's not, well, you asked for it.
So there's still a difference.
Mickey is the other Journeyman.
The other who is around.
Yeah. Go falsetto who we can force to do this.
So and again, I kind of miss this era where they weren't tracking who was Mickey.
Very well. Multiple Mickey's in its confusing.
There's a lot of sloppiness to it.
But what a nice song. What a sincere song.
Yeah. Yeah. Describing just being in a pool, I guess, really, or the ocean.
It's what all the kids were into.
What they took from Flashdance is that the kids are all
is Flashdance the one where she dumps the water at the end?
Is that why?
Yeah. That's the one that was a there was a show in the European Park.
Yes. Yeah. With the bucket. Right.
Or at the end.
So I guess that's what they were thinking.
People want it because that had a lot of pop songs in it
and it had splashing in it.
Well, that's true. It did.
It is very much of a piece of the current
birdbrain take that like, well, everything everywhere.
All at once was very people liked it.
They love the multiverse.
Multiverse movies are hot.
And it's like, was that what people?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, I there's a yeah, there's a real cynicism.
My. Oh, yeah.
Everybody likes multiverse movies.
So let's all right.
All every every character we have in storage.
Bust them out. Throw them together.
Oh, yeah. Convoluted way.
Fast and Furious.
The Fast and the Furious was a big hit.
People love car movies.
Oh, yeah. You got to get some cars in movies, you know.
Well, that one follows a little more.
I guess it follows a little more.
I just feel like all movies are movies to some extent.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
I am. Most big movies have a big car race.
Yes. Yeah.
Strange to shift focus all of a sudden.
Well, but hey, they figured it out.
They did a song about skipping through the sprinkles.
Yeah. The lyric.
There's the the the sounds in this, the little like beep beep.
Like all that stuff is just so sad.
I can listen to that without even the vocals.
Yes. And the little if you those little splash sounds.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Our our synth samples, those do come out of like.
So it is kind of an interesting album in that regard that it has all these little
squiggles and bits of character.
The gyro gear, gear loose song has a lot of those just odd little like
blips and buzzes, which were pretty pretty new at the time.
So fun start. Good.
Let's talk a little about happy, happy birthday to you.
This is this is a big one.
This one, like, has a lot of life, I feel like outside of the album.
This is a different birthday song.
Yes. That was my very like 10 seconds in.
I'm like, oh, this is an attempt to make another birthday song.
Now, you heard this before. Huh?
Have you read you run into this birthday song before?
I it felt very familiar.
It was not glued in my mind like it didn't.
I didn't immediately recognize it.
Yeah, it's one of those.
It's like in my childhood somewhere.
Yeah. Did you have was this around for you?
I for sure recognize that I was it on like DTV or was it on Disney Channel
when we were a little probably right?
Some other use of it that they started using it in the parks after this.
And they amended the lyrics to be like it's Donald's birthday or or or
it's Mickey's birthday.
Birthday land, maybe.
Yeah. The the the main melody itself, I think is well here.
You know, I play it and I'll I'll say my take.
Yeah.
Happy birthday to you.
I want to do something special for you.
It's your birthday and you're special, too.
So I brought some wands from the outer wands.
You want to talk and squabble and sing just for you.
Happy birthday.
Happy happy birthday to you.
Yeah. OK, so this was used.
It was changed a little in 84.
To celebrate Donald Duck's 50th birthday used in a live parade
at Disneyland and Walt Disney World in Donald's honor and then used again.
It's for Mickey's 60th birthday
in the show Mickey's 60th birthday surprise performed at Disneyland at Disney.
Oh, OK, OK. Gotcha.
Yeah, there's a lot of stuff for the 60th.
So they want to celebrate these characters big, big birthdays,
but they're not given those Hill sisters a dime.
I say good riddance because this is this is better than the birthday song.
This is better than happy birthday.
Isn't it when it happens at a birthday party, aren't you like, oh, the song
garf, it's like embarrassing.
If it's your birthday, I would prefer not.
Now I have a birthday and then everybody has decided to sing happy birthday.
Happy birthday. I'm thrilled.
This is great news.
I want to I want to replace it.
I say, let's pass it the baton.
There's a couple. I mean, there's other birthday.
So I could Stevie Wonder, of course, has a birthday song.
I mean, any of these, I think, are good options for replacement.
Yeah, there's yeah, there's been a number, I feel like, where, yeah,
why not switch this?
I think we have perfected the model, but it's so it's so grandfathered in.
Well, I think the birthday song is like this awful US
Constitution type thing that prevents us from moving forward and changing.
And the traditionalists hold us back.
I say, I said, get rid of happy birthday.
It's time to replace it. I agree.
I mean, chain restaurants have all maybe already done it.
Some of them have their own signature birthday.
Like the band again, the whole thing.
Clat, happy, happy birthday.
Oh, yeah. Like, yes, you know, it's true.
Happy, happy birthday from Ben against to you.
Like, I don't you know, I'm not 100% on the start of that lyric.
I'm not 100%.
If anyone knows, please tell me.
I think we should all write our own new happy birthday song. Yeah.
That's I think what better it requires a little more work.
But what better gift can you give to your friends then?
All right. It's my birthday at the end of the month.
And I have written a new birthday song and I want you to sing this birthday song.
Do not sing the don't sing that would be a boring one.
Get practicing because it's complicated.
No pitchiness on the singing.
If you you won't be pitchy, if you practice, practice, practice.
I love it. And the earnestness of the vocals.
Yeah, I I brought this up to a friend who had this lodged in his head,
who just said, oh, yeah, the most like genuine song ever.
And then the lyric and backwards they sing.
There's a there's a weird little practice, practice backwards part.
I think maybe the big thing stopping this from becoming the main birthday
song is all of the specific mythology about Gwong's.
Do we really want to hear about Gwong's?
But I think that was all out by the time they did it for Donald and Mickey.
Sure. It's mainly about the chorus.
That's that's all I care. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think that's right.
We should see if there's the version of it for Donald.
I mean, it's probably has to live somewhere.
The the newer maybe the newer version for Donald is better.
Yeah. You just replace Donald's name with whoever.
Is there a Chuck E.
Cheese specific birthday song?
I want to say there was. Yes, I'm not coming up.
There might be a few of them.
I think they do.
They say it's your birthday.
Well, that's the Beatles, right?
OK, I feel like everyone agreed we're going to sing that.
Yeah. Instead, some people hate on that classic rock song.
And I don't I like it.
Classic Rock radio stations would always play that song
and then list what classic rock stars birthday was great.
Great fun. Good.
That's a good segment.
We're all going to write our own happy birthday songs.
That's the assignment eventually.
Yeah. Yeah. Change it up every year.
I mean, it makes you incentivized to keep going to birthdays,
to hear what the new song drop is.
Jason, you're going to have to write a song.
OK. OK.
I'll do my best.
I know. You wrote it.
Funny energy. You improvised the song.
I was not but six months ago or. Oh, yeah.
If you can call it that, sure.
I would call it that. Yeah.
Um, digital duck, digital duck, as mentioned at the top.
And now we're this is maybe the first that we fully arrived
in the initial premise of the album, which has nothing to do with splashing,
splashing near digital ducks and androids and robots.
Not a good idea.
I don't know why they put these premises together.
Right. They hold better than you'd think.
Digital duck.
This is about Donald Duck having a lot of these hordes of devices.
Love's devices.
We referenced it at the start of the episode.
Yes. Donald loves technology.
Born completely out of nothing.
Right. This is completely there.
Is there any short where Donald is like tinkering with a new TV or a new gadget?
Well, here's my thought is that at this time,
I feel like if you had a lot of gadgets, that was your that was a quirky little hobby.
Right. You were like a little like basement inventor kind of guy.
Yeah. And now we all have a million gadgets and their shackles and they burden our lives,
even though they're supposed to make it better.
But at the time, except for podcast devices and apps, this and Patreon.
So this this all is the enhancement.
I mean, we're coming up on like 20 years of podcasts.
So stuck around.
So that's got some saying.
Yeah. And profound.
The medium perfected right around now to 2017.
And now is really where it is.
Last five years, a golden age.
You know, really good for the industry.
And they they call them podcast feeds because you're like, feed me more.
Yeah, because of us.
Yum, yum. Say that to you next time.
It's the episode pop up.
And who's I think it used to be a little quirk, a little look at this weirdo.
And they, you know, like Wayne Zelinski, you know, but those are the inventor, though.
He is an inventor.
Yeah, inventor.
But Pete, well, or a peewee peewee had like Rubert Goldberg devices
to make like toast that the open up the one movie, right?
Not a gadget guy.
He I think he just like lives in a world of whimsy.
But they're both kind of like quirky weirdos.
And see what you're saying.
These are a little akin. Yeah.
Maybe that's maybe this was a phase of Donald's, you know,
and you're right that it comes from nowhere.
But why not? I love that.
A song with a big new trait about a character,
because what else are they going to say?
You know, again, do we want to hear a song?
You see, we do want to hear that.
I do not. Well, we we.
Jason, you're going to write a song about Donald Seat as well.
Happy birthday to Donald Seat.
Beep boop beep boop.
I did have to play it through twice because I was not 100 percent certain
that it was not Donald is a cyborg of some sort.
Like Donald is the gadget.
Yeah. You know what I mean?
He's a digital duck is what's said.
But then you have to hear the full context of
Donald loves his gadgets, even though they run amok.
He's a digital duck.
The chorus of digital duck is is a high point on this album, for sure.
Yeah. I guess I guess we should play a little bit of it.
But yeah, but you know.
Oh, yeah. Well, I guess we'll give you a little intro.
I am a man.
I'm not home.
Play with your machine.
I'm a song that you do.
So Donald has an answering machine, which is the first odd thing.
It was how when did the answering machine get invented?
I think, yeah, I think answer machines were there around pretty well in use
in the early 80s.
In the song of Donald using technology and it's an answering machine.
So that's the first thing.
Well, it's a big, you know, you start with a basic before you
you stretch it out to, you know, what's got this and crazy ones coming soon.
Yeah, well, I'll give a verse in the chorus. OK.
It's most gadgets, electric devices, a microwave blander
that cuts, chops and dices, chocolate detectors, a long takeover.
Donald has dozens in every room.
So he sounds paranoid, actually, when you listen to it.
He's got like detectors in every room.
Yeah, he's got like it sounds like he's kind of one of those guys
that thinks the government's watching him.
I think of all the like me like six
Disney characters, like the big six or whatever.
It's probably Donald, right?
He's like he's like Dale on King of the Hill. Yeah.
He's really paranoid about the deep state.
Well, but you also the flip side could be that he
you know, if you were the if you were the most paranoid,
you might not have any devices.
Maybe maybe maybe he actually trusts the government.
This is him being very patriotic.
Oh, that he because, yeah, you would get rid of all of it
if you really thought you were listening.
Yeah, it's either and you either have a full like army,
Navy surplus store in your house or you have nothing.
Yeah, maybe it's that he's trying to scramble the signals like the more
did I have interfering, creating like a digital interference wall.
Right. And they can't hear me because everything in my house is electric.
Yeah, we could do some really good bits if any of us could do this.
Donald voice. We are ultimately.
I can't. I was like, I'm like, can I try because I can't.
Where we go when we go?
I don't know. Yes, it's it's it's.
But I can't talk like that. Yeah.
Yeah. Now it's like like staring at like a like a ramp that you're like,
do I try to hit this on the bike?
And I think I will fall. I think I'm going straight into that chasm.
It's yeah. Evil can evil.
And you've you've never made the jump. No.
Now, try you've tried three or four times.
I know you made it out alive those times.
And I guess I just don't want it bad enough.
Yeah. Worry of the Donald impression.
I guess chocolate detectors.
His chocolate detectors.
Jason, did you catch that?
I'm liking that.
Well, I think I think an important thing to point out is that the gadgets run amok.
And I think this was another common like thing of like, oh, yeah,
they have a bunch of gadgets.
These gadgets, they don't even work.
You know, this this goddamn thing, this answering machine,
it reads as many messages as it records, you know?
Yeah. But he also has untested technology like chocolate detectors.
Yeah. I mean, that's a he made that up, I think.
They're sort of implying he invents, but they don't really.
He's trying like beta versions of things, right?
Because he's bought so much.
So now the catalog entity is offering him experimental.
Right. What would how would it how would a chocolate detector work?
I mean, is there any way?
I would assume like a metal detector.
It would be more if you were near chocolate.
Yeah. Yeah.
That might be a nice tool to alert you.
But would it be a scent based?
Is there something in chocolate that would that you could use to detect?
Or would it just be like you needed a dog?
This is yeah.
And is it is a digital version really going to be better than the biological one
that many cartoon characters have where it pulls them?
Yeah, they just like there is
in probably more cases a pie and then they are just they are flying.
They just are are in flight without even making the choice.
Maybe this is a way for Donald to attempt to get those Yogi Bear powers,
which he doesn't inherently have.
Oh, right, right, right.
Why not try to be able to smell? Yeah.
From so far away.
Maybe Donald has no sense of smell.
And this is really a tragic tale.
Oh, wow.
Do ducks need them?
Ducks have a prominent.
That's a good.
Prominent bill.
But how are their olfactory abilities?
I don't know. That's a good question.
Yeah, I don't.
In a way, does he not have a nose at all?
What's the I don't know anything about duck biology.
Can ducks Jason Google can duck smell?
I already have can ducks have chocolate pulled up?
And the answer is yes.
Stock chocolate is toxic to dust to ducks.
So oh, so maybe it's an anti chocolate.
He's trying to make sure he isn't around.
He figured it out.
And especially if he's got goofy or Pluto who comes over.
That's going to be a bad news.
On a later album, the Disney characters address a scenario
where Minnie makes a cake and then it is dropped.
I believe the word womb is involved.
I think the song is called Womp There It Went.
Right. And which now I'm realizing is actually a tragic tale,
not because of the waste of a cake,
but because if a cake was dropped in front of you and you could not
have chocolate, it was toxic to you.
That'd be a nightmare scenario.
It's straight to the hospital.
Jason Google can mice eat chocolate?
Because goofy, Pluto and Donald cannot have chocolate.
So if the if the dogs can't.
Yeah, dogs cannot have chocolate.
I mean, if you have a little milk chocolate, it's not that big of a deal.
But you do not want them eating chocolate.
OK, this seems like half a chocolate chip
or a few shavings from a chocolate candy bar won't kill your mousy,
although it won't do anything to contribute to his nutrition either.
This from animals stop mom dot com.
The mom that they jam a dot mom in there before the dot com.
I know you're mousy.
I thought you were subscribed to chocolate is only poisonous to mice
in large enough amounts, so it is possible for you to still occasionally
feed your mouse. They should all of Mickey.
Minnie should not be having trouble.
They should not have chocolate.
Hmm. None of these characters.
Well, this is why they have to splash dance because right there.
Robbed of the great joy.
So the chocolate detector makes a lot of sense now.
We cannot have chocolate in this house.
Yeah, this is this is what saves the lives of the big six or whatever.
The big the fab six.
All right, let's get to that course that I called a high point.
Gadgets, even though they're all about the.
Did you do that?
Wow.
And what?
I don't know.
Oh, what?
I have a Larry's in front.
It's it. Oh, it's a digital peanut butter spreader.
Oh, OK.
I think all the animals can have that.
Yeah, I think that's OK.
Oh, yeah, that's fine.
Dogs can. Good.
You know, there there's a marshmallow.
Toaster specifically for marshmallows.
There's a gravity sandals to climb up the walls.
Yeah, that's that's that's huge.
That's a big one. That is cool.
But I assume it malfunctions from time to time.
So it's it's I would like to see it.
This is like something where I would like to see this illustrated.
It would make sense of this was like a music video.
Mm hmm. But it's not as far as we know.
But like Donald doing all this crap and hurting himself, you know,
we'd love to see it.
I'm so confused by this.
Oh, ranch dressing.
Your child did not want.
He wanted nuggets and then he no longer wanted nuggets.
So now we get nuggets.
Leaving the sin.
I wanted to take a look at some ranch dressing.
I just have it.
No, I delivered to us behind me.
Yes. All of a sudden, a plate of chicken nuggets and organic ranch dressing
was placed on the table.
I think I could have dealt with the plate, but the ranch dressing just threw me.
And I keep you saw me.
Listeners can hear like I'm trying to push through it, too.
I was like, you know, I'm going to be very professional.
I just keep talking.
It's one of those things where I was talking.
I don't even know what I was saying.
I was just like, I'm just keep talking here and we're going to get through this.
This ranch dressing situation.
No, when ranch dressing delivered to you, Jason's chicken nugget
detector went off in his bag.
Damn it. No, I was going to say she put it down next to your existing plate
of chicken nuggets that you always have going for the show.
Yeah. Humans can eat chicken nuggets.
So that's good.
I mean, hey, feel free.
During the episode, that's clearly what's
we'd be rude to not share with the listeners.
Listeners. Yeah.
You can make it here now while we're recording this, which is impossible.
You'll be hearing it later.
But you would if you found us, you'd be welcome to chicken nuggets.
And ranch. That's digital duck.
The though I'm not in a rush to get on to hoedown at the robot farm.
I'm not a big fan of hoedown.
I'm not a robot arm, but Jason, I think I purely like it for the title.
You know, it's a good title.
It's goofy singing.
I go down at the robot farm is the most like you had this track.
You were trying to hit 11 tracks and you got it in here.
You farmed out one track, which is notable.
Hoedown at the robot farm in the next song, One Little Android.
I not my favorite songs on this album.
Let me say this.
My notes about I made the space for if I had notes about one little Android
and the only road I wrote down was hmm.
Yeah, yeah. So I'll hear.
I'll just give it 10 seconds of each.
We can go.
This is where I wrote down they should have called it robot.
Through them.
Right.
Think yourself a partner with plenty of charm is a hoedown at the robot farm.
Now, hoedown the robot firm at least has like goofy
like square dance calling and stuff.
So there's something there's that element is good.
He says swing your robot. Yeah.
So I think the robot farm is a place.
It's like a like
I think it's a dating scenario for I think.
I think Goofy is has set up some kind of sex robot
and that's where it loses.
Like, you know, you kind of here's the mixer.
You kind of you choose your robot, you swing your robot
and then you see where things go.
And I don't know how he got into the shade.
You swing like not a literal swing.
Swing is in part different partners.
Well, I I'm not sure.
I mean, I think it is.
I take him at his word that it is a square dance scenario.
But it is like, here's the fun part where we dance before we,
you know, get a little wilder before we get wilder.
I think that Goofy has been suckered by some shady organization.
He's being abused of his celebrity status.
He's like he's so he's dumb and he's honored
that he's been asked to endorse something.
And then he's landed. Now his face is on this
this place that's frankly not safe in a number of ways.
If there's a malfunction, if these robots go run amok,
much like Donald's gadgets, then you're dead.
And you're dead in like a situation.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Hold on at the robot farm or you end up like what's is the T 1000
that you get like suddenly like a big like metal spike through your head.
You're just trying to have innocent sex with a robot.
Anything could go wrong.
You know, your robot army could be defeated by a child
that flies a star speeder into the central like nervous system
of the control for like Phantom Menace, Anakin Skywalker.
We need to feed the entire battle droid army.
And they all shut down.
They all shut down. Yeah, that could happen.
Yeah. And they like clamp.
They clamp down on your dick.
Right. Then they shut down in the auto
the shut off mode.
Scrimmage. You would hope.
OK, look, you would hope if you had a sex robot, that there is some fail
safes to not like it's not going to just close it down like it's,
you know, chopping it.
Not like an airlock, like the way that people characters die in movies
all the time because the airlock. Right.
It cuts it. And now people now people are in like they get sucked into space
or they're in a room where all the disease is.
I don't want that to happen.
You cannot. If let me just give this advice to future sex robot builders.
You cannot even have that as possibility.
No, if anything, it's got to be an airbag.
This has to be a situation where something soft, such as people
are going to get permanently damaged down there.
Write it down if you're working on it.
It can't be any thoughts on this one.
Well, you know, I'm just thinking it could be a valuable way
to teach people lesson about the hubris of man.
Oh, no. You're clamping.
Yeah, I might be taking a serling approach where it's just like folly.
So you want to like play like the play dough thing where you just can cut it off
and it'll fall.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah. When you're slicing up like a play dough,
they all eat like a bit of spaghetti or something.
So you'll say it'll be like
like an episode of HBO's perversions of science.
You want to teach a lesson.
I'm baffled by that one.
But that HBO is just the real.
No, no, I think that's a real show.
It's the name of science.
OK, do we not?
If I never brought up the HBO Max featuring.
Perversion of science.
Yes, I am correct.
This is the name of it.
1997.
This is a real.
Danny Elfman.
Whoa. Original Network HBO.
Your brain was a sponge at this time for Sebastian
Jackles and Deadly Games and perversions.
Well, there is an episode of Crimes of the Future.
Eastern promises perversions of science.
There is classic Cronenberg.
There is an episode of perversions of science starring Mr.
Kevin Pollock about a sex robot.
Is it him or is it Christopher Walken?
My memory is it's him, but I maybe I wouldn't know in 97.
Wait, so this is like an anthology.
This is like a Twilight Zone kind of thing.
Yes. I feel like Shatner was on one, but maybe that's a different anthology.
Shatner and whoever Melanie Shatner is daughter.
Probably daughter, but who knows, could be wife daughter.
But Perversions of Science was like a sexy anthology show with like,
I assume, some sort of morality component, but maybe that wasn't part of it.
Oh, my God. There's one with Vincent Shiavelli, that crazy guy from Batman
Returns that were like insane bulbous man, the character actor.
And then ghost to be sent to another plane of existence
where his murdered wife may still be alive.
Murdered wife played by Elizabeth Berkley.
Oh, my God. Where is the show been?
All my favorite actors.
I mean, look, is this a great show?
Ray Newman, Needy McClurg, every episode I look at, it gets better and better.
Let me read you the synopsis of the of the Kevin Pollock episode
called Boxed in Sex Farce about a horny, faithful space ace who,
after several years, finally arrives home for a tryst with his fiance.
Unfortunately, her admiral dad forces them to wait until marriage.
I think that's Shatner.
Our admiral dad forces them to wait until marriage.
So the pilot decides to use a sex bot.
Big mistake.
So these are written by David Goyer.
Wow. Oh, my God.
Toby Hooper directed. Wow.
All right. We got to hang. OK, OK.
We got to calm down. Barry Williams.
Oh, my God. Every day I'm in blue in this Wikipedia.
I was with somebody.
It makes me want to stomp around the DuckTales theme.
All I'll say is I was with somebody two days ago said,
oh, I got to call Barry Williams and I'll tell you off. Oh, man.
I think I've alluded to the fact that I could think I can get Barry Williams'
phone number very easily. Whoa.
Yeah, I don't want to brag.
It's the most obvious.
You see, you don't think my Rolodex is any good.
I want you to skim down to W.
Notice it.
Recognize it. OK.
One little Android.
I have nothing to say.
I wrote down I'm not a fan.
Why don't we like one little Android?
Because this one's the kid like this is just like a like a
fell down and then we were.
It's a.
Sing along day.
Yeah, this is a perfect song for kids.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the noises are good.
The music is good, but it's like a little it's slow
and there's not much going on.
How many lyrics? Not much of a narrative in place.
Yeah, boring. Yeah, yeah.
Now the next track, Chippendales vacation.
This has a real this this intro, you know, I it.
I don't love hearing chipmunks sing.
I'm going to be honest.
I don't like I'm not dying to hear a lot of Alvin and the chipmunks
covers or anything.
So it loses me when vocals kick it.
But this intro is this is real peppy. Yes.
Wow.
On vacation.
My name is just one.
We want to check the life.
I watched the show.
I just like fantastic.
Yeah, they trip the light fantastic.
That's stuck out to me.
That in Mary Poppins returns.
What's that? Isn't that a song in Mary Poppins returns?
It might be thinking of that sounds right.
I mean, it's just a phrase for dancing.
There's a hat when this stuff hat go.
The one that the notes go like half step up.
I'm in heaven.
If I mean like it's like, I don't know.
I should really I'm not.
My band is going to be upset that I didn't explain that better.
I like when.
This is what I'm talking about.
Here we go.
Done done.
I said, and then it fully goes full steps.
And it's very satisfying.
I like when they each sing what they like and then they both start singing.
Yeah, I was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was too hard on their vocals.
I think this is a good song.
I was also I heard was listening to it yesterday and I go at first.
I go, I don't know.
And then by minute and I go, that's good.
Yeah, I like it.
I think it is a catchy song.
It probably.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a blast.
You know, since that was a big hit of fun synth sounds, let me say
my favorite thing that I discovered about this album.
So these people who composed most of the songs, but not all Michael and Patty Silvershire.
So they owned a keyboard store in Palo Alto.
This is where they came from.
So they would sell keyboards, but they also had early access to keyboards
that were not being used everywhere.
And they were particularly a fan of Yamaha keyboards.
So they would make demos in their off time and then send them to Yamaha.
Hey, what do you think?
We use your keyboards only and we love them.
Yamaha got in touch with them and said, you get better sounds out of our stuff
than anybody we've heard.
This stuff is amazing.
What can we do for you?
So they Yamaha started like put them in some artist development program
and may have even made the connection to Disney or like giving them a little bit
of money to make stuff that got Disney's attention ultimately.
So that's the big thing with these people.
Like they wrote fun songs and I think it's Michael who's singing on a lot of them.
But the like the the the Yamaha aspect of it can't be overlooked.
So they start recording this album proper.
They're doing it at a Yamaha facility in Glendale.
That's where this was recorded.
Not a recording studio, but like a Yamaha plant, essentially.
Where they are developing their new synth technology.
And so they are they're literally like things are coming off the presses and handed to them.
Hey, we have this new thing.
Do you want to use it?
And the biggest one of these was we've got this new keyboard.
We're dying for people to use it.
It's called the DX7, the Yamaha DX7.
This is where I'm sent nerding out a little bit.
Have you ever heard of the DX7?
Is that a great thing?
But major basically what happened is please use this.
We need somebody to use it.
This is 1983.
The keyboard is brand new.
So most of the sounds on this album are the Yamaha DX7.
Within three years, it is the dominant keyboard on pop radio.
It's so much of what anybody likes from that era.
There's literally I saw like in 1986, they was on this keyboard was on 40 percent of the number one songs that year.
So and at the time it was only this weird Disney kids.
It was only Chip and Dale's vacation.
Just to shout out a couple uses of it.
It's a lot of like 80s ballad electric piano.
That's that's a lot of it.
Chicago hard habit to break or Whitney Houston.
It's a big sign. I forget what against all odds.
Phil Collins song.
If OK, the very beginning of danger zone,
but really, I think the base that is one of the big DX7 things is the really plunky base,
which is also another part of me, the Michael Jackson song in Captain EO,
Mr. Mr. Broken Wings that has the
take on me is the big one that cracks it open.
So like this thing is just all over all these incredibly iconic songs,
including and one that I found yesterday as I'm digging down the rabbit hole,
something I complained about on the show once that then then was a gripe.
Then somebody was mad that I complained about.
I complained about what I think is kind of a dopey keyboard solo
on what's love got to do, right, right, which has this sudden harmonica.
But I found out that is the Amadeus, that is the harmonica preset on the DX7.
So things that I love, things that I find kind of goofy,
but I like that that person said, hey, why don't you shut up and enjoy it?
Just enjoy the goofiness of the and isn't that what all these sounds are on?
Splash dance is some of its legit good.
And then there's all these bloops and blips that are sometimes silly.
Not every song is great, but that seems like the spirit
of this great iconic keyboard, the Amadeus seven.
Some dope and some silly, but it's all fun.
I was just taking a look on eBay and I think those go for like seven fifty.
But I have a my grandmother had an like a keyboard synth
in the 80s in a basement that I have now and it still works.
And that's a PSS four seventy.
Yes, that's four seventy, which is similar.
I think that the other one is like a higher end model.
This was more of a like casual one.
But some of the sounds on this I could I could make with this old piece of equipment.
I almost use this to make the McGruff album,
but then I could not figure out a way the music wasn't popping enough.
And again, I'm not a good mixer producer.
And I was like, it's going to be too tough to like make this like
give yourself the digital crutch like there are the the analog.
I guess it was not analog, it's a digital.
Yeah, but it'd rather just go straight into the Pro Tools or whatever you're using.
Yeah. And I was using like logic and stuff.
But in a in another in another multiverse,
there was a scenario where I would make a splash dance song for the episode today.
But it's a busy, busy couple of weeks.
Yeah, so but maybe in the future, if there's yeah.
Hey, if you can find some sounds, yeah, dig into that.
I bet there's some stuff in the family.
Yeah, I have I have a little demo stuff to from this as well.
So, oh, boy, great.
Yeah, I would love to hear some stuff in the spirit of splash dance,
because what a delight.
And I think side two is maybe superior to what I think.
I think the best stuff is coming.
Yes, for sure. Including.
Well, here we go.
After that big tear about stuff that I like.
Now we've landed on fucking Sparks, one of my favorite bands in the world.
The only outside artist, I think, on this album, sort of inexplicably.
With the song Minnie Mouse.
That was a good talk.
All is just a house.
What a house.
Minnie, Minnie, I like Minnie.
Wonderful. Yeah, wonderful.
What do you guys think of this song as not as like
not as big of Sparks heads?
How does it as this hit you?
Yeah, Yellowstone, I have been every year meaning to get way into Sparks.
I will. It's a big blind spot for me.
I kind of always knew them as like
the Velvet Underground or Joy Division of like influenced a lot of what came after.
You know, yeah, yeah.
I ran into that.
I didn't know they were advertising that movie, the Edgar Wright
documentary as your favorite band's favorite band.
Yeah, and that does.
I they were my favorite band when I was a middle schooler.
But that sounds like very early.
They might be a giant.
Like it feels like there's a story line.
Yeah, they're compared a lot in terms of and I don't know.
They might be giants at all,
but they're compared in terms of idiosyncratic themselves,
no matter how much times they cover a zillion genres, that kind of thing.
Yeah, they're like smart, funny guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can get that. And then, yeah.
Which funny is a tough area if you're like it's always a dicey zone for our.
It feels like either we want our music serious or we want it to be weird, Al.
And it's just all the way funny. Yes.
Occupying the middle space is because it makes you go, is this a joke?
Is it a novelty?
And I think people are always weirded out by this.
I mean, because they're they are weird.
They look weird.
They've always been pretty aggressively weird.
What I love about them.
I mean, when I first looked them up, I think a few years ago,
you guys saw them, is that right?
What do you see? Yeah, I saw them at the Ace Hotel in 2015.
That was the first time I saw them.
And then I saw the trailer for that documentary.
And I am sure people who don't know, I mean, I had to look it up.
But one of them has a mustache is called a duster.
It is a style mustache that was popular in the early 20th century.
And the notable thing about that kind of mustache is it's just a little bit longer
than a Hitler mustache. And I was like, what's going on here?
Oh, are these guys pretty? Is this a British joke?
It's like a John Waters kind of.
Yeah, it's kind of like a job.
That's a little longer way to.
Yeah, that might be his style today.
Yeah, that as well.
What's that little Richard had that kind of thing?
He had a little little pencil thin. Yeah.
Well, so he's run both kinds of upsetting.
But since he's done it, yeah.
Oh, that's true. Yeah.
Yeah. The pencil thin.
Yeah. These are provocative mustaches.
Jimmy Buffett song pencil thin mustache.
He has a pencil thin mustache.
I wish I had a pencil thin mustache.
You want to stop in you, Jimmy?
Go for it like Boston Black did. Mm hmm.
Like pulp detective character Boston Blackie.
Oh, of course. Of course.
We all know. Yeah.
It's like, well, that's yeah, that's that's Ron Mayall.
It's brothers Ron and Russell.
Ron is the mercurial, mostly silent keyboard player
with a Hitler mustache for a long time.
The Russell, the singer who very androgynous
sounding for a long time, a little less so now,
but he's always been falsetto, just the early stuff.
You I mean, like it's very common for people to think it's a woman singing.
And it was in kind of a glam rock era initially.
A great part of that documentary is when John Lennon tells someone about Sparks.
It's someone else impressive.
And I can't recall now, but John was like, did you did you watch
Top of the Pops last night?
Mark Bolan was playing with Adolf Hitler.
It's a pretty good breakdown.
Mark Bolan of T-Rex.
Yeah. So like glam guy mixed with silent
Hitler, who just glares, who's just joyless and remains such
it's a great part of their show now that he gets up and dances once
and he's very tall and imposing and he's like Frankenstein.
Or so that when he walks to center stage, it's kind of upsetting.
Like, what's he going to do?
And then like it loosens the tie.
It's a big process, a big procedure.
And then just does the most like simple, big flailing arm dance
you ever seen. Everybody loses their shit.
There's so much fun.
I don't want to just go on and on.
Oh, of course I want to go on and on.
This is the opportunity.
But let's talk about Minnie Mouse specifically.
Oh, yeah. A spin off song, I guess you could say.
That's correct. Yeah.
So they did an album in the early 80s called Angst in My Pants,
which has my favorite album cover of theirs where they're getting married.
It's a nice brother wedding.
It's very, very touching.
And that is a song called Mickey Mouse, which I also highly recommend.
Odds. Both songs are kind of like not.
You almost imagine they wrote them with their vague knowledge of the characters.
They are not exactly like, yeah, here's everything we know,
especially Minnie Mouse feels like, all right, let's figure out how to intellectualize
based on one foot. What do we know about her?
She's a mouse. She's an address.
She dates Mickey Mouse. She looks good.
Yeah. Yeah. Mm hmm.
Friendly. Nice. Nice.
Yes. So Mickey Mouse, this very odd song on this early 80s
and the album of theirs, Disney is initially upset about it
and maybe thinking about how can we squash this?
But then it starts getting some local airplay in L.A.
They are they realize, oh, this might be a good thing for us, actually.
As Russell said, if it helps them advertise their theme parks,
suddenly they're into it.
So this album was brewing at the time and they said, hey, would you want to do?
Is there a companion song?
Do you have anything else like, I don't know, Minnie Mouse?
And they were like, how can we do this without breaking the bank creatively?
All right, let's do exactly what they said.
Let's make a song about Minnie Mouse, which is very delightful.
This thing otherwise is like kind of a genuine.
Let's make a nice album for kids.
And then in this case, it's these like very subversive artists.
They're like, how can we play Disney for some money? Sure.
Which seems like a lot of their careers, like,
how do we get our weird shit into movies and kind of keep this odd little engine
afloat? So hats off to them for playing Disney, for reversing their initial.
It is funny. Dislike of it like Devo does Disney stuff and then like
they might be giants as a kid album, children's album.
Yeah, there are two.
Well, and they do the cover.
OK, let me see if I can get this right off the top of the head.
They might be giants to a cover of Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow
that is on the soundtrack of that
spacey CG animated Disney movie.
Is it called Meet the Robinson?
Oh, really? Yeah.
Oh, that's weird. OK.
So all these like similar kind of guys ended up with Disney.
So well, it's a way to. Yeah.
It's a way to make some dough for our band that doesn't like a lower
naturally make a zillion dollars every year.
It's a good point.
Which that's what I love about all of the bands that you've listed.
These are all like they are not like meant to be like these are not.
This isn't what big bands are like, but they they stay afloat and they stay weird.
And I love them. I got to see Sparta.
It was my first concert back after all this time at the Disney concert
all earlier this year.
It was so emotional.
The standing ovation went on forever.
There's so much love in the rent, so much like we've missed you
and we appreciate we love that you are like at a career height now
with your documentary and with Annette, this big movie
that they're spiking 50 years in.
They will. I love them so much.
I do that anyway. All I have to say, check out Sparks.
And if this song may mess, it did kick Sparks back open for me
because I knew a couple of the big I knew.
Come on to my house, the big glam album and the Georgia Marauder sent the album.
But I didn't know a lot.
And then I stumbled on to Minnie Mouse and I was like, wait a sec.
Because I didn't know about kind of the early 80s, kind of like breakfast club era.
Like they have a song in Valley Girl, I believe.
And then that was my way back in.
And now I'm into like, oh, my God, I've missed like 17 albums that rule.
So I credit Minnie Mouse for that.
I wouldn't call it like one of their top 50 songs,
but it has everything you want out of them, I think.
And it's catchy and odd.
And I don't know.
But but also, I do I have blinders on is Minnie Mouse,
an album low light, and I am missing it.
No, it's not a low light.
I will say I think I like the next two songs a little better.
Oh, sure.
I mean, we're coming up. Oh, I love the next two songs.
This is just a great block of an album.
Yeah, yeah. So so no, it's up.
It's up and it's the second.
It's toward the top of the songs I like in the album, for sure.
Yeah, yeah.
That line about that.
You could say she's just a mouse, just a mouse.
The Taj Mahal is just a house.
What a house. Yeah, yeah.
And the discussion of her dress, where did you get that dress?
It's Parisian, I would guess.
That's where I'm really like they looked at a picture is what they did.
What do we what do we possibly how can we do?
All right, we can get a stanza out of her dress.
That's one fact that we know about her.
Pretty good rhyme.
They class her.
This is, I think, a very classy portrayal.
As is look, as is the next.
So this is kind of the mini block. Right.
That's true. Album, I would say.
She really gets the time to shine, if not time to sing.
But you're thinking about her. Yeah.
She looms. She's on your mind.
She was. I mean, she's always on my mind.
That's what I think. But that's another story.
What you always on my mind.
How do you how do you feel about this next one?
I love this song. Oh, boy.
Mickey, she's got a question.
It's all the time. This has come up before.
This was in some special.
We talked about it. I don't remember why, but it's that they do a version of it
in some parade or something or other.
But this is one of those also that you might know outside of the album.
You want to you want to get a quick hit of it? Sure.
I mean, does it get any better than that?
Just basic.
I feel like the Olivia Newton, John of it.
I feel like Laura Branigan.
This is just like a nice girl song from early 80s.
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
That's one of the best.
You can tell that this keyboard is going to have pop dominance.
Yeah. Off of that, if it can do stuff as catchy as that.
Does how does it make you feel given your feelings about Minnie Mouse?
Mick Mick is kind of a nickname for Michael.
So you could call me Mickey.
It's not out of the realm of possibility.
So can I listen to this and imagine this lady is singing to me?
You know, Michael, would it be better if she said my full name?
That's not my birth certificate. Yes.
But I can I can dream.
Yeah, she's got it.
She's like just this.
It's like I'm imagining this woman is my friend.
And she's like, come on, man, don't you see it?
She's into you. Don't you get it, man?
What Minnie Mouse? Are you crazy?
Why don't I go to the moon or something?
That's impossible.
But a girl like Minnie would never be the guy like me.
I mean, I'm a letterman jacket in this scenario.
We're by my locker.
And this letterman jacket has the marching band
on the one breast.
Well, it is tennis and marching.
And it's a guy. Yeah.
And then this will this girl, who's my friend,
who's secretly in love with me, but I don't even know it.
She's telling me about many.
Yeah, I was going to say this song.
It's like, oh, it would be a lot easier for us when we were young and stupid.
If we've had written songs about who had crushes on us.
It would, you know, it would have been a lot better even.
Yes, because I was actively avoiding anyone who had a crush on me.
Yeah, I think I imagine that this is how it would work,
is that there would be a middle person who would spell it out.
Yeah, I will always at any time and that, no, you're not going to have to
feel out the vibes yourself, potentially land on your face.
I like if only if only this song could have existed for us to point us
in the direction of people that we dated or wanted to date or in your case, mice.
It would have been high school would have been a lot easier
if there were multiple songs explaining things to me.
How did this?
Mickey, here's how you kiss a girl.
Here's how you kiss.
Here's how you kiss a girl.
What's the rest of that?
Yeah, let me let me show you on this doll.
Mickey, let me show you on the doll.
You don't need to worry about what you're worrying about.
It's not real.
Your parents were just watching the local news too late and couldn't sleep.
Yeah.
Scott, don't waste your high school years on this long distance relationship.
It's an excuse to not date in real life.
These are these are all been very helpful.
Yeah.
What? Why did this has come up before?
Do you remember the context of the song?
Yeah, I think it's that it's in some special act it out in something.
I can't recall what, though.
Yeah, we definitely thought.
We need to.
Yeah, there's a little like sketch essentially.
I don't I don't remember what or why we we watched it.
But yeah, this again, this one like Happy Birthday
kind of remained in the in the family a little bit.
Yeah, they ended up with this nice pile of like updated songs.
So we have things that aren't high.
Ho, we've got I love that they're trying.
Let's can we get some new Disney classics and standards into the mix here in 1983?
And it almost works.
These had legs for a little while.
I think we've forgotten them now a bit.
It doesn't have.
Contempt is too strong of a word,
but doesn't have the indifference to the Mickey rap album.
Like the Mickey rap album feels very.
What's the word? Yeah.
Crass trying to take advantage of a moment.
Crass is probably right.
Sending. Yeah, condescending is probably like.
What does he say?
Mickey even on there, he's like, clean music squeaky squeaky clean.
That's really patronizing.
Just as as hair away from going rap more like crap.
You know, here's how it's really done.
This is what you need. It's one.
I'm that's it, though.
They don't have disdain.
I mean, that's the other way.
It's like we have to do a rap thing now.
Somebody told us as opposed to we found this nice couple
who sing so genuinely and who really care about getting cool sounds out of Yamaha.
Let's take advantage of this and make some happy songs for the kids.
Yes, it is. It feels.
Yeah, it feels it feels pure, whether it was or not.
Yeah, yeah.
We just have to feel that way.
Just like love.
Like it could be not true, true.
But as long as it feels that way, that's a lesson I should have learned.
Yeah, great. Yeah.
It could be a total sham, but if it feels all right, feels good.
You know what? Love, love always starts with one of the two people
being totally indifferent to you.
Continue to pursue them through their indifference.
We'll eventually do a 180 turn.
All the media you've consumed has led you to that where you're supposed
to like pine for someone for months.
And destroy yourself.
It's not that most media is written by people who used to be fucking losers.
And now they're rich.
They're writing the fantasies they didn't have.
Yeah, that was a long tear in the Mickey voice.
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, you ass whore.
You ass whore.
You losers.
I'm going to talk about Gyro Gear Loose.
Oh, yeah.
Which again, it's tough on an album with Sparks and my favorite bands
that it is possible that this lands at number one for me.
And this has come up before listeners might recall that this is a song
that I have genuine emotions about.
Mm hmm. I feel I feel feelings about this.
I don't know what they are exactly or why.
Like lyrically, I don't understand why I have so many because I don't.
It's a song about a Ducktales character who exists only in comic form at this time.
Right. So why am I so moved by the tale of Gyro Gear Loose?
And I think it's I think it's that music.
Hmm.
Oh,
shiny line.
It's so sincere.
I'm just rolling this through.
Yeah.
It's a no rush.
This is a thinky song.
We're not driving to that chorus.
We don't even have drums yet.
Are you crying yet, listener?
Crazy car.
Digitators and solar skates that glow in the dark.
Is escalator sneakers once you've.
Good base.
And it's a bumpy base.
Up and down.
So folksy.
I do.
I makes a teaching feel also in people's sleep.
They learn to spell.
Instead of counting.
There we go.
Wow.
Now they're just cutting loose.
I mean.
That's the.
What's OK.
Why is this?
Why do I OK?
Well, emotions about the song.
The synth is a lot of it.
Obviously, I saw a lot of it.
Yep.
The little like Tomorrowland bloops and bleeps and like the.
Little they hit every song like one of them is like it's like a snore.
It's like a digital version of a snore.
Also, when they're singing about gyro gear loose, they're making them sound like.
Who's a pot like the greatest man who ever lived like the nicest.
Yeah.
Pure man, whoever duck, whoever lived.
This is like the you know, we want these billionaires and these tech people to save us from things.
And it's never going to happen.
We know how dark all these people are.
Yeah.
Gyro gear loose could do it.
It sounds like it.
He's like he's like humble.
He's selfless.
He's helping everyone.
And makes a carbon remover that takes it from the sky.
Saves the planet for every girl and guy.
Gyro gear loose invented by Carl Barks created by Carl Barks invented in the Disney comics.
And eventually shows up in DuckTales and the newer DuckTales.
His first appearance was in the.
OK, this name Sport Goofy and Soccer Media.
It was a 1987 TV special.
We get some sport in the next song too.
That's what that's from.
Wow.
So predated DuckTales a little bit.
Yeah.
They clearly pulled him because it was this it's this robot tech oriented album.
That must have been the idea.
But yeah, I agree.
It's like these these inventions are so nice.
A smile suspender to keep people's faces up when they're feeling like.
Clockwork Orange.
Yeah, I guess a little bit.
Yeah.
But I don't think that's how he views it.
I think he's like I see people frowning all the time.
What can I do?
Yeah.
I think this is a big thing.
There's a verse that's kind of about how there he makes mistakes.
Sometimes the inventions don't go right.
I think this is a very Rex like character.
I think he's a guy who's trying his best with 80s technology.
I think it's a lot of synth sounds surrounding this nice character.
I just I don't know.
It's I bet if and I look this up because sometimes I'm no real musician,
but I will pick out chords on the piano and I will see something and go,
oh, that's why.
That's why that one hits like I like.
All right.
It's a F major seventh.
Everything I've ever looked up with F major seven is something that hits me in the heart.
And I bet if you did the notation of this, it would explain why this song I know I would
look at and go, oh, there you go.
That's why it's one of those or is that it's sustained or something.
Yeah.
Well, yeah, chord progressions certainly like the chord progression of gummy bears
is so satisfying if you just play it on the acoustic guitar.
Similarly, if you play the theme song to David the gnome on the guitar,
it's a similar sort of vibe to it.
We're so in that it's in the DNA.
It's not about all this instrumentation, even though they have the cool Yamaha's.
There's a walk.
It's got to be in the song.
I love a good walk up, which has is on like the Mickey.
She's got a crush on you.
Boom, boom, boom.
Like it walks it up.
This is your thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Talk about this before.
Like I miss you on the Rolling Stones or in like any disco song.
We're like, boom, boom, boom.
Like it's one.
It stays on the same note and then the other note.
Like you play it bounces back and forth between the same note and then an ascending note,
usually like a full step.
You know, it gives it all lift.
That's the and it lifts it up and I love it.
I miss sucker for it almost every song it's on.
Wow.
So there are these weird little musical things that people love,
whether they know what they are or not, or they can poorly explain them like I have.
This is like, I don't know how sincere we are
a lot, especially lately.
You get me talking about you're talking about these these step ups,
talk about chords, gyro gear loose and sparks and yama.
This is what's in my heart.
We've heard some of what's in your heart.
Yeah.
And it's funny the gyro gear loose is inspiring all of it.
You know what I was trying to think of?
Like, is there a song that does something similar to me?
And I thought of one, which is, have you ever heard the album version of Thank You
for Being a Friend, which we know is the Golden Girls theme,
but is originally by the artist Andrew Gold?
Right, right.
Look it up.
I have not heard it.
This is like, I think it's got a similar where it's like you feel some feelings about it,
partially because it's a theme song about some nice characters,
but it's got a lot of inherent heart where it's a little cheesy potentially.
And what it also has is a guy harmonizing with himself beautifully.
This is something I think across music that I love.
Michael Silver sure is doing it great here.
Uh huh.
Andrew Gold does it great.
It's why I like Rundgren.
It's why I like Queen.
Anything with like really great.
This guy is going to, Michael McDonald,
anything where somebody that stacks on himself and sings really heartfelt.
Uh, I'm a sucker for it.
Is there a song, let me, let me really get real here.
If we're talking about it, we're in the, if we're down here, uh, uh, is there a song
that you just like, it's like a little too much emotionally for you sometimes to listen to,
or all the time.
Oh.
There's like a song, there's one song that pops into my mind.
It's more of a recent song or I like cry.
I just cry.
I don't know why.
Oh.
Not like uncontrollably necessarily, but I start to like well up.
Uh, so not dude looks like a lady.
It's not dude looks like a lady.
It's, uh, uh, amazing by Aerosmith.
Understood.
Just push play by Aerosmith.
I'm a crazy guy.
Yeah.
I like crazy too.
No, it's a song by Randy Neumann called Wandering Boy about a guy who's like son.
Like, I don't know if he's like something happens to him and he hasn't seen him in years.
And he's like imagining that he's okay.
I don't know why this song gets me.
Well.
But like it really like immediately I'm even getting weird talking about it now.
Wow.
It's weird.
I don't know what it is.
Oh my God.
It's strange.
Look at those chords.
It's probably all in there.
It seems like lyrically thematically.
I think it's thematically.
I mean the music itself, there's a lot of Randy Newman songs that are so sad.
Like I think it's going to rain today.
There's like something like so devastating about him.
I don't know this one.
Maybe I haven't dug in a lot.
Wandering Boy is newer.
I know some Randy, but I, you know, I'll throw on.
So I'll willingly put on I Love L.A.
Of course.
That's all that.
Yeah.
Oh, sure.
That's the song they play when the Dodgers win.
I like guys.
I like other guys.
I like people that go from insanely sincere to just fucking sarcastic.
Like Randy Newman is like goes wildly both ways.
Just cutting and mean and sarcastic and evil.
And then just the like saddest shit.
It's a little Sparks tunes.
A little Elvis Costello.
You know, that's a bit with that Elvis Costello, Burbeck, or I can't handle all the time.
That's a hell of an album.
Boy, that is like, look, I'm not in a divorce scenario.
I hope.
But it's made me it's an album that made me understood what a divorce must feel like.
Yeah.
So it's such a heart ripper.
That warren zeman song.
The one he wrote when he died was dying to keep me in your heart for a while.
That's a real sad one.
Won't you listen to what's too much?
I think I stop.
I stopped right before getting too emotional, but that Ben Folds five song boxing,
which is about like the interview with.
Is it Howard Cassell and Muhammad Ali?
Yeah.
Oh, I got to gear up if I'm going to listen to the song time, which is on a solo album,
which oddly weird Al sings on.
Sings like really good.
Oh, yeah.
Time is on.
Background vocals.
Time is on what's a song for Solomon.
That's oddly my favorite one.
Interesting.
That's a heavy one for me, though.
I'll avoid some Ben Folds.
Another episode to do after this, but I'd like to just talk about music for a few hours.
I'll be honest with you.
All right.
Back to the.
Back to it.
Back to Sport Mickey.
Well, you know, here we end up at a now we're in an area of, you know,
a band that we have some emotions tied up into and that's Halix because
we're so proud of what's happened with Halix, the way Halix has exploded.
In these last few years.
And so this song, you can always be number one
sung by Laura Mumford, who ended up being the singer of Halix.
So she was in the Walt Disney Records, which, by the way, there's some shared personnel
essentially like the people producing this thing were also working on Halix at the same time.
These were the attempts of these people who were doing kind of boring read along
albums to like, what if we could make some music?
When you look at it that way, they're making this thing where they bring sparks in.
There's a bunch of sense.
And then they're making a band in Disneyland with a fake wookie and a guy driving a keyboard
cart around.
It's like these guys were getting trigger happy in a fun way.
Yeah.
It's I will say this.
The person I was with who knows Mary Williams also knows Halix.
You said that almost as though I don't want anybody.
I don't want the neighbors to hear.
I don't want to call Barry Williams.
Yeah.
When I first started listening to this track, I thought it sounded a little like ABBA.
Extreme.
Oh yeah.
Like your opening sounds like take a chance on me.
They're starting to take a chance on me.
Not necessarily.
You can always be number one.
You can always be a winner.
Even if you play the game for years.
Yeah, that's an ABBA.
Yes.
Yeah.
Really powerful part.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah.
The world of sports is.
So yeah.
World of sports.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think it maybe wears the ABBA a little too much on its sleeve.
It's nice.
I think it.
Yeah.
That's a big queen kind of breakdown though a little bit or not.
Yeah, for sure.
I like it.
Yeah, I like it too.
It's coming after it.
This is a tough run, but it's again in the superior second half.
I feel like a lot of albums that we've talked about end up falling apart a little as you speed up.
But here we go.
We're going on and on because all the emotion is here in the second half of Splash Dance.
Yeah, we're talking about Harry's House.
I've been listening to Harry Styles' album and the first half is so good.
And the second half is good, but maybe I just haven't gotten to it enough.
But this I feel the opposite.
Yeah.
So we'll see.
That's the case with you can always be number one.
We just have to.
Or we got to like work out to it.
We got to go do a big run with it.
Yeah, we should.
We should work out to it.
Yeah.
I like the I don't know the melody of it, but I wrote down the lyrics in my head.
It's like Goofy has been known to goof.
That's how he got his name.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
It was not his first name, but yeah, that's how we got.
Oh, that's right.
That's it.
Yes, he did have to get his name.
Dippy Dog.
Who's Dippy Dog first?
Yeah, Dippy the goof.
Oh, yeah.
And then Dippy the goof.
Dippy the goof.
George Lucas schooled us about he educated us about some of this.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
So that's how he got his third name.
It should be really the line here.
Yeah.
So points for lost for accuracy.
Mousekamania.
You know, I think this album is similar to the what's the last song on the McGruff Smart
Smart Kids album.
It's like a real hyper.
I'm I'm glad I'm me.
Oh, yeah.
I'm glad.
That's the one that has that kind of Devo.
Right.
Everything is super duper much like a robot he's talking to that comes out of nowhere.
Similar to this, I feel this ends with this like, all right, let's go out with just a
lot of tempo and a bunch of sounds.
So let's just get a quick hit of sure Mousekamania.
Yeah.
Oh, Devo.
Wow.
Yeah, really a high energy.
This was for this is for the Mosh pit, I guess.
This is the way that this has like, you know, because some of those Halyx songs are pretty
good and just genuinely sound like what the radio sounded like then.
I think we're not too off with with Mousekamania.
The only difference being that it's about collecting Mickey stuff materials.
Yeah.
It was when they first saw the signs of like, Disney and I think the collection.
It might be.
Yeah.
This stuff is getting out of hand.
Hopefully they do less of it.
You freaks.
Thank you.
And then the next year, the year after this, a fella named Michael Eisner shows up at the
studio and things change forever.
Things change.
I think that this and like, it's a pretty muddy era, right?
Between 66 Walt's death and 8 or the new King's arrival.
There's a lot of missteps, a lot of not great movies and weird live action.
What the fuck is this?
Condor Mans and what have you.
But this is really, I feel like a nice gentle product of pre Eisner.
We're not micromanaging these things to death.
Let's let the guys down in records do whatever they want because they made us some money with
disco, which was them doing whatever they want.
It's just a, I don't know.
This is a really earnest project.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think produced an earnest episode.
I think so.
I feel there were jokes.
Sure.
But crying songs.
I like that.
I think we got to mix it up.
We got to be ourselves at some point.
And you know, actually one funny thing about this too, that so that's a song about hoarding.
Right.
And then I feel like this just came up in an episode.
Were you, Mike, talking about the new Mickey Mouse cartoons?
And there's an episode about where Mickey's a hoarder.
I think Jason was talking about that.
I, yeah, I think that's right.
Or did we just find this independently?
I'm trying to remember because there's the cartoon made for Hollywood studios
that I watched that references other episodes of the car.
Like there's pictures and there's, there's little reference,
but I think there might be a hoarding.
It's like that kind of sounds right.
One of those things is called the wonderful, wonderful spring of Mickey Mouse.
And it's about Mickey as a hoarder and Mickey has all this shit he's not willing to get rid of.
And a lot of the stuff we would all kill to have, which is like old ride vehicles.
So it's a good Easter egg episode for, oh, I was one of the old sky buckets or whatever.
But when he's kind of in a rush to sell, like am I getting rid of this or not?
One of the items he holds up quickly is a pristine non-drawn,
just a photo put on top of animation copy of Mickey Mouse splash dance.
Oh, yes.
So these new cartoons that we like nod to this album and Mickey on the digital wave with his seat.
It is, it's part of the history.
They nodded to it and it's, it's nice.
I'm glad it's still, even if it's just as a snarky reference,
I'm glad Disney is holding on to this.
Yeah.
I feel like the people making those Mickey cartoons have a genuine affection for some of this.
I would assume.
I think so in the history.
Yeah.
I know it's a good way to like tie together.
That's like a genuine, okay, we have all these properties around and bits of Disney lore.
How do we spend something new out of it?
Yeah.
It should be like Disney was relying on Turner and Hooch for their reboots,
but don't you think, you know, splash dance should come back more in some sort of way?
Well, as what?
I don't know.
Like, is it a jukebox musical of all of these songs?
Or yeah, jukebox musical.
Sure.
Well, you know, with the sparks connection, they just, you know,
they just did all the songs for Annette.
Why can't Disney do Annette?
Something exactly in that tone.
Yeah.
And people, people out there are probably also saying,
why can't podcast The Ride of the Second Gate do an episode about Annette,
Funicello and her singing career?
It's so, well, yeah, those club three results, we had to start deleting how many people were
begging for the Annette, Al, but once the gates were open to the public, it's like enough.
People just screaming.
Like I had to start screaming and deleting.
Fine delete, fine delete.
Hawaiianette, Italianette.
Well, we've already, look, there's other music ones we talked about on this episode,
even we've got to end up doing.
So it's still there.
It's still, it'll happen one day.
Well, and isn't this episode a nice example of what happens when we talk about music that
isn't Aerosmith and Green Day?
Right. It is, it is interesting.
When we stretch outside of our, well, when we stretch outside of your comfort zone.
That's where I like to live.
You'll go back, you'll get back in the car and crank up honking on Bobo.
Oh yeah.
Forget all this ever happened.
Baby, please don't go.
Yep. That's the first track.
I was in this morning, I was doing a long, boring interview with a guy who directed a
lot of those Aerosmith videos and he was asked honestly what he thinks of Steven Tyler.
And he's like, don't like him.
A lot of demons.
You know, I think he's a lot.
Steven Tyler, I will give you that.
So wait, this was not a new interview?
I don't know.
Okay. I was going to say it's a new interview.
It's like kind of no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
between demon battles.
Okay.
Okay. Anyway, so very nice.
Nice to talk about all these things.
You survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our new Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month, which is chosen by you,
the audience and our regular episodes ad free albums are good.
This is, it's nice to break these things down.
If there's an album you want us to listen to, but any and all topics we are always open to.
Can I ask just maybe for a little blast of the end of Mickey, she's got a crush on you
because I think this is actually one of the catchiest things on the album.
Very like these calling response vocals.
I like nice heartfelt wedding.
Oh, my goal.
My goal, my goal.
Not Mickey.
The crush is on my goal.