Forever, dog.
Warning, the following podcast is the origin of the podcast The Ride hosts.
It may contain hamburger factories, substantial boats, and t-shirts that would make the big
Johnson people embarrassed.
Come learn about Mike Scott and Jason's very regular childhoods.
It's the parks that made us on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride, where today we stop thinking about the theme parks in our
heads and focus a little more on the theme parks in our hearts.
I'm Scott Gardner, driven by Mike Carlson.
I'm acting.
I didn't know what that, I thought that was legitimately choking on food or?
Choking on my own emotions.
I see, choking on emotions.
Beautiful.
Yes, that's good.
That's what I want today is choking on emotions.
Let's all be doing that, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, let's get this actor some more jobs.
Let's get this man booked.
Well, please.
I say booked.
Jason, I beg for work every week here.
We beg for work on the show at this point.
It's pathetic.
So yeah, please, if you didn't hear that.
We don't do it every week and I don't think you should start, but as much as you feel
like you need to.
Yeah, that's true.
It's happened a few times.
That's not so much our hearts.
That's more our guts, the rumbling, the stomach acid churning in our guts.
Needing hunger and eating treats.
I think more just anxiety pangs a bile.
If we're talking like, if you want like the lone gunman from X-Files on your show, three
guys who are a little quirky, a little strange.
If you've ever seen the X-Files, there were the three kind of guys that were like Mulder
would go to like for research and they were kind of like conspiracy theory guys and they
would give them information, but they were a little odd and they had their own spin-off
that didn't, I guess, do well.
This is the three of us could do that on some show, I think.
Sorry, you're pitching us as people who had their own show that failed.
Well, no, no, I'm saying in the future we could be on a show, we could have a spin-off
and then it would fail.
But you're okay with the failure of the eventual show as long as we get the rates for recurring
on a more popular show.
Prime Time Fox, a full season of that?
Prime Time Fox one season in 1999 or 2000, whatever that was.
Were they on more than one season of X-Files or there was only one season?
More than one season of X-Files.
Okay, well so the lone gunmen are doing fine then, I would assume.
I don't know, but I'm just saying we're available in the same sort of like, oh these three quirky
guys for a show.
If your show needs three quirky guys, here we are.
If your show is looking to hire three whites at once, just a big glut, let's really up
the white numbers.
Maybe that's part of it.
I don't know how, but maybe that's part of it.
It's mocking the idea of that.
It's an ironic view.
That's right.
So here we are.
Less than that.
The new lone gunmen ready to be inserted in your TV show.
And today you'll see the soul in the heart of us.
We'll see where we came from.
The origin story.
That's right.
Yes.
Yeah, that's the idea.
What we're doing here today is Mike and Jason and I are all going to talk about a park
or a themed attraction that meant a lot to us growing up.
That's like way deep in the psyche.
And you might say, well, you do that all the time, but today this is not, we're not talking
no corporate Disney universal, the man, man.
That's not what it is.
We're talking about places that were local, that were homespun, and where even though
we maybe recognize the flaws and the chinsiness, it's always going to be in there.
It's part of us.
It affected us.
Part of our origin story, as Jason said.
Yeah.
So we're excited about this.
There were many places even I think we could have picked, multiple places, but we've chosen
one.
So there's sequel opportunity for this episode too.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well especially because I think we all, being that we all fetishized some place that wasn't
even meant to be enjoyed.
The fries electronics that was based around Alice in Wonderland.
That's a viable, but God knows I've talked enough about fries, but we probably all have,
there was a post office and the roof was interesting and that was the thing that had a lot of impact.
Oh yeah.
I think I've said this before on the Woodfield Mall episode or maybe before, there was a
shoe store that had a little circle that you could sit in.
I forget even how to describe it, but there was a little play thing in the shoe store
and I was just like, this is the greatest place I've ever been.
I'm trying to picture.
And that's probably a chain and I can't think of the name of it and people probably know
exactly what it is.
There's a slide inside as well, but to get in the store, if you were just a kid sized,
there was like a hole kind of that you could walk through and you could chill out in this
sort of hole.
You had a special entrance, a special entrance for kids in this mall.
Basically, yeah.
Like the Imaginarium, that's what I said, the Imaginarium was a store with a little
door.
Yeah.
I miss doggy doors for children.
I don't think I've been anywhere with my son with a tiny door meant for him and that
I couldn't fit into that.
I'd be humiliated if I tried to go into and we need more of those.
We should.
Somebody really should make, I mean, there's been so much talk of like Wonka attractions
over the years.
Somebody should make that like door, the tiny door at the end of the weird room when they're
about to go into the factory, something like that.
Obviously, that's not the way it's portrayed is impossible, but there's a version of it
only could fit in a certain door.
Make all those blustery dads and moms have to get on their hands and knees.
Make the mom and dads get hurt.
Make them scrape their knees.
Wear down their already worn down limbs.
Everyone's wearing suits and dresses because I guess it's England in this, 1960s in this
scenario.
They were all fancy.
That was like Disneyland in the 50s and 60s where you dressed up.
I guess that's a momentous day and they probably knew that Willy Wonka dresses up as well,
so they had to match.
There is a class element, I feel like, to Willy Wonka because Charlie and his grandfather
probably have the least amount of money of all of them too.
That's probably part of it, but also people dressed up back in the day.
Grandpa is wearing a suit, but it's probably like a less nice suit than the others.
Oh yeah, those snooty other people, they're on to him.
Remember it probably stinks.
He's sleeping with the other grandparents.
He's got his own elderly stink that's amassed the stink of the other elders.
Then they make nothing but cabbage stew in there, so probably every article of clothing
has kind of a cabbage reek.
He could have taken his annual shower though before.
I don't know.
Was that the situation?
There was one shower?
Maybe.
I think it was a bath.
I think they were heating up a bath.
So that makes sense.
They're also using it for also cooking up cabbage in there to make stew.
They're getting the bath water to eventually eat.
Multi-purpose cauldron, yeah.
Will they show the grandpa bath in the Chamolais, whatever, the new Wonka?
Chalamet.
Chalamet, what's his name?
Excuse me, I apologize.
I like Chamolais.
Chamolais, funnier.
Will they show it in the new Wonka, the grandpa bath?
Sure hope so.
I'd like to see every detail, and with crazy CGI.
Yeah, CGI grandpa in water.
So anyway, childhood parks.
We're talking, yes.
So yeah, the places that felt like ours, where maybe you could go, you could talk to other
kids about have you been to Disneyland, but anybody could go to Disneyland.
These places felt like, almost to me, maybe I'll never meet anyone who also knew these
places.
Unless in your case, it was like, oh, all the kids in your area are talking about whatever
your thing is.
I think my case, some of the kids were talking about it.
I think it's pretty well attended.
It's been around for a long time.
So I wouldn't be shocked if people in the area at least went once.
But it definitely, it was not getting Disney levels of attendance.
But it is still open and it's been open since 81.
Mine is, I guess, should we roll into mine?
Yeah, well, we didn't talk about the order.
I was going to say, I mean, let's roll into yours.
I was going to say, does it make sense to go for the person to go last who thinks that
theirs is the worst?
Yes.
Do you think that's yours?
No.
Okay.
I don't think so.
Jason?
No.
Okay.
Maybe it's me then.
Yeah.
Having just been and revisited, I would say it's seen better days.
I haven't just been, but mine still seems kind of charming.
Yeah.
I think Mike should start because a thing of mine I didn't realize until I was a little
deep into it.
It shares some things with what little I know of Mike's.
Okay.
But mine also has gotten increasingly more elaborate where I learned things today when
I was working on stuff where I was like, well, I didn't know that.
And like, oh, this is a very funny folly for a thing to a car.
Follies to come.
Follies.
Novelty garden architecture.
I was trying to find follies for mine.
Roller coaster construction mishaps.
I don't think I found any major follies that have been documented.
Well, then by all means, let's dive into yours, Mike.
I also think that something we should, let's compare, contrast these.
We'll all lay our specific parks and places out and based on those, we'll determine who
had the best childhood.
I think it'll be a winner.
I think it'll be clear.
So yeah, I guess let's start.
Brian, I have a video that I sent.
It's a pirate video.
I think we should probably start with that.
This is a newer commercial just to give you a little taste.
Discover a buried treasure filled with summertime fun at Pirate's Cove Children's Theme Park
in Elk Grove Village.
What theme park?
Pirate's Cove?
Children's theme park.
Come on, children's theme park.
Come on đấy.
Two to nine to explore.
So sail over to Pirate's Cove Children's Theme Park between June and August and take
me word, you'll be hooked.
Yo ho ho.
So that's Pirate's Cove.
The graphic design has been updated.
It doesn't maybe look like it's been updated.
Home of the slowest moving kids in the whole state.
Pirate's Cove.
So I went there.
I don't know the first how young I was.
I was probably five or whatever.
And I've brought up this place a couple times and I think I've brought up a few times, not
five timers, but it's a couple times.
There was a UFO ride back in the day where you would go inside and there was a video
that would play that would show you launching into space.
And I thought it was 100% real.
Oh cool.
And it flipped.
It made me nuts.
I thought we were going into space and I was so scared.
What's happening actually on the row?
What kind of ride are we talking?
We're talking a little UFO shaped place.
You walk inside, you sit down and they hit play on a VCR.
So not even, does the room not move?
Oh, this is not even a ride.
This is just a video screen that shows you like, hey, now here we go.
And then there's like a shot of the UFO that you're supposedly in.
It's probably like night, which doesn't make sense either because it's daytime when you're
in there and you're, but your kid brain doesn't, maybe doesn't put it together.
And then the UFO launches off into space.
And if you're little enough, you believe it or dumb enough, I guess you believe it that
you're going into space.
I wish I had that still.
Well, how great would it be every day that you think things like that or that you take
everything on faith at a theme park.
Yeah, I love that.
It would love to be tricked.
I love to get, yeah.
In wrestling, they say worked.
I love to get worked.
I love to get tricked.
I like it when I think something might be real, but it's not.
That's fun.
Now, is it also maybe scary?
Maybe would also turn your day into a terrifying nightmare of like, oh my, like if you go to
Disney, you're like, I was on a runaway train and then there was any rocket ship going into
the middle of the space.
Like maybe it would be a little too intense, depending on your level to go into a mountain.
And there was a monster in the mountain several times and he swiped it.
Yes.
On a woman in a puppy coat started screaming at me and she told me she was going to like
take me and help put me in a puppy processing plant or something like there is a little
too much.
I think that the face character should be saying something like there is a dirty old
house where the dead do not rest.
Almost a thousand haunted house telling them telling me that they're going to kill me and
countless ghosts.
I saw many, but by their math, there's a lot more I haven't seen.
One of them came home with me.
So that's why I'm just calling you right now.
I'm quarantining.
I assume it's the same rules as COVID.
I feel like by two weeks that ghost is going to be gone.
I just want to be safe.
I don't want you to get haunted.
I want you and you and be careful.
I saw my dad give his credit card.
He paid for us to go in this place.
This nightmare world.
We chose this.
We gave our hard earned money away.
So yes, exactly.
This is the this is I thought I was going into a real pirate ship.
I thought I thought a lot of it was real.
Obviously, as a lot of kids little kids do.
So now you may wonder why was there a UFO in the middle of Pirates Cove?
I don't know the answer to it.
I don't know the answer to this question.
I could not find even documentation that the UFO was there.
I know it was there unless somebody is going to tell me this is some weird like there was
a one off UFO attraction in a parking lot, someone which I do not believe it was at Pirates
Cove.
Yeah, there's two reasons, I think.
One, you can't copyright pirates or aliens.
That's true.
And two, yeah, just get in there.
Kids like it, probably.
Yes, of course.
Kids like aliens, kids like pirates.
So let's put up a slide, Pirate Slide one real quick, just to give you kind of an overview
of what the park looks like.
This is, again, a newer map in a newer version of it.
I was very happy.
So yeah, this is if you're yeah, we're on YouTube.
If you're just listening and you want to if you're dying to see what this park looks like.
Now a lot of it hasn't changed.
I would say that the big showpiece is that pirate ship right there, which is number five.
Pete's pirate ship.
Pete is the pirate.
OK, this is the IP of the Elk Grove Village Park District is Pete the pirate.
You heard I assume you heard him in the commercial there.
That's a performer playing Pete.
And this was like a really impressive ship to a kid because it had like stocks.
It had like a little jail in like the bottom floor of it.
But you could go on the top and they had the whatever the big wheel and you could
spin the big wheel around and going on it as a kid.
That was kind that was the whole thing.
That was the attraction to me is going to get to hang out on the ship.
And they had like I'm trying to think how to describe it.
It looks like it's gone.
But you used to be able to hold on to like these big yellow plastic pieces that were
on zip lines and like fly down into a bunch of sand.
Wow. Does that make you remember like something like not one of those where you'd hold on
like kind of with your two hands, but one there was like you would sit on this yellow
like seat and you would like hug this like yellow piece of plastic and then they would
shoot you down into the sand.
And that was so much fun.
And going to this thing, yeah, as a kid felt you knew it wasn't Disney, but it was it
was pretty fun and felt kind of special.
And I'm impressed that it's actually still there.
This was born built in 1981.
I saw some figure of like seven hundred fifty thousand dollars to build this, which
look, if you look at the video, it seems a little high.
No offense to Pirates Cove, but it seems a little high because like they had that I
believe they had that little train ride that we saw in there and they had the ship and
they had like a carousel of some kind.
But this isn't we're not there's not like any ticket to be found here, which is OK.
Maybe there was like a bunch of chemicals in the ground or bodies.
They were raising a bunch of corpses and that added to the expense.
Can we go to Pirate Slide six?
Now, these are these are walk around costume characters that I don't recall seeing.
Oh, wow. But these are fun.
These are fun as hell.
Pirate. And that's Pete with a giant head and a giant smile.
Like imagine like imagine Mickey Mouse at Disneyland, but he had like a big set of
teeth like imagine Mickey just like this, like big like Ren and Stimpy style human
teeth and the bottom row of teeth as big as big.
That's really the unsettling part here.
Imagine all like remember Sonic's teeth.
We all remember Sonic's teeth from the first version of the Sonic the Hedgehog trailer.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Imagine those teeth on any of the costume characters at Disney or Universal like Woody
Woodpecker with big teeth or Frankenstein with big teeth.
And yeah, you're kind of in the ballpark of what this Pete the Pirate looks like.
Yeah, he looks a little like a minor league baseball team.
Yes, that is going to do a foot race with other minor league baseball mascots.
And whether they're a pirate or a watermelon, they're all smiling.
Yes, they're all smiling.
What lucky team has a watermelon for a man?
Got to be got to be a watermelon.
I mean, everyone sends me I've gotten it delights me to no end when someone tells me,
hey, a minor league baseball team has a hot dog mascot now or like a scrapple mascot
now. And I'm like, well, I guess I got to buy more hats.
Is there a scrapple mascot?
There is a scrapple one, I believe.
There's a pork roll one, I think.
Oh, my God. We got to look into that.
Yeah. A big piece of scrapple, though, is either just going to look like a brick.
It's just a slice. Yeah.
Is it called Scrappy?
I don't know. I don't know if they've assigned names to the character.
Like, well, we you need to you can't just wet our whistle a little bit.
We need the full meal here.
This may be a topic before the boys of summer are gone that we look at minor league baseball
That's fine. Yeah, I'm comfortable with that.
Before the boys of summer.
Oh, yeah. The boys of summer.
The term refers to baseball when baseball's over.
The song Boys of Summer is about baseball players calling it a season, basically.
Well, I love you even after the boys of summer are gone.
I didn't know this, honestly.
I think that's what I always heard.
Really? Did you know this? No.
About the boys of summer? I didn't.
I haven't I've tried to not think about the boys of summer as much as possible.
Well, I take a wild stab based on the general music tenor of the show that you both are fond of the song.
The boys of summer.
Both for both the Atari version.
I was just in a you guys I was in a casino just yesterday.
And I went I went well, you did a mic point.
The point that you do when an extremely obvious and omnipresent song comes on.
I think it was I think it was that it was playing in the bathroom.
But then when I came out into like the hallway of the conference,
so they're playing like Turn Down for What or something.
And I was like, well, they got multiple tracks.
They got multiple music setups.
Because Tari's, of course, the only difference is they changed the sticker.
That's right. That's a black flag sticker.
Isn't that interesting? What are you talking about?
There's a line I saw like a deadhead sticker on a cat a lack in the boys of summer.
And then they change in the Atari's version to I saw a black flag sticker on a cat a lack.
Yeah. But then it's that's the only lyrical change in those two versions.
Is there anywhere in this business pirate park I can drown myself?
Oh, yeah. Buccaneer Bay Boots.
I saw it. There are a number eight.
Do I have a lot of boat hit me in the head?
I don't actually have a photo of that because it's not that interesting.
I think they're like little kid paddle boats.
And I can't remember if they had that when I was younger.
I was always a little bit, I guess, scared of those little boats, but they're they're very shallow.
So let's see, let's go to slide three.
OK, we don't know. Hold on. Hold on a second.
Let me wait a reveal. I'm realizing it's a reveal.
Oh, OK. OK.
So when I was like nine or 10, let's say, I remember them announcing a big expansion.
For this place, this pirate's cove, there was a big thing coming next summer or whatever.
And I was pretty psyched. And it was a new theme.
It was Camelot. Oh, and my kid brain was like when I saw a photo of this, I went, holy crap.
This looks amazing. This is like some crazy like Disney style castle.
Now, I haven't thought about this in 30 years or whatever, or 20, however old I am.
And I found a picture of what Camelot looks like.
OK, all right. And here it is.
OK, OK. Remember, I built this up very big in my mind.
Place of your dreams. This is slide three.
OK. Oh, no.
It's like a giant like plastic like what you'd have in your backyard, just very big.
Yeah, it is not bad. But I went, whoa, that's it.
My memory of it was that was going to be a big castle like the ship was a big ship.
That's not the case. I mean, it looks fine.
This is a smallish theme park.
And you were imagine when like looking at that artwork of Galaxy's Edge before it opened,
like the ornate painting that was up outside of the site.
Yes. You thought that Camelot would be a 20 acre endeavor.
Right. The castle would tower high into the sky.
Right. I think it's like it looks like it's maybe 25 by 25.
And there is a big dragon slide, which is awesome.
And there's a little photo of it here. And we'll put some more photos online.
In the map, it looks like the dragon had an eye patch.
Does that square with your memory?
I don't remember the dragon. I'll say this about it.
I believe when Camelot was installed, it was the last year we went.
OK, that I was too old for it after this. So I don't remember a lot of Camelot.
Camelot was not in my like prime going days.
This was sort of I would love to know exactly.
But like no one no one was documenting this.
No one was documenting my life this hard.
Right. Because in the in the commercial and the audio of the commercial, it said ages two to nine.
Yes. And that is a certain certain kind of park.
Yes. Where it's like, oh, you're too old for this.
There's no role like the other place that I went to a lot with Santa's Village,
that at least had a roller coaster or two.
There were at least some like that had a like a tilt to whirl.
Yeah. Which is something.
Everyone can enjoy. But this is a little kid park.
So, yeah, so I did not get to I don't have many memories of Camelot
other than just seeing like an ad for Camelot.
So is a parent at Pirates Cove struggling?
Is there is it just like, well, it's something for them to do.
I there's I don't think you can get a drink if that's what you're asking.
I wasn't. But I guess that's a that's a fair question being that like
now I'll say that I have not had a drink with my son at Chuck E.
Cheese, despite having recently taken him to a far away Chuck E.
Cheese for him to see a full munch.
Right. I did want to introduce him to the band, which I did one by one.
That was a short trip, though.
Yeah. If he was having a full birthday there,
yeah, I would maybe maybe dad has a beer.
Yeah. Yeah. This was it was also 10 a.m.
And I'm not that bad yet.
Yeah. Yeah. Plus you want to be clear headed for the show for the Rock and Roll show.
Yeah. Yeah. No, I don't.
Chuck E. Cheese do Boys of Summer.
Can you do a quick Google?
Oh, I love that. Let me say especially early 90s.
Chuck, that seems very possible.
Yeah, I think so.
Where they do the song Sincerely, but then like, gee, Jasper, I love baseball.
See then the baseball players are going away.
Didn't you know what that's the song was about?
It's November way past summer.
So you know what that means?
The boys of summer.
It makes me hate that in the song.
The boys of summer and slightly after and slightly before baseball ends in October.
Baseball goes forever.
It's not just summer.
Boys of summer by a long shot.
I got to look up that to see.
Well, fall balls got a very different feel to middle of fall ball.
Fall ball. You never fall ball.
I've never heard of fall ball playoffs in the series.
Let's see. So there's a better let me get a better picture of Pirate Slide five.
This is a better picture of the pirate ship because this is the main attraction here.
OK, yeah.
And it's it's pretty it's in my again, in my mind, it looked like the Black Pearl.
This isn't quite that, but you can see there's like levels to it.
There's cannons like you can pull like as a kid, you can pretend you're pulling the cat.
They don't let you climb like the top to get in the observation tower or anything.
Obviously, that would be too dangerous.
But this felt like stepping.
This felt like the closest thing to home, maybe other than a Chuck E. Cheese,
where you could get in some sort of like sort of imagine your place.
Sure. You could get in some sort of immersive place.
I can't recall anything else like this other than like miniature golf and you walk through
a castle, but then the rest is right. It was not as themed.
I would have I would have loved this for sure.
Yeah, a lot of this sort of stuff near me, it was either indoor family fun centers with
a small arcade, maybe a pizza kitchen and like laser tag, or it was a pool and one
water slide next to I-95.
You're like, is this the best place for this? Is this the best place?
Like, I don't think I have no memory.
I have memories of driving by the water slide by I-95.
And I know some kids who had like summer birthdays would do birthdays there.
I have no recollection of ever going there.
But this is slip one slip and you're on the road.
You're in the freeway.
This is so much more like lush green.
You know, it's going to say the grounds.
That's the adult in me now.
Like, oh, it's very well manicured grounds.
Let's go to Pirate's Light 7.
I never saw anything really here or did anything, but this is the Pirate's Wharf fun stage,
which I found referred to just as the fun stage before.
So it seems like they can put shows up.
It feels like a local like concert band could do a performance here as well.
This is a confusing scene.
I feel like I'm seeing not just Peter Pan and Captain Hook, but also Maleficent, perhaps.
Maleficent.
I feel like there's an Aladdin in there.
I feel like a Tangled or Rapunzel and maybe a Snow White on the left.
Yeah.
This is, boy, this is an all-star.
The greatest crossover event ever.
Are these teenagers or children or college students?
Unclear.
Maybe 11-year-olds.
I mean, they look older, but the back.
But the backdrop is like a little bit of Pirates.
I don't know, like a little town in the Pirates, whatever IP version.
Tortuga.
This is Tortuga.
There's an academy.
There's a door that says academy.
There's a door that says marketing.
And then there's a door, two doors that are open.
Don't actually have doors.
They're just holes in the wall called Blackbeard's Bank.
So Blackbeard has a bank in this stage.
So you could put on any sort of show about Blackbeard and his bank and his various,
I don't know, financial holdings.
The FDIC refuses to insure my holdings.
Yeah.
Sure to chain up those pens.
Less GB.
Losing them.
Well, you've got safe deposit boxes, which is just McGruff.
Well, you've got safe deposit boxes.
What would McGruff say, but just with Yarg Mady at the beginning?
Be careful of counterfeit banks, R. Mady.
Yo hoi, ya landlubbers.
Be careful of counterfeit bike helmets.
Yarg, counterfeit doubloons.
Infest pirate chests wherever.
Also, you may be tempted, but don't pee in a pirate's chest, Yarg.
Yeah.
So yeah, I guess they probably put on little shows here.
And could we do a show on the Blackbeard's bank stage?
I bet we could.
I bet podcasts the right could.
I'm saying-
We'd be doing them a huge favor.
I think so.
And when I say show, I don't mean the live podcast.
I mean a live pirate show that I wrote for us.
Oh, okay.
Where Jason plays Blackbeard.
Yarg.
Yeah.
So and then Scott, of course, plays Peter Pan.
And I play a different Peter Pan.
I'd rather play Don Henley.
I play an older Pan, and Scott plays young Pan.
Yarg, I need some ID from one of you.
The big reveal at the end is that Jason is also Pan.
Blackbeard is a secret Pan.
Yarg.
He opens a magical chest that turns him into Pan.
I was just playing dress up.
I'm going to have the Disney lawyers secretly bust the show.
All right, well.
They'll all be disguised.
You'll think that they're pirate extras,
but then rip off their pirate clothing
and they're actually there to sue you for intellectual property.
Plain clothes lawyers like the officers sniffing drugs at the theme parks.
So the one thing, I mean, look, this is,
I was trying to find some controversy, not much controversy.
I found an ad for this in a Chicago Northwest Suburbs magazine,
which I'll show, I'll put pictures on Twitter.
We don't need to look at them now.
The one thing I realized is I'm looking through this,
and I don't remember if I brought this up before,
is that the Elk Grove Village Park District
seems like it's more fun than most park districts for some reason.
And it, there are like party rentals, places you can go.
And I remember that one time there was a birthday party in Elk Grove Village
and they had, I swear to God, an animatronic.
I cannot find any documentation of this.
I cannot find proof that it exists, but I'm almost positive that's where it was.
It was inside somewhere right next to Pirate's Cove,
because I remember being like, we're right next to Pirate's Cove in a birthday.
Now here's the closest thing I could find,
is that inside the park district, there is a birthday rental room.
And this is slide eight, Pirate's Slide Eight.
And this place is called, and let me just make sure I'm getting it right,
Jumps and Jiggles.
Now I don't know if Jumps and Jiggles is where I saw this animatronic,
but I believe it is.
I believe that at a certain point, Jumps and Jiggles had an animatronic.
And I cannot prove it yet, but if anyone out there knows anything about the Elk Grove Village
park district and Jumps and Jiggles and the history of it, let me know.
– An animatronic of what, you think?
– I don't remember.
I remember a very distinct sitting in a show, like a curtain rising up, and there being a robot.
– Based on the photo, it's kind of a circus situation.
There's some trapeze monkeys.
So it could have been a monkey, there's a bear on a bike.
– It could have been any of these things.
– It's got the high tubes where you're like, I don't know, 12 feet, 15 feet off the ground.
And one of them leads to a little fake helicopter, which is really fun.
– That looks new.
That looks like maybe that wasn't there when I was younger.
I'll tell you this, I love a nice high tube as a kid.
Holy crap, was I excited when you saw third story tube like this.
– Yeah, and I would always –
– The higher, the better.
– I feel like stand-ups or something.
People have stories like, ew, and then you're stuck in the tube with a stinky kid or someone's shit.
– Which stand-up has the axe?
– I don't know.
First off, I knew you were going to ask that.
But I feel like everyone has horror stories in the tube,
and I only have fond memories of a high tube.
– I don't care.
Kids could have farted on me all day in that tube.
I love those tubes so much.
I never noticed any.
Maybe I did notice a smell, but I was having too much fun.
– Your stand-up act is when you get in the tube with a smelly kid and it's great.
– And it's great.
– Look, you got to accept that a high tube is going to be a little musty in one way or another.
– I don't remember a single moment when I was unhappy to be in a tube.
– You don't see them a lot these days, I don't think.
Like, Cheez-E-Cheese definitely –
– They got rid of most of their tubes, I believe.
– Yeah, but maybe independent play centers still have their – what are we calling them?
High tubes?
– High tubes.
Especially high tubes.
Ones that seemed like really high up.
Even though I was afraid of heights, my feet were not dangling.
My legs were not dangling in these scenarios.
So it just felt like you were going up in a cool little structure,
especially when you were a little kid.
– It looks like it gives a kid a chance to pretend that they're John McClane.
– Yes.
– What other scenario would you have where you're having to sneak through vents and be stealthy?
– That's true.
You're not called upon as a kid to save a Christmas party from terrorists very often.
– Exactly.
So, a little – I mean, look, was I allowed to watch Die Hard until I was 17?
No, I wasn't allowed.
– Yeah, I don't think I watched it until I was 25.
– Yeah, yeah.
I'm still catching up on all the R-rated movies I wasn't allowed to watch.
But, yes, high tubes here.
So I'm putting that out.
If there was an animatronic in Elk Grove Village, I want to know about it.
Send me letters.
Don't email me.
Send me a letter.
Explaining this.
– Also, Jumps and Jiggles, I just want to say, is my favorite Brian Setzer orchestra song.
– Yeah, that one's really hopping.
– Yeah, it really sings.
– I would say that's a cool one, Daddy-O.
I would say.
– Jumps, jiggles, jumps, jiggles.
– But I was trying to find, like, oh, controversies.
Did something dumb happen here?
And I really – there was an issue, I think, where some of the water had too much chlorine
and people got it in their eyes and they had to shut down for a little bit.
And I think there were some financial issues maybe at a certain point.
But it was all owned by the city.
So I think as long as they're charging money and recoup.
– That's interesting.
Yeah, my childhood miniature golf course is now owned by the city, which feels weird.
You're in an arcade that's owned by the city.
You're playing a giant Monopoly game that the city owns.
There's something strange about it.
I guess nothing wrong with it.
– Yeah.
– I don't know.
Is it a socialist's dream to have the state owning the themed entertainment?
I don't know.
What is DeSantis?
DeSantis doesn't want to own Disney, does he?
– This is poor business.
– He shouldn't, yeah.
– We have to cut the – why are we paying for the back and forth basketball hoops?
– I think, look, there's a lot of things wrong in the country.
But if a senator or a congressperson would slip in some, like, state-owned or country-owned theme
parks into bills, I wouldn't be mad.
– Just a little bit of funding for high tubes.
– Oh, gosh.
– Oh, yeah.
– High tubes everywhere.
High tubes at the bank, high tubes at –
– Viable transportation option, possibly.
Take a high tube to work.
– At the bank – I keep saying the bank.
At the post office, which is government-controlled.
– You're thinking of Blackbeard's Bank.
– I am.
I have Blackbeard's Bank on the brain.
– We'll all be thinking of Blackbeard's Bank.
– There's a bill in the California Senate to establish a Blackbeard's Bank.
Public banking and Blackbeard's Bank.
– That's what I'm thinking of.
– We're going to let the pirates take over the banks?
We thought the current financial institutions were corrupt.
– Uh-huh.
Yeah, no.
That's going to be a talking point in November.
So, anyway, this is it.
Yeah, this is Pirates Cove.
This is Jump and Jiggles.
– I have a question.
How maybe, Eith, if we're digging to the core here, how do you think that this –
– Oh, yeah, yeah.
– How do you think that Pirates Cove or Jumps and Jiggles affected you
in a way that maybe even Disney parks did not?
Is there any way that we should all think about this for all of them?
This specific place made you, made any of us the strange adults that we are today?
– That is a good question.
Here's what I'll say about Pirates Cove, and I guess then Chuck E. Cheese,
is that there was something to the fact that going anywhere that was far
felt like we were going to the moon, felt like we were going somewhere impossible
because we didn't travel a lot and we went to Disney World.
But that felt like an ordeal.
I got sick going on there.
It felt like we were going, we were no, or not no, well, we were, what's his name?
The other guy from the Bible going through the desert.
– Moses?
– Moses, thank you.
Gosh, Moses to the – it felt like an ordeal to go anywhere, like a stressful thing.
So getting to go somewhere themed that felt nearby, I think, made – that brought,
I guess what I'm saying is it felt like you went through such a crazy ordeal to go to Disney World.
That almost felt like a different universe.
So seeing the stuff in your universe locally was, I'm sure, part of making me weird and obsessed
with this stuff because it was –
– Having an outlet for it.
– Getting to go home.
After being on a pirate ship, after seeing Blackbeard's Bank and going home that night,
it brought it closer to the real world for me.
– Yeah.
– If that makes sense.
– You're like, what a day.
You're lying in your little bed.
– Yes.
– And you're like, wow, that was really fun.
– It was important to note that the bed was little.
– Yeah.
– It was a little –
– You're lying in your little bed.
– Little.
– Your little boy bed.
– Well, because Mike has always been six feet tall, so he, you know, stretched out of the double bed.
– That's right.
I was like that rock in that picture when he's like 16 and he looks like he's a 40-year-old man.
– Yes.
– So, yeah, Pirates Cove.
– I would love to see Pirates Cove.
I wish there was a Pirates Cove to take my kid out to.
– There are multiple Pirates Cove around, but I think it's generic enough.
– We could all start our own.
– That we could – each of us have our own.
Each of us do our own Pirates Cove.
– I could at least just put the sign that says Blackbeard's Bank on my kid's room.
– Yeah.
– You'd probably think that was cool.
– And then charge him to get in.
– Wow.
Jason, let's delve in.
– Sure.
Great.
My park is called Playland, located on the beautiful Ocean City, New Jersey boardwalk.
Would you, Brian, please bring up that aerial shot of this park?
So this is just kind of establishing shot of part of the park.
As you can see, you got a Ferris wheel.
You have the type of ride that Dr. Doom is.
– Oh, yeah.
– That's our – yeah.
– Uh-huh.
– Yeah.
My favorite thing in this picture, if you look in the lower left-hand corner –
– I see it.
– You see a Tilt-A-Whirl.
– Oh, I thought you meant the Dairy Queen.
– The Dairy Queen.
– Yeah, that sort of caught my eye, too.
– So Dairy Queen comes into play later, but there is a Tilt-A-Whirl,
and that was my go-to every time I went to this park.
Slightly past that, a little deeper, you see a roller coaster track,
and that was called the Flitzer.
– The Flitzer?
– The Flitzer, yes.
– Wow.
With a Z?
– Yeah, with a Z.
So that opened in 1994 and closed in 2015, and I know this because, one,
I was very sad when it closed because I still stop at this park every summer
when I'm back at the Jersey Shore seeing family, but I also found out that local
roller coasters are pretty well cataloged on Coasterpedia.
– Really?
– Yeah, because of another coaster that comes into play.
– Wow.
– So I went to Playland pretty much from when I was born to present day,
and I should mention a connection to Mike's Park.
Brian, will you pull up that image that has the pirate ship in it?
This park was renamed at some point in the later 90s to Playland's Castaway Cove.
– Wow.
– Look at that.
– Yeah.
– Pirates all around.
– So it's a pirate ship, and this was very hard to locate.
I found it kind of on a half-functional website.
These characters that you see in the sign and on the pirate ship
are apparently named Captain Sebastian and his pirate chief.
– Wow, so this is not Blackbeard, even though he has a black beard.
– No, it's Captain Sebastian.
– Captain Sebastian.
– We don't know where he binks.
– Anyway –
– Maybe it was on bank.
– Here's a more recent photo of this facade.
Brian, could you bring up that one that is charred, I'll say?
– Oh, no.
– Yeah, and so I couldn't remember if I told this story on the podcast before,
or if I told it to you guys just when we were sitting around.
So you'll forgive me for forgetting,
but there was a fire in January 2021, and this facade –
no, that's the shooting gallery, we'll get to that.
The front of it was pretty badly damaged.
And so this all was happening, like I was watching the news updates.
So here's the fire.
– Oh, my God.
– This was a four alarm fire that happened in January 2021,
and this was happening in the morning as we were about to record
the Fortune Teller episode with Avery Monson.
And I'm wiping tears out of my eyes.
– That's why you kept audibly vomiting.
That's why you kept saying, Captain Sebastian?
– Well, because everything was burned.
Brian, if you could bring up that aftermath picture
of everything kind of charred and burnt.
– Oh, no.
Oh, that's what we were just seeing.
That's where the Pyre, where Sebastian stood.
– That seems targeted, doesn't it?
– Well, the –
– Rival pirate?
– What's the law enforcement division?
That's the Bureau of Narcotics and Firearms and stuff.
They investigate it, because I guess they investigate arsons
above a certain level, and they found it was faulty equipment
like in the office space, like in the back.
– In the pirate ship?
– No, in the –
– Oh, I wonder it.
– The hangar.
That whole hangar.
– It was just, it's old and crappy.
And maybe buildings that weren't meant to have a lot of electricity.
This probably should have been torn to the ground.
– Right.
– Scott, that's a great point.
Brian, I'm sorry to just throw this at you.
If you could bring up the black and white photo.
So I borrowed an e-book of one of those images of America
with the sepia cover, as you'll always see.
So this is Playland back when it was apparently called
Bingham's Kitty Ride.
– Bingham? Who's Bingham?
– I don't know who Bingham was.
This was news to me that it was called Bingham's Kitty Ride.
– Just a nice guy who wanted a lot of kitties around.
– The hangar was originally used in the 1939 New York World's Fair,
and then packed up and put here as the boardwalk was developing.
And that's a thing you should know about boardwalks.
Fires happen a lot.
And you'd think, oh, a cigarette on the wooden planks.
Usually, no.
It's electrical issues from 80 to 100-year-old buildings.
– So you're saying there was no foul play at all.
You're absolving any sort of…
– Well, yeah, because most of the actual rides were untouched.
So what was taken by the fire was the arcade and the Dairy Queen
and my beloved Hamburger Construction Company,
which occupied one of those places.
– Oh, did this…
We talked about this recently, the Hamburger Construction Company.
– Yes.
– Yeah.
What's the deal again?
Was there anything important about it or just the fact that that was the name?
– Yeah, I mean, the food was always great,
and the mascot was a little guy climbing a ladder onto a big hamburger.
– So it was like a one-inch man who would complete a hamburger for you?
– Yeah.
– Was he going to sleep in it?
– Oh, yeah.
Where did he sleep?
– Which does sound nice, sleeping in a big hamburger.
– In between two big patties?
– I mean, assuming it was cool or room temperature.
– Oh, yeah.
– If it was sizzling hot, I might not want to be in there.
– The place was definitely not room temperature, certainly not air-conditioned,
mostly some fans.
And shocking no one, the poor beleaguered man about my parents' age
opted to just retire and not open the restaurant because they're still rebuilding.
– I see.
– Okay.
– So the arcade isn't back yet?
– The arcade's not back yet.
No, it's just kind of pylons and stuff.
But they are rebuilding it and they're rebuilding the pirate ship.
– Did anything – wait, you said those buildings were gone,
but did rides make it?
There are things that didn't explode?
– Oh, yeah.
Well, Brian, if you could bring up the blurry image of a shooting gallery with a gorilla in it.
So this was a shooting gallery.
Again, as far back as I can remember, this was there.
And I believe the creatures in it were from an old haunted house attraction,
that when they closed it, they repurposed them for a shooting gallery.
And there's not a lot of pictures of the shooting gallery online.
I pulled this from a very blurry YouTube video that I did not want to play
because it's mostly the skeleton coming out of the coffin on the right, screaming.
– Sounds scary.
– Oh.
– Yeah.
So there's a gorilla –
– Thanks for not showing a clip.
– There's a Frankenstein.
There's a skeleton playing a piano.
And you shoot them with the shooting gallery guns from Disneyland.
– Right.
And then it would just do something fun, I assume.
You wouldn't kill them.
– Yeah.
They would just move or scream.
A lot of screaming, a lot of shaking.
– It would be funny if it was just a –
– That sort of thing.
– You hit the ape and it was just a realistic version of like, oh,
and you kind of grabbed the hole and was just writhing in pain.
– You shot smart ape.
– Right.
Smart ape speak can somewhat convey feelings.
– Look what you've done to me, Jason.
– Why do you use your quarters to cause me pain?
– I hope it's just like his bow tie spins or something.
– You are same as Trump sons who shoot wild game for fun.
– Jimmy John's founder and you have lots in common.
– So could we pull up the image of the facade that looks like it's a slide,
it's kind of curved.
So when around the time that this was happening,
that the fire was happening and the demolition of the ruins was happening,
I was looking for pictures of the facade that were decent.
And I found one from the 70s in the Library of Congress website.
And I had never seen this facade before.
This is what it looked like in the 70s.
They're advertising a ride called the King's Tomb.
And then there's the Hamburger Construction Company,
which they kept this sign for decades.
– I see what sticks out to me right now is of course the Taylor pork roll.
– Taylor pork, that's right.
– You just wanted to see the words Taylor pork roll on a nice TV.
That's what this is all about.
– Oh, me too, yeah.
– Well, there's that.
And then you can see the tiny man climbing onto the hamburger.
– Oh, yeah, the tiny man.
I like that.
I like the Dairy Queen.
I like the little Dairy Queen booth.
I'm a big Dairy Queen fan.
Do you know the Dairy Queen is still there, Jason?
– No, that was in the fire.
– That was in the fire too.
So is that something rebuilt?
– There's a smaller Dairy Queen further in the park.
– Because here's, I think I brought this up on the show, but not for a while.
I swear it has been a while since I brought this up.
A Dairy Queen, they have certain items on the menu that are not, if say you open up
a new Dairy Queen, you are not given access to all the different items you could possibly
have at a Dairy Queen.
But if you've had a Dairy Queen open for 30 years, you can still have, say, a cherry
dipped cone because it's been grandfathered in at your location.
And they will still send you the ingredients to make these old Dairy Queen treats.
– That a new franchise would maybe not be allowed.
– Exactly.
You go to the Dairy Queen in the Burbank Mall and you can get maybe a chocolate dipped cone,
but you can't get butterscotch and you can't get cherry.
If you go to the Schomburg Dairy Queen, which I went to my whole life, you can get cherry
and butterscotch because it's been open for so long.
– Clearly this should have been the park that made you.
– The Dairy Queen, yes.
You could get a nerd's blizzard at the Dairy Queen.
You could get a cherry dipped cone, which I recently got going back a couple years ago.
But I wanted to know, this looks like an old Dairy Queen.
And if they rebuild the Dairy Queen, will they still be allowed to serve the cherry dipped cone?
– Oh, how do the grandfathered in limitations work?
I would argue that it was an act of God, the fire, or whatever you want to look.
The Dairy Queen didn't do it to themselves.
– I agree.
– And why would they?
Because they would lose access to all of the grandfathered in recipes.
– I would say this should be based on location, not physical walls.
– I will argue this to the bastards who run Dairy Queen.
– I'm in full agreement.
I think this is great.
I hope the people at Dairy Queen are as reasonable as you are.
– Yeah, well, and there is a second Dairy Queen location within the park.
So that to me says continuity of service, even during the rebuilding.
– You can't have different things at the different Dairy Queens.
That's bedlam.
– I agree.
So Jason, when you go back and Dairy Queen's back there,
you got to tell me what kind of dipped cones you can get.
– I'll keep an eye out.
– Did you have cherry dipped as a kid?
– Well, no, because we didn't really go to the Dairy Queen.
We went to the local chain, the Coors soft serve.
– You were anti-Dairy Queen?
– No, we had plenty of Dairy Queens in our hometown,
but in Jersey on the boardwalk, you went to Coors
because they had the richer frozen custard.
– Okay.
Did you ever go to Dairy Queen on the boardwalk?
– I must have, like occasionally.
– Did you ever have a cherry dipped cone at Dairy Queen?
– No, I've never had that.
– Dairy Queen not that well represented out here.
– There's more now.
I would say they were not around when I was a kid whatsoever.
– Well, a lot of the Dairy Queens out here flipped to foster freezes.
– That makes me sad.
– Those were like franchises that broke off from Dairy Queen.
– Makes me upset.
– Makes you sick.
– I mean, hold on, I'm going to act again.
I'm sad.
– The sad noises are pretty good.
– Thank you.
– That's pretty accurate.
– Either me or us.
– Yeah.
– Get to that because you know if that's the starting point
and we know that the spin-off requires the most emotional range
as with Better Call Saul, if that's where you're starting,
think how deep you can dig.
– 100% that's how deep I can dig.
You've seen it here.
And imagine the type of conversation you have with me on set.
So, cherry dipped cones, you ever had one?
You ever had one?
Did you know that you can get your grandfathered in
if you want to go to Dairy Queen?
– How old was the Dairy Queen around where you grew up?
Because if it was like 90s, then you probably wouldn't have had
some of the things with it.
But the further back it goes, I'm trying to think like
Francis Ford Coppola, what did you have on your Dairy Queen growing up?
– Hey, look at me.
Don't look away.
Was there an old Dairy Queen in your town?
– Make eye contact with me because I believe you're lying.
– Yeah.
– So Francis Ford Coppola has made a return to television specifically
and he's hired the three of us.
– Well, it could be in a movie too.
– And we're talking his ear off about Dairy Queen.
– It could be in Tetros.
– Tetro 2 is the lone gunman.
– Lust, caution, the return.
– Bram Stoker's Dracula 2 starring the three of us.
What? What's so funny about that?
I think it works.
80-year-old Francis Ford Coppola decides to make Bram Stoker's Dracula 2.
– So think about that, that it's not some new,
it's a sequel specifically to Bram Stoker's Dracula
that he comes back for.
– That's right.
– It's not a new Dracula.
– Yeah.
– Not a new one, no.
It's the same one.
Jason plays Peter Pan in that for some reason.
I don't know why.
– We filmed entirely at the Elk Grove Pirates.
– That's right.
It's a low budget.
– So what else about Playland?
I remember when we went to Playland,
I was messaging a little with friend of the show,
Sean Rice, who we met and hung out with a little
when we were down in Florida a few years ago.
Because he, as always, messaged when I mentioned Ocean City on the show,
because his family went there growing up too.
And I said, do you have any memories of Playland or weird stuff?
I'm forgetting about Playland maybe.
And he goes, well, we were a Wonderland family,
so it was kind of an adventure if it was an excursion if we went to Playland.
Wonderland is the competing park at the other end of the Ocean City boardwalk.
Rides were a little bigger, catered to a little bit of the older kids.
And one reason why we did not go there,
every now and then we went there,
but their tickets expired at the end of the season.
– Oh.
– Playland tickets are good forever.
So we probably are still, if we go and do a couple rides,
are probably still using tickets from the early 2000s or the 1990s.
– So you bought them in bulk at a deal, at a discount.
– Well, what happens, both parks do the same thing.
Off season, the tickets are half price.
And Playland also did a thing where on July 4th, all rides were half price.
So if the Tilted Whirl normally cost four tickets, it cost two tickets.
So that night we went crazy.
So the play was to buy your tickets before the season,
but if you bought Wonderland tickets,
you had to use them before Labor Day or use them before mid-September.
– Can you further define going crazy in this scenario?
– We might do five or six rides in a night instead of three or four.
– Oh, baby.
– Holy shit.
– You psychos.
– You wrote it so many times that this happened on the Tilted Whirl.
– That's right.
– Well, first of all, two things.
So in an off season, they would sell Playland tickets for half price,
but you could use them if you held onto them till the next summer.
That's what you're saying?
– Yes, you could use them every summer.
– So it's as if Disney gave, like Disney did some sort of a three-day deal
that they do out here, but you could hold it forever.
So you could stock up.
– Which my family has done.
– I 100% believe it.
– Like 10 or 15 years ago, my dad bought a four-day park hopper,
and he's like, yeah, we'll probably back next year or the year after.
We'll use the other two days then.
– But that's not, you can't do that anymore.
– Not really.
– Disney stopped letting you do that.
So that's out.
But the Playland hack still exists.
– The Playland hack still exists.
– Yeah, so I would always do the Tiddler Whirl and the Flitzer,
and then ride three or four were like wild cards,
which probably my most unpleasant ride experience happened there too.
You know that ride where it looks like the arms of an octopus,
and you're kind of going up and down, but you're also spinning?
My dad and I rode one of those one night,
and it went to the point where you're like,
wow, they're giving us a lot of time on this ride.
It went past that point to like,
we're starting to feel queasy, we'd like to get off this ride,
and it's still going, and we're like, please stop, please.
And it just kept going forever.
And the teenager finally ended the ride, acted like nothing was wrong,
but we were just dizzy for a while.
– Yeah.
– And you never, you didn't question him?
You didn't push him up against the record?
– What was that? What was that all about, buddy?
– No, I think we gave him some dirty looks,
or like, yeah, but it was very strange.
– Do you think in hindsight was it five minutes?
Because those rides, what, last two minutes?
– Yeah, it was probably between five and eight minutes.
– Eight minutes is a long time.
– Yeah.
– It's been around.
– Can I say the Tilt-A-Whirl,
if you had asked me before, I guess non-Disney rides,
Tilt-A-Whirl all day long was my favorite ride.
I loved the Tilt-A-Whirl.
I remember, I haven't pushed it in a while.
I pushed that we should do a Tilt-A-Whirl episode.
– Yeah.
– I was so excited.
– Okay.
– Oh, I could gamble.
– I was so excited.
I haven't been on a Tilt-A-Whirl in over a decade also.
Where is the nearest Tilt-A-Whirl from here?
– From here, that's a good question.
– I don't think.
– There's maybe something, because I remember this came up.
I couldn't even really say what a Tilt-A-Whirl was.
– Or a Gravitron.
– That's the one where the floor drops out?
– Yes.
– Yeah.
– Okay.
– Not really, other than maybe carnivals or something.
– Is there like an electric daisy carnival we could all go to
and get on a Tilt-A-Whirl and only do rides and not do the music that we paid for?
– There's both a county fair and a state fair going on now.
– Oh yeah, that's probably a good place.
– Okay, so that was one of my discoveries about, so the Flitzer,
I was saying, that closed in 2015.
And another coaster called the Python also closed in 2015.
That was the first upside-down coaster I ever rode.
And I only rode it once because it was rough as shit and I hated it.
The Python is now located, they sold them both.
The Python is now located at a park called C.J. Barrymore's Family Entertainment Center in Clinton.
– Michigan.
– C.J. Barrymore? Who's that?
– I don't know.
– A very vain man, I think.
– I am.
– Poor woman.
– Somebody who really wants their name out there.
– I'm looking up C.J. Barrymore.
– The Flitzer was sold to an amusement company and now travels around to carnivals.
So it's still out there.
If I can find a carnival with the Flitzer, I can relive my childhood.
– Still called the Flitzer?
– It is still called the Flitzer.
– Wow.
– What's flitzing?
– It's unclear.
It's kind of futurey, it sounds fast.
But if I could just briefly talk about what replaced those two.
It's a large coaster called the Gale Force.
And if we could get that image that says Gale Force on it.
Yeah, here we go.
So this is a small compact coaster.
It fits in the space of two smaller family entertainment coasters previously fit in.
This is an SNS coaster, which is a major coaster manufacturer.
Manufacture stuff for Six Flags parks.
I think some joker the ride.
Playland announced that this was coming in 2016.
And the other rides closed in 2015.
It did not make the 2016 opening day.
In 2017, it was operating sporadically.
But everyone said it was very pleasant and very rough.
So they're like, okay, we got some new vehicles for it.
That'll make it smoother.
And then in between the, during the off season,
they just decided to retrack the whole ride.
They judged it to be not not ideal suitable for a human.
Yes.
So eventually 2018 comes around.
It starts operating normally.
And then in 2019, when they were running some tests on it,
two crash test dummies flew out of it into the nearby hotel.
Into the balcony or the window onto the roof damaging some shingles.
Sweet.
Like the stunt tronic at Spider-Man.
So another thing to notice about Gale Force, why it might not,
anytime I walk by, it doesn't seem to be running,
is it costs $10 to ride this single ride or worse, 14 tickets.
So you're better off just spending the $10.
And this promotional image, Gale Force,
not what you want to hear when you're at the beach.
And these storm clouds look like these sort of storm clouds
that roll in before a summer thunderstorm that makes everyone flee from the boardwalk.
The promo image of Gale Force here is something where it's like,
this ride would not be operating in these weather conditions.
Yes.
This would be extremely unsafe.
This is not fun.
This is not a fun storm either.
This is a realistic storm.
Yeah.
Also a bold choice to call something Gale Force
that was opening five years after Hurricane Sandy ravaged the shores of New Jersey.
I thought, look, if I was going to punch up this art, I'd say, okay, regular day,
but then like a cartoon cloud making like the blow,
like he's blowing like a little bit and then he's got a little brain.
And his name is Gale Force.
And now we've got original IP on there too.
Not John Force, Gale Force.
Oh yeah, I love John Force.
Just speaking of names real quick,
I was just trying to figure out what CJ Barrymore is.
Yes.
And all I found, it says who owns CJ Barrymore,
and all I see here is a guy named Rick Iceberg.
So is there no CJ Barrymore?
That's what I'm trying to name of Rick Iceberg.
Rick Iceberg might be CJ Barrymore.
Whoa.
Does anyone want to guess what they renamed Python to at CJ Barrymore?
Python 3.
Nope.
Iceberg the Rife.
It's listed now as just Loop Coaster.
Loop Roller Coaster.
Boring.
That's boring.
Not creative.
Yeah.
Stinks.
Yeah, no made up words like flitzing.
That's what I want.
Yeah.
Well, what do you think, if you're summing it all up,
what did Playland give you that the corporate parks could not?
Well, I think due to my parents' rational and cost effective method of like,
all right, three rides tonight, please, three rides,
and also we want to go home, it's late.
We need to go.
We can't go to the other one.
The passes will run out.
Yeah.
Never wonderland.
We're not a wonderland family.
You hear me?
It was that.
And then also one summer, Playland just doubled in size
because they took over the empty lot next store,
next to this historic hotel, the Flanders Hotel.
Used to have these massive, I'll just show you guys this picture
because I don't want to make our poor engineer bring up any more.
But this used to have three saltwater pools outside.
Oh, there it is.
Three saltwater pools.
Hotel Flanders.
There it is in full bad res.
Yes.
That empty lot to the right used to be, is where Playland is now.
That looks like the Grand Budapest Hotel or something.
It is very much a grand old hotel.
And it's got a very detailed history on its website,
most of which is like, and then in this year,
the Flanders fell on even harder times
because it dates back to 1916.
So it's seen some things, it's seen some wars,
but yeah, this is back in the day where the amusement was,
you're on a boardwalk by the ocean and look at this public amusement,
three saltwater pools.
But those closed in the late 70s.
It's how they all started.
We wouldn't have any of these places if it wasn't just, hey,
want to go to a pool?
Right.
Yeah.
And there was a previous Playland on the Ocean City Boardwalk,
which I think was just indoor roller skating and live music.
And that, of course, burned down in a fire in the 30s.
All these fires.
There's a lot of fires in the history of New Jersey amusements.
And New York too.
Some of them were shady.
Some of them were definitely shady.
Yeah.
The Coney Island, there were so many amusements lost to time due to fires.
OK.
We did the fire Final Four.
Yes.
Let's rank all of the...
Theme park fires.
Yeah, one of the best theme park fires.
We should probably, ones with a low or zero body count would be nice.
Yeah, those are out.
Yeah.
Anything that didn't kill anybody we'll rank.
Well, now that...
What if it killed people in the 20s?
Then nobody, we wouldn't know them.
The statue.
It's not sad anymore.
100 years or over is our statute of limitation.
There was a fire at a gift shop called Fisherman's Wharf when I was very young,
like six or seven.
And we heard about it on the news.
And I was like, is that the Fisherman's Wharf we go to?
Which was just a shop that sold seashells and maritime souvenirs and Simpsons toys.
The first generation of brightly colored Simpsons toys.
It was my favorite place on the boardwalk.
And then it just burned down.
Oh, it was the one?
It was yours?
That was the one.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no.
File play or not?
Unclear.
OK.
I'm not sure on that one.
If we crack one of these cases open, we may be in trouble though.
That one seemed old in 1991.
I know.
But I'm just saying if we uncover some sort of mob thing going on that set a fire,
then we're going to have to really be careful is what I'm saying.
Yeah, yeah.
Some podcasters are on to us.
Yeah.
I mean, it doesn't help that in a lot of these short towns,
three or four families run most things.
Gillian's Wonderland is run by the Gillian's family.
One of the Gillians was the mayor for a number of years.
Was Rick Iceberg ever a mayor?
Like he was far away.
Wait, here we are making fun of him.
And now it like the icebergs rule the town.
Yeah, we got to be careful.
Yeah, we're going to get some scary packages and then send mail for us to Forever Dog.
Chill.
Or our chili packages.
That's not fair to a dog.
And whatever.
I'm not taking the hit.
I see package.
Iceberg will put it.
Find me iceberg iceberg.
I'll take your head off and he'll put it in a big cube.
You don't want that.
So you're so the big the big take away this park taught you thriftiness.
Yeah, it taught you how to save a couple bucks.
But also like they did rotate rides a good amount.
So I knew like, OK, there's some stuff that never goes away
and some stuff that does change.
And then occasionally there's like a whole other section of park
because like the park practically doubled over the course of like one year.
I think the the playland people bought.
Oh, wow.
There he is.
Oh, Rick Iceberg.
Oh, my God.
We found Rick.
This is Rick Iceberg's LinkedIn.
This has been sprung on us.
Yeah, Michigan.
He's in Michigan.
Oh, my God.
OK, what do we what do we learn from that?
President is the president.
He's the president of C.J. Barrymore.
Clinton Township.
That might be there might be some power there.
I don't know.
And I'm president.
We're going to have to dig in here.
Rick Iceberg.
Do we have a new guy?
Do we say join to connect?
This might be the our method of finding a lot of people we want to talk to might be LinkedIn.
Yeah, more than it's Twitter.
Oh, 100 percent.
Yeah, we should we should really get on LinkedIn.
How much I am on?
I've got a burner on LinkedIn that I use to look up.
What's the name?
C.J. Barrymore.
I don't remember what the actual name is.
Is it a fake name?
It's a fake name.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
You know what it is.
I think I don't know if it comes up right.
What do you think?
I don't know.
No, I'm not going to tell you.
You know what it is, though.
I use it to poke around on theme park people.
Oh, wow.
OK.
J. Mysterioso.
The guy with the big mustache.
As the avatar or as the icon or whatever it is.
How much power do the auto workers unions have in Clinton Township, Michigan?
No, I don't know.
We have to find that out before we make one more joke about Rick Iceberg.
That's right.
Well, moving on to me.
Do I close it out?
Yes, please.
All right.
Well, I would like to talk about the Balboa Fun Zone, which is part of the Balboa Peninsula
in beautiful Newport Beach, California.
We landed on this as an episode topic.
We're going to talk about these core childhood parks.
It happened to line up perfectly with that I was going there in a couple days,
that my parents had rented a little house on Balboa Island.
It's like a place where you rent little German cottages, and then there's the one nice street
with the little bit of shopping and the fun desserts.
So we did a little three generations trip where we took the boy down.
And it was just a wonderful nice time.
But it lined up nicely to where I could look at this place that I went all the time as a kid
with fresh eyes.
So it worked out perfect.
Basically, so Newport Beach, it's like half an hour from Disneyland probably.
My dad spent a lot of summers there.
We would go down to visit my grandma who lived there.
The area is maybe mainly known pop culturally as the basis for where Arrested Development
spends a lot of its time.
The Banana Stand is based on this area.
The main drag of what's confusing is like there's Balboa Island, but then you go to the Peninsula.
But anyway, this frozen banana stands around and there's that deal where two of them claim
to be the original and there are only five doors from each other and they're mad at each other.
What's the general feeling on frozen bananas?
Because I wouldn't be fighting to claim them.
I'm not a fan really.
Like I'm once in a blue moon.
You know me and bananas.
It's a little bit of a little allergy.
Oh yeah, what am I saying?
Maybe the frozen though somehow knocks out the bad elements.
Frozen does probably help knock the bad elements out.
If it's got the chocolate outside of it, it's better.
Just frozen by itself is not always the best.
Sometimes you have frozen bananas, you're making a smoothie or something if you want to eat it.
It's like kind of, I don't know, I don't love it.
But if you got some chocolate a little bit on the outside, it's a good flavor.
But I think it depends.
They dip them right there.
These things called Balboa bars that are really fantastic that are kind of like hand dipped
Klondike bars.
Oh yeah.
You pick it and while the chocolate is hardening and you can do some other stuff.
My kid loved it.
I loved it.
It might be up there.
My dessert zone might be like it's the white, it's like vanilla with chocolate casing.
They'll do that at California Adventure.
They will make a version of that where they dip and they'll put some sprinkles or nonsense on it.
Clarabels.
Oh really?
That's up at the front of the park.
Named after the cow character.
I think so.
Yeah, you're talking about the one next to Starbucks, right?
Yeah.
That's the one where you can get the Mickey Sunday in his pants.
Sometimes.
It comes in his little legs.
It comes in his pants.
Yeah.
It's not what I-
It comes in his pants.
No.
No, no, no.
You said it.
But that was when they first opened.
They were like hand dipped ice cream bars and then pick what you wanted to roll it.
Chocolate chips, sprinkles.
I think those are still there.
They're still there.
This little main drag, whatever you call it in Balboa, it's like a, it's a real
like stroll down memory lane for me because there's the two dessert places and then right
between them is a very compact little church where we would go on vacations.
I remember it really specifically from when the sermon was, the only one I remember was
when the sermon was all about dogma.
When the priest was-
The movie dogma.
Yeah, yeah.
There is a film coming out.
I don't remember the details of, there is a character who is,
like what's Chris Rock in it?
Oh, he was the 13th disciple.
That's mainly, I think it was the, that's what they're trying to shock you with.
They claim that there is a 13th apostle.
Apostle.
And he is quite profane.
It's the only sermon I remember.
Wow, that's so funny.
The movie wasn't that popular.
No, it's weird that they, that it even got on the radar of we're going to be mad.
I remember a sermon about that and a sermon about powder.
Really?
Powder.
It's my primary, I'd kind of just be like snoozing in church a little and then like-
What was powder?
A pop culture reference.
That's the movie about-
I know what it is.
Yeah, yeah.
Why powder?
What was about powder that-
I don't remember.
Yeah, why was it anti-religious?
Maybe.
Does he have powers?
Does he have like-
He has powers.
Why is it like a black magic thing?
And if you get remotely imaginative, the Catholic league would be after your ass.
They would just get so furious.
They imply that a special boy named powder has powers akin to Jesus Christ.
Were they mad about phenomenon?
Like the John Travolta?
I don't remember a sermon about phenomenon, but that might have been an off summer.
I might not have been in Balboa.
Michael was the Travolta angel movie.
Oh, they loved Michael.
No, Michael's a nice one though.
That's a religious thing.
That's an affirming movie.
But maybe they didn't like phenomenon.
Am I conflating phenomenon and Michael?
I believe you are.
Everyone does all the time.
They're essentially the same vibe and obviously the same primary cast.
It's an Armageddon deep impact kind of thing.
Except the same star.
Except the same person, yeah.
And then powder was different.
Though powder, I do get kind of confused with phenomenon.
Yes.
Because they were both like people that had like a problem that killed them?
Maybe.
I've only seen phenomenon.
I've not seen powder.
Kind of like Jesus.
Kind of like K-Pax.
I know.
Now, I never confuse K-Pax with these other ones.
There's only one K-Pax.
So which is the twin?
Is it Michael and phenomenon or phenomenon and powder?
What's the what?
Which is the what's the what?
Which are the twin mood?
It's like two sets.
Phenomenon and powder are similar.
Michael is angel.
Yeah, thematically similar.
And Michael.
And phenomenon.
And Michael are Travolta.
Travolta.
They're just Travolta feel-good.
Where they're playing Motown songs and he's dancing around in a big coat.
Elton John.
Eric Clapton, I think, if I could change the world was on the soundtrack to phenomenon, I believe.
I believe we've talked about phenomenon before and I believe I explained that my sister and I,
when we came home from seeing it, we got a string and we tied it to her Barney doll's hand.
And we started making Barney do phenomenon moves.
Let's make Barney play phenomenon.
We knew it was funny.
We weren't like like we love phenomenon.
We were just like, hey, mom, look what Barney's doing.
And he's like making a spoon move or something.
Barney's phenomenon now.
Barney is phenomenon.
Okay, just don't play powder.
We there's no no playing powder in this house.
No, no, we did not play powder.
Wow.
Well, you know, if they were opinionated about pop culture back then, I think that culture has
remained in this area because here's okay.
When I say that I got to experience this area with fresh eyes, I kind of wish that I didn't
have fresh eyes because there are some things that I could not unsee.
This area, if you don't know all of Orange County where Disneyland is, it's a very conservative
area, so I shouldn't have been surprised, but it's also just I remember it from my child and
it's probably louder and prouder now.
Things you might see are a there was a private dock that had a mast, then they're flying flags,
and one of the flags is a thin blue line flag, and another flag is a don't tread on me flag,
which if you're in the area, not just of boat ownership, but of dock ownership,
I think that's the that's precisely where you are not being tread on.
No treading is occurring.
It's all they're not creative signs either.
At least give us some fresh signs, I feel like.
Well, which we'll get into.
Oh, thank God.
Well, less flags and more shirts, which we'll find in the theme park.
Oh, well, yeah.
I'm very excited about some of these finds.
Also, one thing that really caught my eye was a very ornate, like a nice,
life-size sculpted statue of Ronald Reagan in a private backyard.
What?
We could see because it's overlooking the marina or whatever.
So just among the plants.
Well, it's a half Reagan.
That's how you save money if you want one in your home, I guess.
A bust, technically.
But is it a bust?
Because a bust is almost like shoulder.
This was it was all the way waist down.
So you had like full suit jacket.
You had all of his buttons.
Interesting.
And he's waving.
But like having I know they all love Reagan,
but enough to where you're going to pay for a Reagan statue to where you live.
You need to live with a half rate with a slice down the middle.
Ronald Reagan, like a magician cut him in half.
Yes.
Like the cleanest cut, a perfect magician's cut.
I'm trying to think about this.
OK, do those type of conservatives love Reagan as much as I love like Michelangelo
from the Ninja Turtles?
I'm trying to think because I have, you know,
quarter scale toys of characters I love.
You know, so I'm trying to think, would I have a Michelangelo cut off at the waist full?
Like it looks sounds like this is one to one.
Like is it was it bigger than like Reagan would be or is it about like a human size?
I think the size.
Yes.
So it's like one to one, basically.
Would I pay for that in my backyard?
A giant?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I don't even like Michelangelo's.
If I would get.
What would you get?
Michelangelo.
Oh, he was your guy.
Who was your guy of Turtles?
I think it was either Leonardo or Donatello.
OK.
So yeah, so I'm thinking I guess in their fantasy world,
Reagan is as cool as Michelangelo, which, by the way, not true.
Bullshit.
No, obviously not.
Not nearly as cool as Michelangelo.
So I guess I could see it.
I guess I understand it from that perspective.
If you think of yes, to a conservative in the 80s,
Reagan is your Michelangelo.
Yes, exactly.
He's as cool as a Ninja Turtle.
But how deep do they go?
Are they watching Bedtime for Bonzo?
Are they watching?
Yeah, what movies of Reagan's do they like?
His many shitty movies.
That's a question is if you have.
Because I do sense that people have to pretend to like The
Apprentice if they love Trump.
They have to retroactively like, oh, yeah, that was great.
You're fired.
That's funny.
We love it.
Yeah.
But do you have to, oh, yeah, whatever boring Newt Rockne movie
that Reagan.
I bet some people do.
I bet they like Andy was the finest act of the most wonderful films.
More film opinions.
I stopped and ate at a charming little hot dog restaurant.
I had a very good Chicago dog there and not a lot of seating.
So I was on like a little very narrow bench that was kind of like there were literally
there were women at a counter inside literally talking over me.
So I'm like under them and I'm hearing their whole conversation and I could not help but
start to write down details because the conversation was these two women in their 5060s
bemoaning how they just can't talk to their daughters anymore because it always becomes
a fight.
It always gets political.
And even when I lay out very clearly that look, the voting machines don't give you
a receipt anymore.
They don't even print out.
Anymore.
You know, yeah, the voting machine receipts sure proves that there wasn't mouth.
If they show you a receipt, they can't have cheated.
They there's proof.
I have proof that my vote went in because they gave me a little CVS slip.
Oh, wow.
So yeah, you're talking people are just like literally the fight is happening because like
somebody like mom, the election wasn't stolen and then it's over.
Then the fight is the fight starts.
You know, we start talking about if the if the election was stolen or not and then it
becomes political.
Mom, you used to vote in a thing where you pushed a bunch of levers down and you pushed
a big lever to open the curtain to lead the voting booth.
What receipt was generated?
Did you have to you had to make the curtain go like you're operating a curtain at a play?
Did you got did you not have that?
Nothing that crazy.
No, it's in the movie.
If you've seen the movie Pecker.
No.
OK, there's a point where it is not powder.
There's a point where Pecker and Christina Ricci, I think, are fooling around in a voting
booth.
Everyone's fantasy.
And it's the ones with all these little levers in it where you click down the candidate you
won and then the final big red lever registers your vote and opens the voting booth.
Oh, it's one swoop.
Yeah, that locks it in.
Wow.
That's exciting.
I think voting numbers would go up if they.
That would be fun stuff like that back.
All my schools were like, you know, polling places.
And so then if they were still around before after the election, they would take us in
and they're like, here's how you vote.
Oh, cool.
This giant contraption.
Oh, big old levers.
Bring those back.
I don't care who gets elected in the next presidential election.
I don't care.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, no.
All I care about is big levers coming back.
Yes.
Anyway, then the conversation went in the direction you would think it would.
And then it got into, you know, and it's even it's even happening at Disney.
And I perk up.
Oh, here we go.
She says, well, you know, Susan, you know, she's worked there forever and she just quit
because they're doing the woke agenda.
They're going back into the old movies and they're putting in LGBT stuff.
What?
And that's not right.
The movies from 50 years ago.
That's changing history.
Yeah.
What does she they're talking about?
They're making this.
They're making the seven dwarfs kiss.
The dwarfs are all kissing now.
And I just I don't think that's right.
Regardless of how you feel about it, it doesn't add to the plot.
We don't need to see them just kiss for seven straight minutes.
You know, say the kissing.
No, no, no, no, no.
Because I was like, for a second, I go, maybe he's maybe he's doing a bit.
Maybe that is what the women were saying.
I don't we're out to lunch here.
So how did we can go pretty far?
Mickey doesn't even do the magic anymore.
The sorcerer comes in and he just gets on his lap and they make out.
And I just don't think that's right.
These fucking rubes.
Who would have thought decades long diets of tab and lucky strikes and lead paint chips
would just be rotting their brains in senior in their golden years?
This is how they're spending their golden years.
They're having like being not being mad at their daughters and be and quit
and quitting companies that are due because of what they think they're doing that they aren't.
I you know, I would at least give them credit if they were.
I wouldn't give them any credit, but it would be something if they were like
America Chavez and Doctor Strange 2 has two moms and you'd be like, well, that is true.
They at least they're wrong, but they're saying true things.
They don't have any facts.
They have no facts.
They're out to lunch.
No, now it's Bambi.
They went back in and gave Bambi to moms and it's just confusing.
One of them dies, but the other is still around.
So it reduces the lowers the stakes.
It's just a worse movie.
Yeah.
So funny.
So Sue's their friend, their friend quit Disney because of things that aren't
happening and then but you know what it worked out for Susan because have you heard of the Genesis
project?
Oh, no, it's the Genesis project.
Well, it's in Kentucky and it's very it's great.
They have a Noah's Ark.
They made a Noah's Ark.
Let's go.
Yes, they started talking about if you remember our episode about the Ark encounter where they
made a life like Noah's Ark with dinosaurs in it because it had to be to the letter of the Bible
and they have a creation museum and it's so we so I'm overhearing conversation about their
friend who left Disney to go work for Ken Ham.
Wow.
Is that his name?
Yeah.
Iceberg and Ham.
I'm not saying they're too similar.
I'm just saying they're fun names.
That's the X versus sever 2022 podcasting 2022 Iceberg versus Ham.
Somebody went to work for Ham, which who?
Yeah.
A Disney to Ham defector.
I don't know if they happen often.
I was very scared when she brought up the Genesis project.
What is this?
Oh, yeah, that could have been anything.
What have you heard of?
Do you know about monkeypox that's going around?
Well, the Genesis project invented that.
They released it to control the population and just kind of like narrow it down to who we.
It could also have been just like some shell company that Trump invented or something that
people have been pouring money into just to line his pockets for five years and they have no clue.
Well, the Genesis project, they're doing a lot of good.
They're eliminating Professor X and his pesky X-Men.
All these humans.
They're working on some excellent lasers.
So anyway, this is just all like.
These are the costumed characters of the place you went.
Yes.
These are the fun ghost characters.
The ghost town alive.
Yeah, the fun local flavor.
If you read just about people with horrible conspiracy theories and they're acting stupidly,
this is where you go to experience it.
Live it.
And risk your own life because I started thinking like,
oh, I'm literally like these women are talking over me.
So if I maybe this wall will protect me, but if they feel the way I think they do about the COVID
vaccines.
Oh yeah, you should not put in there.
Which by the way, the last I'll get to the rides, I swear.
But the last time I was down there about six months ago with Aaron,
we went to just this nice little coffee place and then there was a big gathering of like 70
somethings and the conversation went where you thought it would.
And then this conference, this following conversation happened.
This guy like kind of holds court and he's like, you know, let me just ask,
how many people do you know who died of COVID-19?
And maybe one or two people raised their hands that happened.
People lost some friends and he goes, okay, okay.
Okay, now how many people do you know who died from the COVID vaccine?
And no one, even in this group, no one raised their hand.
And you could tell that this was a big deflation of the moment that he wanted
because he's because no hands go up and then he goes, okay, we'll go because I know three.
Three.
You know, three people.
Who died of the vaccine.
Yes. Yeah.
And it's only been, they've only been around for.
Right. It's recent.
Yeah. Yeah. A couple months at that point.
Yeah.
That was, so this conversation happened in like the same half mile.
That makes sense.
That's the other one I described.
So it's a scene. It's a scene down there.
But all of this, I would not allow it to tarnish the nice childhood memories that I have because
I love going here with my dad and my sister and it was fun to do it with my son.
So I'm looking forward to, all right, here we go.
We are heading to the fun zone.
Once you get past the Reagan statues and the Genesis project conversations,
then you get a really fun thing because you get on a little ferry.
You get a ride before you get there.
And there's this odd little, it's these flat platforms that hold three cars and a bunch of
pedestrians and you drive your car onto the platform and then it takes you across this
little body of water, which is just a fun.
I think these are pretty rare, like little independently indie fairies.
I like to check out the indie fairy scene.
That's good. Yeah.
It did give me some bad memories because they price the ferry based on your age.
And they're so adults are one age, but kids five to 11 or another.
And I was down there a lot in the summer where I believe I turned 13.
And so whenever the guy running the like counting the coins when you paid for the ferry,
who was probably himself 16.
Sure.
So he's going around and he looks at my dad.
Okay. So one adult and one kid.
And I, it gave me the most anxiety, like more.
I thought about this for more.
I got more stressed about this than anything in my adult life.
It then worried about having a kid.
I was just like gripped with anxiety about is that how young I look,
how please make my dad pay 25 more cents on this ferry to make you seem cooler.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm curious to see how you'll handle the like, well, if you, if you were to have
a second child, I definitely have memories of my parents going, if anyone asks your brother is three.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
The little vacation lies because it could save you a lot of money.
I mean, at Disney, it's the difference between nowadays, $150 and $0.
Huge. Yeah.
It just got me into a Minions Rise of Groove with the free.
Oh yeah.
I tried to take him to a movie and I was like, this might work if the Minions are on the screen
as soon as we walk in.
And instead it was a bunch of little guys with spikes who were mad.
And my son got the most upset and like quivering lip I've ever seen.
And we left instantly.
So I ended up being free for everybody, but I'm glad we didn't pay $10.
Yeah.
To be scared of whatever opens the Minions movie.
I'll never find out.
Okay. Anyway, so once you arrive, it's a nice dramatic entrance with a big Ferris wheel
right next to the harbor.
And this is just very nice.
I think a Ferris wheel next to a body of water like Playland had is just always great.
You get legit views.
They call it the world's longest Ferris wheel, I assume, because maybe they let you be on it
for longer because there aren't a lot of people down there as much.
There's not a demand.
These days, yeah.
Childish Gambino music video, 3005, filmed entirely on this Ferris wheel,
as well as Nick Viall's first one-on-one date in season 21 of The Bachelor.
So in the film Dirty John, also the mini-series Dirty John, which is set in this area in general.
So Ferris wheel still there, still thriving.
But then I keep making my way through the Balboa fun zone, and I think the fun has decreased.
There's almost nothing to do anymore, which is a bummer.
It's like, I think it's been COVID hit, and that's the bummer about it.
And developers have always been after it.
We had to turn this into condos or something boring.
And I really hope it doesn't happen.
But it already, there were bumper cars and there aren't bumper cars.
There was a carousel that is now tables and chairs.
So where it was, you could get a little afternoon of rides out of it.
There's almost nothing now.
What you can run into, as I referenced, are some fun shirts.
And I think there are some slides labeled shirt.
Let's talk about these really quick.
So here's one.
We're right.
So zoom out of this a little.
I'm going to have to tilt our heads.
Here's one that says, don't be a salty bitch.
And it is the logo.
It's the famous girl from the Morton Salt logo.
So this is fun, right?
It flips the famous Morton Salt girl on her head.
It really defies all the feelings.
The associations we have about the Morton Salt girl.
And then there's one more.
This one didn't even strike me as crazy.
It's right-wingy, but it didn't really hit me as bizarre until Erin pointed out.
So this shirt has a big gun on it.
And it says, since we're redefining everything, this is a cordless hole puncher.
OK.
Now, I got a few notes.
Yeah.
What is a cordless hole puncher?
Well, yeah, this was Erin's thought.
Yeah, you know how hole punchers are all electric?
First of all, we're all using them because we all need paper to have holes that we can
put it into binders.
We're never not punching holes into things, whether it be a single or a three hole.
Hole punching, our whole lives.
We love it, yeah.
But the cords, we get tangled in the cords.
So many cords.
Yeah.
Think about all the hole punchers you've ever used and the forest of cords that you end up
tangled up in.
Yeah, of course.
But a gun solves that.
A gun, first of all, eliminates the need for a cord when you're punching holes, but it
also lets you punch holes into undesirables.
It punches fatal holes.
Yeah, what are you talking about?
Cordless.
If you took cordless out, I guess this is a hole puncher is a little flat.
Yeah.
This is a hole puncher.
Cordless just isn't right.
They're not electric mechanisms.
And I looked up there are electric hole punchers, but they don't have their battery operated
typically.
Nowadays, I feel like the last corded hole puncher was decommissioned when Ronald Reagan
was in office.
We need to get back to the time of American values of Reagan and of corded hole punchers
because it makes my shirts make sense.
The point.
Okay, so the philosophy behind the shirt is idiotic and the attempt at cleverness is idiotic
as well.
Yeah, just as a piece of writing.
Yeah, I'm saying all the ways.
This is four quadrant stupidity.
This hits all the parts of stupid.
You know what I was thinking just now that gender has to be thought about for two seconds
and that's it.
Well, if we're going to do that, then maybe let's change the names of guns.
Let me get to my computer and type.
Oh, man.
You're also like, okay, all right, great.
So guns, we're going to do it.
We're going to reclassify them as cordless hole punchers.
You got your wish.
No, I want that.
I want to call them guns.
It was a joke.
Don't do it.
But anyway, all this is is is problem because the thing that I really want to talk about,
and this has come up on the show before I've talked about my favorite ride that anchored
this place and the place has never been the same because it does not it for many years
now has not had something called the scary dark ride.
I think the I'm putting in there falsely.
It's called scary dark ride.
You would walk up to this facade and you would find a big scary laughing woman.
I think the character is laughing Sal, which might have prompted this discussion before.
Yeah, kind of like missing tooth and stringy wig and she looks crazy.
She's an unbalanced person and she is wearing like a sweater, like a fuchsia sweater.
So, okay, what does that tell me about the scary dark ride that I'm about to go on?
Well, it doesn't tell you that it like everything we've talked today.
I talked about today is pirate oriented.
Yes, it's all pyre.
All of our kid things are pirates, but it's more than pirates though.
It's everything.
This ride is like it's it's pirates mixed with some haunted mansion mixed with seven dwarfs
like mine kind of stuff.
Isn't there a part in this in the Snow White ride where there's a bunch of eyes in the dark
looking at you?
Yeah, the old is the old wood scene.
I believe so.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's in this too.
And then there's like you pass by a bunch of explosive barrels like Mr. Toad or like
a couple rides have.
I don't know what how the pirates it's old treasure, but current explosives.
This is the least discernible ride I have ever seen.
It was so strange.
It's the smallest space that a ride has ever been fit into.
I swear like even a carnival like the traveling dark rides have some space
and maybe even a second story.
Right.
This was so claustrophobic and just jammed in there to where now it is just an office.
It has just become the corporate office for whoever's running the Balboa fun zone.
You walk up to it now and it's just a gate and there's a door that says business office on it.
Wow.
And it's heartbreaking to me where something so odd like such colorful local flavor used to be.
And now it's just business office.
It's so boring.
And it's all so right there in my memory.
You walk up this awkward little flight of stairs and I remember the it's like little
rounded bricks.
I know them anywhere.
It's always so eerie to walk up to this flight of stairs.
I miss this ride so much.
I actually I've discovered that there is a video of it because there's a listener Paul
Durso.
I think we've all met Paul and he I've talked about scary dark ride before.
He's like, oh, there is a video of it.
And thank God one person preserved it because otherwise there'd be so many details that
would be gone like before you like you walk into like a crate.
The right vehicle is a crate and it says I don't know.
They all might say different things, but the one I saw says garlic on it.
So you climb aboard a garlic crate to go to a pirate's mine.
Sure, sure.
It's so convoluted.
There's like party city decor just like stickers and cutouts on the door.
Then it's the creaky is to just like the the loudest track you've ever heard.
Right.
And then just occasional strobe lights and scratchy speakers that all just say dead men
tell no tales.
And other things say cursed be be blooming scala wags.
And some lines are just inaudible.
You just cannot tell whatsoever.
This thing is so janky.
But of course, it's a jankiness that I love that I was very fond of.
And I remember because it was this janky even in the early 90s when I would have started
to go on it.
And I remember thinking I knew enough already about Disneyland that like, you know,
some of these rides are from the 60s, but they still hold up.
And I thought the same thing about the scary dark ride.
Like presumably this is a 60s relic and it's rusted away and the speakers are bad.
But you know what?
That's part of the charm and we keep it alive because that's what you do.
Um, then in my little bit of research for this episode, I learned this ride opened in 1988.
The speaker problems were not from age.
It was just poor speakers.
It was designed that way.
Yes.
Yeah.
Wow.
So I'm going on this and and the ride then was as old as Rise of the Resistance is now.
Right.
There was no sign of this.
It was really like, I mean, it's like, I guess somebody like aging a lot from drugs or smoking
or whatever.
Fast, fast aging.
Yes.
Yeah.
Uh, a rapid decline and that's kind of what happened to the scary dark ride.
Although as Paul noted, somebody in the comments claims that they did the hand painting and it
does have like cool blacklight painting from somebody who claims that they also did that for
the Disneyland, the Fantasyland redoes in 1983 because some of it is
legit.
Like the actual the painting is of quality if the speakers are not and the story is not.
But I just, boy, I love this thing so much and I miss it a lot and it deserves better than being
an office.
A bunch of things all closed in the fun zone in 2005.
They tried to sell the whole ride to a museum in Temecula and then the deal fell through.
So as of 2006, it was like, we're good.
We will give you this ride for free.
Oh man.
And I, God, I wish I knew that.
I mean, I wasn't, I like, yeah, I lived in a garage in 2006.
I shared half of a garage with somebody in college, so I would have had nowhere to put
the entire scary dark ride.
But oh my God, today I would absolutely go through the hassle of the truck rental of moving the,
I'm sure very heavy garlic crate ride vehicles.
God, if I could have the entire, if anyone somehow knows what happened to the scary dark ride,
I would so happily fully recreate this in my garage, never have it for parking or recording
ever again.
My garage might be bigger than where the ride used to be.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
So it would be a downsize.
Well, you could pay for the public storage facility that would inevitably get broken into like
everyone I know is rented public storage.
It's like, Hey, you know that stuff you were storing, if it's gone.
But if you kept it all powered up and then the burglar was encountered a strobe light
skeleton saying, Oh yeah, boom and scale away.
They're going to be out of there in two seconds.
Yeah.
It's its own security system.
Learn the folly of their ways.
Yeah.
This might scare them to death.
I hope it would.
So it sounds like it's the most depressing trip you could take now going down to
admittedly.
Yes.
The fun zone was not the high.
I mean what it became, but well, if here, if I could say what actually, if the, how
this place impacted me, it's, it's on, it's on two levels.
One I'm like, how did this affect me in a way that the pilot pirates didn't or because you
can never have ownership of those, but you can have ownership over weird bullshit.
That's only in one place.
And when I add up all the things that light me up, talking to people or on the show,
it's always, do you know, there's like a big sad bear that's outside of the Rocky
mountain chocolate factory or there's themes in the fries and this one's like a spaceship
or there's a car wash.
It's like an old river boat.
For sure.
That all came out of the scary.
I don't want to talk about the haunted mansion.
Everyone knows the haunted mansion.
I want to talk about the pirates.
Mine ride in a garlic crate that makes no sense and it's bad and scary.
Yeah.
Where my friend smoked weed one time and I still feel bad about it.
We shouldn't have befouled this place.
I'm still mad.
It's not somebody I see anymore.
And I wonder if that's personally why maybe he lost me smoking weed on the
interest.
Very dark red.
You know, I would love, is there, is there any sort of research done on people's brain?
Cause also in addition to just what you're describing, there is a type of person and
I believe all three of us are this type of person that likes having a little thing that
not everybody knows.
What is that design?
What is that called?
There's something about our brains that like, oh, by the way, did you know?
And I feel like it's maybe 20% of the population has some version of this.
And it's the, it's the fandom I can relate to the most.
That's sort of how, I mean, the fact that when we started talking about theme parks,
the first time that the word screamscape came up the first time, like, okay, well,
this guy knows his shit.
Yes.
Screamscape.
It's dug deeper.
Spent a good amount of time for screamscape for this episode because smaller parks are
one of, they are pretty good at calling.
I called it as a joke, screamscape a rag many years ago on this podcast.
That was a joke, by the way.
I just want to apologize to screamscape in case they thought that was serious.
That was a joke, not just because it was a funny like reference to call them a rag,
but also in that time we've seen just how bad theme park sites can be.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
I might've met some of those ladies might be writing for Inside the Magic.
It was not a real day.
LGBT content going into.
I mean, those ladies are doing the same thing.
You know, they're, they're living their own Marvel universe and they're all in MCU with
alternate reality, the multigirl multiverse they're in right now.
Especially, I mean, a lot of conservatives, but especially Q people, it's like, yeah,
they get to like live in a VR simulation of life at all times.
Yeah.
But if I could, if I could also be sincere, what I really love about this area is it was
like the launching point for some very nice bonding and bike rides with my dad and something
that I hadn't gotten to do since the one, two punch of pandemic and child.
And it was so that like, yes, lots of like the, the places run down and bizarre conversations
you're over hearing and, and confusingly written t-shirts, but riding bikes with my
dad in that area, nothing replaces that.
Sure.
So that's what, that's what made me in this zone.
And it's all, all priceless.
And it was so nice to do it again.
Yeah, that's great.
I would have, I mean, I wish pirates cover here to get to do it again.
I mean, maybe I'll do it at a certain point if I go back, but it is, it is, it would be
fun to go do some of this stuff again to feel it, to feel the memories is what you're saying.
Well, now that we've introduced everybody to these places, then they'll all be cheering
us on.
That's true.
Yes.
When we end up back there, when you're walking or when you're, when you commandeer Black
Beards Bank and take it over.
When I put a watch in a safe deposit box at Black Beards Bank, people will be very excited.
Sure.
And when Jason, next time Jason saves coupons at Playland.
I am either adjacent or in Playland as this episode is coming out.
Oh, no kidding.
Yeah.
Somebody might look up and see you.
You get to see the magic.
It's possible.
Yeah.
Wow.
I've gone back, there were two summers I didn't go back.
One because of a shitty job I had where they're like, well, we really need people.
We can't let people take long vacations this summer.
And then 2020, I did have tickets to go to New Jersey and it just, yeah, didn't happen.
Well, it's going to be a great homecoming.
I hope this was a good audio homecoming.
Yeah.
And tell us your version of this, the parks that made you, because maybe they're episodes
or maybe we just laugh at a picture of something cruddy, but feel free to reply with those.
But for now, you survived Podcast the Ride.
And yeah, I don't know, fun little trip, I feel.
Yeah, great.
I just realized I'm parked on the street and you can't park after the time that it is.
No, it doesn't know at six that you can park whenever.
Isn't that right?
I think it's no parking after six.
Oh, shit.
Well, let's get the fuck out.
Hey, you can find us on all the socials at Podcast the Ride.
MerchantRT, Public Store, three bonus episodes every month at Podcast the Ride,
the second gate or one more bonus episode on our new tier club three.
All of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Are you actually leaving too?
Let's take a quick look.
Dear nobody, there's no way.
One of our cars are towed, Scott.
I already finished that.
That makes me want to, I'm going to take my sweet time.
I want to thank Brian.
Thank you, Brian, for being great with this.
I have to go.
Now you're saying we shouldn't be thanking Brian.
Thank you, thank you, Brian.
I also have to pee.
Thank you, Sean Rice.
You're going to end this nice moment with Brian.
You're being selfish about your own car.
I'm thankful for Brian.
I thank him.
Why didn't you go when I went?
Because I'm more professional.
Oh, fine.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production, executive produced by Brett Boehme, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.