Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
the theme park podcast where a couple of smooth characters
kick back and have a conversation
that's quite simply smoking.
I'm Scott Gardner, equally smooth as Mike Carlston, hi.
I'm so relaxed today, I'm feeling good.
Damn, nice exhale my brother, Jason Sheridan, hi.
Wow, that's real American tobacco, our finest export.
Yeah, the way they used to do it.
And as always, anytime we talk about a topic on an episode,
we endorse it full throat endorsement.
Yeah, that's right, it's literally,
it's covering our throat, it's smothering our throat.
The T-zone, the T-zone as they used to say
in all the old 50s ads where like four out of five doctors
tell you to smoke luckies.
Yeah, let's get that out of the way.
We are, you know, like does this episode,
is it an endorsement of the product?
And yes, 100% fully.
Yes, we love cigarettes.
Well, you know, not all of them, let's be, you know.
Yeah, cause it's those other brands that cause cancer
and impotence and some of the bad, but Camels,
nothing but.
Nothing but goodness.
Nothing but good times.
Nothing but solid smoothness.
That's why we're so excited to talk about,
but it won't be mainly about the product, I would say.
I think largely we will focus on the character
that this wonderful brand was forced to retire.
Yeah.
Yeah, cause the marketing memos behind it that came out,
turned out to be like 10 times more ghoulish than I thought.
Oh really?
I think inadvertently they picked up you smokers
with this cool, fun character.
On the other hand.
You said inadvertently?
Inadvertently they picked up very young ones, I mean.
But then there were memos saying like,
we need to hit the youth market.
It's more sustainable.
Cause if you pander to the older smoker market,
eventually they go away.
But the youth market stays around for a while.
Yeah, I don't think anything.
Until they die of lung cancer.
Nothing was accidental about this.
Nothing was accidental, but they were like,
they were winking like in testivodes.
Like, oh I don't know.
They wanted to have their own Ronald McDonald.
And it worked.
And it worked, it's so fucked up, it's crazy.
Well yes, yes.
I'm gonna throw a premise into the mix here.
We're talking about Joe Camel, the spokes camel,
the smokes camel of Camel Cigarettes,
which was heavily around in America from 88 to 97.
Our sweet spot.
Our childhood sweet spot.
Yeah, it was right there with everybody we love.
With McDonald Land and Chuck and the Disney gang.
Yeah, he was right in there.
I think probably a lot of people listening.
He was part of our childhoods.
Yes he was.
He was a lot.
He was very around.
The forbidden character.
Like I knew him and I liked all the bright colors
in the ads, but I knew like this is naughty.
Yeah.
You're not supposed to know too much about it.
Well, which this is my, okay, because you guys,
we were talking about it before we started,
that we, you know, you were watching YouTube videos,
reading articles about this phenomenon and this character.
And a lot of it is very hard, stridently,
this was the character designed
to make children smoke cigarettes.
Sure, sure.
And I think there's some truth to that,
but here, just keep that in mind as we talk
about what these ads are.
Because I maybe take a little bit of umbrage
with the idea that like, how do we nail kids?
A poor playing camel?
Yeah, well what do kids like?
Okay, well for sure billiards, definitely billiards.
I'll say this though, I liked billiards as a kid.
Yeah, I liked billiards too.
Billiards looked like a cool adult thing to do.
Sure, but you're both like, you know,
you're from the 90s by way of the 30s.
Cause we watched The Hustler when we were little.
Yeah.
The Paul Newman movie, The Hustler.
Jason probably did.
Great movie.
One of my dad's favorite movies.
No, I didn't see that until a few years ago actually.
I've never seen The Color of Money,
the pseudo sequel that Scorsese directed with Tom Cruise.
I haven't either, yeah, I've been meaning to do that,
digging into the full Tom Cruise filmography.
But like, that's what I, yeah,
you hear what I'm saying that like,
some of the things that we'll get to,
that Joe Camel is associated with.
I am a little bit, yeah, you know, kids,
you know how kids love,
Well teens though.
Like fedoras and swing music.
Yeah.
Like Gen X maybe more was being marketed to
than us who were littler.
I think, yes, I think that it's more,
That's still 12, 13, 14 year olds.
Yeah, I think it's more like teens acceptable for sure.
And I think there was, I think sure,
the idea that a cartoon character will be used
for this cigarette brand is going to end up netting kids.
I'm not saying it's a good thing.
I just think that there is some real stridency
in what's been written about it.
And again, just keep it in mind as we go.
As we look at some of these ads go,
yeah, you know what a kid would like this.
Some of the ads are really funny.
Mm-hmm.
Well, yeah, and look, that's why, you know,
I don't think we're here to moralize.
At least I'm not.
I think that we need to separate the art
from the bad company with the bad intentions
that produce the art.
Well, yeah, I can swear, growing up,
I got it from every direction that like,
this is no good, this is bad.
This might've been the main chunk
of media literacy education I got was teachers going like,
we're gonna do something different today.
We're gonna talk about subliminal messages in advertising.
And this being like a big example.
Well, but the subliminal part of this is that his nose
looks like a big penis.
Yeah.
It looks like a dick.
That wasn't explicitly said at the time.
Yes, that for sure is the, it's impossible to unsee
once you realize it.
That's weirder.
But like the stuff of like, yeah, cool parties
and like motorcycles.
Yeah, that's not subliminal.
Like he's riding a motorcycle and like.
He's got a cool bomber jacket on.
His jeans are so tight.
Joe Camel's jeans are just so tight.
He looks like Bruce Springsteen
on the cover of Born in the USA.
Wow, look at this man, this camel man.
I wanna be a ripped hunk like this guy.
Look, I know that I'm a quiet seven year old
who reads basketball stats and Disney annual reports.
But he was.
But I think, boy, that's who I wanna be.
Vroom, vroom, rev, rev.
He did catch my eye though.
I was like low key interested in him.
Yes.
I knew I was told smoking was bad.
So yes, he was a forbidden character.
But.
It did not inspire me to ever smoke a camel cigarette.
No.
I don't believe in the brief period
where I would smoke one cigarette like every several weeks
and make a big show of it.
I'm stressed.
Jason does that too.
Or he did that.
That's what I've sensed yet.
You had a dark.
I would smoke backstage.
Brooding.
Improv shows that people were smoking.
I would walk, yeah.
Every two years I'd walk outside at a party
and Jason was just smoking on the porch.
And I'd go, what are you doing?
What is this?
It was that class.
It was that teacher.
The teacher made him wanna do it.
Marissa's smoking periods here and there.
Sure.
Well, that camel, Jason was like,
well, you know, it was the camel with the dick nose.
It was the camel with the dick nose.
It was cool.
If it's good enough.
For the camel with the dick nose.
Sorry, if it's good enough for this dick face.
The way, Harry, wait, I need to look at a picture
and just see where the cigarette kinda comes out of.
Because really it's as if,
if you wanted to recreate this,
it's certainly going with this.
You would have to put the cigarette
under your right ball.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, go take a look.
Pause this podcast if you don't know
what your camel looks like.
And it does look like he has a penis
and two balls are his snoot.
And his cigarette is hanging out of his right underball.
Yeah, and it's a flaccid penis.
That's an interesting, if we're talking about,
because it's the ultimate badass
and who you wanna be rev rev vroom vroom.
You know how I want a product that makes my face feel
like a not hard dick.
Like a droopy.
I don't wanna get too weird though,
but it does look, it has a good size
is what I'm saying, even not.
That's true, you're right, you're right.
Let's be fair, there's an implied
that when it's brought to full steam.
There's a virility that's implied.
Not virility, it's not the word.
Did everyone watch the TV Fun House?
Like re-watch the TV Fun House?
I remember that from the time.
The segment where it's like, Joe Camel.
It's like, yeah, Pokemon was pretty new at the time.
And yeah, Joe Camel had a big penis
and then Team Rocket's guys had like,
were clearly breasts and a vagina and a butt.
And then they would show you all the products.
And then as it went on, it would start showing montage
of real quick shots of products
and there were very clearly cigarette packs
every third image.
Yeah, the Pokemon parody and like tackling
that collect them all.
With some truth to the fact that
the Joe Camel products were unreal.
There's so many.
There's unlimited.
There's no way that we got them all.
There's no way that we saw pictures of all of them.
No, no, and I didn't dig super hard into the products,
but some of them, yeah, like if you take just his face
and make it, and I can't picture,
is it like a, there might be a mug or something.
Anything where it is just primarily the nose
and the face droops.
It does, like if you walked into a room
and didn't get up close to it, you would just go,
why does this person have a novelty mug of a penis?
Yeah.
The tone doesn't help.
The skin tone doesn't help.
No, it's absolutely what they were,
the artist was going for.
Should we do some, Jason, you have the history brought up
of Joe Camel?
Well, I have something about the art.
Did you come across the art, Jerry LaFaro?
Cause it was. Some of the art.
It was like drawn in 1974.
Drawn by a French designer for like French marketing stuff.
And around for a while before it came to America.
Not in America, I didn't realize that,
that the American run was only 88 to 97.
Yeah.
That's like, that doesn't feel right to me.
The way that he looms large, you're like,
he had to have been around for more than nine years,
but apparently not.
It feels like there should have been like 1960s,
like Camel ads.
Cause we feel like, you know, it feels like he was with us
forever.
Yeah.
I mean, the Camel on the cigarette pack has been around
since the beginning.
And that Camel's name is Old Joe.
Old Joe.
He's just a regular Camel.
Yeah.
Essentially.
Yeah. It's kind of insane that the first American use of him,
I believe was in the 75th anniversary campaign.
That's pretty lit.
Like we're that deep into this product,
which I guess speaks to the like old tiny nature of cigarettes
a little bit.
And they, they, they thrive for a long time with this very,
like a kind of line drawn Camel that could have been on a
product in 1802.
Sure.
But then, you know, but now it's the eighties.
It's a different world.
We got to get cool.
We got to get like airbrushed.
And that's, I think what I did again,
if I'm just purely the art of it,
cause in the recently I've been seeing some of this stuff and,
and if you can see it in the highest quality you can,
it like it rules honestly,
just pure like however they painted it, whatever the,
I don't know if we're getting into early digital yet or maybe not.
Maybe I'm reacting to the,
an older school style of color and illustration.
Well, I came across the guy,
Jerry LaFaro who drew some of this stuff also drew like the
t-shirts with animals on it.
And if you were in the nineties, you,
what you're imagining is what I'm talking about.
Like save the rainforest.
Like save the rainforest, like really digital art,
dolphins and stuff sometimes sold at aquariums and zoos,
sometimes sold as fundraisers.
I feel like we have them at school.
You know what?
Jerry LaFaro?
Jerry LaFaro.
Jason, if you look up some of those pictures,
if there's a picture of a dolphin,
does the dolphin's beak look like a giant penis?
I mean, it could be argued that this is a little phallic.
Yeah, but they naturally are a little phallic.
Yeah, yeah.
And the camel is less so.
So, I mean, this was a more,
like more unnerving discovery that I didn't know that like,
oh, the same guy drew on Joe camel sometimes was also
drawing all those animals.
So there is like a connection with a thing that I knew and
liked.
Funny story,
a few years ago,
he was quoted in,
I think Yahoo News,
there's an article,
Joe camel illustrator,
e-sig maker jewels marketing seems more egregious.
Where it's because there is like,
there were jewel ads a few years ago.
I know they're like in trouble now,
but there is like hipster jewel ads.
Yeah, yeah.
Like basically saying hipster smokes,
vapes jewel.
It's been a rough time for jewel.
We've gotten some concern about the sector keeper's
wellbeing.
Yeah, that's true.
Anybody talked to him lately or he might be,
maybe he's not really reaching out just given that he's so
bummed about it.
Yeah, I don't know.
He hasn't been around.
I feel like he's been really depressed.
Yeah.
He's probably,
what I would imagine is he's going everywhere that jewels
are.
Oh yeah.
He has ghostly powers.
He would rather,
he'd rather collect as many as he can and hoard them than
hang out with us.
It's like Elaine with the sponge episode of Seinfeld.
Yeah.
Just a lot, but no laughs.
Just one very sad ghost.
No laughs.
So legit artists part of this.
Yeah.
Cool art that definitely as a kid,
I liked and was fascinated by it,
but it did give me a feel like a lascivious feeling.
I feel felt inappropriate looking at it.
I don't think it had to do just with the cigarettes.
I think he was exuding something.
Slee, yeah, it's a little sleazy.
This is one of our sleaziest topics.
I think we've ever covered.
Is this the sleaziest?
What are the sleaziest?
Like I just feel like,
I just feel like it's all very sleazy,
like cigarette advertise.
But I'm saying if we do what Scott was saying and separate
the, if it's just the image itself, is that what it is?
Is it sleazy?
Is it cause like Joe is so confident and like he's exuding
a camel sexuality that is making us uncomfortable?
Like a hedonism sort of thing.
Well no, but he's not like in the middle
of a giant orgy or anything.
He's in the middle.
He's in the middle of a pool hall.
You don't really see Joe Camel at work.
You don't see him with a Protestant work ethic.
You only see Joe Camel at play.
At only at play, yes.
Well here, let's try to, let's analyze some photos.
Here, let's, this one's like a classic one to me.
I think if you look up Joe Camel hot tub, you'll see it.
So he, I mean, all right, is this one sleazy to us?
He's in a jacuzzi.
He's looking over a beautiful purple 90s dusk,
pinks and purples, which I'm a sucker for.
Yeah, of course.
With a pack next to him and the smoking in the hot tub,
empty beer, empty sleazy kind of, he's ripped.
Well, if you look at those, they are fully human.
He's jazz. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I kept coming across that like his hands
would only be showed when necessary.
And it's kind of necessary the way this image is composed.
They are weird.
He's got three big dick fingers on the one hand.
Yeah, they're real sausagey, I was gonna say.
They're real.
I mean, there's other moments, there's one image
where he's like wearing an elaborate coat
and on the cuff is the Camel image from the cigarette pack,
like really small.
And I think it's one of the 75 years and still smoking,
which is such a grim, that's so funny.
Yeah, that's something, if you take the cool N apostrophe
out of it, it's a statement that you could say
about an old relative you're concerned about,
75 years and still smoking.
Still smoking.
And you're like, is it killing them
or is it keeping them alive?
You know, it's where. Oh yeah, at this point, yeah.
Pickled, as they say.
Like you guys and Lucky Charms and Coke Starlight.
Stopping would be the issue.
Is their pack a day and their daily seven and seven
keeping them going, you know?
Here's another one.
This is kind of outside of the style.
It's a little bit of a 60s throwback a little bit.
In fact, I think they're clearly edging him over
to the Connery bond era.
He's in front of a surfacing submarine
or a sinking submarine.
Did he do something to destroy the submarine
but yet remained in a tux?
Hot lady behind him in a fuchsia one piece,
kind of a Daryl Hannah thing going on.
That's one thing about Joe.
He, I think primarily is into human women.
And human women are very into him.
Yeah, well of course.
There is a big party scene.
There's a big party scene
with a lot of lady camels in there too.
They introduced some ladies.
Yeah, when you get into his nightclub.
His friend, well then there's his friends that come up.
Well, let's focus on Joe.
Let's focus on Joe right now.
I do wanna say, I'm gonna shout out this YouTube video
by a user named Alyssa Erin,
the history of cartoon cigarette advertising.
Because Cool Cigarettes for a long time
had Willie the Penguin.
Okay.
And they say Willie was the,
he looks like a penguin in a tuxedo.
And his introduction kind of lines up with like,
oh, he also inspired the Batman Penguin in the 30s,
in the late 30s.
What, the cigarette?
The mascot inspired the?
Yeah, and I think when you,
if you see like this kind of,
Tim Burton's movie, Penguins,
kind of look like Willie the Cool Cigarette.
Right, right.
And his girlfriend, I forget her name,
but they were on like, you know, ceramic stuff.
They were on, you know, ashtrays and all.
Wow, oh yeah, geez.
I didn't realize this was around so early.
Yeah, and she played a clip in the video.
They commissioned Fleischer Studios
to make a short, Fleischer Studios who did Popeye
and Betty Boop.
They did a short of the penguins
in a factory making the cigarettes.
They make them.
What Mike loves are the Disney characters.
That's right.
Clean Disneyland.
So, but probably the most alarming thing was this,
I learned was a series of comic strips
from Dural Cigarettes where the pack keeps saying,
taste me, taste me.
But most alarming was learning that I am apparently
in one of these cigarettes.
Oh my God, oh, oh.
Whoa.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
Wow.
What's happening here?
What are you doing?
It's a bride and groom.
The bride appears to be like six or eight inches taller
than the groom.
Story of my life.
And they are getting married.
They're cutting the cake.
And the cigarette box just keeps floating through the air
saying, taste me, taste me.
And then at the end, they're in their car driving away.
How do you feel about it?
I mean.
What's your story of your life?
I'm more confused that they're just keep,
they have like four nicknames for each other.
Like one of your friends, Lamb Chop,
no Honey Bone, that's Dural.
Dural.
Who invited Dural?
How can a low tar and nicotine,
low tar and nicotine cigarette talk taste?
Try one, Mike.
Try one, my pigeon.
That unfortunately does seem like something I would say.
Yeah.
Ah, my pigeon.
My pigeon.
Yeah.
Wow.
Wow. Wow.
But are you smiling in there?
Are you happy to see Dural?
Yeah, everyone's happy.
Well, yeah.
He's yeah.
He seems close with Dural.
And then she smokes.
Do you like the taste, Schnuckums?
I do.
And that's the conclusion.
Driving away, just got married.
And she learned about a new cigarette.
That's what it would have been the scenario
if you and Jane had had that weed in New York.
Oh, yeah.
What do you think, darling?
Do you like this street weed sold from a car table?
This three-car Monte table, my pigeon?
Do you like this very legitimate weed
sold next to the police car
that they are paying no mind to?
Well, so a rich history, evidently, of cartoon.
Yeah.
Yeah, Joe's part of a proud history.
I'm gonna bring into things my main piece of research,
which is, so I was,
I've been working with this very funny guy, Joe Carnegie,
and he was, I know that he has given some office gifts out
in the recent past that are Joe Kamel-oriented.
Here's a little notebook that has that Joe
in the hot tub image on it.
Wow, the hot tub.
So he's spoken of, they're actually legitimately liking it
from that artistic angle, that airbrushy angle
that I dig as well.
And so I said, okay, we're doing a podcast
right about Joe Kamel, what can you point me to?
And he said, oh, you gotta borrow this book I have.
Oh, interesting.
There is a coffee table book,
and this book is called A Kamel Named Joe,
the Illustrated Story of an American Pop Icon.
Wow.
And this book is pretty phenomenal.
I was into this thing.
When borrowed it, a lot of funny stuff about it.
The first thing is like leafing through the entire thing
where you get to see a ton of the art
and a ton of backstory and say,
even information about secret Joe campaigns
that didn't come out.
This is really the mother load here.
But one thing is every page that I turned,
I started realizing, oh, this book reeks of smoke.
There are pages that have not been like, okay,
so no one, wherever this book has been,
whoever did this, who sold it on eBay,
nobody has opened pages 87 to 88.
Because of the smoke has stuck them together?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, yeah, some of them might.
I mean, I hate to be vulgar, but was it come?
I don't think a preview,
I found no evidence that a previous owner
came all over the book.
Well, like, Jay though.
But they were sampling the product.
What were you going to say, Michael?
I'm afraid.
No, I was just gonna say,
Jason was saying it was like a lascivious ad,
so maybe somebody was really into the book.
Unless it was pages that I missed or just could not,
they were so sealed together, so coded.
No, I know it.
The pages opened fine.
Stickiness was not the issue.
I would just turn and then go like, ah,
just get the most stale smell.
But Mike, it is not the pages of the book,
the physical book that were ever soaking wet.
It is the copy.
The copy in this book is just dripping,
dripping with desire for Joe Camel.
It is crazy.
It is like so from the POV of people
who want to fuck Joe Camel.
It's wild.
Can I ask, does it seem like the book was written
five or 10 years later of a look back,
or does it seem like a book that you would cash in,
Camel cash, and receive the coffee table book?
You are right on both counts in a way.
I believe this was done a year or two
after the campaign had been retired,
but it was a book that you could purchase.
We can't use Joe in the ads anymore,
but I don't think anyone, you know,
Bill Clinton has not told us that we have to stop,
that we can't sell a coffee table book
and sell it with our Camel money, C notes,
is that correct?
C notes.
Yes, they were called C notes.
So what you're saying is this is like a eulogy.
This is a celebration of life.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
At the very beginning, the book is very solemnly dedicated
to for Joe Camel wherever he is.
And then he started going, okay,
so this is so crazy, the love of this character,
that this must be from the company.
And sure enough, at the beginning, you can look up,
okay, it's from R.J. Reynolds, it's from the company.
And then there is a foreword by somebody
who is an upper level executive, I think,
in that enterprise, which, let me read.
Okay, so he, you know, because this comes right after
Joe has been banned, essentially.
And you might be wondering, is it gonna go over that stuff?
Are we gonna hear their side of that story?
No, no, no, it's a celebration.
This book isn't about politics.
This is quite simply a book about Joe,
a charismatic camel who became nothing less
than an American pop phenomenon.
And then the foreword goes on.
Okay, buckle up for this.
So talking about how crazy the popularity
of the character was, he got mail, lots of mail,
even got a wedding invitation.
Somebody invited, just like Doral there,
what was the name?
Yeah, Doral, the cigarettes.
Somebody tried to have Joe come to their real wedding.
And then, in a particularly telling example
of just how real he became
in the American popular imagination,
a New York City focus group of racially diverse
20-somethings spontaneously got into a heated debate
about whether Joe was black or white.
Joe struck a chord for racial harmony that day
when they finally agreed that he was, after all,
just a very cool camel and consequently belonged
to everybody.
What a moving, true story.
What a great real story that really happened.
And so insane.
You missed out, Euniceff.
You could have had a perfect ambassador
who belonged to everybody.
As my son gets older and I have to answer
some of the more difficult questions about our world,
and if he asks, what is with the racial strife
in this country?
And I'll say, well, I'm not sure where it began.
I think it had something to do with all of the races
fighting over who could claim ownership
over this sexy camel.
And then all his questions will be answered in that moment.
Oh, I see, I understand.
I would fight very hard to claim Joe for my race as well.
Of course, we all would.
We can't blame anybody for that.
Right.
Penis-faced camel in a pool hall?
No, we want the penis-faced camel.
We want...
We are all smooth characters.
That's what Joe taught us.
Yeah, I mean, you know, yeah.
And look, I think, yeah, I think it's beautiful.
This is a beautiful tale.
I would just get like,
when I'm reading sometimes about masked spokes characters,
the people who create them
and the people of the ad companies develop either love
or like incredible connection to these characters too.
Like the guy who was McGruff
but like was doing the voice until he died
in like late, his early 90s, maybe, when he died.
He was an older dude.
And I said, I listened to YouTube.
Maybe we played it on the first episode.
We were like, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got every cut.
Like, you're like, oh God, somebody needs to...
Maybe new voice time.
Yeah, but I mean, I think he had a lot of like,
he created this character and it was like,
it was everything.
So obviously like this is lustful,
these crazy stories in this lustful copy.
Well, and that's just the forward by the way.
Because then the actual book is written by David De Smith.
Who is David De Smith?
Okay, he wrote copy for Joe Cammie.
He was part of the campaign.
So that's where it just made the tone of what I'm reading
make a lot of sense because it just started to feel to me
like the Mad Men, Don Draper monologues.
Like when he comes into the meetings
and just perfectly summarizes
not just what the product is all about,
but what this country is all about.
And as I started reading it in that voice,
let me just hear some of the better little snippets.
Wherever Joe went, a part of each of us went with him
when he was sitting six feet offshore in a lounge chair,
tickling his toes in the warm turquoise water.
He was just sitting in for us.
Yeah, you know, it's just really assuming.
I think even like, what is the average camel customer
think of Joe Cammie?
They're like, hey, look at that camel.
He looks funny or he looks cool.
Yeah.
That's the end of it.
I don't think a lot of, even people who buy,
well, because it's an addiction at a point.
People who spent the most money on camel cigarettes
are not like, and there he was, both father and brother.
Yeah.
Father, son and the Holy Ghost, all one.
How many kinds of embrace can one character give?
The answer is all.
You smoke a camel when you're happy.
You smoke it when you're sad.
They're always there for you.
It's like a carousel.
Jesus has returned and he has a dick face camel man.
There's water and there's camels.
Everything else we can figure it out as we go along.
If I got those two, I'm fine.
I'm alive.
Even guys with like a Joe camel beach towel,
I don't think we're like pouring over this copy
and being like, look at this man.
This is the ultimate man.
This is who I, this is my God now.
Like I don't think.
It's who I want to be, who I want to be with.
Never had feelings for a man before,
but is that even what's happening?
He's beyond man.
He's beyond human.
There has to be.
He's beyond camel.
He doesn't even have a hump.
If listeners are our age,
reach out to us if like your dad had our thing for Joe camel.
Cause I wonder if there were a couple of straight people
like dad really liked Joe camel.
Yeah.
I mean, people definitely have allegiance
to a cigarette brand.
Like I smoke parliaments, I smoke Lucky's.
But I wonder if it was like, yeah,
he had a lot of Joe merchandise and ads.
Like I wonder if there was,
there were particular enthusiasts of Joe himself.
Was there a man cave?
Was there a garage that was particularly, yeah.
Would you go into your dad's garage
and it's full of weird Joe camel stuff.
Not like a normal garage.
It's full of fries, electronics, liquidation sale,
inspirational posters and old Epcot signs.
My big memory of friends, parents who would smoke
in their house growing up was just that
there were ashtrays everywhere.
And an abundance of blueberry candles.
That that was what,
that's what we're going to cover up the smell of cigarettes
with, you know, Yankee candle, blueberry candles.
But then what happens is that you just smell blueberry
candles and secondhand smoke,
like in that caked in smoke smell.
Yeah.
And I just-
Which that is nasty.
Like the, I can even like,
I could still feel, I haven't smoked in a long time,
but I could feel the appeal of somebody smoking next to me
in the smoke itself.
Like, oh, that's a little, that smells okay.
But it's, but that caked in that just like tar, ashy,
what I was getting out of this book with each page turn.
It's so nasty.
It's so, like, I remember going to like, yeah,
sleep over at a friend's house and the parents smoked
inside the house.
And it was just crazy.
You were like a little, your little boy clothes
smell like smoke.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah.
And like, yeah, you're on like, like sleeping on their couch
or something and it's like you're rolling in their fucking
like secondhand smoke that's like settled down on this couch.
Yeah.
It is crazy that in our life,
I always forget that in our lifetime is when like
smoking bans started and bars and stuff.
Oh yeah.
It's like when we went to college, like you smoke anywhere.
I remember being a kid, the first thing they'd say
at the host stage is like, smoking or not.
Yeah.
And oftentimes it didn't matter
because everywhere it didn't matter.
You'd get blood like right next to the smoking section,
which had no like hard divider or air filtration system.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're just getting smoke.
My dad smoked a pipe on and off when I was younger,
but always smoked it outdoors.
So didn't really smell, would smell like in passing.
How often was he smoking that pipe?
A few times a day when he was smoking it.
Oh, okay.
But like he would take a few years,
he would stop for a few years.
He actually got off it in the last 10 years
by smoking e-cigarettes and then Juul.
But he changed a couple times.
Wow.
My dad's a cool millennial.
My dad's a Juuling cool millennial.
Yeah, it's got him.
How was the pipe?
Can I ask it was the pipe like, what did it look like?
Was it a corn cob?
No, it was just like, there's just like a regular
kind of like pipe you can get.
It's very labor intensive.
It takes a while.
You have to pack it
and then you have to get it going and stuff.
Was it like, I'm trying to think it's,
yeah, corn cob pipes with Popeye head.
Yeah.
Just like brown, like wood, I guess.
Just a regular like curled up pipe.
No, like a straight pipe.
You're never gonna get what you want out of,
I know what you wanna hear is that the pipe was like,
you know, 30% bigger than Jason's dad's face.
And it was small enough he could fit in a pocket.
Yeah.
And the smoke made sounds as it came out.
They didn't make a toot toot.
The smoke was silent, unfortunately.
I know what you're after.
I am after a toot toot.
I think that's absolutely right.
But I'm trying to imagine it.
Cause I, my grandfather smoked cigarettes,
but I don't remember what the brand was.
But he did not have a pipe.
You're really, you're pissing off the listeners.
They gotta know what your grandpa smoked.
I'll have to ask questions.
Write them all a letter after this episode's out.
I'll have to ask my mom if she remembers.
Yeah.
That was like just a few weeks ago.
That was the big news story one day.
It's like the FDA is going to ban Juul.
And it was kind of like,
oh God, why is every Democrat just Michael Bloomberg now
banning the big, so like, who cares?
Like you've already taken most of the flavors of like all.
I can't think of any bigger issues
that need to be solved right now.
But that was like, oh, this is,
this is stupid news story of the week.
And then the next day Rover's weight was appealed.
Like it's like, what the fuck?
What?
I thought this was a stupid news week,
not a horrific news week.
Well, they'll do what we voted them in there to do.
They're going to get rid of those robot cigarettes.
Yeah.
Are the big sodas still banned in New York?
I don't know.
I haven't heard about the big sodas in a while.
They might've scaled that back.
You got to go to a weird table.
You got to go to a little table.
It's got to go to a little table next to the car.
A former three card Monte table.
Former three card Monte.
You can tell, you see the card stains.
It's by the knockoff designer bags and scarves and stuff.
In Japan, you couldn't get a large.
You couldn't get a big one.
In Japan?
Yeah.
Well, then what?
Like a big drink.
You made sure to get a big drink in Japan.
You can't.
Oh, you can't.
No, you aren't allowed.
Didn't hit that T.
That's why, look, Mike, that's the importance of little.
That's why we hit those T's.
Right.
Yeah, I think most countries don't serve.
I think our small is upsetting in most countries.
I think that's right.
Yeah.
Mike's fighting for the right to drink full fat Sprite.
So in the, in the, the narrative,
like the writerly voice of David DeSmith,
I think informs some of the character because like, okay,
there's no, there's only so much you can glean from the ads,
from silent ads, because as far as I could tell,
unless you guys hit some mother load,
there is not some secret Joe Camel animated series
that was made that we dug up.
So there's not a lot of places to like hear the voice
of the character.
No, I think Nixon banned cigarette ads
on television.
I did find there is a Marlboro ad without Joe Camel,
but Scott, I thought you would think this was interesting.
Maybe this is from another country.
It's like a Jeep going through a jungle and it features,
maybe you know this man, Rushden Rocky Pamplin.
No.
A former college football player and model
who was employed as a bodyguard for the American rock band,
the Beach Boys in the late 1970s.
Wow.
Oh, a piece of Beach Boys mythology.
I don't know about Rocky Pamplin.
He's a hunk.
Like he's a all American guy smoking a Camel.
Geez, I can't believe they didn't get that guy up on stage
like Stamos.
That was the whole thing with Stamos.
It's like maybe we're losing our hunkiness.
We need a ringer hunk.
All right, I'm gonna learn all about Rocky Pamplin now.
Thank you for that.
No, so there's not a lot where we get a sense
of the character, how he speaks or whatever,
but this is where the book comes in handy.
With some of it probably written by this guy himself.
There were odd bits and pieces where we get a sense
of what's going on in Joe's brain,
such as on matchbook covers.
I think they put out one issue
of a magazine called Smooth Magazine.
And I think all of these things,
I'm seeing it on matchbooks,
but then I think this was a feature
in Smooth Magazine as well.
Something called Joe's Smooth Philosophy.
So if we're trying to tackle the character,
this might help us get into his head.
Here is Joe's Smooth Philosophy on movie rentals.
The reason that it's so popular these days
is that you can do things at home
that you can't do in the theater, like smoke camels.
So we know this about him.
He likes movie rentals.
I bet he's a guy who'd tell you to be kind, rewind,
and smoke smooth.
For a second I thought he was talking about,
and again, I hate to be vulgar, but jerking off at home.
Not in the theater.
I think that's the implication.
You think it's jerking off, not having sex with?
You think that specifically, you know,
because what a smooth character would do
is pull out his watch.
Plunging himself alone in a theater.
Joe Gamble, when did the local video store
went to Blockbuster, went to West Coast Video,
got a copy of Hudson Hawk, went home,
pulled out the gold bond, and just was like,
well, it's Joe's evening.
This is just for me.
The gold bond?
The gold bond, I don't know.
I don't even wanna unpack that.
Pulled out the Jergens, pulled out the gold bond.
I wanna go on a camel riff,
but I'd love to talk about gold bond.
Man's best friend, if you know what I mean.
If you're looking at non-nude scenes with,
who's in Hudson Hawk, Andy McDowell?
Or hey, teach his own, Frank Stallone.
Sometimes I just...
A big throng.
I admire old Frank.
I've got a big tub of gold bond.
I've got a double date tonight.
I'm watching Ghosts.
I'm joined by Patrick Swayze and Whoopi Goldberg.
Who's the love interest in Ghosts?
Mm. Fuck.
Well, I'd need more.
Demi Moore and of course, my friend Nivea.
The finest moisturizer a man can buy.
A big problem is they make these porno theaters
for you to go watch,
but they don't let you jerk off in them.
There's always a cop there for an undercover sting.
That's why I like to rent the movie
and go home and get a big tub of gold bond powder.
Have I gone through a tub in a night?
Try two.
Gold bond powder?
I don't know what to go.
I don't know what to get.
They have a full range of products.
I mean, when I Google gold bond, I find powder.
Yeah, it's powder.
Yeah, but they also sell like lotion and moisturizer.
Okay, so when you were talking about...
You were talking about gold bond.
I wasn't talking about using gold bond medicated powder.
Look, you made an old timey reference
and I assumed you were talking about
masturbating with powder.
Okay.
Fair enough.
Hey, look, Joe Camel.
Hey, what can I say?
I know billiards and what do you do when you...
Hey, this looks like...
It looks like I was just doing a bunch of cocaine,
but I assure you I was not.
I was masturbating.
That's why I meant...
We're just masturbating with a bunch of powder.
You chuck up your pool cue and you chuck up your camel cue.
That's why men were so irritable in the past.
Why they smoked and drank so much.
They were so irritated and then one of them
happened to try their wife's night cream
and we're like, this is miles better.
Like their face cream?
Yeah.
It's better than powder, you know?
Like what is this weird, what's this pie filling
that the mother puts on her face?
Ooh, are there other uses?
Look at all this, look at this child's play sand.
I wonder what else you could do with this.
Oh, weird.
It's just like setting up for an Olympic,
setting up for the pole vault,
different kind of pole vault if you know what I mean.
Just toss a bunch of powder in the air,
clap it against your hands and you're good to go.
But I'm no sprinting involved, I'm taking my time.
I do think we are missing an important piece
of Joe Camel's vibe and that is he kind of fits into the,
he's kind of a blank slate.
He can kind of do any like relaxing vacation cool guy stuff.
He falls into like the big dog, here he is like fishing,
he's in a full fishing attire.
That's true, he has a little of the Margaritaville thing too.
He'll be in the keys and the capes and what have you.
I was gonna say he fits into like the mold of 90s t-shirts
of like big dog at Big Johnson,
where like they can kind of do anything.
I think he wrote that a little of that way.
A little bit of it.
A little bit.
I feel like nothing Joe does in any of the images
I think would be out of character for him.
It's not like he's, I mean I guess he's James Bond,
but he's also Jimmy Buffett.
Yeah.
Which I think honestly kind of lends it.
Tully Mars is sort of that way, Jimmy Buffett's character.
A lot of times there's like a Miami Vice, Don Johnson,
kind of like he's got a suit with the sleeves rolled up
at like a nightclub sort of thing.
I'm trying to think if there's anything
that would be like too much, like this guy can do,
he's too much of a jack of all trades.
Well, was there like him in space or anything?
Is there him with like a shotgun, like shooting skeet?
They're taking care of the city.
Put taking matters into my own hands.
Just joke, is Joe Camel a one man militia?
Maybe.
Joe Camel is the substitute.
Joe Camel in Death Proof Five.
Let me read a little bit of,
let me go back into Draper mode.
Here's something asserted by this author.
Joe was nothing if not optimistic.
He didn't sit down at the craps table
or the blackjack table or the high stakes poker table
expecting to lose his shirt.
Joe was a winner.
Whether he was shooting pool
and clearing the table in one turn,
playing golf and scoring in the mid 20s for 18 holes
or I'll stop it there.
Things just went his way.
And that was one of the reasons he was so well liked.
So here are some new facts about Joe Camel.
First one, typically we see him shooting pool
in a lot of the ads.
What we don't realize maybe is that he sets up
all of the balls one shot and most of them go in.
He's like a trick shot guy.
He's a trick shot guy, yeah.
So he's, yeah, he's perfection.
And that's it.
Now you use the word trick.
So it is possible to like,
oh, I just know the mechanics of the pool table.
I can figure that out.
But it's really logic defying,
gravity defying everything,
laws of space and time defying
that he can play golf and score in the mid 20s.
Just to remind everyone of golf,
like the par in golf typically 72.
You gotta have a lot of holes in one.
It is, yeah, we're talking primarily holes in one.
We're talking that like a two,
that a double eagle would make Joe go,
damn, I'll get them next time.
It's kind of in my head that,
I think Tiger at one point got a 59,
holy shit, a 59, but that's camel scoffs at Tiger.
There's one king of this jungle, that's camel.
This is like Kim Jong-un propaganda.
This is like other countries dictator propaganda
where you're like, he's never scored over a 30 in golf.
Everyone's like, wow, he's amazing.
That's, it's so kind of him to be our leader
rather than to use his God given gift
as the greatest golfer has ever walked the earth.
That's similar with Jett.
Like it's boy, he could be, he'd be cleaning up.
He'd be the great, like by leaps and by like times three,
the greatest golfer ever to pick up a club.
Yeah, for sure.
That's just, you know, that's one of the many facets of Joe.
I'd rather spend my time getting the word out
about a fantastic product.
Yeah, Joe is essentially like the same gimmick is used
by alcohol company.
Like Joe is essentially the most interesting man
in the world gimmick.
Sure, yes.
But he's a cartoon camel and he's selling cigarettes.
That's true, he's a precursor to that.
Everything that like cigarette companies
they had to crack down on in advertising,
alcohol companies never stopped doing, they still do.
Who is the most prominent character?
Yeah, well like is it the most interesting man in the world?
That's like the most popular alcohol character?
Well, obviously it's Clooney and Gerber on the bikes now,
but at one point in a less enlightened time.
Well, the Bugweiser Frogs.
Yeah.
Spud's McKenzie.
Of course, yes.
Spud's goes right with Joe.
Spud's and Joe. You know they partied.
Yeah. Yeah.
Spud's doesn't have the,
he isn't as lascivious.
He's like sleazy a little bit, but he doesn't,
he doesn't make me feel all my, the feelings I feel.
What is that kind of dog called?
Oh, let me look, I forget what.
Bad ass.
Spud's McKenzie is a, oh yeah.
Oh, a bull terrier.
It's a bull terrier.
Yeah, I mean he was, there are cartoon,
well, you know what, look at this,
look at this ad with Spud's.
There's sort of a Kim Basinger-esque woman.
Oh, top dog.
I went to the image and not to the Top Gun logo.
Yeah.
So this is a very, fairly like,
she's hitting on this, okay, this is a real life woman
with her arm around a dog in a bomber jacket.
And there's a beer, two beers.
The dog is drinking a beer and she's drinking a beer.
Spud's made all of the other dogs
go into actual flight training.
They vomited at 12 Gs, of course they did.
But you know what, great performances,
can't argue with that.
But you know what, this is obviously,
this is still a little cuter and more innocent
than the Joe Camel stuff.
Even though that's just a pure,
that is an actual woman with her arm.
But he's just a dog, a real dog.
Yeah.
So he's not making like, a goo goo eyes at her or anything.
You're more creeped out by the ability of the art style
to kind of merge man and camel.
Yeah, I am.
Into one sexualized being.
Yes, here's a dog in a Hawaiian,
here's Spud's in a Hawaiian shirt, like pouring a tap.
And it's like, this is weird.
I'm not just, I'm not denying that.
I'm just saying this is not quite as,
doesn't feel as evil.
Well, okay, where things start to get really creepy for me
is, you know, all right, so I'm with him
for the first little bit.
And here is this one, one cool camel character.
But as time goes on, we start expanding Joe's world.
And we start going places with him
where there are other man camels.
And here's one that I'll show you guys.
This is a nightclub scenario
where a bunch of, just a smoking bar,
if they were drinking anything, I don't know,
cause the glasses are empty.
But mainly they got together to smoke and smoke.
So this implies a world where
it is primarily upright camels.
There is a woman working there.
They do allow a human woman to serve them.
But we got little scenarios here.
We got two like arm wrestling ones.
We got one with extra, extra limp face balls,
who is kind of like a forties gangster in a white suit,
whisper in a secret to one who looks like
he's got those like severe glasses,
like Slugworth in Willy Wonka.
They're like, they're from all different eras.
There's like modern construction worker.
It's a real village people scene here.
And then one detail at the top,
this bar is in demand.
Everybody, everybody wants to be,
but hey, one rule, only camels allowed.
And there is a detail at the top
that a cowboy possibly presumably the Marlboro man
is in a, has tried to get into the bar wearing a camel mask
and he is being booted by a camel bouncer.
Camel bouncer dressed like one of the blues brothers.
Yes, yes.
Hold on to that thought.
More to come.
The Marlboro man, of course the Marlboro man
used by Marlboro for decades,
much longer run than Joe Camel.
Yeah, and he's a fucking loser and all that time.
He did nothing noteworthy.
He just dreams of the day that he can poke around.
He's like, if they'll just let me into their world,
their wonderful world for 20 minutes,
I know I'm gonna get caught.
But if I could just experience what it's like
to not be this loser cowboy that I am.
Take your ass back to flavor country, bud.
It's just a name.
We know it's a lie.
All the flavors here in Club Camel.
Club Camel.
So this is where we start getting into
that there are other characters, right?
But mainly it's just, all right,
here's a bunch of like generic extras.
We don't know details about them.
They're not personified in any particular way.
And as the book put it,
things were actually getting a little saving for Joe.
Even camels can cry.
Big pull quote in the book.
Joe was in danger of becoming the world's loneliest camel.
The hard pack changed all that.
Do we come across the hard pack?
Yeah.
Yeah, I believe so.
I always forget that's their name.
That's his friends.
And that's how they existed for a little while.
But after not too long, they became more,
they did what all the best friends
ultimately get together to do, which is start a band.
Joe Camel was in a band.
The hard pack.
And here's, all right, now I don't have these,
you couldn't give me flashcards,
but listeners, you can try it.
You can run your own drills at home.
Here's what I like about, okay.
The hard pack, four unique individuals,
each with his own style, his own instrument,
and his own preferred kind of camel cigarettes.
By the way, hard pack refers to this weird,
that's like a functional term.
A lot of the new campaigns were always about,
okay, how do we push this thing?
And that's like a type of box.
I don't quite understand.
Yeah, it's not a soft, it's like a soft pack
you can kind of smush.
Hard pack is, I think most modern cigarettes.
It's a fixer, yeah, it's like a cardboard,
a thin cardboard box.
Okay, wait, I can't even picture what a non
would just come in a bag?
What's a non hard pack?
No, you've seen it, like in old movies
where a character like gives someone a cigarette,
but they're like squeezing like a really soft, like,
it looks like it comes like pre-crunched.
It's just like a flimsy paper plastic kind of thing.
Oh, okay, okay.
I don't know if I've ever seen one in the wild,
but like in old movies, characters will like hand someone
a cigarette from a soft pack.
Okay, as opposed to the hard packed in
where you gotta like pound it against your hand,
which might be the beat of a song by the hard pack.
Why there's Busta on guitar and hard pack lights,
Eddie on drums and hard pack 99s,
Floyd on sax and hard pack ultralights,
and Max on harmonica and hard pack filters.
Maybe not a great idea to have two instruments
in your band that require dexterous lung abilities.
Ultimately, the shelf life of the hard packs music
is gonna be limited.
Perhaps a piano you might consider.
I'm not sure what Joe himself played,
but he was in there.
I mean, I'm assuming he was harmonica.
Well, but Max, I mean, they probably did double duty.
We know he could play everything.
He's like Prince, he's a virtuoso of every instrument,
but he has to have other people
because he can't play all at once, at least not yet.
There's a, figure out a way.
An image of all of them on a series of packs.
Oh, they all got a custom pack?
So there's Busta and there's Floyd?
This was a giveaway.
This was in a rancor article.
I had some little information about them,
but they also in the list of friends,
they include a Josephine.
I didn't come across a picture of just Josephine.
There was a picture, okay.
They also had their own lighters.
Did you see those?
Of the hard pack?
Yeah, the hard pack had their own.
Like each character was on a lighter.
Oh, cool.
But then I saw Josephine listed as well.
And then I also saw them in the background of,
and I should, I'm not being able to find the photo.
There was a club camel photo with them in the background,
but they look different than their like blues brothers look
that they were in most of the ads.
That's largely how you find them.
It's sunglasses and it's cool hats.
And again, this, think about kid.
I mean, the way that they're marketing to kids
and how much kids love the blues brothers
and smokey clubs and harmonicas
where they are weaponizing our kids' interests.
But there's another mode and you'll like this mode.
Mike, everyone will like it.
It's the tropical hard pack.
They got into that, that buffet,
that coral reefer territory.
You know what?
Actually Joe probably plays piano because there's that.
He is here.
He had a, that actually, now that I'm thinking about it,
he's got a very like a Goldblum at the piano look
in some of these ads.
So I guess maybe it was Canon that he played the piano
before the hard pack came along.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Oh, and Goldblum's a perfect because they, you know,
it's not just about the music.
He's telling stories too.
It's the charm.
It's grabbing the hands and what can I tell
about the hands and ah.
Jeff Goldblum as Joe Camel is a good idea for a movie.
Oh man, like a mocap that you can really tell it's.
It's a Mecus Joe Camel movie starring Jeff Goldblum.
Well, well, I have a band.
I have a band.
You should come see the band.
You must, you simply must see the band.
The hard pack, the hard pack.
Josephine, Josephine.
The longest two handed handshake you've ever seen.
Have you met him ever?
Huh, no.
Have you?
Yeah, funny or die.
Oh, you had to, you had to kick him out of funny or die.
You had to pull a fire alarm
to keep him out of funny or die.
He is exactly, we saw him twice at when Rockwell.
Rockwell, yeah.
Oh, you went to the show.
We were in, we were in line and he just walked it down
the line, talked to everybody and touched everyone.
Everybody did not spend a ton of time on you and me.
Talked to Lindsay and the women around us a lot longer.
Certainly was a little more interested in women.
Why not?
You guys are very interesting.
People pay to hear what you talk about.
Do you have any stories?
Any Cronenberg stories from the set of The Fly,
Mr. Goldberg?
Later, perhaps later.
Ah, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, what are those lines?
What are the lines?
I mean, he was doing, here's what I remember from that.
He was like, there were two ladies next to us,
maybe like a mother and daughter.
I'm trying to remember how he got to this,
but I will get there just by making it up.
He's like, ah, yes, hello, what is your name?
Ah, yes, oh, else and oh, and what's this?
And what's the family lineage?
Oh, yes, oh, your father, what is your father's name?
Ah, Herman, Herman is Herman.
Herman's Herman, it's Mrs. Brown.
You've got a lovely daughter.
And I know he for sure got there by the end of it.
And I was like.
Playing a game, it's a game show.
Yes, yes.
I took, I.
Doing a live Six Degrees of Kevin Bacon.
I took my friend to see him too when he was in town
and we went up to him afterward,
right after Grand Budapest Hotel came out.
And he was, my friend, I don't know,
we were talking with him.
He's like, oh, the movie was great.
That's right, he's in Budapest, right?
Yeah.
And he's like, ah, yes, isn't it wonderful?
It's a wonderful film, isn't it?
Isn't it great?
Oh, isn't it?
It's just so great, great to be in that film or whatever.
But there were no women around, so he did.
Yes, yes, great West, the great West.
So Wesley, Mr. Belvedere, Streets of China,
I never met him before.
But he's.
I've ever.
He is, he's that way all the time.
Is there still, is my video still,
I pulled a video, an early post on YouTube for me.
Oh, it's, oh, here it is, okay.
This is a seven second clip that I put on YouTube
forever ago.
Here's just, it's a little flavor of,
this is Jeff Goldblum doing some scat jazz piano
on the Howie Mandel show.
I think we remember the.
I've always been coming up on this show lately.
Thank God, we're only heading into good territory.
All right, Jeff Goldblum scatting.
Oh, I like it.
Now I can.
Have I brought up the Aerosmith Goldblum clip?
I have, right?
You have brought it up, I believe, yes.
On the show.
Yeah, I think like two weeks ago.
You brought it up.
Jurassic Blues.
Yeah.
What is it?
What up?
I forget, but it's like really that.
Oh, we got an ad here.
Jurassic Blues, it's only, there's a 42 second clip
on the YouTube channel, Jurassic Finds.
I mean, we'll play a clip of this.
Jeff is just jamming on the piano next to Steven Tyler.
They're playing Big Ten Inch.
I don't know why it's called.
I think there's a better clip.
I'll edit that in.
What's he's just jamming with him?
He's up, he's up.
He's wearing his like lost world era outfit
with the leather jacket and the white shirt.
Cool.
And Steven is shirtless and they're just,
he's at the front of the, I don't know how this came about,
but he's at the front of the stage with an electric piano
and they're jamming out and.
And that's just what, that's what American bad assery
looks like to cancel it.
There it is.
Tyler Goldblum together.
That's man in man.
Wait a minute.
Why are we playing Jeff Goldblum?
Guys, guys, the hard pack was not just a band in pictures.
The hard pack put their money where their penis mouths are.
And they made an album, the album meet the hard pack.
Do you want to hear a little clip of meet the hard pack?
An album available exclusively via C notes, camel cash.
By the way, you can buy on eBay,
like 300 C notes for five bucks right now.
So I don't think they have any legal.
The conversion rate is getting better.
Yeah, there's no conversion rate.
It's like Confederate money.
Like you can't really do anything with it.
No, it's actually crazy.
No, I get like all the headlines are about crypto crash
and everything, but what you don't realize
the next thing is going to be camel cash.
Camel cash from the 90s.
That's the new, it's like, wait, I knew,
I knew crypto was gonna go away.
It's just, it's, but see, that's the new C.
Just add the customer service desk at a Cole's baking.
Like, please convert my C notes to Cole's cash.
Please help me.
So here's a little taste of meet the hard pack.
I got the empty lava blue.
I have no butane.
Every time I hear blues, I have no butane.
Well, it hit an ad and that might be for the best.
I believe me when I say that doesn't go anywhere.
This is just in case, like I was very excited to discover
there was this album.
However, in case you were thinking
there was a spiritual error to the McGruff album.
It isn't, that's the most interesting song by far.
There's a couple of tracks that somebody's pulled
on SoundCloud, which is a flagrant violation of the seed,
the camel cash system.
That's the only way that you were able to access
this incredible music.
Joe Camel and Metallica teamed up in the early 2000s
to try to get rid of streaming.
Shared interest here, man.
Broken lighter blues.
Gonna get myself some striking matches
before this lighter drives me insane.
One of the interesting things though,
is that that might be Joe's voice.
That might be the only time.
That was my question.
Yeah, it doesn't say.
Although do we know, were there like liner notes
on the actual album maybe that would say specifically
who sung what?
I don't believe so.
I did check discogs.com.
I think nobody has archived this.
I think you're in a different world
when you're mainly exchanging camel bucks for camel albums.
So I would have loved to have known.
Although, still from this book is let me know
that Max's last name, the harmonica player,
his name is Max Match Books.
That's good.
I'm not sure if they all got last names.
Yeah, it's possible.
It's possible they did.
Did we all come across the kind of exhausting
ad busters riff?
Does everyone remember ad busters?
Sort of.
They were magazines,
there was a magazine and they were kind of,
you know, Photoshop ads, you know,
cause advertising was just so,
like it seems charming in the 90s.
Like what they considered like,
this is so insidious, advertising is so insidious.
They kind of went with the low hanging fruit
with Joe Kimo for this.
It's pretty lazy.
Meanwhile, in 2022, this just came out a few hours ago,
a vice article that says leaked video show Disney
is the biggest ad tech giant you've never heard of
with a bunch of internal Disney videos
featuring Baymax and Bunsen Honeydew
telling you about what a great product
their ad vying network is.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Internal videos starring Bay and Bunsen.
Starring Edna Mode.
Edna, what?
Edna Mode?
Yeah, Edna Mode, yeah.
Mode, okay.
Yeah, here she is talking about planning,
activation, reach and frequency management.
I'm still gonna say that cigarette ads are worse.
Cigarette ads are pretty bad,
but these are like weirdly more invasive
in your daily life.
Like the way ads just play on the internet
or before videos and stuff.
I guess we found the answer of what Disney will do
with the Muppets.
Yeah.
Internal corporate ad by,
hey, he ran for president.
He, with the camel party,
the party that knows how to party.
Hey, I'd vote for him at this point.
Let's take his win.
Let's get a smoker in the White House.
Although I guess Obama was a smoker secretly, so.
It wasn't long ago.
And that was a thing like,
oh, will he be able to win?
He smokes a cigarette once in the blue moon.
Right, right.
You know?
Everything has really changed in a few years.
Yeah.
Really fast.
What the public will, yeah.
Look, look.
But the thing, you know, we know this other guy.
It's part of his brand that he casually commits
five crimes a day without realizing it.
Obama knows better than to smoke
and wear a kind of suit we don't like for some reason.
That's right, yeah.
Your C notes will go to good use
as we take our message to the people.
It's gonna be a tough race,
but I'm sure with a little luck,
the best party will win.
Joe.
And then his signature, which also appears in the book,
the J is smoking.
It's like a ball jowl within the J.
It's just, you can't, it's so funny.
Like so much, it's just so funny.
That's what I'm saying.
The more I'm reading it, like, hey, I love everything.
I can tell why this guy's so in love with his own work.
And then we get to a chapter.
First of all, okay, let me go back
to something I read earlier.
Joe was in danger of becoming the world's loneliest camel.
The heart pack changed all that.
The loneliness, as with any, if you're a good man,
your loneliness is cured by getting a blues band together,
not by having a life partner.
That wasn't the good, no, no, no,
that's not gonna, how loneliness, who cares?
I got my gold bond, I'm sick.
You got your blues brand.
You play your songs about like how Prilo Sec
helps your heart burn.
You do try that Prilo Sec.
Lipitor, da da da.
But he, you know, there was maybe desire
for a little bit more in his life.
And that's why we get, then we get to this chapter,
an idea whose time hadn't come.
Big capital letters coming.
And this is the chapter that addresses
why is there not a female Joe camel.
Okay, so Josephine was brought up.
I did not come across Josephine.
I don't think Josephine was even in the book.
Josephine thrown under the bus, not part of history.
What I learned about in the book was a character
by the name of TJ.
Here's TJ.
If anybody has a descriptor you wanna throw in,
I mean it's like, well here's what,
very airbrushy drawing.
And if I covered up the head, you'd go, oh hello.
90s cocktail, like kind of like Sharon Stone dress
with a pool cue.
Wow, and then you keep, then I remove my hands
to reveal the big eyed camel face.
This is, what do we think of TJ?
TJ is, I'm trying to think, she looks almost like
a planet of the apes ape.
Oh yeah, like Helena Bonham Carter.
Yeah.
She's got, her arms are very long.
Yeah, extremely.
Normally long, which I guess is cause of the camel,
half being a half camel.
She's got kind of, yeah, yeah.
Or just like statuesque, like a Kate Upton or something.
Just like a tall woman, certainly.
But like she almost looks like she has
like Navi length arms.
She looks maybe like a Navi in the size.
Oh, and by the way, if you couldn't tell from the ads,
cause I'm only with other camels, I'm 14 feet tall.
Yeah.
We all are.
She's doing the thing with the pool cue.
Mm-hmm.
At the top.
Oh, she's chalking, you know Joe likes that.
Yeah, yeah, and she's giving like sort of a little bit
of a flirty look at the camera.
Mm-hmm, big earrings.
TJ, does TJ stand for something?
I don't know.
I mean, that I couldn't figure out.
Yeah, I don't know.
The joy of smoking.
TJ, the chapter about TJ is just like,
hey, look, we tried and it didn't work out.
They tried one ad with TJ.
There was, you know, we know Joe likes motorcycles, right?
So they had her riding behind him, arms around him.
And a lot of the copy, a lot of what they were saying is,
there was a bunch of like pseudo feminist,
but not really jargon about like, and she's no fool.
And she doesn't take no crap from anybody.
So when she was behind him on the motorcycle,
that's not the character.
That's not the 90s woman that we're painting with TJ.
So they switched it and they put her in front
of the motorcycle with Joe behind.
And everybody at Camel was like, no, it's worse.
That's weirder.
Kill the campaign.
It's not happening.
So this one image, nevermind, no women.
So that's a stupid idea to begin with.
Can I see?
So then the next week, Joe was wearing a shirt
that says, if you can read this, TJ fell off.
TJ in this photo looks as a different vibe though.
She's getting out.
Yeah, kind of messy hair.
Yeah, yeah.
Kind of like Olivia Newton, John at the end of Grease
when they drive off to heaven.
Oh yeah, man, stud.
Yeah, so yeah, they never figured this out.
No, why weren't they just riding bikes
next to each other then?
Yeah, I guess that would be the equal.
Wait, yeah, I don't know.
Seems like an easy fix.
Well, and as we know, Pete's two greats riding motorcycles
next to each other is the most compelling advertising
campaign there could ever be for an adult substance.
That's right.
So they should, yeah, they really screwed up.
I feel like they were, I feel like they sabotaged TJ,
poor TJ.
Yeah, yeah, she got an unfair,
I think maybe there'd be some,
I think now if they came back,
especially to like a future,
whatever future great administration we're gonna have
and said, hey, we know we made that rule way back when,
but like, come on, we didn't, what about TJ?
TJ never got her chance.
You wanna stay in the graces of female voters?
That's right.
TJ, and then we roll back,
the cartoons can't be in cigarette ads and things.
Well, and then when TJ comes in,
then finally Joe Camel has a bunch of kids.
That's what we're missing.
The Joe Camel kids.
Camel babies.
What do those look like, the Shrek babies,
the Farkel of Camel World.
The Supreme Court will rule that you are allowed
to market children's camel based characters,
two kids to make them smoke,
to allow them to be interested in smoking.
It is like unusual looking at all this now,
like, yeah, this is all stuff we liked, lots of characters.
Yeah, I think that's why it's a worthy topic to bring up.
Chuck and Cheese tickets.
Yeah, yeah.
That's a big argument, yeah, for the marketing,
because when you look through the merch,
it is great, the amount of merch
and the way you get the merch is fun.
That it's with, yeah, do we even really,
we were talking about their specific money,
but we didn't discuss that it's Disney dollars.
It for sure is their version of Disney dollars
and it's bright, vibrant, colorful money,
much cooler than our regular stupid green money.
And it's Joe as George Washington
and Max, his harmonica player friend as Lincoln.
Yes, in the five.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
And then there's a 50 that just stops looking like money.
Now it's, on the 50 scene note,
it's Joe as George Washington,
but back in a leather jacket
and just tossing money in the air.
Oh.
These are good.
I mean, I would love to have a pack of C notes.
Well, a lot of this stuff is not so expensive.
Yeah.
Because I was on eBay and I think you can get,
here, you can get vintage a lot of 310 camel cash,
C note, C note, Joe camel cigarette, 1990s,
$5, $5 shipping.
And that's a buy it now price.
Wow.
So you could make it rain in C notes
whenever you want for like 10 bucks.
Yeah, you can get like a $10 Zippo lighter
with Joe on it for 10 or $11.
Yeah, camel cash.
You could use his own lighter
to burn up a bunch of camel cash and then just buy more.
Yes, camel cash is cheap right now.
The value can only go up as far as I'm concerned.
That's what I'm saying, it's the next wave.
Yeah, you're right, you're right, yeah.
That's what you pay for the second gate for,
get in on the next financial big thing.
Camel, yes.
Where this TJ thing went is that they said,
all right, never, all right,
it's not gonna be his consistent girlfriend or nothing
because we can't tie him down.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's not his rebellious spirit flag flying free,
ball face flapping in the breeze.
So then it became, all right,
well, he's got his nightclub Joe's place
and that will just be full of women.
Women, female, creepy female camels are now
just all over the Joe-iverse.
And this, I mean, there's too many details
and this is a veritable where's Waldo,
where here's a camel with a broken leg
and another camel is signing the cast.
There's a bunch of like flat top ones
and some are dancing to a band
and one guy is handing a rose up to a female camel
on the second level.
I, just seeing them be like anatomically correct
is really, I think the women are somehow creepier than the.
That's probably right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that makes sense.
So now there are just women in his world, great.
Things just keep getting better.
And now I'm gonna move to one,
it's sort of the final big topic on my end
which is that Joe, all right,
we know he likes pool and billiards,
we know he likes nightclubs,
so what place would he love more than Las Vegas?
Of course, sure.
Hand and glove.
Let me go back into the copy.
There's one place Joe Camel belonged.
There's one city that he should have had all the keys to.
It's without a doubt Las Vegas.
New York may be the city that doesn't sleep
but Vegas is the town that doesn't even nap.
Which I say, talk to Jason Sheridan.
A lot of naps in Vegas.
It's the only way you can keep going,
especially in that summer 100 degree heat,
it'll take it out of you, you gotta stay hydrated,
you gotta have some naps.
That's the only way you can keep going.
Take cocaine or something.
Oh yeah, you could take cocaine.
Joe wouldn't, he would smoke.
Or just crank camels.
Then you're good to go.
So anyways, fully associated with this,
here's a cool image of, he's at the poker table
and he is flicking an ace at you.
A custom ace with a camel on it, flying right at you.
You know that game in Vegas
where you're flicking cards around?
Yeah, the Ricky, what's his name?
The guy in the Mammoth movies who can throw the magician.
Ricky J.
Ricky J, yeah, Ricky.
Yeah, I'm playing a Ricky J's table.
Turn cards into weapons like Ricky J can.
Just Ricky J in it, you know me.
We're thick as thieves, Ricky and me.
All right, the dealer's bleeding, sorry.
Lesser thrower, it would just bounce off his neck
as opposed to mine which sliced it.
How many C notes can I give you to make this right?
So let me get to this.
Okay, we've talked about how Joe and the Joe-iverse
has so much that we like.
It's custom money and a big universe of friends
that expands and expands but there was no cartoon.
There's an album, that's good.
That's good.
There's one thing that we are missing
and especially with the premise of our podcast
that Joe did not have a physical place that you could go.
There was no Joe Camel themed experience
or so you would think.
I take you now to November 22nd to 24th, 1997
to a little event called Camel's Big Vegas Groove Blender.
What?
What you were looking at, okay.
Joe Camel is on a big video wall
and on one TV is Caesar's Palace,
must be the location, hell of a place to party.
And then another thing says ready to party with my recipe
and Joe is just stuck on the monitors 2D.
He's just there and he's got nowhere to go.
No, wrong, false.
He is reaching out of the video wall
and he is pouring a bucket of psychedelic fluid
all over you.
This must be concentrated liquid groove.
I love to have a little nip of absinthe
with my Camel lights.
That's what you could have gotten
at Howl at the Moon though, in a big bucket.
That's true, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No blue Curacao but every other color of Curacao.
This is trippy.
This is gonna be a nonstop over the top weekend
in the party capital of the universe
and everything's on the house.
So what this was was a Willy Wonka style
golden ticket situation where keep buying those Camels,
keep buying those hard packs
because you might just get an invite to the groove blender
and 500 lucky smokers did along with their guests
and this was a private party weekend
that was only for Camel smokers.
Let me get to my info on this.
Okay, so here we go.
This is, look, I'll be honest.
I'm just gonna read a lot of this book about this event.
A futuristic neon powered look into the world of Joe
and the culture of Camel.
If you weren't one of the lucky 500 smokers
and their guests who want a trip to the blender,
it went something like this.
You entered through a circular shaped entrance
swirling with lights and color.
A video column projected your image
between several huge video screens
before swirling it around into a quickly dissipating vortex.
Watch out, Hunter S. Thompson.
This is, if you and Benicio are tripped out
by just the carpet,
you ain't taking a trip into the groove blender.
Buy the ticket, take the ride.
Buy the C-note.
The floor below spun with neon blades.
The fuck, that can't be true
I don't think you would even have to be tripping
to be scared of blades on the ground.
That doesn't just mean a design, shut up.
There were no neon blades.
Then suddenly you were inside.
I mean, probably because there wasn't that much space
to work with.
Yeah, then imagine a door and you're in it.
The main room where you encountered two giant lava lamps.
Holy shit, whoa.
Dance cages and a lot more.
You saw a Swami booth, a pyramid shaped structure
with four live Swamis, weird lighting.
We're giving up on the copywriting now.
Weird lighting and sky beams.
You said what?
You stopped to check out the interactive Swami
and came away enlightened.
This doesn't sound like the Joe Camel voice.
I'm confused here because there's something, yeah,
there's something classic, all-American,
swing and ding ding about this guy.
He's not about, he's not an electric daisy carnival guy.
That's not even, I don't think who they're marketing to
because these cigarettes specifically are like
salt of the earth, denim.
This is a Jay Leno type of guy, American car guy.
Traditionally masculine.
A bunch of Jay Leno viewing.
Yeah.
Love the monologue.
Right, Jay, I assume Jay adds for Camels
in the early days of this night show.
Joe Camel says, I try to turn in early,
but sometimes I watch Leno's monologue and then drift off.
Joe Camel will.
I know he left before the end of the day.
I wish Joe was on in the early days too.
Like a self-fully animated,
where they have to keep the camera still.
Yes.
It says here you're a smooth character, isn't that true?
From there you went onto the virtual reality room
and played some head games.
You even went for the ride of your life
on a Smoke and Joe's racing simulator.
What the fuck?
Are we getting into that there was a Joe Camel ride
that was only available for three days in Las Vegas?
This is huge news.
Sounds like it.
And yet no information fully about it
What I did find was a big crazy press junket style video
about the Groove Blender,
which before I continue the description of the Groove Blender.
The laziest name too.
The Groove Blender?
The Groove Blender.
No, that's okay.
That name's okay.
I don't know.
It doesn't fit the Joe Camel aesthetic.
I view that.
Maybe that's what's rubbing me wrong.
But I think the Groove Blender is groovy.
I think it's cool.
Yeah, baby.
How do we imply that just,
we're gonna take everything that's groovy in this world
and mix it up in one room.
And by that I mean cigarettes,
Swamis, neon blades.
Swamis are religious teachers.
Come on in, explore some new fates.
What month did Austin Powers come out in 1997?
Oh, that wasn't 97, wasn't it?
That was early in the year.
I think that was March or so.
Or it might have been May.
Okay.
Who's warning of Austin Powers influenced Joe Camel?
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, yeah.
There's this new, the swing 60s are back.
But it wasn't a phenomenon yet.
There was a big 60s comeback in the 90s in general.
All the smiley faces and inflatable furniture
and bell bottoms, all that garbage.
That is true.
They tried to get him.
Can we just, Mike, can you just send a video of saying,
of you saying, this blender is very groovy, baby.
They didn't get that, but they got a bunch of
people who clearly from looking at them
are hardcore smokers.
And they got everyone to, well, here's just some thoughts
first of all about like, why the groove blender?
Why now?
I think it's amazing.
I think it's exactly what needed to happen.
See, for Christ sakes, people, the TV's boring.
We want the cigarette burners back now.
Kind of some Dennis Leary style, not just thoughts,
but camera work.
It's all spin in and then kind of like a
grunge bass player with beard braids.
Yeah, I think it's great.
I think it's exactly what needed to happen right now.
You know, with everything.
97's been a tough year, right?
With their cloning the sheeps and what have you.
We gotta, I think, what do we need?
We need a groove blender now more than ever.
And then.
Here are the guys.
The groove blender.
Groove blender.
Pretty fricking groovy.
And then there's a glimpse of a guy unloading
a bunch of boxes.
Like, yeah, we're gonna have 5,000 packs of camels.
We're giving away Z notes.
The groove blender montage of people just saying it
is pretty clear to me that no one had anything
of substance to say.
So they're like, well, let's just get them
to repeat the name.
Like, let's just make that seem like the excitement level
is at an all time high.
Just a handler walking around to like 30 people.
Hi, hi, can, could you say groove blender
into the camera real quick?
When you see the light come on, that means it's on.
Groove blaster.
No, no, let's take that again.
Back to one.
Light your energy though.
Thank you so much again for doing this.
We'll let you into the groove blender in a second,
we swear.
By then you were hungry and thirsty.
So you sashayed over to the oasis and grabbed a cold one
and a bite to eat under a neon palm tree.
You sat on the biggest pillow you've ever seen.
Are you sure?
The biggest pillow in the world is a groove blender.
The biggest pillow, what is this change of scenery for Joe?
I love trying to navigate a plate of sloppy buffalo wings
on the biggest pillow I've ever seen
with my camel long burning for a while.
This is like a Tim Burton, Nelson Wonderland style
like a copy here.
Well, you're exactly right.
Well, because next is you satiated,
you decided to saunter over to the Turkish Bazaar.
And yeah, now we're in sort of like groovy,
who could not go not Joe's vibe.
Wait, what year, was this the year that Joe was?
Wait a minute.
1997, I think it was over.
Is there no Joe at, did they change the vibe
because they couldn't have Joe there?
Was that what we're figuring out?
Their excuse, I mean, their justifications
were always very funny for all these years.
But when they discontinued Joe Camel,
they were like, well, it's just, you know,
the way marketing goes, you just change it up sometimes.
And we just want to change it up a little.
What's the, yeah, wait,
what was the president and congress saying?
No, we haven't been paying attention.
No, we're just, we're already thinking
like probably not gonna do it anymore.
At RJ Reynolds, we're concerned about your health
and quality of life.
So I wonder, yeah, were they like,
we have to get rid of Joe,
so we're gonna make it like sick, the sick, groovy 60s?
No, but he's in the promotional image.
Yeah, well, and it was explained in the book
as if this was like the ultimate trip into Joe's mind.
What?
This might've been one last go for Joe.
Yeah, maybe, there was, yeah, one crazy blowout
and then he's done being alive.
Wow, then they, yeah, at the end of the.
He knew he was gonna croak.
They took him out back.
You have three days to live.
Perhaps you should spend them quietly and reflectively
or I could invite 500 of my closest buddies to Vegas.
And then they can all go out in the desert
and watch as they put me, they bury me alive.
Don't worry, everyone, one thing's for certain,
I've learned nothing.
Keep smoking, folks.
Load more sand into my lungs.
I can still feel something.
Hey, you there, come on, take a shovel.
Everybody get to turn.
500 of you, it'll be done in no time.
Hey, if you hit a body, that was the mafia.
Don't worry about it.
Steve Wynn threatened to kill me and put me on the desert.
Yeah, I've had so ever run afoul
of some interesting characters, as you do.
Joe Kamel was like, well, just leave my body in the dunes
before the implosion and then I'll go to heaven.
Ride that wave of smoke up, up, up to the top.
I just realized we're doing the
Odenkirk impression of Robert Hicks.
It's kind of, yeah, yeah, it's right in there.
Odenkirk, he didn't get it quite as deep, I feel like,
but it's the this and this and this, and here we go.
Which is also great.
And then we end up with, now we got
belly dancers, snake charmers, sword swallowers,
flame swallower, flame breathers, right?
That's the ultimate cigarette, right?
Yeah, right.
Oh, if only, oh boy, if I can get it all done
with just one big stick.
When's Kamel kind of start offering torches?
Oh man.
Then you go play roulette and craps and stuff,
but with scene notes.
So you're one wall away from a real casino,
but then you're playing with fake money,
with a camel and a wig.
And then-
Is there a photo of the camel with a wig?
What's that?
Is there a picture of the camel with a wig?
I mean, just on the scene notes.
Yeah, yeah, you know, that's what they were,
I mean, George Washington,
oh, now one thing I haven't said,
oh, here you go, after you had a chance to kick back
and watch a live camel do some laps around the room.
So here's what we're gonna do,
we're gonna pack a bunch of smokers into a room,
pass out a bunch of cigarettes,
and then, and just crank music,
and then have a camel walking around,
just farting it up.
You know what-
Breathing second hand.
Look, wildlife love two things,
they love cool camel, second hand smoke,
and they love being indoors.
Don't worry, he won't freak out,
kick all the roulette tables down,
chips go flying into your drinks and eyes.
Was there a camel in Siegfried and Roy's show ever?
Not sure.
Was there already a camel easily accessible in Vegas,
is what I'm asking.
They have to bring one in.
I feel like there was a good chance,
like the Sahara or something,
there was just like a camel that was on loan.
There's a couple menageries,
there's two kind of things, I feel like.
I'm sure it was not hard.
There was probably some sad thing
where two camels were in a space
where people could get drunk and bang on the glass.
That's what I'm saying.
It maybe wasn't much of a stretch
to get the camel over there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, very possibly.
They might have had to stretch a little more
to get the bands.
Big head Todd and the Monsters,
the Smithereens and Southern Culture on the Skids,
rocked the palace with their own special brands
of alternative sound.
And then right after that,
it was the kind of party that only Joe could have dreamed up.
Yeah, you know, we know what Joe loves.
Swammies, the Smithereens,
camels who are not walk around upright camels like him,
but regular ones who are forced to breathe a lot of smoke in.
That doesn't sound like the music Joe likes.
No, I don't think so.
No, we heard the music he makes.
He likes public domain blues
that is amended to be about lighter shortages.
Right, he would like a South Side Johnny maybe.
He would like a kind of bluesy.
Something that swings, Daddy-O.
Yeah.
No, this is all completely confusing.
What you were saying about the food
and like barbecue at the Pillows, there's a shot.
I'm gonna do a cut down on this video
because boy, I love this Groove Letter video.
There it does involve.
Okay, first of all, it goes from a shot
of like three people all doing what I can only describe
as like a cigarette threesome.
Like they're all lighting up,
from one center point,
all getting uncomfortably close to each other
for like breathing in one big flame.
And then it cuts straight from that to like a tilty shot
going over like a really pale taco salad.
Just a big open container of sour cream.
Look, Ash is gonna get in there
and maybe the camel spit in it.
That's what everything's getting blended up.
You knew what you were getting into.
It's Groove Blender, baby.
It's Groove Blender.
What a terrible event.
I mean, there's just no way it wasn't.
No, everyone was so hard on the gathering of the Juggalos.
Yeah, that looks like a fucking.
And yet Groove Blender just passed with no comment.
That looks like some decadent
like ancient Roman party or something versus this shitty.
Yeah. Joe camel event.
But live camels in a room with swamis
and all the cigarettes we can find.
And let the record show that Mike said,
it's the worst event he's ever heard of
before I introduce this element.
All I gotta say is that when camel throws a party,
they do it upright.
Did you see it?
Wait, first of all.
The guys have got a VR helmet.
So there's 94 or 97 era VR.
But that music you were hearing was coming courtesy
of some blues brothers impersonators.
All that plus fake blues brothers.
Oh my God.
What?
The worst party I've ever heard of.
This come RJ Reynolds.
They are preying on our children
and putting everything they like in front of them.
Sword swallowers.
The blues brothers.
Cocktail lounges.
Taco salad.
Open containers of sour cream.
Getting dusted with ash and camel spit.
What hope does my six year old have?
The six year old though was, to be fair,
wasn't going to the party.
I don't think he knew about the party in Vegas
for 500 of the closest, closest smokers.
I'm just saying if this is the Joe vibe,
I've somehow failed to see how this is hooking
someone who's otherwise watching the Teletubbies.
If you're saying that they didn't always do a good job
of marketing to children, I would agree with you.
Yeah, it might be right.
I would agree with that.
Once in a while they weren't hitting the spot
as far as making kids go,
mommy, I want to go to Vegas and eat barbecue on a pillow
and I want to see fake Elwood.
Mommy, mommy, can we go see fake Elwood?
I want a lunch pool trick shot.
I forgot that.
There was a speaking of Odenkirk
and there was a Van Hammersley walking around.
That's all right.
It was one.
Oh.
This party, holy shit.
This isn't one, but I was imagining like,
then further satiated, then step into the next room
and watch a live camel birth.
What?
Joe's offspring is coming right at you
and you can catch it and you can keep the camel
in your hands while you do it.
They won't mind, he's a born smoker.
Maybe try to wash some of the camel fluid off your hands
before you dig back into that taco salad.
But if you don't, we ain't watching.
Would the listeners come to a live show
that was our own version of this party?
Groove Blender.
Podcasts that ride's Groove Blender.
A tribute to the classic Joe camel party in 1997.
We found.
I think the answer is yes.
We got catering for the place called
the worst restaurant in Los Angeles.
In the last live show, I said we need to come out
as the Blues Brothers one of these days.
Oh yeah.
Free Blues Brothers.
And we haven't even talked about Blues Brothers Con.
Oh yeah, so you were saying the event,
this is in August at the retired prison.
August 19th in Joliet, two day event.
Only one day does Jim Belushi and Dan Aykroyd appear.
The best day of your goddamn lives.
They will perform.
I hear the train a-comin', comin' round the bend.
They don't do that.
They don't do that, so I know it's a pressure.
It's just the association with a prison performance.
The prison music.
But then also on the Blues Brothers website,
they are auditioning for Elwood and Jakes.
Huh?
You didn't see that?
I sent that to, I said Jason, you and I have to audition.
Oh, that was a real, oh that was based on
that there were auditions.
There are auditions to be new Blues Brothers.
For what and where?
For if there's ever a Groove Blender again.
It doesn't specify, but I think a Groove Blender.
We are lobbying Congress.
Jim is working on making sure
that cannabis farms stay unrestricted.
Meanwhile, we're also trying to roll back
the cartoon cigarette legislation
so that we can have another Groove Blender.
Licensed Blues Brothers can be there.
Jason and I need to put ourselves on tape for this.
To be Jake and Elwood on the road.
As long as you're willing to show our listeners that tape.
Yeah.
Well, what Elwood, of course.
And you do that thing where like,
these guys are just standing there.
They're just standing.
I paid to see dancers and they're only standing
and looking grim.
But then when the song kicks in,
you shuffle all around like no white person has ever done.
They won, yeah, they won dance.
Which is to say just like randomly shaking.
I'm looking, I have the copy here.
I just want to make sure I get it right
in case any listener also wants to.
If you want to do it a little Joe,
or if you want to do it a little Draper,
because I think you're going to read
some beautiful copy here.
Let's see what it comes to me.
I can't remember, what did the Blues Brothers sound like?
Well, they're sort of like clipped
and kind of where you got to do it.
Looking for young talented Blues Brothers performers.
Blues Brothers approved ventures
in association with legends and concerts.
It's searching for a young fresh Blues Brothers tribute act.
We only approve the finest ventures.
To potentially use at several of legends
and concerts locations.
We are looking for.
Well, that's an established brand.
Legends and concerts.
We are looking for a dynamic duo
that can portray Jake and Elwood
during the Saturday Night Live era.
Well, so not like, wait a minute, not the current one?
For some reason not.
Not the one where it's 70 somethings
who need to hold hands to walk down a small set of stairs.
As they did on the fucking SNL anniversary,
they have to let you take my hand.
Like Trump.
Strong familiarity with the Blues Brothers characters
are essential in order to accurately replicate
their voices, moves, dance, skits,
and comedic flair live on stage.
The tribute act must have experienced performing
in front of a live audience.
in front of live audiences
and developing good rapport and timing with them.
Guys, years of podcast the riot, years of Harold team.
That's it.
I think you're set.
Candidates to consider must sing live
and the Elwood character must be able to play the harmonica.
This is your opportunity to help us continue
to celebrate the comedic legacy
of these beloved iconic characters.
Please send all submissions for consideration
to Legends and Concert 4570 West Post Road,
Suite 100 Las Vegas, Nevada, 89118.
Or info at Legends.
There's a phone number here too.
The Blues Brothers is a registered trademark
of Daniel E. Ackroyd and Judith Belushi Pisano.
All rights reserved.
Yikes.
Wow.
Well, guy, I mean, extensive knowledge of the,
I mean, you could point to lots of podcast material
about them too much, most people might say.
To manifest the physicality, just really quick,
both of you just move your arms
and let me see if I think that it's like the Blues Brothers.
Just, okay, go for the, wow, oh my God, it's perfect.
Whatever you just did,
have you been in a dance school for five years?
That looked exactly like the Blues Brothers.
No, you know what?
We just have a big Blues Brothers fan
so we watched a lot of their old stuff and we picked it up.
Yeah, I did one or two coaching sessions
with Judith Belushi Pisano.
Oh my God.
John had an energy, John, he was a maniac.
What can I say?
Wow.
Jason, are you Belushi or am I Belushi in this scenario?
You think I'm Ackroyd?
I might be Ackroyd, but wasn't Belushi shorter?
Belushi was shorter.
Eventually I think you're Ackroyd.
I think, what, now I'm doubting if you can do it.
You were just asking who's who?
It's obvious who's who.
I mean, I guess height wise it's obvious.
Yes, I guess it has to be that way.
I guess height wise it could be the other way around.
I understand why I was asking.
Look, when you're trying to be a tribute act,
you gotta look at it from all angles.
Jason has to bring that Belushi energy
and I was wondering if that's something he can summon.
Yeah, I don't know if that's coming.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's tough.
Although if he gets a little rammy maybe.
Oh yeah.
He could get that Belushi vibe going.
We're gonna have enough gold bond in the pocket.
Sure.
Scott here, I found a picture.
Called the Joe Camel Collection and a woman in it
explains that I think her grandmother moved in
with her family and they had to clean out the house
and there's just dozens and dozens of camel things
they found, Joe and old Joe.
But here's some soft packs of cigarettes.
You can tell they look like they're already crunched up.
Like they already look like shit.
Oh, I see.
Okay, okay.
So I think the innovation of the hard pack
was these cigarettes will stay in good shape.
Mm-hmm.
In your pocket.
But just look at this.
It's just a montage of thing after thing of Joe Camel stuff.
Oh, that's an example, yeah.
Cue ball.
Cue ball, ashtrays.
Plates and forks and of course they're in a clock,
a cool clock, a bout pool and ashtrays and hats and shades.
And this is the lifestyle.
I guess it goes hand in hand if you were a guy in the 90s,
you were a dad in the 90s who had a lot of Playboy stuff.
Mm-hmm.
This is sort of my, I wanna-
Inspirational.
Yeah.
Or any shots, oh yeah, my relatives really into Elvis.
They're really into Betty Boop.
Then they just have walls of this stuff.
Yeah.
I mean, look, I know about having walls of stuff
of a certain character. Sure, yeah, yeah.
Well, and why not Joe?
Maybe it's time to introduce Joe.
And you know, let me, to summarize how the book
brings things to a close,
it's pretty much what Jason was saying.
Like, yeah, and then his days were numbered.
It just, you know, felt like time.
Maybe the world would no longer accepted this rebel
and he had to ride off into the sunset.
Certainly we were not forced to stop doing this.
But you know, then they bring things to a close
with this statement.
Any way you look at him, Joe Camel was one of a kind.
And even though he stayed around for less than a decade,
he made his mark in ways that few advertising characters
ever have or will.
Joe's style, his attitude, his joie de vivre
made his mythological world seem more magical.
And it made our world seem a little bit more magical too.
He will be missed.
The eulogy.
Again, then a 21 gun salute happens after that.
21 puff salute.
Fire.
Pull.
Poof.
But how do we feel?
Do we, are we, do we love him more?
Do we get him more?
Having taken a trip, now that we know about his world
and the heart pack and his music and TJ
and a miraculous weekend called the Groove Blunder.
You know, I, my feelings as a kid was,
I was fascinated with him,
but I was put off a little bit by it.
But though that being said, I was like,
there were certain ads in the magazines
that I knew were adult ads.
So that's part of it, part of it's his penis head.
But when we look in, there's a pretty rich mythology here
when we talk about all of it.
So yeah, if, if.
And if we, look, what we love is we, you know,
we admit to the shortcomings and the evils
of the Disney corporation.
Sure.
But if some magical IP and storytelling comes out
of this bad organization, isn't that what everything
that we're obsessed with?
Yes.
Isn't that the same that's happening here?
I know being opened up to a magical world of Jouadevive.
I didn't realize I was going to be opened up
to a magical world of Jouadevive.
So I am, I have been taken on a journey in that way.
So yes, I mean, Joe himself, I like him a lot.
I do.
I, his mission, you know, Joe wasn't born in,
Joe wasn't born into the world of cigarettes.
Joe just existed.
That's right.
You have to examine Joe himself.
The people that were pulling the strings on Joe,
that's a different story.
But Joe himself was just a cool, confident,
smoking man camel who loved to play pool.
He lived the leisure life.
You know.
And here's the thing, he wasn't like a leisure suit
Larry character who was like really like out there
probably being gross and saying inappropriate things
to women.
Joe was a classy guy.
That's right.
Joe was someone who wasn't like Duke,
the 90s characters who we think of who were Duke Nukem
characters who were, you know, they would be, you know,
put in jail now they would have been me too.
That's not necessarily Joe.
I don't think it's Joe.
I don't get that vibe from Joe.
Just wanted a good time.
Hey, I put a, I tried having a lady camel
on my motorcycle once.
We tried two positions, didn't like it.
I drove off left and right dust,
but I gave her a chance and that's the Joe way.
I think there's also a chance Joe was either, you know,
bisexual, asexual.
Maybe there's like, there's no,
when you're reading all of this,
there could be any number of scenarios for Joe
as far as what his actual sexuality was.
And I'm not going to out him on this podcast.
I don't know, but I think that there's a lot of different
things under the surface there that could make Joe
even more interesting or unique.
So yes, once we go through all of this,
I do have a lot of affection for Joe.
Yeah.
And I'm more comfortable with him now than when we started.
So what's some of these episodes are about is tackling
something that made us feel uneasy as a kid.
We talk about it for a while and where do we land?
Sure. I love where we land.
I think we've gone on a lot of adventures,
the ultimate dick faced easy rider.
Oh man.
Places where you could have the worst Caesar salad,
man has ever imagined.
And just like, we haven't even, I mean, we're wrapping up,
but we haven't even like touched,
like there's a Joe camel plush,
like the merchandise is out of control.
Yeah.
Truly out of control.
And if I learned anything from looking at this book
and leaving through this book,
if we were to buy it all on eBay,
oh, the smells we could smell.
Well, that's the problem.
Cause there's some plush and Jason brought it up
that there's plush you can get,
but the chances of that not smelling like awful smoke,
there's two specifically here.
I don't know, Jason, this is the one you were talking about.
It has like big sunglasses and a leather jacket.
This thing is horrifying looking.
It's real bad.
I found a camel, camel the game.
Yes, I found camel the game as well.
A smooth deal for two to six players, 21 and older.
What do you mean?
What is it?
I think it's just playing.
I think it's just a deck of playing cards.
Oh, okay.
Here's a blues brothers Joe doll.
A blues brothers plush.
Blues brothers plush doll of Joe camel,
which is a hundred, this is expense 120.
And I believe it's got someone's phone number written down
or it's like some sort of a product thing written
in Sharpie on his feet.
Or maybe just maybe a lady eager to get with Joe
right now where he could see it.
Yeah, he writes, yeah, he writes the ladies number down
on his foot on the bottom of his bare feet.
But we'll post some of this stuff, but it's just,
it's overwhelming how much stuff there was
and they all, it probably all smells like dirty smoke.
You know, there's other.
Don't bring us, by the way, don't bring us
like a live show any dirty smoke Joe camel stuff.
Any stinky Joe camel stuff.
If it's newer and it doesn't smell like smoke,
okay, I may be interested, but the same.
And honestly, take that, sell that stuff on,
like those t-shirts probably cost a fortune
at vintage shops in LA.
There's a lot of really cheap groove blender shirts,
which those were peruse.
We were a little interested in that.
A groove blender shirts, like I could maybe go for it.
But you're talking about a massive body of work
and a lot of arts and a lot of great music
packed in by a pop culture icon that really only,
that where it all came and went within nine years.
Remind you of anybody, maybe like the fab four.
The Beatles.
This is our Beatles.
The Beatles of cigarette mascots.
The Beatles of scrotum faces.
The Beatles were their own cigarette mascots though,
if you saw them ever.
I can't find it now, but I did see,
Kool did attempt to make Willie the penguin.
There was like an extreme roided out version of Willie.
Really?
For a short period of time in the 90s.
And they were like, we don't see any resemblance
to Joe cow.
I don't know what you're talking about.
And I don't think it really lasted.
But that looked more like a kids fruit snack mascot.
I'll say this real quick, just about the kids thing.
There are some ads though,
about the advertising to kids like this one,
where this is clearly three smoking camels
offering cigarettes to a child.
Oh yes, because there's no child in the frame,
but they're all pointed down.
It is like a POV, a point of view of like a child.
They're looking up.
Hang on.
Couldn't that be the point of view of somebody
who passed out on the floor at the Groove Funder?
Okay, that's possible.
They just, no, they just socked a guy
and he's like lying on the ground going, oh,
and they're like, here, smoke a camel,
you pathetic piece of shit.
That's possible.
I know you-
Get this into your mouth before you,
we knock you down one more time.
I know you don't want to think bad,
but there are a couple of those where you're like,
that is definitely Jim's camels offering it to a child.
No way, man.
A really little child.
The point of view is so low.
There's only one scenario.
What's lower than a little child?
Somebody who's lying down on the world's biggest pillow.
Who got a little too groovy in the blender.
That is true.
That was what really got them in trouble was like,
you know, smoking gun stuff would be like,
well, you know, we're going after younger markets,
you know, ages 14 to 24.
And it's like, hold on, hold on.
Four years too early.
Even eight to 18 would be legal.
A lot of places, you'd be 21 now to buy cigarettes, I learned.
Could you take the cigarettes?
I mean, would we like Joe Camel without the cigarette?
Could you-
A thousand percent.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me think this through.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
Okay, Camel comes back without the cigarette,
but with all the iconography of the old Joe Camel,
what are they now?
It's just a cool cat.
It's like Bojack Horseman,
but without any of the sad stuff.
It's just Joe Camel.
There's no conflict.
He just goes around doing cool stuff.
Just jumping in Jacuzzis, nailing it at golf,
holes in one all day, and then he leaves.
Yeah.
So he could survive without cigarettes.
I don't, yeah, I think we've proven there's enough to him
to his friends to max and bust a,
that's the cigarettes is where it started,
but it isn't where it ended.
And he is, Jason was pointing out he's flexible.
Here's an ad where he's like kind of dressed
like Tucker Carlson is on that fake show
that he does in like a log cabin
to pretend he's like a man of the people.
Again, Mike, you're watching the worst shit I've ever-
Jason, you know what I'm talking about?
Well, yeah, cause he does this thing
where he goes fly fishing a few times a year
and someone always confronts him at the tackle shop.
No, I'm talking-
No, I know, but he has his own,
he has like his own like-
It looks like he's in Santa's workshop.
He's in Santa's workshop.
And he wears like a fucking flannel shirt
to pretend he's like a man of the people
and not some rich asshole who's lying
to a bunch of old people.
What is he the heir to,
Swanson TV dinners or something?
Yeah, there was a story going around
where his mom didn't-
His mom left him a dollar.
His mom left him a dollar, she hated him.
Yeah.
So, so anybody, I'm saying Joe is kind of dressed like that,
like man of salt of the earth guy here.
So yeah, like you can see even just Joe
going out to the baseball game here with his camel friends
and like there's one camel wearing like funny,
like Dame Edna glasses in the top left there.
The answer is yes.
I think the way to bring a conflict free animated series
about just a guy who kicks ass,
who happens to be a man camel with a scrotum face
is something I would like to make and I'm gonna do it.
I called it, nobody else can do it
and happy to do it, not putting cigarettes in it.
It's about the character and you can pay me in camel bucks.
Is this TJ?
That might be TJ.
She's in like one of the ads,
like kind of toward the right,
but she's not being featured prominently.
They showed, yeah, you're background now.
We're trying to feature Xtreo,
but back to background please.
Never Joe though, Joe's in the forefronts of our minds,
you survive the culture as you always has been
and always will be.
You survive podcast the ride.
Thank you for your subscription to the second gate
and if you wanna dig even deeper,
join us in our exclusive club,
even more exclusive than Joe's Place Club 3,
where you get one more bonus episode every month,
regular episodes ad free
and maybe there's a couple of cool human camels
wandering around.
Sure.
Well, we don't know who's in that listener base.
Some of them might be camel freaks of nature.
I hope they are.
I hope that's most of them.