Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is a little intense.
If you choose the Orange Team more intense podcasting mission, you may encounter turbulent
tangents about rides that are like Wounds, astronaut rap careers, and America's Daddy.
For a less intense experience, Green Team is invited to choose another podcast.
That's right, get the fuck out.
As for you Orange Team, you'll definitely want to hang on.
This is Mission Space on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast where one of the hosts recently tested positive
for Gary Sinise fever.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
I am here.
It's going to be tough.
I don't want to reveal the answer yet, but it does, if it means being excited about the
Lieutenant Dan band, then I don't know.
Think about it.
Think about what we know about us.
You know where some of my research time today was spent on a certain Wikipedia, but let's
see.
Maybe it could be all three hosts who've contracted this.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
I can safely say it's not me.
The only thing I have recently tested positive for is the novel coronavirus.
And there it is.
All right, poor Jason.
It happened.
Yeah, we're back on Zoom.
I just wanted this, but I came back from Vegas a couple hundred dollars up and a couple
of one specific virus heavier, I guess.
One virus up.
So you're up.
Yeah, I'm way up.
My damage was up.
You could have got rid of that at a table.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, only a couple hours the first night.
And now it's just been fatigue.
OK, yes.
Now, yeah, nursing Pedialyte as we started.
Got a big jug of Pedialyte there.
Yeah.
What flavor is it?
Can I ask?
It's strawberry, but I think my favorite this week was blue.
Blue Frost.
Blue.
Oh, wow.
So they have all the different Gatorade type flavors for the Pedialyte.
They do have, yeah.
In Pedialyte Advanced, they kind of up their flavor game a little, which my sense of taste
and smell only working at about 50 percent right now.
So I can't fully vouch for Blue Frost.
Oh my God.
So somebody could get away with leaving a pie on a windowsill.
Yeah.
All the pies are safe.
Everyone has been much more pie-ed lately.
The five mile radius around your home is for once safe unless there are errant bears around.
Yeah.
Well, we're glad you're doing pretty well, all things considered.
I think.
Now, Mike, you had it a while ago and you seemed to...
I think I've had it a little worse than you.
You had a lot of canker sores.
Was that right?
That was like an odd side of that for you.
The listeners will want to hear this detail about the fact that there were...
I on occasion get canker sores.
If you know what a canker sore is like, it can be pretty brutal.
I decided, my body decided to get one on my tongue and in the back of my throat during
this situation.
Great that you say that because I have one on the very front of my tongue right where
it rests on the roof of the mouth and it's terrific.
It's a stress...
My body does that when it's under some sort of duress and it decided to do it during that
time.
I remember we were talking about recording too and I was like, guys, I cannot talk.
I cannot speak right now.
I'm not exaggerating.
It's like pretty crazy.
But yes, I...
Yeah, we lost two weeks because you could not...
Your voice was shot because of sore, not even the voice.
My voice wasn't shot.
No, no, no.
When I tried to talk, the pain that would happen was so strong.
I would like punch a wall.
I was like an angry man in the 20s or something.
People punch walls still this day.
I know that happens.
I'm not saying...
It's a tradition that's carried on even past to the 1920s.
Right.
I don't know.
I was just picturing it.
There was a real specific scene I had in my head when I was talking about this.
But yeah, it was insane.
So it was not that I lost my voice.
It was truly just that it was like having a big cut on your tongue or something.
So when I look like this, I would be like, ah, like a scurril of yelling, trying to talk.
And I really only noticed it when I was like, oh, you know what a healthy thing to eat
during this time that my body would like?
Fruit salad with pineapple.
No, no, no, no.
And no, was not ideal.
Liked a cantaloupe and watermelon, did not care for the citric acid.
Yeah.
It's an interesting situation, this disease.
Everybody has a different twist on it.
And Jason's body decides to do a whole new fun little thing to deal with it.
And yeah, yeah.
So just do not consider throwing a banana into the mix that will blow up the entire.
So we've got Jason got bananas here.
I still live on the edge.
You know, I recently got a drop off from Jane and Garfield.
So three bananas, three bananas.
Does she not listen to the show?
Does she trying to kill you?
I've got a I've got a breakfast burrito base for it to land softly on.
It's the base with Jason.
Jason just cannot eat it first thing.
That's the problem with him.
That's what came up before.
You've you've discussed before that your view of stomachs is that they need like a cushion,
like a lining, like like trampolines that would soften the blow of a stunt man
jumping off of a building.
Well, I saw some infographic this week that was like, if you're going to drink juice
in the morning, don't do it on an empty stomach.
You can upset your stomach.
So it might not be that far off.
That's what they're for.
OK, you've just OK.
You've proven then that your body is like stunt padding.
It's like, yeah, that's true.
What do you mean?
Our main source of modern information, Ikea, like dumbass infographics
that people just share around social media.
You know, when a dog eats something it's not supposed to.
Oftentimes, you're supposed to just give it a bunch of bread to coat its stomach.
So, you know, and bread is like the walls of it's like stunt padding or like
the walls of a hospital or something.
Right. Same thing. Yeah.
So, OK. So Jason, so next time you want to do something bad to yourself,
like a banana, just couch it in a big pile of bread, a nice cushion of bread.
Yeah. A big Sarah Lee, Sarah Lee, way bread
crash pad.
All of these all of these foods are would be like a delicious treat to an
astronaut coming out of hyper sleep, by the way.
They got to eat all that goo and dehydrated stuff.
That's the transition I was about to go into was like all this talk of something
unpleasant is perfect for the ride we're talking about today.
I got one more. I got a segue myself.
Go for it. Go for it.
My segue is that, well, so because of Jason's unfortunate Covid,
we're we're now back on Zoom, which means that we are glued to a screen
with very limited, uncompelling imagery.
Yes. Much like happens on today's ride.
Yeah. We all had one.
We all tied it together.
I felt intermittent pressure on my skull on it all week.
Not to G levels, but, you know.
Something like that.
Yeah, I think this landed.
I think this was meant to be.
I think this pairing of situation and attraction, I think it's
it's very apropos, we're talking about mission space.
It's come up recently because there was the talk of as there often is talk of
what is the worst attraction of all in Disney World, in this case specifically,
because over on the second gate, we talked about a wild mouse
that people are not too fond of called Primeval Whirl.
Although I found in the aftermath of the episode, there were a lot of defenders
and even we became defender.
So Primeval Whirl, I would say, is out of the running of Worst Ride for sure.
Yeah, I bet there's going to be defenders of this, too.
I think so. We've got one on this show.
I found out recently that I didn't even know about.
Well, OK. Yeah, because Mike, you kept offering
that you and Scott could just do this episode on your own.
And I said, Ah, no, probably I should probably rally and do it
because I'm the only one who kind of likes this ride of the three of us.
Or at least I used to.
I've had much more in the last 10 years, have had much more mixed results.
Wrote it in the last fall, wrote in twenty twenty one felt OK.
Wrote it in twenty fourteen.
My entire family was like, Oh, I need a bench.
We just sit on a bench for a while.
What what happened?
It's a it's bad tales throughout for this thing.
I did a little straw poll this morning.
I went to the Universal Studios and I ran into some friends of the show.
Julia Prescott, I saw said she was she got off the ride
and was chased by a cast member because she was she ran off
white as a ghost, like to either go sit down or I don't think she threw up.
But the cast member was so concerned that like, are you OK?
Get back here.
Ma'am, ma'am, get back here.
We need you to go again.
If you do it again, it counteracts the first time.
We'll spin it the other way.
This yeah, this so.
So I think it's I think our opinion is common.
But I'm sure there are defenders of mission space out there.
I think so.
We'll we'll we'll find them as we go.
And if you don't know why this ride is
embattled, I think that the basics of it,
if and if you don't know this attraction, it is a simulated trip
to outer space that involves a centrifuge
that is probably the closest that real astronaut training equipment
or vehicle or whatever you want to call it.
The closest situation has been to like consumers and regular people
getting to do real astronaut training.
So it's a tad intense.
And boy, we'll walk on eggshells about this.
But the ride killed a couple of people really early into the run.
And it was it was intense for everybody.
There were a lot of hospital trips and then killed a couple of people.
And then they had to back way off and do a less intense version.
Those are those are the basics of it.
But we can, you know, we can dive in more fully.
Yeah, it's sending like I I guess I didn't even
I guess I didn't even know until I was looking into it, like this episode.
It is so like, I think, accurate to the experience of blasting into space.
I knew it was like they were going for accuracy and whatever.
But like it is fucking you up really good.
And that's like, obviously, like because you have like people
that train to go into space and need to be prepared for how bad it can fuck you up.
And it's like looking at the diagrams or what?
I forget which YouTube video I was looking where they're showing
what is actually happening.
I'm like, oh, OK, yeah, this is like hard course.
This is like unpreparedly sending every person into a like space camp, just
dashing everyone from young to old to not screening for any health conditions.
Just like, hey, get in the centrifuge.
Good luck. Like it's pretty wild.
And I know, like, obviously, like a lot of theme park rides
jostle you and throw you around.
But this thing is pretty when you really think about it, it's pretty nuts.
I agree. The video that I watched that had
it was even just a simulation of here's what it would look like, because, you know,
there's no vantage point where you get to see the ride
actually spinning and doing its thing.
I don't think I realized that the individual capsules that you're in
on the edges of the centrifuge, that they also spin and rotate
and that you start the attraction on your back.
I don't I don't think I ever knew what was actually happening in the ride.
And I think if more people could see what it was doing, they wouldn't get on it.
It's a little creepy to see from an outside vantage.
You know, with with like rollercoats, with like the incredible Hulk,
you can see it from a mile away.
You can tell you can hear it a mile away.
And, you know, like, oh, that's probably a little intense.
Maybe I shouldn't ride that.
But this is I don't know.
It's an interesting thematic building.
It's it's tells you there's space involved.
But you literally go into like a room the size of a large living room
with these capsules like you don't really know what you're in for.
You don't know that it's like equivalent cheese to some launch coasters.
You know? Yeah.
And it's hard. It's also like this is when you actually do the ride itself.
For me, at least.
And I don't know.
I'm sure everybody has a different experience.
When I actually do the ride itself, I can't I don't even notice
how much is happening to me.
I just know I don't like it.
I just know it's unpleasant.
Oh, this is a good question to open up because, Mike, you've been the most vocal.
And I don't think we said we at the end of this episode about Prineval World,
we were trying to land on everyone declared definitively what you think
is the worst attraction, at least at Disney World, maybe not of all time,
but at Disney World.
Mike, your answer pretty cleanly was Mission Space.
And I guess are you implying that it's less because of what it does to you
and more or equally because you just don't like.
It the the things that are said and the things that you're shown.
This feels like such a wrap up statement to make, but it feels like what the situation
and we haven't quite explained everything, but it feels a combination
because I hadn't done this for 10 years.
It was built in 2003 or open in 2003 and I did it in 2012 zone.
So they had basically we'll talk, I'm sure more about it,
but they had reduced the severity, the intensity by that point
and also had another version of it in the same ride where you could
where it wouldn't jostle you like barely at all, like a little bit.
So I was like, well, I got to do the real version.
The orange is right. Orange is the bad one.
Yeah, and yeah, yeah.
And I did it and I was so like my brain and my chest
felt so messed up after I did the orange one.
And then on top of it, I didn't even think the ride was.
I didn't think it wasn't fun to be in a little claustrophobic box
with a scott put it like underwhelming screens like it wasn't.
Yeah. So it's like, you know what, if they're going to fuck me right up,
at least give me something to look at.
At least let's give let's give me a robot or something.
I was shocked when I did it and realized that that were
you're going to be looking at very little screens with at the time.
It's better now.
There's kind of a Mach 2 of it, but Mach 1.
The graphics were not good.
Let's be honest.
And like so I'm going to we're watching like a video game
simulator, you're watching like a roller coaster ride through essentially
like it's that somebody made in Planet Coaster, except it's simulating
taking you to Mars.
Yeah, I agree.
If it was a more dimensional experience, I think it would be more worth
the potential trauma.
The screen is like an iPad is bigger than the screen.
So I'm like, OK, I'm in a claustrophobic little box.
There's OK, there's buttons to push, which obviously as a kid,
we all like buttons.
We still I think we're all big buttons fans to press them.
I don't think there's any person out there that's not a fan of pressing buttons.
Make yourself known if you're out there.
But I think that's pretty universal.
Yeah, but maybe not.
But so so one of the things I like in Millennium Falcon is even though
not everything does something, there's so many buttons and stuff to push.
So especially if you were a kid, I think as a kid, that would have been nuts.
And the most exciting thing in Millennium Falcon is hitting the button
for hyperspace to go to hyperspace.
But here it's kind of I like the randomized nature of the buttons
in Millennium Falcon.
And here it's sort of you got one button on your left and one button on your right.
And it's a little confusing because in the pre-ride, you've been told,
do not look to your left or your right.
Yeah, so strict.
It's so strict and and I get it.
Like I get what they were going like.
You can admire that they were going for like a completely pure space experience.
No frills.
Yeah, you get a little senise and that's fun.
But it's not like it's not like you got a droid on the on the thing with you.
Sorry, you you did get senise.
Yes, I guess you did get senise.
Senise recently recast.
Yes, I know. Yes, that's so less senise.
I mean, you still get intro video.
So it's not like, yeah, completely pure NASA.
I don't think there are like pre-ride videos at NASA, but maybe there are.
Maybe there's like a video they wheel in on like an old VHS projector
and you like they put the VHS tape in and hit play
and they teach you how to be an astronaut that way.
I'm not sure. But yeah, she's style.
Yeah, Chuck E.
Cheese break room style or cleaning the suit out.
How do you clean out the NASA suit?
Is it the same as cleaning out a Chuck E.
Cheese head? I don't know.
What's the spray? They put like a 401 cleaner.
You have to spray that in the helmet.
I do remember someone I know who used to who did the college program
and was assigned a mission space.
And I believe did have to do a lot of cleanup on this ride
because they eventually added barf.
They added they added barf bags.
I I I'm not 100 percent on the term.
I believe the term that they would use on the walkies was
we have a protein incident.
We have a protein incident.
I've heard protein spill.
Protein spill might be it. Yeah. Yeah.
It's just like generic enough, but unusual and specific enough that like,
hey, this means something.
But if people are walking by and they're hot and they're not paying attention,
they're not going to freak out, you know.
Right. Because I'm sure that happened because like after a while,
people might have been offended when it's like, oh, we got a kid
puking his guts out over here.
We got some lady that's just just hurled.
Some lady hurled on her kid over here.
We got to clean it up.
So they're like, all right, we got to change the language on this.
Got a human fire hydrant and capsule eight.
Yeah. Yeah. Is any.
And I know I don't think this is anywhere close to a Transformers.
I don't think there's like a versus going on here.
Oh, wait. Jason is defender.
I don't know. But I think Jason, just chime in if you're disagreeing
with anything, especially it seems like Mike's maybe a little more extreme.
I didn't like it.
I certainly would not defend it.
But Jason, if you're as close as we have to a defender, what do you think?
See, OK, look, I'm an essay little freak.
I like G-Forces on a launch.
I like a roller coaster launch and I do.
No, not like not not done, not done.
No, no. I also and the opposite of claustrophobic.
I love to be in tight little spaces.
We like a cat.
You're a cat like a cat.
Yeah, like a cat, like in a little cardboard box.
They're like, what is that?
What is that called?
Claustrum? Is it like claustromaniac?
Mania claustromaniac?
You're a claustromaniac.
I'm a claustromaniac.
I think it's comforting.
So like when that thing comes down, I I don't.
I'm sure a lot of people go like, oh, fuck, what is this?
And fair enough, there I can't think of many other rides that do something like that.
Yeah, wait, let's explain what happens here, because
Erin was entirely unfamiliar and asked if she wanted to watch a video of it
right before we recorded.
And you get in your capsule that's going to spin around and simulate space travel.
But not just that, there's like a big panel in front of you.
And it's a small space, right?
It's already a small space.
And then, all right, time to go.
Let's let's seal her up.
And then the big the entire panel in front of all four guests in this capsule
slides right up against your face.
Your face is kind of shoved into a little cubby, a face cubby,
where you stare through and watch a screen.
And she just watching the video was like, nope, no, no, no, no, no.
It's it felt like an MRI or something.
Yeah, like it freaked her out just to look at a video of it.
And I wonder how often if you like you have psyched yourself.
All right. I know it's a scary ride and I know there's been incidents.
And then that's the thing.
It's like I'm raising my hand. I am done.
Yeah, I think I was a little bit shocked by that.
And I'm not a big I am a claustrophobic.
I'm closer to phobic, claustrophobic than claustromaniac.
So I think that's what you're going to do when the mission space capsule folds in on you.
And kids, you got to be healthy.
You got to eat your greens, eat your pasta and your tight little enclosed
space spaces.
You got to keep your protein inside your body, brother.
You don't want employees having to spend to clean that up.
Put your hand around your own neck to restrict your breathing,
to get an extra thrill when the mission space capsule closes.
That's no, that's not that's not Kari.
So these little you nasty little freaks.
That's great.
Can you hear that's great?
Can you hear is in the move?
It's sorry.
The it's not great.
I'm an autofocus.
Yeah, I was talking to you.
Great. Can you hear an autofocus?
Yeah, I thought I thought he was making an autofocus joke.
Is it does it wait is Hulk into that?
Is that what that's referring to?
No, Jason said he was a nasty little freak and I just like, oh,
oh, that was off of the national.
I didn't know if that was some Hulk Hogan mythology that he's like.
No, I made a little bit of a leap.
Sorry, I went A to D and not A to C, as they call it in improv.
You did the more difficult mission, the mission orange.
Yes, that's true.
Rips. Yeah.
What were we saying?
Cluster mania. You're not a cluster maniac.
And so the folding in.
Yeah, yeah, you like it.
Could you let me ask you this?
Could you would you love a more enclosed space than even that?
Um, no, I mean, I think that's good because I don't I I, you know,
there's there is a little unnerving of like, I don't have control.
This ride is like just under four minutes long, so I do have to deal
if I start to not like it, you know, would you write?
Yeah. Would your ideal ride vehicle be that like
goo sack in the matrix that Neo comes out of? Oh,
I mean, I guess if I could breathe or anything,
too positive of a sound for the most terrifying thing ever.
You have the thing in your throat to breathe that.
Yeah, OK.
That I don't know about the tube and I need to like test the goo beforehand.
You know, it's like getting into a pool.
You got to dip your little toesies, you know.
What Jason's saying is that he wants a nice, warm, non terrifying space
to curl up in or maybe the goo is nice
and all of the breathing and maybe eating is done for him.
What he's referring to is a womb.
A womb. Jason's ideal ride vehicle is a womb.
I almost said womb earlier. Yeah.
You'll take that with this, right?
Do you consider this ride vehicle like a metallic womb?
I, you know, well, daddy, I mean, daddy, astronaut, Gary Sinise.
But then now there's a mommy astronaut.
So I don't know.
I suppose it's a little womb like, but it's a little uncomfortable.
I'm assuming you don't feel much discomfort in the womb.
If everything's, you know, going well.
So womb like, but maybe not directly womb.
The conditions of a womb is not what you're looking for.
But womb like is your ideal ride vehicle.
You know, I would say, you know, upkeep everyone,
even the big boys, Universal Disney, even they struggle with upkeep.
So I'd be real concerned with how quickly that goo goes downhill.
I mean, there's already Guardians of the Galaxy.
Already people getting dizzy off of that.
And there's like a one story stairwell that you have to go down to exit.
Oh, wow. I didn't know that.
What? Yes. Someone just ate shit going down those stairs,
like landed on their like an older woman, like landed on her face.
Yeah. Other than this, are there any other womb like ride
vehicles on Disney or Universal property?
Well, I find the doom buggy very comforting.
Like that surrounds you on both sides. That's true. Yeah.
Tucks you in it. It folds up a little. It does.
Oh, we haven't even talked about that.
It's like a womb.
The Haunted Mansion tucks you in.
That might have been comforting as a child because I didn't like scary stuff.
But I love I love the Haunted Mansion, which got past the scary elevator.
You know, right.
You know, it's a womb like sequence is the because Doom Buggies, I hear you.
But then it's still there's you're going to do scary stuff.
But when you the one part where you're reclining
in the Little Mermaid ride and the projection of the bubbles is washing over.
Like you're you're supposed to be descending and the music is soft
and there's just Ariel's nice voice.
That's kind of a womb like sequence because you're on your back.
Yeah. I mean, I guess, yeah, you're descending like when you're going
into the graveyard on a mansion, you're also on your back.
But it's not as pleasant as it's a little. Yeah, it's not as pleasant. Yeah.
So, yeah, that's true.
The day today, the three boys discuss which ride is the most womb like.
Well, this look, I anytime we talk about a new category or a topic like this
after five years, I get excited.
I go, we haven't discussed this before.
Well, do you have a do you have an answer besides OmniMovie?
I think it's a really good call on Jason's part.
But anything else that's woomy out there?
It's a good question.
There's probably like a six flags thing.
The ride vehicles for Transformers and Spider-Man,
you know, when that comes down, you're you're pretty enclosed on that one.
But it's a little bit less, less intimate.
It's like if you're in the womb with octuplets. Yeah. Yeah.
It would be nice if there were a sleeper chairs on Soren,
you know, like little oh, yeah, or like benches.
Oh, like a long flight, like if you if you pay for a nice like a chaise,
like a is there a chaise lounge chair on Soren?
You can kind of lean back and really that would be awesome.
That's the only way to improve it.
Yeah. Already, you know, more relaxing rides.
That sounds nice.
If Galaxy's Edge had an attraction that was like the beast
that Luke burrows into, what is that?
The tauntaun. That's a tauntaun.
Yeah. If they had a enclosed yourself in a warm tauntaun experience,
that would be pretty close.
They make a sleeping bag of a tauntaun that you can really. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You thought they smelled bad on the outside.
I think I have we talked about that on the show?
I don't know. Maybe we had a tauntaun sleeping bag.
Yeah, here it is.
There's a child dressed in full Hoth outfit, too, which is really funny.
Well, this is the I mean, Galaxy's Edge move over
because this is the most immersive Star Wars experience you could find.
You're literally swallowed by Star Wars.
Oh, and he's cute, too.
The tauntaun is smiling.
Yeah, it's happy that it's been killed and is used for warmth.
This tauntaun died peacefully in his sleep.
OK, that's a good. Yeah.
You need to know that to feel good about it.
Lived a long and prosperous life. Right.
It was his time. Exactly.
Let me talk in terms of like ride
mechanic stuff and stuff that might be a deterrent to liking this attraction.
We have discussed G's a little bit thus far.
Something we don't talk about a lot.
I don't think we've had a lot of breakdown of G's because we aren't very technical
and we're not a coaster podcast.
And even now, there's not a lot I can say about G's.
But just the literal fact on this thing,
the attraction exposes riders to forces up to two point five G's
more than twice the force of gravity at the Earth's surface,
which feels like it is multiplying your weight by two point five.
That sounds intense, right?
But you hear that number and it's like two point five doesn't sound like a lot.
So I went digging a little more because this is not the most G's
that you can get at Disney World even.
Rock and roller coaster is five at the launch and the inversion.
So that's heavier in a G's sense, even in credit coaster
and probably anything with a loop in it, you're getting something like four.
But the big difference is those are over in a couple seconds.
In this thing, you're doing two point five G's for around 15 seconds.
So that's pretty sustained.
That is a long time to maintain being two point five times your body weight.
Right. And it's also like, I wonder if I could have handled it better
if Aerosmith was blasting on the ride on Mission Space.
Yeah, look, I you know, while you while your Aerosmith
affection is perhaps more than two point five times mine,
I do agree with you that Aerosmith music is something.
It's definitely something.
Yeah. As opposed to this ride, which is largely people yelling at you.
Right. Yes. You guys want to ride through it.
It is just like, no, don't. No.
Pull back. Yeah.
Stop. Wait. OK. Now. Right.
Is that why they there is the new mission captain?
And because she's a little more pleasant in her yelling at you,
he's a little less intense than Lieutenant Dan telling you what to do.
And a guy who can barely smile, his energy is just so
grumpy and then he's yelling at you.
No, not that button. The other. Yeah.
I mean, if he did it and and like, stop, tell me what's that sound.
Everybody like if that was playing too, it would be a little more like,
oh, well, I know what this is.
You mean if we did Lieutenant Dan, Dan band cover songs while you were playing,
you're trying to like calm you down.
Oh, you've got to step further.
I just meant if you play the album track, the regular Forrest Gump's
Vietnam music, now we're in a Vietnam.
Yeah, Vietnam music.
And then you're like, oh, it's Lieutenant Dan.
He's yelling at. OK. Right.
It's almost strange that it's like the one thing Forrest Gump
didn't do was go to space.
He accomplished anything else.
He did everything that a human could dream of doing in the 60s
and 70s and 80s, except for go to space.
I have not read the book.
He does he go to space in the book?
I don't know. There's a sequel book, too.
Oh, the sequel. Yeah, I would I would love to.
I should. Why have I never read the sequel, the sequel where he meets Tom Hanks?
Let me see Forrest Gump in space.
It seems like it could have been in number two screen rant.
Forrest Gump puts you with this means Forrest Gump.
He flies into space with a male orangutan called Sue.
Really? In the in the in the book that the movie is based on
or in the weird sequel, the events of the film can compare to Forrest's
wildlife in the book it's based on written by Winston Groom.
The novel version of Forrest Gump also sees Forrest become a pro wrestler,
a chess champion, a Hollywood stuntman, and in his craziest adventure,
recruited by NASA to fly into space with a male ape called Sue.
What? So there you go.
I can't believe I produced that thought.
And then it does exist in the longer.
Wow. In the true uncut Forrest Gump.
As it stands, it's one of the only Tom Hanks movies that does not involve space.
But yes, yeah, it had been allowed to fully breathe.
It would have to. That's insane.
Wow. I got to learn more about the adventures of Forrest Gump that we don't see.
That's really crazy.
I have one more thing to say about G's.
And I think it will.
OK, what are the most G's you can get on a ride today?
And there's really a ride in Johannesburg, South Africa
that's called the Tower of Terror that just stole the name.
And on that, it's kind of a drop right.
I don't even understand where the G's are coming from.
But you're getting six point three on this thing.
So six point three is the most G's you can get on a ride in current day.
But that is not it for all time, because that stat was doubled.
You could get 12 G's on a ride called Flip Flap Railway.
What?
What are the finest names for a ride I've ever heard?
Wow. From that name, can you surmise that this is a ride that existed in the late 1800s?
Wow. This was 1895 to 1902
in a specific Coney Island zone called Sea Lion Park.
And the very dry G based website where I read about Flip Flap Railway
said that the ride sometimes broke riders necks.
Oh, my. For 100 years.
No, no, no, I'm sorry.
It went from 1895 to 1902.
So it was only it only broke.
It only broke necks for seven years.
It was a zoo. I misheard. Yeah. OK.
Seven years of broken necks.
Seven years, seven sweet years of broken necks.
Before the man came and said,
maybe people should still have used their necks after a roller coaster.
That's so many G's.
That's a lot of double what's available anywhere on Earth now.
Wow. What I wonder, like what like coming through space travel.
Did you did it say on there what the G's were like coming down, reentering, reentry?
That I don't know. No, I'm going.
There's I could consult a research document
that was recently released to the public called Top Gun Maverick.
That breaks down G forces and levels pretty strongly.
Flip Flap Railway would have like that would have wiped Miles Teller out.
Until Maverick pushed him to his limit.
Oh, imagine imagine the theme park theme park,
reporters and bloggers and bloggers, you know,
podcasters of the time.
It's like, hey, hey, good time, boys.
I've got another bone to pick.
The Flip Flap Railway was down again when I went to Cody Island.
And the other half of Cody Island was on fire, as it always is.
I went on Flip Flap Railway and it didn't even break my neck as promised.
I feel I did not get the full experience.
There's like a guy who's like, I have the toughest neck in America,
and I'm going to challenge the ride to break it immediately.
Immediately breaks it.
I've been defeated.
That's that's how Houdini died.
He was like, you can just punch me in the neck.
It won't go. And then 12 hours later, he's gone.
That's right.
And a completely barely fact checked.
I'm seeing like 11 G's if some if somebody's like reentering the atmosphere.
What the fuck? 11.
I don't know. You could get 12 on a like fucking held together
with twine attraction in 1895.
I'm confused. Obviously, like we don't know what we're talking about.
But like apparently that's if like you're going like completely out of control.
Reentry.
What are you?
So these ride the right the makers of Flip Flap Railway
exceeded NASA's capabilities.
They beat NASA.
And the ride, by the way, if you look at a picture of it,
it's just a loop and another loop.
It looks so I mean, but like way more severe, like,
you know how in credit coasters kind of like a perfect circle, it feels like.
This is such a like squished, severe, like, you know, from the shape.
This is bad news.
We're designed by Augusta Schlitterbond the first, you know.
Were G's different back then?
Was it like inflation where G's have gotten like less like
it's a reverse inflation with G's like
did 12 G's mean different things 100 years ago?
Oh, maybe. Or are they?
They sent like huge barrel chested divers on it.
Remember when we were looking at the shirtless photo of the guy
who voiced Fred Flintstone?
Yeah, that massive where you can have like, you know, a hundred pounds up in your pecs.
Maybe that was who was riding it.
So that tilted the scales somehow. Right.
The the other fact about this ride is that the Flip Flap Railway
was tested with sandbags and monkeys before human riders were allowed.
What the shit? Why?
What do you mean monkeys?
Where are you getting them from?
How are you?
How do you have enough access to enough monkeys to make go on a ride?
And how do you strap them into the same?
Like the bar can't lower on the same level between a human and this.
I, you know, maybe maybe we've reached the end of the history
or it's just beginning and there has to be the full Flip Flap Railway episode.
We have to do it. Yeah.
We have to figure out.
We'll learn more about Sea Lion Park either way. Right.
So anyways, the history of G's led me to a wonderful
town, a wonderful, wonderful railway full of flips and flaps.
Wow. 12. That seems great.
That seems wrong.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe that was like eighteen hundreds braggadocia.
I don't know.
And just one more thing before we move on,
because in thinking about coasters being tested by sandbags, Jason,
in last week's episode, you were talking about
one of the coasters in your park that made you being tested.
And listeners have let us know that you said the phrase crash test dumpies.
And we did not stop to acknowledge.
I do remember. I do remember it, I think.
Just and I think I kind of remember, too, and I remember thinking,
well, you're he's barreling to something I don't want to stop.
But you are a real role.
And sometimes I'm like, don't be an asshole.
We know what he meant. That's fine.
I three days later, I had tested negative for Covid that day,
but was starting to feel pretty bad around then.
So I was a little I was drinking like, you know, a bunch of cold water
like so, like the next day I was a little woozy.
So you believe the fact that you covid on the fact that you said crash test
dummies? And no, I was just excited to talk about my hometown park
to talk about Playland.
I should I, of course, have had to move my trip eight days.
You call juggernaut.
You called juggernaut the junker not the other day, too.
And I called you out on that. That's fine. Yeah.
I don't know. Sometimes I just get too excited.
Yeah. No, look, this isn't fair.
We shouldn't pile on and make Jason feel like a dumpy.
I already feel like a dumpy. It's fine.
Does that does that sum up your covid experience?
It has the whole as the entire experience made you feel like a dumpy.
I feel I feel a little bit like an asshole whenever I talk to everyone
and anyone, because I'm just like, I'm so tired and I feel so lame.
But I've been saying it for days, but it is true.
Like this is the most the long prolonged sickness I've had in quite a while.
So Jason, from my experience, you've been saying I'm so tired for years.
Well, it's a different kind of tired.
It's got to assure you.
I I knew something was off because one day I heard a song and I
like the second day, like the first full day, I was like here.
And I was like dazed.
And I I heard a song and like, I think it was, you know,
a Spotify came up automatically or something.
And I was like, wow, this is a beautiful song.
I knew this at one point in my life, but I haven't heard this song in years.
And then I looked up what it was.
I realized, oh, wait a minute, it's just a fucking song from Drive.
This is the main song for the movie Drive.
Something I need to lie down.
I'm getting emotional from the drive song.
A side effect of covid is to get emotional.
It's movies.
So when I feel bad, I feel I feel physically bad for long enough.
I feel vulnerable and then I get emotional and, you know,
can I can I ask a question real quick?
Yeah, really a little bit.
But when you're sick, because this is a big thing between Lindsey and I,
sometimes where when I'm sick, I want to curl up in a corner of a room
and I don't want to see anyone for like days.
And some people are the opposite.
Some people want to be taken care of.
I was just wondering what your you want to go off like into the wood,
like a bear in the woods.
You want to die there?
I want to go off in the woods, not die.
But I do want to like go into like an old hollowed out tree stump
and just like lie there for three days and then reenter society.
Bear society. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be again.
I'm 100 percent the same way.
Is Lindsey the opposite?
Does she like to be taking care of baby a little and change the same way, too?
It is a men women divide.
I've talked about this classic gender roles. Classic.
No. Hey, let me refer you to a film called Phantom Thread.
That's true.
The most machis were the angriest man who just wanted to be a little boy
his scones and his bacon.
I Reynolds just need to be brought back down to earth as we all do sometimes.
Scott, if I could say you're talking about history,
um, can I talk about the Disney company in 2003
and that the environment this ride opened in?
Oh, yeah. Bad stuff ahead.
What's happening?
I got that Disney war book out of the library because Mission Space comes up in it
because everyone was mad at each other in 2003.
Roy, Disney, Eisner, the board.
Everyone's just pissed at each other.
Oh, yeah. I was out what?
Like two, three years later.
That's right. And so I swore I could not find it.
I might have misremembered. It might have been a different event.
I swore they, you know,
did a truce for the opening of Mission Space.
They all put it aside to go to this ride opening.
And I could not find that in the book.
What I did find was that
at the end of the year, 2003 report,
Eisner celebrated Disney's big successes in 2003,
the Pirates of the Caribbean film and the new attraction, Mission Space.
Also in 2003, Roy, Disney was resigning from both Disney Animation
and the board of directors.
And I believe the shareholders did a vote of no confidence in Michael Eisner.
God. Oh, another funny detail.
This ride initially sponsored by Compaq computers.
Compaq soon after bought by HP,
which led to Carly Fiorina attending the opening.
If you don't know Carly Fiorina, she's one of those fucking business losers
like Meg Whitman or Howard Schultz,
who are the heads of companies.
And then they try to run for office and they never win.
And they just eat shit so hard.
So she was there.
Yes. Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mike embattled vote of no confidence, CEO
Michael Eisner and Carly Fiorina,
who has been booed at many Hewlett Packard events lately.
She I saw today
a list of the worst mergers of all time and coming in at number one.
What is the Hewlett Packard compact merger?
She was forced out of the company a few years later.
And then as you were saying, Jason, she ran for president
in the awful dogpile hell year 2016 that led to probably 2015.
But you know what led to to Trump
had Ted Cruz gotten the nomination, she would have been the VP.
No, come on.
She a person willing to align with Ted Cruz for any reason.
She major anti-abortion activist
and has said a lot of bad stuff about planned parenthood.
And this is a quote that I'm going to just try to read unaffected.
And there will be a reveal within this quote,
which television personality is talking to Carly Fiorina about planned parenthood.
So let me just dive in.
It'll be a fun reveal midway through.
This happened on television.
Carly, I need to stop you.
I need to stop you because you know that's not true.
Carly, you know, no one is harvesting baby parts.
No one is harvesting baby parts.
Carly, come on, girl.
Whoopi Goldberg interjected.
Oh, wow. They weren't harvesting baby parts, baby.
Wow. This was an exchange, presumably on the view.
On the view. So in the Disney family.
That's true. Yeah, she's still in the Disney family.
When Carly and Disney team up, great stuff happens.
Oh, my gosh.
Also, the the estimate from that HP merger.
I mean, this was just a quick look on her Wikipedia
was 30,000 layoffs and
I don't know, there's it could be 150,000.
It's so many that you would have you would have had.
I don't know.
I don't know what that 150,000 number is.
That's two out of it.
But that's still a lot for the vice president.
What is the vice president's accomplishments before taking off?
Oh, laid off 30,000 Americans.
Proceeded a merger that some have said is the worst merger ever.
But, you know, that's that's that's some people's opinion.
You know, after you got through some incredible
opening moments from embattled CEOs,
then you got to party the night away at the opening of Mission Space
because there were performances by the B-52s and Sugar Ray.
And there's one bit of footage of it
that with the camera is just panning over like a blue ice pile
where shrimp cocktails are sticking out of the whole thing.
And you can hear distantly like 30 feet away,
Sugar Ray performing their cover of Is She Really Going Out With Him?
I know that song. I know that cover well.
Mm hmm. Oh, no.
How often is the last time you played it?
How often do you know?
I haven't listened to that one in a while.
I ended up you know what pops up more on my playlist?
Or when I put like I click on Apple or Apple Music or whatever it's called.
And it'll be like, I'm going to play stuff you like.
What will come up a lot is Sugar Ray's cover of Steve Miller band Abracadabra.
Jesus, Mike, what have you done to your algorithm?
For fuck's sake.
I know. Right. We understand this guy.
We the machines.
Let us give him the perfect offering.
Do you, Scott, let me ask, do you like the song?
Just Steve Miller's version of Abracadabra?
I do. I don't choose to listen to Abracadabra really.
But yeah, I like it.
I would. You know, after we're done, I'll listen to it.
But Sugar Ray, that's one of those where they don't really like add anything.
They just do it. Oh, no. Yeah.
No, no, there's nothing.
There's not much of a flourish or anything like a special Sugar Ray sauce
they put on it or something, or it's not hard.
It's not hardcore or anything.
Are you insulted then by the algorithm or is it like, yeah, all right, get in here.
You got me.
Yeah, I'm usually I'm usually looking at the algorithm on my phone.
I'm go, you got another one.
You're right. You are. Yep. You're right.
I do like I do want to hear this.
You know what? Should we just see what it comes up with?
Yeah, yeah. Go to you, guys.
Let's see what happens if you just go to like, don't just read them all.
What's what's a it might be good.
It might not be good, but I'll come to the first one that'll like be worth talking about.
OK, I play it.
OK, the first one is a solo song by the Bare Naked Ladies, Steven Page.
A song called Shooting Star.
Yeah. Let's see.
There's a Wilco song. Oh, it's too cool. God damn.
Abandoned Luncheonette. Oh, my taste is too good.
It's all a note song. It's defeating.
Yeah, I know. I like like man.
All right. Well, look, sometimes here's what's good about the Apple music algorithm
when it's telling you what you would want to hear.
Sometimes it's like that.
And then sometimes if you're like me, who does listen to like
all the Matchbox 20 albums, it will just give you the hits from like the night.
It'll give you like tell Bachman she's so high.
What I was really hoping for, like the jewel that could have come out of that was like
it's a cover of who I want to be like you from the Jungle Book by Alien Ant Farm.
That'll happen, too, though.
Oh, down at the Lottie Dab by Jimmy Buffett has just popped up.
All right. OK.
Now we're now we're in the territory.
Let's make sure we talk about some things on the ride.
One thing we haven't talked about is that this the like unpleasant trade
that happened here where this was done in the space formerly taken up by Horizons.
We did an episode about it.
Very pleasant ride.
Really just nice forward thinking, hey, the future will be wonderful
kind of ride. And then it fell into disarray.
Or so they say.
I even saw a press conference where
from the channel Martin's Vids that we consult with sometimes.
And they some executive is in a like pre written little skit
saying to Michael Eisner, we have an attraction.
We're so excited about that.
The the building we currently have wouldn't be big enough to to fit it.
And then Martin's Vids puts a title on to editorialize.
It says actually the Vision Space building is smaller.
But anyway, go ahead.
The video I watched also says and that was a blatant lie.
Like there were also that's a big thing, I guess, in all these videos
to make sure you know that Disney lied about the size.
The thing that hit me like looking looking at this ride was realizing how like, huh?
Horizons pretty.
I don't know if the right word to use, but pretty whimsical,
like a pretty novel view of the future.
It's like if we keep going down this path, you know,
if these innovations keep going this way, this is something we could have.
It isn't that neat.
And, you know, the the building also very like whimsical,
like interesting architecture.
And this I kind of like it.
I kind of like the front.
But I'm like, yeah, but that Horizon building looks so cool from a distance.
You know, I do like the Mission Space building.
I hate on mine.
I think it is funny because I think like I appreciate it on some level
what this was trying to do because it was trying to make it a very accurate
experience, make it something like.
And I assume they were like thinking, oh, this could this could inspire
a generation of people that want to go to NASA and train to be astronauts.
And maybe it did.
And maybe somebody out there who is an astronaut now will say that that's
what happened. But I feel like more people were like inspired to do stuff
like be an astronaut or go and be a scientist or something by crazy,
nonsense, bullshit like Star Trek.
Like you hear that a lot where somebody was a, you know,
a big Star Trek fan when they were little and then they went to they started
like training to be an astronaut or they studied whatever astrophysics or something
like nonsense.
When you're a child, that's fun.
To me seems like it's probably it could be rooted in some reality,
but it feels like it probably would inspire kids more than putting them
in a little box and accurately simulating what it's like to go into space.
Yeah, I think so. Yeah.
I mean, why?
I don't understand why this couldn't have been more fun because there are
there are logic leaps like you do.
You do a hyper sleep of three months in a in the blink of an eye.
Because you go to Mars. Yeah.
So they have to do silly stuff and then kind of a star tour thing
happens at the end where you go up to a canyon and what?
So they're all they're a little bit there.
And then otherwise, it's such a dry,
clinical kind of experience that, yeah, I agree with you.
I don't know that that's going to make people want to join the program.
Yeah. And maybe it's maybe somebody will disagree.
But I wonder how much was possibly planned of like, there's not in this attraction.
Of course, there's not so right.
There's a rise in references here and there, especially the the logo, the icon.
But there's also props and some nods to the 2000 movie
Mission to Mars itself, a reference to the attraction Mission to Mars itself,
a sequel to Rocket to the Moon.
And I'm wondering how much when they were making that movie
Mission to Mars that came out in 2000, a few years before this,
how much were they like, this is a hit.
This is a big hit.
We get a ride out of this, you know, we get an attraction out of this, you know.
And then this kind of is what came out of it, maybe where it is.
I wonder if they would have made it like it is Mission to Mars, the ride.
But then it didn't really land.
But maybe they kind of casually promised Gary Sinise on the set.
Hey, and we're doing a space ride and we put you in it.
You can be your famous character.
You're the your widower character.
That is the only fact that I saw about Mission to Mars.
You can be your widower again in the line.
They did some like like what year was the movie Mission to Mars?
2000, 2000.
OK. Yeah, I think I'm trying to think there was a guy.
You probably have this already.
There's a specific video where they were hyping this right up,
where I maybe I'm misremembering what they were talking about,
but there's some famous people in it to talk about.
I think you do have this.
I think I do. But do what you were going to.
Well, no, we'll do it later. Actually, it'll be better.
OK, to do it later.
I wonder if we have the same thing.
It's probably the same thing.
But anyway, well, here, let's let's talk a little about the pre show is nice
and that big rotating wheel thing that is left over from Horizons.
Correct. That's a prop that they repurpose.
But pretty quickly, you're into
the pre show with with Gary Sinise, where he's your Gary Sinise
is your Capcom. He's the Capcom.
And he's going to tell you some stuff about how this is going to go
and that the mission is going to take three months, which is very jarring.
Here's you know what? Let me just generally say about Sinise.
I remember thinking at the time, all right,
Disney's thing right now is to use all of these kind of character
actor guys that a lot of people would recognize, but you couldn't necessarily name.
And like Gary Sinise, probably pretty nameable.
But, you know, he's in there with we've talked about a lot of these other ones.
Wallace Langham and John Michael Higgins and Patrick Warburton.
And I just remember thinking Gary Sinise is my least favorite of these,
of the Just a Guy actor who started appearing in rides in the early 2000s.
I think this is a a flat performance.
I think he does not seem excited.
It does not hype me up to be there.
It just kind of adds to the clinical nature of everything.
But but so I guess I've just added myself as the one who didn't test positive
for for Gary Sinise fever.
Did anybody who's excited about is anyone excited about Gary Sinise in this ride?
That's a good question. I don't know that I'm excited.
I mean, it's I would say it's a little unfair to Sinise,
I think because you're also planting him in this ride.
Like if Sinise was in the pilot's outfit on Soren,
I'm not saying it would be better or even as good as Warburton.
But give me some of those lines.
I would like to see what he would do with the I would like to see what he would do
with it, which this is kind of a funny thing to like recasting,
like recasting videos, like pre show videos with different actors.
You know, like what if, which is a funny, you know, what if.
So I think if you give Sinise, if you planted Sinise
with the dialogue of these other pre show rides,
I think you're going to be a little bit more excited about Sinise.
Huh, huh. But isn't but doesn't he land where he's supposed to?
Like, he seems pretty humorless.
I can't recall seeing Gary Sinise in a scene where he's cracking a joke.
Is there a screwball sex comedy that Gary Sinise is in that I can't think of?
I'm not sure. I don't think so.
Did he end up getting a part over Gutenberg or something that I'm not aware of?
I what is let's see.
He's on CSI New York, Forrest Gump, Apollo 13.
He's in Ransom. These are all laugh riots.
What are you talking about?
Well, he kind of he see like smiles in Forrest Gump as Lieutenant Dan.
If that's something. Yeah.
Yeah, I guess there's not a lot of goofing around with Sinise.
And I hear what you're saying.
You want a little of that, but that's the tone of this ride.
The tone of this ride is not goofing around.
You want to you want a serious man.
Yeah, it is a serious guy.
I think if you put Patrick Werber and it as this part,
it is a little more fun.
It's a little more, you know, a little more wild.
They watch out for protein spilled, buddy. OK.
Yeah, exactly. And that's good.
But it's not the tone of the ride.
You're right. It'd be it'd be out of place.
Look, I'm just going to as much as I want to talk about things on the ride,
I of course was like, I have to come up with
I have to find something new about the Lieutenant Dan.
Oh, there was no way to not.
And, you know, the lieutenant as look, as with the rest of Sinise,
it's pretty serious, right?
It's a little bit mockery proof because it is a good thing that they do.
It's like USO tours and right.
They do perform for the troops.
But there's one interesting thing I found about the Lieutenant Dan Band.
So on the Wikipedia for them, there's a list of like honors
that they received, like awards because they're given these, you know,
here's this Bob Hope humanitarian thing or here's the Ellis Island Medal of Honor.
And then at the end of the Wikipedia, the list of awards,
it says that in 2016, Mr.
Sinise was awarded the National Daddy Award.
Well, look it up.
It's there in the Lieutenant Dan Band Wikipedia.
He was unless I'm hallucinating, this is the beginning of my covid.
I swear to God, it said that he got the National Daddy Award.
What? So I am immediately OK.
The National Daddy Award. Tell me more.
I Google the phrase National Daddy Award with quotes.
And the only results that I find are related to the Lieutenant Dan Band
and the alleged awarding of the National Daddy Award in 2016.
Wow. What?
So I yeah, I so I'm beginning to question whether or not the National Daddy Award
is a legitimate.
Oh, yeah. You look it up.
It can be given the pick.
The first picture is Sinise playing that bass.
Uh huh. Uh huh.
Potentially the only National Daddy Award ever given unless it was not given.
What I'm starting to wonder is, is this some prank that I'm not understanding
on the Lieutenant Dan Band?
However, even with that, I love the phrase so much.
I'm in love with the National Daddy Award.
And if it look, if it's all stolen valor
and nobody's the recipient of the National Daddy Award, then it I say it's up for grabs.
So what I would love is, look, I have a Wikipedia page
and I don't know.
I don't really know about editing Wikipedia pages and I don't know.
I think that's not even right to do to do yourself.
Right. However, if there are listeners who like to edit Wikipedia
and you would be willing to say that Scott Gardner received the National Daddy Award,
it would be my honor.
It would be my highest honor to be to fall in line with Gary Sinise
and accept the National Daddy Award.
I think that's great.
And if anyone wants to add that he is one of three Disney daddies with a Z also,
just you don't have to put that part, but
you could set up a different website and that is the source of it.
Yeah. And I wanted to ask you guys about it just to brainstorm this,
because I really do want this.
Is it better if I got the National Daddy Award, like in twenty twenty one,
after which I became a daddy?
Or is it better if I got it right after Gary Sinise?
Like if the Wikipedia said
in twenty seventeen, Scott took the crown of the National Daddy Award from
Scott. I'm sorry.
Wait, you have to put it really dry to get away with it, I think.
In twenty seventeen, Scott succeeded Gary Sinise as the recipient
of the National Daddy Award.
I you know what I love is when a restaurant will be like voted best pizza
in the city.
Two thousand seven, two thousand eight, two thousand ten, two thousand eleven.
Where like there's a like what happened in two thousand nine.
So I would love a skip year if you got it.
Two thousand seventeen, two thousand nineteen, twenty twenty one.
And it's like, what happened those even number years?
If you look at and I'm sure this works for baseball championships,
any sort of sports thing.
But if you look at like a wrestling pro wrestling Wikipedia,
a wiki type thing, it'll have a list of like intercontinental champions
and it will go down the list of like who won it from who and then like
what date it was.
So, yeah, if you could get you, Sinise and then you under it
and then maybe, yes, Sinise gets it back, like Sinise the next year,
then you get it the next year.
If it's mainly like kind of a little a little chase between
you between me and Sinise, but be creative, throw it
whoever you want into the National Daddy Award.
I'd say maybe leave out Josh Demaro because he'd be more
the recipient of the National Daddy Award.
Oh, yeah. But yeah, just just whoever you think of when you think daddy
and whoever reminds you of me and Gary Sinise.
There's a real whoever else fits in that mold.
The Daddy Awards have been going a long time and a lot of Disney CEO
E. Card Walker won it in 1970.
It's been primary. Yeah, Ron Miller.
Yeah, it's been primarily Disney CEO.
The National Daddy Award respects the space of the National Daddy Award.
They they write different things and they they even like host
events together, banquets.
They're not enemies.
So don't don't don't put them against each other.
That's not the. Yeah.
Hopefully somebody will let us know.
Please take me up on it.
But don't you know, be dry because otherwise Wikipedia might flag.
Just make it as because it like almost I almost glazed over that
in the Lieutenant Dan Band article.
I almost went right past National Daddy Award
before it became 15 minutes of this episode.
Now, yeah, we got to I'm assuming you look like was there a ceremony?
Was there a press release like it feels like if it's on paper,
if it's just they sent a certificate, that's different than if there's like
a party at a Dave and Buster's, you know?
Yeah, yeah, I think it's like a mid level.
Like they film it, but just kind of for industry, it's not televised,
but they like they do it up nice and there's like a hearty chicken dinner.
You know, all the daddies, all the daddy nominees get their due.
I don't know who hosts the National Daddy Awards.
Is that like a who's like who's who do we think of when we think of America's dad?
I mean, America's dad, that's a phrase I think of.
And I think I can't think of a person specifically.
Wait, wait, does that mean you are thinking of someone as American?
It means I'm thinking of Bill Cosby. Yes.
Oh, oh, that didn't occur to me.
America's dad, not America's daddy.
I thought you were talking about Stan, the main character in American Dad.
Well, I think about him, too, but I sorry.
That's it. It's a fun.
It's hosted by it's like they comp in in
there's a live, oh, yeah, yeah, an animated American dad.
That's great. But he's still daddy.
He's not daddy. Yeah.
Well, who's America's daddy?
What? Who's America's daddy?
It's a good question. Yeah.
It's a hard line to parse.
There was a what show in the 60s called Make Room for Daddy.
Oh, yeah. Who is that?
Is that Danny Thomas?
That Danny Thomas?
I was trying to remember who there's I was like, is it somebody from the
from like Daddy Daycare 2?
And then I'm looking that up and everyone involved is problematic.
In the film Daddy Day Camp.
So it's not them.
OK. You've Daddy Day Camp out of it.
Wait, isn't that other movie?
Wait, what's Daddy's Home? Oh, Daddy's Home 2.
No, no, no.
Sequel has problematic people. No.
I know what you mean.
Mark Wahlberg can do it. Mark Wahlberg's in Mark.
Oh, yeah. He's never done it.
Nothing problematic.
Yeah, nothing bad about Father Stu.
That's America's daddy, Father Stu.
OK, well, now we can all agree on that.
Well, let us know.
It's tough to decide on the spot.
Let us know who you think America's daddy is.
But anyway, back to mission space.
I let's well, let's talk about this, that for a long time, it has not been
Gary Sinise. There was a redo of this attraction.
And who is that new Gina Torres?
Is that correct? Yeah, I think so.
I think she is great. She's good at it.
She's on Suits.
She was on Suits with Meghan Markle.
And as we all know,
the star of the Suits spinoff, Pearson,
which is, of course, the last name of her character, Pearson.
So it's Gina Torres from Pearson.
Wow. I didn't know that existed, believe it or not.
That's one of those these alternate dimensions that we all exist in.
We're like on our side, it's like the only shows that exist are Barry and Hacks.
And then the other side has never heard of Barry and Hacks.
They're entirely about Suits and Pearson.
We're the liberal bubble here.
We don't know anything that happened to Gary Sinise on CSI.
Friend of the show Buzz Buzz talks about how we're all in our own bubbles,
in our own realities, a very unique theory. Yes.
But he he does not even listen to the show.
It does not know the run. He just said,
I mean, the only thing anybody really watches is Yellowstone.
So wise words that we ourselves have said.
And yet Mike continues to defy and I am going to get to it.
Is Gary Sinise been on Yellowstone yet?
That seems ripe.
Seems ripe for an entire Yellowstone.
Yeah, one of the spin offs, I would think.
That is an anecdote I only like half half remember from the Disney
war book where they're talking about, like because they just had so many
like fine live action middle of the road movies.
And they're like, oh, what?
You have a big awards movie or what?
What do you want? You want another cowboy movie?
Kevin Costner, like said, dismissively.
And it's like, wow, cowboy movie might not have worked,
but cowboy TV show seems like it's working fine.
See, cowboy TV shows, the only thing like keeping Viacom around.
It's like doing better than all the other ones because of one cowboy TV show.
One cowboy TV show.
I anyway, here's here's my big takeaway from, I'd say actually,
especially the Gina Torres version, and I'm not sure if this was done
specifically with the let's make sure people don't get on Mission Orange
unless they know what they're getting into.
I feel like they ramped it up because we're what there's
there's like the bigger screen that you watch before you go into the little room
where the capsules are and then you watch another little video there.
And these videos, I swear to God, over and over.
It's just like now, remember, this one is intense.
You have chosen Mission Orange and that is intense.
And if now is the time for you to tell a crew member that you want to go,
then you might want to and then you're in the next room.
And keep in mind, if you're prone to this or that, you could go.
You know, hey, look, don't
no shame on my part.
If you want to keep walking out that door, be the flight director.
I'm not going to tell. I'm not going to tell anybody.
There aren't a lot of rides that try to talk you out of the ride.
I think the moments the door will the door in front of you will open.
Keep walking through it and then out the next door and don't do the ride.
Seriously, don't do the right.
Like, tell your family that you did it and they're not say
you got a little woozy and that's it.
It's a clean alibi. Don't go on the ride.
So here's part of the plan.
We get in a gantry lift unless you don't want to.
If you don't want to get in the lift, don't worry about it
because it goes up and down pretty fast.
Don't worry. You're not a chicken.
I still respect you and you're a big part of the plan.
You'll be waiting for your friends after.
But if you do want to go, we're going up and down.
We see the monsters. The scary.
If you don't like that, leave now again.
I will not be upset.
Maybe just go outside. There's a little cart.
They got big cream puffs.
You can just get a cream puff.
Don't even worry about it.
We play the songs out in the gift shop.
You can hear them. It's not you're missing nothing.
You're missing nothing by the ride. Not going on.
Just put them on a playlist and hop up and down.
That's plenty. Yeah.
Same shit doesn't matter.
No one's going to be a big baby.
Open the Disney Play app.
Then you get to go on an adventure where you try to figure out
how to regain the battery life to your phone and just exactly
why it is so very hot now.
Your phone gets hot. It's exciting.
That's odd. It's not usually that hot.
So it's just the same as going to the dumb ride anyway. Yeah.
Why are you still here? Get the fuck out.
It's scary. Don't do it.
You think I want to do it?
If I wasn't fake, I would leave.
Scott, I did like right before rewatch this again,
and it is shocking how much they say
this is orange version, the more intense version,
or this is green version, the less intense version, which
I had too many things I wanted to do down in Florida.
It didn't dawn on me like, oh, I should have gone through again
and done green version. Yeah.
Should you let down it?
It's weird that like it's not just that it's a less intense
trip to Mars. You don't even get to go to Mars. Right.
Why not just still like, isn't it kind of insulting that like,
OK, you chose mission WIMP.
So that means you leave Florida and fly back to Florida.
You chose Google Earth View,
something you've been able to do on a desktop computer since 2004 or 2005.
Yeah, it they both share that the
they miss the run or they go too far off the end of the runway.
Either almost go off a cliff or they knock over a fence,
which they should figure out.
They didn't figure out the runway situation, huh?
But they made the new the new version of the ride.
Still a lot of runway issues.
Still a lot of there is a runway, which Aaron, not knowing it at all, was like,
what do you mean a runway?
And I said, no, it's not it's it's not the first mission to Mars.
Like people have been there.
They've like laid down infrastructure.
They paved.
What do you get?
So I'm the the one hundred and twelve flight to Mars.
It gives a shit.
These aren't stakes.
I want wild wilderness.
I want to hit giant boulders.
Yeah, there's like a Macy's on the Mars at this point.
It's like there's been we've settled it.
It's like who gives a shit.
You're just going on a routine trip into space.
You're you're dropping off a load of Ben Sherman polo shirts.
We're filling the Macy's stock of Ben Sherman.
The Martians are wearing polo shirts.
You know, don't hit the Peloton studio.
Yeah, you're restocking the Mars gift shop.
By the way, I just right before we started recording, literally minutes before,
I found a link to an article about how the the
base at Guantanamo Bay has a gift shop
full of Guantanamo Bay merch.
What?
I mean, for like like there's like a straight out of Guantanamo
shirts for the people that I'm guessing are the people that are released or for what?
Uh huh.
For the employees, for the service members and their family.
Yes, straight out straight out of Gitmo.
This isn't a bit.
There's a be here now.
Guantanamo Bay coffee mug.
Be here now.
Like it's a mindfulness that be period here, period now.
Wow, you're right.
I'd rather be there now than a couple of years ago.
They have a plush dinosaur that says, Guantanamo Bay on it.
What?
No.
This article is three years old.
And that was the biggest revelation that this has not come across my eyes before.
What the hell?
The COVID era has been very tough on the gift shop at Guantanamo Bay.
We're not sure if it's going to recover.
The merch at Guantanamo Bay is better than that at Universal Studios.
Straight out of Gitmo.
What the hell?
Oh my God, a Guantanamo Bay lizard.
This is fucking perverse.
Jesus.
This is insane.
God damn it.
We're going to doing an episode about this is going to suck.
We're going to do the Guantanamo Bay episode.
But the tone the entire time is like, oh, this.
Why do we have to?
Yeah, because it's like you don't have to.
Why are you doing it?
We do.
We have a podcast.
We have to do it.
There's a McDonald's.
Everyone, but every there's multiple times we've been like, well, the flag at the Gitmo
McDonald's is that half mast again.
Oh my God. Can you mobile order from the Gitmo McDonald's?
Can you do can you use one of the dollar coffee deals?
That's a good question.
Let me see.
Siri.
What stage of of covid cabin fever is it that you're mobile ordering
from the Gitmo McDonald's?
I bet you I bet you I bet it's like an airport McDonald's, although sometimes
you can mobile order in an airport McDonald's.
I have done it.
You can.
I think Jason planted all of this to ensure that it didn't seem like
Mission Space is the worst tourist attraction in the world.
You know, I never got to go to space camp.
I always saw it as like the prize on the Nickelodeon.
Well, yeah, I didn't.
Yeah, I chose.
So I guess this is kind of a little taste of it.
There's a little play area when you get off and a gift shop, you know,
I never seen terribly exciting any of that stuff.
Probably not.
You know what's really crazy in this ride?
If we if we're jumping around, if we want to just talk about the ride that you
again, the idea you have to like whip around the moon, use the orbit of the moon
to whip you in the right direction.
And then it's like, OK, night night.
Like they put you to hyper sleep and then the the glass fogs up and it's kind of
it's sort of icy for a second and then just all of a sudden.
Get up, wake up. You got stuff to do.
It's so crazy.
It's so jar like they do.
They do produce like a much more jarring way of waking up than probably any of us.
That's but that might be number one most unpleasant.
Like what if there was a ride where a loud alarm told you to that woke you up
from a three month sleep?
Who, Jason, that's for you.
That's a strike against this ride, don't you think?
Well, that it's it's a noisy wake up.
Yeah. Yeah.
The end of it. You get to experience the end of a long nap,
a jarring end of a long nap. Yeah.
Yeah. That's the worst part.
You know, I I I like that they don't belabor it too much.
The hyper sleep like like it's really is it like interstellar or one of the where
it's like always sad when everyone's coming out of the sleep?
You know, I'm trying to think of like an alien when they come out of the sleep
in the first alien.
It's very gentle. Yeah, it's very.
Yeah, they're really taking their time.
You got to adjust. But no, these people, these monsters of the
whatever un catchy acronym they are, you P R T.
I don't know what the I see.
See, yes, I don't know what the this is.
Nobody likes that.
Nobody wants like shirts of this, of no of the not NASA that they made.
It's less fun.
Like everything they wanted to make it so realistic.
Nothing's fun.
Graphics, not good.
The graphics got better.
But boy, those graphics like it's it's real flat.
And then this has a weird moment like the the Millennium Falcon,
that that Millennium Falcon stall thing where it's like, wait a minute,
there's a disturbance. Yes, right.
Was not anything.
You can go by this.
This is the only get that once in a while in this ride.
It's caked in that like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're looking over a chasm.
Lean back. OK.
You lean back successfully.
You're free to go by.
Like it doesn't start a more exciting chapter of the ride.
That's like a trope in movies like you're at the edge of a cliff.
No one move.
Inevitably, someone's going to move.
I feel like I. Oh, what is that movie?
I watched it a few weeks ago.
Is it the Lost City?
The Channing Tatum, Sandra Bullock one.
There's like a moment where it's like, don't don't don't follow.
The car fell over the cliff.
Oh, I was.
It's either the person has gotten out of it and you didn't see them get out,
or they go for a ride and they tumble down the cliff.
You know, right. But not on this ride.
I'm assuming they're telling you, because if you tried to get out of the car,
the compartment would need to move towards the cliff
a little to reset to get you out. Right.
Oh, yeah. We're all going to die when we open the hatch.
Yeah. So you're being towed by a mater or something. Yeah.
Like a bad fun.
But there was no mater then. There is now.
Well, that's the plus up. Get mater in there.
Yeah. Well, sure. Please.
Mater on everything.
Or even you know what?
Really, the plus up.
I don't know if you want to jump right to that already.
The plus up is like Disney's capsules
and it's like planes and cars.
And yeah, they've all got tongues.
They've all got tongues. They talk.
So, yeah, when you're hearing like instruction, it's from the actual ship
itself that's yelling at you.
But like, it's fun. He's got a fun voice or it's like
it's Sebastian Madaskalco or something is the voice of the capsule.
And he's yelling at you.
So hit the button or whatever.
Don't hit that one.
Wake up, wake up.
No one wants to work anymore.
Party let you sleep in for three months.
It's they throw some water on your face and get back to work.
You ever go to Chipotle and they're giving you the beans.
Oh, no, no, no. Let me correct you.
It is Chipotle.
Right. You go to Chipotle.
And you're looking at this these kind of Chipotle.
Yeah, that that is much more accurate. Yes.
So crucial part of the bit that it is Chipotle.
What do you think you'd have a little Chipotle
and then you go to sleep for three months?
I love much better.
I love being mad at a restaurant that literally walks you down the line
of how to get your food.
It's the best bit, because if you never watched the semester
Maniscalco Chipotle, Chipotle bit
where he's he all the premises are wrong.
It's like, you got the people reaching around.
They're going up all over the glass.
And you know, I have never seen that.
This has never happened to me in Chipotle.
He is making a he is like is like every like that.
Put the cheese in the rub and do the cheese.
He's like making motions with his hands and everyone's like dying.
You're like, I've never seen this before.
I've never heard. What experience are you describing?
They're scooping the beans with the big bean shovel.
No, I've never seen that they don't have a bean shovel.
But it's under all the actions are funny.
That's the thing.
Right. We're the only killjoys who aren't having fun.
If we would just embrace the silly movements, the silly man is doing.
He's making silly movements as if really all that's registering to people
watching it are like it would be funny if somebody was acting this silly
because I've been in that line before.
So I can imagine this.
And we're like, no, that's not it.
That's not the authentic experience.
Go to a chip chipotle.
It's I can't even go backwards and say it the right way.
It is business as usual most of the time.
Sebastian, I take umbrage with your premise.
I think the bigger unusual thing is all that listeria
they were cooking up back in the day.
All that food poisoning.
Mission to Mars, that's safer than going to my mom's kitchen.
It gets all scolded by the sauce.
He's the cat voice of the capsule.
He'd be a great, you know, in the way it's a perfect equivalent
of where I don't like Larry the Cable Guy's comedy,
but I do enjoy him in cars.
And it's a I bet I would love a Sebastian Maniscalco
leading voice in some movie.
Yes, he's got a great cartoon voice, as does Larry.
Yeah, he's he's a good quick appearance is crazy.
Joey Gallo in The Irishman.
Oh, yeah, yeah, right.
Yeah. Why doesn't do isn't Disney take an advantage of it?
Well, yeah, I agree. That's the fix.
We got it. You make it capsules.
Disney's capsules done as long as.
But you know, remember, and another thing that's boring about this ride
is that you walk into this room and it's just this training facility.
Right. And you just it's so industrial when you walk in there
because it is just undressed capsules, essentially.
In this version, they would have to show us what that capsule looks like
and maybe show the capsule sucking down a big pile of spaghetti.
Need fuel for the ride.
They should show when you're in the capsule and you see in the little screen,
they should cut from that little screen to like an outside camera, too.
So like you can see he's got like a big bib on ready to eat
the spaghetti or something.
Once he has face getting sucked back. Yeah.
This is like five thousand hairdryers.
Yeah, you think the the fuel you think the liquid nitrogen
in this capsule is intense.
You got to try my mom's famous sauce.
It'll melt your face off the gravy.
This would triple the wait times for this ride.
People would still come out feeling very ill,
but they would be so entertained. So it wouldn't matter. Yeah. Yeah.
And everyone would just call it.
It would just be like, have you done the chipotle ride yet?
No one calls it the right thing.
But it's a poll at the end of the ride.
Like this is a good this is a very synergistic.
What is the chip?
Did he say something about synergy recently?
I would imagine he says something about synergy many times every day.
Yeah. Put your yields, the yields, the results of the yields
are going to be through the roof.
Oh, the results of the they were this is an opposite compact
HP Carly Fiorina.
We're going exactly the other way. Yeah.
Straight to the stratosphere.
We're unfavorable.
We're unfavorables. We're three of the unfavorable.
I do it. I forget someone posted that
a website that makes like signs or T-shirts and magnets and stuff
made the magic band like sticker or the key holder sticker
that you got. And it said like unfavorable attendance on it.
Wow. Wow. Oh, that's pretty good.
My plus up was going to be that if you were feeling like you are two point
five times your weight, your body weight, you're being pushed backwards.
They should make the visuals match the feeling
and they should have the multicolor 2001
kaleidoscope effect going on the screen.
You should, you know, enter a new stage of being like Dave does
when he crosses something that would.
Well, while a cool idea, I feel like that might completely mess you up.
Yeah, man.
Really make you throw up to go on a psychedelic
like carnival pinwheel style like the path to death.
Do it. Make it the Halloween version.
Make it like Halloween plus the Wonka Eve, like the scary Wonka River,
like with the like psychedelic images.
I mean, that's a good idea.
That's a good ride in general. Yeah. How does that ever happened?
Just because it would like make people vomit in terror.
Yeah. I mean, they're even talking about Wonka Rides Forever.
But that's obviously the ride is on the river.
The chocolate, the gross chocolate river.
Maintaining the chocolate river would would really be something. Yeah.
OK, so Jason wants it psychedelic.
Mike wants it with a living
fun Italian capsule.
I think we presented some really excellent ideas.
It's just making it less dry because I think maybe the effect
is interesting and worth upholding.
But the presentation is just I don't know.
That's its downfall. I think it's just it's just not fun.
I will say, though, because we the old scale where it was like
he says is plus up or burn it down.
I'll say burn it down.
I think it's still burn it down.
I think take it to take this freaking thing down.
I don't care. I don't want to plus it up.
Take this freaking thing flushes down the toilet like a bunch like yesterday's
chipotle. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I agree. I don't know, Jason, where'd you land?
Did we did we slide you either way?
I don't I I feel like I overall
there's not as many nasty little freaks like me.
I feel like more guests are getting ill or having a bad time on this experience.
So I may say burn it down and start fresh, if only because
I feel like the ride technology has come so far.
You could do like half as many G's and have a more
pleasant experience and also a more whimsical like
horizons, more future looking interesting ride.
Because the other thing is big downgrade in terms of like animatronics,
like a lot of screens, no animatronics on this guy.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah.
Burn it down and build Flip Flap Railway Mach 2.
Get it up to 24 G's.
It stopped too short. It only broke one part of your body.
You should end it. You should like it.
You should. It should be a full reset of all of your bones.
Yeah. Yeah. Look, slapping Kano on it.
You know, that's big hit.
We don't we don't we don't talk about Flip Flap Railway.
You know, the Kanto presents Flip Flap Railway.
They're done. Perfect.
The big the big panda get tumbles out of Flip Flap Railway.
He comes out of your car and then goes at the loop.
It comes back in your car.
That's always funny. Right, dudes.
From. Yeah. Turning red. What did I say?
I don't know. I don't know if you said turning red railway.
I don't think it's a turning red.
It's a big red.
Isn't it a big like a red panda?
They're different than the other.
It is a red. I guess you're right. Yeah.
Clearly lots of better things you could do with this land.
And I think we got it.
I I'm going to say you survived podcast The Ride.
But I feels like on the way out, Mike, what are you heading?
Do you want to?
Do we have the same clip here?
Does it involve a real astronaut?
It sure does. It does. Hang on.
Well, let's get there.
But let me let me say here on the way out,
because this is a good way to to to play it out.
OK, it's been crazy.
Jason got covid bunch of stuffs going on.
It's been a nuts time for us.
So we are going to take a much needed summer vacation.
We're taking the next two weeks off on the main feed, including Labor Day weekend.
But if you don't want the good boy fun to stop,
if you want your favorite national daddies to keep flipping and flapping,
then there's going to be new stuff up on podcast The Ride, The Second Gate
and our new tier club three for a fun episode about Disney dollars coming up.
And you will find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast The Ride.
So apologies for our absence here, but we'll re-release something.
We'll unlock something and we'll be back
refreshed and raring to go.
But super fun stuff happening over in the paywall city.
So, Mike, what you're describing,
is this a sketch from the magical world of Disney or whatever you call it?
Starring Jerry O'Connell. Yes.
Jason, have you seen this?
No.
Well, not only Jerry O'Connell, but there's more
fun cameos to come.
So, you know, he's promoting mission space
and he's being assigned his flight crew.
As our crew, the success of this mission depends entirely upon you.
Ma'am, you're our commander.
Son, you're our engineer.
Sir, Colonel Buzz Aldrin, sir.
You're kind enough to be our pilot.
Colonel Buzz Aldrin, he really walked on the moon.
And you're our navigator.
I don't have any navigator experience.
Navigator, I don't even know how to read the compass.
Buzz, you got my back?
Yeah, I'm with him.
That's great. Then they throw it a commercial.
That's kind of all he does.
And then there's one little one more little appearance.
So, yes, Mike, when you alluded to this, I'm glad you found this too.
Buzz Aldrin delighted by Buzz.
So happy to see him.
I was going to ask, do you kind of like me, do you kind of equate
Buzz Aldrin and Ringo in any way?
Where they both like did incredibly impressive things,
but they're kind of these like funny little guys now.
Like they're similar, they're really similar to me.
I know what you're saying.
Buzz Aldrin feels like this is I don't want to insult this guy.
He feels like he'll do anything.
He feels like you like you go, hey, you want to show up at this?
And he goes, yeah, right.
Which honestly, like, hey, you should go.
He did. He walked on the moon.
God bless. I I.
OK, I might not be remembering this correctly,
but there was a funny or die event.
Yes. Yes. This is where you were.
I'm thinking, yes, I was there, too. Yes.
OK. Yeah, it was at the Egyptian Theater,
historic theater on Hollywood Boulevard,
and they were screening a bunch of videos from that year.
And there were some live comedy, too.
And I believe was it he got on stage with Zach Galifianakis and Sarah Silverman?
Something like that. Yeah.
I mean, which is like fun.
Like, I don't I should I guess really what I was like, I was like,
Buzz Aldrin's at this dumb event with us.
Yes, we don't deserve access to this man, to the second man on the moon.
That's what I kind of.
Full right around goofing around.
Yeah, he was a pretty good sport.
I believe it was it alive between two ferns with the three of them.
Oh, maybe. Oh, that's fine.
You know, you did the lead in.
So, you know, forget the end of this.
He just kind of says like, hey, I'm going to get back on it again.
And I don't know.
I don't know.
Wait, did you have a part you wanted to?
Yeah, I thought, look, it's not the great.
I mean, that's the gist of it.
But there's they're like, did you see when they're working together?
Uh, let me play it.
Do you think it's this?
I think it might just be this. I think, yeah.
We're not going to make it activating boosters.
Five thrusters now.
I can't find it. I can't find the button.
Yeah, I got it.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Yeah, they're not on the ride.
Like they're just like probably making the ride going.
They got buzz. I got a great line reading there.
Yeah, I got it. Yeah, yeah.
That's really all I wanted to play.
Oh, it's so great.
Well, then let me go into because.
OK, I've talked before about how much I love this crazy performance he did
with Thomas Dolby of you.
She blinded me with science where he's the old man who yells science.
But one time he messes up and says, silence.
And I'm very glad people have noticed this and enjoyed this.
And look up the clip if you haven't seen it.
But I was like, do I have to bring this up on the show?
I think I have to.
And it is his main funny or die collaboration.
I may have talked about this before,
but have I ever played it? I don't think I've played it.
And do you guys know what I'm talking about?
I think I do.
So right before I got to funny or die, this was like this looms large.
So I was like, where what am I heading into?
What's this dream factory making?
And what they were making was a Buzz Aldrin song called Buzz Aldrin's
Rocket Experience.
And now I'm I know that this is like novelty.
I know that he is not trying to top the rap charts.
However, so I'm just going to say that that I am aware that there's a level of camp here.
And it's great. Look, this makes me so happy.
I just want to share it with you guys and with the audience.
So maybe this will this will kind of take us out.
And for a little bit, this will guide us into a little summer vacation.
Our own little bit of hyper sleep.
Precisely.
OK, so here now a little taste of Buzz Aldrin's
Rocket Experience.
The most like Broadway trio back in the month.
And what?
Your singers.
Are you ready to put on your space suit strapped in for the G Force lift?
Oh, count down is getting very close now to the adventure of a lifetime.
I've been there now, I say it's your turn.
All we got to do is make the engine burn.
This is how you save the ride.
They should just play this.
Just put this on.
Are you ready?
You chose a mission orange now.
Don't forget, it's a little more intense now.
Don't even show us the video of seeing Mars or anything.
You show the video this.
It's just play. Yeah.
If you can't reach the button, the computer does it for you.
Remember not to pile it, but don't look left or right now.
Or else you get sick and your face will turn white now.
Though that's it.
We're all right. We have so many souls.
Just do one of them. For God's sake, Disney.
You don't need Carly Fiorina's permission anymore.
Put the Buzz Aldrin music video in the ride.
Damn it. That's it.
We're out. We're out for two weeks.
Bye. Bye.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.