Forever, dog.
Warning, the following podcast includes hundreds of animatronics
and almost as many charisma-free General Motors CEOs.
It's an exploration of ingenuity, ninja turtle gratuity, and cat-facing nudity.
Gear up for a slow-moving spin on Epcot Classic World of Motion on Podcast The Ride.
[♪ Synth beat with m究dimiia and
M someday Kindboddy-s clap.
To be free as opposed to podcast ride the second gate where we believe it's fun to pay five or eight dollars.
I'm Scott Gardner joined in the room by Jason Sheridan.
I look just like GM's quality automobiles.
Not everything can be free.
You know that's well I would not expect GM to issue cars for zero dollars.
Yes no.
Or it would be funny if like podcasting they put out some of the cars for free and then other ones you need to leave.
If you want the really good ones.
Yeah.
It's a little extra.
And joining us from somewhere else on God's green earth it's Mike Carlson.
Hi I am.
Hey I'm here.
I'm broadcasting live from the Ninja Turtles underground headquarters from Ninja Turtles 2 secret of the ooze.
This is the abandoned train station where I've made my home and where I'm choosing to raise my child.
So the ultimate lit wow that's where she's oh my god.
Well yeah instant jealousy not just for from all of us I would think.
Yeah we're recording some video on this so if you want to see me live from the underground train station just go to YouTube forever dog right.
Forever does YouTube I believe.
That's correct.
Yeah yeah.
Well that rules.
What are some of the amenities of the underground train station.
Do they have.
I mean they they have to like think of a weird way to get pizza right.
They can't exactly like enter that into the app or I guess on the phone.
I think you know I think they did it like in the first one where they just kind of wait by a sewer grate.
And then they just a disembodied voice yells at the pizza person to slip it through and then they pay with cash.
They're all they don't like a cashless society.
I assume the Ninja Turtles they're not they're not in favor of the great reset that will get rid of cash and turn all of our money digital you know they're old school guys.
Well that's what I only recently realized the dimension it's weird about restaurants having to scan the menu that it like essentially boxes out people who don't have phones.
And that's sort of what's happening.
If it's if it's a cash free society that severely impacts mutant turtles who live in underground layers.
For sure.
Yeah.
And they're they're probably good tippers right because they're about virtue and justice.
So why do you miss out on a different way.
And this is not the topic of the episode but I have a lot of thoughts on which turtle is the best tip.
I'm more than happy to abandon and shift as much as we want to get to the world.
Donatello is the best tipper.
Ah OK.
What's the what's the thought there.
What's the logic.
Donatello I think he's just the most sort of thoughtful and the most empathetic of all the turtles.
So I think he understands that like being a service worker like it's hard like it's hard waiting on people it's hard delivering pizzas.
So I feel like he's the one who's probably most in tune with that.
I would say number two is Leonardo who's pretty empathetic as well but also I think can get a little wrapped up in himself.
I was going to say would he be a little bit like cut the shit at some point there's a job to do.
You can't be nickel and diming.
He might like have a limit where he's like look just deliver the food.
Yeah.
And then I think like it maybe it's even like Raphael next even though I think Raphael is one of those guys who's like the food was late.
They're getting half the tip.
They're getting half the normal tip I would give them and you're like just give the full tip man like the bounce the bounce of rage.
It depends on when but if you get catch him on a good day maybe he tips.
Yes a lot.
And then Michelangelo look I love him he's a party dude but I don't think he's the kind of guy who's just like oh I didn't have anything.
Sorry bro.
Yeah.
He's like a child.
Like yeah he's like a child.
Yeah.
The only time I ever like a group of friends and I ever just did not complete the check was we were all like 15 at a dentist.
Complaining about George W.
Bush and we all just pathetically like I have some more nickels I found some more nickels and we just did.
So that's you know yeah.
Michelangelo is eternally 15 I think.
Yeah.
That's a great break.
I would find there's no debate over here right about that.
That all adds up to me.
Did you say Leonardo.
Yet.
Did I use to.
Yes.
OK.
Number two.
Yeah.
So Jason paid attention to three quarters of the list.
I.
Yeah.
I just missed one.
I was worried I was I was ranking that I was following your ranking and I remember he's just got General Motors facts in his head and he's running.
It's got a lot over and over again to make sure he doesn't forget them.
I.
Yeah.
My general unease with how many times they talk about low key talk about freedom just has me a little off kilter.
Fair speaking of George W.
Bush.
Yeah.
Freedom talking about freedom and talk about Paul McCartney you know talking about freedom his famous song.
And they were talking about your freedom to buy a Chevrolet Malibu.
Yes.
A car I owned at one point.
That's right.
How lost is the reference to freedom at this by 20 year old song Paul McCartney's post 9 11 extremely sorry.
Yeah.
My fault.
No I'm just curious.
Maybe people have a strong memory or fondness for freedom.
I think the rising is the one we all remember.
That's a Bruce Springsteen.
That's Bruce's song.
Yeah.
But I was not written and look I'm in the weeds already but Bruce did not write that song for 9 11.
It just happened to come out after 9 11 and feel like it was a very prescient prescient.
That's word song something that was a reaction to freedom was written after 9 11.
I just want to make that very clear.
Yeah.
I think it's hard to go on from my co-hosts about this.
I was I went to wherever Jason went during the turtles list.
I think I went back to thinking of the turtles tipping pizza people when I was talking about the rising and maybe think I should go back to that.
Denny's which is still open and just and just like complete the bill.
I know it won't be the same people.
I don't believe.
I mean how much could the tip have been on like a plate of fries and a sherry coat.
Oh yeah it was all it was already.
Yeah I'm sure we're all.
OK.
So how much hammy do we all get between the five of us is it an even five split on this moon.
How many moons do we all get.
Yeah we split it five ways.
OK.
Today we are all in theory.
Hopefully we'll be talking about world of motion an opening day Epcot attraction.
We are right around Epcot opening day the 40th anniversary.
I'm wearing a commemorative shirt Epcot forever.
That's what's that's how I feel in my heart.
And wow almost 40 years since the future began any general feelings about or sentiments you want to have.
Sentiments you want to send to this venerable park.
And it's a good question.
I mean I'm happy again I'm happy there's new stuff we've gone over this many times.
I'm happy there's new stuff and fun stuff to look forward to.
But I do get wistful for the boring stuff they got rid of.
Yeah.
And which this definitely fits.
Oh this is I'm delighted by it but I think it's.
Yeah.
I think you'd be I think you'd be faking it if you said there wasn't at least some of this that is boring.
I see Jason's face is really fired up.
I was coming in ready to defend this just on the sheer fried into my memory first traffic accident scene and then I watched it.
And I was like there's a lot of fun stuff in this one.
There's more fun stuff than I remember.
First off there's yes nearly 200 animatronics so yeah high marks for that.
Yeah.
And then I like the ride I was to I do too.
This is not a mission space situation.
Yeah no no no no let me get that out of the way.
Oh I like the writer I like boring.
Yeah.
But I think there is more fun in this ride because I because you had this was one of the only rides Ward Kimball worked on one of Walt's nine old men.
And then you had Mark Davis working on it you would Claude Coates working on it.
Buddy Baker and exit Tensio did the song and all the names right at the top.
I'm blowing all the names.
Shoot talk about purely a CEO Robert Stimple.
Well look I'll say Stimple for you.
I didn't have Stimple.
This is more to make the point that I think those guys generally had more fun creative work more fun in animation than say Ray Bradbury and Buckman's.
Or Fuller.
Sure.
Well you've got like a goofier lineup of people Mark Davis is responsible for a lot of the like silliness and attractions Jungle Cruise.
I feel like he's like great Disney like silly playful animatronic tableaus or Mark Davis and then yeah Ward Kimball was like this is the only ride Ward Kimball.
See only ride not otherwise didn't otherwise make the shift.
Well Ward Kimball they did name he is there is a locomotive named after him at Disneyland named after him in 2005.
This locomotive was repurposed was originally used to transport sugar cane or sugar cane plantation and then it was at Cedar Point.
And then eventually the Disney train was not a Disney original.
They like not as original.
Really.
It's also the only Disney locomotive not named after a railroad executive.
All of the other ones are named after old timey railroad executives.
Wow.
You're here.
You're heroes.
My hero.
Yeah.
Surely great guys.
Right.
Railroad variants.
Yeah that's right.
Yeah.
And and of course I tried to find a picture of Ward Kimball and first thing on a like Disney fan blog is Ward Kimball with a real big smile doodling one of those crows we don't talk about anymore.
Oh no.
OK.
All right.
So she hadn't been photographed.
Yeah he's he though like a lot of fun silly character.
He's he was Jiminy Cricket.
He was Dumbo.
He was Tweedledee and Tweedledum and he's like he's a crazy Coke bottle glasses loony guy like he looks fun.
Yeah.
To look at.
So the ride is going to be fun.
It's more fun from a fun looking guy.
We discussed that about Imagineers if the Imagineers are fun looking their rides are often better.
Is that something we've put together like.
What is that true because is Tony Baxter fun looking.
He's just like a man.
I think he is.
Yeah he's got that big bushy mustache.
That's pretty fun.
I think he is like kind of iconic features.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
You know I like him too.
I'm just like he's like a guy.
He has a mustache and he is.
I wouldn't put him in the same ballpark as a guy with big crazy like a guy who looks like a scientist from a movie.
Well maybe we look it's too much to do now but we maybe we rank the fun look of all the Imagineers at some point.
You know who looks the most fun of all the famous imagineers.
Joe road he looks fun.
That's true.
That's undeniable.
But then you've got your Bob Gurz.
Who looks fun now.
He looks fun.
Yes.
But at the time I think he was we always talk about like just the white shirt the leg buttoned up.
You know a lot of those guys were very formal.
I think I think it's you can make the argument the other way that you know if you don't look fun and maybe you're you inversely come up with fun.
Young.
Roly Crump was like a hunk.
Kind of a hunk.
Yeah.
In that world fair one.
But he looks fun in his older age he likes looks fun in his older.
This is all these are parameters we're going to figure out for whatever this takes shape this.
What age is it that you have to look fun by fun features.
Final four.
If I could quote what you said about Tony.
Well you said iconic features but we're going to rank like what their noses and shins.
Where are we heading with this.
I don't know.
That's I'm saying we have to work the parameters of this out.
What we'll each have our own of our ideas about what about costuming because word Kimball was also in the Jax Dixieland jazz band the firehouse five plus two.
And I believe they're wearing fine outfits.
That's going to help them if there's pictures of them wearing fun outfits.
Yeah for sure.
Yeah.
Costumes.
Glasses.
Look there's no argument about word Kimball looking no argument and the sense of fun that he brought to the history of transportation.
Which you know this could have gone a more clinical way.
I think that is where the story of it potentially is that they they partnered with GM.
We want to tell the story of transportation.
There was an earlier version I think that Claude Coats was involved with that was a little more dry as some of Epcot Center ended up being.
And they said have more fun with it Disney it up.
And they came up with something that definitely feels like all right it's the pirates vibe.
Yeah there's so many characters and big chaotic scenes and things that feel literally taken from pirates like the like a guy coming up from like from a well or a manhole cover with big goofy eyes and looking around like what what just happened.
Garsh.
Doesn't that feel that happens in this right.
I feel like that happens in a lot of Disney right.
They always they might always use the same mold of like the befuddled man with big eyes and a like little quivering lip.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
I mean that you would in the Haunted Mansion it's probably the same mechanism that like has ghosts pop up behind a headstone or something.
Yeah.
Pop ups and pop outs and they pop up pop up some pop outs.
Yeah I mean they're riding to two ways right now that the huge success of Haunted Mansion and pirates and they're also not too far out from the World's Fair.
I was talking to my dad about this ride he's like you know I always liked about the original Epcot stuff those pavilions felt like the World's Fair pavilions that he saw as a kid.
Right.
And he's like he always liked those and also a very dad observation about Epcot he's like and also they were very relaxing and it was cold in there.
So that was a nice and they were long and long and long and that was a nice comparison to the Florida swamp.
You are your dad's son.
And I am.
Yes.
With that history with the 64 World's Fair that's definitely a big part of this.
So Disney had like Disney already had a car industry girlfriend honey I don't know what you want to say but they were already paired up with like they already hooked up with Ford right.
Yeah they weren't they weren't messing around with Ford and Ford and Disney were going steady.
That's the way you put it.
Yes.
Yeah it's the early 60s they were going steady.
They Ford sponsored the attraction the Magic Skyway at the 1964 World's Fair showed how successful Disney could be merging with transportation and telling transportation and futurism kind of stories.
But I didn't realize this that you know those Disney attractions at the World's Fair small world and Carousel of Progress those feel like a big deal now.
But at the time if you ranked guest satisfaction and popularity at the 64 World's Fair the Disney attractions were 2 3 4 and 5.
They were none of them were number one and number one that the guests liked the most was a General Motors ride called Futurama.
They had an attraction called Futurama in the 30s which whatever year the 30s World's Fair World's Fair was.
And then Futurama 2 was at the 64 World's Fair so they beat Disney somehow they managed Disney managed to not have the most liked attraction at the 64 World's Fair.
So that's probably where Disney's eyes started to stray.
What's going on.
Are they available.
Will they be available someday.
We take GM over to Holiday Hill.
You know what I'm talking about.
Ford is out of town.
What happens.
Well I watched the Martins vid Martins vids does these great video essays about Disney attractions especially long gone ones.
And one of the very first slides and a screen grabbed it because I thought it was very funny.
He said having seen what Disney did for Ford at the 64 World's Fair General Motors did not want a rival stealing the limelight at Epcot.
So they were the first to sign on for Epcot first pavilion that went vertical at Epcot.
OK.
So they were.
Yeah they were on board.
They got right to.
They well and they gave Disney.
They said come out take a tour of our test track the facility where we road test the vehicles.
Maybe that could be an idea for a ride.
They said no never that will never happen.
We will figure out something better.
So test track did not occur then.
But yeah they got.
I think this is beautiful.
This is like kind of two people in unhappy marriages.
I think the other.
Well maybe if there's ever a divorce or a death maybe that's what happened with Disney and yeah they finally hooked up.
Disney and the backup plan.
This is yeah.
Is that a movie.
Is there a movie called the backup.
There definitely is but there is.
OK.
As soon as I said it I was like surely someone has made something probably one of the like if we're not married by the time we're such and such an age or if we don't have kids.
I mean I'll look it up.
Yeah.
A plan.
The bad plan that Jennifer Lopez.
It is Jennifer Lopez.
It's Jennifer Lopez and Patrick Dempsey.
It is.
Hold on.
But is it about divorcees or people who want to get out of their unhappy marriage.
I think and she froze her eggs and she just met a guy and the eggs are about to expire.
I feel like I don't know the eggs expire.
Or it was some sort of in this world in this in the backup plan a verse.
Yeah.
Freeze your eggs.
It lasts a long time.
A woman conceives twins through artificial insemination then meets the man of her dreams on the very same day it is Alex O'Loughlin.
He is in the movie.
Is an actor or what.
That's the star of the movie.
Who's Alex.
I think so.
Is the star of a movie.
I've never heard this name in my life.
Maybe maybe that seems to be the top two.
I will tell you this that makes me very excited.
Also in this movie.
Happy Days is Tom Bosley.
All right.
Well just go skip through just the Bosley.
It isn't Bosley.
She doesn't get with Bosley.
If there is a movie from 2010 where Jennifer Loveless and like an 85 year old Tom Bosley hookup we would have known about it already.
I think would have been covered.
It would have been a saga.
Alex O'Loughlin.
Alex O'Loughlin had starred on Hawaii Five O for 10 years.
It's an alternate dimension celebrity.
It's a CBS or USA person.
I've never heard of them.
A handsome guy.
Yeah.
And then he had other TV show Moonlight and Three Rivers for previous shows he was on.
OK.
All right.
World of Motion.
We'll try to get more stats out of a backup plan as we go.
But stats about World of Motion.
Here's one of those.
OK.
I figure we're going to get into that area that always comes up of where we are.
We have like the if any of us went on that and I would have been on this when I was like seven or nine.
We all have that fog of like OK which one is this.
Is this the one where the is this the one with Mona Lisa.
Yes.
Is it the one with the cavemen.
Well a lot of them have cavemen.
Is it the one with the orange smell as engineer Jordan said.
Like you get you get a lot of these dark rides mixed up and in trying to parse which is which and what makes World of Motion special.
I just want to talk about like is there are there definitive ways that World of Motion was the best.
Is there an area where we think we got back up we're looking at a backup plan now.
There's Alex O'Loughlin.
I've never seen this man in my life.
He's the star of a movie.
And a show TV show he's like a guy he's so rich he's so famous to certain people.
Yeah.
I've heard of him in your life.
And I haven't.
Yeah.
No offense.
I think he might be a great actor.
He might be awesome.
Well people might be shaking to meet us too.
And he assuredly has never heard of Scott Mike and Jake.
O'Loughlin hive rise up.
Get our asses.
No don't.
What does that mean.
OK.
Areas where World of Motion might be the best one does.
And let me just throw some stats out because it at least is like the winner in some capacities.
I think probably the winner of longest Omni mover one thousand seven hundred fifty feet.
That is very very long.
This is a long ride.
Fifteen minutes we said.
That's incredible.
So I don't know if that was an estimate.
I don't think that's that's about right.
It definitely feels like there's a lot of scenes.
And you can tell when they spent through their budget when you get to Centercore the city at the end.
I think it might have been cool though.
It's just hard to tell on the video.
Yeah I think it does look cool.
I think it was cool.
Yeah I think the video is so crappy on it.
It all culminates in like you're driving by a big futuristic city which is like minimal and dark.
True.
But no animatronics by that point.
But I think maybe video isn't isn't doing it justice.
So it's it's very long.
That's good.
High ride capacity.
I don't know capacities to save my life but I know this thing.
Three thousand two hundred forty guests an hour.
Highest in the park at that time.
Wow.
For comparison Space Mountain 2000 on a mansion 2400.
This might be one of the highest ride capacities ever.
This could swallow so many people every hour and yet still had a very long line when it opened even though the capacity was was crazy.
So putting up good stats but does it have the emotional pull.
Mike is there any area where you think you've gone over this and gone well I think this does this the best or that the best.
I think the ending is probably I mean maybe other than like figment.
I do feel like maybe this has the best ending of all of the original.
I say it lovingly boring Epcot dark rides.
It does that that city.
I do have I for sure went on this as a kid.
There's there's some video of us going on it.
I don't think we have video of the ride but there's a video of us on the ride vehicle as we start when we were little.
And I do when I watch the videos I do remember the end.
And I think that it's a great it's seemingly a great finale.
I want to give some credit to the start like going in the Omni mover going up like in a spiral almost outside.
Yeah.
Would you get almost like a picture frame view of spaceship Earth and later on the horizons building.
That's just very cool and unique and was probably a pain in the ass to deal with during Florida thunderstorms and hurricanes.
Was it covered though a roof.
It has a roof but it's open.
It's open to the outside.
Yeah it's yeah it's interesting because if you even stack up horizons and world of motion and then you put it up against spaceship Earth which is the last one standing basically at this point for us to cover.
Or or that exists period.
Right.
It exists.
Yeah.
Right.
You probably can make an argument that a lot of elements of horizons world motion are better than spaceship Earth.
It's just that spaceship Earth is in the ball.
It's in the iconic ball.
And you end the elevation really.
And that's such a cool element to know you're in the ball.
And then at the end even though like I always as a kid was really impressed obviously at the end of spaceship Earth when you're like that's the ball we're inside the ball.
So like that element always was was really impressive.
But when you watch the video you go maybe the robot parts of these rides were better than spaceship Earth.
Yeah I think that's right.
I think the novelty of being in the ball you're exactly right.
And this one the novelty I think comes from more like comedic scenes you know.
Yeah but there's still it's still Epcot and it's still as we've talked before it's a big long experimental concept.
Album where all the rides blend together and it's not like we're doing pop songs like pirates.
We're doing more free form songs where it's not like tight.
The rides aren't tight.
They feel a little messy to me and there's great stuff in all the rides.
But they all have like big empty rooms I feel like like there were like yeah that came up with Carly and the the maelstrom of the frozen ride like it's empty for a little bit.
I feel like every one of these rides was just dark for at least 45 seconds.
Am I hard to know with these old videos exactly how they played.
But I do like it is interesting because when you think about Pirates on Haunted Mansion it's like all killer stuff.
But those have genre tropes to fall back on.
You have pirate stories fall back on.
Ghosts to fall back on.
These are you know you said concept albums nebulous concepts.
The communication transportation horizons like the future transportation probably the cleanest.
Yeah.
The cleanest of the concept which gives you like a quicker into like where what are we going to show.
All right.
Well it will be like early fumbling attempts at how we get around as you and stuff through like things getting kooky in the 20s and higher tech.
And some of the history stuff the history gags in this almost reminded me more of like J Ward cartoons than Disney cartoons in terms of like Peabody and Sherman.
Like I feel like reinventing like yeah like here's a fun rewrite of history instead of like accurate.
Re-write.
Spaceship Earth is a little like humorless.
That's not the point of Spaceship Earth.
But this takes some liberties of making jokes about Da Vinci or Columbus or whatever.
Or like like applying like vaudeville or borschtbell kind of jokes to like historic like use chariot lot feels like it would be in like a bullwinkle cartoon.
Oh totally.
Yeah.
Richard said well that's an area where it maybe tops the others is the the fun and the comedy because I'm still maybe my heart wants to say horizons is my favorite.
But horizons is not about you're not laughing in horizon certainly.
No.
I know.
I think this wins for animatronics and scenes and then horizons might win in terms of sets.
Yes.
I feel like there is.
Yeah.
Yeah that's true.
Incredible environments and like inventive and the you know like the multiple futures you could chart and yeah.
And then again Martin pointed out in his video the combination of like kind of dry factual narration with like gags scenes like whimsical scenes that is an interesting like.
Interplay.
Yeah.
And you get a lot of mixed media stuff too with like animatronics and projected animation or projected like stock footage.
Oh everything on screens is really fun.
It is like it's like an early supplementary screen right.
It's not it's not a screen right but there's lots of screens that like help transport you or support what the animatronics are doing.
Yeah it's so so it all comes it all feels like the five and we've talked about this on horizons and there's some literal character parallels whatever the word is.
But like it's all carousel progress it feels like this is all born these are longer sort of versions kind of born out of the carousel of progress and that sort of style of like talking about progress technology and whatever.
But it is interesting to think about carousel progress is such a and I hate it so annoying that I keep saying this but it's like carousel progress to me is like got a great song.
The ride feels so tight as far as like no dead space in it and then you go on this thing and it's like it's more freewheeling the song isn't nearly as good.
Yeah I'm not going to know a lot.
It's not the best Epcot song.
I want not not at all.
And it like to be free is the song I referenced it in the opening joke and I feel like I always like assumed when preparing the episode I was like oh then I'll look it up and I'm sure I will be washed with nostalgia for the great song fun to be free and then I didn't you know it didn't really take for me.
Not a great song.
And also I wonder if I hate to be like what would Walt have done you know but I wonder with like Small World or anything I wonder if it was Walt who was like and then we need like kind of a refrain on some of these experiences that kind of fills in the transition spaces on the ride.
Yeah.
Because that's such a small world I know it's people think it's annoying and it is a little bit sometimes but it's such a hook for sure.
It's such interest it's so interesting that that these rides don't feel like they have that rhythm that some of those older rides do they feel like looser in structure.
It does have the small world trick of like that song in lots of different styles maybe that's true or different styles and to some extent it is an ear worm.
Like it did get stuck in my head last night but I wasn't excited about that like I think you're upset.
I was fine I didn't feel one way or another about it in not in the way that the original like listen to the land song that when we talked about that ride it's like where is this.
Let's get this song back in here like this 20 percent improvement just put the fucking song.
Yeah.
Universe of Energy which we're not so high on I think.
But song both songs.
Yeah.
Now that we've kind of been through a lot of them or imagination could be.
Imagine is up there I think I do the universe of energy is so great.
That man.
That's all.
Feel the flow.
Yeah that's got some real.
Yeah that gets me a little a little pumped.
You want to hear one here one that's not good that's not in the ride but that is related to the ride.
Yes and I'm sure well I said I feel like you were you already talking about these weird promotional videos which we need to talk about one of them.
There is a video that they put out seems like internal for GM mainly it's called reality of dreams and Jordan if you could pull up the clip reality of dreams.
Metal man is.
Traveling like that.
Joe.
Ocean but an ocean.
Is.
The.
LRG.
Of.
Was I wrong was I wrong to hate on that.
Not feelin it.
Yeah.
I think that I think the verse on that is actually pretty fun and chill but the
chorus is a little bit.
This is kind of too airy.
Reality of.
I think that verse is good though.
I was actually the verses I was like okay maybe I'm into.
The.
Course.
I am.
Here's my thing to admit when I was I did have that song in my head even though I
don't like it really but I was I think what was in my head was that style of
singing I couldn't stop doing it reality of.
I was getting ready this morning and my wife walked in on me in the bedroom and I
was singing that next to the very reality of trees but I was about to take a
shower so I had a shirt but no pants on and I was about a foot away from the cat
and she walks in on this tableau.
What are you are you serenading the cat naked.
Winnie the pooing.
Yeah.
Donald Duck in your ass.
Hey bunny I got a show for bunny can I teach you about the reality.
I did now look I just was I just wasn't thinking and I was not aware of the fact
that I wasn't wearing pants and I definitely was not putting on a show for my
cat that involved whipping my junk around for her amusement.
You said where you said she was a little under the weather too so imagine walking
into that and just being like what the fuck is this I'm already blowing my nose
nonstop this sucks.
Last thing I need.
I have a weird cat show you're doing.
Is that can I ask is that off the top of your head is that one of the weirdest
things she's walked in on.
I don't know.
I mean it's always you know because hey when you're living with a comedian there's
a wings of flying you never know what the I can't think of anything weirder.
Now that I add it up especially that like if she didn't grill me but if she had
like what was the song.
That was a song from World of Motion well not from World of Motion from an internal
GM video called Reality of Dreams promoting World of Motion.
The level of it's pretty unexplainable that's for sure.
Yeah I'm trying to think I don't know if I have anything that beats that winning
the pooh style but I mean the amount of times Lindsay walks in and I'm like
listening and singing along to like Brent Spiner's jazz album or something.
You think more than once.
Brett Spiner's jazz album.
I've done it.
Yeah or I should say old standards it's not maybe someone's jazzy but it's not
you know.
We got to know the genre of the.
It's like more like I get a kick out of you.
Big band.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
It's a MacFarlane stuff.
Yeah.
Old yellow eyes.
Seth MacFarlane.
My Bonnie lies over the ocean.
Yeah.
So that's Reality of Dreams.
Do we want to talk a little about some about these videos because and we'll say
more stuff that we like about the ride but I because I have I have some little
moments from what I'm talking about is there was that video there's Reality of
Dreams and then there is this other one called Make Your Own Magic.
Yeah that's the one I watched.
I had a tape of this and I was like why did I have a tape of this because it also
feels like internal General Motors promotion of Disney.
It felt like it's you know telling employees hey we have a ride now you should
maybe go there and here's what else is it.
Disney World.
But I realized that there was a time where if you left this ride they gave you a
little slip and it said free offer from GM if you give us your address and you
think oh a car.
No no no a tape and the tape.
So I think that's why we had I think my parents must have filled out this form
and then gotten a tape promoting the place that we just came back from.
Yeah I I got to say I misjudged this one just on the like you know preview image.
I thought it was going to be it's mostly a Disney World promotional video.
Yeah.
With little snippets of world emotion mostly at the end but then intercut
throughout they kind of tease it a little.
Yeah but they take you through it's like all the footage we know like there's one
shot of people walking past Spaceship Earth and right as the monorail goes by
that is in everything every piece of Disney World footage or special or sitcom
or there's like flying over Mickey on top of Spaceship Earth they use all the
footage that we know which I've watched dozens and dozens of times.
So I was I'm always happy to see it.
But when you're talking about why you misjudged the video is it because of the
boring man and there's a very boring man in the thumbnail and I was like all
right let's go.
I believe Jordan has the boring man cued up.
Here he is now.
Something for everybody here.
Something for everybody.
Today we come to expect even demand variety and almost everything that affects
the quality of our lives.
The history of transportation here at the world of motion shows how people
throughout the ages have searched for and found better ways to get from here to
there.
That speech goes so much longer than just showed that I mercifully cut it off.
You know what I forgot about the his name on screen because I was just like man I
like that sport coat.
Yes it is a really striking like baby blue.
It's kind of a Johnny Carson suit a little bit.
Yeah it is.
Yeah.
Yeah it's it's it's very sorry it feels very it doesn't feel like it feels good.
It feels 70s like he is Robert Stemple the CEO of General Motors may have gotten
stuck in a very he might have got there is one type of suit I like and that's
what I wear.
Don't buy me anymore.
Keep cleaning the one.
Scott how does that compare to the was it Carl Wilson's jacket.
Was it a blue jacket.
You've you've always wanted to know.
No that's a well that's a green jacket a green green jacket that he wore in a
concert that they filmed in the early 80s and there's no question that's the no
that that's the winner.
I admire Robert Stemple's jacket but I don't think I would wear it myself.
Carl Wilson's jacket I would wear every day.
I still waiting for you to find it and wear it all the time.
I should I have not made any particular effort.
That'll be the next thing Aaron walks in on Carl Wilson jacket.
How much are you paying at this auction.
Then you're she finds you just wearing it with nothing else.
It's just the jacket.
It's singing Carl Wilson's songs.
Trader.
I also think I have an old like a real vintage tie from my dad and I think it's
pretty close to that tie like from the 70s or 80s.
So like man I might have to get like a simple cause but the black pants the black
pants with the sport coat is very striking.
It's a choice.
If you went to if you had a live show or at like a D23 type thing dressed like that
I mean you would have to have visual reference but if you dressed like this and wore
glasses like that slicked your hair back.
I mean you could bald cap it.
I don't want to I don't want to make you spend more money.
Look time's already doing that to me.
I don't I don't think I'll have to work too hard on that one.
Well then you would just print out a lower third for yourself that says Robert Stemple
Robert Stemple the crowd going insane like people just screaming.
It's like the Beatles are here again.
Maybe now maybe now that we've dropped it.
Yeah.
Wow.
This is we're here for the show where Jason's Stemple Stemple.
We're recording this while D23 is just starting and I wonder if there are there any
Stemple cosplayers on the floor right now.
I don't think so.
I think this would be a totally unique Disney world related cosplay.
Disney bounding is Robert Stemple.
Like a hot 22 year old jacked guy cosplaying.
What's up fam.
We're checking out the new Halloween cake here at Disneyland and I'm just like Robert Stemple.
Cut off sleeves from the jacket like the blue jacket cut off sleeves and he's like jacked.
His arms are huge.
Or a beautiful girl.
I'm watching her vlog like why am I so in love with this Robert Stemple.
Yeah.
All right everyone let's meet up at the Disney bundle stage and you'll know how to find me.
I'll be dressed like Robert Stemple.
Is there was there ever a discussion to make a Park star vinyl figure of Robert Stemple.
I just that maybe somebody threw it out there.
It didn't happen but maybe somebody threw the idea out.
People a lot of people filled out the free offer that a lot of people sitting on that tape and we're
cutting that business off if we don't make a little toy of Robert Stemple.
That's right.
The chairman and the CEO don't forget.
So that's right.
And he knows you want freedom the freedom to choose which which very angular car.
Which bizarre undriveable car you want.
Robert Stemple incidentally 15 years before he filmed this this dry intro his son was kidnapped.
His third year old was just picked up in a car thrown into the trunk where he remained for two days straight.
And the kidnappers demanded one hundred twenty five thousand dollars which he paid but they did the old.
They they the police knew the numbers and so they tracked the money and got them.
They actually they actually only tracked one of the guys and the one ratted out the other immediately like they didn't even know there was a second guy.
So these kidnappers this is a very poorly put together plan but the 13 year old his this guy's son Stemple son carved his own name into the into the trunk.
Like he found a blunt object and put his name in there.
So like if they find the car they'll know that's why.
Wow.
Yeah isn't that's a resourceful that is really smart.
There is a tip if you get kidnapped an audience.
Boy do I hope that none of you get kidnapped but you do.
Stemple it.
All the stumbles are.
But right.
Right.
Your name don't write Stem.
Don't write.
Robert Stemple's 13 year old son.
Oh shit I wrote the wrong.
Oh no.
I wrote Stemple.
I do have a bit of an axe to grind with General Motors.
Yes sure.
Because you remember that ignition switch recall this massive recall from like I guess what would it be.
Like seven or eight years ago now.
And it's that your car could just turn off sometimes.
And in the middle of a drive in the middle of a drive or if it was jostled a little and I had a Saturn Ion which was a GM car and fell under that recall.
And I had to deal.
I had issues.
I started having issues where my car I would turn it on and it wouldn't start and then the key wouldn't come out.
And the bigger issue this only happened to me thank God one time I went over it like a speed bump like an uneven like part of the road when I was like first moved out here was doing like a P.A.
job doing a run in Long Beach and my car like like really came down hard like over this bump and it slowly just turned off.
And like thankfully I was in like a residential neighborhood but I just pulled over and I was like what the what's going on.
And I like let it sit for five minutes and turned it back on and it was normal.
And then like five or six years later I started having this issue where I thought like oh is my battery dead.
What's wrong my car won't start.
And eventually the dealership said like oh this is part of the recall.
We don't have the parts yet but hold on.
They took a screwdriver and popped a panel off on my steering column.
And they're like if your key stuck in the ignition hit this button and you can release it.
And I'm like what the fuck is this like this was a secret button years long problem with my old car.
And eventually I got the free like recall work done and it fixed it all.
But it was like there were thousands and thousands of cars in America that had issues with that.
There went over a bump whenever a bomb and more.
Sorry I'm going to need a minute.
Give me a second.
Yeah.
I'll be just give me an hour buddy.
I'll be fine.
Or just weird like hey I was 20 minutes late from work because my car wouldn't start and then it released the key and then it started fine.
I think it was on cold mornings it would do this.
This is scarcely an improvement from the days of making zebras carry all your belongings.
No I'd rather have a hot foot in the cave.
It was simpler when I had a hot foot.
You'll be fine.
Yikes.
Wow.
So you're telling me that GM is not that the products are not always quality.
I just like what our beloved theme park told us.
Just saying.
I know it's American made but I haven't had any issues otherwise with my Honda you know with Honda Civic.
So I have I also have a General Motors beef which is related to a CEO.
It was like so who else.
Well first of all the history is very spotted of the CEOs.
I mean Robert Stempel seems solid.
We love Stempel.
We're going to cosplay Stempel.
We agree on that.
But the guy before that the CEO when this ride opened was Roger Smith.
That's Roger and me.
That's like the guy in the movies about.
Yeah that's who started Michael Moore's career and killed Flint Michigan.
And yeah.
And so you would get you they would hand out pamphlets telling you about the fine GM products that don't die immediately after going over one bump.
And there's like a smiling photo of Roger Smith as the like probably you could have the movie was out and you might get handed this pamphlet.
So weird there.
But then the first.
OK.
So I went and found a this was an internal GM magazine employee newsletter or something called News and Views.
And this is from 1982 when Epcot opened when World of Motion opened.
And this was just an article right.
And it said the very first line of the article was Walt Disney would have liked Alfred Sloan.
Like that's an interesting assertion.
Who is Alfred Sloan.
I guess anyone reading this if you work for General Motors you know who that is.
So let me do a quick Google.
Oh Alfred Sloan the first CEO of General Motors the beginning of this lineage that leads to Roger and Stimple.
OK.
So he built the company into what it is today.
Oh his Wikipedia has the headline criticism.
What could there be to criticize him for.
Oh Nazi collaboration.
Ah so the first CEO.
The story here is that GM also owned a German auto manufacturer called Opel and Hitler is starting to gear up in the 30s and some shareholders are saying hey maybe we should not be running Opel anymore.
What do you think Alfred Sloan.
And he said we have no right to shut down the plant.
In other words to put the proposition rather bluntly such matters should not be considered the business of the management of General Motors.
Then a year later the invasion of Poland began the Blitzkrieg and all of the trucks used in the Blitzkrieg were built by General Motors.
Oh my God.
One year after he said don't worry about it shut up.
So just to remind you where we got how we got to that guy.
The phrase was Walt Disney would have liked Alfred Sloan.
And within five seconds I got to Alfred Sloan built all of the artillery for the invasion.
What was the Nazi scientist guy that was affiliated with Tomorrowland.
Oh in the in the opening day special.
Well we're we're in a brown brawn all the like Operation Paperclip all the scientists they got out of Europe and then ushered to America to work on weapons or start NASA.
Yeah a lot of them show up in Disney's like documentaries and Tomorrowland stuff.
Yeah.
It's just a stone's throw away.
Always a stone.
Yeah.
See collaborators.
You think General Motors.
I truly thought they were going to be in the clear.
I thought you were going to make the leap to Mercedes Benz or BMW because they have like those are German automakers that have like not great.
There's a section of the tour missing.
Oh right right.
Yes.
No somehow the American company found their way and they built bombers and landmines and torpedo detonators.
And apparently this guy did not resign from the board throughout the whole of World War 2.
And again Walt Disney would have liked Alfred Sloan his best buds Mickey Mouse and Pluto and Alfred Sloan.
And then a more innocuous CEO Harlow Curtis he didn't do any work with the Nazis but after he retired he was on a hunting trip in Canada with his retired vice president of GM and he accidentally shot and killed him.
What is the hunting trip but we're hunting ducks and then he killed his own former vice president.
Vice presidents shouldn't go on hunting trips is really what you're saying.
On either side they're going to do any vice.
Yeah they're going to shoot somebody in the face or they're going to get shot in the face if you are or have ever been a vice president.
They're not go hunting.
You'd rather be a moose on it out in the field than a vice president.
That's it's just it's why they're not president.
It's why they're vice president.
Poor aim notoriously poor aim.
For sure or for aim from ducking away from a bullet.
Yeah.
Aim poor aim on both sides.
Or get invited on a hunting trip.
I always ask are any vice presidents coming along.
Raise your hand vice presidents raise your hand.
Or they have great aim and they have an axe to grind.
You know also possible very possible.
Yeah use these hunting trips as cover.
We're on to you vice presidents of the world.
We know.
Is there a vice president of Disney right now.
I don't know if we know the who's who.
Well we'll keep an eye on them.
Anyway so these are some of the great people who are bringing us this attraction.
But it's just you know this is how it goes.
We've run into this many times.
You have to there has to be horror shows of human beings to finance our animatronics.
If we start talking about some of the stuff in the ride this has been alluded to already.
The high volume of animatronics.
Crazy.
This is this could be a record that world of motion has.
Now it depends on the source because I've seen a lot of things that say one hundred and eighty eight animatronics but I've seen some that low ball it at one hundred and thirty.
That might have to do with figures like one hundred thirty of them are human.
Yeah proportion and then the rest are like objects or I don't know if chickens count.
So it depends but let's give them the benefit of the day and say one hundred and eighty eight which is crazy.
I don't know a lot of these numbers.
Pirates one hundred nineteen hundred nine on imagine one hundred and fourteen America sings.
We know that one had a ton.
Hundred sixty three in Sinbad or beloved Sinbad in Tokyo.
So this might be the record of an audio and try that's a lot almost two hundred.
Yeah that's I that feels like maybe it's just because it hasn't been around so long but I was like I was shocked when I was like yeah this thing has the most robots.
It's really crazy and then little little for the 40th anniversary of up cut.
Let's give this this park some credit for what it did to the robot population of the earth on just the day that it opened.
So that's a let's say one hundred and eighty eight just for world emotion.
Then and then you start thinking about the other rides.
There's a ton and all of them.
We do it fast.
American Adventure 35 Listen to the land 35 Universe of Energy 34 Spaceship Earth 63.
I'm not sure about all these.
These are you know their estimates so we'll fuzz it.
Kitchen Cabaret has a lot 28 while horizons not opening yet or not open yet on opening day.
So let's just October 1st 1982 a conservative estimate would be three hundred and eighty one.
And it might be more it might be north of 400 on a single day.
I don't think we have Epcot center for all the ways that we love Epcot for the crazy architecture and the ambition of it.
Sheer robot count.
That is nuts.
A single theme park 400 robots.
God.
Yeah.
Is anything ever come close.
Nothing will come close to that again.
Yeah.
No scenario.
All parks are we're going to get cool rides here and there.
But we you know one of the only things where I might agree with you Mike and your otherwise grotesque breakdown of transformers versus.
Rise of the resistance.
We do give you know like we're impressed that there is you know 30 animatronics on something.
But when the bar 40 years ago was almost 200 and 400 in a single park.
What have we done.
What what's happened to our.
This is what they took from us.
Yeah.
We have to go back.
I I would have given even make audio animatronics great again.
Yeah.
Maga.
I want to give a more specific note for or accolade to world emotion a lot animatronics in the post show area in the what they call the trans center which is what Ron DeSantis supporters called Disney World as a whole right now.
It's their favorite.
It's one of their favorite activities after only frothing at the mouth and posting on next door.
This is our favorite things to do.
But yeah there there was there was a lot of stuff in the post show area looks pretty fun.
Yeah on this.
Oh yeah.
There was a robot and a bird doing a double act.
You know I think that count that I get I think if if it's one hundred eighty eight I don't think that even counts it doesn't count burden.
I think that takes it up to one night and then original animation at the water engine theater.
That's a weird show.
That is weird.
Part of me wants to do a second gate just on the post show Eric just on the trend center.
But I don't know if it's needy enough.
It's can I just read the I found a I was I guess looking at 80s magazines.
Listen to this was this one I think it was called like industrial design magazine was really mad at this post show which is called really water engine.
They hated it.
They hated the whole park.
They actually they said GM takes the prize for vulgar excess with its ride through the history of transportation.
And one of the things about it is a truly nasty multi screen exhortation by a macho cowboy portrays anybody working on alternatives to the good old combustion engine as a creep a crack pot or a wimp.
Oh yeah I'm not endorsing the message of water engine.
I was just impressed by original animation for like the walk by post.
Oh the end of the animation is all really fun.
But yeah they're not.
I mean I think this guy.
Why are we using say nasty and nasty very nasty post show.
Let me tell you that it is that is technically the premise though is that a cowboy good old American cowboy says well nothing's ever going to beat the engine and then seven weirdos show up to provide all possible alternatives to the engine.
And then in the end he just kind of sits there calmly and is like yeah not engine though.
And they're all like yeah you're right.
He is he does give them credit.
He's like if anyone can pull it off I'll happily endorse it but I don't think so.
And it turns out that glum cowboy was right.
Besides the plug in the begrudging plugins we have nowadays.
Yeah yeah especially the show is called water engine and the one who says what if there was an engine powered by water is a.
Igor lab freak like he's I know it was our engine.
He's like Peter Laurie voice.
Yeah yeah yeah he's like like he's one step away from being put in an institution.
So that's how crazy a water engine even though it's the name of the show.
What else would a weird kids you want to stick around for water engine we got water engines starting in four minutes.
I'm tired but water engine.
I don't care about dinner reservations let me just watch water engine one more time.
I can eat at home I can't watch water and.
In the Guardian the new guardians right queue and I really love the post show what water engine.
That's my favorite show video to watch.
Oh God and the all and concepts 2000.
Where he showed you what cars might look like and how they might respond to different.
Wind speeds love God awesome.
Oh so sweet.
Someone was mad at us when we posted that and it's like oh sorry this world famous actor doesn't know as much as you 30 year old guys.
And it's like we are we are we're cold of that person.
Yeah.
Yeah they got square.
We're not I don't think that was the criticism I think the criticism was hey man maybe read over the script on the card of the.
Maybe give it a pass a couple of times and ask some questions if you're not sure.
I think that depending on the level of style not cutting them a break but you know having worked at Funny or Die I know the.
The the pressures of the.
The celebrity is here for precisely nine and a half minutes go go go and it shouldn't be that way the rides people should be excited to be on the rise we're going to see that forever.
But I have a feeling that second takes are always tough if it's an A-list star I think I think that like.
I think Pratt was probably like looking at the door that's where his eye line is he's like the door is open and his car door is open.
And as soon as cut is called he is barreling into it.
Yeah he's in the middle of changing shoe he's got one shoe on one street shoe on one costume shoe on and then they're like oh we're not going to see your feet doesn't matter.
Look I guess I'm just a little naive I'm just more like all right everyone we're putting on a show like.
I don't like it's definitely not good.
I the only thing I could say about it is sympathy for and you know what I know from a different podcast that another a Lister will Smith that he was like they had no time with him on men in black.
Yeah and I don't approve of his slapping but he did give it his all with his one take performances in the men in black alien attack ride far pre slapping.
Those are that's the will we want back.
J. J. L. is lines Jason's acting like on that Hulu commercial that's airing right now they didn't say all right we're going to try it again and Jason goes no I'm good.
I did my one I'll be back in the trailer I'll be at the I'll be going to get a breakfast burrito.
Give me some cards put up the cards I'll do another one if you give me cards real big.
A lot of running you know it's running and gunning in a heat wave to shooting outside on a hill and take Sheridan.
Well it wasn't it wasn't when the heat wave was the worst though you're right it was hot but it wasn't sorry it was only ninety five it wasn't a hundred and five.
It is a difference now.
I guess I would you the day where you were very stressed out because of the swimming we haven't seen the swimming yet.
No there's a bunch of other stuff that was shot I think just for social media just for like Twitter and Twitter and Instagram ads.
It was so funny that we were texting you about stuff and then you were flustered and like I'm guys I'm sorry it's just it's been a lot of swimming and.
I'm talking about hours in a pool hours in a pool like it was and is it like.
It's like a lot how crazy is the swimming like I just you know even in an inner tube just shredding water and then paddling back to one.
Lake paddling back to set word like on the side of a pool and like you know you think that be fine but it's like oh the way they need it the background to be we're in the deep end.
So like I'm like holding myself up and your dog paddling little kind of yeah a lot of dog paddling.
Are you a lazy let me ask you this are you a lazy river guy.
I am a lazy river guy usually okay.
Yeah I love I'm a big lazy river guy Scott ever been in a way I ever what are your feelings on it yeah I love lazy rivers.
Oh I love a lazy river yeah but that's a lot of the pushing for you and so so you're saying that when you were in the inner tube it wasn't you weren't but first sitting with their legs out because that's the most no no no human could be in.
I know I was step into it you were like this and pull it arms over and then other people were sitting in it but even then they're like all right with kind of got a paddle back to the camera mark.
Do you think what is your guess when the commercial comes out do you think that it will be clear the amount of effort that was put into the swimming or are we going to watch it and it looks like there's no way there's no way it's clear.
No because most commercials whatever you whatever you give and whatever everyone was laughing and it's the best one it's just the fastest one is probably what goes in because you're you're judging by seconds.
So this is not going to seem like you were in a Greg Lugina's biopic.
No.
Hey it's not it wasn't clear in the Wendy's commercial that I had to do stunt driving that they sprung on me about an hour before it happened you know so I'm sure it's not going to be very clear of all the swimming Jason.
Yeah also again I'll say this was one of the most fun shoots I've ever been like this was like a delightful and everyone was very good and stuff.
You hear that Hulu.
I.
So he said it.
I hear him again.
We're delighted.
Make him the face like my feet were bleeding my.
Almost ripped my swim trunks off.
It's almost naked like that swimming and singing to the cat.
The brand new not my swim trunks wouldn't have been my choice necessarily swim trunks.
They couldn't afford a good string ripped right off on the show.
I couldn't say that.
OK OK.
So let's let's say some ride stuff.
We said hi and I'm trying to count.
Who do we like.
Who are our guys who are fake guys in this ride.
Well I will say for your theory of like stuff blending together.
Yeah I didn't remember exactly that it was in this ride but the sea serpent looking into the guy's telescope the goofy look and see sir I had no idea which one that was.
But glued in my mind.
Clued in my mind like I mean I knew the traffic accident was in this scene because there's cars everywhere and a horse and stuff.
So that one is great.
That's neat. It's like possibly Columbus or a generic explorer.
I don't know but looking like the idea was that like he has this telescope right up to that almost like the black pupil is filling the entire telescope.
So he doesn't even know there is a full giant dragon.
Oh that's.
Yeah.
Is that possibly the full gag.
I mean it's like it's fun no matter how you slice it.
That's cool.
I like what you get cavemen.
You know what I was going to say this in.
I think this justifies our how we feel where they all blend together a little bit for us.
This is from an imagineer.
This is from.
Oh why can't I find it.
Geez.
The guy was Tim Delaney.
That's right.
Tim Delaney who was the star of this documentary about Space Mountain in Paris.
He was a bit like kind of pioneered the launch in a way.
The ultimate launch queen.
Tim Delaney.
He he worked for Imagineering and worked on a lot of these rides.
And this is from the defunct land podcast.
Kevin interviewed him.
And this is an imagineer saying this that he just kind of flippantly says.
Well you know a lot of that early Epcot stuff it's like basically all caveman to space shuttles.
So even he is like OK it's another one where it's like see things were very simple but now they are very high tech.
And he said his specialty was the future stuff.
That's what he was really into.
So I maybe have to credit this guy with a lot of the very good.
And I think he had a lot to do with that ending the future city center core.
He designed that I believe.
So he was like the Epcot future design guy in which case he has my heart.
But he said I didn't mess around with the cavemen.
They had good cavemen guys.
They were they were covered on cave.
I love that. That's like when Disney says we had good fake rock guys like cavemen was like there were people who specialized in that.
And are there cavemen in every one of these.
Probably not horizons but.
Yeah I guess not.
Oh yeah.
But it's definitely space ship Earth.
You go back right.
Pretty far.
Energy.
Universe of energy.
Is that just dinosaurs.
Well there's dinosaurs.
Yeah.
Because they they would be accurate cavemen were not around when dinosaurs were around.
This is kind of a universal reference point of like the earth in the past pre pre man or pre modern man you know pre modern civilization.
Yeah.
And those are I like the caveman.
The guy blowing on his foot because it got all.
Sure.
Hot and.
Scarred.
I want to shout out the pig in the hot air balloon.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
I mean that should be a go.
I mean I guess it's just because it's not around but that should be like a big thunder mountain goat.
I feel like pig in the hot air balloon.
Pig has got a real kind of creepy grin on its face.
You got a couple of pigs correct because then you got the one of the more memorable tableaus is the the guy in the white Mark Twain suit landing in the mud.
And there's pigs around him.
Another pirate's gag is a very similar pirate's gag.
Yeah.
This guy seems like he's in there not by choice whereas the pirate in the slop seems like he loves being there with the pig.
He wants to be there.
Yeah.
I mean there's still there's still kind of inventing the modern Disney dark ride animatronic loaded up dark ride you know.
But yeah it's yeah.
Another.
I mean the robots are good.
I don't want to make it seem like I don't like this because there's so many good robots like the newsie boys and stuff that come later.
Yeah.
Oh the ice picking boy.
They're picking apart the big block of ice.
I like the.
There is the just married car and then the car full of reality college students.
That's what college students did for fun in the past.
They just put too many people in a phone booth or too many people in a car.
But there's banners above the one there's projections going on at the same time.
There's banners above the newlyweds that say Vanity Fair Vanity Fair referring to the phrase.
I looked this up on Miriam Webster dot com a senior place characterized by frivolity and ostentation.
So this was a phrase before the magazine Vanity Fair.
That's why it's called that.
But the weirder banner I want to talk about above the college kids there is a banner that says college humor.
Oh yeah.
I think that I think college humor was maybe a magazine before the one that we know.
Before.
Yeah.
I saw that in some article.
I think that jumped out of me as weird.
Yeah I think that name may have existed.
Humorous frivolity like of the piece with Vanity Fair it feels like like look at these outrageous.
They've all got letterman jackets on and they're sitting on the top of a flagpole.
Can you believe the youth.
But it did not overlap with the website.
It was not.
There were no further.
They didn't reference a streeter.
There's no no no.
Zack Oyama baby Zack Oyama came along after this ride.
Yeah yeah.
But here's what I would like to talk about which is the you get into the flight is taken off.
There's a lot of which also is confusing because you have that Delta dream flight that gets into it's the crazy history of playing that is like 1920 stuff and weird barnstorm and planes.
So there's probably memories we all have that we think are in this but are actually in Delta dream flight.
So it's still goes to Magic Kingdom 2 but this does have a woman who's really impressed to be next to a real barnstorm and pilot and I just have this on my computer.
I don't have it.
Let me get it on camera.
But this is like does this guy who has the aviation cap and a mustache and this guy always kind of scared me and if he's in like Epcot promotional videos he scares me.
I think his his his face is so sharp.
It's a big sharp chin and a big sharp nose.
He's too big.
The other animatronics in this ride are really realistic and then he's he's scary.
He's like the fiddler.
She looks like a 70s woman.
She looks like they're like they don't know.
Yes.
Like they don't know where Sible Shepherd.
Yeah yeah.
And then he looks like when Snidely whiplash wears a disguise with Snidely whiplash is trying to fool everyone.
So he makes himself look not like creepy and everyone's like oh who's this count.
Who's this captain of the industry.
Or this would look if Jay Leno was like wearing prosthetics for a sketch for a hidden camera.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
Look like this pilot.
And was that a nod.
I mean it was not a nod to the future of Jay's big dog.
Like obviously Jay wasn't well known as a car guy back then.
So it was just a happy coincidence.
I don't think this is a nod to at the time David Letterman.
Regular guest on David Letterman's late night show.
I don't I don't believe he is and they probably wouldn't put a mustache on him but maybe I don't know.
Might have been the inspiration though.
So sorry.
Miriam Webster dot com covered in Pinocchio.
I'm just realizing they're playing in the background.
This dictionary website covered in ads for live action Pinocchio.
So I guess that's what I've been looking up.
Well happy happy Disney Plus day everyone.
Yes.
Happy Disney Plus day.
I like so I like that there's a scene of the train a train robbery.
So we're learning about motion and we're also learning now because of the invention of different modes of transportation.
We learn also that you can be robbed in transit to someplace on one of your favorite modes of transportation.
So I honestly think they should have stuck with this and shown robberies happening on every different type of transit.
Who knows maybe someday robberies on a hovercraft.
Yeah like a future robot comes down with a laser gun.
People's hands in the air.
I just a very funny thing to put in the middle of like the positive.
I mean it's I guess it's a gag because there's like a guy in a fun like little suit.
And I guess you could say that I don't know.
I'm just gonna say that maybe they're rich people so he's robbing from the rich but I don't know.
They're not really indicating I guess they're not indicating class or status.
I really see the size of the money bags.
No but yeah I know it's like presented as comical but then the guy there's a guy who has a gun like an inch away from his face and he is shaking.
That's his animation is he is trembling like way that would actually the more you stare at it you have a choice to make flip a coin.
It would be like on Carousel of Progress if he's like well you know my identity was stolen again.
Folks what happens is someone takes your Social Security number and then they start they take all the things and they can use your credit cards and then you have to get it back and it's a long process.
Boy do I not like my identity being stolen.
Oh my that's right.
That's progress I guess.
Cost of progress.
You know I didn't like it happening but I did appreciate the progress.
So noisy around here with the next door neighbor out Philanine Burton Schreli has gone off to jail.
He's moving out.
He's got a special album though that's still in the house only one of a kind.
The scene rotates.
Well this is progress Martin Schreli out of jail starting something called a Web 3 company.
I'm still trying to just log on to AOL.
That's progress for you.
Each scene just is about Martin Schreli.
What does the future hold for Martin Schreli.
Oh due to the agreement with the contract because the United States government now owns the Wu Tang Clan album they are free to release it as there was only supposed to be one owner.
Uncle Orville invested too much in a theory and the crash happened mere weeks ago.
So needless to say Uncle Orville has no money left.
He did it all on a smartphone.
No privacy at all around.
This isn't our house.
This is a set that we snuck into and then security guards show up.
Oh crap.
Got to go.
Hey kids.
Lost the house trying to buy GameStop stock and then Robin Hood app wouldn't let me take my winnings out.
Movie pass seemed like a good opportunity at the time.
They also laughed.
It's a great big beautiful tomorrow.
My new job at Quibi will last forever.
They're flipping videos two ways now.
Who'd of thunk it.
So yeah so it is interesting to see to see that portrayed in that way on this.
Yeah.
Oh and well I got something about the train robbery.
So well this is something to say you know this is a lot of animatronics and this ride disappears in 1996 very beginning of 96.
And you don't just throw one hundred and eighty eight animatronics in the garbage.
That doesn't seem right.
They were trying to find some other purposes for all of them.
And I remember strongly I think it was later in that year or could have been 97 that the first of the umpteenth pirates redo's happened.
And where the headline of it was the women are chasing the men now.
How will society ever continue.
But I went on it when it reopened and my main thought was are those the animatronics from the world of motion.
I don't know if they're still there all of them but like they added extra animals especially there's pigs.
I believe your beloved pigs I think showed up in pirates somewhere and maybe some chickens.
I think some of the chickens went to the ride Goofy's barnstormer.
Oh OK.
They had chickens popping up in the barn.
There's some characters who they added.
I don't know what they're doing in pirate but like in world of motion they're pulling on ropes to control horses and donkeys that are getting out of control.
And I think similar stuff's happening in pirates and they just put like pirate rags on them.
So at least some of these characters ended up in pirates.
But there's one that and I've only found one source saying this so I don't know if I believe it.
This is just the website Walt dated world dot com and they said that one of the animatronics when this ride closed moved a few feet over at Epcot center and was repurposed to become the Ellen DeGeneres animatronic in the bizarre redo ride Ellen's energy adventure.
Wow.
I could not.
I really tried to find other sources on this and I couldn't.
But then I was like I want to figure out if there's any truth to this.
So I started looking at animatronic.
There's a lot to go through with one hundred and eighty eight.
I'm like looking for posture basically as I said there's there's robots that are pulling a pulling a rope.
And if you remember Ellen that's a big if if you remember the Ellen robot she has a big branch and she's trying to either feed or fend off a big dinosaur.
So I'm like was it one of the rope holding ones.
No I think there's there scrunched too much and they ended up in pirates anyway.
But there's why I have one candidate and I want to see if you guys think this could be Ellen Jordan can you pull up the photo Ellen.
This is the only possible one to me and just hear me out for the listeners.
So Ellen is holding a big branch.
This train robber is also holding items not one big item but a hat to put money in with one hand and like taken a chain robbing a piece of jewelry with the other.
And then the legs are bent at a similar angle not very that's not like a 45 degree.
That's just like a little three degree bend.
And maybe I'm just thrown because the hair is a little similar like it's kind of dirty blonde.
And then and it's like like khaki shirts but you know they could they redressed the animatronic I'm sure.
Am I crazy.
Is this the only this is the only one I think that possibly could be Ellen in hiding.
Well I think a couple of things I have questions on.
Yeah one is how customizable are our movements.
Because the our movement in the train robber is like doing two different things.
It's got the gun it's got that.
Ellen is holding the branch very low much more different position.
Absolutely. But think about this the hands are constructed to be holding something and maybe you just move them down.
You just sweep move them down and then reprogram.
I bet that's possible.
I think that's OK.
But Jen but they didn't have to remold hands and look at the angle on the left hand.
I think there's like a little bit of an elbow bend.
Yeah that's true.
I'm thinking about what I remember from Superstar limo where Drew Carey was a robot that was holding a bunch of maps to the stars homes and they got converted to a monster zinc robot that's also holding a bunch of pictures that say have you seen this child.
So I'm using that logic like OK they probably if it was holding something it also still has to be holding something.
But I think you could move those arms down.
OK. My other question then is with the bank robber what's under the bandana.
Did they finish the face.
Oh yes. Do you finish a character's face.
If what if the hair looks pretty similar.
What if they did the math and said I think that could pass for Ellen.
All we have to do is put kind of female features on the lower half of the face which right now is just pure robot.
It's just pure.
There's just no skin under that mask.
You make a very good case.
I think it seems very possible.
It doesn't seem that crazy.
But again I only saw this on one.
I think it's either either this train robber is hiding out as Ellen to get away from.
They're on the lam posing as Ellen or this fact is not true.
And this was a custom Ellen degenerate robot.
However this robot has always been very bizarre correct.
Very bad.
It would have to be reused.
I was explaining all of this to Aaron and saying OK so I have a theory.
Now what do you think.
And I pulled up a picture and I said OK so here's Ellen.
And she said OK now show me Ellen.
And I was like no no that's Ellen.
Wait the one we're looking at right now is supposed to be Ellen degenerate.
Yes yes.
This is the after I'm showing you.
And then she said please also put pants on please.
Why must you conduct all of your business.
And put the cat down for God's sake.
God please.
The boy the boy learns from watching his parents.
He needs to know the anatomy you'll have one teaching him a lesson at all times.
Ellen looks like Lady Elaine Fairchild from from Mr.
Rogers.
Oh yeah.
That big version of that Mr.
Rogers puppet.
Oh yeah.
And thank you Jordan.
Yeah yeah that's it's very like that also stern.
That was very scary.
In a stern look.
That that does sound like a dun dun dun.
Yeah that's a like it's terrifying.
There's almost like very scary.
Yeah.
I mean there's kind of like a like there's like a 70s horror movie.
This it's taken the brow is so like is it.
Am I just thinking of like Yul Brynner in Westworld.
Probably.
I just have eyes or the dinner scene from Texas Chainsaw but like a distant relative
of leather like a grown child of the corn.
Yeah.
Stuff stuff where they were like you know we have a hundred dollars to cost you the
seat.
So just put some putty on their face.
Anyway if anyone knows this this might be another like this this could be like a
gem in land.
I don't know if they listen and if you do sorry I've done impressions of your
voices once in a while and if if you aren't listening somebody get the words.
I would I'm really curious if there's any truth to this.
Well look Len took on the J.
Big case so I think there's a decent chance he's listening.
I'm pro bono detective work out of one.
Yeah.
So Ellen also the train robber.
I feel somebody out there knows this fact and we got to find him.
We'll figure it out.
Will we won't figure it out.
Someone else will figure out.
As you said the first time it's easy.
Yeah.
Like we can we can solve any mystery with someone else solving the mystery.
Exactly.
Did you guys catch that when when this ride closed in 96 it caused a chain reaction
it caused horizons to open back up.
Oh oh.
Like a few weeks down to a people leader right.
Yeah they were down too many attractions.
So like I think it was something like the 23rd or 24th of December like right around
Christmas they reopen horizons.
So for a while they had both open for the Christmas rush.
OK.
And then in the new year they close world of motion for test track which was of course
then a pain in the ass because it kept not working.
And there was just no ride for this this section of the part that side of future world
that it's so rough for a while still does.
Yeah.
Well the only reason I wouldn't say that is because they have guardians now.
But oh that end of it.
But the other half of it.
Yeah.
Boring Ellen ride with this with this framing like this Ellen who's going to stab you with
this tree branch and then rob you.
It's still got the robber instincts.
And then these two really like problematic rides in their construction in the rides
functionality not due to racism or anything.
I don't think.
Yeah.
Right.
Mission space or test track.
I don't believe I think they're those two.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
Unlike a lot of rights they're in the clear.
Bad area though for Epcot.
Yeah.
While it did this ride purely close because we have an idea for a thrill ride and that's
the.
Well I think what it was was I mean GM you know they had the first sponsorship contract.
They renewed it.
There's an economic downturn around the time that that is being renewed.
OK.
Early 90s maybe 92 about and then they kept doing one year contracts like we'll keep
sponsoring.
OK.
It's still going but we'll keep sponsoring.
Which was like good for Epcot because everything did the 10 year and then bailed but they at
least kept doing little renewal.
GM still the sponsor never went away.
They've just Chevrolet is the more specific line is sponsoring it but still GM.
And so I think after some year long contracts are like we want to keep doing it.
Could we get something new in there.
And Disney was like well we are missing a thrill ride and then that's when they make the
connection like what we did you did show us your test track.
Gotcha.
Is there something there.
Yeah you know yes.
And then which isn't a bad thought but certainly the first few years even the first decade
of Epcot I was looking up what were Disney's thrill rides were first Space Mountain and
Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
The earliest one of those was 1975 was the first I believe that would have been Space
Mountain at Disneyland.
They got into thrills very very slowly.
Yeah they got in very slowly.
So like it kind of makes sense that it took Epcot a while to get a thrill ride because I
don't think they were thinking about like oh yeah parks need to have dark rides and
thrill rides and show like they were still you know figuring out what this is.
We just need slow moving trips from caveman days to an optimistic future that the
corporation sponsoring the ride cannot make happen.
Yeah.
There is a funny one of the cars at the end looks like the Tesla Cybertruck.
Yes it does.
Yeah like very very similar.
Very similar.
I don't know the Tesla Cybertruck offhand.
Oh it's a really angular.
Everyone says it looks like polygon like early PlayStation 1 car.
You realize.
It's so pointy.
So the pointiest car.
That's the one where Elon Musk said he was he was on stage and he said that the windows
could never break and then he hit it with like a big hammer and then the window broke.
Yeah.
It's like a QVC blooper.
Yes.
That's madness.
A high profile QVC blooper.
I think some people speculating because they're like oh there's no rear view mirrors on
the sides.
It's like aha there's cameras and everyone's like what the fuck are you talking about.
Cameras break all the time.
Yeah what if.
I think I don't think we figured out something better than mirror yet.
Is it long.
As long as it has a secret button in case the key won't come out then I think it'll be
already.
No no.
But Saturn Ion.
It's guaranteed to get caught on fire that fire departments cannot put out.
That is the special kind of Tesla type fire.
Yeah.
It's not normal fire.
It's futuristic fire that it's harder to put out.
No.
New types of fire.
We're excited about that.
That's my attempt at a new one.
It's pretty good.
Doesn't he.
He does kind of ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
He like laughs weird right.
Yeah.
That's yeah.
No it's hard.
I've tried to do him before and it's not.
I can't do it.
That's that seems close to me.
That's that's pretty good.
They're clipped and.
That's close.
I'm going to get.
There's another weird car that they showed off called the lean machine.
That's in the show and it's called the lean machine not just because it is very thin.
It is a one person car.
Aaron described it as looking like a motorcycle with a house.
Yeah.
Like it is.
It is because you're reclined.
It's like a recumbent bike.
But then it's got like a little pod on top.
But also it's a lean machine because you lean.
It's like it's the same idea as the segue where you're using your own balance.
So you like you know turn your legs in the way you would on a motorcycle.
But you're also steering.
And this thing just looks like it's a tin can like if anything like a large dog landed on top of the car you would get crushed to death.
Yeah.
I will say a lot of proof of concept stuff a lot of you know blue sky thinking sort of stuff in the post show area.
Yes.
Much more fun and optimistic than a lot of test track.
Yeah.
I current test track post shows just like hey everyone here's the new Chevy Malibu.
Oh yeah.
Here's the current model Chevy.
There's a saturn eye on it.
We should post photos of your saturn eye on it.
It was a very reliable car.
You know I still think you drive that.
I'll see it on the road sometimes and I go oh Jason.
Oh no no I don't have it anymore.
Because I am so.
You get your hopes up.
Jason.
That's like a dog waiting for an intermaster to come home.
It was very specific.
That's like your Batmobile.
Color green.
I loved that color green.
It was very easy to find parked on the street.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
We'll find some photos.
I was going to say I think if you quizzed me in 90 whenever whenever test track test track open I would have definitely said oh good world.
This is much this is so cool test track is awesome.
But in hindsight not not as good as this right.
I think.
Huh.
Yeah.
I mean I would I would definitely love if this was here today.
I was thinking how insane it would be if like again we're recording this on D23 weekend.
We don't know what they're announcing but if they announced imagine this hadn't happened and they announced what we're going to do is build a 15 minute ride about the history of transportation and there will be one hundred and eighty eight robots in it.
Go what in the world now.
That's what's happening.
And what for what IP for what Marvel.
No no no no nothing.
Leonardo da Vinci is in it.
Does that count as IP.
There is a man on a flying carpet.
Apropos of nothing.
Aladdin esque.
Yeah.
So yeah I don't give a shit.
I don't need to I don't need to fall into your IP trap.
I'll give them a lot of credit in the post show and the building out front a lot of good colored lighting.
Yeah.
Oh and this building is a shape of a wheel.
Uh huh.
Yes.
So that's fun.
That was on purpose that they have stuck with.
There was the outdoor track which you do get in test track was there was a plan for something like that here.
Where it goes outside.
Well I think they were talking about building a second ride.
The early blue sky stuff is interesting where it was like a much bigger atrium or like yeah yeah Martin's is really good.
Yeah.
And he also was overall that I watched a ride through.
Kind of a grainy ride through on YouTube and I was like I wish I found a better quality one.
Most of the Martin's vids is a recreation of riding this ride cutting together people's home videos and it is incredible.
Like if we gave him all the footage he could probably reconstruct the JFK as he could answer.
He is so good at constructing like every angle of a scene from like people's grainy super eight and VHS.
I found the I found home movies from the CIA with very clear plans and it's very clearly murder plans.
George H.W. Bush standing right there clear as day.
He was in Dallas that day.
Yeah what's the other thing about world of motion.
I mean just for my taste.
Yeah.
The first car accident the first traffic accident scene.
Lot of good old timey nonsense ice truck a bus label Jitney.
Still a lot of Jitney is the old timey name for buses or trolleys sometimes taxi cabs just back in the day.
And a lot of the small like Jersey shore towns that have been like vacation towns for 100 plus years still refer to like the Atlantic City.
Jitney has been running for like since 1917 consistently.
Is your old timeyness a product of growing up around there where it's more of it like the remnants of it are around more than California.
Well yeah but then yeah there's there's a lot more remnants around and then also like the early Disney stuff all of the middle aged people referencing the past in these rides.
Then just embed in my brain.
You learn a lot about the 19 the early 19 years from all these up from this.
You know the bugs bunny doing Humphrey Bogart impressions or the Marx brothers just in the stands of a Mickey cartoon or something.
And you hanging out and growing up with the other little rascals of course.
Yes that's true.
Yeah.
When you hear the phrase 1964 World's Fair you have a little cowlick that pops up.
That's right.
I drank my polio medicine and now I get to go to the World's Fair.
Three.
Another thing about World of Motion haven't mentioned yet a very good icon.
I think a top tier Epcot icon.
Yeah yeah it's hard to rank them they're all good but that one has a dot in the very center as if and it's like making centrifugal force happen around.
You know what they're doing the idea of motion.
Yeah.
This forward momentum within the little circle.
That's another rank.
I love them so much.
That's another rank trying to rank the original Epcot icons.
We could do that.
You know that.
Yeah.
OK.
Happy anniversary.
Yeah yes.
And here in one more before we wrap it up maybe I think this is an iconic scene and one that I like which is the the invention of the wheel and this idea that there's people are pitching other wheels and the other wheels are hexagons and triangles before you get to the to the good old roundy.
I love the idea that that's how that's what happened like they made it as far as we're going to have a cart we're going to have like a little room but a room you could move.
And now what we need is a stick and a shape.
So what should the shape be.
And then people go off and say OK I think I the stakes are high they're going to execute me if they don't like this.
Yeah hex a hexagon.
Now star maybe a star.
Five points.
All right.
So I made my wooden star.
Let me see if it moves my tiny room forward.
It doesn't.
Maybe they'll just like the design of it.
Maybe I can sell it anyway.
All right.
I'm late for my meeting with the king.
Better get over.
He's going to be going to poke both of my eyes out with his pointy hat.
If he doesn't like my my moving shape.
Yeah.
But then he went like really abstract with the shape and like designed a new shape.
Oh yeah really bad.
Yeah.
Just like weird jagged there's still no name for it.
I like that the three guys with the other shapes are like losers.
They have like poor posture and they're nervous and like I don't know I'd like that on paper.
And then the wheel guy is like hot.
He's taller than them.
He's confident he's swarthy.
He's got just like a beard just like I find General Motors employees and executives.
You look your best.
Think your best.
The cars you make perform their best.
That's how it works.
There is a good idea.
People with the best ideas are always hotter.
That is just like being represented here.
Just like Elon Musk.
That's right.
That is correct.
Say what you will about it.
My man's a fucking stud.
We saw those pics.
We all got those alfalfa cowlicks popping.
Blowing.
All right.
I think we made it.
Or throw in any thoughts on this as we go out.
But you survived podcast the ride.
World of motion.
Happy 40th birthday Epcot Center.
Thank you.
And we say this with love.
Thank you for all your boringness.
Because people say keep Epcot weird or whatever.
But I say keep it boring.
I get nervous with these roller coasters with.
I you know what.
I like the poor line read.
That feels like I agree.
I said it before that that's better that it's bad.
But it's funny.
Yeah.
Well if we if we want Epcot to be at least a little boring in a fun way.
And what better way than seeing an A-list actor get bored while saying his own
line.
Yes.
Will that age into the next generation of thank the Finns.
Will that be caught like people.
Whatever his quote is.
Yeah.
Like his nervous hesitation before saying yeah the veggie veggie fruit fruit.
I think so.
I was going to say the last thought I had.
Well do you want to do the plugs then I'll give my last my final.
Yeah let's do that.
I'll throw these out.
Hey so.
Oh thanks to engineer Jordan Katz here at forever dog.
Thank you Jordan for everything.
And hey you can find us on all the socials at podcast the ride.
Merch is available in our tea public store for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode which you the
audience votes on on our new tier club three.
We'll find all that at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Mike I was going to say you know Ellen they gave it.
There was a there was a time we talked about many years ago in the universe of energy
which started as a much drier ride and then they asked they added Bill Nye added Ellen
to it because those are 90s icons.
But I mentioned him already but was there ever an idea let's throw Jay Leno on this
thing to save it.
Well he was an Epcot.
Don't forget there was that little thing in intervention.
Yes.
Where you could be interviewed by him on this which imagine 10 year old me I'm like
biting my tie like watched it and learn the rhythms so that I wouldn't be any
downtime.
We got to do that as an episode too.
Yeah we I'm sure you could find somebody's footage of it.
But but you know Martin Short or many people had multiple appearances in the park.
So it really I mean you could definitely come up with a Leno sort of hosted world of
motion where he talks about you know the invention of cars and that would have to be
even longer because he could he would stop at every car and tell you like no this was
you could do Seinfeld.
You could put Seinfeld in there too.
But you could have all the 90s car guys.
All new clothes.
Yes.
Modeling clothes.
If it was still around now there would be that would shut it down to put Seinfeld's new
clothes on him that are in that photo shoot that just came out.
I since Leno has come up I texted you guys right before we started recording.
Bethy Squires who we've met before is a good writer and she posted about how learning
about Jay Leno has been voicing a character in the Mickey Mouse cartoons for years.
Oh you don't say I see it.
Yeah I'm excited.
Yeah we're the character.
What do we know.
I don't we will just have to find out.
Oh OK.
Well we will know it's not weird or I don't think it's weird.
I think we'll just literally have to find out.
Oh no that was literal.
Yeah.
All right.
OK well we'll do that and get back to you.
But for now the episode's over.
So is over so long.
Now I think it's a super Conan.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason
Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to
our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.