Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
I'm here, I'm ready to soar.
Yeah, and you are, Jason Sheridan is not.
This is another no Jason.
No Jason, yeah.
And I'll tell you why it is due to his deep
and longstanding hatred of astronauts.
He's been very vocal about this ever since we met.
There is one area that he just has a lot of ire for.
Yeah.
And it's, as he's put it, and Frank,
I'm glad he's not here to go on the tear himself,
but as he's put it, filthy astronauts.
He is no fan of them.
Well, he likes mission space more than we do
because he felt like you shouldn't need to be an astronaut
to go into space.
He felt like it was elitist.
Oh yeah, and it kind of democratizes the experience.
Well, that's because he's always been kind of anti the elite
in the top 0.1%.
And I think he puts astronauts in that category,
which I don't know if they are monetarily,
but in terms of experience and just what they get,
the access they have, which is to the moon
and space stations and such.
Well, he sees that suit they wear
as a very fancy sort of status symbol.
And he said, why can't you just wear cargo shorts
on your way up to the moon?
Yeah, and we try to tell him it's more of a technical thing.
I'm sure some of them would love to wear sweats,
but he's just not having, I think he was raised with this,
maybe it might be from his parents.
It's hard to say, but he just,
we told him this topic and he said, never.
He got upset.
Fuck no.
The other ones were due to,
we lied about the other one over the COVID was part of it,
but this one, he just did not.
Yeah, we woke him up.
We woke him up, we said Disneyland Rocket Man.
He said, no, he went right back to bed.
We live in a monkey style apartment altogether.
Mm-hmm, yeah, we didn't talk about that enough.
The monkeys from the 60s, not some.
Not monkeys.
We are not in a tree house.
We're not in a zoo, we're not in Animal Kingdom.
Not fictional band, but put together band.
The same way One Direction was.
The fabricated band, you might say.
That's too much judgment to put on the-
Too much judgment, they belong
in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
I said it five years ago on this podcast
and I'll say it again.
You remember saying it.
I remember saying it, yeah.
Because John Daly told me no.
Oh, wow. That's what I remember.
Oh, that's fascinating.
I don't remember this at all.
Yeah, I said monkeys should be in the Hall of Fame
and he goes, no, TV show.
Is he just saying that they belong in the TV Hall of Fame?
I don't know, maybe that's what he meant.
I'm not sure.
It gets dicey because so many other people
wrote some of it and you know.
It's almost like the Hall of Fame
is confusing in a lot of ways.
There are a lot of people who are in the Rock and Roll
Hall of Fame who have like three songs.
And the monkeys have a lot of songs.
A lot of good songs.
A lot of songs they wrote.
Singers, there's a lot of great singers
in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
So I feel like that alone.
You think you need to be able to play an instrument?
No, no, I'm saying if singers are in the Rock and Roll
Hall of Fame that don't write their songs.
Oh.
Then the monkeys are more than qualified
to be in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
Yeah, that's kind of an unfair judgment.
Yeah, that's all.
They aren't even on the ballad, I don't feel like.
Never.
It's so far out of.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Well look, you know how I've never seen Toto in contention
and that makes me angry.
That's a little elitist thing.
Every year.
That's a, there's a lot of elitism in there.
Todd Rundgren, of all the people I like to talk about,
Todd Rundgren got it and didn't go.
Right.
And they played a clip saying,
they played a clip of him saying,
if elected I will not serve.
And then that is what happens.
A man of his word.
A lot of people don't like it.
Steve Miller did it but doesn't like it.
And the Black Keys regret inducting him, they said.
Because he was a jerk about it?
Fuck the Black Keys, I don't care.
Yeah, that's annoying.
We regret the Hallow dolls.
Yeah, yeah, shut up.
That's a lot going on with that one guy.
Bernie, make some more music
for barbecue restaurant commercials, why don't you?
Very rich.
Okay, that's not what we're here.
We are here and we better save the topic sooner than later
because it's a little bit of a confusing one.
It's the Disneyland Rocket Man.
And I want to say this.
You might be looking at this episode title and tweet
and maybe there's some photos from black and white
or the 60s and you're going, this is boring.
I will sit through this.
But I'm not excited about this one.
Well, if that's your attitude,
let me quote another famous rocket man owned by Disney
named Luke Skywalker and say this.
This is not going to go the way you think.
That's a little tease because there is some stuff
happening in this episode.
There are some rabbit holes, there's some weird wild stuff.
Yeah, of course, rich little.
That might be a Dana Carvey invention, I think.
Weird wild stuff, Johnny Carson maybe never said it.
Like the Regis I'm Out of Control.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dana invention.
And Arnold didn't say, I want to pump you up.
These are stories we hear every week
when we both listen to that podcast of Dana and David Spade.
Yeah, yeah.
Here, let's do a quick,
I'm gonna do a quick impression of that.
You start, be either one of them that you want.
Okay, oh yeah, so.
Yeah, yeah, also I was,
I've never heard more talking over.
No awareness of who has the floor.
And then Lauren wouldn't let me do a commercial.
I want to do, I think talks about the commercial so much.
So different there now, you know,
because Lauren said I couldn't do the commercial.
I lit up so much of that I scared a dog.
Yeah, yeah, I swear every episode Spade talks about
not being able to do that commercial,
as if he didn't have every opportunity
to do every commercial ever since then.
Yeah, but it's haunted him and it's one of like
the only safe stories he can tell about the time there.
Oh, that's true.
They're both very on, they both don't want to like
give any good stuff.
Yeah, yeah, sure, yeah, they're hedging bets.
It's a safe batch of stories.
So it's easy to go wrong.
They aren't honest like us and are revealing Jason's.
No, no, no, no.
Hardcore astronaut hatred.
Yeah, no way.
Where were we?
Oh, Disneyland Rocket Man.
Yeah, look, there's twists and turns here
and I'm excited to talk about it.
Did you know what I was talking about
when I proposed this?
Yeah, my vision, when you said it,
the first thing I thought of was the opening of Disneyland
or the first few years or whatever it is
with the guy in the suit flying around.
Yes, yes.
That's the first thing I thought of when you said it.
And that is it.
That is what we're talking about.
It's very like early Walt era footage
of it's kind of pre a lot of the redo
and maturity of Tomorrowland.
Yes.
When there wasn't a lot there,
there's great old footage of a guy shooting up
on a real jet pack flying past the castle
and coming back down to the ground.
Yes, and I will admit, I think for many years
I thought this was fake.
I don't believe I thought this was an actual jet.
I thought they were doing this somehow with tricks.
I think they used this footage and recontextualized it a lot
and probably juxtaposed it with Mary Poppins.
Like it's a montage of the magic of Disney
and there's Mary Poppins flying,
which I'm sorry to say was fake.
I did know that.
Yes.
I was aware of that.
They did not build a rocket powered umbrella.
Yeah, too bad.
But this was real.
This guy really did this.
But I'm gonna come back to that.
I'm gonna put the pause button.
You're going the other way.
So now that we've established what that is,
I wanna say kind of how we got here,
why this suddenly seemed relevant to me.
It's because of a joke that I saw on Twitter
that I liked because recently there was this weird thing
where Disney was promoting the now beloved American
canon classic Lightyear.
And part of the promotion of this was that Lightyear
is in the park.
And I say Lightyear, not Buzz Lightyear,
even though that's the character's name.
But I mean current Lightyear because this wasn't like
a plastic molded, the toy that we've loved for many years.
This was just a guy, a regular guy.
And he had a wig to standardize the kind of regular guy
he was.
And it was inexplicable.
Like it's in your timeline and I'm staring at it
and like, it doesn't look like Lightyear in the movie.
It's just a, it's a man.
It's so, this is nothing.
What is this?
That's like, just like pick like somebody
you went to high school with and now they're in Disneyland
waving.
It's still a cartoon.
Lightyear is still a cartoon.
Yes.
And he still has kind of a big
bulbas. Exaggerated features.
Chin and neck.
Yeah.
So I would say that plastic would still be in the cards.
I think, I think representing him as just a guy
is really confusing.
I agree.
But they tried to make it seem like that was a live action
movie, right?
In Andy's universe.
Well, yeah.
And this is the question.
I think, I think you've answered it,
but I've been asking people just to get full clarity
is the idea that Andy's, when Andy,
a human being in the Toy Story world,
he goes to a theater and sees other human beings playing
Lightyear and Commander Hawthorne or whatever
the other characters are.
Have you seen it?
Did you see it?
I've seen some of it on Disney Plus now.
Oh, it's on Disney.
I didn't realize it's on Disney Plus.
Yeah. Yeah.
I've seen a little, I watched a little of it
and tried to see if the boy was into it
and he handed me the remote so fast.
Really? No, no.
I mean, he does that every day.
Okay, all right.
I was gonna say this is the first time he's ever done it.
Very patient otherwise.
No, it's, yeah, I got through some of it,
but do you know what I'm saying?
Like what, so it's not, like it's not a cartoon to Andy.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
But then what that opens up is that there is this guy.
There is a, like, it's not Chris Evans.
There is a man out there in Andy's world
who went and played a character.
Yeah, there's an actor that, yes.
Yeah.
He would be a fan of that actor.
And who's that and why don't they say his name?
And is he still around in Andy's world?
Is he had a right wing turn like Tim Allen?
Right, well, turn, you know.
I don't know if there was ever really a.
Started to be more vocal about his right winginess.
His laziness, yeah.
It's a good question.
I think that's, that is what ended up happening.
I think that, honestly,
I don't think they were thinking that hard.
They were just like, let's do a new version
of Buzz Lightyear.
And then it was like all this like,
and I could totally be wrong,
but then they have to retroactively go,
well, okay, what is it?
Like, what is it in relation versus like,
like there's plenty of, there's a new Spider-Man cartoon now
and it's like, well, it's not in the canons, whatever.
Don't worry about it.
Yes.
This is just a light year.
They just made him,
the Evans tweet set off a firestorm.
I think I've said this before.
That set off a firestorm of logic policing.
Yes.
Because there was no reason for it.
It's like, oh, it's light year
and it's a new version of a different voice.
We all understand that.
It's an action adventure inspired by,
we know that there was a property.
What was it?
Let's look.
And even that I got where it lost me was,
it is 1995.
They say this at the beginning of the movie.
In 1995, a boy bought a toy.
It was from his favorite movie.
This is that movie.
And then it begins.
That's too specific.
It can be inspired by,
but when you tell me that that is a movie from 1995,
I have a thousand questions now.
This is like when I saw the Beatles cover band a week,
like last weekend and fake John was telling a speech
about real John.
That is so funny.
The lie he was like, he sat down.
He's like, you know what?
There was a man who lived a while ago
and you're like, is he talking about,
is fake John talking about real John?
And he believed in love and peace
and wouldn't it be nice if we all,
and I'm like, fake John is doing that.
What's the logic of this?
John can't talk about John being your character.
Why do you need to say like, I believe in peace and love.
Why not?
Yeah, it's you.
What do you mean?
Right.
And then he was, he even said something like,
you know what he was,
and he was senselessly murdered.
And you're like, what?
I mean, I guess it's weirder if he says it.
And then I was killed.
I was senselessly murdered.
Have you ever wondered what if my music wasn't popular,
but a guy in the 2010s did it instead?
And then he came and found me and I was an old man
who was wise, but not a hit musician.
That would have,
there were more questions with that as well.
But this is just the way he was presenting it.
I go, why don't you just play Imagine?
Because he was going to play Imagine,
which by the way also doesn't make sense
because not a Beatles song, then it's a Beatles cover band.
Did the other Beatles play?
Yes, the other Beatles played on it.
I mean, Ringo was playing,
what were they wearing?
Because they were doing Sergeant Pepper outfits
right before that, but I think they switched.
But Ringo plays drums on Imagine.
Oh really?
I didn't know that actually.
So, Ringo is the only one,
fake Ringo is the only one who should have been there.
The rest should have left.
It should have been like something that I heard
that they did in a Spice Girls reunion tour
where they're up on platforms
and then they're about to do one of the songs
from when Ginger was gone and then she's lowered
into the ground and then came back later.
I actually really like that.
That's really funny.
I mean, there's a lot of bands with that problem
with a member that was gone for many years.
Yeah.
And what do you do?
I think mostly just throw them in.
I don't think it has to be addressed
other than when there's death involved.
Well, if Ed Robertson would get over whatever it is
and it lets Stephen Page back in the Barenake of Ladies,
there's gonna have this issue as well.
You somehow, in referencing the Barenake of Ladies
in every other episode, have never said Ed Robinson.
Robertson.
Yeah.
Okay, so that's new in the-
I'm mad at him.
Well, for Jason, it's astronauts.
For you, it's Ed Robertson.
I don't know who these men,
but I believe that he's the reason
Stephen can't come back.
I think Stephen hurt him too much,
and I understand that on some level,
but the band needs to be together, Ed.
I have a good backstage Barenake of Ladies story
that I'll tell you after this.
All right, fair.
My catch then, Sader.
Anyway, so point is, there was a light year in the park,
and he was just a guy, and I saw a tweet that was like,
this is just a guy in a space suit.
This is like they brought back the Disneyland Rocket Man.
I was like, oh, that's funny, and that, oh, that's right.
There was just a guy in a space suit, and that was it,
and he would fly around in a jet pack.
Then I realized, wait a minute, these are different things,
and we have to give a little bit of mention
to the other thing, which is not,
the Disneyland Rocket Man is not the Tomorrowland Space Man.
That's different.
That was an opening day thing.
Actually, they did that, I think, for 10 years.
This jet pack guy was only there for three weeks.
You heard me, I got confused earlier.
I said opening day, it was not the jet pack guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, that's a separate, that was just like a limited time run,
a jet pack guy is gonna fly around.
What they originally had was just a guy
in a big heavy space suit walking around,
which was apparently exceedingly popular.
People lined up, it got people away from attractions
that were malfunctioning, like, oh, get the space man out,
that'll distract him.
It's a really funny, like, sci-fi, 50, 60 sci-fi outfit.
Yeah, do you got a picture in front of you?
Yeah, it's the biggest though.
Oh, great, that's the hugest helmet ever.
It's so funny.
He's got a round, giant, clear helmet,
but then he's also got, or no, I guess it's not a hat.
I'm confused by the geography of it.
He's got like, it's almost like it's like a globe,
and then there's like sort of an exoskeleton around the globe.
And then it's hard to tell if he's wearing kind of like a nun's habit
or if it's just like something that's part of the actual helmet.
I don't know, I can't tell.
And then he's kind of got, I would say like,
like Goldar or the Green Ranger, like kind of a,
I don't know how would you call it.
You mean like the bubble collar?
Yeah, like a metallic shawl or something.
And there's like four, there's four like kind of like poofy tubes,
like poofy tubes.
Yeah, so he has a bunch of pool noodles attached.
Yeah, and they don't look, yeah, the idea I'm sure is that it's like
providing oxygen or something, but they look,
they don't look like they have any use.
They don't have any practical use.
Nah, it's just for comfort, I think.
And then yeah, he's got, it's all silver.
And then he's got kind of a belt with what's, I don't know,
like a piece of metal stuck there with some bolts attached to it,
which I guess it looks like a transmitter,
like there's two antenna coming out of it.
Oh yeah, some like little doodad bog.
There was just a probably Bob Gurr tossed that together in 45 seconds.
Guy, he's like, oh, gotcha, what do you want?
Some Buffett voice for Bob Gurr.
Oh yeah, he's also got, excuse me, on the helmet,
he's got kind of like an antenna too, like a fun alien,
kind of like antenna with two little satellite things.
It's a fun, silly 50s outfit.
Just a great classic.
Yeah, from this very sci-fi era, they were starting to dream of space,
but man had not been to space yet.
Down to where, apparently, the word astronaut had not been invented yet.
Oh wow.
Jason's wish.
They, like, that's how new all this was, that they just, well, what do we call it?
I don't know, spaceman.
I guess it's a spaceman.
Yeah.
So this guy would walk around.
Actually, why he showed up originally is that there was a weird tomorrow,
we got to do a weird Tomorrowland episode at some point, like early Tomorrowland.
There was a thing there, I think we've never talked about this in the show,
it was called the Kaiser Hall of Aluminum Fame.
No, we've never talked about that.
And I did not get that order wrong.
The name of it was, it wasn't the Aluminum Hall of Fame,
it was the Hall of Aluminum Fame.
Wow.
It was devoted to fame within the arena of aluminum.
Man.
So that was this aluminum company called Kaiser,
and they wanted a presence in the opening day festivities and television shows,
so they got this spacesuit together and they called him K7, the K for Kaiser.
And he was around, and there's even pictures of Eddie Fisher and Debbie
Reynolds, like shoving a Coke down this guy's-
Oh, I've seen that.
We might have talked about that in the opening day.
Yeah, we've talked about that.
Yeah, well, that's who that was.
That was this, this was the spaceman, also sometimes known as K7,
until Kaiser ended the sponsorship.
I liked this story.
I've referred before this book from David Koenig about like all the people
who worked at Disneyland in the first year.
This is from that book.
So opening day went great, and then Kaiser called and said,
hey, can you keep using that guy?
Have him like walk around and tell people to go to the Hall of Aluminum Fame.
And they're like, yeah, I guess so.
We don't have anybody to do it.
And some employee like, hey, we need you.
And they strapped the suit on him, which weighed 66 pounds.
Oh my god, it doesn't look like that.
Not at all.
It looks crappy.
Yeah, it looks really, it looks like Halloween store flimsy.
Yeah, the helmet must be heavy.
Might all be in the helmet, because the helmet is huge.
Yeah.
So here's how this story is told, which is great.
They got the guy in the suit.
OK, we just need approval.
So you need to follow us backstage.
And this guy walks in this heavy suit.
It's so hot.
It's middle of July.
And like, OK, go in that house.
And then they walk into this house.
And the spaceman, the guy in the suit, walks up and sees a guy sitting at a desk.
And his eyes are bloodshot.
It looked like he hadn't slept in a month.
And then his handler says, hey, Walt, what do you think?
And Walt says, fine, put him in our land.
And puts his head back down.
Wow.
So Walt approved this.
And by approved, I mean two seconds of delirious.
What?
Yeah, whatever.
I don't care.
Grunted at him.
That's so funny.
Blah means good.
We've learned this.
That's the scenario I described with Jason earlier.
We woke him up and we went, argh.
We're back to sleep.
Well, that was Walt, apparently.
And so off of that, there was this guy walking around for years.
The spaceman had to be six feet tall.
They had to be very imposing.
And then that also became true when they added a new character, the character
Space Girl.
You ran across Space Girl as well.
Space Girl is not protected from the elements.
Space Girl has some magic ability.
Yeah, she's like a character from a Godzilla movie or something.
Like those magic, there's like magic twins that show up.
Yeah, right, right.
It's that kind of like she looks like she could fly.
There's a cape.
Yeah, she has a cape.
We're out of the realm of practical, like, futurism here.
Space.
Like, I don't think any division of the government is working on capes
and turning turning ladies into superheroes so they can fly into space.
They should be.
I agree.
I'm just saying.
Actually, you know, kind of what actually the episode is about
kind of harkens to that in a way.
It was like a sillier time.
Yeah.
For the government.
And then but then, like, you know, you could be realistic
or you could have a pretty gal show off for games.
And while the her games are on display, I don't want to be vulgar,
but it is the second case.
So we said gal and games.
Yeah, this is look, it's something for dad, I guess.
Disneyland.
You know, we should go check out Space Girl, see what she's up to.
Don't you think, kids?
Dad.
Yeah, so I guess that is probably what the thinking was.
Well, we can't put a lady in a space suit.
Also, there's probably the sexism of the time.
Lady can't be an astronaut.
Yeah, probably. Yeah.
You can you can't be a spaceman.
That's a job. You can be a space girl.
That's kind of like a cheerleader for spacemen.
Yeah, exactly.
So she is a cave like she's a cheerleader.
Yeah.
There was also a weird calculation that like, well, the space
people need to be six feet tall.
And that applies to the women as well.
And thus there was a woman who worked.
She was a greeter in the Carnation ice cream shop.
And this I think was in that same book or was it?
No, it's on a website. It's on Dave Land.
This woman worked in the Carnation ice cream parlor on Main Street as a greeter.
Quote, it was quite imposing to see this six foot two tall blonde
asking people how many in your party.
So they said, why don't you be the space girl?
Interesting story.
The only problem being that it makes no goddamn sense.
What do you mean? What's the problem?
You can't have a tall ice cream greeter.
This only an outer space with this being true.
People are just confused.
Like, I don't see any people used to be shorter, I guess.
Were they my 50s?
That's I guess that's not that long ago.
Mickey Rooney recently, if I'm going by that logic.
But I think he was particularly sure.
I thought people used to be shorter.
Did people used to be shorter?
Well, this woman existed.
Well, yeah, that's true.
But like, she was an anomaly, I guess.
Huh? The average.
Why if humans have humans have evolved to be taller?
But since the 50s for the last 300 years.
OK, well, that's not that far off.
Yeah, that's 70.
So maybe they just weren't used to it.
Yes. So let's see.
You're defending the notion that you as I love that notion.
Off up your ice cream when you saw that woman.
Why isn't and she's not a space girl and she should be probably be a space girl.
Anyway, so there were tall space people walking around
and that went for a decade or so.
But then I don't know how it came to pass that they wanted to up the game
and they wanted to showcase some real jet age technology in the park,
especially with the cameras around.
And that's where we end up with not the spaceman, but the rocket man.
Rocket man.
A rocket man. The rocket man.
What this thing actually was, where we know this footage from.
This is a special from 1966.
It's called Disneyland around the seasons.
It is on Disney Plus, so you can watch it in very solid quality.
It is the last special that Walt appeared in.
It aired three days after his death, which I imagine must have been very
strange and disarming.
Immediately after the cold open, the very beginning of it
is this jetpack guy flying around the castle.
And then they use it again, kind of show it to you longer.
And then I feel like, you know, you just see this.
It's like it really represents like a certain era.
Yes. Old Disney.
We're shooting in color now.
It's kind of a kooky Jetsons past.
It's just it is cool.
Iconic Disney footage, I feel.
Yeah, no, it's it's it does feel like I've seen this more than some of the other
like one of the one of the top clips I've seen of Disneyland opening
or opening like 10 years, I guess.
Yeah, yeah. The top only number one, I think, is Walt and the big map.
The Epcot big map.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe not number one, but that's the one that I forget if I said in the
when we talked about the founding of Disney.
What Aaron is like, she's had it with the big map.
Big map. I have seen this big map.
We saw any funny that big map episode, though.
Oh, yeah. Just going through.
Oh, is that that must be where the conversation went. Yes. Yeah.
Let's talk about what was.
Oh, well, Aaron's not going to be happy.
We go full big map for a while.
That map is so big, it's like three space girls.
Too scary.
But yeah, famous footage.
Yeah. Reused a lot.
There was a thing in Tomorrowland at the time called the Flight Circle.
I didn't know this, that it was like it's like a big compass on the ground.
And it was surrounded by a chain link fence.
This is kind of like now where it's sort of outside of
a Star Tour store.
And, you know, it's where it's where the big marble ball is, where the fountain is.
Right. This was all a fenced off circle
where apparently children would test model airplanes just every day.
And they were very loud and annoying.
That's what Disneyland was like.
They would test them in the sense that they would like
people there wanted like a play test for these things.
And they just like kids like mess with them.
I think if you were a kid who was interested in model planes,
you were more than welcome to bring your model plane to the Disneyland Flight Circle.
It was a bringer kind of a thing.
I think I really know.
Could you fly a kite on Holiday Hill in the old days?
I don't know.
I guess there's not that much room up there.
Kites, there's like a is there an issue with because they don't want it
like if what's it made of and if it hits a power line?
I guess that's true.
I don't know if kites have ever been in the plane is going to hit.
A model plane is going to hit stuff.
Well, if I think we're talking like it putts around, you know,
a couple of feet off the ground. OK.
They hadn't experimented truly with height until the Rocket Man. Right.
Came into the picture Tinkerbell.
Oh, you Tinkerbell, I guess.
I don't know why this happened.
I don't know why they did it, but I guess it was a neat thing to do.
A cool bit of publicity.
So they pulled this thing together.
And the guy who
did the flood, the Rocket Man, the Rocket Man's name is Bill Suter.
Bill Suter.
That's who was in William Suter.
William Suter.
And he was the top
rocket man for decades.
Yes. This is what's interesting. Yeah.
OK. You look into the like if you've ever seen footage of maybe not jetpacks
in general, but a lot of if you just scan through, where have I seen jetpacks before?
If it very well may have been this specific thing,
which is actually called a rocket belt,
and it's got like two tanks on the back and then two little joysticks.
And you sort of blast straight up.
It runs off hydrogen peroxide.
Whoa. That's what I read.
Wait, isn't that like what you clean your mouth with?
Yeah, wait, yes.
It's a common household item, is it not?
Yeah. That you filled up the rocket belt with?
I'll double check it, but I'm almost 99 percent sure that's right.
That's the magic. As I said, it does sound fake.
It's weird. Well, double check.
But I'm pretty sure it is.
I don't know. I don't think that would have stuck with you if it wasn't true.
Yeah. Hydrogen peroxide powered rocket packs.
What?
Hydrogen peroxide power engine is based on the decomposition
reaction of hydrogen peroxide.
Nearly pure hydrogen peroxide is used.
Pure hydrogen peroxide is relatively stable, but in contact with a catalyst,
for example, silver, it decomposes into a mixture of superheated steam
and oxygen in less than one tenth of a millisecond, increasing in volume
five thousand times.
So I read now I'm remembering now what I read is that it's hard to get.
This method of jetpack is not used anymore because it's hard to get pure
hydrogen peroxide because like the stuff you rinse your mouth out with is not pure.
It's going to say they can't sell like explosive jet.
It's a little or yes.
Yes. In your mouth.
Yeah. Yeah. So his his what I believe was hydrogen peroxide based.
The ones he would use.
Wow. Weird.
That that really amps the insanity of saying so.
He's going to come and I thought this was fake footage for years.
I don't think it was said I didn't learn it today that it wasn't fake.
But recently, I think I learned that that wasn't some sort of visual trick. Wow.
That that there was jetpack is like people would say like jetpacks aren't real.
But then you look back and jetpacks have been around for 100 years.
Really? 100 years.
Like it looks like it.
Wow. The first jetpack or the other jetpack.
Yeah. I'm not sure if there's anybody as famous as Mr.
Suter. The first pack was designed in 1919 by the Russian inventor Alexander
Andreev. The project was well regarded by Nikolai Rinin and Arinin
and technology historians.
You V. Beer. You Cove.
Huh? Another Russian guy.
What was that like in 1919?
That seems so oxygen and methane powered.
Oh, my God. With wings roughly.
Yeah. So seems dangerous and surely.
So so yeah, like I it was kind of crazy when I learned that this was not fake
footage and that you like a jetpack exists because this is another one of those
things where you're in a kid, you expect this is the future because you watch the
Jetsons and you expect this to be the case.
Like, you know, in 10 years time, everybody will have one.
Yeah. And there's a common maybe overused joke of I want my jetpack.
You know, where are my jetpacks?
Oh, like they are.
The future is very boring.
My flying cars or whatever.
Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, there was an attempt made to the reason we've ever seen this
footage is because the U.S.
government, the army, yeah, legitimately was trying to figure out jetpacks.
Yes. To use in combat, which is so crazy to just imagine a war.
I don't know with who.
Well, at that point in time, the first one up would have been Vietnam.
So at that time, jetpacks or well, landing in a more recent jetpack thing.
There's a I'll show it to you after this if you haven't seen it.
But there's a new new version of a jetpack or newish version.
And the video online that's showing off what it can do is a person
basically leaving a small boat and landing on an aircraft carrier.
Whoa. In this thing.
Oh, my God. Which is pretty insane.
And I've seen some of these videos recently.
I've seen like water versions of the jetpack where you have like
kind of like Iron Man Gauntlet type things that shoot water out.
But there are still oh, yeah.
Newer versions that have just of jetpack was not water based.
Well, that's the I must at some point in the five years of the show reference
from my favorite videos, the starts right now.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
How there's a guy on a water jetpack who's going to open up the local news.
And he goes, all right, and it's live at five and it starts.
And then they hand it to the guy and he goes, it starts right now.
And then he gone on.
Now he just collapses into the dock and they zoom away.
They crash zoom out.
Yeah. To be ready for his incredible flight.
But instead, he just falls into the water.
But then they do the like action news and then come back.
And now it's working and he's flying with the most demented smile
you've ever seen.
So it worked out and they applaud.
I haven't seen that.
Oh, it's one of my favorite. Oh, God.
The one every any time I've ever seen a water jetpack out in the world,
I've said, oh, it's a starts right now.
Wow. I got to see that.
I don't think I've seen this.
Oh, wow.
So all right.
So there are versions of this.
This particular thing was the rocket belt.
This was the army went so far with this that they did a demonstration to JFK.
He watched.
Here's what a rocket belt could be like.
Issue was they could only fly for 20 seconds.
Yeah, yes.
Uh, and that's just not that's maybe not worth like the millions of dollars
to give all the soldiers shipwrecks.
Like, what does it really do?
Unless it's such a like a kid's idea of a war where like we have to.
There's a wall. We have to scale the wall.
How can we do it?
Yeah, I mean, I think unless you have like full Iron Man,
like you can go that fast, you can go that high.
You're that flexible.
I don't know that it makes a lot of sense.
If I'm putting my generals cap on here to strategize.
But I played video games.
I played video games.
Yeah, you've sent a fake man to die.
That's correct. Red Alert Command and Conquer.
Oh, sure. OK, OK. Yeah.
Anyways, so it just didn't.
Also, the way anyway, the way this guy Bill Suter got involved
is that they needed a just a guy to do it with no experience.
That was the requirement is that you have no rocket experience.
Not what Buzz Aldrin wants you to have.
All you need is no rocket experience.
He lived next door to the guy.
Oh, that was. Yeah, he lived next door.
The guy might think he mowed his lawn.
That's what I read. I went in an interview with him
and he was like, I just live next door to this guy.
Was that the interview promoting his one man performance piece?
One hell of a ride. Oh, my God.
I don't know.
I was like doing a speech called One Hell of a Ride.
Oh, I got to find this.
I got to find the article again.
So he just yeah, it had to because that's what it was going to be in the army.
It was just we need to give these jet packs to, you know, to dummies
fresh off the truck.
We got to like, all right, there's a rocket.
Can you do it? Go.
So he fit the requirement and in the process became the most skilled
jet packer around.
And then with this type of the rocket bill, like nobody's been.
There was one other guy maybe in the two of them were friends.
So any other thing, we would always be these two guys.
And basically, because the army retired the program,
it just became only for entertainment for this Walt Disney thing.
The maybe the most famous use of it.
Thunderball James Bond movie.
Sean, it's a Sean Connery era bond.
And he there's it's mixed with, you know, bad close ups of Connery pretending to do it.
But then there is practical jet pack footage and it's the same guy, Bill Suter.
And he's wearing the helmet and they tried to talk him out of the helmet,
apparently in the movie.
Wait, I believe that if I have the story right, is that they he's wearing
like a helmet in the movie and they were like, can you please take the helmet off?
And he was like, no, I want to wear the helmet.
Oh, you mean for like, oh, for like safe for his own safety.
Yeah, please.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Doesn't match the shot.
Or it's like he needs to.
Yeah. So wait.
So then they made Connery.
They felt like James Bond would not wear.
I got to go back and look at the clip.
But that's what he's saying is that they were arguing with him.
I found the quote about the he more more recruited his lawn boy
as a guinea pig joked suitor.
Oh, my God.
I don't know some dumbass.
I had some some kid, some neighbor, a bowl here.
His neighbor was Wendell Moore.
Yeah. So he was a 19 year old kid mowing this guy's lawn.
And they were like, hey, you want to get in the rocket?
You want to get in the jet pack?
So the world's going to lose another grass cutter.
Yeah. Yeah.
Would put hydrogen peroxide and put pure hydrogen peroxide in his kid's backpack.
Let's see what happens.
Pretty crazy.
And then what an incredible gift, because he became the only guy
who does this or, you know, it's two. Right.
So there's other and these these are not immediately familiar to me,
but incredibly prominent uses out in the world.
The very first Super Bowl halftime show
was this guy and his buddy flying around and again for only 20 seconds.
So that's not too much of a show.
But they were still figuring it out back then.
Hey, they were still doing Elvis Presto, the Elvis magician in 1987.
They were not quite at that.
Just a good band plays.
Yeah. Here, let me hear.
This is what he's in his own words on the James Bond thing.
His mission escape a Chateau's third.
This is James Bond. Third floor balcony.
Scoot over the castle wall and land near the waiting Aston Martin.
The director begged the flyboys not to wear their helmets.
It didn't match the shot of Connery, but they refused.
The March Day was chilly, which caused ignition problems on a second flight.
I hit cobblestones like a ton of bricks and bounced in the air.
So it told me it wasn't a pretty landing.
Is it in the movie?
I don't know. I don't know the sequence well enough.
I'm not really a Bond guy.
Yeah, I like Bond, but I'm not a Bond guy either.
Yeah, I don't know.
It cobbles.
Oh, I don't think they would put that wipe out in the movie,
but maybe it is in there.
They had no choice.
That's just what it was.
But yeah, it doesn't feel like Bond, like Bond would do it perfectly.
That's that gets smart.
Oh, yeah, yeah, right, right.
So anyways, these just use like an entertainer.
Yeah, Rocket Man.
He opened the 1984 Olympics.
Yes, which is awesome.
Yes, yeah, it was awesome.
L.A. Coliseum.
Yeah, it's so exciting.
That stage, which is the most like,
you know, Disney, the 80s, Goddy,
like, boy, the color uses at that thing already.
I love the 84 Olympics so much.
I didn't even know there was Rocket Belt at it.
Yeah, it's crazy.
For the Coliseum is huge.
There's so many people there.
It looks so cool.
And again, it's like now watching and I still have since it looks
just like that Disneyland footage.
I still kind of I'm like, that's it looks fake to me.
Yeah, because I was so used to thinking that was fake.
There's something about it.
I think it is such a like,
it does feel like some weird Lost in Space contraption or something
to where I think like the odd and the janky way it's built,
because it's not like beautiful, it's functional.
So it feels like a silly sci fi prop, which I think maybe makes you think
it's just for tricks.
I think it's that mixed with the fact that it's a pretty imprecise
feeling of flying, even though it is good.
And he's not like zooming up and down or whatever.
But it's not like it doesn't feel like it's on some like perfect flight path.
It feels like it feels like it would if you were just hauling a guy on a wire.
Yeah, it feels like this kind of weird thing, like it's being pulled by a wire.
Like there's something about the movement that also makes me feel it.
Make it makes it feel fake.
I think maybe I thought that this was some that they paired this up
with the Tinkerbell on the wire and that they also did a space man.
I thought maybe this was when they opened
people move a rocket jets, all that that well, then let's put an astronaut on.
Because it is so yeah, it does feel like smooth wire flying.
Right, right, right, right.
It's great. It's wonderful that it's real and that James Bond had a real
rocket belt in it.
It's all very magical and so silly that this thing existed.
But then, like, listen to what we're describing.
He does the 67 Super Bowl and the 84 halftime show.
I'm sorry, the Olympics.
That's not a lot right.
And the army's not using it.
I don't know what Bill Souter is up to day to day exactly.
But rocket belts are not exactly taking over the culture
until the early 90s, when some gentleman in Texas
made a go at bringing the thing back.
Do you have any idea any of what I'm about to say?
I was reading about the history of jetpacks, but I don't know.
I don't know at first blush, so I don't think I do.
I'm excited about it.
But I have more about what's his name, too, though, about Souter.
We'll get to the end. OK. OK.
Yeah. Well, he's look, I'm not done with Souter.
So you might have crossed over some of this, but I have boy.
Am I excited about what's coming?
So it's it's Houston, Texas.
It's the early 90s.
There is an entrepreneur who loved that thunderball sequence.
I described so much and dreamt of the day that he could make
bring back the rocket belt and do it better for real.
He paired up with an inventor, a scientific mind, whatever you want to call it.
And they and then and then a third partner,
they ran the operation out of this guy's failing stereo store.
And they figured out successfully
how to make a rocket belt that goes way past that 20 second limit.
This one goes 30 seconds.
Yeah, I did see that. I did see that. Yeah.
They made it.
And this one, this is the rocket belt of the future.
It is called the R.B. 2000.
I am. Yeah.
So the future is bright, right?
We figured out it's 30.
It's 30 seconds now.
We have everything we need.
The stereo store, we're bringing back the rocket belt better than ever.
And the only thing that brought down this operation is that every single person
involved was fucking insane.
This was did you find out?
You know what I'm doing? I don't know what you're doing.
I am. Yeah, you're telling me this stuff for the first time.
But I know that the other stuff. Yeah. So.
Yeah, I'm going to. All right.
I'm going to describe three guys and I don't.
The names are not going to stick with you.
I was going to get confused by the names.
So I'm going to tell you, yeah, kind of what they looked like.
One. OK, I'm going to call Silver Fox.
One is schlubby guy.
And then third guy, it doesn't matter what he looks like.
He factors in a little bit.
But just picture kind of like Svelte Silver Fox and then sort of
angry schlubby guy.
They fought all the time.
They fought over money.
They accused each other of stealing.
This operation was coming apart at the seams.
The third guy on the stereo store was addicted to crystal meth.
Schlubby guy accused Silver Fox of stealing money from the company.
And things got really heated.
So Silver Fox got a hammer and hit schlubby guy in the back of the head.
I do not see any of this.
They've got a belt of the in-fighting amongst the top
rocket belt mines of the early 90s.
God knocks him on the back of the head.
I don't know if it literally went straight from bang bang to this.
But Silver Fox flees with the rocket belt to not be seen again.
They don't know what happened to it.
Where's the belt?
The belt is gone.
And schlubby guy, this is like he's built all of his dreams on this.
He sunk his own money into it without the rocket belt.
I am sunk. I have to get it back.
How can I find out what happened to it?
Then it's 1995.
The Houston Rockets have won the NBA Championship
and schlubby guy turns on TV, watches the victory celebration
in which a rocket belt is propelling a man
from across a harbor or something in Houston,
where he lands at the victory celebration.
A 30 second flight. He did it.
The man's name, you ask.
Bill Suter, the Disneyland Rocket Man.
They got Suter. They got him.
They got the rocket belt.
I'm getting schlubby guy out of here.
I'm getting a hold of Suter and we're going to do the best.
We're going to celebrate the Houston Rockets.
Akima Lajuan, this is for you.
This is so funny because whatever I was reading left out the hammer stuff
because I know that Suter in the game there.
It's like I missed the interesting.
You did get to that part. OK.
Yeah, no, no, no. This was his final.
Right. But I was reading that it was because there was this
because there was a fight.
The Maxwell hammer.
A guy who was wrong.
He I don't know if he was stealing money or not,
but you shouldn't hit somebody in the back of the head with a hammer
and then steal your co-invention.
The rock. I agree. I completely agree.
Wow. So this tells schlubby guy,
oh, my God, it's out there.
I so all right. I have proof it's in Houston.
Maybe I can do this.
I can get this thing back.
But Bill Suter hands Silver Fox the rocket belt.
All right. That was fun.
Silver Fox leaves never to be seen again.
Not never. He's seen again.
Yeah. Rocket belt.
Bill Suter, the rocket man, never sees the rocket right again.
So schlubby guy is angry.
He takes Silver Fox to court and sues him for ten million dollars
and custody of the rocket belt.
And he will win.
I think maybe. Yeah.
After what he's been through,
John joined in the head with a hammer.
Yeah, they don't have to share.
I get it on weekends.
I fly on weekends.
No, you're just the rocket belt will be told what Silver Fox was like.
You don't know. You don't get to hear about your other daddy.
He's a bad man.
So he won. He won custody.
Silver Fox, you need to give schlubby guy the rocket belt and ten million dollars.
Instead, he stays away and gone and nobody can find him.
And he doesn't give ten million dollars.
And he certainly doesn't give the rocket belt.
So until one day, Silver Fox gets a call about a potential Hollywood
use of his rocket belt and he thinks, oh, yes, a job.
Showcase, the rocket belt can do.
He walks into some mansion and the four guys there are really edgy
and they grab him and put like a hood over him.
And the next thing you know, it this got Silver Fox is in a box.
Silver Fox is stuck in a box in a box.
The Fox is in a box.
My God. Kill Bill.
Yes. Yeah, it's really it's really close to being buried alive.
Jesus. It's terrifying.
This is by the way, I'm skimming a Wikipedia.
I'm seeing some stuff.
And then I saw the phrase trapped in a box and I went, wow, hang on back up.
And this is happening concurrently with member a few episodes ago
when I said I was listening to those women who were saying that Disney's
putting woke agenda into the movie and their friend forced to the right.
As that is happening, I'm reading the phrase Jetpack Man trapped in a box.
This is I am I getting covid right now?
Am I delirious? This is too much stuff.
So anyway, this guy is kept in a box for eight days.
He is not fed. He thinks he is going to die.
Yeah. And the only thing that can get him out of the box
is revealing the location of the rocket belt.
Eventually, it's revealed that if you can guess who was behind it, Schlubby guy.
He shows up with like a notary and like, you're going to sign this
and you're going to give me the rocket belt.
But they aren't looking at a certain point and he escapes.
He runs out.
He gets a hold of the FBI.
Oh, my God.
They get Schlubby guy and all his accomplices and they go to jail
for making Jetpack Silver Fox be in a box.
Whoa. Oh, my God.
All the craziest bullshit ever.
And I skipped one detail.
The third guy I talked about with the meth addiction,
who was also involved in all this at some point in all of these events.
He was bludgeoned to death.
Oh, my God. Probably by Schlubby guy.
I don't know.
You would assume, but it's not actually allegedly.
I'm not even saying that.
I'm going to second gate for this one.
It's you know, this is out.
This has been well, look, this story is out there.
Yeah. You can track all of this in an Atlas Obscura article called
Where Eagles Dare, the Jetpack Murder.
Oh, my God.
You can also look up an ABC news story from the year that this all happened.
They a news story that is narrated by ABC reporter Chris Cuomo.
Whoa.
Wow. He's like young and fresh, I bet.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Real eager.
And yeah, I'm going to do a good job.
Not weird.
And I just want to talk about the jetpack box.
That's wild.
Anyway, the jetpack has never known to this day.
Nobody has ever seen the rocket belt again.
The name of the episode Disneyland Rocket Man Bill Suter.
He said, I don't want any part of it.
I don't ever want to touch a rocket belt again.
I want no further involvement in the project.
It's not worth my life.
The so the quote I have from Bill, I don't know if it's in reference to that.
He said, this is so this made me so sad.
He goes, I'd like to keep the idea of jetpacks alive.
Suter said when we spoke, but I've become a nonbeliever.
So it feels like the death of the of the optimism of the 60s age of the space age.
Yeah, this is and this is really this is from this year.
This article is January 24th, 2022.
And I believe he's 77 years old.
This guy's going this guy doesn't have a lot of years left and he's going to go.
He's he he might pass with disbelief, even though we all saw it.
We've all we all saw it.
Even though we all saw it, we've all we all watched him at Disneyland.
Walt talked about it.
He did do it.
Do we think we could get him up in the air for like a live show of ours?
Whoa. Like, why are they doing this outdoor show?
Why did they think they could fill the Greek?
They must be losing a lot of money.
For sure, we will.
Oh, look, I'm popping away.
It's a 77 year old man in the sky.
Oh, my God. If we could say ladies and gentlemen, Bill,
so this guy's a fucking legend.
I apologize for cursing, but he is.
I think he let you.
He deserves that.
He rules. I love Bill Suter.
I love that he is just a cool guy in all this.
He's not in these fucking criminals.
Every one of them.
Well, I guess that no, well, you should.
You can't do crystal meth.
Yeah, that guy is a criminal.
Nobody deserved to die.
Nobody is.
Jog should be maybe decriminalized.
What's a drug should be maybe to be decriminalized.
OK, yeah.
But for his own sake, you probably shouldn't have crystal meth.
But you're right.
And I'm just saying.
Certainly shouldn't have been blood.
None of this should have had. This is all bad.
These three guys were just not meant for each other.
But that's not Bill Suter's fault.
He just got to fly around.
And by the way, if you're thinking that that story that I just described,
that sounds so crazy, I wouldn't believe it if it was in a movie.
That sounds like it could be a pretty interesting movie.
It was a movie in 2008.
The movie is called Pretty Bird.
You have not heard of it.
I have not heard of it
in the role of a guy, Paul G.
Amati. Wow, really? Yes.
We got to watch this fucking movie.
The ultimate schlubby guy.
I thought about the entire time saying, imagine like, I don't know,
a Paul G. Amati.
I thought that might be too confusing to track.
Apologies to the guy for calling him schlubby guy.
But also he did a lot of bad. He put a guy in a box.
Sure. Sure.
So that schlubby guy and in the role of Silver Fox, Billy Crudup.
Wow. Really?
This is a meeting of the minds that I am very excited about because I love G.
Amati. Yeah. Nilo Nimalato himself. Yeah.
Billy Crudup.
I had no particular feeling about until the last few years.
And I just want to say this.
I think Eva Anderson will join me in this.
If you are not watching
Billy Crudup's Emmy winning performance
as thousand toothed agent of chaos,
Corey Ellison, major executive at UBA on the morning show,
then I don't know what you're doing.
I don't know. Everybody's binging.
Look, I know Saul is around there.
Well, weeks ago when this comes out.
Look, there's been there's been a lot of shows.
I know there's a lot of shows.
Everybody's talking about seven.
But but just flip one over from Severance
and see a man with the most teeth you've ever seen in his mouth
and the biggest dream jetpack size dreams of starting up a streamer called UBA.
Check out truly.
I'm fascinated by Billy Crudup.
And now you're really high on this movie because of this.
I am unfortunately. I see it.
I watched the movie. I did rent the movie.
OK, it's pretty sleep.
I can see why nobody it's also got Kristen Wigg in it and just a thankless
kind of like and then you're the girl.
Like she doesn't know it.
She doesn't none of what we know Kristen Wigg for. Right.
This movie is written and directed by Paul Schneider,
early Parks and Rec cast member like that guy from the first couple years.
Couple years. Yeah.
He wrote and directed a movie about the jetpack murders.
Yes. Oh, my God.
So this exists out there. It's rentable.
If you want to watch that, do it.
If you want to watch Chris Cuomo tell the story
or if you just want to, you know, hear it the way we told it
with these disparaging names, not Silver Fox.
That's a guy I want to dress him up because I like Billy Crudup so much.
Yeah, I wanted to honor him with a cool name, even though he hit a guy with a hammer.
And there's the hammer, but you can forgive it because he's handsome.
He's a handsome guy. It's OK.
It's wow. The movie, the only it's so not interesting
unless they're saying the word rocket belt, which thankfully is a lot.
Yeah, yeah. Like that's it's G.M.O.T.Y.
like hugging crude up and like,
we could have been friends, we could have been friends.
You and I. Where's the rocket belt?
Where's the fucking rocket belt?
Like, that's all pretty good.
Yeah, that sounds good.
You say it's sleazy, but that sounds good.
So you're saying the rocket belt has not been found.
No, that right. Yes.
The guy answers the question by saying, you never know.
So we got to get suitor up in the jet pack.
We have to find the jet pack.
We have to find this jet pack first.
The rocket belt. Yeah, yeah.
And what's that?
Maybe can we would he come on with?
Should I say his real name?
I want to get everyone involved on this.
I mean, sooner we could probably get I think sooner we could get.
Yeah, he might want to avoid a lot of this unpleasant.
Brad Barker is the name of Billy.
All right. OK.
I don't know. He's not going to answer any.
He's not going to tell us where the rocket will talk about this.
Well, he might.
He might talk.
What if I don't know, just spit balling here.
What if you and I could get kind of like an enclosed space, like something small
and put that put Brad in it and like, I don't know.
It's not coming to me.
Like, can we put him in
maybe a box?
What did you just say?
We'd see that again. Maybe a box.
A box. My God.
That's the most brilliant idea since the invention of the rocket.
Hey, it just came to me.
There is now and now I'm regret.
I regret not looking into more of the different rocket
because I was going through Wikipedia and like there are some great names.
In 2013, Fritz Unger in Germany is developing a jetpack called Skyflash.
Fritz Unger from the odd couple.
Yes, Fritz.
So
Oh, Felix Unger.
It's almost there.
Almost there.
Flyboard Air invented by Frankie Zapata.
Like everyone's got a fun name that's involved.
Everyone's always got a good name.
Yeah.
There's Suter, the All Stars.
That's what we should. We should wait till we have.
Then we just weirdly, you know, you know, in Soarin,
that kind of humorless part of the line that's just kind of like a tribute to.
Yeah. Aviators.
Right. Right. That's we do an outdoor live show that just weirdly is like
they gave their lives for science and for man's dream to fly.
The audience is like, why?
What is with this oddly solemn?
And then a bunch of men come out and then we all give them pins.
They're meaningless.
OK, I've got a new idea to now for this show.
What we have to do is Jason has to start mowing Suter's lawn.
Oh, so he can pass on the tradition of jetpacking to Jason.
You there, boy. Yeah.
Now, is Jason significantly older than Suter was when he started mowing lawn?
Yes. Oh, yes. Yeah.
And is Jason be willing to mow a lawn?
No, not that I would.
One of these is not just maybe one of these newfangled electric ones
where it doesn't have the gas and it moves a lot easier.
But I used to mow a lawn once in a while.
OK, I pulled the thing and it was gas and give him a hydrogen peroxide
powered one, get him interested, because Jason would find that interesting.
Like, oh, and actually hydrogen peroxide powers this.
Yeah, it's like this rocket mower.
Well, if you're interested in that, why don't you?
I got something to show you.
And then Jason thinks that he's like a he's a crazy old guy, like Doc Brown.
Right. Oh, is this guy going to pull out a gun and shoot me?
And then, no, he instead he unfurls a sheet.
And there it is, the original rocket belt in all its glory.
Jason would love it because he's a hype miser.
That's right. Yeah. He would like it.
This would scare me, honestly.
Maybe I would do the water one, but probably not.
Could we get him in?
Could we do a live tandem
Jason and 76 year old jet belt legend
rocket belt legend Bill Suter in conversation
down at like the Disney concert hall or something?
Just to sit two seats on the stage.
Now, when you took the ultimate leap
of starting a theme park podcast with your friends, right?
How was it invigorating suitor interviewing mostly Jason?
Yes.
And questions.
Tell me about Scrapple.
Tell me the different flavors of Pedialyte.
Tell me about what they like.
How did you feel much better after the blue or the blue better?
Or was the darker blue better?
Yeah, all these are good ideas.
Hopefully Jason won't listen, but we'll we'll fill him in.
Well, it'll be his ears will be red when he hears us praising these dirty astro.
It's true. Yeah, that's a good point.
But there's man, there's so much more jet.
I feel like now I'm now I'm we need to look into more about jet.
I would. Well, this I think, look, we did it right.
We this was about rocket belts and the RB 2000.
We've closed out that unless we want to do a full commentary on the film
Pretty Bird, which we do, but certainly.
But that's the end of the rocket belt content.
But other jet packs, just jet packs, exclamation point, its own episode.
Absolutely. It's on. I want to show you this.
This is the newest thing on the Wikipedia.
And I have seen this video before.
The Daulis flight pack, which is the newest in like jet pack technology.
And I want to show you this video because it's insane.
And it's like definitely something Tom Cruise is going to be doing in a movie.
Right. Yes.
You have a McAfee support warning on your well, that's a Carlson's endless pop ups.
Whoa. That's so precise.
It's crazy. So you have like bullets on your arms or your hands.
And then it's like you also have them on your feet.
And this is a person going pro footage of landing on an aircraft carrier.
That's insane.
So it is like that's Iron Man shit.
That's like Iron Man. It's wild.
Whoa. Real life Iron Man like Elon Musk.
Exactly. A guy who's never flown around and won't.
Yeah, but he will say he's doing it.
And then there'll be a bunch of reasons he can't over the next year and a half.
And we already talked about this real life Iron Man thing with him.
But it's funny that like people focus on that he, you know, because he's rich and not.
So you don't think of the main
facet of Iron Man being that he flies around.
No, no, no, no. It's more about his holdings.
That's why just if purely if you compare numbers, like look at the books.
Elon Musk is a real life Tony Stark.
It's based on a joke.
Maybe it's no, it's not.
This was before that.
But there's a joke in Justice League where somebody asked Batman, what a superpower.
And he goes, I'm rich, which is a funny joke.
But people do. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Well, if you have enough money, you are you can build rocket shoes.
It's like just pure purely financially.
And I only mean I don't mean the car and the fighting clown men.
I just purely financially.
Jeffrey Katzenberg is the real life Batman.
Yeah, it makes sense.
He must think it's so funny because I think also he loves the idea
because he was in Iron Man two.
Yeah. And then I think there were a few years here was like really cosplaying
is that where like the kid like those people was the kids are stuck in the mine
or something or the miners were stuck, excuse me.
Oh, yeah.
They're minor stuck.
And he's like, I'll send them tiny subs over.
I'll send some tiny subs and send anything.
And then like the sandwich, the one guy made fun of him.
He called him a pedophile.
And then it's like just like tunnels will tunnel everywhere.
And everyone's like, oh, my God, this guy's are such a genius.
Meanwhile, the article just came out that he's never built like hyper loops.
All this is bullshit.
He's never going to build this stupid tunnel.
We talk about Twitter, Vegas tunnel.
Oh, my God.
This is the Elon Musk.
You are the death of Rocket Man Bill
Suitors dream, your reason if you put all of these resources
into a jetpack that can fly for 31 seconds.
That's right. And now then maybe wouldn't have to criticize you so much.
But until that day, I think the future.
I don't know. It's not as bright as it was that day in Tomorrowland
where Bill Suitor took off into the sky without a cloud, without even the cloud
of that a bunch of people will all murder each other about the rocket belts
eventually. And the pretty bird would not be released in 2008.
Despite a good showing at Sundance and due to the financial crisis,
there just wasn't really a market for it. Right.
So many bad the curse of the rocket belt.
And I hope it doesn't affect this episode.
I really hope so, too.
We can get out before it.
Oh, no, it'll be the one that is hot in this garage.
OK, well, then let's let's wrap it up.
You survived podcast the ride the second gate.
Thanks so much for subscribing.
And if you want to dig even deeper, join us on our new Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular
episodes ad free and typically one more host who will be back.
I think this is the last with no probably Jason, I think.
Probably less. He's so furious about anything that happened in any of these.
I just you know what?
That's a those jetpack guys.
That's a group of three that all started hitting each other
with hammers and trapping each other in boxes.
We have to make a pact to the three of us to not trap each other in boxes.
He's done it so far without hammers for five years, but I don't know.
I don't know when the breaking point is here.
Six portend when we run out of classic Disneyland rides,
that may be all hell will break loose.
Today's episode is about get him.
Yeah, that's right after we do the Space Mountain episode.
And then it's like all the chaos is pure chaos and violence.
Tell me the password to the Patreon.
You don't get out of the box.