Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains boundless ambiguity,
a wholehearted endorsement for a beloved
Southern California business,
and cheering, cheering, cheering.
We take a look at all the Disney Parks
announcements, air quotes, in our D23 wrap up
today on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a celebration of stories,
storytelling, stories about storytelling,
and the storytellers who tell our story to storytelling stories.
I'm Story Gardener joined by Mike Carl Story.
I'm here, yes, and I'm full of stories.
I'm bursting with stories.
I hate to be so vulgar, but when I go to the bathroom,
I make stories.
That's just how many stories are inside of me.
That's what we bond over, is our shared love of stories
and of eating stories and peeing out stories.
And having excess stories, wasteful stories.
Always better to have too many than too few.
Too many stories. Stories, that is.
Jason Story didn't see that.
Oh, and there's nothing, there's nothing quite like stories
and we're bringing them back.
We're looking into it very strongly.
We're bringing stories back and what better place to do it
than the boundless future that is this episode.
Oh, yeah.
A grim start.
Yeah, the chills just hit me.
If you don't know why all this is happening,
this is at least my, all of our general impression
of the D23 Parks panel,
which is the main thing we're focusing on.
But we're doing sort of a roundup of all of the Parks news,
the thrilling Parks news that came down the pike this week
that we've been looking forward to hearing at the D23 Expo.
We're so happy that everyone was back.
We weren't, we weren't back,
but we were back with our friends.
We were watching people be back with their friends.
For the first time in three years and what a thrill it was.
And we've got a language professor coming in
to tell us about the boundaries of stretching the phrase news
to fit what occurred the other day.
Which, yeah, maybe, maybe we'll learn that the,
it is, if technically, if new information of any kind
is presented, it might count as news
or that linguistics professor might teach us
that jack shit was announced this week.
We'll be debating that.
But besides that, also stay tuned because,
hey, it's the D23 spirit.
That means we have to get in the PTR 23 spirit,
our personal convention.
And while we wish we could be back with you in person,
we didn't figure that out.
We didn't rent a ballroom this time.
But what we can do is for the first time in three years
at the end of this episode, induct new PTR legends.
Get ready.
Will it be you?
Keep listening to find out.
I did think about inducting you as a PTR legend,
but then I guess I'm ruining now what you just said.
So I ruined the T's.
So the answer is not you.
You did not, at least, you're not inducted by me.
It's not the general you,
but someone could be listening to this who is a PTR.
That's how Griffin Newman found out.
He was just in a store or something.
And then he was like, wait a minute,
I got accidentally inducted as a PTR legend.
That's right.
Look, we don't necessarily invite everyone.
There's no luncheon.
We don't really provide you anything
other than being able to sleep at night
knowing you achieved something on this earth.
Yeah.
Which is a strange thing to say
because some of the previous inductees
have been milkshakes.
So probably a milkshake is not listening to the show
and does not need to care about sleep.
Jason talks about milkshakes so much.
I think there might be a few milkshakes that do tune in.
12% of our listeners are milkshakes.
I was thinking about inducting Papa Steve again,
just because there's some changes going on
that part of the book.
Oh yeah, yeah.
We'll have to see what happens to Papa Steve.
Well, that's one of the things.
Can I, I want to propose an idea.
Because we said we would do PTR legends at the end
to end on a fun note, positive note.
Do we want to start on a positive note too
and touch on fun things?
Negative note.
Okay, good.
I'm negative.
Brother, that's my instinct.
That's my instinct too.
I'm just trying something different.
And if I'm wrong, fair enough,
trying something different.
Whatever you want to do is fine.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
I was just joking there.
No, well, let's, I think let's try it.
Let's start positive, why not?
Yeah, go for it.
Do we have the materials to start positive?
I have a couple of things.
You go, you go, you have an idea.
Well, I think the one, I mean,
we were all tweeting as this was happening.
And I think, Scott, I think it was you tweeted,
like the Pacific Wharf redo into San Fransokyo
from Big Hero 6.
No complaints.
Yeah. It's fun.
I think that's neat.
I was saying to you guys,
I like a redo that doesn't desperately need to happen.
One that's just like a fun,
let's plus it up because we can.
I do like that.
And by the way, just in general,
I did this, you can watch this panel on YouTube still,
I would imagine.
We're mainly referring to the parks panel
that occurred on Sunday,
which was earlier in the week as you hear this,
in the morning hours of September 11th.
Don't forget, never forget the news that occurred that day.
So yes, that's a pretty good one.
That's California Adventure.
Yeah.
Turning the Pacific Wharf area
into a Big Hero 6 themed area.
And the Pacific Wharf area, by the way,
we've touched on some of this stuff.
It's where Ghirardelli is, the former tortilla factory,
the current bread factory, the bakery,
where you meet Papa Steve,
who we've been obsessed with for a little while.
Is it correct?
It's kind of a Papa Steve episode,
but not a bakery episode, right?
Correct.
Still haven't, we parsed those out.
Clock is ticking though on this place.
So we gotta get to these places
before they transform into Big Hero 6 stuff.
Yeah, yeah, geez, God.
They may no longer be playing those
Whoopi Goldberg, Colin Mochrie videos to no one
as they sprint as fast as they can through the,
like, how fast can we get through this
having already received our free morsel of bread?
Yes.
The Karl Strauss cart, will it be there?
Will it remain?
That was my biggest concern
because that is one of my favorite alcohol locations
in the park.
I don't see why.
My beloved big fishnet photo opportunity,
which the last few years I've just been delighted by.
That has been there for 21 years now.
Yeah, that was an opening day fixture.
Yeah, if you stand far away from it,
it looks like you are in a net, not just meant for fish,
but just, but swarming with fish.
Yeah.
Hundreds and hundreds of fish in it.
And you are the catch of the day.
I, yeah, I don't know.
Do those things have to go, is there enough,
if it's San Francisco, maybe it already
is San Francisco feeling.
So do they, is it now just a matter
of injecting the Okio part?
Yeah.
Maybe they just have to up the Tokyo portion,
which is, which I, you know, from the concept art
they showed, it's glowy and futuristic.
And, you know, just like strap some new lights on stuff.
And I'm always happy.
It seems like they're going to do that.
And it's, it is interesting that it's like, all right,
it's a CG animated movie in between two Pixar things.
It's a Disney animation movie.
It's also a Marvel property.
Oh, right.
Oh yeah, I forgot that.
But it's not connected to the Avengers campus.
Yes.
Maybe, but it's near.
Kind of near.
Right, it's near.
It's near.
Oh, that is confusing.
I forgot the Marvel connection with that.
Baymax has not yet been folded into the MCU.
Somebody on Twitter pointed out,
and forgive me for not knowing who pointed it out on Twitter,
that they got rid of the Golden Gate Bridge
at this front of California Adventure,
but now they will be adding the futuristic
Golden Gate Bridge to this area.
Is that right?
So the bridge, because that's one of the entrances
is a bridge.
So that's becoming, wow.
So the bridge was considered too tacky before,
the one that they have.
And now we're getting a new one.
And I wonder if it'll be more nuanced,
because I didn't like that Monorail Golden Gate Bridge.
It felt silly.
It looked like a Lego set.
So maybe it will be a little more textured ornate,
plus the future side of it.
I'm excited to see this bridge.
Yeah, so the bridge, this is all, yeah, this is all good.
This feels, the whole thing feels like,
and this is the best description I can think of,
is when I, I would try to pretend I was playing soccer
and I would head toward the ball.
This is the closest, one of the closest things
they got to actually like something that feels like
impactful, this announcement is what I'm saying.
Yes, yeah.
Like they were trying to present many things
as if there were big things coming,
but they were avoiding the ball,
like I did as a kindergartener in soccer.
Now, if I, I don't wanna put negativity
on our attempt at positivity, but isn't it positive?
I actually, I think that maybe most of the good news
at this panel, we are lighting up at,
because we are SoCal residents.
Yes.
And we go down there a lot and a lot of our concern
is eating and drinking down there.
So a lot of it feels like good news for us,
but if you're say in Florida or the half of the country
where Florida is your destination,
maybe you're less psyched because,
the hell did Florida even?
I don't wanna jump around,
feel free to keep saying positive stuff.
I'm just saying like, I'm like, yeah,
wharf and downtown Disney restaurants that we'll get to.
But I bet somebody in South Carolina could give a shit
about what's happening to the wharf.
Well, cause yeah, I was looking,
mice chat very helpfully divided up all of this
into different articles, one for Disneyland,
one for Disney World and one for the international parks.
So I could review it because by the end,
I was a little like spacey
and they were doing this blue sky thing
where they were like teasing things they might never do
and that was bizarre.
But there is a graphic that shows each year
stuff that's opening around the world.
And it's like the center of Epcot,
the world celebration with the commuter core building
and then the Moana journey of water,
that's not opening until later in 2023.
And the Tiana Redos for both Splash Mountains in America,
that's not until 2024.
Late 2024 was on the graphic.
And in 2025, again, this has been said a lot of times
by a lot of people,
Universal is opening the first new gate,
theme park gate in Orlando
since the last time they opened a new gate in Orlando in 99.
After a streak of pretty good rides and expansions,
they now are opening a new park,
which seems massive in scope.
It includes Mario Brothers, it includes monsters,
the classic monsters.
There were monster leaks.
We haven't even talked about this.
I said, did we talk about it maybe?
There were in our private life, did we talk about it?
Did we privately talk about monster leaks?
There were monster leaks about-
Well, Park Stop had a lot of-
Yeah, oh, the monster stuff is so good.
It is, yeah.
What are the leaks?
Pretty good.
So there's a concept that at first,
I was a little bit like, I don't know,
but the concept is sort of in its modern day.
And there's like, they've turned like,
say like an old time monster village into a tourist trap.
Yeah, it's like the heir to the Frankenstein family.
And they've turned it all into a tourist trap,
but the basement of the castle is filled with the monsters.
And they-
They're still there.
Oh, interesting.
And there's like a new Elvira type character,
like a sexy lady monster.
She's not a monster.
I think she's like a-
She's a scientist?
Something.
Yeah.
But she's sort of like presenting all of this stuff.
And then the big ride is that thing
we've talked about forever,
which is like a Kuka arm type thing,
which is a crazy ticket through every universal monster
who's like living in the basement of like,
Frankenstein's castle, I think?
Frankenstein's castle, yeah.
And they don't separate them, like all the monsters.
There's one ride that's the monsters ride.
All the monsters are on a ride.
I think they're all, I think it's a roller coaster track
with a Kuka arm.
Yes, it's like a crazy new version of the Kuka arm.
Like it's, this is the greatest,
this sounds like the greatest thing ever.
Yeah, and it seems like they've scrapped the show,
but it might've been replaced with a spinning roller coaster.
There might be a new ride also.
There's gonna be two rides in there
in addition to like just an old time Frankenstein-y village.
And this is also the closest thing we get to like non-IP,
even though it is IP,
where it feels like it's old stuff at the very least.
It won't be based on like,
it feels more in the Spider-Man spirit,
the way that the Duns and Adventures Spider-Man ride
is like the spirit of Spider-Man
more than any specific Spider-Man.
So it'll make it feel like original,
so like whatever this monster take is will feel kind of new.
Version of the classic monsters basically,
I'm assuming, because it's not the monster version.
They're not so precious with the monsters
because they're just so ubiquitous.
I think they feel like they can have multiple versions
going at one time.
Yeah, needless to say,
that's the most excited I am about anything
theme park-wise in the next few years.
And then in 2023 in Hollywood, we get Nintendo,
the beloved multi-generation, beloved video game company
shows up here.
Oh, you mean, yes, which you're a new addition to the park
that we are as excited about as current six-year-olds
will be excited about.
Like he has perfectly caked in interest
for many different types of audience.
Yeah, sure.
Well, there's all that.
But did you know that the projection show
Wishful Magic Kings, which was already announced
that we got new art that shows you what the colors
of the spires are going to be.
And it will only be delayed by eight more months.
Yes, I did know that.
I saw the presentation and I know that very well.
And I got very excited about it.
Yeah, people were shrieking about it in the hall.
That's the one, boy, it must be nice to be in these,
Pam, must be nice because we're at home snarking
and then we're watching a feed of it.
And they say like, hey everyone, you're getting a donut.
And everybody like, ah!
It is the great, it is pandemonium for all these
kind of nothing announced.
I mean, I'd be excited to be getting the,
that's a bad example.
We'd all like to get that.
Gordos cheese roll, oh.
Is that what it was?
That's the one that I.
It showed the picture.
Wait, did you say you don't like the cheese roll?
No, I did.
I love it.
That's a fantastic, yes.
My question on that is that cheese roll
they were giving out, I went to the Porto's website.
Those cheese rolls retail for $1.05.
What will the Disney market be for these?
Oh my God.
Massively baked, like baked in the biggest batches
you have ever seen.
Porto's is literally right around the corner over here
and it is pretty cheap compared to,
for like a good meal.
It's great. In general,
a pretty cheap everything.
It was a godsend during the pandemic
because they were doing like curbside pickup.
Yes, I did.
Just a little taste of like a fun,
like a Cuban sandwich.
Banana chips.
Yeah, those are good.
Yeah. Those are good.
But yeah, no, it's like,
there's no way at downtown Disney,
like everyone will go there if it's the same exact,
like prices it is up here.
It's gonna have to be more competitive
with whatever, Black Tap or whatever.
Yeah, it's also a few miles away in Buena Park.
Yes.
Where it will be cheaper, presumably.
So if you're a local,
you're probably not dealing with the hassle of
that it's $10 parking and then that's,
those cheese rolls are $10 each.
And then, so when you add all that up.
Yeah, that in general here, if we're getting into that,
some of the, amazingly,
some of the bigger announcements were new restaurants
at downtown Disney, as if geared to us specifically,
who spent time going through every restaurant
at downtown Disney.
I felt crazy when they announced it because I go,
why is this being presented in front of
To this crowd?
An international audience of people?
Cause like,
Porto's present, like the logo reveal
as if it's Dr. Strange or something.
Like, like seeing, I did like seeing the name
of good local restaurant chain, Porto's.
Family owned business for decades.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, great, great.
It's as if like, but it felt as if like,
Josh Tomorrow was like,
and now we're going to bring out Joey Kramer
to talk about what's happening to the Rock and Roll.
Like it felt so specific to me and us.
Yeah.
That I was like, what is going on here?
Like, this is bizarre.
And I'm happy it happened,
but I guess they were so low on announcements.
They're like, I guess throw Porto's on there.
You have to really puff up.
That's big now.
Din Tai Fung is big.
That's a more well known, I feel like, even in Porto's.
That is an international, it's in Taiwan
and it's in Las Vegas and California.
But how do you describe the, it's like,
it's like a like smaller bites kind of restaurant.
Yeah. Oh, sure, sure.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And there's a rendering of what that building's
going to look like.
And it does look beautiful.
It's great. Yeah.
It's fine with the great.
Yeah. We got some better aesthetics
coming to downtown Disney.
It's almost a little surreal.
Cause it's like, they're getting real,
like this is both these places are amazing food.
Like this is great food.
This isn't just great for theme park food.
This is like real deal food.
Yeah.
And I kind of couldn't understand.
It's like, wait, it's going to downtown Disney?
Okay.
Doesn't make sense.
You're saying doesn't add up.
Yeah.
Not Tapp and Palace Point are like both good, but like,
I mean, Brewpub is its own sort of thing.
I mean, it's been slowly,
quality has been slowly ticking out for years.
You know what a lot of them aren't though, is like,
the place is famous for the good food.
Like Palace Point is like, I wonder if the food's good.
You go when it is okay, great.
But like these are, you know, famously solid restaurants.
Yes.
Well, it's just how people feel about Salt and Straw,
even though you despise it Jason Fudge.
I just think it's a little overblown.
And I got really, I, any, anyone I found I like of the like
newer fancy ice cream parlor,
like there used to be a sweet cream,
there's sweet rose creamery by me that closed down.
And then the, what is it?
What was the one at Disney?
They used to be Los Feliz.
Oh, that was in-
It's still in Brooklyn, but it closed a lot of them.
It was in the house.
It was in the like Heidi Fleiss's
Dr. Fathers old practice.
Yes, it's in the old place.
What, really?
Yeah.
Yes, that beautiful craftsman house.
I think that's an interesting fact that could be wrong
if Eva's listening right now.
Did you tell me that?
I hope that's correct.
And Eiger had invested in it.
Oh my God, what is it?
It's two words, some Ample Hills.
Ample Hills.
I believe this is, wait, you forgot,
didn't you do a Doughboys about it?
I did do a Doughboys about it.
You forgot the name of an ice cream place.
It's been gone.
COVID haze is real.
Look at poor Jason.
I, yeah.
Brain fog is mostly pushed out
to the name of different ice cream houses.
I am shocked by that.
That is also like post COVID world,
like it closed like a.
It was a nice spot.
Another world to go.
It was a great spot.
You could sort of chill out on the lawn after you got it.
It was always busy, yeah.
And then it closed like,
it announced it was closing two days later.
Geo texted us and was like,
it's closing, there's giving away ice cream.
And we were just like, get over there.
It was like right at the,
it was like right before COVID maybe or right there.
Did you go to some sort of ice cream looting type?
I didn't go.
Okay, okay.
We were made aware of it.
So, so yeah, it's like all these,
again, all this is good, but this is, okay.
D23 they do every other year.
And now it's been three years since they've done it.
What are some of the, that's sorry to interrupt.
What, what, what has been announced at these previously?
I've been, okay, let me say this.
I am, look, do I make snarky snark comments all the time?
Sure I do.
But do I want to go into these big halls
and cheer and celebrate?
Which I've done a few times for different things.
Yes, I've been there.
It's fun.
I was not at last year's D23
because we were not invited, of course.
I made that very public when we were at our own convention.
But I was there two years prior
and I was there when they announced Star Wars land.
So I was there.
Oh, so that got an, oh, the whole land about Star Wars
was once the bar and now it's a nice,
tasty dumplings restaurant.
Here's our like little photo collage from 2019.
What was announced.
That big E ticket Avengers ride, which has now shifted
that the Epcot, some of the Epcot redo
also now scaled back.
Spaceship Earth out.
Yeah, Spaceship Earth.
There's a little more of like Avengers,
they had sort of, I forget if they had alluded
to Avengers campus four years ago.
And then they were, showed it off two years ago more.
And then here's the private island lighthouse point,
which if you recall during this battle,
Josh tomorrow was standing on this deserted island
filled with palm trees and scrub grass
and nothing had been built there.
Oh my God.
I don't recall because I walked out of the room
at the cruise part.
I check out that's that's seven thing.
That's seventh inning stretch for me.
I go pee, I go stretch.
They do a lot of cruise during these panels.
Yeah.
And I guess obviously they're very popular.
I just, I've never been on one.
I'm not against going on one.
No.
I don't care.
I don't care that the new ship is named.
What is it?
Treasure.
Treasure, Peter Pan and Tinkerbell.
Do you want to hear the name of the new ship?
And then like everybody goes, yeah.
Ah, I want to hear a word.
Oh my God.
They showed the word portos up on a big screen.
And then they showed the word treasure up on a big screen.
This panel was epic.
Yeah.
But I mean, three years ago,
there was more along the lines of like actual announces.
This year it's more, we're hedging our bets.
Well, in a lot of we have announced this
and here is a little more about it.
Yeah.
Those, that stuff was a little more hopeful
and a little more fruitful.
For example, they put a lot of eggs into the basket
of new splash mountain Tiana's Bayou Adventure, correct?
Yes.
Which looks great.
Every little bit that they show looks awesome,
but it, boy, you feel that like they had to pass the ball
to that, that attraction had to do a lot of heavy lifting
in the lack of brand new things.
And I hate to be negative, but in that,
that I'm a little already worried about,
everything I'm worried about budget.
I'm worried about the budget and everything.
Yes.
Yeah.
Cause it's like, I'm sorry, splash mountain, a long ride,
a lot of space to fill.
A lot of space.
And I'm a little worried.
Even the idea that there's a bunch of mist.
Well, this is the thing.
Could be good, but what if the mist ain't working?
What's in the room?
They say mist.
And the first thing I think of, so to explain,
they kind of talk about how there's gonna be like
some sort of mist in the ride,
and there's gonna maybe project things on the mist,
which to me means we're not gonna do as many robots.
We're gonna do a lot of mist.
Now, maybe that's gonna look really cool
and I'm gonna look like a fool.
Hopefully that's the case.
I bet it's good mist.
I don't doubt it's good mist.
But the first thing I think of is Nintendo 64 and fog.
And if you know what I'm talking about is that
Nintendo 64 famously in games,
when they weren't able to render like levels
fully in the distance, we just throw up a lot of fog.
So Superman 64 is one of the most notoriously bad
Nintendo 64 games and it's filled with Superman
flying around in like foggy metropolis.
And you see it in a lot of different Nintendo 64 games
because that was the easiest fix to just not have to render
that far into the distance.
So the first thing when they said mist, I go, uh-oh.
We don't want to, we can't render.
And I'm like, okay, all right.
I mean, they showed like some sort of a woodland creature
playing a banjo and I think there's still gonna be
maybe the celebration at the end.
So hopefully, but the outside and the initial promo art
looked a little bit more like they had changed
the whole mountain versus what the model looks like.
The model looks like basically they took out the spikes
and they threw out the hill.
Yeah, the briars, yes, which are good.
Don't throw me in the spike patch.
Yeah, but then they just threw up the cool.
I like the water tower.
There's like the water tower that's fun.
It says Tiana's.
And the general, like the night vibe,
which Splash Mountain doesn't particularly have now.
They've made it, it looks like Pandora now.
We're getting a little mini Pandora here.
Seems like they're doing a lot of research.
They got a lot of the voice actors back.
Music's great.
Anika Noni-Rose, great performer.
Felt a little bit, she did a great performance,
but I felt a little bad because it's like,
well, I think true quality will be reached
when she just gets to walk out in a blazer
and a baseball cap and wave.
Like she doesn't have to do a show.
She doesn't have to do a shift of her job, you know?
You were just thinking about how hard she was working.
She had to do like a whole thing.
And like she didn't get to,
like other people are just coming out, hi, bye.
But she did like a great show.
Ruffalo phones it in is what you're saying.
Ruffalo literally skifed it in.
He doesn't have to come in dressed in green
and do a whole thing.
Hey, Kevin Feige had to act and emote
next to a bizarre giant Hulk suit.
Well, yeah, we got to.
That was heavy lifting acting wise.
Real quick, I like all like the Tiana's restaurant.
That's come, that seems real fun.
Oh yeah, that'd be great.
And it seems like I'm interested,
let's talk about this real quick too.
I'm interested, are we going to,
is Critter Country going to go away?
That's an interesting thought because-
Well, you can't get rid of poo.
Splash Mountain is not going to be in Critter Country
anymore because it's going to be New Orleans Square.
Is it annexed?
It has to be because we're in New Orleans
and that's where Tiana's, the restaurant is going to be.
And that's where this ride takes place.
So it's going to all be New Orleans Square.
But is Tiana's taking over the French market
or the Hungry Bear?
Unclear.
I don't think it's, no, I think it's, yeah, yeah.
I think it's in New Orleans Square.
But it's in New Orleans Square, so.
So, and I don't think they're going to,
they're not just going to get rid of Hungry Bear
for no reason or poo.
So I think Critter Country is just cut in half.
It has one, exactly one ride and it's a little kid ride.
It's like Paradise Gardens Park, still lingering.
Awkward little redistra, gerrymandered.
Slither.
Where they are going to add back in, right?
They're adding in that exclusive entrance
for the Pixar Place Hotel.
Oh yeah, there was an entrance there.
That used to be there in the early days
is coming back, I think.
Yeah. That's good.
So I think Critter Country then will be saved for now
just because they're not ambitious at all
in doing anything.
Like, I'm sure they have it in the back of their mind
that we should just make this fully New Orleans Square
and put a different ride or put a different theme back there.
I bet they don't though, because we need to put,
that's like where they make their poo books.
That is where they make their poo books.
And then meet and greets, like that whole center zone,
the trail that you, I'm a little swayed
by having done this with a kid once,
like the little trail where you meet Tigger and poo
and Eeyore and everything.
I don't think they're getting rid of that
unless they got something really solid.
Well, is there any land,
is that going to be the smallest land in any park?
Could be.
Maybe.
It just feels like they might have an idea for it,
but that we'll get it to a 25.
It's an awkward, it's like,
what's that area, what's the little mini fantasy land
in front of the castle where Figaro is?
Oh, the fantasy fair?
Yeah, it's like that.
It's like a little,
or even a little more substantial because there's one ride.
Yeah.
Maybe I'm a critter, maybe I'm a critter country defender.
It's so like gentle and brown back there.
I don't want anything to happen to it.
I'm not saying I want it.
I'm just saying that it makes,
it would make sense then to just sort of make that
all New Orleans Square somehow.
I suppose so.
Just from a space.
Well then what are they doing with poo?
I don't know.
You need poo in the park.
People want some.
I'm not saying get rid of poo.
Any criticism I have is leveled by just the sheer,
like look, Ewer's out.
Get a picture of me.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
That does a lot of heavy lifting for sure.
So I mean, look.
We gotta get,
they have to look into all of their great
New Orleans properties.
Have they ended up owning like the big easy?
What does Disney own that's set in New Orleans?
Yeah, Justin.
Can we get Raylan Givens?
Well, there's a walk around Raylan Givens
from justified face character.
He has to end up in New Orleans tracking somewhat
at some point, right?
No, Raylan, you stumped me with that reference.
Oh, that's Raylan Givens.
Oliphant's character.
Oh, that's the name of the main character of justified.
Okay, I have not watched justified.
Elmore Leonard creation.
Oliphant will probably,
the way they're adding new characters to Galaxy's Edge,
Timmy the Oliphant's character will be there
in about 2042, I bet.
The Mandalorian, yeah.
For Mandalorian, right.
The pace they're going.
Do we transition with that into
some of what they top loaded it with?
The big announcements at the top.
They bring out Favre.
They bring out the creator of Star Wars,
Jon Favreau,
to showcase the new,
and look who's here.
Oh my God, it's the Mandalorian and Grogu.
And he's got Grogu.
And I'm like, wow.
So that means Baby Yoda and the Mandalorian are coming to,
oh, this got announced already.
I forgot this got announced.
That what they are doing is showing us
that they didn't stop making it.
Right. Right.
And they're, and they said,
and now you'll be able to see him.
And I'm like, oh, they're going to say like,
he's there today.
And they're going in November.
And I'm like, he's there, look at him.
He's good.
He's ready to go.
Send him in.
Holiday rush.
Have him walk up hard.
Walk across the street in the costume.
Let's do it.
Why do we, what?
November.
And then they're like,
well, we've been working on this since before the pandemic.
We had to get it just right.
And I'm like, what do you mean just right?
I've had the suit from the show be in another place.
Yeah.
His Grogu head, I guess, probably is a robot of some kind.
So I guess you got to get some of that.
Right.
He kind of looks upset to be in that bag.
Yeah.
It looks a little, little cranky.
When he's covered,
I guess that's helpful if you're trying to smuggle him
somewhere, but like,
I think he's among friends at hall D23.
Why put a drape over him?
I thought this was also going to be like the start of,
I was like, okay, I'll go like, they got Favro out here.
I go, okay, they're bringing the Mandalorian.
I go, this is going to be a big announcement sort of about
what they've announced about adding other characters.
We're going to see like,
and also that's not it.
And then they bring out like all the Mandalorian characters
or you see Babu Frick or whatever,
and there's going to be a big cavalcade.
No, it was just him.
And then Favro left.
That was it.
Bye.
I was like, why do they have him for just for that?
Like, obviously I want like,
I wanted like the whole hyperspace Hoopla clan to come out
and drop it like it's hot to play in.
Yeah.
Do you think, well,
that audience probably freaks out for that.
I think, I think people at home are blinking audibly, but.
Maybe.
If they say hyperspace Hoopla,
yes, maybe the people at home are a little confused,
but on the stage,
if all the Star Wars characters came out and they danced,
yeah, people go nuts.
When was the last time something that fun happened?
Since the last hyperspace Hoopla.
Mm-hmm.
That was it.
It died with Snig and Goopla.
What were their names?
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, that's it.
Snig and Goopla.
So yeah, Favro was out.
He had been there already for the day before
to talk about the new Star Wars stuff.
So I guess he was still down.
He always, he's one of the guys who you always see,
he goes into the park after this.
So he's always like spotted.
You always see him hanging out
because I think he's a big parks guy.
Sure.
So, I mean, yeah, if you go,
he probably gets that extra two days free Disney
with a guide trip when he's down there.
We're starting through if, like,
do they comp the meals or does he still have to pay for those?
I think.
What's a John Favro trip to Disneyland like?
Well, I think I'm just saying, like, they were like,
well, you can stick around the next day
to show off the Mandalorian
and he probably gets a second day on the trip.
Not that he couldn't get it regular
because he's pretty high up at the company at this point.
And do you think Per Diems,
does he park somewhere special?
I know, look, there's the, you get the guide for free,
but you have to pay.
Generally, I think if you're on like the Disney plan,
you're like, you know, you do something there.
Shonda Rhimes, I mean, they shafted her.
That's true.
So bad on the park tickets,
she jumped to Netflix.
Right, that's true.
That was because of parks tickets.
Well, it was like the final like indignity, I think.
I think it was like her relatives were going
and she was like, oh, I have these extra passes,
go use them.
And they were like, they're not good today.
And it's like, God, no, don't give the TV.
This person created like three hits for you.
You have the money that's been put.
And you gave them blackout tickets?
Tony Baxter was aghast when I asked him
if he just had to like make a quick call
to get like tickets to Tokyo Disney.
He was like horrified that I thought
it would be that easy for him.
Wow, not if he doesn't, wow.
Yeah, he was making it seem like there's no,
he has to pay for everything.
It's bizarre.
This is like the most powerful,
one of the most powerful media companies in the world.
There's so much about it that's like so weird.
If you don't think about it.
Such petty nickel and dime.
I mean, as evidenced by like, you know,
I mean, JPEG's had worse things to overcome PR wise,
but that Scarlett Johansson thing was so bizarre.
So why?
This is your enemy is Scarlett Johansson.
Yeah.
Constant unforced errors.
But now he's back and he looks so fucking rad.
His silver Fox Lincoln, his bald Lincoln look.
JPEG?
Yeah.
I, him with the beard does kind of look like those renderings
that people online go like,
oh, if Mr. Trump grew a beard, he'd look so cool.
And it's like, I guess what he'd look like.
Is that a gross, that bizarre sect of things
that like draws Trump as super cut and ripped.
They also like, I bet he'd look sharp in a beard.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
He'd come back stronger than ever.
Whatever the guys, Robert McNaughton or whatever,
he was always painting like presidents with shotguns
playing poker, whatever.
Republican presidents, excuse me.
Yeah.
He had the weirdest beard.
There's no way if it was like his top hair
would just be like dripping down like a wet dog.
I think the beard, I'll say this unobjectively,
I do think the beard looks good.
I think I would encourage him to keep it.
I think it looks good versus-
You like JPEG's beard?
Yeah.
I, well would you-
It's like the Triple H beard,
the bald on top beard on the-
Yeah, I think that's a cool look, honestly.
I don't think it's usually a bad look,
but I didn't really, I think I was watching
like a grainy video of one of the JPEG things.
I couldn't really see it from like
wherever the person was in the back of the hall.
Yeah, no, I think it's a good look.
Mike's looked, he's checked that high res
JPEG beard shots.
Yeah, I was watching the presentation of 4K.
I paid for that.
Is this just, are you just so stuck in the pattern
of thinking that all of the CEOs can get it?
We've gone into this so many times
that look how handsome Card Walker is.
Are you just so mired in this
that you have to accept JPEG's beard as handsome?
It's possible, I mean we are not always aware
of our own biases.
You're not attracted to the man,
you're attracted to the chair, to the office of Disney CEO.
The idea of a CEO as the president's-
Exactly, you drop, Trump hostile takes over Disney
and suddenly you're like, you know, kind of sharp,
but he'd especially look good with a beard.
Wow, that's a guy who's been to the Aspen Ideas Festival.
Nice.
I think, look, there's also like,
there was a new, we're jumping all around,
there was a new beard also on a different character too,
which I think-
Oh, King Thanos.
We can jump to that, yeah, King Thanos.
Let's look through the Marvel real quick
because we alluded to the Ruffalo and Feige already.
Sure.
So it starts with Feige coming out
and they're doing a little bit of back and forth,
Josh Demaro and Feige, classic comedy bits.
And Feige is a big, it is interesting.
A lot of these guys, I do feel are true blue parks guys,
parks people.
So let's get them on and off.
They cannot linger.
So they get in and out, yeah.
And then they're talking about Avengers Campus
and I thought, you know, they had a pretty,
for D23, the comedy of showing Loki three times was good
because they were showing all the different characters
and they said, and we have in the park,
we have Loki and then Black Widow and then Loki
and it was him in the different costume
and then a different character than Loki who was-
Yeah, that was genuine comedy rhythm.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so they were hyping all the stuff that they do
and I was like, yes, okay, I approve of all of this.
And then I'm trying to remember the way that it played out
is that I think Ruffalo interrupts.
He's in like a hotel room somewhere and he sends a video in
and he wants Hulk to be in the parks.
So I'm like, okay, that's good.
I'd like to see the Hulk, sure.
And then a really funny giant, I don't even know how,
what is it?
Like it's a person in there, obviously.
We were trying to figure that out and I think, you know,
Jane had seen some stuff like that when she worked
at Universal and there's probably a person in there
but the hands are like grabbers, you know,
they're controlling the hands.
They're probably on small stilts, small raised stilts.
Yeah, sure, sure.
And then they're also firing off the voices
on the like controls.
It seemed like a lot.
Yeah. And it's a big, it's like double the size of a person,
triple the size of a person.
The shot that followed him out did not provide the context
of another person.
So the suit comes out and like cool suit
and then he lands by Feige in tomorrow.
Like, oh God, he is twice their size.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's funny because the Hulk is wearing his
time suit from Endgame.
Yeah.
And his famous helmet, the Hulk's famous helmet.
I know it so well.
So bizarre, a giant green creature wearing ripped jeans
and they're like, put him in a space suit.
Well, it's obviously done because.
His lip flap can't.
Yeah, they can't.
They didn't get it to look right with him shirtless
and with the mouth.
Right. And he talks now, he's smart now.
It's smart Hulk from Endgame.
And he's been smart ever since Endgame.
Just in case, Scott, I want to catch you up.
Hulk is smart now.
No, I did not know that.
Yeah.
I did think he was oddly like,
why is he just like mumbling here?
This is not Hulk smash.
No, yeah, he's just Ruffalo, smart Ruffalo Hulk.
So.
I was a little surprised.
I thought he was going to say,
let's get some Hulk in the parks.
And it was going to be she Hulk
because the show is running right now.
It's getting a lot of good reviews.
Well, they should put her in a big white suit too, I guess.
And roll her out.
Well, let's do the she Hulk.
Well, she'll be in the.
She's in the art.
Okay.
Yeah, everyone's kinda.
It's not.
So the ride, they re-announced the Avengers ride.
It's no longer you're gone to Wakanda and aliens attack.
It's a multiverse thing.
Yeah.
And it also, there'd been,
it'd been alluded to a little bit in concept art
that you are flying on your own somehow.
Like you're on a.
Yeah.
Quinjet and then suddenly you're flying solo.
And I don't think any of us knew exactly
how that ride mechanism was going to work.
But now they very distinctly show just a car.
You're in a car.
You're in a Transformers car.
Which like, and that's,
so we're using the greatest ride system ever.
Well, if we do.
Yeah, if we use the greatest ride system, then okay, good.
But the old art made it seem, oh my God, what is this?
Yeah, we're maybe no longer in the territory
of new type of ride.
Yeah, cause the old one, there were enough,
the promo art or whatever you call it,
the concept art is like you were in a Quinjet
and then somehow you got out of the Quinjet.
Like you just plunged down,
like you were skydiving or something.
And then you were in little chairs
in like a 360 degree theater of some kind
watching an insane battle happen around you.
Which sounds amazing.
Sounds like a crazy new thing you've never been,
like you're in little like bungee chairs or something, maybe.
That's been replaced with cameos.
And that now, yeah.
Cameos of every possible character.
I think that this was a budget concern,
like many things that happened in the Disney company
in the last few years,
including not paying Mindy Kaling and Bill Hader
to reprise their roles in Inside Out 2.
Announcing Inside Out 2, but not.
Lowballing them and forcing them out
because they're not going to pay actors as much anymore,
even actors that are famous.
Wow, yeah.
So I think that this, whatever they figured out
is that we will just have screens with characters on them
and not pay the money for the new crazy cool ride system.
That's a guess.
I again, hope to be wrong.
I hope to be proven wrong.
And that this thing will be amazing.
But we know what we're looking at.
We know that it's a, and it'll probably,
look, there's plenty of great rides
where you are sitting in a car.
But just when you're coming down from the possibility
of a crazy new type of ride.
And the, yeah, it's got all the,
it's got like an animated Spider-Man in the promo art.
It's got Tom Holland's Spider-Man.
It's got Daredevil.
It's got She-Hulk.
It's got a good variety of characters.
Does it have Megan Thee Stallion twerking?
It does not have Megan Thee Stallion.
I want to say I am pro Megan Thee Stallion
twerking on She-Hulk.
Yeah, I'm pro as well.
Unusually current reference for a Disney prop today.
It's a little, yeah, it's already a year or two
maybe behind, but still.
I feel like she's just gotten bigger
in the last year or two.
That's true.
No, you're right.
But it's not, yeah, it's not at the,
I don't know, maybe what,
I don't know what years are anymore.
I feel like. Yes, that's true.
Yeah, it would have been like exactly.
She featured on a lot of big songs during the pandemic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, look, if Megan Thee Stallion,
if they want to put her on the ride,
I think that's awesome.
I guess that you would so with that, yes.
If all of a sudden she's like punching Thanos in the face.
King Thanos.
Oh yeah, so did we explain King Thanos who has a beard?
What's different about him besides that he has a beard?
Well, they said he won.
Oh, he won, that's what they said.
But he also kind of won in the movie too.
He did win in the movie.
He kept winning.
I think that's version.
He was winning so much he got so sick of winning.
Yeah, we're all gonna be,
we all ended up so tired of winning.
Yeah, he won in Infinity War and which famously Jason,
when we saw it in the theater,
Jason was upset by the end of Infinity War.
Real sad, kind of sad to watch Spider-Man dissolve into dust.
I said, oh, that was actually one of the better Marvel movies.
I really enjoyed that.
I thought that was like, it was a dark ending and it was cool.
And Jason was like,
but think of all the kids who will be upset by it.
Well, I also didn't know the second part
was coming one year later.
I thought it was gonna be another three or four years
in between movies.
So you thought that was too long of a wait
for kids to be sad.
So I thought that was gonna be like,
well, a lot of kids think Spider-Man's dead for a few years.
So yeah, Thanos wins in Infinity War.
Then he goes and retires.
And then at the start of Endgame,
the remaining Avengers go and find him retired.
And even though he's not a threat anymore,
Thor chops his head off.
He mercs him.
Yeah, just to be safe, yeah.
And so yeah, but he won.
I mean, Thanos won ultimately.
He got his way.
And then the Thanos they fight at the end of Endgame
is a different, is the past Thanos basically.
Right.
It's like a different Thanos
because they go back in time.
So this is a multiverse, a different Thanos
from a different multiverse.
They haven't explained which one.
So it's not Thanos.
I've been saying Thanos my whole life.
Look, I've been confused actually
as long as I've been reading comics
about exactly how to say it.
So whatever the last person who said it is how I say it.
Okay.
There's probably podcasts that rise
where I say Thanos, honestly.
But so-
Just jumped out.
I feel like it was like, that was like,
and then King Thanos was just different
than Thanos in Thanos one.
Yeah, no, it says nothing.
I'm just whatever, whoever said it last
is how I say it.
There is, like, there's definitely weird comic stuff
like Ra's al Ghul is Batman villain who is pronounced-
Ra's?
Ra's al Ghul is pronounced, on the animated series
that's what they say.
In the 90s, that's how they pronounce his name.
And then in the movies they call him Ra's al Ghul.
So I don't know.
I don't know if I have a good answer for any of this.
Anyway, he's got a beard now
and I have no other information
about what makes him different.
But he's-
Is he only in this ride, this version of Thanos?
He's exclusive to this ride.
It says first time they've rolled out a new version
of a character.
Okay, yeah.
Just in a ride.
That's something, yeah, yeah.
I kind of thought the way they were leading up to it,
I was like, they're gonna announce a big, scary villain
from the comics and it's just getting rolled out
in this ride.
That was not the case.
Okay, okay.
It was the one people recognize, which, hey, fair enough.
It's a theme park.
Yeah, you gotta go where people know.
If I could amend a Simpsons quote,
Malibu Stacey has a new hat.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's the good one.
Very much.
New hat, new beard.
People are gonna be excited.
Hey, wait, speaking of hats, big hat,
related news and parks and characters,
the Hat Box Ghost is coming to Disney World.
Don't care for it.
Oh, you feel edged in on-
Give him a new ghost.
Keep the Hat Box Ghost exclusive to here as well.
What if you live there, wouldn't you be like,
I want the Hat Box Ghost?
I bet that is how I would feel.
Well, there we go.
I don't care, I live here.
Crack that puzzle.
I don't want them to have it.
I want us to have it.
They can have a different ghost.
Give them a different ghost.
There's no legend at that haunted mansion
about the Hat Box Ghost.
Mm-hmm.
That's the whole point.
That's what I'm saying.
The reason the Hat Box Ghost is special out here
because it's a specific legend to here,
to Southern California, to Disneyland.
You can make up legends and put them anywhere.
Sure.
The power of storytelling, anything can be a legend.
Make up a Orlando legend of a different ghost
that maybe was on the ride the first week of opening.
You know what I'm saying?
I guess so.
I understand that, look, Leto is the Hat Box Ghost.
And they're gonna have to have-
Is that right?
Isn't that right?
I didn't make that up right, yeah.
Oh, I forgot about that.
Jamie Lee Curtis is Madame Leota.
Oh, I missed that one, really.
And she came out in the Doombuggy.
Oh, she came out in the Doombuggy.
She was revealed at D23.
Oh, that's why I saw her in the Doombuggy.
I didn't catch that announcement.
Okay, interesting.
So Leto is the Hat Box.
So I understand he's gonna be a popular character
and they want him on both.
In case, that's Jared Leto, not Leno, just to be clear.
If you were mishearing it.
Who'd go either way with us?
Who'd go either way?
Thank you, yeah, thank you for clarifying.
So yeah, no, I feel they should have their own unique ghost
to that ghost.
Do you feel like anyone,
have people in Florida been jealous of us having it?
Because you seem like, I don't want them to have it.
Do you think on the other side,
has ever been like those smug bastards in California?
Yeah, I think it has probably been like,
this is not the same as me not wanting like people's
student loans forgiven because I paid my student loans.
That's not what this is.
I'm not trying to punish them.
You want some forgiveness.
So you want, and then so would you be okay
with some Hat Box ghost?
Hat Box ghost, but he's smaller or he's harder to see.
They put in a lot of mist.
I want a means tested Hat Box ghost.
That's what I want.
If somebody is worthy enough of seeing the Hat Box ghost
in Florida, they are allowed to see it.
No, but I just, I feel like it's fun.
It was a special thing because of it being to Disneyland
and the legend of it.
So when it finally appeared here.
So I'm not that mad, but I don't think honestly,
but I still don't think it should be there.
I don't think they should have it.
I'm not that mad.
You could rearrange that sentence to be, I'm mad.
You could if you wanted to, but it's fascinating.
You need ghosts, put a unique ghost there.
That's what I think.
I can't argue with that, but it's gotta be,
there has to be the like inherent clever.
You have to like give them something as cool
as the Hat Box ghost effect.
Well, as long as there's a need.
Use the same effect and it's a different ghost
and his head is going into a different type of
like carrying case of some kind.
So you're okay with still.
Suit Box ghost, suitcase ghost.
Orange man ghost, this guy used to sell oranges
door to door.
No, not, no, no, we've got to take the phrase
orange man back, an orange salesman.
And he got lost at the haunted mansion.
Fine, yeah, great.
So wait, sorry, his head goes into his box,
which is otherwise full of oranges.
Is his head a big orange?
Oh, well, maybe his head disappears
and a bunch of heads appear on the oranges in his box.
His oranges that he's selling.
That he's selling.
By the way, so he got lost and ended up in an old manor,
him being a citrus salesman.
He thought it's like a mansion.
I bet there's a lot of money here.
They'll buy a bunch of oranges.
I'm gonna move so many oranges today.
Yeah, it's okay.
That's, I'm for that.
I'm for all of these ideas.
I just think that it's special.
It's not special anymore here.
So you're, so are you now gonna go on the haunted mansion
and be like, ah, he'll do like a big sigh
when you pass that box.
I don't know that I'll exhale aggressively,
but it just, I like your little like little treats
on the different coasts with the different rides.
And it will feel a little less special.
Unless they do, maybe they'll do something different
with him in Orlando.
Because all they did was show his head.
And who knows with the way they roll stuff out,
maybe we're waiting till 2030 to see him.
They didn't give a date, I don't think.
No, they did.
That was on the timeline.
Cause they had to flesh out that timeline.
They had to like, how many logos can we populate this with
to make it look like something?
The one year, I guess it's 2024,
had the Tiana logo on it twice.
And then underneath real small, it said Disneyland,
Disney World.
And I'm like, well, no, that's cheating.
Those aren't different things.
That's like when you make your font,
when you had to write a paper in school and it's like,
okay, I'm making it 13 point.
I'm making the margins really small.
They must have been really big.
Everybody got like Marvel,
Marvel like TV and movie pills.
So they're like, we should do that too with the rides.
It's fun to show the big graphic of all this stuff.
It must be so fun.
And then they all reveal and fade up.
And then people are staring at 50 logos.
We gotta give them 50 logos or it's not a panel.
So somebody threw that idea out and they were like,
yeah, let's do that.
And then they were like, oh shit.
Oh, it can't be a year with like little ones coming out.
Okay, switch it, switch the access.
Okay, yeah, now they're all this.
So the year is this way and the years are stacked.
So it looks busy.
It's a little Jenga tower.
It's not a timeline because we don't know what the hell's,
we might not have any money by 2036.
Well, so one of those would just said Cotino.
It's like, that's just a housing development.
Oh, did it say Cotino one?
Yeah, I was on there.
Yeah, it's just a housing development for millionaires.
That doesn't count on this.
No, no, you could tell they like, but you know,
you could sense them like trying out the material.
Like if Cotino got a cheer in the room
where it's the easiest ever to make people cheer,
then maybe they'd keep pushing Cotino a little harder,
but it managed to not get a cheer in a room where people,
it was like, and the boat will be going to Australia.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah.
People were removed on stretchers,
like at an old Rolling Stones concert.
Elvis.
Women passing.
All right, we got 10 faints.
It happened again.
A boat has a new place to go.
Josh Demaro is like Elvis in a lot of ways.
Do we still have the fond feelings for Demaro
after watching a whole parade of,
because we were texting about how like,
now there's a lot of like,
he knows that people like him
and we're all going to do run Disney
and I'll be there running.
I run, you know that I run anyway.
He's self aware now.
I think so.
I think we figured it out.
We got to see him ride Tron.
I mean, we're not going to be able to ride Tron for a while,
especially there's a virtual queue.
Those things are always fucked,
but he got to ride it.
So we got to see his home movies.
Ha ha ha, yay, whoosh, whoo, wow.
Oh, the wind and his perfect silver hair.
So it's done.
So you're saying it's done.
So you could open this because it's done.
Well, a little more.
Well, there's a, we got to pour some asphalt first.
Why is that going to happen?
What did they say?
Spring 2023.
So five years since groundbreaking.
Six more months.
Yes.
Why?
Open the ride.
I don't know.
Universal opens the rides two years too early.
Hadwards opened two years too early.
Secret Life of Pets still breaks every time you ride it,
but it's open.
You get to go.
As soon as it's legally allowed, they open the ride,
whether it's been tested thoroughly or not.
Yeah, I was at a food festival riding Secret Lives of Pets
and everything else was like, half the rides are open.
And it's like, oh, okay.
It's all willy nilly there.
We got one shot of the vaccine.
I guess that's good enough to go inside
and ride these rides.
Yeah, so.
Well, speaking of getting a little too ahead of it,
let's talk about what so much of this panel was.
Musical performances.
Which was, well, that, okay, yes.
Very talented performers, but again,
we know what you're doing.
You're filling for time.
Great singers, dancers, musicians.
They hired great people.
But again, weren't you supposed to announce
theme park rides?
Yeah, yeah.
So what a ton of it ended up being
was this odd scenario of, and we have some ideas.
Well, I don't know if we should say.
I should, oh, don't make me.
Hey, in front of all these people,
you're gonna make me say,
yeah, I guess you want a man up.
Do you have balls or not?
Do you have the nuts to show a slide
that for sure was loaded up on the screen
ready to go before this panel began?
There was so much weird.
So what we got was like the suggestion of a shape
of what a ride could maybe be
if they do have the funding for it.
This was the weirdest possible way to do this.
Edging.
This is like, this comes about,
the panel was actually, I think,
scheduled only 90 minutes.
They went about two hours, 15 minutes.
Maybe it was scheduled for two hours
and I read this thing wrong.
But 90 minutes in, they bring out like a line of Lena Bell,
Duffy's friend Lena Bell.
And you're like, this is like 100 minutes in.
And they real quick go like,
and there's gonna be a stop motion Duffy series
on Disney Plus.
Moving on, like, wait, what?
Yeah, so they're like doing it.
And you're like, okay, all right.
And you're waiting for the big thing.
Yeah.
We're all waiting for something.
We're like, even though if they did all this stuff
and then at the end they went in New Tomorrowland,
I think we'd all been like,
well, at least that's a pretty big deal.
Worth it.
So, okay.
So like, he starts talking about, listen,
like a way of like a little cheeky,
like this is gonna be,
we're talking about some big stuff.
I remember going, okay, wait a minute.
Maybe we've been, maybe we're wrong.
Maybe they're about to give us some big stuff.
This is like how, you know,
like the buildup of Alien is kind of slow,
but it's on purpose because the shit goes down.
Yes.
And it lures you in.
You got tricked.
And then this is, as you were saying,
the most confusing little play that they put on.
Where it's two, it's a Disney film person.
So the person they'd have to work with
to bring some of the more recent properties to life.
And then I forget who the other guy was.
He was Imagineering.
Okay.
So then they do this little play
where they're not supposed to say this stuff
because they say like,
oh, we're really thinking about doing this.
They're both trying to say,
these are like, we're really planning
and thinking about these things,
but also this is 10 years away if we do it.
They're saying both things at the same time
where it's like, this isn't just,
Beluse, this isn't just like a thought.
We really would like to do some of this stuff.
We have a really fuzzy watercolor of it.
Two fuzzy watercolors.
One for Animal Kingdom, one for Magic Kingdom.
But also it's not happening anytime soon.
Which he also says, which is so bizarre.
Like, so my reading of it is that
somebody looked at this presentation and said,
this is a little thin.
Like we've waited three years.
These maniacs in the audience would maybe like a ride,
maybe like a ride announcement
for one of the domestic parks.
And they went, oh God, what are we gonna do?
Okay, well, let's share some like possible things
we could do.
But this is not, these aren't green lit.
No.
These aren't, these are not maybe that fleshed out.
It felt like them feeling the audience out.
Like whatever wins on the cheer meter,
maybe they will sort of fast track to presenting it
to Mr. Baldbeard to see if he'll cough up ill,
if he'll move some of the lounge money over to.
It really seemed like kind of, they rushed through it.
It's like, oh, animal kingdom.
They didn't even say.
Dino land, it's gonna become Zootopia and Moana.
And then in the magic kingdom, we'll do Coco and Enchant,
or not Enchant, what's it called?
Encanto.
Encanto, and we'll do all the Disney villains.
And they'll all be neighbors.
They'll all be in a row.
And it's like, what the fuck?
It's like all of it.
How could all of that be in those places?
That seems like too many things.
It seems like they called an audible
like halfway through the thing.
And they were like, hey, get the Imagineering.
The director of, I forget which movie she directed.
She produces a lot of them.
Yeah, she produces a lot.
She's been there for a long time.
What's her name?
Jennifer Lee.
Jennifer Lee, thank you.
I think she was a fixer on Zootopia.
Okay.
Which I say fixer, but like every Disney movie,
the last 10, 15 years are always like, and it was a mess.
So we threw everything in the garbage
and started back at one.
Yeah.
And 30 people worked on the story.
And I was like, why do you guys always say this
as the narrative?
Like that this is a new thing you've hit upon.
Well, cause that's Toy Story 2.
It's Toy Story 1.
It's like everything has that point, you know,
that one where Sting got screwed
and they threw all his songs away.
It's like, I think it's every Disney anime movie.
It is the behind the scenes drama,
but it's just so funny when they're like,
and Imagineering's hitting 70 years,
the company's hitting a hundred years.
And it's like, okay.
I mean, you're still doing everything ad hoc.
I guess that's just the industry at large.
Chaos.
Everything is chaos.
Movies and Imagineering.
Yeah.
But yeah, it felt like,
cause they already had talked about Zootopia in Shanghai,
which has been announced and like they showed some of the,
they showed some of the puppet stuff outside,
which looked cool.
Like I liked the idea they were using like puppets
on the streets.
Oh yeah. They'll sort of flesh out the street scenes
and environments with puppets.
That's fun and animatronic looked good.
Yeah.
But then like, this was 20 minutes ago.
And then they're like, and maybe we'll,
they're like, how about they,
which I thought was weird.
They say, but like Dino land.
And then they were like, we're going to bulldoze.
Like it's so funny.
Cause they usually don't say like,
we're getting rid of this to do this.
They'll say like, oh, we're going to do this.
And then later you put it together like,
oh, they're getting rid of that.
Yeah. Yeah.
You do that part, but they like said really front and center.
Dino land.
Like we're going to bulldoze Dino land.
Maybe.
Which is again, why it felt like they called an audible
backstage to just send them out.
And this part wasn't so polished.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, and I don't think that's what happened,
but it felt late in the process.
Cause it didn't, this part felt a lot more,
a lot less smooth as the rest of the presentation did.
Yes. Yeah.
So yeah, they like threw all this stuff out just to make
people think maybe we're going to get a ride here.
And yeah, they threw up some concept art,
which would be great if it happened.
But then it just looked like the spinner ride triceratops spin
just becomes Moana spin.
It's Maui spin now.
Didn't seem like it was anything amazing.
Yeah.
Rodie was commenting on it too on Twitter.
Well, he had, it was a couple of years ago.
That was an old post.
Oh, was that old?
Yeah.
Cause he would just that his theory of like about, you know,
we're not rushing Zootopia in there.
Cause that's animals telling human stories.
We're trying to let the animals speak for themselves
with nature conservation.
I'm like, that's very nice, but I want some fucking rides.
I don't give a shit.
Whatever it is, zoos in the name.
Just put it, I know it's,
they haven't used not a zoo in a long time.
It can be a zoo.
It could be a Zootopia now.
He's just there now.
He was just there hanging out.
Yeah.
He was chilling at his old, you know, alumni.
Yeah. All the greats were wandering around.
That's a, that's a fun part of it.
This D23, when we were at Star Wars celebration,
they were pop-up bars.
Like every 20 feet, you could get like a canned cocktail.
I wonder if they were at D23 too.
Maybe. I don't know what the, yeah. Anaheim.
Anaheim's loose.
San Diego is not like that.
We've talked about that before.
You cannot get a drink.
San Diego would be lawless if they did that.
Yeah. But yeah, in Anaheim,
you can get a beer in the convention center.
Yeah.
So all this stuff, that's lawless by the way.
You get a beer in the convention center.
No, I'm just saying cause here,
I'm just saying the vibes are a little more agitated
at San Diego.
I feel like the vibes are not as good
at the San Diego convention center.
The Anaheim convention center always feels more chill
whenever I've been there.
You can go to Rockin' Baja and get hammered
and go back to the- You can, yeah.
But you gotta, you gotta walk the mile.
Or you gotta walk the half a mile.
We've been to the Wired Lounge
and you put back a drink or two and head back to the floor.
You got a Rockin' Baja at the Wired Lounge.
Yeah. Well, if you're, look, Rockin' Baja,
you have to go if you're a San Diego main,
Comic Con mainstay like we are.
Sure.
What's the, what's the, what do you recommend
at Rockin' Baja?
Some sort of fried fish.
Yeah.
Big bucket of fried something.
So you can get hammered.
Margarita. You can get hammered
on those fried fish.
That's right. Yeah.
You can get a big margar, big gross margarita
and a big, big thing.
We're more Joe's people. It's one of the closest one.
Get the shark bite.
Well, of course we love Joe's Crab Shack
as far as the San Diego place.
And I went there, I didn't go to Comic Con
cause it would have been irresponsible to.
The way to a child, yes.
Lindsay, you go into labor during Comic Con
and I'm down at Joe's Crab Shack drinking the shark bite.
Hang on, almost done with my shark bite.
Yeah.
Labor takes a while, right?
I'll get, I'll hit the road now.
You are like two miles from anywhere
that you could call a Lyft.
I would have had to get in a.
I have to close the bill.
I have to close the tab at Joe's Crab Shack.
It would have been faster if I got in a boat
and headed back to Los Angeles.
Yeah.
With that location of Joe's.
Just start swimming.
So yeah, but no, oh, there's a lot of, yeah.
Rockin' Baja is an almost annual tradition.
As far as a Comic Con.
Well, look for Mike there, maybe next Comic Con.
Yeah, I'll be there next year.
So now the stuff looks cool.
I don't know, Coco and.
Yeah, it'd be great.
And Contest, yeah, it'll be.
But Disneyland Forward looked great
and there was no mention of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the last I checked on that,
cause I signed up for the email updates
and they were showing the first episode
of the Imagineering story on Zoom.
And that was the last I heard.
The first thing you've seen already.
If you don't know what we're talking about,
Disneyland Forward, they presented this huge piece
of promo art that showed them adding 10 rides, 12 rides,
big lands to both parks in California.
And what it probably really is,
is a scam to fool Anaheim into thinking
they were building that when instead they just wanted
to be able to build more restaurants and hotels.
Yeah.
On the land.
It's probably a big con for the city of Anaheim.
And that's what I'm guessing ultimately,
because you would think they would at least,
if they were gonna tease more stuff that maybe
will be built, they would have gone to the art
that they already had from 2020?
Yeah.
Two years ago at this point.
That's not happening.
But it's not, that's not happening.
Yeah.
You know what is happening and this maybe this is,
in our world is the biggest thing to an hour.
This wasn't even part of the panel.
This was a detail in a model of the previously announced
Mickey's Toon Town.
And if you didn't already see this,
we have not publicly commented on this.
And I think now is the time that there is a new
food establishment coming to Mickey's Toon Town.
Yes.
And now forgive me.
I actually forget the, is it, let's,
does anyone know the exact names?
You should reveal it if you know the,
I forget what the last word is.
Good boy grocers.
Good boy.
There is a, now Disneyland will have a food stop
with the phrase good boy in it.
Yes.
What happened here?
Pluto is in the logo.
Right.
But also we like it cause it's our thing.
We're going to be down there.
We're all going to, we're all going to meet down there
when it opens so we can get a picture under it.
And Mike is going to miss his daughter's first steps.
Like that.
You again, he will be in the farthest part back.
You were in the Joe's Crab Shack of Disneyland,
the furthest part away.
This will be, look, I'll be,
it'll be more like a 1950s dad who missed all sorts of things
about their kids cause they were busy at the office
or something.
The office for me.
Yeah. The office for me though, will be Mickey's Toontown.
Good boy grocers or Baja.
Rockin' Baja.
Comic-Con.
Right.
These are my places of business.
This is where I work.
I work in these arenas.
Like, oh, I'd love to, I'd love to come home.
Your voice becomes that.
You become a cigar chomper.
Things are going all crazy at good boy grocers.
No, no, I don't work there.
It's, I take pictures under the sign.
I sign autographs or podcast fans, you see.
Yeah. Yeah.
We get like one every six days.
It's been a madhouse.
Oh yeah.
I'm getting swarmed here.
The Disney photographer is annoyed
cause we keep pulling them away from taking pictures
of Goofy and we're like,
can you take a picture of us under this sign?
It's a thing on our show.
It's Weet Say, but now it's up here now.
Yeah.
No, it's probably a coincidence,
but it's more fun to think that they dropped it in there
as a reference to us.
Yeah.
I do like also that the Toontown models looked cool.
I also liked that a lot of the signs
appear to be using the bad tea party font.
Like it's just a little of that, like kind of kooky.
A little twisted.
The two, I'll say this Toontown, they're really,
it feels like they're adding back in the sort of like
little kid play areas, which I'm happy about.
Yeah.
It feels like there's going to be a lot of space
for kids to run around.
That was the point of it, I think.
Yeah.
To kind of reclaim all this space.
So that's good.
Yeah.
All that Toontown stuff will be nice.
And I'm excited cause I get to, by the time that's open,
I'm taking like a three year old there.
Oh great.
He's in the prime.
Yeah.
Am I going to force a six month old to try to do it?
Yes.
The answer is yes.
Do you want to be at daddy's office or not?
Runaway Railway is pretty smooth, Mike.
So I don't know if you want to even print like,
an eight month old on it.
Some of that stuff in there.
Yeah.
Sure.
They just, there's like a window that you have, I think,
where like, because she's currently in the window
where she just doesn't know what anything is.
Yeah.
But then if they, when they learn fear at all,
because I've tried to do, I had one successful run at this,
but my son, the second one was a lot less successful.
We went on the oft broken pets ride.
Not broken, like it's not running.
They run it and it is broken.
Right.
Always slows down and stuffs.
Which gave me a panic because like,
he is really afraid of, as you might be,
like the bar is coming down on you.
Yeah, yeah.
And he just does this very sad, like, no, no.
And I'm like, uh oh, we got 10 minutes
of this thing on you, buddy.
Let's, look, there's a dog.
Is a dog, you like dogs?
There's dogs.
You can be cool for 10, possibly 12 minutes
if it breaks and it will.
Yeah.
Oh right, if you get stuck.
Ooh.
Yeah, yeah.
That was a bit of a fear.
We made it out okay.
It was all right.
But that's what Jason's onto something.
You probably, you want to take her in the window
before she understands what any objects are.
Yeah.
Because maybe you lose some rides from one and a half.
Who knows?
I'm not out of the window yet.
But then I was afraid, I, when we went to Disney World
for the first time, I was like five or six
and my sister was three and she was fine on all the rides
and I was scared.
Yeah.
So you never know.
How that's gonna work.
Yeah, yeah.
Your kid can be really wimpy at any age.
That's true.
I can attest, you can attest.
Sounds like Jason can't attest.
No, we can't all be Jason.
I'm a hero.
I did, recently I was watching some old footage
for something I was looking up for the show
and I saw like shaky camera footage of a place
that is like a very clear memory of my mind
where I met Belle and the Beast
and it was like high, very tall ceilings and stuff
and it turned out to be like the entryway
of the Soundstage restaurant.
Yeah, I have a lot of hazy memories of the Sound.
That's in Florida, you mean?
Yeah, at MGM Studios and it was right by the stairs
that would go to the short-lived catwalk bar.
Where everything was upside down or something
or there was like a bunch of bullshit up on the catwalk.
Yeah, it was as if they built a bar
and they're like up, you know,
the lighting rigs and stuff of a Soundstage.
That may have been a fully Aladdin overlaid restaurant
for some, for an amount of time.
I just remember, my trips,
I remember we were there a lot, oddly.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
Someone did a big blog post about like the history
of the short-lived catwalk bar
and that was very fun to comb through.
Well, episode coming.
So yeah, so there will be a walk-around figment.
Again, date to be determined,
another one of these things where it's like,
don't you have the puppet lying around?
Isn't it just a person with a puppet?
That's what Dreamfinder,
the walk-around character used to be.
So they did this whole big like,
oh, you know that little character
that y'all like so much from Epic?
I feel like, yeah, we love the character.
It's like, well, you'll get to take a picture
with a puppet of it.
Here's shots of merch of it
that proves that it is financially viable
to do something with it.
Yes.
Speaking of Epcot, another thing they announced,
like for Disney's 100th anniversary,
you've all been enjoying Harmonious?
Well, we're putting something out
and Jane was like, no, it just opened.
Why are you closing it?
You were the only people that gave it a good review,
I think.
I guess, but it was packed.
And you can't really watch it was packed.
But I think it was a problem from the start.
I suppose, yeah.
So yeah.
This is where I have to, I'm like,
the very first thing I think was,
and we know that you love Happily Ever After,
and that is why now it will be,
and I'm looking at Twitter and Carly's like,
Happily Ever After, and I'm like,
I don't know what the fuck it is.
I have no idea what's being, I'm sorry.
If you haven't figured out by now,
my interests are selective, all of ours are.
I'm sorry, I don't know what it is.
I'm happy everyone will be happy that there is more of it.
Those shows and then the new one,
Wonder, was it Wondrous?
Wondrous Journeys.
With the Hey Ho song, the Lumineers song.
I'm begging for that Al Citty,
paint the next song to come back.
Begging for Al Citty.
Look, I like, the Happily Ever After,
like fine, I like some of that,
I like watching those things.
I'm not particularly like enamored with that.
I do like a Mickey's Mix Magic,
which is different than those shows,
which are very much like what you expect with Disney.
And then the Hopes are on the wings of dreams.
And that's what it's like.
It's all that same nonsense, empty stuff.
And then, you know, songs and fireworks, which are cool.
And the projections are cool.
But for me, I like the stuff that's a little otter,
like Mickey's Mix Magic, that's a lot weirder.
It's a little more of a party on Main Street.
Havant Gard.
Havant Gard, Mad Tea Party.
So yeah, I can't keep track of some of that stuff either.
But yeah, there was a lot of that
where I kind of glaze over and go, okay, sure.
What else did we miss though?
What was the other big one?
Or did we just say it somehow?
Oh, no, Absence of Tomorrowland.
Well, yeah, of course.
There have been a lot of rumblings.
That's the football, Lucy, the football here,
where it's like, that was three years ago,
I remember everybody going,
and they're gonna do the tomorrow,
that's gonna be the thing.
They're gonna say, finally, Tomorrowland redo, no.
And that ain't happening for Disney,
like 70th anniversary of Disneyland's coming quick.
Nothing's gonna happen except for, I guess,
we'll have Runaway Railway and the Tiana ride.
Yeah, things we know about.
But yeah, Tomorrowland, they gotta start that now
if they were gonna do it for that.
And they are not, it is not happening.
Yeah, hey, exciting year or two
coming up for us out in California.
We get Nintendo and we get Runaway Railway.
It's fun for us.
Sure, yeah, sure.
That'll be fine.
All right, so I guess there's stuff to look forward to.
And there is, there are good things.
It's just, we just want a little more.
We just wanted it to get pushed a little bit.
But let's not dwell on that.
Let's be positive and let's honor some greats
because we haven't gotten to do this in a minute.
And I know people are similar to that.
People are trembling with anticipation
of who will be named the 2022 PTR legends.
Does anybody wanna go first?
I'm gonna propose maybe I go last
because mine, like tomorrow's presentation,
mine involves a song.
I think you gotta close out on a song.
Of course, yes.
Well, I will go first.
Although I think my choice is a bit of a dark horse candidate.
Great.
And I'm sure people might have been expecting
when we were teasing this that I would select a treat.
But for the first and maybe last time in my life,
I've picked something relatively healthy.
And I'm of course referring to the humble
Cuties brand mandarin oranges.
Recently, a recent replacement of the disgusting apples
with no skin on them in a wasteful plastic bag.
Cuties brand oranges have shot to the top
of your obligatory side choice
when ordering advanced ordering on the app.
But for PTR listeners who may well remember
these Cuties brand oranges,
probably the only things that kept us from keeling over
during our hot dog hullabaloo,
like a pirate or sailor warding off scurvy,
chomping into a bitter lime.
We of course spent the day
supping upon the delicious Cuties brand mandarin oranges.
And they were a delightful treat
and gave us some actual nutrients
in between bacon and cheese covered hot dogs.
The tiniest items,
like as healthy as they might be,
which might be, they might be like paper and water
for all I know.
But even if they were extremely healthy,
the smallest amount of healthiness you could get.
Yes.
And also get prevented,
I'm sure it's prevented someone from getting scurvy.
Yeah.
So, no.
Could have been us.
I don't know what's in all of those hot dogs,
but there could have been the materials
for us to get scurvy.
I wouldn't put it past whatever they're made of.
So you Jason, officially induct PTR legend Cuties.
Cuties brand mandarin oranges.
You know, I thought about doing the fishnet,
but it's a more recent obsession.
And I thought like.
Give it time to linger.
Give it time to linger in my mind.
And some pictures of me with different glasses
and different haircuts and different Phillies caps,
you know, allow some time to pass.
Well, that's beautiful.
Wow. Congratulations to Cuties.
You made it.
PTR legend.
Not the movie Cuties, the orange.
Just want to clarify.
Sure.
But you never know what mine is.
That's a good point.
Now I won't, okay.
I'll do mine now and I don't want to step.
Hopefully yours is not going to step in any way on mine
because mine is a little, I don't know.
It's a little bit outside the box.
I would like to induct into the PTR legends hall.
Hall of legendary.
Any hard to get guest that we've been wanting
on the show for many years.
Ah.
This is a blanket PTR legend status
that can apply to Michael Eisner, Jay Leno
or anyone else that we've for long, many years said,
we've got to get so and so on the show.
Breck Eisner.
PTR legend.
So this extends to anyone that we have said over and over again
we need to get on the show because we would like to trick them
into coming on with an honor because people love being honored.
Yeah.
Yes.
So this can, and there were probably people we've forgotten
that we've said we wanted on the show.
We've done this dumb podcast so long.
Who knows what we said, but they are a PTR legend as well.
So we can apply this blanket.
This is like one of those blanket pardons
that people were looking for.
I don't know why we've talked about Trump today for so much,
but this is one of those,
a lot of his cronies were looking for like blanket pardons.
This is a blanket PTR legend status applied
to anyone that seems hard to get that could be swayed
with some sort of a status, some sort of a title,
some sort of an award.
Yeah.
The visual representation of this
can just be that silhouette on websites
when they don't have a person's picture to use.
They just use that black and a lime.
I'm using my induction for, as a bribe.
Sure.
And you know, we run the PTR hall of legendary
and it's not dictated by,
it's not governed by any other sort of entity.
So it's legal if we say it is.
That's exactly right.
Yeah.
So there you go.
Great.
So, you know, take some of that,
just edit out the part where we said it's a trick.
If there's somebody you think you have a connection to,
we want you to come get this very legitimate honor.
That's right.
We can promise you a banquet,
which may or may not have Cuties brand Mandarin oranges.
Also among the PTR legends that you will join.
It's funny, I guess Cuties could be the contents
of the orange box ghosts.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's great.
Great tie in.
Well, that's what you've talked,
you were talking about how you want like a legend to their,
well, we just went and tied up that plot, didn't we?
You want Florida to get their own legend.
Cuties are now a legend.
So a guy selling a box full of Cuties.
That's correct.
Little Lado heads.
One Lado head becomes lots of little Lado heads.
Lado?
Is it Jerry Lado?
Oh, is it Lado?
Oh yeah.
Oh, okay. Excuse me.
Oh, well, Lado.
Oh, okay.
Lado.
All right.
So Inductees, Cuties and you, like you said,
but not, it's not all of you.
Not all of you.
No, no.
But that's saying if any of the people I just mentioned
are listening.
Then it is you.
Yeah.
And if so otherwise it's not you.
And if you are an accidental PTR legend who was hoping
this would be the year that you became a purposeful PTR legend,
this is not your year.
No, not happening.
Look to the future for any change on that,
much like the panel.
Okay.
So, you know, I think we can all agree that music
is the magic passport that we stamp when we land
from a flight in a place called Disney Magic.
And there is one musician synonymous with Disney
whose music transports us to a whole new world.
His songs are as fun as a trip under the sea
and he paints musical pictures more evocative
than the colors of the wind.
Sir, your music allows us to be part of your world.
And so we invite you to be our guest
in the hall of PTR legends.
I'm talking of course about J Bigga.
J Bigga, this is your year.
It had to be 2022.
You kicked off the year, J Bigga.
And ever since a censored cover of one of your songs
played in that one Incredibles ice show,
your music has captured the hearts
of some of the hosts of this podcast.
Your songs make us want to go the distance
and kiss the girl on her pink chocolate.
So what better way to pay tribute to a great artist
and now a PTR legend than to play a different J Bigga song
that was not played the last time that this came up?
Great.
And so here now from the album Laced Me Up,
as all his other classics were,
is a stirring anthem about giving a lot of notes
to a beautiful woman who is trying to fuck you.
Oh wow.
The song is called Use Your Tongue.
And here it is from non-accidental PTR legend, J Bigga.
I wish I could say
You always use your tongue
Cause that's what I'm all about
But you're doing me wrong
Now you don't know how to do it
My instructions were clear
Don't you care
I just want you to
He gave instructions and she's not following.
Don't you care
I just want you to
More chorus.
We can all sing if you want.
Just want your tongue
I just want your tongue
Use your tongue
I'm not down with your technique
It ain't kicking, it's a matter of bigger
Tongue is the problem, girl
It ain't making, I'm a do-me-do
Sexuality
I'm not too self-aware of it in a way.
Yeah, it might be a little bit.
But it's, you know, that's, I think,
haven't we all been in that position where
the day worked out great for me,
a beautiful woman is having sex with me,
but she's not doing any of the specific instructions
that I gave.
Let me clarify this through music.
And worst of all, my beat machine is broken.
It's slowly dying.
It's sputtering out.
Sputtering out.
Well, he fights through it and he makes music anyway
and his resilience, that's why we salute you, J Bigga,
as do we cuties and open-ended high status possible guests.
Well, what a closer.
And I'm just so happy that we could do this again
and we're all in this together.
And we're not doing any more rides for the rest of the year.
Okay, so,
the You Survive Podcast The Ride.
You can find us on all the socials at Podcast The Ride.
Merch is available in our T-Public store
and for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out Podcast The Ride The Second Gate
or get one more bonus episode a month
on our new tier club three.
You'll find all that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And I think, wait, it's announced, I think,
and I think it's just a few days from this,
the good boys, not the grocery good boys,
but us, the good boys, all appearing on Blank Check
with Griffin and David,
with continuing to be accidental PTR legend Griffin Newman,
talking Pinocchio, that comes out very soon.
So there's a little bit of bonus,
we're going to another podcast,
that's as exciting as the Disney,
it's not the treasure,
the Disney boat that's going to Australia.
It is the treasure.
No, the treasure's not built yet.
The treasure's not built yet,
no, a currently existing boat is going to Australia.
Shit, so embarrassing, I'm gonna edit this out.
I look like a fool.
Eggs on our, they're never gonna be on our podcast now,
these people we want.
Shit, so humiliated.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.