Forever!
Dog!
Rise and shine, Wolf Pack!
Today's activities include
a vaguely threatening song from a robotic owl,
a hike down the trail of dark money that funds oat milk,
and a refreshing swim with a fake child corpse.
Justin McElroy takes us to parent maddening waterpark
and hotel chain Great Wolf Lodge on podcast The Ride.
Music
Welcome to podcast The Ride,
a podcast about theme parks hosted by three guys who love nature.
The roof, the slides, and especially the chlorine stench.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by fellow nature lover Jason Sheridan.
I prefer to consume my nature via skylight.
It's nice, you get just a little bit,
but there's a little bit of barrier instead of that raw nature
that might fuck you up, give you a heat stroke or something.
Mike Carlson, hi.
Hi, yes, I love nature.
Have I told a story on the podcast before
about getting chased out of Joshua Tree by goats?
I tried to go into nature, and 30 goats surrounded me,
and then my friend and I drove away from there
to a different part of the park,
and then we went up a hill and it said,
watch out for the thirsty bees.
Thirsty?
Bees are so dehydrated that they will just go into your car
because they sense there's water in there.
So it was like, beware of the thirsty bees.
And I was just getting, nature was just telling me,
it doesn't want me, it does not want me out here today.
Go back to your artificial nature,
and I have gone back to it ever since.
Okay, well, a couple things.
Not thirsty as in horny.
No, the bees are not horny.
They weren't pumped by a bug,
they weren't so flower depraved.
No, I don't think they were horny,
but I think they were of a normal level of hornyness for bees.
They were thirsty as in literally dehydrated,
they had no water.
Okay, yeah, you didn't have the chance to get attacked,
in which case it might have been like,
we're getting stung, no, wait, it's something else.
The bees weren't waiting for me
at the end of the bar or anything.
There was nothing like that,
like in an old cartoon or something,
like Bugs Bunny's dress.
They all had eyelashes all the time.
How does bees have eyelashes?
You could hear the sound of their eyelashes bat,
there was like a thousand of them,
and they could all in unison were batting
their bee eyelashes at me at once.
That did not happen, that's not what happened.
Okay, well lesson learned on your part.
Again, we're talking about real nature,
and the kind of real nature that you can find
at a chain called Great Wolf Lodge.
It is a chain of indoor water parks slash hotels,
slash there's arcades and restaurants.
There are many theme parks, or what they are,
and this topic comes to us courtesy of somebody
who has been, because I don't think the three of us
have been, correct?
No.
I've only walked around a lobby.
No, I think I would get hit with a sap immediately
if I walked in.
Hit with a sap?
Like a sap or a nightstick or something,
and it's like, oh that weirdo's here alone.
That weirdo's here with another adult weirdo and no one else.
It's pretty specifically family oriented.
I think our guest went with his family,
but who knows, it might have been a solo expedition.
We will find out all the details,
and he just so happens to be a prolific podcaster
from My Brother, My Brother and Me, Adventure Zone,
and Saw Bones, it's Justin McElroy.
Hello, welcome back.
Hi, what a pleasure.
Hello, hello, hello, thanks for having me.
Oh, absolutely.
It was a pleasure to talk about Great Wolf Lodge.
Thank you for bringing this to the table.
It's one of those that I've sensed people are excited about.
I think a lot of people on our social media are excited to talk about it.
They've been wanting us to talk about it, but what do we know?
Again, I walked around a lobby for 20 minutes.
I'll bring some of that to the table, but you've put in the work.
You've really done it, and I'm already excited by just the observations that were DM'd.
Yeah.
So tell us more.
I spent a lot of human hours at the Great Wolf Lodge.
A lot of time at Great Wolf Lodge.
Wow, wow, multiple trips or one?
Oh, multiple trips, yeah.
Really?
Okay, a little context is probably helpful here.
The Great Wolf Lodge that we started going to was right next to Kings Island in Cincinnati.
Oh, yes, it's almost right by the border in the parking lot, it seems like.
It is, I mean, you can walk.
It's not uncommon to have people walk over there from the park.
There's a walking path.
It's a hall.
But there is a walking path from Great Wolf Lodge to Kings Island.
So the two work in terrible synchronicity, right?
So you can't take your kids to a hotel, even if it is a water park-themed hotel,
and see coasters in the background and be like, don't look at that.
We're not going there.
Don't look.
At the same time, we go to Kings Island and look right next door.
It's the Great Wolf Lodge.
Well, certainly you got to stay at Great Wolf Lodge if you're going.
There used to be a hotel across the street from there called Coasters was the restaurant,
and it was the Kings Island Resort.
It was seen in the Brady Bunch episode.
Is the hotel in the Brady Bunch episode?
Is that where they stay?
Yeah, they stay in the Kings Island hotel.
That's all leveled now.
So your options are like stay at a chain nearby or go to Great Wolf Lodge next door to Kings Island,
part of the Cedar Fair family.
Right, right.
We talked about that.
That park's great.
So that's a trip you've done a couple of times is the in tandem.
And you grew up with Kings Island, is that correct?
For sure, yeah.
Like where I live in Huntington, West Virginia, we have...
So we do have a theme park.
It's called Camden Park.
And that would be even more specific than Great Wolf Lodge is like no one's been to Camden Park.
But if you look up videos some day, it's a real classic.
There's a lot of...
There's an extremely old roller coaster called the Big Dipper that there's a really, really unnerving log flume.
There's a haunted house that is like something from another dimension.
The whole place is wild.
Is it unnerving because of like anything spooky or unsettling along the way or is it just...
The gum wall is a big part of the unnerving part.
That's like some 60s gum.
There's like beach nut in there.
Like I don't fool around with the gum wall at the haunted house.
But that place is a trip.
But if you want to go to an actual theme park that is more than like an hour of dodging hepatitis,
like you go to Kings Island, which is slightly less hepatitis infused than Camden Park is.
But yeah, we went to Kings Island.
Like that was the...
Like if you're in band or choir or whatever, like that was the trip that you took.
Oh, sure, sure.
At the end of the year.
So I spent a lot of time there.
Preferred it when it was owned by Paramount.
There's a lot of theming.
The Murphmobile was there for a while from Wayne's World, which is a big deal for me.
Oh, that's great.
I remember all the like...
There was a Top Gun thing.
There was Days of Thunder.
There was Italian Job when I got to go and then they had to strip it all.
Drop Zone.
That beloved Paramount property, Drop Zone.
Was that...
Is that a movie?
Yeah, it was Wesley Snipes about falling out of planes, I think.
But they rethemed all those and stripped out all the movie theming.
So like Top Gun becomes like Hang Pilot.
I don't know the new names.
Ever since they closed the vortex over there on Harbor.
Exciting plane.
Yeah.
Thrilling.
Fast train.
Thrilling undercarriage.
But Great Wolf Lodge is relatively newer in that area, right?
So that wasn't there when I was a kid.
That was like...
It predates my kids though.
I think it's been there about 12 years.
That particular location.
The chain is from the mid to late 90s.
And I think it started in the Wisconsin Dells, if you guys have ever been in that neck of the woods.
Mike has, right?
I have, yeah.
A few times.
So there's 20 of them now.
20 Great Wolf Lodges.
Okay, so here's the pitch.
It is a massive, massive resort.
And the, I mean, huge.
Really, really big.
And then connected to Evergreen Wolf Lodge, like in the center of Evergreen Wolf Lodge, is an indoor water park.
Like Wave Pool, Lazy River, a bunch of different slides, raft rides.
You know, some other like obstacle courses and things like that.
You got that big, the bucket that slowly fills up and then pours down the roof.
That classic.
Bucket.
The classic, there's this giant bucket that just dumps at whenever it feels like it.
So if you want to try to get through the park to someplace else, you're not going to stay dry because it just dumps a huge bucket of water on you.
Just keep your eyes on the bucket.
There's a restaurant.
There's a restaurant in there called Buckets, which is a delight.
The restaurant is generous.
There's a place where you can stand in a lot short list for 20 minutes and get some hummus or chicken tenders out of the deal.
Now I want to, Buckets is correct, but I want to give credit to the full name, Buckets Incredible Cravables.
Make sure we get that jargon out.
Yes, Buckets Incredible Cravables.
It's good.
You can conceptualize it.
I have not been to one of these kinds of things, but I think it's like a sandals for kids.
You know what I mean?
Like an all-inclusive, like kids show up.
You don't have to leave.
So that's like the main thing.
If you're in the room, then if you're staying in a room there, you get a band for the water park.
You get to go to the water park, which is like Great Wolf Lodge was the place when COVID really got started, where it's like, we'll know COVID is over when Great Wolf Lodge opens.
Because if you can imagine a worse environment for like spreading disease, then just like we maintain it to make it the most comfortable for all bacteria and viruses.
And all of the like, the sense that I get of it and from my brief walk around and watching videos, they're like, they just feel like a bit of claustrophobia.
This is the water park, which is a breeding ground.
But then all the hallways where you go on these adventures and stuff, which we'll talk about, but like those are all just hotel hallway.
This is not some, it's not Grand Californian sized, like expansive lobbies.
And it kind of is just like a Radisson that has some like fake nature in it.
There's nature.
There's a, there is a, gosh, it's what order to talk about these?
Okay.
So there's the water park.
There's the rooms.
They have, there's a arcade, huge arcade that is open 24 hours a day.
So if your kids wake up at 6 a.m., you can go down like, come on, let mom sleep.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we'll go down and play the minions.
VR, right.
Fine.
So I've spent a lot of mornings like, there's a Duncan inside where you can get just, if you like your, if you like your hash brown soapy, there's no better option than Duncan.
Duncan, they're nuts.
There's also like a big, they have a big buffet kind of thing.
And then there's like the, they call it, which is why there's an upscale, upscale.
There's an adult sit down dining place that they puzzlingly called the Lodge.
It's like, well, it's just, it feels like the sequel to Great Wolf Lodge and it's your restaurant.
Very difficult to Google just that restaurant.
Great Wolf Lodge, the Lodge.
The Lodge.
I was like, the Lodge is like the high end, like the hip way.
Like we're just going to the Lodge.
The Lodge.
It's like the high end, the high end version or whatever.
They've got a lot of, there's crafts and all kinds of activities for kids.
They got yoga, if you want yoga.
The weirder stuff is like, they have this thing called Magic Quest, which started as like a comparable to like a laser tag or like Q-Zar where you would like go there to do Magic Quest.
And Magic Quest is you have a toy wand.
And of course they're like all very customizable with lots of flair you can, you can buy for them.
But you have these wands and they have IR receivers in the tip.
And when you point them at things in this game, you can do like quests and collect gold and interact with things in the hotel.
There's things in the hotel where if you flick your wand at them, like the bear will talk to you or the, you know, the knight in armor will like light up or something like that.
So there, but there's also like you go to these trees that have TV screens on them and you see a man who like, he's so old.
He's like playing a wizard giving you quests.
And it's a video of this dude.
And it's like, he's so old and the stuff there is so old, like you're just faced with this certainty that this man is dead.
Like you look at it, you know, like without any doubt, like there's no way this man is still alive.
There's no way. And he's going to request from the on the grave to like go get the lightning rune or whatever.
And then you have to find other community theater actors pretending to be princesses or fairies that will give you other quests.
And like you collect the runes and you collect gold.
There's a channel on the TV that tells you who's got the most gold and class.
Wow.
How exciting for the kids to make it to the TV.
Well, it's thrilling.
Except for there is a certain class of kid that you run into a Great Wolf Lodge that you're pretty sure isn't staying there, but is on his grind.
Like usually capes are involved.
If you see a kid with like every time I go, there's at least one kid with like a cape and a wand holster who you can tell is like mom dropped off at 10 a.m.
She's like, I'll be back at three.
You knew this kid, you do it too.
And those are all.
So that's weird because it goes through the whole hotel.
So if you're walking like from your room to the lobby, like you're walking through some kids like adventure playgrounds,
playgrounds, like these little dorks running around careening into you, no awareness of where you are because they've got like a red gym to get to before the time runs out or whatever.
So that's playing out around you.
Which that like so that is mixing with like the family hauling in the suitcases and like, come on, let's go.
We got to get to the desk.
No, don't stop there.
And then some kid might like crash into you and poke your kid with a wand.
Yeah, I saw a video of like tips and tricks.
For magic, magic quest.
I also heard it called Magi Quest.
I think it might be.
Yeah, the spelling seems like but then there are Magi involved.
Right. Yeah.
Magi are a part of it.
But but some of the tips and tricks are like, take the stairs.
There's hidden stuff in the stairway, but there's also like fire escape warnings in the stairway.
Like it's a regular stairway.
Not those stairway.
And like I saw they were recording this video and a guy is just walking behind them shirtless because he's just like, look, I'm just trying to get back to my room and get some stuff.
But then the other detail was like you go through the whole resort.
However, it's it's by the elevators.
The stuff on all the floors is by the elevators.
If you hit guest rooms, you have gone too far.
Stop walking through guest rooms.
Right.
And there's they're on miserably cruelly.
They're on different floors, the different things you have to do.
So you are like up and down stairs, like trying to get to the different quest objectives.
So that's a very wild.
The the weirder thing about it is all the magic quests or magic quest, if you like, that were outside of Great Wolf Lodge have been shuttered.
So this these used to be standalone things.
They don't exist anymore.
The company itself that ran magic quest was like subsumed into the Great Wolf Lodge Corporation.
So this technology, no one seems to know how to fix it or maintain it is in no way maintain or fix.
And I think that's like institutional knowledge that no one has anymore.
Like once the treasure chest stops opening, no one seems to know that guy's gone.
That guy's long gone.
You know, he's working for another partner.
We don't have to fix anything.
There was one guy who knew how to do it.
Right. The one guy built is like, well, as long as this keeps working forever, should be fine.
He got fired.
The magi in the sky have decided that the chest will never open again.
Your work here is done.
They there's an adult.
There's like a more not adult, but there's like a more grown up version of magic quest called Compass Quest where you get imagine the thrill of casting spells with your wand.
Now imagine instead of a wand, you have an incredible compass that you can put into divots if you want.
Boy, the thrill, the sheer joy in your child's eye when they take a toy compass and put it into a compass shaped divot.
Boy, let me tell you, it is a wild and wooly experience.
And I have a feeling Jason was into compass as a kid.
I could be wrong.
I liked fiddling with my boy scout compass and I never fiddling with my compass.
Yeah, never used it well and fiddled with his compass.
I just I like turning it and like trying to get it to find north.
But then when they're like, all right, we'll align the compass and now find your bear egg and now right.
Figure out where in the sky.
And I'm like, no, this is no, we're not.
I'm not doing school to already have to go to school.
It's the weekend.
That's why friends who would go to Catechism would go to CCD.
I was like, you have to go to school after school like school to you would have liked it better if you were putting it into things and magic like thing.
Quests were unlocked.
Yeah.
Anyway, sorry.
There's no please.
There's a a show, an animatronic show that plays twice a night at the same time.
So in the lobby, there's like this big it's like it looks like a tree and the tree has a face and then there's different forest animals and a kid in the log.
And they just look at you with these like dead lifeless eyes for 22 hours and 30 minutes out of every day.
And then for a brief 15 minute window, they are brought to life to to delight parents at literal like the loudest of ear splitting, ear splitting volumes.
What makes it what makes it worse is the show is maybe 10 feet from the check in desk where the employees are.
Where the employees all are.
So imagine twice a night.
And you are you have to sit five feet from this ear splitting.
Actually, I downloaded the set the song for you all.
Oh, yeah.
The show out just so I could play a little snippet of it.
Yeah.
I think we aren't getting I can't hear it.
One sec.
Sure.
I think I have the video maybe too.
If you if you haven't.
I think I might have it here.
Wait here.
Well, you can tell us if it's the right thing.
Jordan, can we pull up a video?
I think we might have a video here.
Here, let's pause it.
We might let's keep we might want to keep going.
But just at this juncture, who's like you got to really squint to see that it is the owl.
The motion is not like a ton.
Right.
And context clues are telling you he sounds like an owl.
I think when he sings, he's got an owl vibe for sure.
Yeah.
How is singing voice?
But this is the one you were talking about.
This is every night twice.
Like there's one at seven and one day and the kids just sit down outside and they watch this great show and the staff is just subjected to it over and over and over again.
There's other weirder.
There's a place called Scoops, which is like is I think Scoops is the.
It's a kid's spa.
I had a picture from when I walked around.
Thank you.
There's an ice cream store, too, which isn't called Scoops, which is not Scoops.
Why would it be Scoops?
It's Scoops is where you get like fake nail polish on.
Right.
If you're a little girl.
It's I found something that was like paint the nails of this raccoon character and then print them out.
And you can get your nails painted and the hook is like everything's edible.
So if your kid wants to just like drink the nail polish.
Oh, that's great.
They're going to be options there.
All they've eaten for days is like buckets and edible nail polish.
And I saw there were the brunch buffet had a big cupcake display at the end.
So it's like, yeah, all my kid is eating is honeydew melon and blue cupcakes and edible nail polish and going in the water.
There are there's also a huge candy shop.
Don't forget the massive candy store and your kids.
When you when you book your room, you get for your kids what's called a paw pass.
And it's like a this really does bump it into like Sandals territory because then it's like you get the best paw pass.
Then you get like the cup full of bulk candy and you get ears and you get maybe like goggles, stuff like that.
Or you can play a free game of laser tag or a free game of light up goofy golf.
That's there. I didn't mention that there's golf.
There's bowling alley.
But but that's all packed in right, which becomes a checklist where you as a parent now, even if you didn't want to do all these things.
I mean, you've already paid for them.
So you are going to have to go, you know, play bowl and golf and all those other great activities, which are sort of like jammed into.
I found a picture I took of the bowling alley.
Ten paws, I believe.
Ten paws. Yes.
Bowling and it like that's small.
It's like in a corner.
I mean, I couldn't believe how much was packed into was where does the Anaheim one or the Garden Grove one, if you will.
I just remember thinking like, boy, everything is like it's all in corners and there seems to be this game and that's all in hallways.
And it just all felt like there's five restaurants somehow in that.
And yet the Garden Grove one, the biggest one in the in the entire chain.
And yet it felt like claustrophobic to me.
Yeah, they're very, they're very packed.
Well, that kind of goes to what I think is like so awesome about the Great Wolf Lodge experience.
And I am using that somewhat sarcastically because as much as there is for kids to do, it is openly hostile to parents in a way, in a way where no concessions have been made for your existence.
Like no concessions.
There used to be something called the wind down, W-I-N-E, wind down.
And what you do is when you check in, you order a wind down.
And that is literally at nine p.m. or whatever.
You set the time.
But after your kids are in bed, someone shows up and knocks very quietly on your door and says, here's an entire bottle and some truffles.
There you go. Enjoy.
We make you make you wait until after your kids have anything approximating pleasure.
Enjoy the cupcake Chardonnay you could have picked up at Target next door.
Less money.
I was Googling prices at Total Wine.
Drastically less than the wind down.
But maybe you get your chocolate covered strawberries, which I'm sure are absolutely.
Oh, yeah.
There's at least four of them.
And each one more delicious than the last.
That service has been discontinued.
Once you're in the room, you are in the room.
There is nothing for you.
Like you what you're you are there once your kids are asleep.
You are not leaving this room.
You are stuck there.
I've started to get into this regard not in Great Wolf Lot.
Now I've done a couple of Disney trips with my now two year old.
And we essentially invented the wind down program for ourselves without realizing this was established.
But you bring the bottle.
We've actually had a lot of fun in the realm of like, OK, let's check if the baby monitor works at the downstairs bar.
No, it stops working as soon as we get down the elevator shaft.
I guess we're in the room tonight.
Sharp tank it is.
Next to the bed.
Yeah, we tried.
But we've had, you know, eight.
Our independent wind downs have been actually very nice, I would say.
But these what my question in reading the wind down section of the Web site, here's OK, one there's different packages and one is called rekindle the bonfire.
And I'm a little uncomfortable with the oh, and then they call it a romantic package.
And I'm just going to take a stab here based on what we've talked about so far.
It's I can't imagine that Great Wolf Lodge is a great place for romance.
Oh, parental romance.
You've come to the right man to ask about romance and great little flaw.
Let me tell you, there is nothing you feel like less.
There is nothing, especially if you spent the day at Kings Island.
Right. You come back drenched, drenched in sweat.
Your kids, your rotten children make you go to the water park.
After all that, you fill up on a bunch of cotton candy and and the worst pizza I've ever had in my life.
Unthinkable, unthinkable.
This pizza, you cannot imagine how bad the pizza great lodges.
It seems like a joke. It seems like they're they're they're running a scam on you.
They can't even get like La Rosa's pizza, like a local Cincinnati pizza.
No, it's it's absolutely the worst.
And there is the in terms of like if you want alcohol, the wind down is gone.
Right. But they do know that you are basically trapped there.
And so you can't buy cans of white cloth for seven dollars.
It's like Vegas.
It's it's it's just so antagonistic that like you can't order things.
There's not like adult movie, not adult movies, but you know, like, you know, RPG 13 movies.
Yes. Right. Anything above that.
It is there is like the restaurant, the lodge is wildly unpredictable.
It's the food quality is always like about a hard sea.
It's like a good solid sea.
The one I went to one in Charlotte on our way back from a beach trip where we had to stop like halfway
and as a treat to the kids and a punishment to ourselves for being so relaxed at the beach,
we stopped a great with Lodge and Way Home and the rest of the lodge there is overlooking the the water park.
So imagine the one thing that is ostensibly an adult experience at this place
and your kids are watching other kids have fun through the glass.
Like how is your dinner going when your kids are like, Mom, let's go, let's go.
Look, they're having fun. We're missing it.
Why are we sitting here?
Just isn't anything.
Son, listen, those are subpar at best.
I love you.
I just want to finish this bad burger with a fried egg on it.
It's the only thing I have had to look forward to all day.
I'm just pretending I want to just pretend I'm somewhere else for a second.
That's like the what I weirdly kind of enjoy about it, though, aside from they have the arcade machines
where you run into these, where you are putting coins in the slot and you get trading cards out of them.
And if you get a full set of the trading cards, then you can trade them in for like a bajillion tickets.
Right. So there's a SpongeBob game, whereas you're pumping quarters in.
It will make like these different character cards fall down the slot.
And if you get all nine of them, the treatment for like five thousand tickets, which can't find a Gary.
That's how they get you.
Very it's like you're walking.
Yeah, you're walking.
McDonald's game.
It's like the McDonald game with the one that you can't find.
Exactly. So every time you walk past the machine, it's like, let me just duck in and see if I got a Gary out real quick.
No, you know, Gary. OK, moving on.
Those are those are fun.
But what I actually like about it is like I feel no.
You know, when I'm at I I love Disney a lot.
I'm wearing a Disney shirt as as we speak.
I'm a huge fan, Disney. But when I'm at Disney, there's this sense of like, if I just do the right things and like plan enough
and read enough and watch enough Disney videos and stuff, then I can really maximize this trip and really get something that the whole family is going to love.
And with Great Wolf Lodge, you just got to get through it.
And the lack of pressure there, I really love like, I don't know.
I don't care what we do. I'm just alive for 24 hours.
Then I'll leave and it'll be over. It's not miserable.
There's nothing for me here. This isn't for me.
And they seem to like really cultivate that experience of like there's no FOMO here.
There's nothing you'd like adults. Trust us.
If you're a Disney you're like, can I maneuver this to where I get a break from the kids and I get to go do Tower of Terror?
And that's exciting. Or if we plan it right, there's actually a really good restaurant in our hotel and the wine is nice and the food is like, but if you take all that off the table,
Disney is like, Disney Disney World, especially it's like a monster that you have to like slay.
You have to plan for it. You have to kill it.
And the Great Wolf Lodge is like monster. Do what you want to me.
Just take me. Yeah, you win.
I surrender myself to the Babadook.
To answer your romance question. Oh, yeah.
You should actually take a look at some of the themed rooms because the suites at Great Wolf Lodge, you can put your kids in.
You guys cuss on this show? Yeah.
Yeah, I know that.
You can put your kids in fucking Albuquerque.
There's like a bunk bed room where they are sequestered off in their own themed bunk beds.
I don't know if they lock from the outside, but I assume.
I got to say, though, I watched a walkthrough of a two story fireplace suite and I was looking at it and yeah, the bunk bedroom had a door.
But then there was a lot where like there was just a bed next to the living room and like a lofted bed area with no door.
And I'm like, so if you're bringing like extended family, if you're bringing a group here, everyone better be on good terms.
Because there is not enough walls in this suite.
No, there's not. And also it adds this.
It adds a real element of thrills when you're in a two story room with a three year old who could at any moment just just plummet right off the top.
You have to track them all of a sudden.
Now, thank you. Great Wolf Lodge.
And I have to monitor my child every second that we are in this room so they do not plummet to their doom.
But they yeah, the rooms are great.
It's like themed like bunk beds where it looks like a jungle or cave or what have you.
But the rooms can get big enough so you can put your kids way away.
The one blessing is you don't have to think about your kids while they're asleep.
You can you can store them for your convenience.
Like it's like a Victorian orphan in a shelf.
Like you just store and put away.
Don't worry about it.
There you can seems like there's some rooms where there are characters looking at you while you sleep.
That because that's something we haven't talked about yet is the characters.
The original characters who I think they do a good job making it seem like they're something even though they are just at this.
I don't know if I'm comfortable enough to like want to sleep with them like staring and playing an acoustic guitar.
While I'm sleeping.
But that's what I'm looking at.
The family of the wolf the wolf pack as it's known at this great wolf lodge is it's weird because it's like it's also another thing that relieves the pressure.
Right. If my kids see Cinderella at out in Disney World I know that I'm going to be stopping in a line for 45 minutes.
If my kids see Wiley the wolf sister Violet they're like please I have no fucking guilt whatsoever about being like absolutely not.
This I.B. is utterly contextual.
You step out that door it means nothing.
Like what kid is going to care that you got a picture with a hotel mascot.
Like it's ridiculous.
These are stars in a bubble.
The bubble bursts.
They are no longer stars.
Not unlike being a podcast.
We're all Wiley the wolf.
The famous utterly utterly exclusive to the to the premises.
The Great Wolf Lodge cinematic universe micro celebrities.
I did.
Nothing made me more feel more old than someone's.
There was a YouTube video called the evolution of the Great Wolf Lodge characters and it started off with the the characters.
And it started off with the guy who made it going like well Great Wolf Lodge part of all of our childhoods and I'm like what.
What.
No.
Oh.
This is mid two thousands.
That's that's that's crazy.
No one is a child from no one was a child then.
I know I messed up your video trying to show you Wiley Wiley the wolf.
This is the original.
You know what I'll do it.
What I'll do is I'll drop a link to this in the chat.
So somebody who can can pull this up in a tasteful way.
Oh sure.
Yes.
Jordan you see it privately.
Jordan cats are the original.
That is the original actual design of Wiley the club club when they were in the club club Wiley.
They've done it.
Yeah they've done like a Chuck E.
Cheese on him though where he used to look cooler and now he's been like kid.
Yeah.
Yeah he used to be a lot more like a wolf.
You know a cool.
Yeah he had a real cool mean.
Cool mean dead eyed and weird.
Is that your definition of cool Mike.
Yeah.
In this instance it is.
They have these there's a channel there where they just play this storybook about the founding of Great Wolf Lodge and it's about like Wiley and these two brothers tooth and nail that are like.
Oh here we go.
Oh my God.
Wait what is this weird clip art.
That's the original Wiley the wolf from the Great Wolf Lodge website like the first time that people were exposed to this guy.
This is what they saw this nightmarish new ground.
Her.
This is a.
This is unsettling.
He's waiting to be claimed by the right wing.
But they're walking around and it's like I mean kids love them in the sense that like they the kids that love costume characters will be into it but it's not like.
They're not characters outside of the of the resort and there's plenty of like merchandise and and everything celebrating these these great characters but.
There are so many characters on this Wikipedia.
Yeah yeah there's Wiley's got a rich a rich anybody jumping out of your mind that no one cares about.
Oh yeah.
Princess Pumpkin.
She was a lady in the leaves a lady in the leaves the air in cloud crest.
What.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah the lady in the leaves is a magic quest character right.
That you interact with to get like your your.
They have a lot of Magi or magic quest characters in this Wikipedia like a Beraxas or Sherlock the red dragon.
Oh Sherlock is fun that's an actual like there's a big screen TV with that's showing this dragon and you have to go in and fight him with your with your wand by casting.
Increasingly I did learn I did learn that how to beat the red dragon.
I did not watch the video to watch how to beat the silver dragon.
Real quick.
Let me show you this.
You got to use the.
I think Scott you're going to be very interested in this and I don't know how this is going to make you feel I don't know if you've seen this already.
Hold on let me just make sure I pull this up so.
It is a bear named Sprinkles.
Oh I think I've got this yes.
This is a bear.
A little familiar.
Yeah I think actually are someone in our Facebook group noted this because just in context I'm really into the bear who only lives in the Rocky Mountain chocolate factory chain of candy stores.
His name is truffles and he's very obese and sad and my wife and I always feel like comforting him and I yeah there's sort of a truffles esque sprinkle.
You said yeah sprinkles.
Sprinkles is he's too happy look problem is I don't want to cheer him up he's fine he doesn't need a hug.
He got a huge PPP loan sprinkles is sad like sprinkles never stop working but he got a little cushion just in case you know.
Yeah so he but he is I wonder what came first I wonder if they ripped off.
Oh I guarantee truffles came first that that chain's been part of our culture since maybe the 80s I don't know our heritage our heritage.
Yeah.
Heritage.
So yeah the the it's just the experience the way it really sets itself apart from from Disney and other like parks like this.
There's a lot of hotels that have water parks right in them.
They are the displeasure that they cause adults that the there is no way to spend your way out of it like the one thing you know about me is that.
I do have some money because I got this room can I please get I an adult give you some money to make this pleasant anyway and they like they look down at you and they say we know you would give us money to make this better.
We're not going to allow you it would sully whatever this bizarre social experience experiment that we're running is you cannot pay to improve this experience that you can't pay to like you if it was Disney you would be paying to.
Exclusive genie parking spaces that you don't have to haul your bags through a half mile hallway to get to your room.
They would you know they would charge you for like you know we'll put food and drinks in your know you can't do any of that you are making your there's is very regular to see families walk through the halls with coolers because they're just that unwilling to participate in the the Great Wolf Lodge.
Justin because you mentioned hostile amenities I have to have to mention a thing I noticed in one of the video walk people have put up tours of the various lodges and in the one video I saw by like the parking lot by like a side door into the parking lot there are all these carts and I was like that cart looks very familiar what is that and I realized it's the cart that's in the great wolf lodge.
So it's like the cart you pay five bucks for at the airport to throw your luggage on if you like have a full family's worth of luggage and you have to push it out to a rental car and I'm like at least at Disney they have standard bellhop carts and they have bag services people that will like take care of this for like you're like okay at least I don't have to do this is much more clearly set up of like all right take that.
Cart to your car load up your luggage and yeah walk the half mile through hallways and side doors up to your room little little wizards.
Little wizards.
Quests getting in your way.
Don't nail the little wizard with your away luggage sliding off the cart.
The first thing you have to do is go have your wristband scanned what you use wristbands everywhere so oh did I mention you're spending the entire time with this plastic wristband that they like a fixed to your wrist that you cannot remove at all because it's what you use to get to the water parks so it has to say there's you sleep in it you have to like you cannot remove this thing.
Yeah because you can't you can't take it off because they don't want you handing your things so somebody else can go to the water park and your stead right when you get to the water park you have to scan your badge and they are your your band and they ask you how many towels you want and you tell them the number of towels you check out the towels for a period of time and if you don't return your wet sopping towels to them like before you leave they charge you for something else.
And let me tell you guys luxury you got it yeah there we go the high thread count on these beautiful towels you're going to want to take some of so they had to curtail the theft of these these horrific glorified watch cloths but he has the best you can't take the towels out of the water park but you're really going to want to take some of these towels.
So they had to curtail the theft of these these horrific glorified watch cloths but he has the best you can't take the towels out of the water park but your room is not in the water park so they have committed you to sloshing them always shirtless and embarrassed and so you're like your teeth chattering you can't even bring your towel back to your room with you and return it there.
Well children run around with capes they have extra clothes they have more clothes than you usually have and you have less right.
Yeah I feel like everyone I feel like this is a humid vacation this is a clammy like as soon as you walk into the vacay the building your clammy you know.
Yeah it is a very sweaty environment.
It's sort of it seems like a big idea of this chain is this is a place where you can go have active water park fun even when the weather is very yes that's a lot of why they've put them in a lot of the places because what are some of the it's like there's the Poconos we're talking about.
Yeah.
That gets stormy I would imagine.
I was going to bring up the Poconos because my family used to go to a resort called the Mountain Laurel Resort and the Poconos and even in the early 90s they were ramping up their indoor pool like complex this was like a resort that was still doing pretty well at the time had a lot of activities had like more restaurants than this better restaurants than this where where mom and dad could go.
The whole family could eat dinner and then one or two nights during your trip mom and dad would go alone and they would leave the kids with like daycare activities kind of things.
But I looked up that resort a couple years ago and I was like wow it hasn't changed it hasn't changed anything since the 90.
I looked it up this morning it seems to be doing well it seems to be getting more towards modern amenities but yeah I think this was a big thing catching on in the Poconos of year round indoor water parks for people who don't want to go skiing or like just just families who just want to get away and maybe you'll hike for 30 minutes one day and the rest of the time you'll be at the water park which is very humid and you have to you get your water to the water park.
And you have to you get used to the chlorine smell or at least you better but you're for sure going to get a headache one day.
They there's no daycare options at Great Wolf Lodge which seems weird until you remember that you might experience some pleasure if you left your children with somebody else for a little while.
So they can't have that they can't have you enjoy not not attending to your children because that might bring you joy as a parent and they are very much in the business of not allowing that to happen at any point.
Oh wait so this is a question for you Justin that you were because you were alluding to even though you would gladly throw money at them to give you something that you want there's no way to do that.
Yeah you know in terms of plussing it up something we talk about on the show what would you like if if you could hand over 50 hundred more dollars to make something happen there.
What do you what do you want. What's the Great Wolf parent plus up that would make the thing better.
It would have to be it would have to be a different.
It would have to be a different adjacent resort.
So contemptible is everything from the aesthetics to the offerings at Great Wolf Lodge to me the discerning adult.
It would have to be like cigarette Joe's Island getaway and it's like next door.
You have to pay a thousand dollars and you can leave your kids at the door.
There was a tunnel in your room to a different resort that the parents could go through a secret.
After the kids are asleep right you can slide down like the water slide like check you just slide down.
All the parents in a tunnel come with me. I know of a place I can provide you passage.
Yeah there's no atheist and foxholes but everyone's a smoker at the Great Wolf Lodge.
You're just like I don't usually crave cigarettes but I would love to go outside alone and smoke a pack right now.
I'm going to have the first cigarette of my life here outside Great Wolf Lodge.
There is a I will I will mention and I guess this is a concession to adults in some sense because the pool in the water park.
There is Grizzly Rob's Bar which is a it says the description of the website is feeling the need for some cool refreshment.
Grizzly Rob's is the place to quench your thirst with soft drinks island inspired cocktails and an extensive beer list.
Stop by for an invigorating break at noon after a day of 84 degree water park play or anytime the spirit moves you.
Spirits being the operative. Yeah and you will never see parents more broken down than parents at 11 o'clock a.m.
like lined up for margaritas at Grizzly Rob's Bar like yeah yeah I know they're mostly iced.
I just need to feel something. Please Grizzly Rob set me up.
Have you had a drink at Grizzly Rob's?
I don't have time for the lines at Grizzly Rob's.
So what I will do is get a there is a buckets.
You can get a frozen pina colada and that is the one offering they have there in terms of like alcohol.
There may be beer. I'm not I'm not a big beer guy.
But it seems like you have to come in with a plan and the plan might help you or not do anything for you depending on where the Great Wolf Lodge is.
Because like it seems like that Ohio one you maybe could go find a target or something like if you wanted to sneak your little bottles in or whatever.
Or like the Anaheim one you know is close enough to like there's stores very close.
But if it's a diss if it's a resort like truly in the middle of nowhere then you got nothing right.
You really there's really you got to like plan for that and come in with your adult amenities.
If you plan ahead you can like there's a fridge in the room right.
You can like bring your own stuff and plan ahead.
If you don't though the it's I'm going to sound like I'm overshading it but like the parking lot I don't know how they make it so far from your room.
But the farthest distance that there is on earth is the distance from your room at Great Wolf Lodge back to your car.
And also if you move your car pretty good chance you're going to have even worse.
When you come back punished as someone will slip in there no questions asked will slide right in.
So yeah it is it is a real crap shoot to to leave to go anywhere.
There is like some convenience stores across the way.
The the dunk I mentioned right which doesn't sound that wild right.
There's Duncan's everywhere but it's the only coffee that you can get in the resort.
Whoa. So imagine if you will eight thirty in the morning at the Dunkin in a Great Wolf Lodge I mean lines out the door.
I mean like beyond because everyone wants coffee and this is the place where they will give you a cup of coffee.
So everyone at the hotel every adult that drinks coffee has to wait in line for for their coffee and the line is unfathomable to a point where I have gone to my car driven to the adjacent Dunkin half mile away.
They go through the drive through and get my dishwater hash browns from from an outside vendor rather than wait in the lines there at the Great Wolf Lodge.
Oh my God. Yikes yikes.
These are boy this is bizarre. This is all so fun to talk about.
Oh yes Mike I have I have checked you cannot mobile order.
No you absolutely cannot mobile order the dog.
That's convenient.
No no no not great lodge. You wait in the line.
You're waiting that you might enjoy skipping the line.
Do you love your family or not.
We're going to be together.
Can I just read some copy that's that that just jumped out at me from the Great Wolf website.
You know it.
The big thing and this is this is recurring in a lot of their spots and stuff you know arrive as a family leave as a pack at Great Wolf Lodge.
So that that's kind of on a lot of their stuff but that it's the next couple sentences that stuck with me.
Experience a world of play all under one roof.
Go with the flow in our water park resort or find adventurous dry play throughout the lodge.
How do we feel about dry dry adventurous adventurous dry dry play.
None of Jason's gold bond involved.
No there's no town.
First of all that would be dry play no town.
That would be because it's powder because Jason was adventurous dry plays with if it's the talc but the lotions are for it.
It feels like just a bunch of lorem to like fill in because like it doesn't we don't care if you want to come or not adult.
We just put some garbage in here.
Your kids are going to make you go.
How do you do.
How do you do fellow humans.
Are you excited for leisure.
Is mad adult like.
Yeah we're an adult like you here at Great Wolf Lodge.
We have the Iron Horse Fitness Center.
You can exercise your commitment to health and well-being in our fitness room.
We offer a perfect selection of cardio and weight training equipment flat screen TVs and towel service so you can stay on top of your game or begin a new.
Imagine you're going to start a new commitment to fitness.
Great Wolf Lodge.
This is my moment.
I'm going to start now.
Well I want to get attractive enough to leave my terrible family.
I will maybe come here if I can get in shape enough to have an affair.
I might experience something.
Fly away from this place.
Then maybe what maybe Wiley's sister Viola will look at me.
The Iron Horse Fitness Center is next to the glow in the dark golf and I've never seen a single human being in it as long as I've lived.
I've never seen one.
Well Justin there's a reason for that because the entirety of Great Wolf Lodge is a treadmill.
You're running and running and you're not getting away.
Dad take your one.
Go up the stairs.
The next quest is on floor six.
The next quest is back on the bottom floor.
All right back up to eight.
Well you raise you do raise a good point Justin.
This this might be a terrific place to have an affair because I don't think anyone's going to be looking for you.
Private eye like they're not letting anyone in with a private eye like a long telephoto lens like oh no pal.
No you're not coming in here.
You're talking about an affair that's deep enough along that it would be on the old show cheaters.
Where private investigators.
Yeah a sleazy James Elroy style private investigators tracking you.
I'll find your man I will.
I'm sorry Miss Wilson I had real good tabs on him and then I lost him in a crowd of one thousand unhappy adults that look like just facing utter mortal panic.
Every single one of them look exactly the same.
He seems to get into a dunk of wine.
Slides a picture on the desk and the affair is actually like obscured by a thousand little wands that are on the top.
The kids holding the wands.
Like you can see they're making out here behind all these wands.
I can't see that.
No I really.
I think some children conspired to use magic against me to defeat my private eye skills.
I did my best.
Could I real quick.
My talk about the found the founders.
Oh yeah.
I'm very excited.
I am excited.
I did not go to the Great Wolf Lodge when I the couple times I went to the Wisconsin Dulles as a youth but I definitely went to their other creation which is Noah's Ark water.
Noah's Ark.
Yeah you've brought this up before.
It feels familiar to me but I don't I don't recall much about it.
Yeah Noah's Ark is not I mean it's obviously somewhat religious like that's what it's called.
But that's like the top.
That's like the the water park in Wisconsin that you go to.
Then it's got the biggest slides and everything and I don't know if it's still in America right.
It's massive.
I think so.
Yeah.
It was definitely like all the that was like what you would do if you were a kid like if you didn't go there you were you may as well not have come back because it was the cool one.
And my mom we I begged to go there because my mom was very afraid of me going to a water park.
This is the place where you were denied.
You've told this one that you were you were shut down from like kids birthday parties.
I was denied.
No I did go here but I was denied.
She wouldn't let us go with like just kids and other kids families that she didn't trust even they were friends of mine.
So we would like lie and say why I didn't go.
She'd be like oh we have to go.
You know it's I think here's one of my favorites.
It would be like it's our anniversary and the kids and I are and Jeff are all doing something.
So this would be the regular birth like because it would always be the same birthday water park and it would always be the same.
Wait but then you would it wasn't your anniversary and you would not do anything.
We would never we would barely do anything.
Yeah we surely you couldn't have gone to Bennegan's another night.
Maybe we went to Bennegan's it's possible we went to Chili's or something.
There's you know I talk about these five timers these stories that we tell this one I think you need to tell at least once a year just to remind everyone where you're coming from.
Important context.
These you know what to be here.
Let me give let me give my mom some credit.
This was the family that would invite us that also called her once and said also I want to let you know we have a gun in the house and the boys know where it is.
So as much as my mother was a little overprotective I guess I have to give her.
Yeah well hold on a second hold on a second.
Did you get to see it.
I did not.
Also I did not go over to that house for many years.
That's fine.
That's fair.
Although I did see the one brother shoot the other brother at two feet close range with a BB gun.
Whoa.
Oh my god.
In the back.
Because they were fighting.
Okay well they wanted one of the sorry I'm so sorry.
One of the brothers was on the roof with the BB gun shooting at his brother when we like rolled up there.
And then the other brother just as like as like a kind of a psych out was like fine come down here took his shirt off got down like this shoot me in the back and I'll show the scar to mine.
And then he did it.
It happened.
We watched it happen in the back.
Imagine that feeling for 24 hours.
That's great wolf lodges in the doll.
It's basically like getting shot in the back with a BB gun by your brother.
And you that you asked for it.
You paid for it.
You wait there.
Your kids doesn't have a credit card.
They can't get there without you.
There's nothing to be scared of here.
You said it so many times.
I feel like there's a lot to be scared of here.
Yeah that's where the song starts and then it keeps getting said.
Jack and Andrew Waterman are the two gentlemen.
The famous water park founders the waterman.
It's so weird.
And then they yeah they they know as arc was first and then they they created great will fludging like 97.
So it's so recent.
Yeah.
For something that has so many locations really bizarre how quickly it's taken up but Noah's Ark has some some magic to it.
Like you could see why another business would be appealing from from the waterman's.
Oh I loved I love Noah's Ark.
It was awesome.
It was like I was scared of a lot.
I was scared a lot of the slides believe it or not.
But like it had enough thing enough things for a kid to get very excited.
And it was just massive.
How much.
How much Noah.
See there's a there's not really much religious stuff and I got to dig back in and maybe there was in the old days.
But it seems like they've it seems like they're it's a very secular telling of Noah's Ark if that's even part of it because it's not there's no like religious theme slides.
And didn't realize Noah did hang loose so much.
You know.
Yeah.
This might.
Yeah this is.
Yeah I would imagine that there was a little more religious tie a little more of a religious tie in early on.
But how.
How is it water park wise just judging it as a water park Justin.
I hate.
I hate water.
It's really hard for me to judge because I I will say it's a little better being in an indoor environment where you don't have the sun beating down on you while you're standing in line for a ride.
That that I appreciate.
I mean I I I but like for example I've been to Disney I don't know how many times never been to like Blizzard Beach or any of those I have zero interest in water parks.
Every time we go to Great Wolf Lodge I live in this tiny bit of hope that my kids would be like I don't really feel like doing the water park this time dad let's just do anything else for the entire day.
I mean the rides are are my kids won't do any of the fun slides so it's pretty much just standing in the wave pool trying to keep them from drowning.
That's the bulk of it.
That seems stressful.
Yeah it is very stressful even the lazy river is just them trying to fall out of the inner tube get swept away by the current.
That's not much not much fun.
Well it feels like you're just a lifeguard.
Well look.
Yeah they've got.
Yeah they definitely have lifeguards and I know about the lifeguard system because and I can't believe this this might be the first topic we've ever done on the show that has been the topic of an episode of undercover boss.
There was a early on in the show.
The then CEO Kim Schaefer went undercover and worked at a lot of the restaurants worked at the front desk which really gave you like the tenor of who comes there.
Like so people so upset at the front desk.
I told you I wanted a high room.
OK we only have floor three.
Is that OK.
Well it's going to have to be.
Oh you're on tell you're willingly on television acting like this.
But then but one of the things she does is she works with the lifeguards and a couple interesting things happen here.
You get to see the training and you know that the lifeguards are trained and have to stay on their toes at all times because on just a regular day not even in the pre work training they might have to pass something called the Timmy test and the Timmy test is when unannounced a different
lifeguard throws a very realistic dummy with a big like gaping open mouth.
Like it looks like an already deceased child.
I mean a CPR dummy but like with a little more going on so that it has like limbs a Kimbo Timmy might get tossed into the wave pool and you have 15 seconds to notice Timmy and rescue Timmy and get him out of the water which is.
And the test that I saw that was on the show was considered successful at 13 seconds which is pretty good.
That guy's on it.
But what a stressful thing for the lifeguards that Timmy might show up and for the guests.
You might just have what you think is a like it looks like an almost dead E.T.
The Timmy test is the watch a child drown simulator like I mean guys I mean I'll grant you that that's a wild practice but like I would like to keep the lifeguards with their head on a swivel for drowning kids.
I mean I don't want to I definitely do want them to have an eye out.
Yeah.
I mean I'm sorry that has to how often I mean they don't get false alarms right.
They're going to get dull every once in a while you got to give a little.
Stay on.
Yeah.
Not a job you can stop paying attention to it at any second.
So that is that yes.
Well bizarre.
Probably a good thing that they do.
I also learned a little bit of the lingo something that you get to see in this episode.
We recently were just because of mission space obviously mission space you end up with a lot of vomit and the euphemism we were discussing protein spills.
There is a different kind of thing that we were discussing in this episode.
We were discussing protein spills.
There is a different euphemism at Great Wolf Lodge and that is AFR.
We got an AFR and the AFR stands for accidental fecal release.
Oh great.
I don't know what happened.
I just ate.
I ate the world's worst pizza and milkshakes for 24 hours straight.
I got diarrhea.
Come on.
You don't want me to poop in the pool.
You got to serve a vegetable in here somewhere.
Yeah.
No telling if the if the AFR was from a child or from a man in his 40s.
I got it.
I'll tell you how was work today honey.
Awful.
We had a Timmy test in the morning and then an AFR right after.
I think my boss is out to get me.
And I was so scared by the Timmy test.
I had an AFR.
I should have led with that.
I'm sorry.
With our new fleet of ultra realistic Timmy's, Timmy can serve not just for the Timmy test,
but we can squirt AFRs out of him.
As your red string just falls around the way.
You have to grab Timmy with one hand and grab the AFR with the other.
That is the experience of being a pair of great old flogger.
They have replicated it almost exactly.
If you can get at least 85% of the AFR in your hand on the first grab, then you are up to par as far as lifeguards.
We got the chunks.
We can't expect him to get the liquid.
His lifeguard is only 17.
What's he going to do?
The end of this episode of Undercover Boss.
She's just holding a lightly singed Timmy doll and she's just covered in shit.
Everyone's getting a $3 raise.
Everyone's getting a $3 an hour raise immediately.
I'm so sorry.
I'm going to go try to get hired at Lockheed Martin.
Literally anything.
Please.
Somehow less crimes against humanity at Lockheed Martin.
There is no fun involved.
Not any capacity for fun.
Well, one more thing.
We can stifle it down a little.
But the crimes against humanity, I think it's time to transition into the crimes against humanity section.
Justin, do you know anything about where your money is going when you go to Great Wolf Lodge?
Okay, now guys, here's the truth of this.
I was so afraid that you all would have to.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
We have to.
I have worked.
No, no, no, because I don't know.
And I've worked so you don't have to be in that place 30 seconds before you realize, like, I would not like where this is headed.
Like, you might start climbing up this ladder.
I'm not going to enjoy where it is.
So, no, I have not looked into it.
Maybe maybe I've had my last trip to Great Wolf Lodge.
But I've remained.
Well, here, let me let me build up before I get to the real source of it.
I started looking up some stuff.
This is the section of my notes just titled Shadiness.
This isn't about the owner as much as I this the Garden Grove location, the only one that I've been to that I walked around a little.
It didn't just feel so odd to me and so barren.
And then it's like it's kind of in its where Harbor Boulevard, it's south of Disneyland.
And it's where it starts to get a little barren and residential.
Like you're finally out of it that it's that every hotel chain has a location and there's a Fleming steakhouse and a Morton's and all that.
Like it's starting to get into just like regular kind of low income OC and a lot of weird stuff.
Garden Grove paid for the whole lot of the garden.
The city of Garden Grove, trying to track people away from Anaheim, footed the bill for like 20 million dollars to have the site prepared.
So they're throwing so much money at it.
They had to the Great Wolf Lodge had to pay one point nine million to settle the cost of relocating 30 low income families living in a trailer park on the property.
So they evicted a trailer park in order to get Great Wolf Lodge built, not counting the legal fees for getting them out.
And then still, it's not like Garden Grove was super site like corporate Garden Grove was excited.
But the neighbors were like, I don't know if I want a six story water funnel in my backyard.
And you know who won this fight because Jordan, if we could pull up the photo I have, look at the view that you have.
If you.
I mean, the streets fine.
You'd happily live on the streets, not like a sad street, but it's made much more bizarre by full waterslide, multiple mismatchy colors of water slides exploding out of this building at the end of your block.
It looks like Dr. Strange has used his fractal magic to draw together a regular neighborhood.
Yeah, there goes the neighborhood.
It's the weird thing about that location because a lot of these are sort of in nature in the mountains, but this Anaheim one, it's yeah, it's bizarre that it's just right next to that.
There's just like a Walgreens right there.
These poor, oh God, like you've survived getting Disney Firework Ash in your yard for decades, but at least you didn't have a water funnel out your kitchen window.
The ownership status of Great Wolf Lodge is its own adventure because at one point in time there was a, what I read described as a rare public bidding war where like companies were going back and forth where it's like I'll buy the company $4 a share, $4.55, $5.75.
Like they're literally doing like an auctioneer getting it.
And so they've had a couple owners and then a few years ago, 65% of operational control or controlling interest, I believe is the phrase I saw, is now 65% by the company Blackstone.
So the company that owns a lot of real estate in America, the company that probably owns some of those houses on that street also owns this.
Pricing out, yeah, they're the big company when you hear about fucking up the housing market and like let's buy all the houses and rent them out in full cash so that people can't buy starter houses anymore.
They also fund rainforest deforestation in the Amazon.
The CEO donated like $15 million to Mitch McConnell's Super PAC.
The CEO was the head of when Trump got elected and there was like he got like a consortium of CEOs that Bob Iger was briefly on and then left.
But there was some like I don't even remember the name of the committee, but like Super Trumper.
It's a it's an incredibly evil organization that OK, let me list some things that in addition to Great Wolf Lodge, if you partake in any of this, you're putting money into fucking up the housing market and the rainforest.
All the bush parks, the SeaWorld, Bush Garden, Sesame Place, they own the Willis Tower, the former Sears Tower.
They own Motel 6.
They own the Cosmopolitan Aria and the Vidara in Vegas.
And then you get into the products.
Oatly, they own the oat milk.
Ancestry is these people.
I'm doing an ancestry of them straight to evil.
They own Bumble.
Honey, do you remember the place where we met and then we fell in love, darling Jane?
Oh, you guys are Bumble.
Yeah, we met on Bumble.
Yeah.
Guess what else they own?
It's you know, it's weird.
What I can't figure out from all this is why you guys have me on this episode when I've never paid to go to Great Wolf Lodge my entire life.
Holy ignorant until this moment.
I've met, you know, I thought about going, but gosh, with that kind of corporate history, I mean, I never would have dreamed of it.
They have their hands in so many pockets like you can't avoid.
They fund both the politicians that complain about coastal liberal elites drinking their oat milk and then they're funding the oat milk.
And and the best one in the list, Spanx.
Blackstone, the evil equity firm owns Spanx.
There's no way around it.
This is just how we have to live.
Somebody else that says, hey, podcast, the right has many guests on there.
What's that vibe like?
And I have to tell me, just fucking do your research before you go in there.
They're going to Edward, Edward Armuro you and the wait to do it.
Well, it's interesting.
I'm glad you've had such a good podcast equivalent.
We dump animal blood on you.
You're complicit.
We all any time that's what it's like to be a parent at Great Wolf Lodge, you're getting animal dumped on blood on you and you people are shouting you're complicit.
You're complicit and they're not an animal blood release.
Any time we try to do it like an inoffensive, just what seems like a bland topic.
Inevitably, you get to the second page of Google results and it's like, oh, no, what's this Isaac Chotner interview in the New Yorker?
Oh, no. Who's he got up against the wall related to like, you know, fun of moles or whatever.
Well, so I'm sorry if you've taken this as finger pointing.
This was not the intent. Yeah.
If anything, I hope that it makes you feel better about that.
Do you feel more justified in what has been frustrating about this place?
In this there is a sense where like this does feel like on top of the final indignity.
We're like, it doesn't.
This pleasure is permanent.
It is not in when you leave the premises.
You're carrying it around with you for the entirety of your life.
I have to respect the hustle that they have towards making me feel bad.
Emotionally, there's a little bit of the Joker like, where do they get those wonderful toys?
Like, oh, you got me again, guys.
Got it.
That's good.
Yeah. In their defense, the animated film about the Great Wolf Lodge characters seems kind of cute and nice.
Nothing about the trailer upset me.
So they're trying to like make the characters where, you know, you maybe could experience them outside.
So there's the movie The Great Wolf Pack, a call to adventure.
And this seems fine.
Now, I'm not going to think about what how it was funded.
I just think that Wiley and Oliver Raccoon and especially Brinley Bear are looking their best.
And it looks like a fun adventure.
I wish the watermen's never sold, you know?
That's right.
They're. Yeah.
If we can focus on the dream of the watermen's.
Yeah.
They just wanted to make a family into a pack.
And right.
Do you feel like not a super not a super pack?
Not a super pack.
Yeah, that's where we got lost.
We went from packs to super packs.
That's right.
Make sure.
Is this a real movie?
Like, will this be out in theaters?
Like, so it's about 10 days ago as we record.
This is so timely, guys.
I'm so impressed with you.
Strange.
I don't know.
I think, well, I'm not sure.
I think maybe you can like buy this stream this or something.
But what I love is that it becomes a movie that you can watch on Great Wolf Lodge TV.
Reminiscent of my favorite thing that there was this hour long Treasure Island movie where you get to see Steve Wynn act.
And it only played in Treasure Island.
It's a nice throwback to that.
So the next time you go, the next time that you're sure to happily go with your pack, you can watch this movie.
Is there some sort of is there some sort of morality offset that I can do where I have to pay my credits to a good organization to justify my presence in Great Wolf Lodge?
What's the opposite of I don't know.
Yeah, I guess like helping low income housing or this is you shouldn't have to do penance.
It's tip 200 percent at the lodge.
As if you're serving.
No ethical consumption under capitalism.
So title of this episode, that's extra true.
Yeah.
Any any closing thoughts?
Have we have we washed away all your bad or any good memories into I feel lighter lighter.
This has been really this has been good to get off my chest.
All right.
Well, well, perfect.
Boy, what a fun thing to talk about.
Crazier that I thought it would be.
Justin McIlroy survived.
Fuck has the ride.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
We are going to be my family and I we do live shows for our podcasts.
We're going to be in San Jose doing the Adventure Zone, which is our role playing podcast on the twenty ninth.
We're going to be there doing my brother, my brother, me on the thirtieth at the San Jose Civic.
And then October 1st, we're in Denver at the Temple Hoyne Buell Theatre doing my brother, my brother, me.
So that'll be very soon, I bet.
As you're listening to this.
So if you can get tickets at McIlroy, McELROY dot family.
Fantastic.
And you could probably pair it all up.
You go to the Denver show and then you go to the Colorado Springs Great Wolf Lodge.
Perfect.
I always encourage people to stay at the Great Wolf Lodge.
Jason, it's the perfect experience for your childless podcast fan.
You're really going to love this.
This is really going to be.
Well, that was an early discovery for me with this is that like looking up videos of it there, they have made no outreach to vlogger to like childless vloggers and stuff.
They've made no marketing push.
Most theme parks of various sizes been like, oh, these people do free marketing for us.
Give them some tickets.
Not the case.
We can get Jason.
Let's see if we can get you down and that sounds like we can get you on a calm room.
It's impossible to say for sure, but I've never seen an adult there who did not obviously have like was not either obviously a parent or had a children, a child like present with them.
I've never seen like, let's just go to the lodge tonight and enjoy a nice dinner.
Hello, sweetheart.
This definitely this feels like maybe the first thing in podcast right history where I'm like, I am not welcome.
They may as well have those nuclear site like this is not a place of honor signs.
Private eyes.
They're going to be watching you.
Yeah, I'm just looking.
Listen, if you just look exasperated the entire time, no one will bat an eye.
Oh, yeah.
I'll take a wand, please.
I'm going to email the PR at Blackstone and ask if we could send our cub reporter Jason share them to one of the great wolf lodges.
Blackstone dot com literal literal cub reporter in this case.
He'll be by by staying there.
He gives his name and his likeness over to a bear like creature named Jason the bear.
I'm I'm happy to chaperone Scott and his son because chaperone chaperone.
Yeah, I've never been chaperone.
I'm happy.
As you said, you were on your own if you ever had to go to this.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I told Justin that I had the agreement with my wife already was if I were ever to take my son down here that it is just dad and son.
And now I wonder if dad has to get removed from the equation.
So Uncle Jason.
Yeah, please let me know how that goes.
Please go.
I don't know any other adults have been to great with watch.
I would really love to hear your thoughts on it because it is a unique a unique still, you know, after all this pay to get in there.
You're going to sneak in.
Uncle Jason is invited and be shot.
So you just give Scott one every hour to keep him going.
Just a B12.
Help me, my friend.
I'm suffering.
Well, yeah, we'll see.
I'll report on that.
Hey, thanks to Jordan Katz, who produced this episode.
Welcome to the show, Jordan.
You can find us on all the socials at podcast, the ride merch is available in our T public store and for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast, the ride, the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our new tier club three.
You'll find all that at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride, not dark money.
There's no dark.
You consider it that the money might flow through me eventually to Great Wolf Lodge and then to Blackstone.
But that's a long ways away and not yet.
So your money this month won't go to Blackstone.
I could promise that.
It's a temporary promise.
All right.
So long pack.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.