Club Three.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride Club Three, the world's first youngest,
is the enemy of progress and innovation.
So let's, we're here to keep it pumped up.
We're here to keep you inter-gaged today.
Yeah, you're gonna be so inter-gaged by this episode.
Mike Carlson is ready to inter-gage you.
Yeah, the only thing we need to get the audience hyped up about us is a high energy video from
someone like a Jim Davis who can really just fire people's loins up.
They fire people to get excited about something.
The magnetism of that man.
Which I think, I don't know, yeah, we'll get there, but I don't know that I ever really
heard an interview with him before and I love it now.
I know what you mean, yeah, I could not, I know the visual of him.
I mean, I'm not surprised by the way he sounds compared to how he looks.
It seems right, but there is something about just hearing it for a while, especially discovering
it because of a man who seems to think he's like God.
Yes.
Yeah.
Yeah, who's working with, was working with Jim Davis very closely according to this video
by Jim Davis.
And imagine having to give that up.
I mean, that's the drama.
If you don't know exactly what we're talking about, somebody being stripped of their right
to spend time with Jim Davis, the creator of Garfield.
We'll get into it.
We started a business before we get there, Club 3 business.
Today's topic won by the biggest margin we've seen, probably propelled along by us cheating,
increasing the weight.
Pretty heavily endorsed, which is our want to do.
There's no rules here.
We can endorse things and that might backfire.
People actually might pick something that we don't want to do one day, including, which
sort of happened in the like in the lead up and we were like gathering the nominees,
the most support went to something that we did not put in the poll.
And that is the idea that Evan Susser would come on and tell the full story that we censored
about his experience at Sesame Place.
Something happened in a bathroom and we elected to instead play us the song moves like Bert.
I remember that.
Maroon 5 parody.
I just wanted to address that really quick and just say we talked about it, right?
We did not bring it up to Evan Susser, who's a busy man.
And I just want to say before we bring this to put before we even put this on his desk,
I think we need more of a plan here because we talked about it.
We all know the story.
Everyone in this room knows the story.
And what we can tell you, the audience who doesn't know it, it's not going to make you
happy.
No, it's unpleasant.
And I, but I'm also worried I miss remembering some stuff because you said we remember Jason
does not remember the story.
I may be making it worse in my head.
So you might be because I don't think it's as bad as you do.
Maybe I miss under next story.
Interpreting something.
Okay.
I'm going to tell you both the story and I'm going to play moves like Bert over it.
No, no, I'll do it.
I want to remind you.
I want to see if we're on the same page about it.
All right.
Okay.
Listeners, get ready for the song.
Back.
I hope I have the file still.
So just do like a big throat clear and then go into it.
Just really set up.
So Evan was in the bathroom at Sesame Place and there was an employee in there from Sesame
Place and he.
And there was something.
Yeah.
And the person was like plush because of.
Okay.
Yeah.
I remembered it exactly.
So does that change your.
I'm still a little queasy about it.
No, it's not a good story.
It's not a fun story.
I don't.
You're getting our live reaction to hearing it again.
And if you the listener want this, I'm just, I think what I'm saying is I think we need
pitches on what else.
Susser, a great guest, a guy we'd love to have around.
I think we need something more on the table for him to do if we are going to bring them
around.
I think he, I think he would not be against telling the full tale, but you know, but then
we don't want that to be a four minute episode.
It's a huge bummer.
And then it's over.
And then we have to wait for the next club three.
It'll be funny if everyone paid the extra tier for a four minute episode.
That would be funny.
Yeah.
I, yes, I agree.
I like that part.
If I wasn't so sure that this would be, yeah, I'm happy after they would turn the thing
off.
So look, it's not out of the running.
I'm just saying, I think we need more information, more pitches.
We're just sending that back to the drawing board, but feel free to come back with any
ideas you have.
Now what is moving on to the next round, the runner up is the idea that we would watch
the entire Bob Iger masterclass.
Which is a good.
Now that is, is that eight to 12 hours of content?
Or maybe I'm not sure.
I don't know the standard of, of masterclass.
I'm just surprised that's the first masterclass that there anyone's proposing that we do and
not a Mr. Spacey.
Do we have copies of that?
So yeah, yeah, yeah.
Somebody I feel like pirated it at the time.
It needed to make sure this wasn't scrubbed.
So Iger, that sounds like a black.
I, I, I, that sounds like funny to me.
I don't want to overly endorse it, but I just, I want to say I like the idea.
However, it may have to wait.
I haven't talked to you guys about this, but remember next month is October.
It is when we transform from podcast, the ride into haunt cast the fright.
And I thought maybe we should try to take this into club three, do the first themed
club three, uh, and just say that if you have suggestions for spooky stuff and maybe we
don't get enough of those and we do, uh, we do throw Iger masterclass in there or it's
a mix, but I feel like we could harvest enough, uh, scary ideas between, uh, weird, scary
rides or kind of like haunted house stuff that we might not know about or obscure haunted
haunts or even like, you know, a lot about our fears at this point.
If there's something we've discussed being afraid of that you want us to, uh, you know,
go to the brink about, uh, that seems like something fun, potentially, uh, many other
suggestions from you guys.
Oh, what, what might, uh, what, what haunt cast the fright on club three might end up
being, I know there's been, uh, some whimsical, is there a Paul Lind Halloween special?
Michael, I'm looking at you.
That's smart.
Of course.
What do you mean?
No, you know, you know,
I'm pretty sure.
I think.
Yeah.
We watched some of it.
But in terms of like Halloween being a time for whimsy and costumes, there's also, is
it Paul Lind at, uh, the spring walk, uh, walk away cheese spring?
I never got Paul Lind.
That's not not that's done.
Not okay.
Paul is not done.
Not so Lind is not done.
Not so I could not remember which actor of that time period.
It was furious right now.
This is like, look, I'm bugging my love.
I'm upset.
So those are more whimsical options.
Paul Lind also has, there's a track called like Paul in castle Dracula.
And he does like a narration of like the Dracula story.
Like our Renfield Renfield.
We might, let me say this.
Maybe I'm wrong, but, and maybe with our, with the club three audience, we might not
have to do this, but just in terms of the year that it is on this earth, what can brief
context for Paul Lind, please?
Yeah, sure.
Well, he, he was an actor.
He's in bye bye birdie.
He was uncle Arthur on bewitched.
He was on Hollywood squares.
He was off in the center square, I believe.
And he's just one of those very specific character actors that I'm obsessed with.
Like an Al Lewis or anyone.
Yeah.
Oddball personality, almost as known for just being himself as being on shows.
This will help kind of a male Joanne Worley.
Yeah.
You really clarified it for a lot of folks.
Great.
So yeah.
So he has a Halloween special and kiss is on it.
Betty white is on it.
The woman, I can't think of her name who plays the wicked witch of the West in.
Oh yeah.
Margaret O'Brien.
Yeah.
And there's a long eight minute sketch that the thing starts with that is just Paul
and not knowing what holiday it is.
So he's like, dresses the Easter bunny.
That's a hipity hop Margaret.
Eight minutes.
So long.
And I bruised, Philanche, I think worked on that.
I think that was in his first gigs.
Oh boy.
I believe.
Of course.
Makes sense to me.
Yeah.
So anyway, Paul.
Well, that's a strong idea.
Somebody throw it in there.
You got to say it for us to put it in.
But anything in the Halloween realm and maybe we'll put, so just put a pin in
Eiger masterclass, which I do like and I want to do.
Sure.
So that business out of the way.
Now we move on to today's business.
What a business.
That literal business.
For the umpteenth time, let me read the full description from Shane Cannon, who suggested
it.
Please discuss the failed Canadian Garfield restaurant, Garfield eats the failed Canadian
Scooby Doo frozen food brand Scooby Doo eats and the founder of both of them archetypal
guy and noted hyper narcissist, Nathan Masri.
And that's what we're prepared to do.
This thing in general, I didn't know any of these words.
I somehow missed it, Jason.
It seems like you sort of knew the vague shape of this from the internet world of the
last few years.
I knew it a little because, um, you know, Garfield, we all grew up with Garfield, I'm
assuming comic strip collections, like the cartoon and we all grew up tolerating
Garfield.
Yeah, we all grew up knowing that Garfield existed and that we were supposed to like
it because we were children.
Did you not like Garfield though?
Because I loved Garfield.
Yes, I liked Garfield.
I just want to make that clear about my stance on Garfield anyway.
Um, yeah.
And I, I Garfield kind of has taken on another life on the internet, been memeified.
There's the, that Garfield with our without Garfield strip.
There's that lasagna cat web series.
The greatest, really great.
And, um, yeah, so I had heard about this a few years ago.
I didn't realize it was as complicated as it was.
I think I heard some Canadian comedians talking about it and I saw either a vice article
or, uh, uh, the, the journalist, Sarah, uh, I think it's Hagee or Hagee.
Um, I, she had covered it in a, in a, I think food and wine.
I just reread that and then the eater talked to her and like, there's a lot of after
action reports out there on the internet where you can kind of get some angles on this.
Yeah.
People covered the spread.
People definitely, this was like documented from all angles for sure.
Um, while it was open and we are not the first, uh, entity to cover this.
As you said, many, uh, many blogs and articles, even other podcast.
I believe my brother, my brother and me did it.
Ben and I haven't listened to any of these.
So I don't, we, if we're repeating material, uh, apologies, but I think we all tried to
find some new things about this, try to shine some light under the rock and find some new
odd bugs crawling around in this absolutely insane story and world.
Yes.
Yeah.
And we, uh, maybe the first time we were given a dossier.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Yes.
This is, I, I, I just generally want to say the like campaign that Shane Cannon mounted,
I was so impressed by that he like kept at it and I saw numbers tick up real time in the polling,
from him endorsing it.
Uh, and then yeah, that's not the first iteration of this, but like audience research,
voluntary audience research.
We got a spreadsheet from Jeff Cole.
Thank you, Jeff, who seemed to completely have new things to bring to the table and
donated them graciously to us, which we will get to throughout the episode.
Yeah.
And to everyone politicking and like, you know, getting, really thinking a lot about club
feet, please do not stress your out on, stress yourselves out on these selections.
Do not beat yourself up for voting for one or the other.
We're all just having a nice time.
I don't know.
I might go the other way.
I think let's put some work into it.
Oh, you want some suffering?
Yeah.
Yes.
Okay.
Let's make the people we're paying us the most.
Greater suffering, greater the peace, you know, it was a takeaway from Mission Possible
Fallout.
I think that was what you're supposed to take away.
Consider club three your buy in to a, to work that you're doing for free.
Scott is the lane of a club or of podcasts.
The ride lane being the bad guy from Mission Impossible.
Fallout.
Of course.
Yes.
Lane lane.
We know lane.
He'll be back.
So, uh, all right here.
I recently, I forget where, but I saw the storytelling advice to maybe that sometimes
it's good to start in the middle and work your way both ways.
And that's my idea of how to, to corral this.
So what I would, I'd like to do here is to, uh, before we get into the character, the guy,
maybe set the scene of what, uh, you might've encountered if you were one of the great people
of Toronto, Canada in 2019.
Um, so in 2019, uh, a restaurant pops up, uh, out of nowhere and it is a restaurant themed
after famous comic cat Garfield.
This is out of the gate unusual because this sort of thing does not happen.
A freestanding, we, you know, we know these pop-up kinds of things that say by the bell
place or the, the star Wars bar or whatever, but often there's a shelf life on that.
But this is an official Garfield restaurant, seemingly unless they just stole it all.
But then you look into it and they did not steal it.
This was, this is related to pause ink.
The company that regulates all of the Garfield licensing.
And I want to point out, I think, cause like Nick, what is Nickelodeon owns Garfield now?
Viacom.
Yeah.
Yeah. Right. Right.
So, but Jim Davis historically will let Garfield be, do anything like license Garfield for almost
anything like Garfield without Garfield, which was a strip that took John out of the Garfield,
like which Photoshop him out or no, excuse me.
The rock field.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It's like John, baby, losing his mind.
Yeah. It just, it's a sad man losing his mind and Jim Davis was like, sure, print it, make
whatever. I don't care. Like he doesn't, he doesn't seem like he's that precious about
Garfield and pausing is what I'm saying.
I think if he can figure out a way for money to go back to him, I read that with Garfield
minus Garfield that he, he allowed it to exist, but then also started making his own versions
of that to co-opt their Garfield deconstructionist idea. So that was his way of getting money to
come back. But yeah, we all know the, you know, the phones and I feel like he, he's almost
Garfield almost more famous from shirts and stuff.
Yeah. I just bought a shirt for $5 from Coles at his Garfield. It's a tie dye Garfield shirt.
You bought a tie dye Garfield shirt.
I went to go get my bivalent booster and I went, Coles was next door and I had an Amazon return.
I returned, I got a $5 off coupon for something in Coles and I go, well, let me take a look around
clearance. And I found a tie dye Garfield shirt.
Did you have to leave the county? Where is the closest Coles?
The closest Coles is on Laurel Canyon and it's like 20 minutes away. It's not too far.
Yeah, they're around. I know. And like what, you know, not too far from LA because every
whole world is just cold. This country is cold.
This country is cold. There's like 2000 locations.
But I had only seen it in the town past Pasadena where the Sonic is.
Oh, right. Right.
It's a Coles.
Monorovia maybe?
I think, yeah, somewhere around there.
That's Coles country out there.
It's Coles country. All right.
You don't have to drive. We have got a little bubble around us where there are no, less Coles
and less chilis, but then it's only a 15 minute drive.
I was at Coles once a week as a child.
Wow.
Yeah, we had a Coles right down, right, like three minutes from the house.
Ours was Mervyn's. Mervyn's got sort of subsumed.
Yeah.
Anyway, so this is, it's a weird thing because when does a restaurant just open about a character
and in 2019, why exactly, why Garfield, why now? What does a Garfield restaurant mean?
And I assume if you have not, like, oh, maybe we should go check it out. What
sorts of things do they have? Well, they have lasagna naturally. Now, this part of it makes
sense. This might be, this might be where the sense stops in this tale, but a Garfield
restaurant that serves lasagna. Sure. Got it. Can't only be lasagna though. What else? Well,
pizza goes with lasagna. Great. How does the pizza stand out? Well, the pizza
is in the shape of Garfield's head.
Kind of.
In theory. That's what they're depending on. The skill of the person rolling the dough or
what the oven does to it. Yeah. So, hey, that's interesting. Garfield, the iconic shape of
Garfield, I guess. Look, it's no Mickey Mouse. There's no features as prominent. And if anything,
it's probably like a circle and then you kind of cut into it and you get less pizza, probably.
Yeah. It's less of an oval.
Yeah.
It's an altered oval. You might be losing pizza, all told. There also seems to be,
Garfield's Orange, we know this. So we're just going to do regular old red pizza sauce.
I don't think so. We're going orange. Now there's sauces that are orange out there. That's not so
crazy, but this place pioneered their own orange sauce that reviewers seem not particularly fond of.
Yeah. I mean, if I was going to try and make that myself, I think I know the basics of cooking.
I would get a bunch of orange heirloom tomatoes. Sure. You know? Okay. I don't know.
I don't know how sustainable that is for like a restaurant to do. Nothing. But well,
what it probably does is drive up the cost because they, and they also made all these
decisions, which are good about GMOs and farm fresh and all that. But then also they claim all
this, but then everybody hates the way the food tastes. And it ends up extremely expensive is what
I'm getting at. The prices seem outrageous at this place. Yeah. That food and wine article,
it's like, oh, and don't forget to use your 50% off coupon. And the 50% off coupon brought it down
from $50 to $25. And it's like this barely fed three people and none of us really enjoyed it.
For cardboardy pizza, for pizza that was not enjoyed. And by the way, not coupon,
goopon. But we'll get to that. Oh, all right.
Okay. So lasagna pizza with an orange, it makes sense. And then, you know,
Garficchino's, whoa, whoa, whoa. Stop the car. Garficchino's. I like the word. I approve of word.
But why are the, why are the primaries of this place Italian food, hot Italian food
and, and then coffee on these things don't particularly go together. No. Especially what
they portray as a Garficchino is like massive. That's a venti drink of pure hot. And that has,
I think a strong dark chocolate component. So you're sucking down dark chocolate coffee
and a lot of it. And then switching over to lasagna. But you can get it orange flavored.
Oh, is that right? The coffee. Yes. Orange? Like the fruit? The orange? Yeah. I know for like
really nice coffee. If you like do a twist of lemon or orange, there's something where like the
acid, you can do this. I'm talking about a cup of espresso that someone is expertly prepared
with a fresh brine and stuff. I ain't talking about whatever pump they're pumping into just this coffee.
Yeah. Yeah. I think, I think subtlety is probably at the window. The beverages go further though.
Oh, well you do tell. Cause your options are Garficchino, smoothies, orange juice.
That is it. No, no, no, no. Oh, carrot juice. Oh really? Yeah. Yeah. Everything orange. Cause
stroke. Cause I, there was a YouTuber, a strange Aeon. They have a lot of videos and they tried the
carrot juice and they said there's a lot of like texture to it. It's not completely liquid. Oh no.
But a thing that's missing that I associate with like eating pizza, no soda. They do not sell soda
pump. Yeah, that's right. There's no soda. They, they similarly with sort of why not this and why
that they do have fries, but no ketchup. And the answer is just well, because chemicals. Right.
And then I saw a discussion of like, well, you, there are ketchups that exist that are lacking in
chemicals. And the guy doesn't want to hear it. We'll get to the guy. So, you know, yeah, no sodas
to wash down your pizza. You're grabbing go pizza with no ketchup for your fries, but it's keeping
you safe and it's pushing you towards healthier items. Like the smoothies, the aforementioned
smoothies, Jeff Cole listener. He, when he went, while this was open, he ordered a mango smoothie,
texted his friends. The best way I could describe this is like banana water.
Yeah. He was not having a good time. Is this smoothie experience?
So all strange what's going on. You, you maybe hear about this place word of mouth. There's this
weird Garfield restaurant in 2019. Why here's the food that they serve. I would like more
information. Maybe at that point you go to the website for Garfield eats and you are hit with a
barrage of jargon. Here is some of the jargon. I don't, I mean, again, take your pay because
there's mountains of jargon that were, I think they made more jargon than food, but here's one.
Here's a stretch that I found Garfield's dreams come true. Garfield eats is the world's first quick
enter gauging restaurant app, both engaging and entertaining. Let's break down enter gauging
for a second. Um, I mean, imagine something being both entertaining and engaging. Never been done.
Never. Yeah. Never. These do not go in the original. It's technically the same spirit as
imagineering, putting the words together. Sure. But those are kind of different worlds that they're
pulling from, not essentially overlapping ideas. I think when I crossed enter gauging, when I crossed
that Rubicon, I was like, I'm starting to get annoyed. I was like this, I discovered something
later on. I discovered a line of thinking about this guy that I hadn't considered and I was like,
okay, it makes sense again. Cause before that I was saying, I was thinking about all the people
making videos, writing articles covering this and I was like, is this bait? Is this bait? Does he know
what he's doing? And then I, I, people pointed out like, consider these people that do not have
self awareness. And I was like, okay, now I understand it again. Yeah. Now I understand.
This is very like the cult movie. There, there's some overlap with Tommy Wiseau in the room.
And that helps thinking along those lines. Because you had to ask that question about
there. You have to like, wait a minute, this is so like perfectly hilarious to a sitcom degree,
so consistently funny. Maybe we're all being played here and he does seem a little self-aware
now and playing up the character of himself. Nathan, I don't know. You have to poke around
a little bit and discover like, you have to be so calculated and smart to be that off of humanity
at every turn. Yeah. There's another, I was watching a couple of YouTube videos and they
were asking that question. I think the one I was watching was like, is Izzy? Yeah. They had a
pretty good. Yeah. She was asking the question too. And I think she spoke with somebody who knows
he's spoken with this man and was like, is this a bit? And they're like, I don't think so. I'm
not sure. I don't think so though. It's at least the smell test you got to do. And I, and I don't
think so. Let me, before we give him the hero's welcome, just a couple more things. App users can
play, watch and order at the same time and collect pause a loyalty coin system to unlock
coupon offers, game levels, episodes, and more. So hang on, wait a bit. We have one thing also,
we've breezed past is the app nature of this. So it's the first, it's an app. It's not a restaurant.
No, no, it's a restaurant, but you need the app to do the restaurant. And the app is like a full
experience. You have to get immersed in and you want it. You're going to want to get on the app
and watch the videos, the video content. What's that? It's old Garfield and friends episodes,
cartoon from the late eighties, the kind of old cartoon. Right. That we w we all watched this,
I assume. Yeah. I kind of liked the friends. In fact, we've talked, we've talked about this
before. I didn't like the friends. I didn't like the barnyard section. You didn't like the egg with
legs. I like the egg with like now there's one episode where the egg is going to hatch and it
hatches and it's just another egg. I mean, that's good. I understand as a kid, I didn't like the
barnyard friends and I liked Garfield and I've said the reverse. I liked, didn't like the Heathcliff
parts as much as I like the Cadillac cats. Okay. Cause they both had like two different sets of
characters that you would get with orange cats did another, they were like, there's not enough
here. Yeah. You've got to flush this out with something else. Right. I've talked about how
Hector was one of my idols as a kid from the Cadillac cats. That's one of my, the coolest guy
I'd ever seen was Hector up until I was like 11. Not your hero past. Steven Tyler took over. Yeah.
After 11 it was Steven Tyler, but up until then it was Hector from the Cadillac cats. Steven Tyler
and Billy Joe Armstrong came into the picture. No, that was years later. Okay. That was like
three years ago. Three years ago. So goop bonds. And if you haven't figured out goop bonds, that's
Garfield coupons, I guess. Yeah. There's no, what is the a good? Yeah. Garpons, Garpons, Garpons is
better. Goopons is much better. Goop coupons. Yeah. Like coupons covered in, covered in goo or that you
get this does goop. Does Gwyneth Peltrow's goop have coupons? Cause that would be, is that too,
that seems like too fun for them. It's like, cause it's kind of a serious, but she's got the vagina
candle. It's not completely serious, but isn't, doesn't, I feel like the vagina candle takes
itself a little seriously. Really? I don't know. I feel like she's a bit self, not completely. She's
not aware of that much, but a little bit. Maybe I'm wrong. What is the, what are the club three
listeners think? Is the vagina candle serious or maybe they began, like some of these things that
became self aware. Now they have a little fun with sure. They should have goop bonds. I like the word.
I like the spirit of this. Um, anyway, so okay. An app is essential, bizarre. Then you, you get to the
restaurant and okay, here we are Garfield eats. Why is the name Garfield eats so much smaller
than the, than the giant phrase in comic font love me, feed me. Don't leave me. Comic sans. Yeah.
Yeah. Let's talk about that phrase because it's from one of the movies. This is the, yeah, it is.
And then it isn't in a way. Cause he changed it. Cause in the movie he says, love me, feed me, never
leave me. And I think he's being cute when he says it, but apparently he says, Jim Davis said,
don't ever use never in marketing because it's a negative, I guess because it's negative. And so
he changed it to love me, feed me, don't leave me, which sounds, I don't know, desperate, sad,
let love me feed me. Don't leave me. Like I don't, it's weird. It's edgier for some reason. Yeah.
It feels more, more vulnerable and more of a more pleading. More goofy, like love me, feed me,
never leave me, you know, like. And also what is this jumble where like anything from the movies
is important? Yeah. I don't think the movies feels like those, those existed to entertain
then three year olds who hopefully immediately abandoned liking this. And they, they aren't
important. You know, like famously Bill Murray just like shat his way through it. Although like
rewrote it as he went, I think he's, yeah, he had to save it just cause he's a human with feelings
and opinions disowned it. But then also like said, he like worked hard improvising stuff. So who knows
what the true truth is without the director around the fake story. Also he tells too about the cone
brothers though that he thought it was one of the filmmakers going cone brothers, but then, yeah,
which I think is fake story. Yeah, it could be. Yeah. Although he knows he might be ease out of
it in a way. I guess, but like you can't even get to him and then they got to him, but he didn't,
like no one told him. I don't know. Wasn't that thing about how you could, you, it was so hard
to get a hold of him. Wasn't that cooler when he made better movies? It was like, wow, what a
Desperado out there on there. Yeah. I'll call back if it's the greatest movie ever made cut to
bunch of shit. It's also like he has a, he has a lawyer, you know, like Leno has a lawyer too. All
these guys who like are big, like, oh, you know, I don't have an agent manager or whatever. It's
like, they got a lawyer. Like you have a most savvy thing. Yeah. Like what, what you still have a
representative. You just made it hard for people to get in touch with you, which fine, but like,
it's not as cool. I don't know. It's not as cool as I may have thought it was 10 years ago. Yeah.
I bought into the mythology a little more. Um, so anyway, uh, bizarre sign, like, so was the name
of the restaurant, love me, feed me debt. Why is this phrase so prominent? It's just something
from the movie, but then that it like viewed as the gospel is like John three 16, but then
changed what's happening. And this is where you start to wonder, like, this is a little rinky.
This is not some, like, this isn't like if some traveling Hello Kitty thing opens up and it has
the Sanrio veneer, especially when you get into the restaurant, it's weird and cheap and falling
apart. Maybe we can't delay it any longer because something you might encounter when you get into
the restaurant is a man in a perfectly tailored bright orange suit. He himself is orange.
Otherwise, like, like facially, there's a weird tan or cream job going on. He, uh, he has a Garfield
pocket square. He's a fancy Garfield man who seems to be like trying to be a human Garfield.
He's probably in the restaurant, uh, talking a lot about himself, getting very defensive about the
iPads and the app that are undoubtedly not working because also there's no cashiers in this
right. It's cashless, no cashiers, much simpler. You get rid of cashiers and all you have is the
owner himself, uh, telling you there isn't a problem with the apps. Yeah. Yeah. Much easier
than handing cash over to a human being. And this kind of predates the rise of ghost kitchens.
Yeah. Someone calls it a ghost. One article called it a ghost restaurant, which I had not heard
before, but does kind of accurately describe it because it's like not, it isn't one of these
where there then there isn't, there's at least a lobby. Right. Kind of like most dominoes or pizza
hut nowadays where there's just a counter. And then every now and then you find one where there's
like a single table with three chairs and you're like, who the fuck is he? What brought you to this
point? It's probably like the people who work at the pet shop next door want to get out for their
lunch break. So they eat like a sloppy pasta bowl at the dominoes table. The only excuse, yes, if
you, if you've walked more than a block to sit at the in restaurant pizza under dominoes table,
we're going to get into the guy. I think here we got to get into the guy. Yep. And this is,
I think a good way to get into the guy. I found out that he is on the app slash website blister.
Oh yeah. You toss this phrase out before we started recording new jargon to me. What's blister
is just cameo. It's a cameo for like LinkedIn people or like motivational barely even explains
what it is. It just got it. It basically just says like, uh, uh, learn from the best in business.
And then Nathan is under there. Oh yeah. The best and like Tory spellings on here and Chuck Liddell
from M from MMA world. Uh, so yeah, to learn from the best in the world. And Nathan is the first one
that they're talking about. Yeah. It's a photo of him and Garfield. Um, and my first time hearing
him was his video where he's pitching himself for why you should listen to him. So I'm going to play
that. I'm Nathan Masri and I'm an inter-gaging motivational speaker and it's time to blow your
brains and wake the F up because my talent is to elevate human consciousness.
Life is a self discovery. Also, he's doing this in front of a thing of a poster of Garfield playing
poker with dogs. That's come up. That's come. A lot of this stuff keeps coming back up.
And this is, this is the video is where you might go, Oh, is he goofing around? I can't tell. Cause
he's kind of putting it on. He's got a little bit of a smile and there's something contrived
about the suit and that he's in a, he's in a Garfield orange. So well, this one, he's wearing
a blue shirt with an A like a, some sort of a ribbon, but it might be a Garfield ribbon. I'm
not sure. Okay. Okay. Uh, is a self suppression
boom.
Adapting to something or someone for too long results in a magnetic attachment yielding to a
sense of loss. If we lose it, we must learn. Also in the back, there is some sort of like fake lion
king music track playing. It's like circle of life, but like it's a royalty free
power of detachment instead. So you don't, I take that back. It's can you feel a love?
It just is. Yeah. That's it. Sorry, sorry. Yeah.
Because we are born alone. So what's the answer? What's the answer? So what's the answer attached
with a lot of question to his face care and he's swinging around a gummy worm. Now I just want to
let you know about that. Okay. Or this worm, but don't create a habit of closeness suffocating me.
You will realize some of your toxic emotions were a result of some bad habit. Take it from me,
break it before it breaks you. Then he takes a big bite of the gummy worm in a comedic way.
And that's the end of the video. It's real like Kendall Roy from succession energy,
overly confident, but also kind of sad and very confusing and a really shitty beard.
Yeah. It's an odd to look at. It's odd to look at. He's really, I know he's a living wax figure.
He's really the way he is chosen to style himself. I think there's a way for him to have a beard.
And to have a little bit extra tan or pigmentation that doesn't have to look like this. I kind of,
I don't love when things kind of lazily say, Oh, this is like Tim and Eric, this is straight out
of Tim and Eric, but I swear I've seen stuff where Tim especially has a, like a beard that feels
painted on and he's on naturally orange. I mean, like it is extremely Tim for sure. It is aging
rockstar. It's an aging rockstar look. Even though he's not that old. Oh, this is a question.
Probably younger than us. Could be. I don't, well, you know what he is. The timeline,
the age timeline gets confusing too. Jeff Cole alerted us to this. There's some sloppiness with
the age. What we do know about him is that he is the world's youngest Garfield licensee. Yes. And
what we know about that phrase is that it is important. We grasp it. We have full context
to know why that is a big deal to be. Well, Garfield licensees famously, very old presidents.
It's only, you gotta be north of 70, but he got to it. He went straight for it. And at age, uh,
28 or 36 or 43, I don't know who knows, but he is, he is that. And he reminds you of that in any time
there is someone in front of him or a camera or anything. Uh, I, so here's our guy and this is a
guy, this is a guy Supreme. This is the definition of a guy. Oh yeah. Um, he is, he's so strange and
that, I mean, where do you even begin? Love me, feed me, don't leave me. Jason, when you said that
that phrase has like a sadness to it and a desperation to it, I think that the phrase
defines him so much and he seems to like find all this meaning in it and in Garfield
in general that I don't quite understand. Yeah, I don't, I don't either. Um, because it seemed like
he had a nice home, like it seemed like he had a supportive family life growing up, which I know
about from, uh, seeing some excerpts from his book and just just telling it, it seems like they
moved countries a lot and there might've been some culture shock or whatever. I'm just saying,
I don't know what's behind it. I know that that, the way he was speaking in that blizzard video
or whatever, um, is kind of a go to business motivation and self-help motivation. I don't
know why, I don't know how that caught on of like, you have to have this philosophy and business
and, uh, when the, the most practical advice could be like, I don't know, just start doing
some things, just do practical things and something will stick eventually. Isn't that what it all adds?
All these books essentially add up to what you just said, but no, you have to be like,
you have to find 700 ways to reframe that. Yeah, it's like, it's like when I was, you know,
for starting comedy classes and all's we ever do with sit at the bar and talk about comedy and
stuff, it's like, no, just go home, just start crapping stuff out and eventually it'll hopefully
smooth out and something good will appear. You know, I liked that all's we ever did.
That was a good look. See, I just like spend so much time like pulling my hair out, waiting for
realizations when I was young. And then as I got older, I was like, oh yeah, you just got to do a
bunch. You just need to clock a bunch of hours and like sand off the rough edges, you know,
you needed somebody who would teach you self-actualization, which is what he's
advertising here. And that's why, why it, you know, people, people gravitate towards that stuff
because they think it's the answer, you know, there is no, there is no answer. There's no magic.
There's no magic sentence. You know, I don't know. I think this guy's going to hit on one.
He keeps talking and talking and talking, which is what he does. What made him this way? What
turns somebody into that? What is this bizarre combination of all the jargon that you just played
him saying, but then also Garfield is a huge part of it. It's a little tough to figure out,
if we parse, if we start getting into where, where did he come from? So he, it does seem like around
1718, the motivational world kind of starts hitting him. Why at age 17, he read, not like
most 17 year olds, he, he, he says himself, I was not off watching the Jersey shores of the time,
the time wasting mindless fluff. I watched a TV show. You can actually learn or to learn a thing
or two from the apprentice. I had all of Donald Trump's books at 17 years old and I was mesmerized
by his branding techniques. Mostly that's because that's mostly what he is. I have Trump, I had
wrote Trump down in my notes because it's like, I don't think we give enough credit that Trump
energized guys like this, like, like energized that kind of bullshitting the way it's guys like
this started to sound more and more like Trump and just talking and talking until stuff just
starts happening around you. But then if you actually look at all of them, none of them work.
He was also inspired and this is from Jeff. He sent us stills from the, from his book.
This gives you a window into his world. The book is called era. We might be, here's how I read it
is Arab biologist. There's a weird, Oh, like I want to say Arab biologist, but I'm seeing a weird,
Oh, it's supposed to be a combination of Arab and scoliosis. I think, Oh, because he had scoliosis
and he spent a number of months in a, in a cast bedridden. Yes. This is crucial to his story.
You said happy upbringing, but there was this rough run around 18 seemingly were six months where he
was pretty immobile and it seemed like what carried him through was the writing of Donald Trump.
And then also who, who is, who among us has not been inspired by Oprah. Oprah really had
a grip on his mind. And here's a section from the book. Oh, do I have it or not?
He just, he, he wrote her a letter at age 18 and like, Oh, that sounds nice about how he was inspired.
Well, kind of, but also the letter is a creepy as hell. Let me find it. Sorry. Oh, here we go.
Okay. Dear Oprah, my name is Nathan and I am an 18 year old who loves hot Oprah.
All right. So far the book has been all about like, and I had scoliosis and I could not,
and I thought all was lost for me until I wrote this letter. I am, I love hot Oprah.
I know it's funny and weird for a teenage guy to be such a big fan of Oprah instead of Snoop Dogg,
but life has compelled me to turn toward you. And thank God it did because it would be a loss to
miss a person so full of wisdom. He doesn't like Jersey Shore. He likes Trump. He doesn't like
Snoopy. He likes a hot Oprah. Yeah. Very straight, which this, you know, if you don't look at how
he's actually behaving, you could maybe think something's okay or like this guy's got gumption,
but then that those cracks hot Oprah, weird, weird. Yeah, we are for sure. And look,
when you really analyze it, who is smarter, the situation or Trump, you know, like really one just
is like a suit on and he fooled more people that way. Well, and that's, that I think is what he,
what Nathan Mesry got from Trump and he is just like put on a suit and have like a color associated
with you. Put on a suit, never stop talking. Doesn't matter if you're saying much, just never stop
talking. That's how they get the jump on you. If you ever give anyone else a window to talk. Orange
man, never stop talking. He really is the new Trump in a way. Well, there's another way that he's a
lot like Trump because, uh, you know, he, this guy, a business dynamo, he got his, he got a running
start. Oh, hot Oprah helped him overcome his scoliosis. And before you know it, he, uh, had sold
his ad agency at age 24. Wow. Then he was, he joined as VP of marketing for Mr. Sub Jugo juice
and Van Hout Cafe, all Canadian brands at this point living in Toronto. Uh, those all are from
MTY group and they all together have $2 billion in sales. That's pretty crazy. I mean, how do you,
that young randomly somehow end up as the VP of marketing for MTY group? One of the biggest,
oh, it's his dad. It was his dad, dad, dad, dad. It was his dad. Uh, this is a, this may be a fail
son situation. If you can believe it, uh, dad is like major, major, uh, UAE money, real estate,
like the, the owning all of the owning TCB Y in Canada is but a drop in the bucket of what
Mr. Masri is up to. Um, can I ask, sorry to interrupt you TCB Y any thoughts? Um, I,
I remember them around in the mall. Yeah. Ocean city. Yeah. I mean, I like, I liked it. Okay. I
don't think we're a big TCB Y family. All right. Nevermind. I prefer the brand, uh, penguin,
which is like sparingly around. There was this, this, I don't know if that's California. There's
a very, I really like this penguin brand frozen yogurt. I think there's one or two straight.
Interesting. I think TCB Y probably the fastest to end up, uh, at I-95 corridor, like rest stops.
Like you were going to find a Roy Rogers and you were going to find a TCB Y. That's the last one
I saw on this. Yeah. I think it was on the way to Disney world or something was the rest of TCB Y
we were both there at the same time. Wow. 15 and didn't know it. Um, so, all right. So it's a fail
son situation. He has enough money, he has enough startup and like a job from daddy, but, uh, what
do I do from here? Maybe it's not satisfying him. He has other ideas, crazier ideas. Uh, I think I
also, you can't find much about, about the family, but I think there's a brother who's a much more
traditional, just like, uh, you know, not making web videos and wearing strange costume. So I have
a whole theory about what's going on here family wise, but, uh, he's not satisfied being a Canadian
businessman. So he takes a turn and goes, uh, to the land of dreams, Hollywood slash Burbank,
where he starts pursuing acting and writing. And this is around 2014, 2015. So I'm like, uh,
Oh, I'm getting scared. When are we going to run into somebody I've met or something with him?
Oh God, possibly. Yes. So whatever I was most checked out at it, funny or die. Um, no, he,
look, he was very productive. He studied under a teacher who taught Ryan Gosling. So he got some
of the knowledge that was, that went into Mr. Gosling later or no earlier, much earlier.
Earlier. Um, then he started, uh, what you were saying, Jason, he started making his own stuff.
He didn't wait around for his own opportunity. He acted in stuff that he wrote. He started Masri
pictures and there is a trail of Masri pictures content that you can still watch on YouTube
to this day. Uh, he produced a short film. This is in 2015 called Ahmed and Howard. Um, this is,
here's the description from them. An Arab and a Jew torn apart by history and brought together as,
as a grocery store, probably at to solve the Middle East crisis with one hummus at a time.
He, uh, later on comes back around to that idea of the conflicts between the Arabs and the Jews,
in a less creative way. Scared, scared. Um, at the time it's just high jinks of like opposing
cultures. It's like a, it's a two-hander and these guys think they don't like each other,
but after a crazy night of mischief in the, in this one odd, not friendly to cameras store that
they were able to film at, uh, they ended up getting along. Uh, it's a two-hander. It's Nathan,
it's the great Nathan Masri, the great actor, Nathan Masri, who's strong enough to go up against
him in 2015. Uh, do you guys, I don't know, is it, uh, does the name Jake Novak mean anything to you
recent past? Have you ever heard the name Jake Novak? I feel like I have heard it, but maybe I'm,
maybe it's just this, uh, did you around June of this year, did anyone pass along? Did I perhaps
pass along to you a video from Tik Tok? Yes. A wrap. Yes, I know it. I know. I know. I know.
I know. Who wants to be the new SNL cast member. No, I know. No, I think, I think this is, this is
a new thing I think I'm bringing to the Nathan Masri story, uh, due to some tweets that he himself
posted a couple months ago when it was Jake Novak made it out there. I could not believe this.
Not some random guy that he made a movie with. It's this guy who got notorious this year and
listener, if you don't know what we're talking about, there was this Tik Tok because SNL is
losing a ton of cast members over the summer. Um, and this guy who had made up a lot of comedy
raps on Tik Tok was throwing his hat into the ring with a rap that is addressed to Lauren Michaels
personally. Smart. I think you got a good read on the guy. Uh, and the, the tone of this is like,
I want to be the next SNL cast member. It's this like very cloying sub Lin-Manuel. Oh my God. I
mean, like you guys saw it, right? I mean, it's the craziest thing ever. But did you,
did you know the theme park connection? I know that he was outed as a member of the dapper.
This is his day job. Uh, so you might see him at Disneyland as a dapper Dan. This thing is so
crazy, especially that he start when he frames himself, like what he could be on the show. He
like thinks he could be the next lonely Island. So he says like, uh, because when it comes to the
county ramps, I've kind of been killing it. And then this, and then like, oh, I'm kind of a, uh,
Lin-Manuel, uh, Lin-Manuel Miranda mixed with Sammy Berg, meaning he, he calls an Andy Samberg,
Sammy Berg, which might be the most annoying thing I've ever heard. And this is an episode all about
annoying stuff. So these guys somehow found each other, cannot believe it. And I just, I want to
say people I think have been bordering on harassing of, uh, of Jake Novak, even outing his work as,
as that Disneyland. And I don't approve of any of that. Nobody should be mean to that. Yeah.
Just do what we all did, which is all quietly pass the link to everyone we've ever met in comedy.
I don't go out of your way to be mean to the guy. They, they announced four new cast members and
they all seemed like, you know, people who had been working for a while, but I, someone did have
a big tick tock file account and I was like, Oh no, is it, is it, it can't be. And it wasn't,
it was, I think they were all mostly standups and someone who was on the league of their own show.
Someone else who was a writer on big mouth, you know. Well, they've missed their shot to have the
sketch, uh, two guys trying to get their jackets, uh, look up this video if you haven't seen it.
Anyway, blew my mind that Maz, Mazari and Novak, which, and which he, he recently was like,
congratulations to my old partner, Jake Novak, you're on CNN, you're killing it. And then you
click on the link and the link is him talking about how sad he is that his life has become,
that people are coming after him for this video, which is, which plays into the Mazari
lack of awareness because he would constantly retweet and post articles that he, that are mean
to the restaurant. But he doesn't, he has no meter for that. It's if I'm being talked about,
it's good. And I get that, but also when it's 95% bad press, I think that no president, no president,
bad president thing doesn't apply. Well, that's a Trump's, I mean, Trump would attack, but Trump
also likes that too. That's another Trumpy thing where it's like, he just wants people talking
about him. He was on all the talk shows and his role was buffoon. Everybody thought that Conan
and Letterman were like, look at this idiot, mock him. But he was getting out there and that's,
that's the move you have, I guess, if you're not naturally, yeah, I know he was in the comments a
lot when people would write one star reviews and either be going to like, these are fake, these are
bots. They're people who don't want us to succeed. And you know, when it's a small family owned
restaurant and you see the owners responding, like, I'm very sorry you didn't enjoy your meal,
please contact us. That I understand. But like owners of like a licensed restaurant getting into
fights online with like, this is absolutely not true. You are a liar. Like that is no,
that's a Trump thing. Well, yeah. And well, and when the restaurant is due, it is to give him
credit doing things that no restaurant has ever done, perhaps for good reason. And people to say,
hey, I have some notes about the new things that no restaurant has ever done. He's like, no, wrong.
There's no possible way any of this could have any errors. Yeah. Really strange. One more just bit of
like, because I think being a guy, you have to be surrounded by sub guys. And like your and your
reputation has to be built off of other guys. And that's what that's what Nathan has done.
Um, including in June, 2015, despite just being a back, a working actor in Los Angeles, it's kind of
strange that he was invited to be knighted by the Prince of Montenegro, Prince Stefan,
chernetic. And that is a younger, that's an honor to be the youngest knighted man in the world.
So he's the, in addition, before he's the world's youngest Garfield licensee, he's the youngest
knighted person. That's wild. Um, and it's only devalued a little bit, I guess, by the fact that
two years later, the Prince of Montenegro was arrested for not being the Prince of Montenegro.
He was an Italian fraudster who this is from Reddit user soggy sauce, an Italian fraudster
who had been masquerading as the Crown Prince of Montenegro and Macedonia, despite the fact that
those countries don't have anything to do with each other. Soggy sauce. Thank you. Thank you.
Soggy sauce. Italian fraudster was the phrase that I like. Yeah, that's most likely have encountered
at least one Italian fraudster and oh my gosh, Tomasso booty, the fashion cafe guy, both a guy
and an Italian fraudster, another Italian fraudster. Yeah. He was knighted by the Crown Prince of
fake country from Princess Princess Diaries, Genovia, Genovia. Wow. The Crown Prince of
Genovia. What this guy would do is just like hand out. Anybody he wanted to meet, he just like
convince people it was a castle, put a bunch of like nice flags all over his car and then like,
please come out. I'll give you a title, including Pamela Anderson. Pamela Anderson came out to
Montenegro and he like put a sword on her head and said, you are now Countess de Gilly. Whoa.
This is what I want to do with the PTR legends. This is exactly the scheme. Yeah. I mean, legitimate
idea. Yeah. Well, okay. We'll take some cause this guy didn't get arrested for a little while
as well. We won't. So if we just get some like nice pins made up, put them all over our car.
Mm hmm. That's the move. Just get 300 pins glued to all of our cars. And they'll think
of somebody who think it's good. That's a big honor. And just rent a house like in somewhere fancy.
That's what'll get Eisner father and son to come visit us and get their award. Now you might be
asking how are we going to pay for this nice house? And the answer is you don't. The Prince of Prince
Stefan Trenetic just like by being a prince. This is another thing. How do they do it? Trump just
gets stuff handed to him by pretending this guy's like, I'm the Prince by, oh, okay. Well,
the bill is substantial. Don't worry about it. He's the Prince. We do not charge the Prince for a
fancy Villa that he stays in for a month and gives out awards to pay all the interest in that.
Oh, and then also then when the daily beast got a hold of this guy to say, Hey, so what do you think
about getting arrested and not being a Prince? He's like, no, no, no, I am a Prince. This is real.
This is all bogus. And also I just want to say on the record how much I love Trump and Putin
of wonderful men. I love the work that they're doing. This is the playbook and it's successful.
Generally, it is always successful. It is not really caught up to Nathan Masri as far as I can
tell. No, he's just, he just keeps dropping names and he got a restaurant open. He found another
sub guy. There's not a lot of information about his other guy, Pascal Heider, who is an Austrian.
And he seemed to finance the whole thing for a while. He, he is, he got rich from ICOs,
which is a form of crypto fake thing. So, you know, he's playing crypto people. He's and then,
but then the key ingredient, you can't just be knighted and toss it around your ICO money.
You got to go to the guy. You got to get a hold of Jim Davis to achieve. Sir, I'm trying to have
forward momentum here, but you keep having, why Garfield? Why? Also along the way, when he's
inspired by hot Oprah, he also like Garfield spoke to him because he talks about how that phrase,
don't leave me. He says like, that's the human condition. Love me, feed me. Don't leave me.
Well, he said that when he would come home from school with a report card, if he had A's,
A minuses or A pluses, his mother would give him a Garfield book, you know? Okay. He's just weirdly
associating success. He's conflating success and Garfield. Yes. Yeah. In a way. And I mean,
I kind of get it. I would get like, you know, $10 if there are comic books, if I got a good report,
you know, I kind of get it. It feels like that could have happened to you,
might like your reward was a Garfield comic book, literally. Well, what I would get is I would get
you go to a book fair once in a while and I would get one of the collected additions.
And there was one specifically that was like silver, like reflective, shiny hologrammy.
And I was obsessed with it. It was like the best day of my life when I would get one of those things.
Initially, they would do the collected editions where Garfield looked weird because it was early
on. The design wasn't perfected. Oh yeah. He was much fatter. Yeah. And he was just odd. Yeah. He
looked odd. And then those books were like thicker oftentimes. And I'm like, yeah, yeah, but I don't
whatever. And then the newer ones, like the cutting edge ones when I was little,
I had like a shiny cover and I was like, yeah, he looks good. Garfield's looking good.
And this cover is awesome. Are you the first person ever to call Garfield cutting edge?
Yeah, I am. Yeah. Cutting edge, looking good. But yeah, I did love Garfield as a kid. I guess I
really couldn't, I'm trying to think of why I loved Garfield as a kid. That's the question.
There's so much why. And I guess it's like, if I really think about what I like about it is I
liked the drawings, I think. Sure. I think I liked the- Like the line weight. The lines were soft and
I liked the look of the character. There was something about it. Big eyes. But I love that,
the voice. Lorenzo Music is the guy. Oh my God, of course. And then his mouth doesn't move.
The volado of it is the voice. He's also, he's fake Bill Murray in Ghostbusters. Right,
the reverse. Real Ghostbusters. Yes, Lorenzo Music. And then Bill Murray did it. Yeah, yeah.
And he created, co-created Rhoda to Mary Tyler Moore's spinoff and he was Carlton the Doorman
on Rhoda. Wow. And he never was shown on camera, but he would always be, hey, it's Carlton your
Doorman. Oh, so that voice was famous for that. Exactly. Oh, okay, okay. And that's the thing I
knew at 10 or 11 and I was a little happy with myself for knowing it because my mother told me.
I feel like we were both the sorts of children at family parties. Relatives would be like,
I gotta get away from this kid. They're talking about Lorenzo Music and Lucille Ball. And I,
there was, I had a name tag at the container when I looked at the container store when I was like
21 and it said Carlson on it because there were so many mics. And an older lady was like, oh,
is that Carlson the Doorman? And they like, she chuckled to her friend, he's not going to know
that. And I go, oh, you mean Carlton the Doorman from Rhoda? And they were floored. And I felt so
good about myself. Your moment finally came. It literally was, it was a perfect moment to use it.
It's the only time it's ever happened other than this moment right now. So two times in 30 years
have I been able to use that knowledge. They were literally floored. They fell on the floor of the
container store. They bled out of their brain. That's right. You had to clean it up. I killed
two ladies with my knowledge of Lorenzo Music. You can confess that on a club three. That's
not going to bite you. This is too deep. Yeah, too deep. Cops don't want to pay the eight bucks.
You know what this might tie into? This might be the time for me to play this video in which
some of the why of Garfield is answered. And it's also what connects Nathan Masri to the creator,
Jim Davis. This is a video made by Jim Davis promoting Garfield Eats after the license has
been acquired. This is my favorite video I've ever seen. I'll skip through it a little bit.
And there might be a special guest in the video as well. Let's see. Hello, I'm Jim Davis and this is
my cat Garfield. Hi, I'm Garfield and this is my cartoonist, Jim Davis. And that pretty much sums
up my relationship with Garfield. A little history on how this orange furball became the most famous
cat in the world might be in order. You see, even as a child- Wait, I only wanted to play that. Now
what I want to play is him saying why Garfield became like a hero. This is straight from the
creator's mouth. Like why did Garfield become a pop culture phenomenon if he did? Just immediately.
And he was born during a time when the fitness craze was in full tilt. We were all made to feel
guilty about eating pasta, skipping exercise, taking a nap, and in general, anything that made
life a little bit sweeter. Well, Garfield came along and defended our right to eat lasagna,
skip the gym, and sleep until noon. In a sense, he was a rebel. I guess. I guess. Anyone a rebel? No,
as a kid, I could give a shit about him eating lasagna. I liked that he liked lasagna, but-
Skip the gym. It's this fitness craze. This is getting out of hand. Olivia Newton-John did a song
about it. Jane Fonda in a robe. Too much. That's too many things. We need a fatso to eat fatty food
and save us from this blight. Wow, that's an interesting revisionist history, I think. Unless
that's something I'm just totally oblivious to. I guess adults thinking that, but children certainly,
I don't think. I would think that- These crazes. I hate these crazes. Children are the primary
audience of Garfield, at least initially. I think so. I think. Yeah. I just don't, I think that rebel
thing- That's something fake. Yeah. Well, it might also be in there to try to like segue from one
topic to the other. Here, forgive me. Back to the, I might repeat a little, but here, he keeps going.
Skip the gym and sleep until noon. In a sense, he was a rebel, which brings us to Nathan Masry,
another rebel and co-founder of a new food experience that Garfield would love. Garfield
eats. It's an easy and entertaining way to get delicious food in a hurry and be entertained at
the same time. Nathan calls it an enter gauging app, entertaining and engaging. It's the world's
first enter gauging mobile app for the restaurant business. Now- Could you pause it real quick?
Because I love how he says restaurant. Restaurant. Restaurant. From the restaurant business.
From the restaurant business. From the restaurant business. It is so exactly the energy of
my other favorite piece of Garfield content, which is our great former vice president, Mike Pence,
taking up Congress's time to do this slow, dottering tribute to Garfield on his birthday
with this great, like he's saying the Garfield basics, like he hates Mondays and hates exercise
and loves to pig out a cat after my own heart. As you know, it doesn't cut C-SPAN or whatever
doesn't cut to the audience, but like everybody's going to be asleep or on their phone and fucking
Pence again. And it's so funny that like, and then 10 years later, people are trying to hang him.
If he just fucking like stayed sleepy, he could have gotten out of this whole mess. Yeah. He got
too- He wanted to be in Trump's graze. Everybody does as Nathan does. Yeah. Pulled into the crazies.
That's right. He wanted to be in Trump's good graces. I just want to go back in that video
when he says, hi, I'm Jim Davis, creator of Garfield. And then a little cartoon pops up, goes,
hi, I'm Garfield. It does. And that's my cartoonist, Jim Davis. Is that Jim Davis doing both the voices?
It does that way a little bit. It does not feel like an official. It's not more Lorenzo Pest way,
I believe. But yeah. Yeah. Jim Davis. Not Bill Murray. I don't know. He didn't answer the phone
for that one. I would, uh, it's, it sounds like you could, with the right deal, he'll like,
we've teamed up with Kohler Toilets and Garfield is now going to, you'll be able to shit in his mouth
with our new Garfield toilet, like whatever, just plant him in front of the camera. And if the check
cleared, he's ready to go. Yum. Yum. Feed me your shit. They make Garfield toilets. You still have
to flush them five, 10, sometimes 15 times. Go now you can wear Garfield bulletproof vest.
Garfield will protect you from gunshots.
Like he doesn't, it doesn't matter. You want to take the ultimate nap? Go with Garfield cyanide
pills. If you're in the middle, you're in the middle of a war and you've been captured. Garfield
just chomp right down on Garfield's numb, numb, numb lasagna, cyanide capsules on your flavor.
You'll take your ultimate nap. Take you to where you don't want to, if you're off getting tortured
by an enemy country, that's like a whole life of Mondays. Quaaludes are back after by popular
demand, but now they're called Garflutes. You will be thinking you're sleeping in a little purple box
with a blue blanket and you're hunched up. Try to point me at the camera and I'll endorse it.
It doesn't matter. It's such a great energy. It's so funny. It's so in line with 70 something.
Yeah, now we know that's him. So why did he say yes to this? Besides just like sure, whatever.
It still feels too shady to say yes to. He seems to attribute it mainly to like,
well, no one has ever come to me with such a crazy idea. Okay, I get I that's it. So for it.
So now this guy gets to do whatever he wants with your license in Dubai and Kenny, can you,
you are fine with just like, you know, 500 pieces of social media where your character is just next
to this bizarre orange suited man. Like they're best friends now. Like you're okay with that.
That is on brand to you that a strange somebody we've never seen. I'd like to announce a team up
Garfield and Alex Jones are now together doing a podcast. There is info wars X Garfield. Garfield
loves nootropics. They help his brain. Ben Shapiro and Garfield now have teamed up for an exciting
new cartoon for whatever the hell that shitty daily color films. Oh yeah. Garfield and Gina
Carano are teaming up at last to take on Hunter Biden and this time shipping him to Abu Dhabi.
Actually, he's already in Abu Dhabi. Hunter Biden is already in Abu Dhabi and Garfield has to
get them back and then ship them again. Did you know Hunter Biden did crack and then kicked a
bunch of orange cats? It's true. Garfield will tell you the tale. The first Garfield eats was in Abu
Dhabi or Dubai. Excuse me. Dubai. It was kind of, but scooters is that I was going to say,
because I can't, I've now, I at least skimmed past every piece of Instagram content from
both Nathan and Garfield eats. And what I did not ever see was a restaurant that says Garfield
eats in Dubai. So was it, or was it all, it was a purely, was that a totally ghost kitchen?
I'm not really sure. They said there was exclusive Garfield scooters that would,
people would deliver the food to you. Which are terrified. They're seeing these yellow
scooters with these like yellow cubes. It looks like some secret military is like
coming to haul you away. Yeah. I mean, different websites had different locations. I mean,
there was definitely some where we're, we're coming to London, Ontario. We're coming to London,
England. We're coming here and, and clearly like, I'm sure. Yeah. The pandemics. What did them.
It's another one. Only the pandemic. Like all these other things. It's another one where he
like declared at a certain point that there will be 250 locations or something. This is the runner
up. Celebrary, nothing but that. This is, this entire thing is like a celebrity where
the celebrity is a guy you've never heard of. But like, and now certainly Garfield was powering it,
but also he, the whole point of this brand that he created is Garfield plus me, Nathan Masri.
Who are you? Shut up. Don't ask any questions about me. Who's your dad? Can't tell you who,
how old are you? Stop it. This is gotcha journalism. Like it's, I want to be famous,
but if you have any questions for about me, I cannot tell you. And I'm furious you add that's
very Tommy Wiseau actually. Right. Like vanity project for me. All right. Two simple questions
about you. Shut up. Get him out of the theater. Would you say he's Mercurial? He's definitely
Mercurial as somebody who's super around could be. He's somehow managed to be both. Yeah. So yeah,
in order for you to buy into this brand, you have to not only love Garfield and be inspired by
Garfield as if it is the teachings of Christ, but also love this orange suit man. And there's
interplay. It's all the Instagram content is the two of them. Garfield's thinking something snarky.
And then so is Nathan. Like here's Garfield next to Nathan and Garfield says, this is the man who
made a pizza out of my face. That's nice, but I'd prefer it in my mouth. What creepy weird. I don't
like this. He started owning the brand so much that there's footage of him like, uh, for sick
or autistic children or something. He's like autographing the kinds of books you would get
mine, uh, from 1987. He's autographing Jim Davis's Garfield books from 1987. He did not have anything
to do with those. He was a child or maybe not even born. I don't know. Uh, who wants an autographe
Garfield book from the guy who took the brand five years ago? So weird. Um, here's another weird
piece of content. Um, this was in the Dubai days. Okay. This is, uh, just kind of like hunky photo
of Nathan. He's got his high hair. He's got his weird beard and he's holding up a log and a wooden
log and he says, I work my back hard while Garfield eats. This log has 4% moisture imported from
Europe. Do you know what it will be used for? Hashtag entrepreneur, hashtag style, hashtag won't
work. Do you, does anyone know what the fuck does that mean? I don't know what that means. What's
his log for? No idea. His moist log, 4% moisture imported from Europe, just the moisture or was
the log imported with the level of moisture that you wanted? I guess the log has the moisture too.
Is this, does this go along with the reusability? Like there were like the, the packaging for the
Garfield each place is like, you can use them for other things. I don't know if those are connected,
but let's talk about that. That's one of the weirdest things. Very strange. This is just like,
come into this restaurant with no seats and learn every premise for a restaurant you could possibly
handle at once. So this is it's because it's all reusable sustainability, but the box is wasteful.
I'm going to add this lasagna box. I'm going to end up throwing it away. Well, not so fast. Oh,
really? Is there another way? Yes. You can turn it into a tissue. You can turn this grease covered
pizza lasagna box into a tissue box. She's caked. So all I have to do is peel the cheese off. Yes.
That is basically merging with the cardboard already. Uh huh. Uh, may try to be okay with the
grease and then take my, all my loose tissues that I have because I am not willing to spend the money
for tissue boxes. So I go to, I buy tissues off the street. Yeah. I go to a dealer who gives me
loose tissues, but I have nowhere to put them because I don't pay for a tissue box. What do I
do with all these bags? So you're the bag hutch, you know, thank God. Finally, there's a better way.
So the way a box to put my tissues in, uh, now these tissue boxes, one thing I hate about tissue
boxes is that they have that plastic part that kind of grabs the tissues and leaves the ones you
don't want in this box. Doesn't have that. Does it? Um, probably not. Oh, thank God. I hate the
plastic part of tissue boxes that I want them to just be loose so that maybe I pull one and pull
a hundred more out, um, of my grease cheesecake, tissues. The fuck is this playing? I don't, yeah,
I don't know. So weird. Uh, what else do you have to learn about the restaurant before you even
start? Well, there's the app. So you have to get an app and you have to watch Garf, you start watching
your Garfield content on the app. Here's another, this is going to blow some minds too.
This is from exclaimed.ca. He's talking about like the videos that are going to be on, uh,
you're going to know where I'm going with this because he's, this is an app that you watch while
you're waiting for your food and maybe you're watching eight minutes or so of content while
waiting. And he says, yeah, so you know, eight minutes, there'll be short form. And you know
what? We learned a lot from Quibi. I'm sure you're aware of Quibi. We think that again,
this is 2020. We think that short form is the future and that's what this is. Interviewer. So
you are a fan of Quibi. I do have Quibi, but I've unsubscribed. I did not continue my subscription
because it's only on mobile and my arm gets numb by holding the mobile. So as soon as they figure
out being on smart TV, which they should have done in the first place, then obviously I'll be
the first to sign up because I do love some of the content. So even he, we want to be like Quibi.
Really? No Quibi sucks. So no, but I do love the content. What's some of your favorite content?
Oh, there's one with JLo and another with Chris Hemsworth. I don't remember the names anyway.
What we want to be like Quibi, but I don't know what their shows are called. And I,
my arm gets numb when I try to hold my phone. Yeah. Now is the time to lie. Now is the time to just
go like, oh, it's great. I watch it every day and like memorize two shows, memorize like,
oh, I like the most dangerous game in 50 states of terror or whatever.
Now is the time to lie. I know he can't. What? Just don't like stop talking. Any interview you
see with this guy, you guys probably had it kind of researching the episode you're in for it because
like a one sentence question, 25 sentence answer, like stop. Why do you talk and talk and talk?
It's such a fun. I mean, I hate to keep bringing Trump back up, but it's such a
specific type of person whose family had a lot of money and they just turned into like a person
that has diarrhea is at the mouth and it gets them in every door. It just, it just, they waltz right
in people with money or I think people with money are stupider than people who don't have money.
Well, this is the big one. I've said this before on the show. This is the secret that middle America
doesn't didn't like as slowly figured out because of Trump. Yeah, they have that point.
People got it up in the point. Everybody goes, well, this person has money. Surely they did
something to earn it. There's no way a rich person could be foolish or stupid. Well, there's also the
aspirational side where it's like, well, I want to be rich and surely I will be like them and I'll
gotta be away for me to live the American dream. So how do I make the American dream habit by talking
and talking, talking, but yeah, no, it is a specific thing to these crazy rich people.
Yeah. Luckily it worked out a lot of people figured out that Trump is a con man and that
he just talked his way into the stuff and only some, a lot of people think that he is Christ,
our savior and will like take up arms for him. Yes, that's true. So, you know,
give and take you and some, you lose him. Okay. Okay. I have a little bit of the, of this Sarah
Hagee's article from food and wine, uh, or her order because, okay, well you said some of this
already, but they really got the runner, like she stuck with it and got what she was trying to get,
but they really gave her a hard time. Yeah. The interface wasn't working and he says it's early
stages. There's bugs. Don't worry about it. So he helped. He put in the order for them, the easy to
order mobile system. They were, you just need the owner to do it for you. They got a Garfield
shaped pizza. They got, okay. I was staring at this for so long before I got it. Did you
guys come across the phrase, the big Agna lasagna? Yes. Yes. I did. I haven't solved it yet. You
haven't solved it. Mike, do you have any idea? No, I don't know. Okay. Cause I look at it as big
Agna, but here's the clue. Agna is in lasagna. It's not Agna. It's Zanya. So why make it two words,
make it big Agna, which still is weird. Did you come across big cow lasagna? Yes. I feel like
that's more of a frozen good. Yo, that's the frozen cow. Yeah. That's when the, when the time
it got kicked out of the location, then he was dealing with big cow lasagna, which was held over
into the other brand. He started, this is where we're heading for four hours here. I have,
yeah, let's just take a break. You want to come back at seven tonight? We probably should cause
there's so many Instagram posts in general. I know. It's like, we could be the longest notes
I've ever had. We could do part two on just the Instagram. There's the landlord dispute.
Yes. Yeah. Well, well, yeah, go for it. Yeah. They got, he, the employees arrived one day,
you know, 2020 mid pandemic, uh, uh, first year of pandemic and found the doors locked, like the
locks have been changed. The landlord locked them out and that only lasted like four to six hours.
Because what happened was he got on the internet and started yelling. And I'm sure in reality, he
just did some phone calls and, uh, did a bank transfer and paid whatever he was owed or something.
But then at some point he said, the only weapon I have is the Garfield fans. When I speak, the whole
world listens. Now that's a threat and that's a Trump kind of threat. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Stand by.
What did he say? Like stand by and stand around. Yeah.
Keep standing. Yeah. Um, yeah. Well, then he started referring to the,
to the landlord and social media as land monster. Land monster is really something.
Um, I, yeah. When like probably just didn't pay and has the weight of Garfield. He's,
he thinks that people were yelling at him on the street. You are the Garfield king.
Why would that happen? That didn't happen. He also, cause there's all these grievances too. Um,
you know, I don't, if the guy encountered some like awful racial stuff, I can't argue with it.
Maybe that happened. But one that I don't understand is that he claims in an interview
that he would get harassed because, uh, okay. This people would say, come in and say things like
you have opened Garfield eats and not bugs bunny eats. And you were a disgrace to the
Garfield brand. You should have opened bugs bunny. It's been longer. Now you're reviving
a cartoon and bugs bunny deserves it more. We will threaten your store. We will threaten your life,
et cetera, et cetera. See, that's just a lie. See, he can lie. That is a lie. You are very
capable of lying. We know that no one cares about Garfield that much. He also,
or bugs. I think it's been longer open bugs bunny eats these bugs bunny terrorists who won't let
this nice man open his business. There's no, that is a complete like flight of fancy he had,
you know, like sometimes when you're like upset or you're like working through something, you start
to have like imaginary arguments with people. I do sometimes where you have like an imaginary argument
like before you might be getting into something. He must be having these constantly and now he has
them. They're so real to him. This is, well, this is also very Trumpy that like the thing,
the line gets blurry of what happened and what you just imagined. I think genuinely they don't know.
Yes. He like, uh, when he was saying, Trump was saying like, oh yeah. And I went to, uh,
I was on Jimmy Kimmel and he came outside and greeted me at the limo and he never does it.
He does not come out and he shook my hand and he had a white glove. That was not, that's not true.
Yeah. He's made that up. Um, now also the, in the darker shade, I, I feel like, uh, I got,
I gotta talk about this cause I, I couldn't believe the pendulum swings on this one. Okay.
Because he started selling Garfield face mass at some point, 2020 people selling face mass with
logos or characters on them. Sure. He apparently did not have permission to do that. That did not
fall under the license, but in when he asked for permission, he never heard back and he just did
it anyway. Before that he was, uh, playing around with COVID skepticism. He had a lot of posts that
it wasn't real, that it was actually sarin gas that people were being exposed to lines up with.
This is very Q ish, right? And then it starts to take a turn. A storm is coming. Military troops
are gearing up. COVID-19 quarantine is a cover up for something bigger. Another post stay at home
order was to prepare for the hashtag storm I discussed in March, 2020. It is war between
Jews and Arabs. Oh no, no. Didn't you learn anything from your Jake Novak video? Meanwhile,
cut to Jim Davis Garfield and I tell you to stay home. The storm is coming. Garfield is right.
This is a heart that says all lives matter. And so he has since disowned this, but it seemed like
he was really into it for a little while. He tried it on for a little while. Can I read now the
Instagram post? Uh, it's a picture of, of Nathan and Steve Wozniak, uh, Apple co-founder. And I
want to read the caption. Steve had mild symptoms and recently was on the news that he may have
COVID-19. I hope I did not catch it. I'd rather hashtag stay home than be with Woz.
What the fuck? I don't know. Is that because he has COVID or are you, you're selling, you took a
picture with Woz, but you hate him? I don't know. And then it's just like he wrote about meeting him.
So I don't know if he was with him. Uh, I don't know if he was. He does a lot of it. This is very
guy is like, let me, you know, the, like we've all, we've had scenarios where maybe we met a famous
person and then like that picture is for us and we don't need to like use this to start a business.
That's just a nice thing that I have not like straight to social media because before Garfield
eats, he had a gross West Hollywood picture with like a, uh, obviously a disgusting looking Jean
Simmons and Lisa Vanderpump. And he's trying to frame that as if like, well, they're around me
because I'm wheeling and dealing here in Hollywood. He also did a gross thing of one of the grossest
things, which is to, uh, get a cameo and then crop out that cameo logo that explains why you have
this celebrity content all of a sudden. Um, that didn't necessarily solve everything in this case
because you can tell the person is reading painfully reading copy that she does not understand.
Who am I talking about? Why actual Garfield family member from the films,
Miss Jennifer love Hewitt. Oh boy. Oh my gosh. Hi, it's Jennifer love Hewitt.
Congratulations on opening Garfield eats world restaurant for Garfield. I think that's amazing.
That was really hard to say. Um, that's so super cool. I want to come check that out.
I loved working on the Garfield movies. I was a big Garfield. And then she just talks about like
this is the most obvious cameo in the world. She doesn't know. And why Garfield eats world?
When was it ever that before? Weird. Don't look. And then, and then the caption is just like
Jennifer love Hewitt, uh, won awards for ghost whisperer and for so you, you're, you think you
can like a stolen Valor her like Canadian television awards from ghost whisperer because
you have nothing to do with Jennifer love Hewitt. Stay away from love. We should. Yeah. Stay away
from general of Hewitt. Uh, I think that's in general, uh, I was going to say we should pay
$75 to get him on blister or whatever the hell it's called, cause that's how much it costs.
So he wouldn't give him money. I guess the ride, the audience will go flooding out the door.
I don't know. I think they'll come flooding in the door. I was worried about this by the way,
like, cause he's going to know about this. If he's willing to throw down $8, he might hear this.
I feel like he like pokes around anything. The tweets will be, I was going to say like,
yeah, it's not a Google search to find this patron here, but fucking like put asterisks in it. So
we don't have to deal with this guy. It's like, it's a swear word. Oh, that's a good question.
Yeah. Maybe we should. I mean, I don't think anything, everything. I don't know if we've
speculated even at all here. I think we've just stated, but I don't know. I don't know. I just
don't, he's going to bother us. We know, we know the time wherever, like he has nothing to do,
but for her as people who are talking about his dumb thing. I'll say this. There's a couple of
other people we've talked about that I was sure were going to contact us and we have not heard
from them in the history of this podcast. Well, you thought your little classified
Anderson was fool me. I mean, I also, uh, I, him and John Benkowski here really,
I thought we could have a good time. Yeah. I'd love to have John Benkowski, Alki David or
something. Let me, oh God, he's too busy being that level of terrifying about COVID is sarin gas,
a hologram and presario Alki David. That's his, that's, that wouldn't even,
he'd censor that on social media. That's too tame for what he posts. Oh yeah. He's horrible. Uh,
okay. Anyway. All right. Grab it. I have a grab bag of other things about the restaurant when it
was up and running. They did not stop at stop at coupons. They were also good meals. You would
walk in and it'd be the most, the most confusing menu you've ever seen with just arrows pointing
to stuff. Dan, you got to order it on the app and then like, and the social media is the similar
style. Um, here's a gram that I have. Um, okay. Here's a piece of pizza and it's got broccoli and
pepper on it. And as an arrow and it says a slice of Garfield's face now available. And then there's
a circle next to that and it says 99 cent only. And if that looks familiar to you, it's because
they stole the logo store and just colored it orange. That's a, that's not just a phrase.
No, no, that's a logo. I like that brand. That's a nice store. Also, when you cut a slice of the
Garfield pizza, it never looks appealing. It looks small and wimpy and shitty. Yeah. Yeah.
People hated this pizza. The orange is horrible. Um, I, uh, cardboardy, uh, I saw some review
that said, Oh, what was this review? Oh, um, my brother-in-law ordered me the lasagna as a joke
a few weeks back. He had to follow up for a week because it never got shipped and finally arrived
in a wet bag and thought with a PC printed Garfield comic in it. After I took a few pictures
for posterity, I told my brother-in-law, I couldn't eat it because thought when delivered and threw it
out, he asked for a refund, but still had to pay the shipping and was told that a replacement lasagna
would be at my door within the hour. That was three weeks ago and I'm still waiting.
Well, I think the, the, the anecdote that I kept coming across was that, you know, he had giant
stuffed Garfields and there were a few stories about it. One is that someone tried to buy it and
they were told that is for serious collectors only, like they were being too, you know, funny
about it. And then the other story I heard is that someone, someone like paid money for one.
It's got a box shipped to their house and it was just a box of sand. It was a bag of sand in a box.
It was not what they had ordered.
Box of sand. How does that happen? That's not anything like Garfield stuff.
Which is very close to like a meme story that went around the internet a while,
a long time ago, where someone went to Walmart and it's unclear if this was a joke or they said this
is what happened. It's that they bought a router and when they opened the box, when they got home
for the router, it was just a bag of dirt that said puto on it. Like,
I mean, that's, that's a fitting for this because this is so like, this took on a life of its own
on the internet. This, this fell right in with all the Garfield meme stuff. I think that really
helps speed it along. Garfield is enjoyed in this kind of ironic, what was this way that gets a
little eerie. It's a little bit in that Shrek zone. It's a little annoying. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But
surely another character might not have gotten this. It's already so primed for internet and
then it's a disaster and he's this was so he guy. It's just the whole recipe is there. I hate to
interject. We're kind of a bonus round area here. Instagram, there's a poster. I don't know if you
came across this. It says under construction, my unique Garfield collection suit by men, fashion
designer and stylist in Dubai. And it's him drawing a picture of himself, I guess, in a suit,
which I don't know that it looks anything specific. Like I don't know why you would have to
draw it. It just looks like a, an okay drawing of a guy in a suit. Yeah, that's really bland.
And then he said, invest in your personal branding to claim your identity in society.
Someone will Google you, which is another threat. Yeah, I know. Uh, and this does not put his name
in the description. How about that? That might, maybe he'll miss it because of that. Um, there's
also, do I have it here? Uh, did you come across, uh, Nath field? No,
I hate him. He wrote the big reveal introducing Nate hashtag Nath field, which is a combination
of him and a cat, a Garfield style cat, uh, far from being lazy. He possesses orangey superpowers.
I don't know. He also has so many on Instagram posts of, of quotes that are attributed to him,
to him. Yes. Inspirational quotes. It used to be Jim Davis, which is being inspired by Jim Davis.
That's like only Mike Pence has ever done that. But then it switches over to, I never knew what
love is until I met Garfield is I never knew what it is. I dream to be a trendsetter, not a trend
follower. And then Masri, it sounded like he had a pretty loving mother. It sounded like he had a
very loving family. And even though they went through hard times, but what, let me propose this
and we don't know, this is all alleged in speculation. What if not? This was Aaron's
theory. Actually, when I was telling her all this stuff about like, he says that Jim Davis is like
a Godfather to me. Um, and that kind of clued me in and Aaron was saying like, what if this was,
what if he was kind of like disowned? What if the more plain brother who we learned about who,
who just like plugged into the business and didn't have all these kooky ideas, maybe this is like a
soul situation, you know, Jimmy McGill, uh, he wore his weird suits and his personality had to come
out and he couldn't just fit into the boring law firm. Maybe Nathan was like not the chosen brother
and he's been looking for a father for me. He's in a little like at least business disowned by his
father and he finally found the kind fatherly figure he's always needed in Jim Davis. I mean,
Jim Davis does have like a kind grandfather energy around him in those, in those videos.
I'll say that. Yeah, there's a picture of them. One of my posts that I highlighted is him and
Jim Davis sitting at a table, Jim trying to work his phone. It looks like, and he writes dine and
wine with partner Jim Davis talking about, guess who? Yup. Garfield and our new app. Jim is young
at heart with many stories to tell. No wonder he is the legendary hashtag comic strips writer of
all time since 1978. So yeah, I mean, there's a, there is maybe a fatherly situation here.
It's also like, this is the brag that you're doing is that you're, you hang out at least
probably on two occasions, maybe with Jim Davis. This is what your breath, like there's other,
there's like kind of wise people who'd like, you know, you could make somebody jealous of by like,
wow, I got to go spend a bunch of time in our imagineering world. You know, it's neat when you
see like, wow, I got to hang out with Bob Gurr or whatever. And it, but who's ever, you liked Garfield,
you liked Garfield more than any of us. Did you ever, were you ever like, God, if I could only hang
out with his creator, Jim Davis. Well, after I saw the video today, yes, actually, I thought,
you know what, this would be great to talk about restaurants with Jim Davis, but no, as a kid,
it was not the coming storm. You know, there's a storm coming, right? Michael, we have to be
prepared. I mean, when you're a littlest, but I was like, even Kevin Eastman and Peter Laird as a kid,
you're, you're like, I know those names, but I want to hang out with Michaelangelo. Yeah. Like
as you get older, you're like, Oh, I'd like to, I'd like to talk to these guys. But yeah,
I mean, I did follow some auctions for Garfield original comic strip art recently. And then I
stopped following them once they crossed the $300 threshold. And I realized they had the data. I
thought it was like, Oh, wow, this is $50. And then I, I had to look again and I was like, Oh,
the auction's in three weeks. This just went up. No one is paid yet. That's why it's $50.
I thought you were cashing in on Garfield. Why does no one know of it?
I have to say, we, since we mentioned quotes, you know, there, there was an interesting,
you know, quote from a professor, I think of this, this eater roundup about how everything went down
and, you know, he proposed the idea of a bad text. This is a bad text and gave the example of like
Rebecca Black's Friday. It became like a game. The fans, people on the internet, they want to
participate in the game and that's how it gets remixed or people make videos out of people.
People want to have fun with this stuff on the internet. And usually you can't do that with a
good text. It stands on its own, but like there's room in bad texts for people to get in and fuck
around. Wow. Totally. Yeah. So I did like that idea. I thought there was some validity to that
idea, but the quote that really got back, got me back on board was from Nathan himself. And it was
about detractors of the restaurants. As for the negative opinions, restaurants, the restaurants,
the restaurant, as for the negative opinions, those were from haters whose taste buds were
psychologically tainted. Masry said, I've learned taste psychology as well. And you know, sometimes
if you hate someone so much when you eat their food, you're gonna just say it's disgusting,
even though it's amazing. And so it's just psychology that if, if I didn't tell you that
was from Nathan, that sounds like Donald Trump. Oh yeah, completely. Oh, and there's, and there
are a lot of people who, if he started a restaurant now, they would like the finest food they're weeping
while they eat it. And it's like uncooked pork. I really, this is as quick as I know, but it's
related to what we were just talking about. I think, and I haven't double checked it. I think
on truth social Trump put like, and even Phantom of the Opera is closing under Joe Biden.
Brandon did this. Yeah. I think that's what he, and the Phantom's not safe. Right. The
chandelier is falling. Trump loves Andrew Lloyd Webber and is horrified that Phantom is closing
on Broadway. This salt of the earth guy, not a brissy, brissy New York socialite. Not a,
not a Manhattan guy furious. He can never go to a Broadway show again. Cause he'll just get
booed by the cast, the crew, the audience. There's no roller skating musicals under Brandon. I tried,
I tried for four years and the swamp wouldn't let me bring back starlight Express. They tried. I,
he tried to make new Cinderella, try to make it in England. What happens? It closes and the queen
dies. And that's under Joe Biden. This guy that 10 years ago would rather have talked to you about
the new actor playing Mr. Mistoffelees versus anything political. He's a disaster. No state
presence. He doesn't know what is, he doesn't know what a Marcus he goes right past it folks.
Uh, that's so Tugger used to be a curious guy. Not anymore.
The ball under Biden. The ball is not so Jellicle.
This is what he wanted to talk about. And now it's just psychology. It's just psychology.
Fuck. Um, uh, sometimes on the social media, they change it to, I hate weekdays.
No, you can change that quote from the movie. I don't care. No one knows that quote. We all know
it's not weekdays. God, even Garfield has limits. He needs to get up sometimes and, and, and then
to keep, but to keep it consistent with the Garfield philosophy, it was closed on Monday.
This new business
I like that though. I think it's funny as hell that a lot of places, a lot of small
establishments are closed on Mondays. Not because not as a tribute to Garfield. Anyone. If you open,
if you own a little store or something, say it's for Garfield. That's more fun. Your Christ figure.
Um, picture on Instagram of Garfield's hand shaking Nathan's hand.
And it says now made good food gone affordable mission accomplished.
Well, judging by most reviews, it was neither good nor affordable.
No, it's so expensive. It's crazy. I feel like I've seen, uh, you know, farm to table places like,
Oh, the foods under season, the selections. I don't know. It's kind of hint and miss. I've
never seen anywhere labeled farm to plate and it's atrocious. You know, which one is he's
farmed a table is the more traditional phrase, but he pushes F2P, which is far too late.
Yeah. He can't just use the one that people use. He's got to invent that too. Um, well,
it's, it's more affordable sometimes because, um, Garfield broken heart weekdays every Sunday.
I can't even, this is so too irritating to read. There's so much busy text, but the main thing is
he's telling you that it's 25% off on from Sunday to Wednesday. And he conveys this with a giant
percentage sign and then attached to the giant percentage per the percent is the point of this
post. And then attached to that as a tag that says 25% so per 25% percent. So you've got just
a giant percentage sign. Like that's the point of the post percent. And then attached to that
is a much smaller tag that says 25%, which is again attached to a percentage size. So 25%
percent. This is not the only time he did this format of put like, let's just put a big percentage
sign, but put the amount smaller, the social media, it's all so, and then what does Garfield
have to do with it? And then often Garfield is saying stuff that's not in the voice. It's just
kind of flat. Do not wake me. It is a Monday. It's not like there's kind of a like foreign lost in
translation nature to it. I, uh, it's all confounding. And then the, and then also on the topic of,
I mean, I'm still obsessed with like, right. Here's a boy. Here's a bunch of like blank orange space
by 90 pause to unlock this coupon. Got it. Okay. For a pumpkin Garfacino. So you bought,
remember you buy pause, but you unlock goop. You cannot buy a coupon. A coupon is to help you buy
for less. It's, I love it. It's so confusing. So much to learn. I, this is, uh, you know,
okay. I don't know. Uh, tell me when you guys, I think I'm out of my grab bag, at least for right
now. I am too, except for, uh, well, does anyone, because what we have, what we haven't talked about
is like the biggest piece of video content that there is. Sure. Sure. Is there any more? Is there
anyone got anything left in their grab bag? Uh, I've got his post Garfield eats. We'll get to those.
I just, I want to wrap the whole thing up with a little proposal that we've sort of talked about
before, but this is, this has inspired me in a way. This is, I think I've thrown this out as a
phony idea before on the show, but I think really I want to get it going now. And this has inspired
me to do it and start investigating. So I want to throw that at the end. Um, okay. Well, um, I don't
know if that idea is to start our own reality show because that is what Nathan Masri did. Uh, this is
available in full on YouTube, his show, love me, feed me, don't leave me. If you can imagine the
show. Um, this has a little fakey the way every reality show, Nathan Masri was the youngest,
a bunch of the shit we've said, he sold his own ad agency at 24. Well, when did he start it? We
went straight to selling it. And then, uh, a probable lie from earlier became a deeper lie
now in transit because he says he even went to Hollywood and studied acting alongside Ryan
Gosling. That was just his teacher. When did it become, wait, weren't you in Hollywood in 2015?
Did Ryan Gosling go back for refreshers? Eddie not been in Oscar caliber films by that point. Um,
so anyway, I don't mean this fucking show. I was interested in this for three minutes and then
they just boy did it. It's just the fakest. It's like re it's, it's all that reality show,
hijinq music like don't don't don't don't don't don't don't. There is a problem in the store.
And then while he navigates like fake problems, uh, like the, the tablets are off really,
really. And he, what's the worst about this is that he's incredibly unlikeable in it in sort of a,
uh, Gervais Michael Scott kind of way, but he also knows it. Like he's, he's, you can tell he's
trying to be the irritating boss and that makes it worse. If you just like actually were able to
document this guy and see the horror show, but then he'd like him like playing this like
cheeky character of a mean crazy boss. Like I'm playing about paying people minimum wage. It's
like really, yeah, it's really hard to piece it out. It's like hard to figure out.
I guess what put upon workers who do nothing but answer questions about store confusion.
Now you get to be in a reality show too. Um, I, and this is in this, you get a really good
look at the face. I think we've maybe underplayed the orange-ness. It's so weird. And the beard is
so bizarre. It looks like if like a, if a woman is playing a male character in an SNL sketch
and they have to like quick change, like peel a beard onto them. Um, but it doesn't, it doesn't
resemble the texture of a real beard or the color of one. It's that like game. It's I've seen this
before about people. It's that remember that, like, that like thing where you have a magnet and it
would, there was like a person. Thank you. Willy, Willy. It was the thing where you would like make
hairstyles or a beard style for the head. And it looks kind of like that. And it looks like when,
you know, someone in their sixties is up on the stage playing rock and roll and they got jet black
hair and they got a jet black beard and everyone in the Ringo all start, yeah, Ringo included,
Ringo included. You're like, that doesn't look quite, I don't think that's the natural stage
make as long as it looks good from the back row. Fine. But then there's like windows where you
could see what his real skin color looks like, which is a normal, not unappealing color. Like
why would he choose the orange over just a red, but then he left some of it. God, it's strange.
Powerful. Like Mr. Trump. He even took, is that why was he like, I have to be a weird orange man?
Probably it's orange is the thing, the color that ties this all together. Yeah. Yeah. But also
stay home. We're all in this together. He, is there anything else about this? I mean,
I mainly the show, the show gives you a good look at what it was like to be in the lobby where you
can't eat. And my main takeaway is there's just a lot of loose wires. The TVs that are playing
old Garfield and friends just have like unpleasant computer wires dangling around. It's just also
true of the hologram theater. That was my memory of Alkydade. It's all so many loose wires.
Just immediately does not inspire confidence in biz. Like if you got some Velcro ties or you got
those plastic tubes to cover wires, like it's amazing the little tricks that you can do to fool
people that like, Oh, this is nicer than things. It's like when you buy the paint, get a sample
size and keep a brush like in a closet. And then if someone, you know, dings the wall,
you have some to do touch-ups like, or your, your face or your, which was chosen from a Pantene
gallery. Anyway, okay. What's left? The, we talked about the book a little Jeff Cole,
he's dodgy about his age. His age changes all the time. I mean, I'm sort of heading
for the end a little bit. Okay. Oh, here we go. All right. So let's, let's take you through the
downfall. Jason, you covered the main thing, which is the COVID skepticism, which is very disturbing,
but along the way, you know, we all know how many landmines there were in all of 2020, even before
the pandemic. And he stepped right in one, one of the great pre COVID tragedies, which is the death
of Kobe Bryant. You know, when you've opened a Garfield enter gauging quick mobile restaurant,
you have to address the death of the Los Angeles sports hero with a post that ties it together
because in 2016 he won a kid's choice award. So thus he's holding an orange lamp. And the tone of
this post is like, well, I have to look as an official licensee of at Nickelodeon, the staff
and I at Garfield, the, it's are equally and deeply saddened by the death of Kobe Bryant. Like,
so only because he won a Nickelodeon award and you're technically in the umbrella of Nickelodeon.
And then it keeps going. Like the legend gone too soon. Hashtag dies. Hashtag children. Hashtag light.
Fuck you don't do this. It's crazy. Why are you talking about Kobe's death? The hashtags,
every step of the way, the hashtags are wrong and unnerving. They never stop. What? Like who didn't
figure out many years ago that hashtags do not get you anything. I think no one looks for hashtags.
The end of 2009, start of 2010, everyone was like, okay, now if you put a hashtag, that's a joke.
Like that is, it's no longer useful. Although I've noticed this, it even fucks up your,
like your joke will have less reach because of the hash. The hashtags are like, what's the thing that
the conservatives think happened to their tweets? It's kind of like the hashtags actually limit the
reach of your thing. Right. I meant more in a figurative sense. Yes. Yeah. Yes. And as an actual
joke tenant, it can get really weird. And I don't know, trending topics are just insane. Now the
stuff like Twitter thinks you want to say. Absolutely. Yeah. So don't, why is he still
doing this in 2020? I don't know. So he, he thinks there's no pandemic. He's posting somewhere. I also
like the really blunt stay inside because it is gas. So this is the first foot he's put forward
in terms of the pandemic, which is sure to wreck his business, regardless of the business being
bizarre. So people, there's enough feedback like, Hey, that's weird. Don't do that. So now he has to
kiss everyone's ass about and be kind with the pandemic and post things like Garfield in a
superhero Cape. Gar cartoons are always immune. Tell us what cartoon you want to be today.
And then Garfield says everyone wants to be me. And then in his caption, he says,
tell us who you want to be, preferably a Nickelodeon cartoon or from Garfield and friends.
I wouldn't be Tommy Pickles primarily because he is apparently immune from COVID-19.
That that's what I, the cartoon character I want to be. Cause he's a baby. Why is he immune?
He had said all cartoons are immune. Oh, all tart. Oh, good. Cause if you're both,
yes, call cartoons are always immune. Hey, I, well, I guess it'd be anyone. Anyone.
It'd be any. Oh yeah. No, don't say that. That's harassment to say bugs, but don't put that on
Nathan. There's a guy outside with a broken pipe, swinging a chain around. He was a big bugs bunny
fan. I saw your post. It should only, only answer should be bugs bunny. I will threaten your business.
The warriors are coming after him. The baseball furies are mad. All dressed in
robe, gray and white fur. Um, then he has to spin it around. He went from in a week,
he went from hoax to I need to help the healthcare community and I need to do this with the Liz cares
program. Now Liz, we all know this. Liz is a nurse who John Arbuckle wants to ask out. Of course.
But he's, uh, scared to. So the Liz cares program, her shadow shows that she has a superhero. Uh,
she is a course, not all superheroes wear capes, but they all do in their shadow. Right. Um,
so Liz and any doctor could from now on get 50 to 75% discounts. Uh, all healthcare professionals
get free Garficinos thanks to this pandemic. That's one of that's even better than everyone
banging on the trash cans to say thank you doctors. Free Garficinos. I don't know if that,
how long that program went. It says permanent, um, 50% off all food items and even special
Garfield and Liz merchandise nurses, doctors. We know this has been difficult. So 50% off Liz,
Liz tall doll, unique pairing. You don't often see Garfield and Liz. Liz is like the 15th most
popular Garfield character. Yeah. I would love to see like a storyline with Liz and Arlene
commiserate. Sure. Garfield's girlfriend Arlene. Oh yeah. Yeah. You didn't know that. I didn't know
Arlene. I guess I don't know Garfield very well. Arlene's pink. Do you know when she got big
eyelashes? Okay. She's kind of got a long neck. Do you think we're going to get a gripe about,
just be sure everything you say about Garfield. Maybe. I mean, if you look up Arlene Garfield,
will you recognize her? I'm wondering. Have I ever seen Arlene Garfield? I mean,
I don't recognize her right now because there was never a food item named after Arlene. Oh yeah.
Pink eyelashes. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Kind of creepy. Yeah. Well, I would say, all right from that,
sorry, that color of pink and the long neck, the long neck. I know what you're going with.
Giant head. Yeah. I come, how could you not? Arlene is a little bit suggestive looking.
Foul. She looks like a foul. Yeah. I designed Arlene. Oh, the plushes are, oh, I do not like
the look of Arlene. I designed Arlene to be foul-like for a reason. Arlene, we're excited
to welcome Arlene Brand Sex Toys into the Garfield family. I couldn't be more thrilled about it. Use
it anywhere in your bedroom, at a restaurant. So, but this isn't enough. Clearly, because
immediately in the comments, somebody says, Liz can't defeat 5G sarin gas though. No. So too late.
He put his pandemic feelings out there a little too early. Land Monster comes in and hurts the
business. Eventually Viacom strips him of the license. We're cleaning house, like Star Wars,
kicking stuff out of Cannon. Garfield eats no longer part of Cannon. And on right before Christmas,
he was stripped of this in an already tough year. He is stripped of his Garfield title
right before Christmas. Those bastards, he said. And that's tough. He did kind of a eulogy tour.
He made some videos saying what's next for him, reaching out to the many fans, which he had to do.
There were so many, tens of people, most of whom were looking at this ironically, waiting to know
what's Nathan's next move. I gotta say, the two part farewell video.
First off, I watched them both. The part one ends definitively. And then part two starts,
and he's talking about other stuff. It's weird. It's already. You'd think it would just continue,
but it doesn't. He's on to the next thing. I'm sure there's a quote attributed to him about how
you gotta move on quickly. No way. I'm gonna read you one as soon as we reveal the next business.
The thing in the video that stuck out to me is that he used the word destiny. And I was not the
only one to clock that because other journalists who talked to him was like, he said destiny a lot.
Yeah, weird. Garfield the cat is his destiny. Being a part of Paws Inc. is his destiny.
He did a zoom saying goodbye to all the fat, like you could get on and talk to him and which people
did. He said, boy, this is maybe where the Jim Davis thing gets the heaviest. He says,
Jim Davis told me take care of the cat and the cat will take care of you. And that is what happened.
And look, it's all I have. I'm not married. I don't have a kid. This is what I have is Garfield eats
and the cat and Viacom has taken that away. Oh my God, my God, how miserable you have the gym and
Jim Davis is sage. I mean, that's, that's a nice moral, but it probably only applies to Garfield.
So kind of a sad little Peter out of this business and Nathan Masri had no choice but to
think about what had happened, collect his thoughts, maybe learn from the errors of his
ways and next time try to start a more coherent business plan that is more guaranteed to have
success. That is not true. He started Scooby Doo eats. Next one. Next one up. The thing I just said
to you, Mike, the, Oh God, where is, Oh yeah, here I am. And then just immediately Instagram posts,
me and Scooby done with the cat. It's time for the dog. It's so funny. That was my Bible done.
I'm about dog now. I have found a new God. Oh my gosh. It has got backwards. So funny.
Just instantly. And look, I know it's just all the same shit, except he didn't even bother with the
restaurant this time. Now it's frozen food, which Instagram posts allegedly affirm that they were on
the shelves at some places, but did he just sneak them onto shelves, take a picture and then smuggle
them out? I don't know. Entirely possible. Oh, things on the table. Uh, no more orange suit. Hello,
Brown Scoot suit, Scooby suit. He's wearing a scoot now. He didn't say scoot. He should as the
one phrase he missed. Um, he'd say things like, thanks for staying Brown. No, no, no. He posted
it. This law. Did you guys watch this like endless video? I can't even make it through of the launch
of Scooby Doo. I didn't watch that. I didn't. This was, I needed a lot of breaks. Yeah. From
this. Um, well we're going to come back to this in general as a topic. So we'll have another chance.
I think, I mean, I do have a little more, which is that, um, remember that post that you showed
Mike where it's his hand, the iconic hand of Nathan Mazury shaking hands with Garfield? Well,
the hand business kept going. Here is one where, um, the, the caption is need a hot dog for your
sandwich and his hand. I'm sorry. Okay. Let me go backwards. Scooby is holding up a hot dog, Frank,
and Nathan's hand is holding an empty hot dog bun. And if we were to take the caption literally,
he is saying that an empty hot dog bun qualifies as a sandwich. You're right. Yes. I disagree
with this definition. Let's ask our expert Jason. Just a hot dog bun. Is it a sandwich?
Well, just the bun. That's what's being illustrated here. Need a hot dog for your
sandwich. And you're holding this and that is, that qualifies as a sandwich. You know, this is
a long running internet argument is a hot dog, a sandwich, right? Um, I don't offhand, but I don't,
but that's a, and that's interesting. I would, I would say no, but maybe in the like the kind of
like early 1900s definition. So, but this is proposing that a hot dog is a sandwich before
there's beef in it and no condiments. No, it's not. It's not. I don't know. Yeah. This is like,
I'll answer for Jason. No, it's not. This feels like the close encounters aliens are playing
tunes at me. And I, I'm like, why, why are they showing music? And it's like, no, no, no,
they're communicating. You don't understand play it, play this frequency. It's like, oh no,
it's speech. It's their speech. You've talked about coupons and inter gauge for, uh, and, uh,
and, and Tolios is Arab, Arab here making a mountain of mashed potatoes. Like Richard dry
fits at this point. Now we're like, why are people yelling at me? Is a hot dog a sandwich
without a hot dog in it? I don't, I know it's just a piece of bread. This is insane. What are you
talking about? A sandwich. Um, and yet not the most insane piece of social media for Scooby
Doo eats. I have to give that one to this. Oh, I have to brace myself before reading this one,
purple background with flame at the bottom orange flame. And it says Netflix and dogs grass fed
hot dog is the date that won't hurt you. I, let's just all, so maybe we all need to lie on the
ground. Just kind of process this. I'll take a nap, whatever it takes this whole endeavor. I,
I wrote this down pretty early when I was coming through this. It feels like when you trans you
use Google translate and you type a sentence into English and then you translate it into
French or Spanish. And then you take that sentence and translate it back into English and everything's
just a little wonky. Yeah. Cause it's just a pure literal. Yeah. And that that's what this all the
whole endeavor feels like. Extreme. I mean that that's just, it is the Bay like the room. It's
the basis of like, you know, I mean, these are all English speakers we're dealing with. However,
like there's something in, I mean, there's something is not correct, but bad. Even if you would grant
someone that, okay, maybe English is your second language. That doesn't feel like what this is.
No, because also something sinister entered in. This is one of the most sinister statements I've
ever seen. Grass fed hot dog is the date that won't hurt you. The date all other dates hurt you.
Hot dog singular one word. Why is it grass fed a grant about the hot dog itself is grass fed
the hot dog ate grass. The three different animals that a hot dog is all three of them were grass
fed. They all the pay the animals that formed the paste all were fed with grass. And the filler that
fills out this hot dog also grass is grass. It literally is grass. The more grass the guaranteed
it is it won't hurt you. Netflix and dogs. Not a verb. It doesn't work even as a spin on Netflix
and chill. My body is liquefying. I know. His spine is wobbly. I'm about to keel over. I know. So we
need to let's we'll start heading for the door, but I feel like something big is missing. Oh, well,
you know, if you have a good idea, you might make a company, you might make a startup,
but have you considered working with Nathan and making a try up a try up? Yeah, you see,
he started a new company that they don't build startups. They build enter gauging try ups,
not startups, not startups, try ups, a little robot in it. Try ups. What's that?
I don't quite understand it. It's basically startups, but I think they cover some more of
the upfront costs or they're really speaking and I want to start babbling. Yeah, I've lost. He's
robbed me of my ability to speak English, but I think the thing that stuck out to me in this image
is, oh, he took enter gauging with him. Yeah. Yeah. Cause he says he doesn't know that the blizzard
or whatever that he says in that video. Yeah. Oh, oh, well also because this has been the struggle
with him is like, what do I do now? I told you he was so tearfully like I've been stripped of
Garfield and it's my identity and Jim Davis is my godfather. So what can I take? And you're
enter gauging is one of them, but he, nobody ever took the social media Garfield needs brand or
whatever on Twitter or Instagram still going. And so what you end up with, and this continues to
this day, a lot of confusing back and forth where the only account engaging with Garfield, enter
gauging with Garfield apps is Nathan Masri. So they, they like ping back and forth. Like when I'm
doing any Craig Healy view, boo posting, I'm just switching between accounts. Spoiler. And so he's
doing the same thing, but for real, uh, like he needs this to work. So, okay, now I sign in to get
and, but what does he do with Garfield needs? Cause he's not selling food anymore. Well,
he creates weird scandals and this is one that, uh, Jeff Cole told us about, um, this is a situation
called staple gate. Yes. Yes. Staple gate, hashtag staple gate. Uh, basically he allegedly went to
A and W the fast food chain. Well, we'll circle back to that. Yeah. Yeah. Never. It's never just
a thing. Um, he went to A and W and found a staple like in his bun or in the burger or something,
a loose staple, which he attributes to like, that must've been part of the packaging that, uh,
surrounding the food. So, and, and somebody wasn't careful and ended up in the food. And he is
furious. He is like, it goes from, I found a staple to, uh, never would have happened with me.
We had a rest also very Trumpy extremely never would have. You never would have found a staple
and then it gets really extreme. So what course of action should I take at A and W
Canada? You almost bled me to death. Hashtag blood. You tried to kill me, but I'm crawling back.
Damn it. You're a stable. You can't defeat me. What were you going to say though? Well, wasn't
there, uh, uh, an epilogue to that was it was actually Wendy's, but he, it was a Wendy's burger,
but he tagged A and W wrongly accused. That was incorrect. And then shortly there, after all this
happened, he tried to start a nonprofit or a business about food safety, like really quickly
after that. Yeah. The next day he's tying it into something called clean label product.org. That's
about like, don't put dangerous stuff in food packaging. So yeah, oddly suspiciously it went
from like this staple gave almost gave me blood to this is part of my brand. Now I'm an anti-staple
swallower. I'm an anti-staple swallowing advocate. And that's what I do. It's kind of similar. Isn't
there a similar to a scene in the Jennifer Love Hewitt movie Heartbreakers where they put something
in the soup. They put something in as a scam. They pull, they pull, put something in the soup. I
believe I haven't seen them moving in a few years. Uh, so maybe when it was just when he was going
through the filmography of miss love Hewitt, it's very strange, but that's just, look, it's not how
it works. It's not like you can just go viral by like, I don't know, finding a shrimp in your
cinnamon toast crunch. It's not the record scratch. That's not how it works. There's nothing to be
gained from something like that. So you said reminded me of a thing that really stuck out to
me in the farewell video. And I think it's that he held up a book at one point he went, we had an
operations manual and that's just so the, the excitement of that is just so funny to me because
it's like, it feels like a, like a small business person being like, we gave customers receipts.
Come on. Like, yeah, you, you should have an operations, but you're a business basic. Yes.
Yeah. Well, that's where if we could tie it to the philosophy, love me, feed me, don't leave me.
That is that like, as much as you want to say, well, this guy's like a self-made, he's just so
sure of himself for a narcissist and he, uh, and the sheer bravado got him where he is
that don't leave me thing is really like the, because that's the tone of the, of the book
and hot Oprah. And I had the manual and Jim Davis and I love him and this is all I have.
There's also just this uncomfortable level of emotion that requires a lot of investment for
like a funny Garfield restaurant that like, why do we know that? Why did it? Why did any listeners
know about this? Why did anyone on the, why have we talked about it for so long? None of this should
have hit us. A real business would not have the owner going like the manual. It's so unprofessional.
Yeah. Too much information for us to know about.
He's overtaken the narrative. The narrative should be, isn't it fun to eat a Garfield pizza?
Yes. That's what the narrative should be. Everything we've ever talked about on the
show has had somebody like having a meltdown, but we don't know it because they pulled themselves
together and like, no, I'm my public persona must be strong. It can't be crying. Oh, Jim Davis.
I remember, and it might still be out here. I'm sure it's come up in conversation. The
licensed burger chain, she burger, she burger in Chicago. Well, no, it was, there was one in
Ocean City, New Jersey. There was one in Delaware. Like, so, so they, they licensed this and it was
just a pretty standard, like burgers and milkshakes kind of like lunch counter sort of thing. And if
you didn't remember the very old SNL character, she burger, she burger, Pepsi, like some might say
did not necessarily translate past the original. Maybe that's right. And so all the parents,
like I remember my parent being like, oh, it was SNL. And the only reason you knew it was
an SNL sketch was there were some framed photos from SNL of those characters on the wall.
And like, uh, the burgers were fine. You didn't need to know this. You didn't need, if you just
went in and you weren't paying attention, didn't see those things. It didn't really matter. The
thing that probably made it stick out more was like every table had a little, you know, a card
holder that had trivial pursuit cards in it to like, you know, do trivial while you wait for your
food. So you're saying they have created a brand that is tied to a pop culture item, whatever,
a piece of content. Uh, but it's not, you can ignore that and still enjoy the experience as
opposed to Garfield deeds where it is essential that you love Garfield, you love Garfield to the
point of tears and you, what's this an orange suit guy? I love him too. Garfield's new friend,
Nathan Masary got it. I love him. You know, way he created Garfield. Nathan did. It's funny. It's
like, I've never seen that before. Where if you will, will something that it actually becomes true
and that Nathan actually created Garfield and now I know that and I love it. And that's actually
more important than having Garfield eats carrot juice this morning. That's actually supersedes
just enjoying the juice. Yeah. I don't think most people want a giant story to tumble out of the,
the business that they're going to. It's just too much. Like most people are in a haze. Give me the
thing. And if maybe if you stick around, you become a fan. It's like, Oh, I've actually met the guy. I
know the story of the place because it's nice. Not like, okay, before you eat here's 15 minutes
of backstory. It's all very upsetting and weird and shady. I just think, you know, one thing that
kind of jumps out at me is now that we've been talking about it, this is that, you know, think
about Tillman for Tita. Oh, I'd love to think about him. Yeah. Another, a guy from a few years ago
on the podcast wrote a book where he's aggressive about owning businesses and stuff. Does he not own
Bubba Gump? He does. Which is tied to a pop culture property, but you can go and enjoy your $25
of seven pieces of coconut shrimp, if you're lucky. And you don't need to know about Jenny and
Lieutenant Dan. Yeah. But I, I think by the time Tillman for Tita got around to writing a business
guy self-help book, he had a restaurant corporation that had rain first cafe and Bubba Gump and
chart house and the golden nugget. And he owned the Houston Rockets. And it, people might think,
you know what, I kind of want to hear how this guy did it. I kind of get that. This was more the
cart coming before the horse was born. Uh, you know, like we are getting the business, we got his
book, we got his memoir, like if he had done a little business, but no one knew him. There's
so much like that where people, what Pete there, what some people want is the guys. Some people
want to be calling action, action, and then dressing like a director and stomping around
and pointing at people and they don't actually care about making the stuff. Yes. There's so many
people who want the air. God, even, I mean, Trump is the most like hollow guy, but he didn't write
the book until he had like done a bunch of his shady stuff. Yeah. Do not to defend tree, you know,
f**k it. Let's defend him. Yeah. Great club three. Finally it comes out. This deep of burrowing.
It feels so good to be honest. No, but it's just a real time that I, you know what the book, uh,
biologists, that was before Garfield eats. Yeah. He was reprinted with him in the orange suit,
but then he didn't, that was before he'd done any, he maybe, he maybe hadn't even been knighted yet
by the arrested Prince. Yeah. There's a, this happens a lot everywhere. It happens on low levels.
It happens with people, you know, in Hollywood or all of a sudden they're like, by the way,
now I'm teaching a class on directing. You're like, wait a minute. Yeah, I'm teaching a class.
You're like, wait a minute. I've just, you've just declared something. Well, the declaring never stops
with this guy because here's something. Oh my God. This was this month, earlier this month. I
didn't even realize, uh, what's Nathan up to now? Why he's working on the reality show,
Mary Nathan Masri. Finally. Oh my gosh. He is calling for contestants, uh, from, oh,
could you possibly guess the name of his company? It's not his name. What else would it be?
Word. He says a lot. Oh, and, and, and, and, uh, the casting real implement the blind date is real.
The marriage is real. The Mar or marriage gift is real. What the fuck does that mean? Stop making
up words. This is pilot episode. Get ready to date. Nathan Masri and hashtag Toronto. Why do
you have a hashtag on a casting website? Casting notices are not evaluated by hashtags and
popularity. What a threat. Get ready to date. Nathan Masri in Toronto venue. TBD most likely
paradise theater. Oh yeah. I bet you think you're having problems with that. Uh, uh, real dates,
real people prize for winner non-paid. You don't say I don't get paid to date Nathan Masri.
Scooby doo eats impressario. No money. What? No way you ever dreamed of dating big cow lasagna
propagator. Oh my God. It's Jesus. Okay. To get, I am tapped out now, Mike, what was your,
what is your proposal? So I've said this a couple of times, sort of joking on the show before
and cause cause this whole licensing Jim Davis association is fascinating to me. I assume he
has money from the family. That's probably how he got involved with Jim Davis. And I've said this
before and I think I'm going to finally send some emails out because wouldn't it be great if we
could officially license one of the King feature syndicate cartoon strips to do something, a pop
up, a walkthrough experience. And when I say one of these, I mean the cheapest one we can find.
So like Mallard Fillmore ride it out. Funky Winker bean. Uh, like, uh, like there's ones that we
haven't like, wouldn't it be great if we could officially do podcasts, the ride X Winker bean
or something like just something in the realm of possibility. We could talk to the, if the creator
is still alive, if we could do an official in the spirit of Garfield eats, I don't know exactly what
it is because we'd have to figure out what's in the contract, what we would be allowed to restaurants.
Restaurant seems hard, much harder, but like a walkthrough experience, a maze, a horn,
something in this room, a groove blender, a groove blender, if you will. Uh, uh, I think this is worth
exploring and I think this is the time to light the fire and I will start exploring the cheapest
licensing deal we can make with an existing property, comic strip preferably. We should see
if that licensing convention that had, remember the licensing convention in Vegas happened. We
didn't find out till after and then I think we reached out to them and they were not interested
in our bullshit. Uh, well, I don't know. Do we reach out to them? I don't know. I think we're
trying to, or you know what? We might've saw it happen in 2019 said, we'll do it in 2020 and that
was not an option. I don't remember that, but it may have happened. I remember reaching out to designer
con and they said no. Okay. That's a different thing though. There's a licensing expo in Las Vegas
where like all of a sudden, say, you know, the couple of last couple of years, you see a lot of
golden girls merchandise all of a sudden popping up. Well, I don't know that this is how it happened,
but a lot of times what happens is people go to this licensing expo and somebody has the rights
to make golden girl stuff and they're pushing the idea that you should license this for your
t-shirt company, for your toy company. And that's how oftentimes things like that happen. I don't
think, I think that's not, that's too much too high profile. Oh, well, you want to get a funky
Winker bean or something that like crankshaft, no one's talking about it. We want to like,
we want the company or the lawyers to go, here you go for 500 bucks. Don't you want, you know,
not to say let's not get involved with King Features Syndicate. However, don't you want
as little corporate association as possible? That is correct. So, so I think it's worth exploring
at King Features, but yes, that might be too much red tape. We may have to go to a different
company that owns even worse comic strips. I think so. Like who owns Love Is or the Lock Horse.
Sure. The Lock, yes, exactly. So, so we're going to go through all, I'm going to go through all the
comic strips. Yes. And fit all the different companies. Yes, exactly. There's some downtime
when you're holding a baby and you're nursing a baby or the baby's gassy. So I will be going to
see who owns all of these things and finding at least something we've heard of that's the
cheapest thing we can get. And then we can do an official branded licensed event of some, maybe
this will take a year, take two years. Yeah. But I think it's worth investigating. It would be a lot
of fun. Is it like, yeah, is it like a, it's an experience that you walk through or like a, it's,
can we like collaborate with a food truck and turn the food truck branded for one night only?
I think that's very possible. I think it's very possible. I don't know that any food truck is
going to be wanting, want you thinking that their food causes zits, but you know,
the teens might like that. Yeah, sure. Um, it's also was brought on because somebody posted a
picture of the cereal that I ate when I was younger called morning funnies. Oh yeah. I vaguely remember
that. Do you remember morning? Oh, no, I don't. It had a lot of different, it had the Dennis the Menace,
high and lowest family circus, and something called Marvin, which looks to be a baby with a
full head of red hair and tiger, which is a comic strip. I kind of remember. And then it's also
adding that now Popeye, now they've added Popeye, Hagar, Hagar, the horrible and funky Winker bean.
Wow. So it was a comic strip cereal that was, I think our King feature syndicates.
I don't know whether the EC Seeger branded characters are owned by King feature syndicate
or if the cartoons are owned by one, the comics are owned by another. I've fallen into another,
syndicate. We, I know we want to stay away from syndicates. I'm a little worried about a syndicate
roughing me up. That's fine. I'm looking for the funniest names I can find. I feel like it's crew
because you keep saying funky Winker bean. And I think it's gotta be in that if the name isn't funny,
that's true. Then I don't think it's going to work. And I just clicked on a word I'd never seen
before called kudzu. Kudzu seems to be about it. Well, all I can see is a truck in it, but I think
there's characters. Anyone heard of kudzu? I think I have heard of kudzu. Oh, it could use a guy.
Nevermind. Kudzu was a 16 year old resident of bypass North Carolina. But the real star is
Reverend will be done. Oh yeah. Yeah. I've seen some of the characters are nasal T Lard bottom
item may wombat, uh, veranda, Tadsworth, and, uh, and what somebody's just called NASCAR dad. Um,
cuds, nothing much has happened with they CBS made a pilot of kudzu, but that was in 1983.
So I don't think it's too in demand. The creator of the strip was killed in a car crash
about 15 years ago and it hasn't ran in a strip since then. So I think that kudzu is not particularly
in demand and at least might be a starting one for if we want to, um, I mean, what else are,
you know, like, uh, put out some nasal T Lard bottom socks. Yeah, sure. And then, uh, or underwear
seat covers is our cute way of saying underpants. We just throw this stuff up on our T public site.
It's mainly the logo of our show, but we also sell merchandise of kudzu character nasal T
Lard bottom. And then like, we'll have like a narrative podcast with Jason playing nasal T
Lard bottom or something rich in IP hungry times, craven times. So maybe we can just get a blanket
license for like kudzu or something. This is how we learned that kudzu is like incredibly popular
in Hungary or very possible. So that's something that we'll investigate here. Um, and we'll have,
hopefully just have a breakdown of how much it would cost to blanket license some of this stuff.
Um, I think maybe another key component to success in this area. Uh, you know, look,
I'm looking at a picture of the cast of kudzu and some of them are just wearing like a white shirt,
uh, or blue and that's nothing wrong with that. However, what did Nathan do? He bought finely
tailored suits to a distinct color. So I think we need to find like a particular shade that you
would not usually see a suit of and, uh, so that we are like embodying nasal T Lard bottom.
Maybe with nasal, I don't know, maybe he's not a little bit if it's, if we have snot green suits.
Okay. All right. But it has to be all three of us. So it's going to be a bigger investment than
Nathan had to make. Right. Right. We all have to get a suit, but you spend money to make money.
Exactly. We're going to make so much money off of whatever this is. I think that's right. This is a
big money making endeavor and I'm very excited to start the journey. Yeah. All right. Well,
so to do list kudzu, uh, I'm sorry, nasal T Lard bottom green suits, assuming that he has, uh,
boogers sometimes. Uh, but mainly you got to look up universal, see if universal press syndicate
seems like a bunch of heavy. Okay. Sure. Sure. They might play ball with us knowing that they're just
letting kudzu money language. Right. Yes. It's, you know, look, there's, there's a lot of toy
companies, small toy companies are licensing, uh, um, and Popeyes a pretty big brand, but they're
still licensing pretty more, pretty obscure stuff, which can't be big money makers for these
corporations. Yeah. I don't think so. A small run of toys. I mean, they may make some money,
but that gives me hope that we can, we can do something here. Yeah. Yeah. I think so. Uh,
and, and who wouldn't to live the dream that Nathan Masri, his year at the top seems like
it was a great sane, normal, happy, and we want to do it. We want to do it too. Kudzu eats kudzu.
Which is just finding someone we know who can kind of make food. I don't know. Just make tater tots.
They could be, look, it's, it could be from the store. I don't care. Mary worth eats
just whatever, whatever it is. Doesn't even have to be a restaurant. Yeah. That's kudzu to Bose's,
uh, famous, uh, toaster waffles. No, we made those from scratch for straight from the farm.
Don't look to your left. Don't look at those piles of yellow,
I go boxes. Don't look to your left. No waste, no waste. That's, you know what? You go use them for,
put tissues in them. That's up to you. You do something with them. That waste is not ours.
And then when we can't get the rights, we'll just do it anyway.
That's really, that's what guys do. That's the guy spirit. Just do it. Um, well, I think we've
come to the end. Boy, oh boy. Uh, you survived podcast, the ride. Thank you so much for
subscribing to club three. And this is for everybody, but especially in this case to
Shane Cannon and Jeff Cole, your bravery saved the podcast. Well done. Freedom fighters. Thank
you. The club three. This is it's topics we wouldn't usually do. Look what you led us into
a six, a great business plan. Um, and we're going to learn a lot more maybe about great business
plans from Bob Iger, but maybe not yet. Spooky topics, please list them below poll coming soon.
Thanks for listening. Goodbye.