Crypt Three Welcome to haunt cast the fright club freak?
Club freak?
I pose to you guys that's a pitch could be yeah I was like why don't we sort this out just in the
you know club freak like me because it's in the same universe yeah yeah it is a little
applicable characters well imagine like the logo that we have and then it's spray painted over
with freak yeah that could be okay yeah yeah but that's a little middling the other pitch is club
eek exclamation point do you okay did you encounter the phrase streaks and foons
okay so could be club treak oh I don't know if they have the copyright of club treak we I'm very
excited about treaks and foons but we are now marrying ourselves to something very obscure
well look it's it's another island so it is adjacent but I'm sure it was going to come up
eventually well let me look I'm not sure either of those are uh home runs so if there's something
else if it occurs to you now or we have to keep I mean we got only like a day to figure this out
but club club three headed dog you would like the like from hell like a cerebus uh-huh yeah how
about that club three headed dog that was a kind that's good so enthusiastic about anything yet
no one's been that jacked well yeah you know we'll sleep on it that's interesting it's interesting
that the listener will know what it is and when we don't currently um and if we landed at one of
those then you know we threw in the towel or maybe you have better ideas uh well we'll figure it out
we're at club something and uh today we are discussing the topic island under siege
which is a it's a it's the marvel scare zone from islands of adventure I will get into that
right after this just just to say this poll the most nail biter yes of a poll there has been
by because often what's happened you know look we spelled out what to do with garfield eats we
pretty much said hey you know vote vote for it we you know we might have cranked the meters
yes hi didn't do any politicking for this one seemingly no no I don't think anybody had a super
a super dog a three-headed dog in the fight I mean I was very pleased with the results it certainly
seems like something I would suggest yeah absolutely uh uh and then I'm delighted because
it's a thing I've never heard of and that's always good to stumble on too because if we exhaust
everything that we know about already in the podcast but if we find out about new things
it can go forever and ever forever uh forever um this one this topic won by five votes wow
that's how low that's how close of a margin with a lot of it with the highest voter turnout yet
uh people really came through that percentage is going up and up but just let that be a lesson don't
say that voting doesn't matter if any if anyone ever tells you according to twitter it seems like
there's a lot of people walking up to randos on the street and saying voting doesn't matter and
then they keep walking so if that ever happens to you don't listen because every vote counts in this
I thought we were maybe heading to to run off here but uh it squeaked it out yeah no it's a good point
and yeah for sure vote in every club three poll that's the number one thing you should vote for
yes this nove and the next one is november that's true so this november vote look I know you and you
might end up exhausted from voting so I understand if you only want to vote for one thing and of
course we want that one thing to be the topic hershel walker oh okay well depending on where you
live of course no no all right if you're there get the vote out for hershel yeah for hersh but
will one of his secret children be the deciding vote in he just by like you know like based on
stats it seems very possible that we have one of his secret children in the audience it's entirely
the audience is growing and it's like oh we could see a repeat of kevin costner's swing vote is it
kevin costner starring griffin newman yes yeah starring griffin newman yeah wait no no no no
that's oh he's oh he's the one yelling at the I got the weird kevin costner movie run but you
all agree that's that seemed right right to me uh-huh no not swing vote draft day draft day I
just want to say I there's a little slogan to remember to vote vote uh vote in okay wait vote
in the ptr no matter who you are that's the wait let's punch that up uh vote for club three and
ptr no matter who you are you know vote blue no matter who vote in club three or like vote
vote in club three no matter who are the okay that's better that's better better better good
punch up that's how it works that's how good ideas get formed maybe some of these creative
juices will eventually be funneled to whatever we're calling this uh yeah or you well no we
know the name of the episode we don't know the name of the thing we don't know what the yeah well
we'll put our heads together because we have to because we don't have a lot of time so uh the
runner-up which barely lost spirit halloween yeah moves to next halloween yeah so we'll put a big
pin in that and now we head into november need you to vote this november and we go back to non
spooky topics unless you still got really good spooky ones sure in the hole in your pocket but
let's open it up to uh to anything and uh the returning fighter of course is suggested by
william evans is uh that we watch all of bob iger's master class now that is a um 12 hour
endeavor is that is it longer or less long uh not sure i can look it up while we some of those are
like four hours i feel like but i don't know okay i think it depends i think it depends how much
wisdom the uh person has to impart yeah so or how much other work they have to do right oh no no no
13 video lessons totaling two hours and 11 oh okay that's not so bad and you know what i will
make a club three promise that in this case i will not tap out at 38 minutes okay this i'm
because this i can learn from yeah i truly thought these were like i i guess i was too
naive i thought these were like great courses plus you know you can borrow those on a few apps for
free on like library lending apps these are scams oh okay that makes sense these are big scams yeah
where's somebody sits for two hours and just does an interview and they cut it up got it yeah that's
true if you yeah i guess you would know well we'll find out well we will one of the things we would
report is does iger ever change his shirt which might indicate that a second day was put in or
at least like a shower i it doesn't feel like it no way um so that's the one to beat but uh will it
win i don't know depends on what you guys suggest so uh keep comments suggestions coming in the
comments we appreciate everything's been great as evidenced by this where all these things were so
close uh monster cereals in there too that i was rooting for that one but we'll but it goes to the
crypt now paul and paul paul and got really betrayed i feel like jason threw it out and
yeah uh-huh it seemed like the you know we weren't nudging people that hard but right i'm interested
to know i mean there's a it looks like it's a good split between what people's interests are because
there's i i'm impressed that marvel won not that i know marvel's popular and we like marvel a lot
but but it's a very this is not the marvel of today right this is this is very much a different
era this is coming out of bankruptcy era marvel and like license like handshake well not handshake
contract but like not not fully watching the shop marvel like nowadays which is beautiful which is
happened potentially yeah so this is an era where a little more fun was being had a little more
random fun was being had obviously yes there's a reason uh maybe it didn't happen again is because
there was too much fun being had but we will address that license well yeah let's talk about
that later because i got some bones to pick with that oh that theory bones all right here just as
a way in let me read the full suggestion and this was suggested by eric b madden island under siege
the short-lived marvel superhero island scare zone that featured carnage and dead superheroes
yeah that is the an entry point and a nice synopsis um didn't know about it until now um basic stuff
about it 2002 yes was the year this is the first universal halloween horror nights
that was held in islands of adventure yes halloween horror nights 12 12 okay retroactively 12
uh i think if you go back to the early halloween horror nights like the first year or two it was a
pretty sparse affair okay and even this one if you got some of the video clips of it and stuff
they don't have all the ips yet you know there's a fear factor house on the other side of islands
of adventure but there's not like a halloween house and big horror weekend yeah big horror ips
yeah this it is but i'll say this the footage of it makes the whole thing seem creepier
oh yeah seems odder and weirder and not polished and feels like you might be more unnerved now it's
possibly it's also partly because of the vhs footage that exists this the small amount of
footage i should say but not a lot to work with here well do you guys know about the art of the
scare did you watch that i saw a comment some listener thank you led me to art of the scare
yes so this was a special for where and what i could not tell um i think it was traveled channel
okay and i think they filmed at islands of adventure at horror nights to that
20 2002 and then aired the special in 2003 okay i'll maybe promoting the next year which then was
also fully at islands of adventure that's there to clarify that that there were at this time it was
not both parks it was either or so for a couple years it went to fully islands of adventure and
then i think in 2004 there was enough uh interest in halloween horror nights that it was at both
places yeah and then eventually just back to the original universal park okay okay uh although that
and that's still how they there's nothing i believe so yeah i don't think there's anything at islands
of adventure well there's uh they have the death eaters the death eaters are there yeah um but yeah
so this was what is it 20 years ago already when we're discussing yeah it's the 20 year anniversary
of island 20 years ago i would have never stepped foot here that being said i didn't even know about
the marvel thing did you know about this at the time i did know about this from reading universal
message boards in college after the fact though after the fact because you were yeah i started
college what fall 2003 so after the fact i learned like oh holy shit there was a marvel
like haunt thing so my first question is would it have gotten you to go uh that may have gotten me
to go because i'm trying to think i think it would have gotten me to go but i'm not sure
i may have still been a chicken to do it would it get you to go now uh now i i think it would
you think it would i think it would you take would you take a flight would you go across the country
to go to this well that's a good question park podcast yeah i'd consider you would have to go
i feel like i would yeah but now they they just wouldn't no i know it's oh i mean yeah it's not
going to ever happen but i'm just i'm just trying to think of would this have like started you on
going to a haunt just because it's such an attractive like ip that you like yeah because
i i'm maybe i'm trying to figure out if i would have done it back then i don't i might have still
been too scared obviously right now i would be amazed it would be amazing to do it but
i'm just wondering if this would have gotten you into haunts 20 years ago well i don't know that
the walk-around characters at island of adventure wherever like a big uh uh selling point you know
yeah sure but i just it's such a fun crazy narrative it is a funny idea uh scott is there
an ip 20 years ago that would have gotten you into haunts what did you love 20 years ago was it uh
saturday night live if there was like uh like uh it's like wes anderson movies and punch
trunk love if there was a punch trunk love oh yeah themed yeah because i was new that year
so i would although well it wasn't i don't think it was out in october so it was in the fall yeah
it was in the fall year around then i feel november is what's in my head but i don't quite recall but
yeah if there was something uh if it was a simulation of uh the valley of north hollywood
around where i used to live a simulation of the the french restaurant and a used car lot and all
the ut and different utah brothers are jumping out at you and and threatening your car with crowbars
and saying they're gonna they're gonna hurt your girl yeah and then uh uh what does he smash the
like the back door or the glass door in the movie yeah like you'd have a well maybe there's some
like you know i feel like it's maybe a trope of mazes that you're like in the the head of one of
the great villains or even like the weekend it seemed like a weird like fever dream that the
weekend had so if you're yeah you're in barry egan's head and like seeing what causes the rage
fits and maybe going it oh that's another way to get a lot of characters in there you have people
playing the the many sisters that he has which causes him to to freak out and right yes the
dinner party you you go through the bathroom as he's beating it up yeah you get to be part and
maybe there's multiple barry egan's all beating up the bathroom um this would have gotten you to go
yeah yeah yeah yeah this or the royal dead and bombs the funny question i asked it as a funny
question but i do think there's like all there's like this is the butterfly effect you know you go
to like 20 years ago something that would have would have gotten you to go the butterfly effect
is the movie the butterfly yeah yeah it was that would be my uh top ip 20 years or me put uh how
about punch drunk love hate rising yeah that's good yeah so that would have done it um because
yeah this might have done it for me this marvel or a butterfly effect action yeah um uh well it's
fun to think about where we were at then and what would it because you need the more extreme
uh teen tastes i guess to yeah to get you in there and this is like this is appealing to a
pretty specific angle on marvel fandom this because there's like there's like uh i get you know i'm
not a big marvel person but there's like there are the materials for if you want like edgy
fucked up like there there is that sure there was in the comics at the time and this is playing
into that completely yeah this is right at the start of marvel max and the mature readers line
carthin is carthin is dirty nick fury book punisher is that when he started doing punisher
you know he did a marvel knights and then that switched to max okay where it could get dirtier
and violent her well i don't know that i've ever read them was it like r rated or was it like pg 13
it was like vertigo it was like dcs like there was like naked jessica jones and luke cage having sex
in the first issue of like nudity or yeah some nudity like butt uh yes it's heavily implied that
they have anal sex in the first issue really yeah heavily implied this was scandalous i this
at the time passed me by alias bendis right yeah yeah okay interesting bryan michael bendis uh
comic book writer yeah uh so okay this might be by the way with what just occurred this might be a
good time to tell you that something that was set up in an earlier episode in the dr doom episode
is still in effect the paper never left my garage oh yeah the fun fun fun facts if you don't
remember oh please yeah sure about no no i'm not doing it now i'm just saying uh that i i wanted
to come with protection you want to be prepared for situations like you don't want to use it
necessarily but if you don't remember what this was right and this is this will just be around in
the future that if there if marvel talk that i cannot penetrate um if i'm sorry to say penetrate
so soon after the anal sex reference uh but uh if i if i fill on the outside of i do have uh
10 beach boys facts okay that are uh not funny but i will i i will read one of no
uh choice but to deploy yeah yeah exactly yes great i also want to make it clear though when i
said but i just meant is there a picture of a but i didn't mean is there any else any well it was
such a perfect transition no you're right it's a one i want to be clear that that's not what i was
asking for i was just saying is there nudity yeah not sexual content anyway so yes they were
that happen in this and at the theme park did they pay tribute to the anal sex implication scene
is there any anal sex at island adventure i don't know that's a good question no it's not
question i don't answer to well i think the the real answer is the comics were more leaning
towards r-rated and this is still pretty pj 13 yeah now let me ask you this because
do i'm sensing now that you may not like this concept at all which concept really concept of
i'm asking jason because because there was a phrase in one of the wikipedia's that that said that
like you know this is obviously the kind of intense for kids or whatever and and i've said this
before the anecdote about jason seeing the first infinity war when half the superheroes are turned
to dust and he said i don't i didn't like it because all these kids are going to be so sad
i you you i i am not wild about it but not for that reason oh okay see interesting i sense this
because i somebody served up a marvel topic and jason's wild i love this i i think this is great
sorry i i'm not let me go back i do like this concept i'm not wild about the objection
to this concept oh okay so you do like so the opposite i misspoke yes oh okay no then you
then you like it i am into i really like this i'm into the uh i thought this would come later but
i'll say it now the objection to it from like somewhat at marvel's side some dummy at marvel's
side was like this is terrible we can't have this what if children see this the superheroes are dying
by 2002 marvel had pumped out so many storylines it was pat to do the the heroes are dead the
villains all won this is mere years after a story called onslaught where all the fantastic four
and avengers sacrifice themselves seemingly they die really they just go into a pocket universe
and then there was another story called legion quest where professor x's son goes back in time
to try to kill magneto in reality what happens is professor x dies this causes an apoc the age of
apocalypse to happen they never do it do they they never do something they never do it i was all
when i heard about the movies i was like whoa shit really they killed everybody like yeah but they of
course they didn't do it right they had around the time of a one-shot comic called the punisher kills
the marvel universe where he does that he does okay okay all right so great now we're talking
now see well now i'm coming from the perspective of i don't care about any of this
so kill everybody as far as i'm concerned sure so like a world where that's that's the deed that
like the we're on marvel superhero island and the heroes are no more and the villi so they're all
gone yeah yeah or like or they're you know they they like ran screaming they like they ran in fear
they're changing their names yeah um bloody captain america shield mounted oh god i saw a
headless spider-man body mentioned but i didn't see a picture of it but that's pretty funny
uh-huh i there's a uh like a wolverine corpse i i read uh that sounds right or impaled impaled
oh do we see a there's a there's not that many pictures because there's a couple videos and
they use some of the same footage and it's like maybe there's like a like a beaten up dr strange
walking around whoa or like a she hulk that's like kind of like looking like she hulks i think
yeah that was she hulk right yeah walking around with a gun she looks yeah like really like she's
seen some shit at this point uh yeah but yeah there was yeah was i like thor's hammer is like
everything's bloody shield uh bloody thor's hammer bloody iron man's helmet bloody because
they're all dead they've been killed stanley sweaters bloody uh-huh uh-huh broken glasses
broken like orange aviators you know red mustache hairs yeah really uh really disturbing stuff um
so well we haven't even said i mean like if you feel comfortable talking about this one there's a
i mean you probably i'll just say it there's a neon sign for one of the restaurants that i think
typically says dine but they didn't light up the n it says die it says diner it's the captain
america diner diner okay i'm sorry diner all right diner well and they turned off the r2 clearly die
it says it's the same gag as mel's diner becomes die okay they love this gag it's a good one yeah
it is a good gag yeah it's easy yeah it's good well it's fun to think about a hero uh you know
you guys know i don't know but just you know or i'm sorry about a villain walking around going like
okay we gotta fix this place up all right oh you know we should do you know what we gotta do
look at the size of diner here look at that okay just like with your fingers cover up the
end and cover up the r guys mephisto bullseye magneto come here come here look at this perfect
perfect because that is carnage is in charge of everything carnage is in charge and carnage is
like venom but worse crazier yeah venom well yeah explain that relationship to me as i don't know
about this venom have you seen the venom films no okay do you know venom he's uh uh i know the
rap song about him the best is a great song uh great song uh so there's a symbiote which is an
alien life form uh and and when it's the comic the first story is that it like attaches itself to
spider-man it turns his costume black he starts to feel bad and like evil or whatever and then
it jumps off and it jumps onto eddie brock and that guy turns into venom but it's the same type
of symbiote that like attaches itself to cletus cassidy who's a complete psychopath a serial
killer serial killer okay so he's like and even like eddie brock is like a bad guy but not like
so bad his nickname is the lethal protector yeah there's like times when he's good there's times
when he's bad there's different people who had this the venom symbiote uh but cletus
cassidy carnage is a crazy madman fully only bad or if yeah so they've made him the main guy who's
in charge of all the signs at islands of adventure he is in charge of making all make sure all the
signs are clever and uh halloweenified well it's nice that he keeps up the theme park tradition of
yeah yeah clever wordplay does carnage speak or does he just growl he speaks yeah he speaks
i actually i will admit i have not seen uh venom 2 where he is played by woody harrelson oh that's
who okay i might like that i tend to always like woody harrelson sure i mean he's great he's in
everything i mean he's he's out of hand in every uh universe at this point maybe one maybe the
only actor where i get excited if he's added to a franchise like the like planet of the apes
hunger games uh well i still now that still didn't get me but if i end you know hey next
time i want to play i will i will try to watch every woody harrelson movie available on planes
at least uh and then you know what you also got to do watch this club random uh anyway moving on
yeah so so carnage is like he's up in like uh what would you call it cherry picker he's not a cherry
picker but it's sort of that vibe but like here i am i'm he's like mickey uh conducting uh like
the water fountain or something and like in a cherry picker in a cherry picker like in the
epcot yeah yeah so uh yeah he's like kind of shouting directions and controlling traffic
from up there he's he's activating the fog yes which is firing off a lot of fog yeah so uh uh
just looking at the vhs footage of all of it with the fog directing the chain link put the
chain link fence there put the barrels there put the burnt cop cars there and it's not so well
lit in these few videos i've seen too where like you go to horror nights now the whole thing is
lit well the music is loud and it's like scary but it's kind of not it's kind of a party atmosphere
i don't know watching these videos to me there i felt more unnerved because it felt closer to
being like oh something's wrong at the park yeah like there is like a bunch of fires that were set
and it doesn't it didn't feel so polished which makes the whole thing feel more unnerving to me
i wasn't there but that's the vibe i'm getting from the footage yeah yeah yeah i think especially
the footage of the house on the island which is called maximum carnage right which was like a 90s
storyline and video game and video game yeah and uh it is unnerving because it's just a lot of like
seems like they're using the dr doom or the spider-man overflow queue and it's a lot of
you know those pneumatic drills they have that they just put on scrap metal and waterfall effects
and uh lighting effects and people dressed as like nuclear mutants or uh henchmen
so it's just kind of a little more chaotic yes it's not it's it's watching the actual maze itself
because i guess we could take a step back real quick is that there was they were trying they
they had it like an overarching theme narrative to the horror nights of the time yes oh yes right
but they had two yes it's kind of yes so initially it was a little girl everything in the same way
that starlight express is taking place on like a little boy's head oh yeah they had this narrative
of a original character named cindy of a little girl and all the different areas of islands of
adventure all the different haunts were like visions she was having in her head is that right
uh yeah that was like her toys and her play things wreaking havoc right but the wiki says
that there were a lot of child abductions at the time and they decided to change this character
into uh what the care the caretaker caretaker yeah uh uh hhn legacy says unfortunately a slew of
child abductions within central the central florida area caused universal to scrap the idea of cindy
and create the character of the caretaker out of her father paul bearer yes which is also a
wrestling man it had been for yeah 12 years yeah it's crazy there was so many florida abductions
matt gates wasn't even around yet oh yes i mean he was around but we don't know where he was
so they had like yeah so they they had tied all the ip to these this original lore this universal
lore so there was like a a seuss they didn't have a maze yeah they did like fog up the seuss area
and turn off all the rides and it was called oh it's uh boo what is it booville thank you
yes this is where to be this is where i got excited because i was a little like
it's a marvel thing is this interesting and then like starting for the special that you mentioned
jay's weight that's already the scare is the special yeah uh because they take you through
they show the map at the beginning and very seriously say all the but to seuss landing
becomes booville port of entry is now port of evil um something's called scary tales
yeah which one is that oh is that the lost continent yeah maybe yeah i don't know what
to do with that one so that becomes scary fairy tales that had nightmare it did was what's that
become an icon i think would come back ah they were like what's nightmare what is he oh sorry
he's just a creepy uh like demon guy okay you know i i am interested in the horror night's lore
you know you got the caretaker you got the director you know you got nightmare and fear they're
different sure i don't know any of this but we will that seem people seem to want to hear but that
so we'll figure that out we'll know i think i'm more interested in diving into all of that stuff
than actually going to horror nights while you're going next year okay we'll see
there's gonna be a smile house people smiling yeah there'll be a lot of smiles they're gonna do like
five on five off because everyone's faces are clenching because they're smiling so much is there
a strain of weed that you know of that would not make you anxious and would make you so chilled out
that you would be like just laughing your way through the whole night oh i don't know you'd
probably want an indica strain for that all right but that would probably just make me sleepy so
well if you can get through a couple houses before you go to bed that's true yeah you know although
i didn't make it through the monsters that's true and you that was you that was a strain that was
an edible though oh yeah you can't do an edible before this too potent okay this fear might be the
real fear might be that he just doesn't just falls asleep in one of the maze in the us house
right that's like a very cozy room yeah yeah yeah and like the exorcist he falls asleep next to the
what's-her-name linda blare linda blare look alike some people walking in there's just a man
sleeping while there's a puppet vomiting puppet vomiting that's so creepy it's just the still
animatronic just a mannequin there it's a nice change of pace from my childhood where i would be
the one up at night vomiting i was a pukey kid what are you gonna do which horror look people out
there have been every horror nights for 20 years which house which classic horror nights house would
you want jason to take a nap in that's my question to you oh yeah if you know the full way of the
land because there's been there's plenty of iconic beds in in 20 plus 30 years of horror nights so
like i said i was very intrigued by this house when i first learned about in college
but in the last couple years i got really interested in the haunt they did walking around
the floor of the mummy ride oh on the tr- whoa on the ground like with the track above you
that's pretty crazy it might have been the floor of kong whatever it was the ground's gotta get
you're probably not totally clear of mummy although maybe i don't know i don't know
i forget which one it might have been kong and you saw some of the city it seems so dangerous to me
there's so much universal horror night stuff i'm not aware of and i feel like it's not even that
well preserved yeah yeah because like this thing this thing you would think there would be so much
maybe people just didn't and it was an awkward era for there's not a lot of internet and people
don't have cameras is readily available and then low light for sure not um even just doing a history
of horror night seems good like it seems like we could get we could get uh three plus hours yeah
content the uh pictures make it seem very blair witch like taking like the old transition from
film camera to digital camera yes sure early digital camera yeah it may add to the creepiness
of it a little bit would you sleep in one of those killer clown like kind of pod things that they put
people in like they trap them in those kind of big balloon maybe i don't know anything about that
okay well they they sort of like have these we're killers in it a bullet yeah that's true
they like kidnap people and they put them in these big like hanging cotton candy
oh sort of sacks it kind of said oh and i kind of like that it looks like a babeson chair but a killer
pod isn't gonna be good well but i forget it's not really that so okay so yeah you could take a nap
in one of those um i guess a simula yeah wait because like the the pods in the matrix are very
scary i don't want to be in one for real but maybe a simulated one you could get a nice nap in yeah
please as long as i don't have to have wires in my head yeah exactly so so there's a lot of options
yeah um if you want to talk about like inventiveness and like oh they use that area for a
for a maze the special kind of goes into a jurassic park one oh yeah yeah this is what's
interesting about this year is what they're figuring out well how do we do a horror version
of marvel and of sue subuville sure nailed it uh but jurassic park what do we do and they used the
walkthrough attraction triceratops encounter where and and had to make use of like
basically that is like going to see a very gentle uh not i forget if sleeping but like kind of
docile yeah word um you know it's a very serene kind of little attraction so how do you turn that
horror it is very like twisting and winding so i guess i'm like oh that makes a lot of sense
but they had to turn it into a scenario where there's an evil there's a bad genetics lab guy
dr burton and dr burton's doing some bad experiments and they just by hiding some
stuff in shadows and blood and flashes and then there's an impaled or like a uh a hung up
uh dr bird decapitated dr burden or something uh um and it's and then they get they made another
triceratops they made a triceratops head that was fully ripped off with a bloody spinal cord
that's coming out of it yeah isn't that's kind of crazy you talk about i mean the thing we're
talking about marvel is like oh something that's kind of darker than the franchise at large
that's there's nothing that fucked up in a jurassic park that's kind of crazy so i i'm like oh this is
a this is kind of a bold situation and yeah these uh the people putting this thing together thinking
outside of the box yeah it's they're experimenting obviously because they pulled it all back
pretty quickly a little bit the one thing you can like you can murder and you can maim but you cannot
mess with intellectual property that's really the lesson here uh because yeah marvel now at
avengers campus they are doing at least doing stuff like you can see the zombie captain america
and werewolf by night is out which is a little short that michael giacchino just directed oh uh
which is like pretty we watched it kind of fun and man spoiler alert man things in it who's like
yeah swamp thing for marvel okay uh basically he's cute he is cute uh that's true so cute he's funny
uh so yeah but they're not gonna they're not gonna go nuts yeah yeah yeah this is a it's a nuts time
and then there's there's one more if we're talking about the lay of the land and the best phrase to
hear said by the the creepy voiced narrator of art of the scare which is the boy i was excited when
i heard the aforementioned phrase treaks and food this is what they did to tune lagoon which is the
home of our king features syndicates pals right from dudley do right and popeye that's pretty
specific to what the hell do you do we have to make a scary zone but also you'll see dudley do
right there and i i can't say i know exactly what they did but they've used the phrase treaks and
foons which i guess is freaks and tunes mixed up they're kind of like killer clowns they're
kind of bouncing freakish things that's what it is the treaks they were like original characters
original characters but i think we're burying the lead they pump the land full of foam foam party
foam an upsetting amount of foam that you have to walk through pretty much to get
to jurassic park unless you go counterclockwise uh from port of entry like a real sicko you and i have
been in a play we had to walk through foam a couple years ago we ended up at the end of a foam party
yeah in a bar that was not far from where i used to live yeah um and you got like lost in the foam
at one point and we went we went out on the patio yes there was a full foam party happening with like
naked like semi-naked people happening in a bar down the street and you had to go through it
no we didn't want to get to the bathroom you did wait but why were you there to begin with i mean
if the answer is you were there to go to the party that makes sense we were not it was the only bar
open till last call it was memorial day weekend like seven years ago and there was a play was it
called michaels no uh and mj mj's maybe yeah it was across the street from the gelsens which used
to be the disney studios and we said was there anything open and somebody said oh there's mj's
it's a gay bar oh but it's the only thing and we go oh yeah let's go over there so we went over there
and it was not just a bar it was a rave happening there were men in their underwear in a foam party
and i was like this is happening right like it's not the like the street where you would assume
big parties like that are happening sure so we were like okay well we're not prepared markets yes
i am not in the shape to have to strip all my clothes off and have a foam part didn't feel in
foam shape at the time i was not if all the bartenders were fucking jacked i remember we
gave them some money like they would just slap it on their chests to stick the dollar bills there
and we were like well let's let's just sit on the terrace i mean we were the five or six of us none
of us prepared to a party in foam and it was a cold spring it was a cold spring it was not in
the weather to be getting in the mix a novel phrase is the beginning of a novel you kind of had to go
through the phone to get to the bathroom which we all went to once and i remember jason disapproved
through the phone and i told turn to the everybody else who was with us and i went we're never seeing
him again he's gonna get lost in the foam i the bathroom i got lost because i was reading there
was a printout much like your printout of beach boys facts there was a sign on the door of the
regulations for the bathroom which were all different ways of saying please do not have sex
in the bathroom yeah and everyone in the bathroom they were everyone was really nice but they were
everyone's in their underwear and they were like why aren't you in the phone like what are you
doing man and i was like look i didn't know we didn't know we didn't know i'm not in the shape
i'm not in the shape to do this we got here 10 minutes before last call we just want to drink
a single newcastle each and leave i'm not against get foamy you only drink if you're foamy i was not
against the part i always wanted to go to a foam party in college i never did it never seemed to
come up um but i was you love your big douchey parties and you haven't been to a foam party
never went to a foam party in college and yes i was wildly i did i went to one really rito
rosarito which one is it really were you sure great town i don't believe no i don't believe
it was required or uh it was uh very bad and it stung my eyes oh okay you're not missing out on
much i went to one as he uh had died down so everything was just kind of clammy and soapy
like everyone was like oh that was fun but we didn't buy enough detergent like someone had
just covered an apartment in tarps oh wow that does not seem like a good usually don't you get
like a warehouse for that yeah you probably should yeah so but anyway so we've learned that the time
to go to a foam party is not the very end nothing in both cases this place maybe not in where i went
in mexico so that your eyes don't sting yeah there's nothing sexy about that yeah yeah
up higher quality foam won't sting your eyes um but yeah then this place closed down the street
and it was replaced by a place that had a bunch of like bad reports of like people drugging drinks
and stuff which might still be there primarily known uh among our friends is like oh don't go
there people keep getting roofied yeah so that's uh they're not doing foam parties i can't even
remember the name is very stupid and i can't remember it so anyway don't go in don't go
anywhere with a stupid name anyway treaks and foons treaks and foons so they're a bunch of weird
little bouncing freaks treaks and foons bouncing around i saw them giving people hugs in the foam
they were popping out of the foam and scaring people do you think that they there was a clear
delineation between what is a phone and what is a tree there was i know what it is i i think they
said in the special they said what makes one is one boys and one girl yeah one is male one is female
wow why what it's so interesting because like why didn't they just do the same gimmick in
tomb lagoon all the good guys are dead and it's the best oh bluto and snow and snidely whiplash
and like uh and uh and kathy's enemy ice cream ice cream is alive uh and what the the wife lock
horn is alive because she's the villain of that strip right i hate this there's a lot i don't know
man lock horn hate his wife jason is that the gimmick of that they hate each other okay so
maybe they're both dead the undead lock horns yeah the um the the the kid from family circus is uh
dead they're all dead and there's just the there's like a little like sprite that one of them could
see they told him to do or like tisk tisk them i don't know the name offhand put that in the
comments but not as a suggestion for an episode i don't think that's strong enough unless it is
maybe i might be strong enough yeah it could be uh so yeah so like that i'm wondering why they
didn't even go that way because it feels like people would be even less precious about those
characters but i guess it doesn't maybe thematically make sense king feature syndicate
might have been in better financial shape than marvel at that oh for sure at that point yeah
that's true so maybe they had more sway maybe they maybe they were presented with an idea like that
yeah it was they spelled it with an i it was king features syndicate right and they just for this
event they replaced that marmaduke photo op where you're holding on to the leash and they like a dog
skeleton was put in the marmaduke oh i thought you were gonna say they turned it around and he was
running right at you running like through you or biting you yeah killing you who's marmaduke's enemy
an empty bowl i mean for sure that is was there a bad was there a villain in the mar is there a
villain in marmaduke it's a good question i don't know the seems like it'd be like a real estate
developer maybe or like the dog catcher did uh uh did nancy nancy had enemies but was there a main
nancy enemy uh in the current run of nancy she has like a rival okay so a very studious rival
gotcha did in the like in the 40s did they all was hitler all their villain in the strips i guess
so yeah i mean and fritzy kind of has an antagonistic real yeah but she loves and fritzy
and nancy she does they do love each other but she's not a true villain yeah um i just passed by i
went oh what's marmaduke walker duel and then it turns out that was something from the civil war
okay all right it's not i'm so i'm no longer interested no boring real life snooze all right
but we've done this full circle around uh the islands was it the islands of fear
uh was that the larger i think the bigger name was islands of fear yeah like that um there's
there's one thing to say about it yeah about this the special really quick before we get back to
marvel because my favorite thing from the special has nothing to do with any of the specific mazes
it's like a general thing for about like maze craft and this is just a little behind the scenes
tidbit that i found interesting scenic pieces play a major role but how do they keep all the
visitors from fingering the props stop that really quick how do they and they're showing the visuals
there by the way or it is like a it's a disembodied hand though do they still yeah fingering that was
that afraid that word was used to mean steal for more right at a certain point like just i don't
know that the shift happened post 2002 i think people were talking about we were we were not
no right we do not have fingering on the brain we don't mean that we were worried props were
getting stolen from our favorite theme parks anyway how do you stop the guests from fingering
oh simple smear them with the gooeyest concoction you can find petroleum jelly
want to prevent fingerings better get yourself some petroleum jelly that's a good just in general
if you don't want anything to get uh uh stolen just cover it in petroleum jelly are you worried
about a rough spade of fingerings if you lube up with jelly pocket pick you know you want to
prevent a pick pocket from picking your pocket just a jelly up your wallet lube in there lube
up your big wallet they're not going to be able to get grasps on anything nothing a pocket full of
jelly this special uh i really like this special uh in the sense it's it's very dry but it's a guy
doing that voice for 48 minutes well that bird wasn't so dry thanks to all the lube all the lube
my other favorite thing about that special is the uh editor in chief of haunted attraction magazine
who appears to be named lennard pickle cool that was a good yeah kind of an unfortunate uh pause
that i showed them um lennard pickle seems fine but he you'd think he'd be very excited being on
television um but he's more of a just the facts man he's like they're all so stressed about with
fingerings yeah focus they go well we got a whole month of fingerings ahead of us the rat lady's
pretty enthusiastic she's pretty chill about it all yeah you get to see a rat lady she actually
is in a little bed uh little glass coffin with a bunch of rats yeah she's very casual yeah they
get in little spats sometimes but it seems pretty domesticated yeah yeah they used to use when we
were at nots they said that they had some they did some weird rat stuff back in the day but then like
people were upset by that so yeah well this as we talked about the animal actor stage like the
the theme park turn away from using animals unnecessarily i think that's kind of a later
2000s thing yeah so in this day and age the rats were running wild um but not on her rat lady was
okay but so yeah that's look there was a lot going on this is a good excuse to get a general lay of
land of 2002 of islands of fear but the most fun thing seemingly is this topsy turvy superhero
dead world yes yeah i think for sure yeah they were having the most fun with this even though
there's still stuff where you go like oh i there's so much more they could have done but for the time
it feels like they were really like swinging for the fences yeah and i want to get it let let's get
into that can we talk about the villains that were used sure they're walking around i mean carnage we
mentioned he was the big one his big bad guy a pretty popular character 90s character 90s character
used a lot over the years comes back a lot um and then the other name uh well i guess the other big
one was the cat in america uh villain crossbones who was played by frank grillo in the movies the
the current movie not in the parks not in the parks no uh played by what looks like a very
gaunt man and then a whole bunch of other guys they had a bunch of crossbones walking around
with chainsaws they were the chainsaw guys we're looking at like seven of them some of these guys
look perfectly cast like they are jacked yeah they look like they worked at that bar that jason and
i went with the phone party yeah those guys are in good shape good shape um crossbones pretty easy
costume to do like a tank top with bones on it and a skeleton mask the other big character i saw
mentioned was craven the hunter this is a spider-man villain um scott just from the song i know him
he's from the david larry performance if you'll remember he's like kind of a big burly guy here's
here's one drawing he's kind of bane-esque kind of bane he's a hunter he likes to hunt
game and man the most dangerous game the most dangerous game of course um this is what he looked
like at islands uh of fear uh he had frosted tips and he was real lean oh yeah yes click on it real
quick oh sorry just zoom in yeah the the most popular craven story is one in which he kills
himself is that what i have never read that craven's last time he's like he's not around
anymore i don't think they did that on the island of adventure but it's craven's last the other
villains try to stop him let him know that the way we love you no uh but yeah that's that's an old
story um yeah he's old his time yeah so uh uh i guess 1987 is when the story is from yeah he did
not have frosted tips in that story 2002 you know no wonder he killed himself geez
now he looks cool yeah yeah yeah um so yeah so so it's an interesting mix because they would have
different they had different villains inside the maze and different villains roaming around
yeah but there's no and then there was like i i think early on there were plans of like and this
film's going to take over this ride and this film's going to take over this ride but it doesn't
seem like they got very far right because it would make sense for the hulk an incredible hulk coaster
to like to be taken over by the abomination which is one of his main villains yes or the leader or
the leader tim blake nelson's character who's going to return in captain america 4 i believe
something like that for the norton hulk has this character and now we're getting norton hulk stuff
in you know we're in the ruffalo and we're gonna have to have a hulk we're gonna have to have a
spider-man with the hulks with banna norton and ruffalo and uh mizlani yeah you know it's interesting
there's a real life villain who maybe bears mentioning oh no he's from uh and i'm speaking
of course of murray wilson the uh brian's abusive father is also the manager of the group uh you know
it's interesting it's fun fun fun that brian wilson's first number one hit wasn't recorded
by the beach boys it was surf city by jan and dean and murray the abusive father was irate that
brian gave away their first number one hit to another group and he called jan barry a record
pirate a record pirate record pirate that's no yeah that's that's quite a slight you wouldn't
want to see any of those walking around islands of fear who is scarier brian wilson's father or the
leader who i don't know let's tell the audience decide what let's just square them off what do
we know about the leader uh he's got a big brain uh jason what help me out with the leader at a
false eye leader has his eyes okay let's see the leader is very intelligent the gamma radiation
made him super smart in the way that it made banner super strong he's very smart too he put
out his own record the many moods of murray wilson and he loved to tell brian hey brian i'm a genius
too okay so they're pretty evenly matched so far this the leader looks like this he has a big head
yeah well that's scarier murray well but is it scarier that just a plain man like murray wilson
could be such an abusive monster that's you might know what's coming for you from the leader that's
true you know if we're talking about gamma radiation we should mention the storyline old man logan
similarly the villains won all the heroes except like hawkeye and wolverine are dead
for the most part um and there's a bunch of inbred hulks that control a part of the country right um
that storyline would go on to inspire the movie logan nominated for oscars that's true some
inbred hulk are they so are they dumber than yeah they're dumber and yeah i would probably
like old man logan i bet this sounds good it's fucking weird and gross yeah here's the one big
cover of it okay i don't see any inbred hulks on there no that's what i want to see they're kind
of in the corner they're these weird little guys in the corner oh i see are they little no it's just
an interpretation they're little well because that's a way that a hulk could be inbred is it
end up very small instead of very big uh it's a yeah it's it's fun it's got some shock humor
you might or shock uh violence as well okay i won't spoil it i mean you're not gonna
wolverine gets mind controlled by mysterio and accidentally kills all the x-men he thinks he's
killing like villains but then like the mind his mind like it's clear and he realizes he just
killed all the x-men wow and then he swore to like like never pop his claws again wow
and they kill you kill him for real yes in this story yeah it's else worlds and whatever what i
want i want permanence to these deaths mysterio also the big villain in kevin smith's daredevil
arc from the right around this time period okay so there you go you're not going to the facts now
after you get hit with something like that well you have kevin smith no fun fun fun facts after
this i have had attention sorry if i spoiled that uh 20 plus year old uh story line for anyone 15
year old story at this point yeah i spoiled some of the story of the film love and mercy
uh well spoilers abound on club three uh but yeah there's other villains in the maze
and one of them i'm really excited about uh do you have the list of them here because i'm really
tell i was having there was kind of a red skull is that right uh yeah let me just find the thing
here because my i just got a weird google ad that took over the webpage i had loaded
oh wait here this is just a sub fact to fill the time brian wilson played the teacher mr
hawthorne on the new leave it to beaver in 1988 well i'd love that that's have you ever seen that
no i haven't he acts he has to do how is it it's so bad yeah yeah now listen to me mr huskull you do
not pass notes in my class as a man not meant to act yeah uh so here we go so the scare actors
they've listed here they have uh uh just chainsaw henchmen vermin they have toad listed
okay zorn listed really yes wait no that can't be accurate that's what it says yeah okay that would
be accurate i guess so zorn has like been both good and bad he's been used the most during
grant morrison's uh new x-men yeah um and zorn again i think i've spoiler alerted zorn on this
podcast before but in case i haven't zorn is uh actually in that run he's raising a human kid and
he's a cartoon and sheryl hinds says no no problems with him uh uh zorn is magneto in disguise in
disguise the whole time oh so people don't know that i don't know that there was a reveal in this
maze but i'm a big fan of the zorn character and reveal that's a deep pull right this is why it's
exciting they did not have magneto they did not have kingpin right there's a list hold on
dr doom was right there yes um but then one was which makes it better because if you're a comic
book fan it's a creepy design kind of a weird design yeah he's got kind of a skull head um
yeah but yeah they had uh electro uh mephisto not mr mechphisto bono's character this is mephisto
the devil is a devil in marvel universe kind of walking around the scare zone too
walking around he was just walking around oh would you be more afraid of the marvel universe
devil or bono's mr mechphisto from the zoo tv i don't know i don't know enough about the other
i mean somebody with the ability to take over your tv feed because bono is the devil too they're both
the devil mr mechphisto is the devil if you're if you're if you hear fisto then you might be
dealing with a barely disguised devil right it's not kit and it's not the door's character kit
fisto not the devil not the devil so not all the stows are devils not all fistos are devils um
this mephisto and mechphisto this uh wiki says the punisher was there oh yeah okay and also guy with
overalls with wearing overalls with a gun scary character that's a real world villain there's an
infinite amount of those the punisher i think i was watching one of the videos and they said the
punisher was like under some mind control so he was like firing at people with his gun uh they also
supposedly had i think they scrapped the idea that there would be snipers on the roofs of this uh and
but apparently in the maze there were laser pointers to make you feel like you were in sites
of characters which is very scary that's really scary uh so they were doing some intense things
i would say that they don't do i haven't seen them do that more psychologically scary a little bit
yeah there was a tunnel with like holes in it they do this trick still where you walk through
something that's like a like a cylinder that rotates yeah that looks cool that's very
unset that's like something from a corn video yes yes it is i don't even mean that's like an insult
the corn videos were very well done freak on a leash yeah where there's holes in the
yeah that but spinning yeah was the video was the jonathan davis video with the chris angel
uh vegas show was it as good as free connelly i don't think it was but it was still similar
i don't now i don't i this sounds vaguely familiar but you saw the original i know you've obviously
seen the new the new um chris angel show but did you see the one prior to that yeah i do look
i'm pretty a mystic of fog that's it's hard to keep when he's clearly topped the previous show
there is a i don't remember no jonathan davis i remember getting blasted with trash okay fair enough
but jonathan davis does do the music for mine his regular mind freak show and i think there is a
music video component uh as well but it's not yeah it's not on the level of the iconic freak
on the leash video so yes there is a freak on the leash style uh thing happening in this maximum
carnage maze cool um but i'll say this just from looking at the video the actual um like
location that you're being put placed into is not that specific in the house no that if i had a
punch up it would be that like give me some more marvel like iconography in the actual maze because
the maze just seems like it's a bunch of chain link fences and like walls and it i was watching
the special and i lost track of that this was the marvel one yes so that tells you it is so not
specific right so it never because this is we know this will never happen again there will never be a
scary marvel or at least not a fully murderous thing like this yeah um so if this was their
chance it does not necessarily give you the full like herbal fun house it would have been awesome
i mean i know they couldn't have done this and kept putting like kept putting it back each night
but like if they had taken the cue of spider-man which is the daily bugle office like and fucked
that up and made that scary that'd be awesome i don't know like cletus i don't know do cletus
have a famous villains layer that i'm forgetting even just something that like they made up some
sort of industrial thing that like felt specific or like a villain's i don't know something specific
to him it well he just feels like some of these costumes are like kind of done generically and on
the cheap compared to like the caretaker or nightmare which were like very intensive
makeup and costuming right yes so like even just something that was a little bit less
fence based little like less fence wire fence based what's look in music videos uh from then
and ever since what is scarier than a chain link fence that's a good point you put it in front
behind the performer and it's a little scary you put it in between the performer and the camera
it's true it's very unsettling very unsettling yeah so yeah i guess look there could have been
some fences but it didn't have to be all of them like it didn't have to be don't rely on fan if
they don't make fences your when you have scary villains at your disposal yeah so but maybe the
budget wasn't that high you know so i would say definitely the budget cheap yeah but it's a bummer
that it like that them doing this coincided with the budget maybe not being as high as it is now
for horror nights and for for uh marvel things we see great iterations of these costumes now that
disney is doing it yeah back in these days um the werewolf by night did you see what i'm talking
there's werewolf he's like on top of avengers uh i haven't seen whatever it is they did like a little
like patch of something up in top and there's like full moon and there's a guy dressed as a werewolf
and like he's howling and you're like yeah pretty good yeah like things are cool yes you want like
this little this little carriage of parades um i do want to know though like what level was the
person from marvel going like we're mad you can't do this again like well it's kind of like a vp or
a licensing person like because writers and editors wouldn't give a shit you know yeah they'd like this
probably yeah who knows and also this is very unofficial all these like halloween horror nights
things are not so officially they feel like in general the story seems to be marvel got mad you
can't show kids dead superheroes don't do this again but there's no real source on that no doubt
that happened but it's so vague but it didn't happen again and seuss i don't think they ever
did anything near halloween again yeah but they yeah it feels like the whole thing the whole
concept of this sort of went away pretty quickly so yeah it's weird because you would think they
would have had to like somebody a marvel would have known what they were doing yeah so that's
it seems suspicious to me that it's as simple as just like you're going to scare the kids
versus marvel saying like it would make more sense to me where marvel said oh it's cool that you're
doing something at horror nights just let us approve what it is because like just doing villains
night at islands of adventure would be cool just say yeah this okay the difference is you can't
say the captain murk is dead you know what i mean like that's why that's that seems like a simple
explanation for why it didn't happen it took over but the heroes will return villains take over i
do think does that shit all the time yeah yes so i don't know it seems simplistic as far as a
reason maybe it's true but it feels like uh this is the reason somebody said no don't do this anymore
yeah so so they did keep doing stuff in this they still used it as a scare zone the next year but
the marvel affiliation was gone it then in 20 2003 it was known as toxic city and if we don't have
all these villains to use how do we fill the space and the answer was foam the aforementioned here we
go from shrieks and shrieks and foons became all right let's move that foam over here and the idea
is toxic city you are in a toxic city and this is toxic foam and some of it is green foam so aware of
the uh the green foam that's spewing everywhere it creepily says you've broken quarantine and
entered a city plunged into a biohazard nightmare uh i don't have to read all of this copy um it
says can you escape this biohazard nightmare or will the toxic avengers get to you first
but is it then is it the toxic no but it sounds so why are you the toxic avenger because that'd be
awesome yeah i said don't use the word avengers if you don't have that yeah copyright or yeah or the
toxic avenger which is a movie and a cartoon yeah great toys really detailed toys the playmates
there the playmates made them and they very much fit directly with the playmates turtles at the
time did you ever know that makes sense i remember it more as a toy thing yeah knowing what the actual
property was yeah me too that and bucky o'hare i remember the toys more than anything completely
the bucky o'hare gang could sit next to the turtles no problem yeah yeah they had a very hard to find
arcade cabinet every now and then we'd be on vacation i'd find the bucky o'hare cabinet
somewhere and i'd get so excited say well mom dad this is where i am for the next five days
this is where i am but you're like me i had the nintendo game i had all the comics and i had all
the toys and now i have the newer toys of turtles and i have a perfect layer oh bucky o'hare okay
i so uh you know they try to do something else here but they lost the moral thing i don't think
toxic nobody's telling us to do an episode about toxic city um so it didn't have the same the the
boldness of killing beloved superheroes ironic because there are like a million toxic based
heroes and villains i feel like in marvel yeah but they don't want any part of it by now so when the
sun goes down you lose the license this would be disney's dream of how it could play out i think
they would bite on that it's okay we at night you get to have marvel at disney world great done can
do great works for me sure we'll buy we'll buy the rest out somehow they've been doing like at the
at the oogie boogie bash in disneyland they do little excuse me they do like a challenge trail
they turn it into like foggy thing with some villains i forget what it's called i feel like
there's not enough room for them to even do anything at disneyland right now no you like
a fun i was there the day an oogie boogie bash was starting and it's very funny how they can't
tell you to get the fuck out but they're kind of telling you you have to leave right like we were
eating an ice cream bar and next to the starbucks and they let jane go in for napkins but someone
went in to try and buy coffee and they're like uh uh no you don't have you don't have a badge you
can't go in you know they got to do that yeah with every like horror nights in the regular park goers
too yeah i had two manhattans and i thought i could outsmart it but with no plan i was like here i know
let's just you me and the child let's just walk into the park confidently immediately oh badges
okay never mind bye oh so you weren't even in the park to begin with oh we were in the park we just
like like what if we try to stay i'm sure no one's ever thought of that before we took our time and
it was fun to hear the music change over it was fun to see some people had very good costumes
when we had left the grand california and people were already entering that entrance
grand california was packed tons of people were staying there and clearly going to this the the it
was like a block long line from that hotel entrance to the park to the lobby there was people i would
this is just a side note this seems like it would be fun to go to but it never seems like there's
enough offerings like a horror nights for me to spend what is 150 bucks which is like a day ticket
well i just didn't think of it this year and then when i was there i was like this does look fun
i'm sure it's like it sells out in a day yeah you have to be at your computer it's so popular the
headless horseman runs down the street during the parade which is fun okay so it sounds like fun but
it always feels like it's not quite enough for me especially because usually i have an annual pass
which i don't know going forward what that's going to look like because we're all so confused and
irritated by the changes i just got a new magic key magnet in the mail because i renewed behind
oh you did oh right right okay hell yeah man they really appreciate you it's blue now
it's blue and the mailing was addressed to magic key holder so no more names no more names
did i say immediately having the child that lindsay has gone from her stance of like we're waiting
till the baby is two before we go to disneyland too we should take the baby soon right
jason keeps saying the baby's free which is really what the attractive part of it is
no we're not doing it imminently but at least she's a little flexible on the on the time table
try anything crazy like trying to get a lunch reservation because you're fucked in that respect
sure uh so anyway yeah disney we should do one of these parties one of these days but
it just feels like you're there all the time it's like am i gonna go and pay more money it doesn't
if it was like eight mazes i've said this before where disney if they did like elaborate disney
mazes that they erected only for halloween season then okay maybe but it just you're like is it
enough to justify in my mind i'll say this the vibe was good i'm sure it was jack to be there
sure that's the case the vibe at the 80s night was great yeah people are so excited to be there
for a themed event and when like when the ambiance is a little different people get
excited like when you go they're playing pop music on main street it was a very suggestive excited
there was a little eyebrow raise there was that seemed like foam party maybe maybe i was a little
excited at the 80s night i saw micky in his tracksuit from uh the mouser size and i got excited
that's why when i was dancing we got a film filming singlet totally mini that night
so maybe that's what is what i'm talking about i i um memory came back a friend of mine from high
school went down to disney and universal around halloween and they went to horror nights
and you know again it was not as built up as it is now but uh there were like margarita stands
like every 20 feet and the only distinction between alcoholic and non-alcoholic was like
either the cup or or a parasol in it or something so our parents just kept buying
her the alcoholic ones and doing the thing to the cup and she was just like yeah i was just
going into haunted houses and we were all hammered by some point
well you can you can get hammered at disney at ogee boogie bash yeah and meet they card a lot
more aggressively nowadays that's true yeah this is having done a lot of these podcasts like
bodiness hammered is one of those listeners do a drinking game with mike and jason with the word
hammered i do you guys are you guys aware of the amount of i think a 16 17 year old has much of a
tolerance you know i think even team part i'm just saying you use the hammered becomes the word i
think of it a lot because you know what always comes up is that irish bar that's next to despicable
me that i say and it's always like you get because you go there and get hammered i you get you get
hammered there's a big wind up always i like the fray i like hammered i mean is it just a fun
yeah it's like thors hammer i just see people who can barely stand it's how tides walk around that
upper lot coming from that bar yeah what would you say your go-to word to mean that is
oh i have to no i think i say a few too many
well we can go to that we made me feel like a trick and a fool we can start saying it like that
so i this one i'm not gonna i like saying hammered and i will still say this is just listen for it in
past episodes and in the future now that i've made it a thing you listeners play a drinking
game with it and you yourselves will get hammered hammered you will get hammered hammered it's always
it's the bit the h gets a lot of hang time i'm trying to think of it a good other way i would
like to say it uh i'm trying to think there's a move john c reilly says getting drunk in a funny
way and i'm trying to remember how he says it i got something whatever okay it'll come to me
there's another way i like to say it but it's not hammered so maybe i'll replace it with with this
thing i can't think look that one up and then you'll straight uh um is there anything else about
i'm worried he says it's in it's in ricky pittson tell it good night he sees uh they're improving at
the table with it when they're saying he's saying he's improv in that movie yeah believe it or not
they have do some riffs he says he's in the front row of a lennard skinner concert and he says i'm
hammered drunk it is hammered yeah it's hammered it might have been the birth of the maybe the love
burrowed into our brains yeah uh the only other thing just there's so many easy things to do like
if they did a maze with doom like as doom's embassy which is the queue for oh yeah the like
why not a great villain there doom embassy like or something carnage it seems like as it was
developed it kept it was going to be in the extended queue for storm accelerator storm force
accelerator and then i think they just built a warehouse because they're like oh we'll keep
using this it's called the carnage warehouse and i believe now it's being used for storage
yeah so put in the carnage warehouse so people yeah carnage warehouse and it's just yeah there's
a lot of chain link fence in there and uh some like uh uh drink cups that we're gonna need when
we run out cylinder with a bunch of holes in it we just spin it around i wonder cylinder i wonder
if it's a pain in the ass to run horror nights at two parks spread out over two parks i mean i'm sure
yeah logistically because i i am surprised as it gets bigger and bigger it hasn't gone back to both
parks yeah i don't know i don't because it's sold out every night so i don't know if they yeah i
don't know maybe it's just easier to stay at one yeah i don't know good question for what's his
name murdy john murdy oh yeah maybe you talk jason talked to him once yeah i think he's mostly out
here though sure but he might know he may know yeah may know don't make me get the list
um
i guess i did establish rules of when the list comes out yeah uh um okay uh a little quick thing
we forgot one thing about the about horror nights 2002 and we've talked about a lot of things in this
episode we have talked about uh unorthodox villain team up super team ups we've talked about uh
intellectual property being done a little sloppily maybe the costumes not being the best
and we have not mentioned the ultimate iteration of all the things i just said and that is the
bill and ted halloween show oh right very well might have talked about this specific one when
we did an episode about that with uh with brad and nick years ago uh but just in case just to like
set the cultural scene that island under siege chill came out chill yeah fall of 2002 cool
progressive yeah yeah yeah great attitudes towards sexuality uh um so the well the big
things this year uh hey well see if you can guess them honestly if there's a 2002 do you have any
that's a good thought what's big what is the big pop culture in 2002 and i'll i'll save you uh i
it's not what i said before barry egan from punch trunk love does not appear it's not the mattress
man does not oh why didn't they say oh the mattress man is that car manage that oh yeah
uh is it the war on terror yeah i was gonna go war on terror as well they get all the guys in
rumsfeld yeah is that it colin fell the playing cards haven't happened yet iraq hasn't been
invaded yet but they're still trying osama bin haydn oh yeah yeah um no amazingly none of that
is referred it's uh why of course it's uh uh well dr evil and but dr evil takes on uh the most
sinister henchman that he could which is serlina from men in black two what yeah you know oh yeah
is that larvalyn boil yes the lingerie uh model who gets taken over um so then all right agent j
comes out to battle dr evil and serlina but mini me fights out and jumps out and fights agent j
and by the way just hearing about agent j you're like oh bill and ted why can you not
be here to have now certain characters in 2022 say keep my wife's name out your fucking mouth
say that to um i uh try guy ned probably that's right yes the team up of uh will smith and try
guy med yeah yeah wait how does it work because he's well he's well will smith is a is an ardent
defender of marriage and try guy ned fucked up and broke the marital vows right in a way that
the try guys seem to feel has never right occurred in history before so they'd be at odds right yes
so they would yes that would team up and then maybe it's keep your wife's name out your fucking
mouth when he tries to apologize but the apology is not because he's dreaming of the food baby
so will smith has to remind him what matters so will smith is the hero i think doing the slap
right that's that's good i think you know you maybe put too much thought into it because it
might just be like then like dr phil comes out and interrupts them yes probably still in 2022
2022 right dr phil comes out because my temptation was is it dr oz because he's topical but i think
mike's right i think it is dr phil because someone on the staff who someone who's there can do a
doctor phil yeah yeah dr oz how do you do that he's just like a weasel then you would just have a big
inflatable because john federman is a massive man he's a tall tall guy this is two of the weasels
but if you could just have a giant inflatable like foot come down and like step up like the
monty python foot on dr oz oh no john federman john federman but if it was florida then like
oz pushes up on federman's boot and he raises up the boot and he wins
dr oz beats everyone cheers you sure well well then they would have to get desantis
yeah that's true yeah yeah probably desantis like he's in the show for real he says he shows
every night he actually shows up in the white boots that's what he wants in the dallas cowboy boots
and tell us cowboy shearley are boots that he's wearing he goes up to dr fauci and says keep the
word lockdown out your fucking mouth right crowd cheers slaps the actor for real even though they
talked backstage please mr desantis uh-huh this sound won't even be audible they're gonna put in
a sound effect but he's too tough of a guy yeah i'm too tough i talk like this and i'm like yeah
i'm a very tough man and he gets the slap and then the whole crowd goes wild they're spilling their
mikulov ultra can bottles everywhere you know some illegal immigrants try to sneak into the show and
give some a free trip to martha's vineyard in the phone booth oh yes oh wow and villain ted go cool
not in the show very much so far i i thought they i thought drag i neck would trying to be like
hide me bill and ted and they're like no way man you're gross yeah look we've done a lot of
bad stuff and we've said some bad slurs about gay people but there's one thing we won't stand for
which is your affair try guy nid and then the audience takes like a couple like a minute of
like contemplative silence then actors playing the try guys respectfully not like those lunatics on
saturday night live actors respectfully come out and reenact the apology video but with no jokes
oh this is not a laughing matter oh i just okay that kind of negates my pitch which
the couch is actually in a big toilet and they all get flushed out of the toilet
i think all the show should end like that oh yeah they could bring it back and it's just everyone
getting flushed down a big toilet like every character epic universe i'm billy eichner i'm
mad about the movie people didn't come out flush down he goes where are the cast of amsterdam
biden falls up the stairs that flush
anyone yeah anyone who's in the news gets flushed this will be an epic universe they're building a
big toilet for epic universe for this new bill and ted show to skewer the center of the park
that's their their castle that's their center of the park anything topical that's happening
will be flushed we see a coca cola dream world what epic universe is like we're bringing back
villain ted every night in the middle of the esplanade might be i don't know we don't know
that could be the biggest weirdly that could be that's the end one more thing there's been
yeah there's been no leak about that there's a lot of leaks about other rides but we don't know
yeah uh well get billed in that big toilet yeah and by the i think also i think they could always
end with how they ended 2002 which is darth vader and gandalf fight and gandalf comes out victorious
darth vader reveals that he is actually martha stewart
that's what snl needs to learn from that's that's funny yeah that's back when comedy used to be
funny then yeah i don't know they just now they don't have their facts straight add the flush and
i'm laughing that's all i say add the flush kind of ever well look you're editing this so feel
free to put in as many flushes as you want uh but that's just if you have time otherwise you
survived haunt cast the fright oh i don't know all right it's been a little time does club freak or
club eek have any fruit to it now i still like my club three-headed dog okay all right we'll see
we'll discuss that one discuss it off mike all fan i'm sorry we didn't handle this but i figured
just get it out you know because this is about communication this is about intimacy which is why
we say thanks for subscribing your bravery saved the haunt cast well done freedom fighters um and
topic wise send us whatever direction you want next time uh hit the comment suggest some stuff
that isn't spooky and if you want to just hear me read the full fun fun fun facts list i'm uh i'd be
willing we could i could be talked into it great and i have the way the perfect way to take us out
oh there's an ad shit it's gonna be a perfect not so perfect oh that gives me time to uh wait
the beach boys did the first album record entirely in pro school
the flush oh oh all right those are loud planes so we should just let's uh that'll do it
unless they want most people want to hear the entire plane pass by