["Avengers Theme Song"]
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright, the cemetery gate,
behind which a good boy, a scared boy is trapped,
cornered, and forced to tackle some major fears
that is Scott Grave Digner, and thankfully,
I have some help and some backup from Jason Skeleton.
I'm very excited for this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Michael Madsen.
Thank you, yes, that's how you say it.
Now, this is a bit of a, this is kind of a second take.
Here's what happened.
We got caught on some weeds,
but I intended to be a quick opening
about something that happened last week
involving producer and Jimmy Buffett's best friend,
Frank Marshall.
If you can imagine bringing up Frank Marshall
caused a massive rerouting.
It was so thorough that we said,
all right, let's just call that a false start.
We'll release that on its own.
You'll hear that, I don't know, maybe tomorrow or something.
We'll figure that out.
It was so thoroughly its own thing.
Yeah, it's like Europe after World War II,
we got involved with the Marshall Plan.
What?
Wow.
It's like a Dennis Circuitus.
It's like a Dennis Miller joke over here.
Oh, I'm trying to get my packet together.
Oh, is he back?
Yeah, he's back on Rumble.
For his radio show.
For his, yeah, just his rambles to his wife.
Yeah.
Anyway. That's great, dear.
That's very funny, dear.
So we decided to reset, we're calling that its own thing.
And we are starting over to focus on the issue at hand,
which is, if you can see in the title,
Scary Trees That Scare Scott.
Uh-oh.
You all right?
I'm okay.
Anyway, so thorough was the tangent,
that sometimes the tangent becomes a mini episode.
We decided to refresh, take a deep breath.
I had more to say too.
We're not gonna do it here, I'm focused, but I'm just.
Well, maybe the more to say can come out
over the course of many, many episodes.
That's fine, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Down the road.
But for now, look, they'll hear that tangent later.
We split off, that went down that road
and we're going down a very scary path indeed.
Scary Trees That Scare Scott.
I've been passionate about doing this for a little while
because it seems like something good to do
in a haunt cast season is to address something
that genuinely scares me.
Always had, I go straight back to three years old with this.
I know my whole life I have been frightened
of talking trees basically.
I think we're gonna talk about some animatronic trees.
Probably some are puppets.
Maybe some don't even move,
but they still have devious grins.
This is something, I'm describing something
and it'll start to feel so familiar as you hear it,
but it's omnipresent in movies, in television,
in places, in toy stores, department stores, restaurants.
The more I started digging, the scary trees never stop.
That's true, yeah.
Now, I wanted to put it on me.
I wanted to make myself the recipient of this fear,
but I don't wanna make any assumptions about you guys.
How do you feel about anthropomorphized trees?
Yeah, I'm afraid of them.
I think it all starts like many things,
starts with The Wizard of Oz.
Yeah, yes.
That's gotta be the root of it.
I think a lot of people are scared of that sequence.
The wizard of Oz is, yeah, there's talking tree,
like trees are throwing apples at the heroes of the movie.
And everything in Wizard of Oz is so scary,
but like hypnotic, especially to a child,
because of just the way they made that movie.
Everything, I don't know if you,
I remember just, I would feel unease
watching the whole movie basically,
even though I liked it and I liked Scarecrow a lot.
It's all upset, it's kinda like a bad trip, I think.
Not that I super know a bad trip.
But like, where somebody might,
if somebody with different taste than you
might regard it as like, hey, that was fun,
but if you're a little edgy and if you're a little kid
and you've been told, oh, you haven't seen,
oh, The Wizard of Oz, what a, oh, you're going to love
The Wizard of Oz, and then it's full of scary voices,
scary things, death rounds every turn.
So much of, even like the characters you like
when they get those closeups with the soft lens,
you go, oh, God, it's like, yeah.
Like even the lion, who I like a lot,
he's like, they go to the soft lens closeups of his face
and it's just the makeup you can see real clearly
and like the fake fur and you're like, oh.
I think I always recognize The Wizard of Oz
is from a different time and that was like
part of the unsettling, in the way that I'm like,
I'm scared of things in like 1940 Pinocchio,
just snow white or anything, because like,
I just feel the like weird grimy 30s, 40ness of it.
It's not like Charmin Newsboy.
It's like, I don't like when the lion says like, no.
That's the comforting part.
And like weird, like the cancer causing makeup
that's caked on those people.
We're like watching men get poisoned.
The original what, Tin Man couldn't do it
because he broke out, I think.
Is that what happened, they lost an actor?
I believe so, I could be completely wrong,
but I believe that's what happened.
Something like that.
They didn't figure this shit out for,
it's rumored that it's part of why Andy Kaufman
died so young, was you got poisoned by the makeup
for the hideous film Heart Beeps.
Is that right?
I think it's in the mix as a possible,
although I wanna say, I forget if it was lung cancer,
but I've definitely seen it suggested
that the makeup made him sick.
Oh man, I've never actually heard that.
Yeah, not sure.
Don't quote me on it, but I'm not making that up.
Yeah, well, so look, we're watching.
Yeah, Buddy Epson.
Buddy Epson was originally cast as the Tin Woodsman.
No kidding, that's interesting.
But he was essentially poisoned by the makeup,
which was made of pure aluminum dust.
Oh, God. Jesus Christ.
It's probably in him when he died.
It's like the ultimate,
like the way glitter sticks around,
it probably like, it was in his bloodstream.
Yeah, nine days after filming started,
he was hospitalized sitting under an oxygen tent.
Fuck.
That's really serious.
Now I don't know, did they just use,
I mean, Buddy Epson lived till 2003, so at least he didn't.
We got a big run in,
but we're lucky we got any Hillbillies,
we're lucky we got any Barnaby Jones.
Right, so he had a good career, a TV career,
but yeah, that was, so I don't know,
did they just put, who played the,
what's his name, who played the Tin Man?
I forget the P. Jack Haley is one,
uh, Bulger is one of them.
Ray Bulger was a scarecrow.
Okay.
But did they use the aluminum makeup still?
Jesus Christ.
They were like, well, that guy,
fucking Buddy Epson can't handle it.
He ain't tough.
Get a non-pussy in here.
Yeah.
Our boys are going, fighting overseas,
and you can't handle a little powder on your face, dear.
Smoking in your face, just ridiculing you
for not being able to handle costume makeup.
Everything you're eating also causing pain.
Right.
Have you found Tin Man?
Jack Haley.
Jack Haley is the hit Tin Man, okay.
And Ray Bulger is scarecrow.
Look, that movie, and that scene, you're absolutely right.
I went back and rewatched it to see
if it would bother me in the same way.
It's the most abrasive sequence ever.
The tree slaps Judy Garland.
If you're believing the character,
well, let's go, all right, in reality,
this is a 16-year-old, I believe, Judy Garland.
If you're buying it narratively, it's even worse,
because Dorothy's supposed to be 12.
You're watching a young person just get smacked,
and then the voice, dear God,
what are you doing?
This is a film of wonder and magic,
and they're so gnarled at the,
here's one of my big things immediately with scary trees.
I'm putting this on it to say scary.
I'm asserting, if you guys wanna not call them scary,
to me, any alive tree is scary,
and I'm made uncomfortable by the degree of,
we're supposed to be replicating something that is hard
and that's made of bark and that's solid,
but at some point, rubber's gonna have to enter into this,
and the gnarled mess of bendy rubber
at the bottom of the, at the base
of those Wizard of Oz trees, disgusting.
Like, what if I had to be in that?
Oh, that's a nightmare.
Somebody makes me be in a tree thing.
It's the start of, just even, we've talked about it
many times, Power Rangers, Starlight Express,
sort of when there's a material,
that when they're trying to replicate the look of a material,
but it has to be a costume
because it's an anthropomorphized character, it's odd.
It's not good, it'll bend, and it makes it weird,
especially when you're a kid,
because it doesn't look like the right material,
and the same way with the trees,
where trees have bark, it's hard, it's not rubbery,
so seeing an abstraction of real life in that way,
especially with a scary face and scary voice, is disturbing.
Yeah, yes.
I'm gonna try to, maybe inspired by Wizard of Oz,
and if you have a better way of ranking these,
I just wanna clarify with some of these,
how scared I am of them.
So being that these are kind of ultimate scary trees to me,
and they pelt our heroes with apples
after smacking them on the face and arms,
horrifying, one of our beloved classic films.
Anyway, there are five out of five apples.
So that's the, if I give a tree only one apple,
that means I'm not too freaked out by them.
Yes, I see. Three of you are in the middle,
but five, they make me feel like I'm being pelted
just by watching them.
Oh, this is great, because I have a list I'll get to.
Oh, boy.
After we see some more prominent examples,
I have some, I would like some feedback on it.
You're just gonna pelt me?
Yeah, I'm just gonna pelt you with images,
and I will be in return pelted by the apples
sitting at your feet.
I will tell you how many apples I'm throwing back,
how many I wanna hit those trees with
to try to knock them down.
You know what, I was gonna say,
now, we should have maybe done this for Halloween,
maybe next year, return to Oz.
Oh, yeah.
Which I've been thrilled that hasn't come up
or been voted for.
Yeah.
What's going on with the trees?
And are the trees back?
The trees aren't, there's a thing called
a lunch pail tree in it.
And that's actually like a good tree.
So there's not the scary tree situation.
No, I don't know, there's no such thing.
Well, here's a big one,
and maybe you have this prepared,
but how do you feel about the McDonaldland apple pie trees?
That's definitely one of those.
That's a two apple.
I am not terribly afraid of the,
they were not my favorites, and I think they did,
maybe the only sin with them is that they remind me
of the Wizard of Oz tree, or did at the time.
They're sort of gone now,
but they were around in ages three, four,
which is when I recall being the most,
I don't know if I ever vocalized tree faces,
but you know what the problem with them is?
It's smiles, it's big goofy smiles on trees.
If a tree is presented as scary,
then it's correctly classified.
If it's got a big frowny face, then that's fine,
because that's what they are, they are scary.
But if one is supposed to be, is supposed to read
as friendly like the McDonald's trees, no, you're scary.
A smile doesn't help with that.
But before we get into scary, would you say,
and I couldn't think of a better example,
would you say Groot is the only good smiling happy tree?
I have no problem with Groot.
Yeah.
And that might play into, this might be a related fear
to the fear that I've talked about the most on the show,
my fear of big things in small places,
with Big Boo in Mario being the ultimate example of this.
I'm so worried about Big Boo on this Mario Kart ride,
because I haven't watched a video yet.
Is Big Boo in it?
I don't know, but I mean, there's a decent chance.
Big Boo is one of his famous villains.
I'm not kidding or playing it up,
that when I talk about some of these trees,
I feel pangs in my chest, and when I talk about Big Boo,
I feel pangs in my chest.
It's a 3D ride, so if they make Big Boo like Giants
on the ride or something.
Look, I know that that ride, well, I don't know.
I don't know this, but my sense is that that ride
keeps moving, and the problem with Big Boo
is when you end up stuck in a room,
especially, I think as I've said,
when you go through some door,
and then the door takes you to, you're trapped by blocks,
and the only thing in the block trap is you and Boo.
Jesus Christ.
Uh-huh.
Terrifying.
I don't think that that's gonna happen in the ride.
Unless it breaks down.
At the Boo part?
In the Big Boo part.
The AR gets stuck too, and I just have to,
and he's just blinking.
And then you could just throw AR shells at him,
I guess, over and over again.
But that's not how Big Boo is defeated.
I better have unlimited.
Yeah, wait, shells don't do anything to Boo.
No, shells don't do anything to Big Boo.
I don't think anything does anything to Boo.
Yeah, if you have a star, usually, you can hit Big Boo.
Okay, I'm amazed that in watching Mario land footage
that I'm not more upset by the big plants.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I'm kind of delighted to see the big plants around.
Somehow they aren't, maybe I'll feel differently in person.
But it's the fish.
What about a big chain chomp?
Are you afraid of the chain chomp?
I am not too fond of big chain chomps.
Yeah, so what about a Venus flytrap
kind of thing like this?
I'm not scared of what you're showing me.
Okay.
If it was moving and there was kind of a snappiness to it,
which is, again, what upset me
about the trees slapping Dorothy.
Have you watched Little Shop of Horrors ever?
I've watched Little Shop of Horrors.
I'm fine with Little Shop of Horrors.
Fine with Audrey.
Audrey II is okay.
Yeah, it's such a fun movie.
I think it helps if I was not exposed
to some of these things as a child.
Like if I'm finding something new and big now
probably won't scare me as much as something
where I still feel the negative energy
from like seven, eight years old.
Well, there's a level.
Did you ever play the original Ninja Turtles Nintendo game?
Like home edition?
I played, yeah.
I don't know if I did.
Jason, did you ever play it?
I did play that, yeah.
Do you remember the underwater level?
Not really.
Okay, because if you had the game,
you would remember this because it's one
of the most stressful memories I have in my life
and they just released all of the games as a collection
you can get on Switch or PlayStation
and the underwater level, I was playing it the other day.
It's still as stressful as possible.
There was seaweed, the controls were bad.
It was hard to navigate as the turtles were like swimming
through the sewer.
You had 90 seconds to defuse 12 bombs
and I remember being four years old, just wrecked,
wrecked with like stress.
It was not a particularly fluid game either.
It was very stiff.
Yeah, kind of a bad game.
It was the first game before the arcade.
Then they switched to that style of game.
But I was playing it the other day and I could feel it.
I could feel that four year old or whatever,
five year old memory of just,
oh, I gotta do this or Michelangelo dies.
Like New York is gonna blow up.
You're having to save your friend, don't you?
Yes, because it was incredible.
I've seen many other people say like if they played it
when they were little, but yeah, you're right.
If there wasn't a big thing in the game,
you're just talking about that you still feel the stress.
Right, I'm saying, yeah, I'm agreeing with like
when you were younger, that stuff can still be unlocked
in there, because it's scarring.
What I was saying about Groot is that I think I'm fine
with Groot because of his proportions.
He's very skinny, string bean.
I don't like big rotund trees
because they have big faces that fill up that.
Like Groot's face is as wide as a human's face.
But when you stretch to an uncomfortable degree,
like where maybe a tree's face is like twice as big
as a human face.
Oddly, that bothers me more than trees with a face
that's like 10 times bigger.
For some reason, that's exaggerated enough.
The rules of this are really weird.
So, okay, it's so crazy.
Maybe that's why I'm not afraid of Audrey.
Audrey's so crazy huge, but it's like mild extension
or magnification of something that should be small.
So Grandmother Willow from Pocahontas.
That's a good question.
I'm not, that's a one apple.
I'm not afraid of Grandmother Willow,
and I was not afraid of Grandmother Willow
in the theme park show that existed of Pocahontas.
Yes.
I don't like Grandmother Willow.
I've never been fond of the character
or the film in general.
But, so I'm not gonna go chase down
any Grandmother Willow media,
but no, not afraid of Grandmother Willow.
So you will not be watching the upcoming
Grandmother Willow Disney Plus series.
Live action.
I saw they announced Willow was coming back.
I was hoping it was the other.
It's not, it's the, oh God.
It's Grandmother Willow, yeah.
Jesus, all right, all right.
No, no, but not because I'm scared.
She's also not interested.
She's also young too.
She's young and hot.
Yes. Oh well.
Wasn't she, she wasn't always a tree though.
No, no, I think she passed away and became the tree.
So it's about just a woman, is what you're saying.
It's about a Native American woman.
A willow rising.
Maybe sometimes she passes a tree
and puts her hand on it, and that's a little,
that's an Easter egg for the true willow heads
because they know she's gonna become a willow.
Sure. Yep.
Let me get into the one that I know caused it.
This for sure is it,
because it's a swirl in my head
of I know that these existed in department stores,
and I kind of knew the McDonald's one,
and they all look similar to the ones from this commercial.
And when I was selling you guys on this idea,
these were the ones that freaked me out.
I didn't even remember the brand.
I knew it was a fruit snack of some kind.
Oh right, yeah.
There were a lot of ads, and I figured it out.
It's called Sun Kissed Fun Fruits,
and there's a compilation called
Sun Kissed Fun Fruits Laughing Tree, 80s, 90s.
And this is what caused it.
This might be too long of a little commercial to play,
but you'll hear them at some point,
and just know as goofy as this is
that it caused a genuine panic with a three-year-old.
Hear anything?
Negative.
Sun Kiss searches high and low for fun fruit trees.
The only tree is funny enough to grow Sun Kissed Fun Fruits.
I found them!
Oh God.
A kid has a bunch of metal detector headphones,
and he's trying to find these trees, and then he does,
and then he gets pelted by fruit.
It's these big trees, and they have big pieces
of, it's not really leaves, it's like giant lemons
and strawberries and grapefruits and stuff,
but then they rain little fruit pieces down,
which is supposed to be delightful,
but I was scared, like this kid gets hurt.
You could get knocked out by what they all shake,
and they all do it at once.
They all like, it's a big hail of fruit.
Of fruit snack, yeah.
Do you understand at all why I'm afraid of these fruit trees?
Yeah, well those trees, I mean those trees look like,
if you told me those were in, just name a product
in a commercial from when I was a kid,
I would say, oh yeah, I remember that.
They just seem like those trees were everywhere.
We grew up with those trees.
Yes, yeah.
It's not true necessarily, but they are burned in my brain,
and yes, I understand there's something
that's very unnerving about it,
and it's what we're talking about, it's the like.
I'm glad you agree.
I didn't know if I'd be facing just a stone wall here.
I don't know that my blood pressure has risen
talking about it necessarily now.
Because you weren't afraid of it then,
but you understand where I'm coming from.
Well, I was unnerved by, I was unnerved by a lot of it
as a kid, I remember this, I remember the McDonald trees,
and it's all eerie, it's zoobily-zoo.
There's like, especially the vibe of, I don't know,
of this time.
The fact that it's supposed to be, as I was saying,
if it's presented as you're supposed to be scared of this,
and then you are, great, I know where to put that
in my brain, but if you're told, here's some cute trees,
I don't like this, I'm scared of the trees,
well, that's your weird problem then.
I don't know what box to put them in.
There's no way, I don't think, is there a way
to make a rubber tree look right?
Like a cartoon tree you can-
Some of them don't, some of what we'll talk about,
these even, look, if I didn't grow up with them,
I don't know, I am afraid of these still.
Yeah, I mean, they are laughing at the children.
It was another one you had shown us,
where it's like the kids were a little in distress,
and they were laughing at them.
They're looking for dinosaurs in this one,
yeah, here, let me get another bit of laughter in, hang on.
Here's another ad.
The laughter is really a big part of it too.
I think so.
When I was describing all this to Erin
and saying we're gonna do this episode,
she was like, I don't understand,
when I showed her a clip of this,
she's like, first of all, I just like them, this is great.
And why do you have a problem with this?
That laugh, oh, that's exactly what I love to do.
I love bellowing, I love, open the cas, oh!
It's like way in my wheelhouse, so why am I so unnerved?
There's something about the way they're stacked
on top of each other and they're all identical,
and I agree with you, Jason,
I feel like I'm being laughed at.
I think they're laughing at the kids, not with them,
and pelting them with shit.
Well, okay, so let me, can I get your feedback
on one of these McDonald apple pie tree ones?
Yes.
Okay, this is like 15 seconds into the commercial.
It's on YouTube as a trip through McDonald land,
and here they are.
Oh no, bad, bad, bad, bad, no.
So they're silent.
Giant nose bouncing around, no.
The full on ripoff of Sid and Marty Croft style.
Sid and Marty Croft.
Oh, I didn't even go down the route,
so I know there's scary trees in those.
I think there are puffin' stuff ones,
and that's like, hey, hell no,
I don't owe that to the listener,
I don't need to watch this shit.
We gotta do full Sid and Marty Croft eventually.
Now how about the very rare cherry trees, cherry pie trees?
What, really?
McDonald's this?
Cherry pie trees in McDonald land?
Hey, Ronald, the cherry pie is ready.
That's right, Big Beck, red, ripe, and ready to pick.
Let's get started.
So Ronald, Billy, and Big Mack picked and picked.
So they're just kind of frozen in rigor mortis.
It appears to be a similar tree.
I don't, I didn't have a problem with that really.
The apple pie, look, I think when they're still,
that's fine, they've benerved me a little bit
at the playground.
I'm not gonna go stand next to the apple pie tree.
I'm delighted by the premise of an apple pie tree.
That's great, not the problem.
I've not, you know, I was rating them two apples,
but when you showed me that giant nose bouncing around,
that notches it up to four.
Why did they do a closeup of the nose?
No need for that.
Horrible.
That's just an old, it's some like six year old crew guy
with his fist in there, shaking it around.
It's like, I'm trying to think, are there examples of,
you know, objects that don't talk or have eyes
that commonly are given eyes and mouths in media
that aren't scary?
Like, so much of it is just, we see a tree every day,
they don't talk.
Now we're seeing in all-
Maybe it's the everyday aspect.
That's what I'm trying to think.
I mean, like Officer Big Mac, I always loved,
I know there's never, I was never afraid of Mayor McCheese
or Officer Big Mac.
But yeah, is there like another thing,
like trees that we see every day?
Like so much of it as like,
we know we can trust the trees in our daily life.
I don't love when a book is alive.
I don't like a book having a face.
That's an, and effectively so in Hocus Pocus,
that there's like a big eye in the book
that brings the Sanderson sisters to life.
Like that's what it's supposed to do is unsettle me
when I was a kid, but I don't want to see that really.
I'm not gonna go out of my way.
What other fun, are there like talking books?
I'm trying to think.
Page Master?
I didn't see Page Master.
Okay, there's a book in there I think.
There's the Evil Dead.
Right?
The book and the Evil Dead.
I don't really know those movies.
Yeah, I don't really know them that well either.
Yeah, that's a good question.
Maybe it is something about that like,
they're, yeah, they're all,
they're around you all the time and they don't have faces.
You can trust them in real life, but maybe you can't,
especially when you're a child.
Now, shouldn't I be less, in working this out,
shouldn't I be less afraid of trees
because they are stationary and they can't run after me
the way like a scary clown could?
But I think it's like, really, the scary thing then becomes,
what if it's too late?
It was too late for Dorothy.
She was right next to him.
She's within grasp.
So if, yeah, if you're at distance
where you could run away, great,
but if you're anywhere close and they can just like tackle you,
like give you a big hug and then pull you in,
I think I'm afraid of them eating me.
That's what I, I don't know.
I have never thought about what I am worried
a big tree is gonna do to me, but I think it's eating.
And I think the fact that they have roots
that go into the ground, it feels like they're gonna like,
that like the earth is their stomach or their intestines.
And they're gonna suck me. That's interesting.
They're gonna shit me into the center of the earth.
And then I like suffocate in there
or it's like monstrous stomach.
And maybe there's other people
that are all like moaning and trying to get out.
That's interesting. That's bringing up,
I'm trying to think that all of a sudden that's,
that diverts me to a different thought of like,
I think there is something where people go down a tree stump.
Am I thinking of like Inspector Gadget or something?
I don't know. They do that in Inspector Gadget?
That might be like, not that he gets eaten.
That might be like a secret thing that he goes into
for like his headquarters or something.
Maybe he's in the opening. I don't know.
Does Fred Penner go into a tree?
Remember Fred Penner's place?
I know he think he runs around a tree.
He was like a Kenny Loggins looking guy with a guitar.
That was a very like low budget Nickelodeon kid show.
Is that what I'm thinking of?
I'm sure nothing grotesque happened in Fred Penner's place.
Somebody had like a tree elevator to get to a base, I think.
Shit, was it Inspector Gadget
or was it what Scott's saying, this guy?
Like in the opening credits of Inspector Gadget?
Somebody had a tree thing
that he would go into an elevator.
Doesn't feel like Gadget to me.
He exists in like steel and metal in my world.
Yeah, that's what I think.
There was some thing as a child
that somebody would go in an elevator to get to a base.
And I was obsessed with it.
Listeners got it.
Somebody's, somebody has a point.
That diverted me.
Anyway, real quick, my thought is also that
I don't know that I ever had that thought
that the tree was going to eat me,
but being a kid being, and I don't know how much like,
I don't know for lack of a better term,
how many forests were around,
but in the Midwest we had a decent amount of like,
oh, there'd be a big bunch of trees.
And when you're little and when it's dark,
going in a bunch of trees is scary as shit.
Yes.
So with the very- Lost, yeah.
Getting lost.
Yeah, so like there were a decent amount of like,
places around where you could like go into the forest.
Inspector Gadget goes into a garbage can.
I remember that, yes.
And climbs down the ladder.
I remember that.
So there's something else.
Somebody had a tree that he would go into.
It was a secret tree base.
That's a really good idea for a secret base.
I love it.
But again, that's like, the mechanics are involved.
Engineers had to come sort that out for him.
That's true, yeah.
That's not like, imagine being, think about this.
You go down into, you get eaten by a sun-kissed tree.
And then you're in like a rubbery root world.
Imagine it's all undulating,
like they're disgusting floppy lips.
I didn't have the imagination to think about
dying that way as a kid, which now,
I never fully fleshed this out.
This is like a discovery in the last week.
I've been like, there's maybe subconsciously,
I thought the trees were gonna eat me.
And then I'm like inside rubber bark.
Oh wow.
And then I die there.
Yeah, I can see what you're saying.
Cause like, the mouths, they all see they're sinister
and they all seem like they're gonna eat whatever.
Let me show you this.
This is later in the sun-kissed compilation.
It's these motherfuckers.
This episode is making me swear a lot.
I'm mad at these guys.
About the sun-kissed trees.
Yes.
This is the one, look at this one.
It is all white.
It is white as a ghost.
Oh yeah, scary.
Look when his mouth moves, it like sucks in.
Look, that guy's, he's ready to slurp a child.
This all white one.
I don't think I ever saw this as a kid and thank God.
Oh wow.
This is so much scarier.
I remember eating those snacks
with like the covered in like, they're covered in like.
Why were they white?
They were covered in, shoot, they were like.
Creams, Supremes is the name of that.
Yeah, I had those once or twice.
Oh like Raisinettes kind of.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
And then it's, and look in the product shot
and then just he's blurry in the background
looking over the whole thing.
You think you're gonna trick me
with this box in the foreground?
Like, oh a delicious fruit, no, no, no.
My eyes are on that blurry object in the back.
It's gonna devour me.
Oh wow.
Make me live in him.
I think there's really something to it being part of nature
because nature is I think on some level scary to us.
Storms, scary.
Rain, scary.
Especially when you're a kid.
And I'm remembering now and I've looked up
to just to confirm rock, a rock structure.
Well you love fake rocks, but I don't think
you guys will like the Return to Oz character,
the Gnome King.
He is, he manifests himself in a bunch of rocks
with a face and I will walk around and show,
you gotta get, look up the Gnome King.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go to image.
And obviously they're making him look scary, but boy.
Oh, you know what?
You know what the problem with the Gnome King is,
is his big real eyes.
It's the disc, if he had kind of abstract pebble eyes,
no problem.
I think this is the, it's the combo of natural structures
with being humanized.
Like stone and flesh should not meet.
Bark and flesh should not meet.
Yes, there's something like even more,
like obviously as a kid seeing the fly
some Cronenberg movie would freak you out.
But imagine, yeah, like it's being a kid
and like, oh, the grass is alive.
This, like this big, the bunch of like rocks
that are in this field are alive.
The tree is alive.
And for some reason in media, they went with tree mode,
cause tree makes the most sense because it's got arms.
It looks like a human body.
So it's the easiest to anthropomorphize.
So, so like your world, on top of it,
just looking straight up creepy.
Your world view has to change.
You have to think as a kid,
yeah, there's a chance.
There's a chance.
Yeah, yeah, I have to allow for this possibility.
I was already afraid of the trees
because I know I can get lost in them
and there could be like murderers in there.
But on top of it, the trees might be alive too.
Jesus Christ.
So the gnome king, you know, you're not coming up.
There's not as many, you saw the,
you see the pictures.
I saw the gnome king.
Yeah, it is the eyes, I think, do it.
If it was just a stone figure.
Well, you're showing us this final form of him.
Yeah, that's right.
But that's even worse.
That's really insane.
Well, I don't know, in a way he's like goofier.
I think I maybe don't like the gray version.
He's, yeah.
You are certain that Return to Oz
is more unnerving than The Wiz?
Or is it just a different way?
Because there's some unnerving design work in The Wiz.
The Wiz is a little different.
It's a different sort of unnerving,
but there's some creepy, I think Return to Oz more so,
but I, your mileage may vary.
Let me get into one that,
because these exist in Theme Parkdom as well, obviously.
And this idea, it got back in my head
after we talked about Adventureland with Gabrus,
and there was something, we definitely played this clip.
There's something at Adventureland,
otherwise pretty unthemed.
There's not a lot of like mythology and IP there,
but they seem to love and be proud of their character,
the haunted tree.
And let me just refresh your memory on this.
["The Haunted Tree"]
Heh.
Oh my God.
["The Haunted Tree"]
Jesus Christ, oh my God.
Yeah, that audio on that really
takes it up a couple levels of crazy.
Yeah, the first voice I believe in there was an owl.
That was an owl living in the tree.
And then it pitched down even crazier.
I mean, this really, and like, yeah, I'm no fan of it.
The head could not be bigger here.
This is like big gnarled roots.
This face is, you know, twice as big,
three times as big as the Sunkist trees.
Look, if you're scared of it,
that's why you want it there,
because it's effectively scary, sure.
But like, this is very, why would you like this?
Why would anyone like this tree?
Yeah, oh, it's so unpleasant, and that noise.
And it's also, you can hear the bad recording.
It's crazy.
Yes, yeah.
Wait, let me rank that one.
That's a, it still might be a four.
Well, oddly, I would give that a four
where I give the Sunkist trees a five.
You didn't see that.
And I give an extra, I give a five and a half.
I need another half apple for that all white one.
You didn't see, yeah, you didn't see it
when you were a kid, this tree.
That's really the difference.
If I had ended up at Adventureland,
I mean, I would have been just afraid
of like a confident New Jersey resident to me.
That would have scared me forever.
That would be the topic of this episode.
Yeah, yeah, my biggest fear.
Men who are comfortable with themselves.
That's right.
Okay, so there's that one.
But when you're talking trees in physical environments,
the one probably a lot of people are going to
is the Rainforest Cafe tree.
There's a lot of those.
I would imagine every Rainforest Cafe
has some iteration of their tree, which is Tracy Tree.
Now, I know I'm not alone in this one.
Again, as I said, Erin does not share this fear at all.
Every tree that I showed her,
before I turned the laptop around, I would go like, ugh.
And then I'd turn around and she would smile or giggle.
She doesn't have this one bit.
But I know that people are afraid
of the Rainforest Cafe tree.
There's weird mythology, creepy pasta stories
about the tree, and a Reddit post with the title,
whoever designed the talking tree in Rainforest Cafe
can go fuck themselves.
So I get a little bit of backup here.
Even though most Tracy's, I would only give three apples.
Yeah, there's a little bit of a different,
some of them have different looks.
They're all destroyed, I think, now at this point.
I think I'm the most unsettled by the wear and tear.
I think it's the possibility of wear and tear.
Wherever these Sunkist trees are rotting away,
they must be so hideous at this point.
This one has just, the paint is just so chipped.
Some of them have different eye colors, which is interesting.
Some are blue, some are brown, some are gray.
There is a wide range within the Tracy trees.
These are all supposed to be the same characters.
And like I said, most, I would say, are three.
I'll show you some threes over here.
Basic model, I'm unnerved by these eyes, right?
Big wide eyes, but it's kind of standard issue.
The more severe and angular the features get,
I get a little bit freaked out.
And then we get into, okay, that's-
Okay, yeah, some of these sculpts aren't great.
At least three and a half, right?
Yeah. And kind of the ghostly white.
When it doesn't match the color,
when the animatronic face part isn't the same color
as the tree base, which is not animated.
Don't like that.
Yeah, an up and running and well kept up Tracy.
I always liked seeing Tracy tree.
Yeah, that's what you said when you,
now you look, you haven't weighed in a ton.
I don't think you have this fear.
I don't really have this fear.
Certainly unnerved by the Wizard of Oz,
when I would see it as a child and just see random scenes.
Kind of, I think if you watch the whole movie,
the dust bowl stuff at the beginning and end
is also a little unsettling for different reasons.
Cause you see what it was like when you were a kid.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So I, yeah, but I think part trees,
I think it's kind of a case by case basis.
I don't have, I remember Tracy tree.
As a kid, I find it more scary actually now, I feel like
than it doesn't stick out to me.
Cause I remember her, her, him, Tracy, female tree.
It is a female voice.
Female tree.
But now that I see it here, I go,
oh, that is a little scarier.
But I was so thrilled to be in the Rainforest Cafe.
Everything was a magic.
It's easy to miss Tracy tree.
There's a lot going on.
So you aren't forced to spend time with Tracy tree.
Yeah, I think now I'm most unnerved
by like a non-active Tracy tree,
like five feet away from a stack of like the book.
The Tillman Fertitta book, which Scott,
I mentioned this to Mike,
but I don't think I mentioned it to you that I only just
in the last few weeks learned about Tillman Fertitta's
family's multi-generational mob connection.
Oh, oh boy.
So that was a fun discovery.
There's some guy stuff.
That's great.
Grandfather and uncle ran like the gambling
and different operations in Galveston, Texas.
And yeah.
Texas mob.
Future episode.
Galveston mob.
I mean all the big.
We got a lot of Galveston to get into.
I don't even know where to begin.
Club three,
because we don't want to get in trouble with them.
Yeah, no.
Let's go as deep as we can.
I mean, the building blocks are vacant.
I'm reading a book about Benny Binion,
the namesake of Binion's casino on Fremont Street.
Oh, right.
He was a bootlegger to start.
He was a bootlegger.
And the book starts with like,
well, Benny Binion didn't always do his own killing,
but sometimes like, it's like, oh, okay.
It's still the name.
It's a tribute to the, whoa.
Yeah.
This guy's a here and I, Oscar,
the guy, I forget his last name.
There's a steakhouse named after him at the Plaza Casino.
He was the mayor of Vegas.
His wife is now the mayor of Vegas,
but he was also a mob lawyer.
Although he insists there's no such thing as the mob.
By the way, his steakhouse is just down the street
from the Mob Museum in Vegas.
Oh, okay.
So, lot of interesting Vegas mob stuff.
Yeah.
What a zone.
All right by Neonopolis,
the shadiest mall in the world.
Yeah.
I also, you know what I forgot is that,
here's another variant with Tracy,
or variable rather, is the degree,
look, like kind of small,
her lips are often black.
Right.
Like a witch's might be.
So that's a little unsettling,
but the bigger the lips get,
that like I'm more scared.
This is like, oh wait, I'm gonna go with,
this is a, we started with a three,
then I like the giant black lips
and her face is falling apart and the color is weird.
This is I think a three and a half.
And then I take it up to four with just red human lipstick.
Ooh weird.
And eyeshadow.
There's full makeup.
Yeah, there's a full face.
Thin eyebrows?
What are you thinking?
Why?
Here's what I think it makes her actually scarier
than some of the other ones,
is that she feels like she's a person trapped
inside the tree and her head is poking out of the tree
because she's like doomed to live as a tree
for the rest of her days.
You think this is a curse.
The other, right.
Doesn't it seem like it versus the Sunkist trees
who like have their faces more in the shape of.
More integrated.
Right, exactly.
This feels like a human face is bulging out of a tree,
which means something has gone terribly wrong.
Why would a tree have a human face emerging from it
unless it was a person that was cursed?
This might be, maybe this is a reason why the tree mafia
might want me and might devour me.
What if I get eaten by a Sunkist tree
and I'm kind of like kicked around the center of the earth
by roots, I'm like physically kicked around
until they find a rainforest cafe that needs a face.
Then my face is like stretched bigger than it is.
I'm like, I'm made big and then shoved out of that,
but my body's gone.
So I have no bodily agency anymore.
I, yeah, I think we could probably differentiate.
Grandmother Willow and Tracy are in the same category
of people trapped.
And the other ones are pure trees come to life.
I think that Grandmother Willow is less of a,
it's less scary because that's a reborn situation.
I think that's maybe a good thing
that she gets to exist in some way.
Right, at the very least.
And communicate with her family.
Tracy's alone, I think.
I think Tracy's nowhere near.
She doesn't always seem happy.
That's true.
There's some miserable Tracy trees.
Yeah.
It's a good point.
I'm wondering if this is the time for me to bring up
some things that I discovered.
So I was unsure where to start with this.
So sometimes if I'm,
if I wanna just get the gears moving
and looking stuff up,
I will just type in a very broad generic phrase into Google
just to start opening tabs and stuff.
So I typed in animatronic trees theme parks.
And I found the companies who make these trees.
Like manufacture these trees.
So I wanna get your feedback.
So this first one is called Dino Make.
And this is just on a list of trees
you would possibly buy from them.
Here's.
That's a three.
Not a fan, but just in the middle.
And not the scariest I've ever seen.
Here's a sample of one of their products.
This is a big tree and it's moving around.
It's moving its face.
It's moving its arms.
Oh, I don't like it.
Now that he's moving four.
Okay.
So that's Dino Make,
which is located in the Sichuan province in China.
There does seem to be a lot of Chinese manufacturers
of big animatronic trees.
Yeah, now this is a little more of a big wise tree.
This is the company is called My Dinosaurs.
What do you think about this one?
I'd have to see it move.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's see if I can get this,
get this going.
Cause this, this'll kind of, kind of move, I think.
You didn't buy one, did you?
No.
Well, yeah, this eye is just.
Put it up in my front yard.
Blinking.
Yeah.
If that came to life and started slapping shit around,
then that that's potentially a four,
but I'm gonna leave it at three for now.
Okay.
So that's, that's My Dinosaurs located in Zigong, China.
Now this chunky fellow, big talking tree for theme park.
This is from a company called Only Dinosaurs.
Of course, Only Dinosaurs is also located
in the Sichuan province in China.
What do you think about him?
This is a little small.
Can you, can you play that video bigger?
Yeah, let me try this.
Oh my God.
This guy's got real chubby cheeks.
Let me see, let me see it move.
Okay.
That's really the, cause you know,
still I'm not too afraid of any of them,
but it's that motion.
This animatronic talking tree, these companies,
by the way, for as much as they're called like Only
Dinosaur or My Dinosaur, they sell a lot of other stuff.
It's not a dinosaur.
Yeah.
Hmm.
These are real closeups of the moving branches
with like public domain music.
I think these are fantastically made.
Yeah, they look great.
There's real crafts.
Now I'll tell you that that last one that we showed,
they did say in the world of the tree,
the talk, the world of the child,
the talking tree is a symbol of kindness and wisdom.
What?
So how do you feel about that?
No?
No, it's incorrect.
Okay.
They don't know children.
They know this person never met a child.
Well, their description ends with whoever sees
this big talking tree will be very fond of it.
Now look, I, very fond.
Jason might be.
I might be.
I mean, and all of these ones, by the way,
you're looking between 1000 and like $5,500.
Now.
Surprisingly not that crazy.
Surprisingly inexpensive.
And on Alibaba, I found a bunch for sale.
Okay.
Also with different companies
in the Sichuan province in China.
So that's your, Sichuan is your one stop shop for,
you could, you go to Sichuan, load up on.
Yeah, I get a bunch of them.
10 animatronic trees.
Yeah.
As long as you can handle the shipping on that.
This is the place to go.
And I, and then just sort of like off the beaten path,
I guess you'd say, I found them.
There is a ski resort in Japan called Rutsutsu.
Okay.
And they have a big indoor complex
with like a fake European village
and like an animatronic band of like dogs
dressed in barbershop gear.
Whoa.
And then they just have this tree.
Okay.
Sort of moving in the lobby.
I'm not too.
These are all.
Upset by this one.
These are all kind of the same.
They don't feel like humans trapped in trees either.
They more feel like tree come to life.
It's about, we figured it out.
It's about trunk integration.
It is trunk.
How well do you blend in with your trunk?
Yes.
If I sense any face.
I've texted you both a photo from the cartoon movie
of the last unicorn.
And this is something I was not,
this is not from my childhood,
this is from Lindsay's childhood.
And we watched this movie a couple of years ago
and there is a very scary tree
that I've mentioned before on this show.
It's pretty upsetting.
It's a very bosomy tree.
Yeah.
And I was like, is this an ass?
No, it's a lady tree that captures the character
in her tree bosom.
It's like squeezes someone.
Basically.
Yeah.
That's what we're seeing happen.
That's what you're seeing in this photo.
You can see by even this like the drawing and the lines,
it's very unnerving.
This is someone on earth's exact fetish.
This is like. 100% it is.
That's what they saw at the right time.
To get smothered by a lady tree's tree bosom.
It's a bunch of things at once.
It's anthropomorphized and smothering
and trapped in gigantism.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a lot going on there.
Enjoy, well enjoy that it came up
if you're one of those people and you're here.
Finally it did.
Yeah.
They talked about it.
That's weird.
Animation doesn't factor in a lot for me
because animation you can blend.
Yeah. Yeah.
Not gonna be good trunk integration.
Right.
Maybe I haven't been afraid of an animated talking tree.
You have a yard.
So you would not consider getting one of these trees
that you can order.
No.
Cause if I had a yard
and a spare thousand dollars sitting around.
You would get an animatronic tree.
I would consider reaching out.
I think I'd be concerned.
What is the shipping from the Sichuan province?
We all want.
And how you program it and all those things.
We all want an officer Big Mac McDonald play place
in our yard.
Yeah.
We do want that.
Even if we don't have children.
Yeah.
Which we've seen priced out in a few thousand dollar range
up to 10,000 or more.
Yeah.
But a robot tree seems like a lot of maintenance.
And I don't think you actually want to keep those outdoors.
I think that that's where the wear and tear.
Look how bad the wear and tear is on Tracy.
And she's indoors.
Yeah.
I think the elements can't be.
Although certainly a lot are kept outdoors.
Yeah.
Just due to their, well, including a,
I was like, I don't know this offhand,
but I would be shocked if there was not one in Efteling.
And Efteling is like you had 20 times the budget
to do that Adventureland one.
Take a look at this Efteling,
which I think is just called the fairy tale tree,
but I could be mistaken.
Here's Efteling.
What do you think on scariness of this?
I think, this I showed to Erin and she's like,
well, that's a macula.
This is like an incredible.
It looks great.
Yeah.
His brow being so furrowed is a little unnerving.
But the fluidness of the mouth,
I think makes it less scary.
Yeah.
I think even a good example of tree mouth undulation
bothers me.
Yeah, he's kind of scary.
I respect the craft of this a lot.
Yeah.
But I don't, I think I might be walking by kind of quick
if I ever move to Efteling.
By the way, these fabrication companies,
some of them are like, we've worked with clients like IKEA
or the video game company Square NX.
The, one of them had shots of like their thing
in the Bellagio conservatory that they update every season,
like this sort of.
Oh, has there been a tree in there?
I'm sure they have.
They do like three or four of those a year.
I'm sure one of these have shown up.
Oh, listeners, if you've ever been in the Bellagio
and there's been a big talk, oh, which that in general,
send us your talking to what talking trees have haunted you
or delighted you.
I don't mean to dictate the conversation.
Jason, is there a chance that you could get a talking tree
and like use it as furniture?
Like you could sit in its mouth and read a book.
I didn't see any as furniture.
What I did see.
No, no, he's gonna fall in.
I'm just saying he really wants to purchase a tree
and I'm trying to think of a practical way
to get it inside the house.
I think it's more decorative than anything else,
but I would think you would need a yard for just size.
But the thing I did come across,
all these dinosaur fabricating companies,
when you went through testimonials,
there's like theme parks, zoos, museums, traveling shows.
But if you kept crawling down on the one website,
you would just see like someone credited as dino lover.
And I was like, oh, these are just individuals
who have purchased the dinosaurs to have.
So you could.
It sounds like Jason really wants a tree.
Yeah, I know.
Now I sort of want, as much as I don't wanna see a tree
and have one.
I want Jason to own a tree.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't, well, how much, how crazy is that
if you had to put a cap on the shipping,
what's the full project?
What are you willing to invest?
I am concerned that like say a $2,000 tree
is coming with $1,000 of shipping.
Yeah. Yeah.
Big time.
That's gotta be the heaviest thing.
Unless you go get it and bring it on the plane.
That is true.
What's the assembly like, you know?
Yeah.
Do they have to send a guy?
And then that's labor.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, labor.
Absolutely.
Okay, say, okay, you're talking to the people over in China
about making you a tree and they go, all right,
here's the deal, it's 1500 bucks.
For an extra 500, we can make the tree very busty.
Do you do it?
Bustiness is not my concern with the tree.
I think width.
I think the wider it gets, the chubbier cheek it gets,
I think it gets less scary.
I disagree.
You disagree.
Like I said about Groot, I like skinniness.
You got to.
Bulbas freaks me out.
You get to design the tree to your specifications.
Yeah.
That's, yeah, yeah, yeah, well, take us through,
yeah, what choices are you?
And if you had to pick one that you have,
what you just showed us,
what's the most important element?
And when you're choosing your Chinese animatronic tree,
what's element number one?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Do you want the face to be close to the ground
or do you want it to have some height?
Close to the ground is where we've never seen
close to the ground.
Well, but you know what I guess what I mean by that
is like some of the stuff you were showing, Jason,
the mouth is kind of like three feet off the ground
or two feet off the ground.
It's not sort of Wizard of Oz style
where the mouth is more where a human head would be.
Oh, this is lower, I guess.
Yeah, this is lower.
It's chubby cheek.
The eyes are very expressive on the only dinosaur model.
Also, all of these show different pictures
with different, they assure you it can be customized.
Oh, look at this guy.
This guy's got like googly eyes.
Oh.
Would you want that?
Weird, is that yours?
Yeah.
No, I don't.
I think if you could configure it to googly eyes,
like this one's older, this one looks more like a hobbit.
I don't like that.
No.
The Hobbit, the cartoon Hobbit nature.
No, that's out for me.
Oh, this one is facial hair.
That looks like Frank Zappa.
This one is Frank Zappa.
He does.
Frank Zappa, weird.
The Muppet News Reporter, what's his name?
Right, right.
Huh, Guy Smiley?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, like I think this, I'm reasonably certain
this is the Bellagio in the background of this.
Oh, that does seem, that feels like Bellagio style.
Yeah.
Well, I don't mind that mustache one at all.
That's a half apple for me.
Okay.
So I'm trying to think, yeah, what would I want in a tree?
I guess I would want it more low to the ground
because then it's less scary
because it's less like the Wizard of Oz tree.
Yeah, also, if you put this in a yard,
birds are gonna fuck this up.
Animals are gonna fuck this up.
You're the one who wants it.
Yeah, don't put it in the yard, Jason, you can't.
You gotta put it in.
I guess.
That's like a boat.
Now you have a boat with the added expense of it
that has to come from China
and you have to program a little animatronic show
to make it blink or else it just stays there dead.
You gotta put it inside the house,
you gotta have the tree's mouth open
and you gotta put part of your bed in it
so you sleep in your bed,
but hardly under the tree or in its mouth.
Hardly gnawing on it.
Yeah, head in.
Your head will be inside the tree.
No, an MRI.
No.
A tree MRI machine.
Oh, this is my nightmare.
You're just, don't make Jason get partially swallowed.
No, this is, no, the trees want it.
That's what you're playing right into their hands.
Bards are big clown beds.
They're big bark hands.
The tree hands grabbing the bed
and pulling the bed into its mouth.
This is the way Jason gets eaten.
But that's why he wants to go out.
I mean, if you had a large entryway
like in the ski resort hotel,
like I think just walking in, you were greeted.
So you had the nicest house.
Yeah.
Like with a ceiling that big,
we're talking, you gotta be in the palisades.
Hey, you gotta remove, I don't want the chandelier,
I don't want the stock chandelier.
Take it out entirely.
Cause I got a big tree coming in.
Like, oh, you want an indoor tree?
Well, not quite.
Now, now.
You're adding expenses.
Now you have to have the chandel,
the existing chandelier removed.
That's a difficult job.
Yeah.
This is on top of that,
you've clearly purchased a $3 million home.
Right.
And there's a tree in every room.
Well, but if you, if you sell the chandelier.
That seems weird.
I don't think you're finding another buyer
for a used chandelier.
That has to transport so easily and there's so much room
for breaking.
When Jason becomes the like flow of Hulu
and he's on every commercial for a decade
and he like just racks the money up.
Well, when the other Hulu guys get eliminated.
Yeah, well Jason's gotta do that.
They get taken out like the cave,
the Geico cavemen who didn't matter.
Right, right.
When it becomes only you, your grand scheme.
So then you have the $3 million house.
There'll be a tree in every room.
There'll be a tree integrated in every room.
What's the clearance?
What's the clearance in this room for the ceiling?
For like a tree, an animatronic tree.
The toilet will be a stump.
Yeah.
You poop into the.
Like Inspector Gadget or with a garbage can.
Or no, you go into it.
This isn't like Inspector Gadget at all.
He didn't have a stump in the toilet.
In the opening he shits in a stump, right?
That's the opening of it.
Not in the one I watched.
That's what happens.
Yeah.
They didn't make it part of the song.
At least it happens in the French Stewart sequel.
Inspector Gadget 2.
Yeah.
That's deep in the straight to video.
You know, I have become a bit of a plant guy
in the last couple of years.
I have a bunch of succulents, tiny succulents.
So that's what this is all about.
You're a plant guy.
Yeah, so I could see expanding this.
So do you want talking flowers as well?
You know, I think that's a different,
like we were asking.
Fetish?
I'm asking Scott about the,
these are from versions of a creature from Chomper
in Plants vs. Zombies.
What are you talking about?
Chomper?
In Dino Make sells these plants.
They call it Chomper?
His name is Chomper in the game Plants vs. Zombies.
These are fabrications of some of the creatures, I think.
And I think the scary plants that have like teeth and claws
and stuff, that's a different thing.
That's meant to be scary.
I'm not going, we are not recording in Jason's mansion
when this works out.
When Jason is still earning his pittance compared
to what he's made in this being the flow of Hulu.
Yeah.
I better throw a bone to the guys.
We'll still do it.
All right, make some room between my myriad
of animatronic chompers.
Sexy flowers.
We can record in the greenhouse.
They're not, when you boil it down to the practical reality
of like, oh, where do theme parks get these creatures from?
Where does like Hershey Parker, Dutch Wonderland,
like where do they get these plants?
And I mentioned those because like some of these websites
mentioned we fabricated stuff for these parks
and such and such.
If you're willing to spend like a MacBook Air's worth
of money to get an ant, you can have one of these.
You are willing, it sounds like.
I mean, I'm curious.
I'm curious.
I'm curious about the-
You brought in an extra dollar for certain beer,
but this, 1,500 bucks for a talking tree is here.
Absolutely not 899.
Ooh, now, $5,000.
A guy, a little animatronic guy from my home.
I think this is gonna happen.
I love that you're a plant guy.
I didn't even know that.
Yeah, I have bought some off the like adoption shelf,
they call it.
They're looking a little winded,
but I take them home, give them some sunlight,
water them and keep an eye on them.
You can bring them back to life.
You're like a hard luck case
as far as the plants are concerned.
I do like a hard luck case.
Look, this is very nice
and I'm happy you're enjoying being a plant guy,
but this is madness to act like this is somehow
the same thing.
So because you have five succulents,
therefore it would make sense for you to buy
a several thousand dollar Chinese animatronic tree.
I'm just considering.
Wow. I'm considering.
I want you to do all of it.
I'm not discouraging any of it.
I just don't know if like I took care of a cactus
is proof that the infrastructure
is gonna work itself out.
Well, I'm sure the sticker shock,
the actual reality,
like my car lease ended and I went,
I'm just gonna buy it.
And I was at the dealership for three hours yesterday.
I thought like, all right, I'm just gonna buy it.
They're like, well, the new model looks really,
no, no, I don't wanna do that.
And they're like extended warranty.
I'm like, no, I don't know.
I just wanna finance.
I just wanna get it.
And it was a three hour ordeal.
Now imagine you're doing this via a translator
and you're discussing length of stump nose.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm not too concerned about the language barrier.
I am concerned about like, okay,
this is the cost of the car.
Well, that's the base cost,
fees and taxes and APR.
You might not be concerned about the language,
but somebody's gotta pay for that translator.
Yeah, somebody that's gonna have to be a translator.
You're splitting that cost.
Maybe they do take care of it.
Maybe they're happy there's a perspective buyer,
but the costs are adding up.
How do you explain you want the robot to hug you
every night?
They need to be able to do that.
I don't know.
I think they work with a lot of international clients.
So I think we'll be able to,
I don't know how programmable in terms of hug capability
a lot of these are.
You're gonna want that though.
Yeah.
Do you want us to massage it such that the arms
don't just hard snap and it risks just like slicing
your neck clean through.
I don't want my neck sliced for sure.
And then the other thing is I'm like,
okay, do you guys have stock voices
or can I record some voices for it?
Can the tree be me?
Can the tree be like-
Good night, Jason.
I love you, Jason.
We can take care of it, right?
And do you want, you have a microphone in front of you.
You could save them some work.
Do you have a sample of what you might wanna say
to yourself as a tree?
Well, let's take the example of an entryway one.
Like, hello, welcome to my home.
I was just gonna say like you.
Yeah, so it's just me.
You don't even do a voice.
It just sounds like me.
Okay.
So I love you, Jason.
Welcome home, you've arrived.
I love you, Jason.
You may have been gone, but I didn't stop loving you.
How about, okay, try this one.
Pooping my stump, Jason.
I can't wait till you go to sleep in my mouth, Jason.
My mouth is extra warm today.
Don't worry about the pressure drop.
I know it got colder outside.
See, is this less scary to you?
Like, if we could program-
Yeah, it's all perfectly natural.
Don't worry.
It's been humid, so my bark teeth are soft.
They would only be able to gum you slightly,
not chomp your face off.
Oh!
See?
All right, I'm loving this.
This is the kid.
It started as scary trees that scare Scott,
and then it became a viable animatronic tree ownership
for Jason.
Who was a plant guy.
Let me run through a couple other,
because they exist.
Sally Darkrides made a few.
Friend of the show, Anise, let me know,
not even knowing we were doing this,
he out of the blue yesterday DM'd me,
hey, you should know about the restaurant
Bugaboo Creek in Canada.
Yes.
Which I think people have mentioned to us before,
but that it had something called Timber the Talking Tree
that talks about Canadian history.
Love that, that's a one apple for me.
Christmas tree is a little less scary.
That seems like a Christmas tree that you might buy
in a sharper image.
And Canadian history is delightful,
so I have zero problem with that.
It bugged me out when I started typing the phrase
Timber the Talking Tree,
because I was like, wait, didn't I do this already?
No, no, no.
Dollywood had something called Tinker
the Talking Christmas Tree.
Both used that full phrase.
So let's be clear, Timber is not Tinker.
Timber is Bugaboo, Tinker is Dollywood.
Scott, I don't wanna correct you,
I have to correct you.
Bugaboo Creek is Canadian themed,
and they were in America.
And I believe I've been to one.
I think they're out of business now.
Really?
But I'm pretty sure my mom was like,
oh, we gotta go to this place.
It's a steakhouse with animatronics.
A Canadian themed?
I think, cause it's a lot of moose,
and that sort of business.
There's like little places in Canadian airports
that are full of big huggable bears and mooses.
Area served United States,
Canadian themed American cuisine.
Whoa, wow.
Oh yeah, there you go, it was based in Rhode Island even.
Wow, that's wild.
Wow, that really complicates it more in a fun way.
I think I would have liked this.
Wait, oh, so this isn't a place we have to go to,
because it doesn't exist, right?
Oh, so we could do this episode no prob.
Yeah.
Oh, we gotta learn about moxie the moose
and goose the moose.
Oh, there might still be some.
They closed a bunch.
There was a bankruptcy, but.
Yeah, there was a bankruptcy.
But maybe there's a few.
Lot in Massachusetts.
Listeners help us out, Phil.
Well, the official website is archive.orged.
So I think that doesn't sound good.
Oh, and you know this is old,
cause it says try our Bugaboo Club lunch combos for 7.99
in finals America.
Please.
I don't think so.
So I don't know, could have been.
This is from 2016, I don't know.
So anyways, oh, here's a big,
speaking of stuff that listeners have alerted us to,
and I'm happy we get to go out on some,
look, this is the one I'm about to show.
This is a WONR.
I'm not scared of this at all.
This is from the oft-mentioned
animatronic-filled grocery store, Stu Leonard's.
They have something, they have a tree
that is specifically advertising
a particular brand of water.
That water is Poland Spring.
And here's a taste of the Poland Spring tree.
It's my pretty white tree.
And I live deep in the Woonkei lane
where Poland Spring water comes from.
From natural springs found deep in the ground of my home.
I love it.
Bear with it, we got a fun song coming up.
Sip, sip, sip.
Glug, glug, glug.
Poland Spring water, give me a hug.
Sip, sip, sip.
Yum, yum, yum.
Poland Spring water, give me some.
I mean, that's-
Honestly, you know what?
The song- No apples.
Yeah, the song takes it to the point where-
The song, I love the song.
Hate Poland Spring water.
Love the song.
Oh, that's a good point.
It's kind of a very specific tang to it.
I love the apples for Jason because of that water.
Yeah, five apples.
I've prepared some non-Poland Spring water for you, Jason.
Sip, sip, sip, my saliva.
Sip, sip, sip.
I'll take it, my man.
You should do one of the either sip, sip, sip
or give me a hug.
Whichever one you wanna program into your tree.
Oh yeah.
Sip, sip, sip.
Give me a hug.
When you finish drinking.
No, don't try to do both.
Don't choke, I love you too much.
Went down the wrong pipe, I told you.
So you know what, that's good news.
Getting towards the end, that's one that I like.
What about this one, and do you even consider it
in this category?
There's a big tree that I find scary
but does not have a face on a ride.
It is the Whomping Willow.
I am scared.
On the Harry Potter.
I am scared of it.
That part kicks me out big time.
I think the whole ride is scary.
I get a little scared every time I'm on it.
A lot of it has to do with the dangling legs
but also the proximity to everything.
It does feel like the Whomping Willow is gonna hit me
when I'm on that ride.
This is an intimacy that you don't enjoy.
Well I do and the idea that I like
makes me a little uncomfortable.
Everything makes me uncomfortable
but it does scare me still a little bit.
Spiders, I'm not a big spider guy.
That part makes me wince a little bit
even though it's silly.
I know, I feel dumb for still being scared of the spiders.
But I'm scared of all of it a little bit.
You're so disoriented in that Whomping Willow.
Yeah and you're on your back and it's like
you don't feel comfortable in the way.
Still even though you know how it's gonna move
you don't know how, you still are a little taken aback
when you get plunged onto your back
like a little baby or something.
And then that thing is like,
the noise is so loud and it's so impressively big.
Even without a human face,
just the branch coming down makes you go like,
oh this is big, this could really crush me.
Sometimes a face might be helpful actually to humanize it.
Even as much as I hate trees with faces,
usually there's something very sinister
about an alive tree without a face.
Whomping Willows for sure.
And I think a lot of people are afraid of trees
because of Poltergeist,
which I've never seen all the way through.
But that has a very terrifying tree scene
where it's smashing its way through.
It's very Whomping Willow-esque.
Poltergeist is so scary, we watched it not long ago.
And it is a very, very scary movie.
Have you seen Poltergeist?
I don't think, is that the one with the,
she's sitting in front of the TV?
That's a couple movies.
There's a lot of horror movies.
The poster is like a little girl in front of the TV.
Oh yeah, I guess because she gets taken in.
And then yeah. She gets taken in.
Yeah, I can't remember if I've seen all of it,
but it is on HBO Max and I do have it,
like I added a bunch of harm.
They have a ton of horror movies up right now.
Jason, Poltergeist is still in your queue on HBO Max.
Should I pull it up for you using my big branch fingers?
Never know when David Zaslav is gonna yank it.
He's scarier than any talking tree.
There's one, there's another one too.
I kind of remember this going around.
Oh, by the way, I just want to point out Produced By.
All right.
My man.
We'll hear more about that, my man.
See you around tomorrow or something.
And we ain't talking Waldo Sanchez.
Yeah, you'll learn more.
Okay.
Just quick other one.
This was a little viral last Christmas.
There is a mall in Nova Scotia with a gigantic talking tree
with kind of a like harlequin clown face.
Did you ever see this floating around?
I don't think so.
This is kind of the ultimate like,
this is non-trunk integration.
This is just a big weird white, like a baby clown face.
But this is so big, it's almost ridiculous to me.
I'm oddly not afraid.
This is Woody in Nova Scotia.
Yeah.
This apparently was a tradition in Nova Scotia
that they hadn't done in 15 years ago.
Look at this like scuffed up.
This is like the mask that the Joker wears
in the bank robbery in Dark Knight.
Scary scuffed up face.
This one's scarier to me than the new and improved.
Oh, the wink.
There's a wink.
The wink is pretty upsetting.
I also saw that if one of this tree's eyelids droops,
the way that they have to fix it is just a mall employee
with a giant pole.
It has to just like shove it back up.
That's like the Tussien Monstros teeth get brushed.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Who knew this was a job?
Oh wait, is this in Philadelphia?
Is this Franklin Mills?
This is not.
No, no, no.
This is in Nova Scotia.
Oh, Nova Scotia.
Is there something like that in Franklin Mills?
I think there is something, yeah.
And then just one more little thing,
and it's a little bit off, because it's not animatronic,
but what's ironic about this fear that I have,
trees coming to life, is that alive trees played a,
or at least one alive tree played a huge part in my career.
Oh.
A pivotal job, oddly, that I took,
and who knew that it would be.
The very first time I was ever associated with Funny or Die
was a video called Arbor Days, spelled D-A-Z-E,
and this was a purposefully hokey,
Jim Carrey style premise wish comedy,
but in this case, it is a guy who does not respect trees
and the environment, and then he becomes a tree
because his son wishes it.
It's a fake trailer they made
for like a purposefully kind of hokey movie,
and this Funny or Die video stars Tim Allen.
This is, in thinking like, oh, this might be
like a weird hacky thing that Tim Allen
would actually be in, and as part of this,
his face is comped onto a tree.
This is some of what I had to do was sift through footage
of Tim Allen with his face made up to look like bark,
which does, it just looks like he just like
smeared liquid shit on himself.
It's really weird, and then made weirder
by seeing his face on a stationary tree.
Anyway, this video is not the greatest.
It seemed like kind of a rush job for them,
and actually the situation was it was the holidays,
and they didn't have a lot of hands around.
Everybody was leaving, so we need somebody
to take care of that Tim Allen video,
so it got sent to me, and that was the first stuff
I ever did for them, and then I was working there
full time, like six months later,
and I was curious if this video still existed anywhere,
Arbor Days, because Funny or Die is like a graveyard
at this point, and I looked it up,
and it's not on Funny or Die anywhere,
but it is on Tim Allen's personal YouTube,
and I pulled it up on his personal YouTube,
and I was shocked to hear my own voice
as the narrator of this trimmer.
Oh, you don't remember that.
I am 90% sure I was not the voice in what they released,
and I think what is on Tim Allen's site is a rough cut.
I think it was something they showed him
just to show how it was going,
because the color's all weird,
and my voice is only coming out of one speaker,
and his audio sucks.
It's a real pile of shit, this particular leaked version,
but it's up proudly on Tim Allen's YouTube,
and I pulled it up just to show Aaron,
oh God, remember this fucking thing,
and my voice is in it, that's weird,
and then my son, God bless him, walks over or watches this,
and then he goes, again, which is what he says for again,
and then we play it again, and then I'll put it up
on the big TV, and he kept asking for it over and over again.
Again, again, twee, twee, and he's like,
Tim Allen laughs in it, and he goes, ha ha ha.
Somehow this became my son's favorite piece of content,
this weird old funny or die thing,
which maybe, hey, maybe this will set him off on the,
maybe he will not carry the sins of the father,
he will not be afraid of trees,
because of this earliest two and a half year old memory
of I remember watching this tree video that I liked,
and Aaron's rationale was, well, think about,
he's here, this is a video with the voices
of his father and Buzz Lightyear.
Oh, good point.
Yeah, that's a good point.
These are the only voices mostly talking in the video,
which makes me very happy if that's how he,
so anyway, maybe, I think my boy is not gonna be afraid,
I think, oddly, after all this, I helped him,
and he's not gonna share the same.
And he also is not gonna,
he's not gonna put up with all these woke people.
Yeah, he's not gonna waste all his money on avocado toast,
or the $10 oat milk.
There is a, in the video, you could tell maybe he put
some of his own agenda in it, because he does say,
we're selling that he's a guy who doesn't care
about the environment, and then he's like,
like, oh, what, is this, oh, he turns into a tree,
and then he says, oh, is this a punishment,
because I didn't watch that Al Gore thing,
which I wonder if he improvised,
which, by the way, I've told you guys this,
and I'm not gonna say it, but this,
my first job for Funny or Die,
I'm sifting through Tim Allen improvising,
when you wind him up and let him go,
the places that he goes, and this is not my place
to leak what I saw, but I will never forget what I saw.
This is funny when you say this,
because off the record, I've heard a couple people
about various celebrities, when you let them improvise,
it's insane, it's truly insane.
Why are Tylenol bottles so hard to get open?
Child safe, seems like they're adult safe.
I mean, that would be probably a better improvised learning
than most of these, but anytime it's like, oh, yeah,
by the way, so and so, when they improvise, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
It's either like they say insane things,
or they cannot do it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, oh, I've seen the,
oh, Funny or Die gives you, this became the job,
was getting a sense of who is a great.
Yes.
Improviser, and who actually cannot,
who's like, and who out there is much worse
than your friend you brought onto the shoot.
Yes.
There's a name in my head, I will say it
as soon as the episode is done.
I wish I could reveal to the full audience.
Anyway, if you're ever curious for more information
about the Tim Allen, I shouldn't even offer that.
Anyway, go to Tim Allen's YouTube, or we'll post it,
to hear my vocal collaboration.
But this is the first time your son is enjoying your work.
Yes, yeah, you know what, it's the most he's responded.
You make him listen to the podcast every week,
and he doesn't like it.
What do you think, huh?
He hates it.
Yeah, went a little long with that tangent,
I guess, okay, I understand.
By the way, Funny or Die, just a, you go to Funny or Die,
and there's just pictures of videos that were there,
that aren't there anymore, and so it's unclickable.
I can't watch Arbor Days with Tim Allen,
and then under it, there's thumbnails for other things,
and the thumbnail right under it is a video
called Murder House, and the thumbnail is Lindsay K. Tide.
Oh my God.
It's like 15 year old video.
That's crazy.
Yeah, Brandon Johnson, do you know what this video is?
No idea, no clue.
Michael Bush, Chad Foglan.
No idea.
Yeah, anyway.
So, I just don't know how, how do you land with it?
This is like a CV website now.
I was just having a discussion with, a couple months ago,
Anthony Geo and Evan Susser, and we were like,
does the Funny or Die website exist?
Can you go to it?
And we were like, we don't know.
And we go, you know what, we're not even gonna check.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, well, I checked.
I found a video with your fiance that I couldn't watch.
I also saw that Jason is a extra
in a video called Puppet High.
You're an extra?
Is that?
Puppet High?
Puppet High.
Oh, I do remember this.
Yes, I remember driving to a high school in Orange County.
You didn't go to Orange County for that?
And I had to.
To be an extra.
They pulled a soul.
And I barely made it, because they're like,
we only need you for three or four hours.
So I was like, oh good, I have to go to something.
And three or four hours, they did like one shot.
And I was like, I have to leave.
And they're like, okay, thanks for coming down.
I don't think you're in it.
I didn't see you.
Yeah, I'm not in it, because I left,
because they were like artists.
There was a good year,
there was a good year where we were fooled a lot by them,
I think.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Just like, yeah, come and be in this video.
And you're like, okay.
And it's like, no money.
Maybe gonna be in it?
Certainly aren't gonna have a line.
I remember those things that, those like,
I was not there for a while,
and then I needed a gig a few years later,
and I did these branded things with you and Lindsay together.
Oh yeah.
I found something, this was never my experience
in the early 2010s at Funny or Die,
but a couple years pass,
and then I found a new challenge as a director,
which is every actor coming up to you and saying,
I have to go.
Oh yeah, yeah.
That's what happens when you pay shit money.
I was like, I can't believe this is like,
and I'm like, look, I'm rooting for you.
You should get out of here.
Yeah.
You have better things to do.
Right.
There's people in those videos whose careers exploded
after filming that shit.
Yeah.
Like, they probably went off,
and they probably did the key auditions
because I let them leave.
Right.
Well, it's whatever, like whoever was making the phone calls,
like every now and then once, I was like,
yeah, I can be there for like six or eight hours,
and then I have to go.
And then when I got to set,
no one had any idea what I was talking about,
because whoever I talked to on the phone
was not there on set,
and everyone was just looking at me
like I was speaking Greek.
Well, ending the month on true horrors.
True horrors.
Swyfe as a minor player in a funny or die video,
circa 2014.
Well, I clicked on the tab that said library,
and it says we are currently populating
and reconstructing the complete library.
How?
Why?
Why did it get unconstructed?
What did you do?
They literally fired the guy who had all the videos,
because there was a day where there was a,
all of us who still talk from there were like,
tomorrow's your last day,
send a list of every video you ever wanna see again.
So we had to like rescue them,
and we didn't think to rescue Arbor Days with Tim Allen.
So no one will ever see the true cut.
You have to watch one with my voice, not stereo mixed.
This page is unusable.
It's like that new website, Seamafor,
if you know what that is.
I don't know what Seamafor is.
This is the guy, Ben Smith,
who was the head of BuzzFeed News,
and then he was a columnist at the New York Times.
He left to do a startup, and this is what it looks like.
It looks just like this Funny or Die library page.
It's just gibberish, and the very first thing is like,
Louis C.K. apology?
Why would you have that be your first thing that comes up
on your Funny or Die library page?
That's what happens when no one has looked at it.
You're the first person to click on it.
The audience.
Why no one's been around these parts,
it's been seven years.
It also says, a deleted scene from Louis.
I don't even think it's an actual apology.
The audience doesn't even know what we're talking about.
No, no, nor do they care.
I've started to wrap my mind around,
there will be, we might already be there,
that the phrase Funny or Die does not provoke
any recognition, and certainly no care.
This links to a 10-year-old Vulture article
written by Elliot Glazer, who is now a TV writer,
I believe, himself, that's the brother of Alana Glaze.
This doesn't make any sense.
There's just clips from at midnight from 2015.
This is nothing.
You're never going to find any sanity.
The further you venture into these forests,
you will get lost, you will get swallowed
as if by a terrifying tree.
This might, the lack of logic,
or the lack of any basic web design,
might be giving me the heart palpitations
that these scary trees give you.
You need to calm down by getting in the mouth
of a tree and lying down.
I do.
Letting them breathe.
The moist mouth of a tree.
Onto your face.
Look, I think, I feel like I sorted through some stuff.
I feel better.
There's some that I'm more comfortable with.
Sunkissed trees, I will never.
Snow White Scary Adventure Trees.
They are presented as scary.
Nobody says, and you love these, right?
So I'm fine with them.
Similar, the trees on the Haunted Mansion,
when you're going backwards, down the hill,
which I believe, if everything goes according to plan
in a few days, will not be discussed.
Not be discussed, correct.
Next year, next year.
Okay, you'll have to wait.
But again, presented as scary.
Listener, I am so curious what trees were in your life.
What trees terrified you, or am I wrong?
Are these all wonderful, lovable huggables?
And I've got the whole thing wrong.
And I, oh, and you know what?
Oh wait, I forgot one.
FAO Schwartz, I think.
That might be a source of weird trees for people.
And Aaron says just like random Macy's would have.
Like the Northridge Macy's in the valley had talking trees.
Maybe made by companies like that.
They wanna like jazz it up for the Christmas season,
not knowing that they were terrifying people
and giving them fear fodder for podcasts
for over 30 years later.
Yeah, wow.
Okay.
Do you feel more freaked out now?
Where did your, are you more comfortable with trees?
Are you gonna buy one like Jason?
I'm not going to buy one.
I would rather buy the Officer Big Mac
or have it recreated for the money.
Of course.
Maybe it would be more expensive.
But no, I'm not gonna buy.
I'm in the same zone with trees.
The scary trees.
Okay, you retain the fears that you had.
It's the same, yeah.
Uh-huh.
I feel better.
Inspired by my son.
I thank you listeners for helping me work this out.
You survived Haunt Cast the Fright.
Thank you for subscribing to the Cemetery Gate.
And if you wanna dig even deeper,
join us on our new Patreon tier,
which goes back to regular Club 3 next month
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
Hey, and also, I think the timing is right on this,
that I think tomorrow, keep an eye out
in the general podcast universe
because the good boys might cross over with a burger boy.
Oh yeah.
So pay attention to socials.
That's fun.
Let me real quick, a little code,
or I don't know what it is.
I was given a tip here and I wanna see
if this would inspire you to go to Wuhan real quick.
Okay.
So this is a person who's telling me, Landon,
who is, I went, he's experienced Minotaur.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Part of the Minotaur.
A great dude.
He said, there's a place thing called Reign of Terror
that he thinks I would like.
Okay.
And I wanna describe it and I wanna see if it's possible
because there's a thing at the end here
that might intrigue you.
So he said, it's got echoes of Boney Island animatronics
with fairground home haunt vibe
of the old version of the haunted hayride,
the atmosphere of knots, set depth of delusion.
Oh, and it's all housed in a fading old
thousand oaks outdoor mall.
Whoa.
Oh, I know the mall.
Of course I know, I believe the oaks.
The owner stores all the stuff there year round
and collects and expands the haunt
with the props and sets of abandoned
and closed down indie haunts.
So the whole experience is massive.
He says, make time for it next season.
Okay. Wow.
Outdoor mall though.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's intriguing, right?
Oh, absolutely.
Okay. Yes.
Yeah, hey.
Nothing but love for those.
The bad vibes of like, bankrupt or closed down other haunts.
Like that's an interesting layer.
I thought you might be intrigued by that.
Yeah, dying mall, I love it.
Alive tree, hate it, but not all.
We found ones to love.
Thanks for helping me through it.