Forever!
Dog!
Warning! The following haunt cast is a dark journey into this year's SoCal Haunts.
Not Scary Farm, Universal's Halloween Horror Nights, and Six Flags' big old teenage fog suck.
But we also journey into the psyche of our own Mike Carlson.
Why does he love douchey Vegas fool parties? Is he a fast boy?
Search Party creator Charles Rogers joins our psychic evaluation.
But one fact is unimpeachable.
Mike loves haunts on Haunt Cast the Fright.
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright, the Scream Park Podcast where the three ghost hosts delight in saying the names of obscure, scare actors from the 1960s.
I'm Spike, bro-blurl blood-ridson.
Joining me as always, Jason Skeleton.
Hi, you were an alien until whatever br-br-br-son.
Was that on purpose? Was that part of it?
It wasn't really on purpose. I wrote it down and as I was reading it I went, I didn't say this out loud.
You wanted to do kind of a take two just to let people know how it was in your head?
I guess I should have said Spike like blood-ridson or something.
I should have kind of grumbled it or growled it like a monster.
Okay.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
This is the voice of, what was yours?
This year I'm trying out Scott Gravedigner.
Okay.
But anyone can veto that.
No, I'm aware of it right now.
If one person says they don't like it then it's out.
Yeah, no, I'm good with that.
All right.
So, no, I guess I feel like I've never found one I like with my last name.
No, not me either in particular.
Jason Skeleton is perfect.
Yes. Yeah, I like that one a lot.
You're locked in.
But.
Well, it gives us something to look forward to in the future.
Yeah.
A reason to keep going.
Let's get up.
Our guys could end this year but we need to get the scary names.
I don't have a fun name for the guest and I'm realizing this.
But we'll bring them in.
We'll figure it out.
We've already done Charles as Gnarls.
But that's a famous band already.
Yeah.
He's the co-creator of Search Party until it's deleted off the HBO Max servers by David Zaslow.
But for now he is still the co-creator.
This is Charles Rogers returning to Podcast Arrive.
Thank you for having me.
Charles Lee Ray.
Is there something there?
That's the Chucky Man.
Is Charles Lee Ray?
Oh, interesting.
That's good.
I don't know.
Wait, what do you mean the Chucky Man?
Yeah, the Chucky Man.
The guy, the killer's name is Charles Lee Ray in Chucky.
Who inhabits the doll.
Oh, gotcha.
Oh, that's the real guy.
You're revealing yourself to have never seen Chucky.
That's one of those scared the hell out of me as a kid.
The idea of it.
The very notion of it.
And my wife had an old thing with it where she wouldn't watch trailers at all until she was 12 years old.
Because she mistakenly saw Child's Play 2, the trailer, and a theater.
So she had to go to every movie late for many, many years.
So it's a scary name to invoke in this house, but not the murderer's name who I don't.
So you could be Charles Lee Ray-gers to tie it into.
That's good.
It's impeccable.
Great, great.
It might be the best.
You plunk it up a little more and then it becomes.
It's the best of all three of these, or all four of these.
It's foolproof.
So yeah, we're in the holiday spirit here.
I guess you would say holiday spirit.
I'm Christmas.
What are you?
Thanksgiving?
Thanksgiving, yeah.
Cool.
Jason?
Our birthday?
Yeah.
We need that more now than ever.
That's right, Charles.
You got it.
Columbus Day.
I don't care.
Oh, no.
Oh, my goodness.
All right.
Everybody listen.
I got some stuff to eat.
Just an episode of Gutfeld.
Oh, man.
No, it's a soprano.
He's taking more of like a Silvio and Polly Walnut's angle on like, got to protect Columbus
Day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a bad tradition.
Yeah, it's about Italians.
My Italian roots.
Yeah.
And we're going to get to the Soquel haunts, of course, because it's haunters of fright
and the spirits are out and we're loving the season.
Mike loves haunts.
And I love haunts.
That's why we're here.
Last year, Mike loves haunts with a question mark because I didn't escape.
I didn't do an escape room involving a minotaur.
Now, I wish I had a report to tell everyone that I have done the minotaur.
I've conquered it because I had a panic attack last year, putting on a mask in this whole
thing.
And like, I just couldn't.
My brain melted down before we started.
It wasn't because of the scary man in the minotaur outfit, which I said on the episode
once the lights were on, looked like shit.
Not the case.
I was afraid of it.
But I was just like, I sort of had a panic, like sort of a mask panic and like claustrophobia
panic and I sat out, I tapped out in front of everybody, humiliating.
I haven't been this humiliated in like since high school.
People you respect and admire, I feel.
Sure.
Yeah, of course.
We had friends and I don't know why I'm reminding you.
No one's invited me to anything since.
I look like a fool.
Industry execs.
People who have given you jobs.
Yeah, David Zaslav was in your room.
He was there.
I'll give you the never delete deal right now for any shows that you ever pitched.
Yeah, he was there, but I know I made a fool of myself.
And anyway, I have not conquered the minotaur yet.
It's not going to be this year.
I'm trying not to give a baby COVID.
That's really what the mission is right now.
So I probably shouldn't be in an escape room trying to conquer a minotaur.
But running through a haunted house is fine.
And you had a mask on.
Yes, exactly.
With a mask on.
I had a gator on over the mask.
Ran through that thing.
I barely breathed while I was in there.
I didn't see you breathe once.
Yeah, so you're in the clear.
Wow.
And then we're fine.
You did it right.
Well, so what is being proven here is that you love haunts.
And so you fought through that you're very busy.
You're very sleep deprived.
That's true.
You still went to do the haunts that you love as of two years ago, I think.
Now Jason and I have made no, I don't want to say we've made no progress because I think
maybe we don't have interest in making progress.
Well, I've been watching more scary movies.
Scott is at least steadfast in his feeling that he's never going to do any of this.
Jason, I won't say lies to me every year, but definitely sort of suggests.
I don't lie to you.
This year I told you I was like, oh, my knee has gotten a lot more flexible, a lot looser
lately, but it's still kind of uncomfortable, long walking.
That's true.
And crowds are not ideal.
It kind of is an anxiety source walking around in crowds.
But I understand working on it.
I have sympathy for that as well.
But I did.
I said, you know, you do one maze and then you can go on that rat, the log ride, a timber
mountain log ride with the famous band that we like, the Calico Creepers.
It was amazing.
Yes.
Mike took me on that for the first time.
I had never been on that before.
Yeah.
Oh, geez.
So great.
I've been to not very scary farm before, but never done the Calico.
Wait, is that what it's called?
Calico Mine Train?
No, that was the it's a timber mountain log ride.
We're getting there.
So, Jason, you're saying you're watching movies now to prepare yourself for next year.
Yes.
What are you watching?
I watched Get Out last week.
I couldn't remember I had ever seen it all the way through.
It was very good.
I watched it a few days after Pinocchio and a few days before The Munsters.
So it was like an oasis in the desert, basically.
Well, well made movie directed, written, acted.
And then the others.
Some others.
Yeah, I saw The Munsters.
Well, I saw the first 15 minutes of The Munsters as a joke.
And then we were like, we actually can't do this.
And then we fast forwarded to Elvira.
Oh, yeah.
That's the end of the movie.
And then we were like, let's watch the credits.
That's what I should have done.
Yeah, we covered it on the Patreon.
And I tapped out at 38 minutes.
Some people have expressed dislike of this.
Some people are upset with you.
Yeah, I think.
It feels insane to me.
Some people sent us messages of like, that you shouldn't get the money from the Patreon.
Somebody said that.
You shouldn't get.
Jason, I should take all the money.
That's an interesting idea.
No, hang on a minute.
Oh, well now.
There is no deal in place that says that the name of the episode, Being a Movie, requires
all three hosts to finish the movie.
Charles is not a witness, but you can second that it's a very difficult thing to get through.
Don't bring me into any of this shit.
I don't know who these people are that are coming for you.
I don't know who their parents are.
Well, all right.
Well, you know, I'm just going to get into the bank account right now and cash out before
this shit goes any further.
When I have COVID, you're like, no cash, no cash.
Like, if you ain't on some episodes, you don't see that green.
No cash, no cash.
I rushed.
How many can we record before Jason's back?
I dock your pay sometimes when you don't say as much as I do on an episode.
I count you by the word.
I always worry I talk too much.
So that is a confusing statement to me.
I don't know.
I don't know that you talk too much on the show.
I think you leave people wanting more.
Yeah, I agree.
Oh, you always got to leave them wanting more.
Thank you, Charles.
You gave me such nice compliments the last time you were on.
You've talked a little too much just to let you know right now.
Oh, OK.
You were just there.
You were in the pocket.
See?
Learn.
I did.
I gave you all really nice compliments last time.
Yeah.
Mixed up your news.
Yeah, well, so speaking of last time, I just want to talk about this real quick.
You gave us a very nice gift.
All three of us received a copy of a prequel novel about the character Claire Dearing from
Jurassic World, a thick hardcover book.
Something studied in colleges.
Yeah, this is.
And we all got our own copy.
We each got our own copy of it.
Amazing.
Three of us are bad.
Well, two of us are bad readers.
Scott and I are bad readers.
Jason's actually the best reader of the three of us.
And I'm a pretty slow reader.
And he's a slow reader.
But I needed to at least peruse this before you came back.
And just have you read?
Can I ask if you've read it?
I have.
I was just being the teacher, not the student.
You'll read Cliff Notes before you have to admit to the test.
Yeah, and I did not read every word.
I will say that.
But this is a story about Claire Dearing, Bryce Dallas Howard from the Jurassic World
series.
It's about her internship.
It's written by her.
Yeah, from her perspective.
Yeah.
So she was like a very.
It's a go rascalis.
Where was it?
There's a woman behind the woman.
Exactly.
I hope it turns out better for Claire.
I mean, it doesn't because dinosaurs are after her eventually.
Well, it's an age old American debate.
Would you rather be on tons of drugs that scare you or dinosaurs chase you?
I'm just going to give a real quick, quick like book report about it.
Claire is an idealistic, like wanting to save the planet type.
Over the course of the book, she's kind of turned cold into the cold businesswoman we
know Claire Dearing.
You remember how she is in the movies.
Yeah, all white heels that click clack really loud.
That's what a cold person wears.
Yeah.
So for her nephews.
I think that's right.
If you're not close to your nephew, someone's fucked up about you.
Yeah.
And that family should be mad at an aunt who pays for nephews to go to an island and then
for them because she has a job.
Because now you learn that her like her love, another intern, and I'm forgetting his name
already.
He is killed.
There's some sort of nonsense with like a raptor that comes onto the island and he's
killed.
And there's also like a murder mystery of a different intern that is uncovered by Claire
Dearing.
So it's a 400 plus page novel with multiple plots.
Multiple plots, multiple new characters.
There's not even as many.
You would think that the Owen character, the Chris Pratt character, which no, he doesn't
show that they meet for the first time, I believe in Jurassic World.
I don't even believe this is a this was a question last time I asked all three of you.
And I wonder if you know, I don't think there's even a mention of the character, Lowry Crothers.
Right.
Yeah.
Now I have a question for you.
Who is Lowry Crothers?
Does anyone want to answer this?
This is the start of our last episode.
I asked everybody this question.
Oh, I got it right.
Charles might.
Wow, really?
Oh, we've done this before.
Lowry Crothers?
This has happened.
We just talked about it.
This has happened before and this will happen again.
We'll say.
We have a term now.
It's five timers.
If we've ever told the story more than once, we've ever told it two times, it ends up being
a five timer.
Is Lowry Crothers?
Is that Jake Johnson's?
Lowry Crothers.
Is that Jake Johnson's character?
That is correct.
Okay.
We had a faster time than last time because everyone gets wrong.
We had a bunch of different answers.
You asked Charles if it was Scatman Crothers.
Right.
So that's not who that is.
Scatman Crothers Lowry Crothers.
In the Smothers Brothers reading.
Anyway, that's basically the book.
That's the gist of the book.
It's a 400 page YA novel about Claire.
It's a Claire Dearing mystery.
I mean, imagine if the CEO of Pixar's book was about a murder mystery in his own life.
Well, another intern has died mysteriously.
Well, off of that, I do want to say, not to jump the gun, but I do have presents for
you.
Oh my gosh.
Two times running.
Well, because Mike and I went without Scott and Jason.
Oh my God.
What's wrong with me?
And Jason.
I decided to make it feel like bring the not scary farm to you.
Wow.
I wonder, is it a jam?
What?
Broad Preserve.
Wow.
Hey.
Thank you.
Now, this is a, now this is a scary.
Wait a minute.
There's something scary in it.
I was going to say it doesn't look.
It's not just regular.
There's a scary element inside.
Should this be filmed perhaps?
Is it a bunch of snakes?
The snakes pop out?
Jason, open it up.
There's just like pubes in here.
Well, strawberry.
What's in it?
Got Charles.
It's terrifying.
Oh, there's a mouse skeleton.
I got an eyeball.
Oh God.
You both have eyeballs or a skeleton?
They were not careful on the farm this week.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
Oh, and it's dripping.
This is very disturbing.
You've given us like the first like in-person surreal, scary image of a mouse skull dripping.
This is what you're missing.
This kind of excitement.
This adventure.
They're not going to sleep for a few nights.
I know.
But you're right.
We have to bring the scares to them.
This is the whole philosophy is that these guys need to be scared constantly in their
own homes from here on out.
I'm scared, but I'm also relieved because I'm almost out of jam.
So as long as you sort of trust where the eyeball was before its insertion, you could
kind of take the top slice off in general.
Just go towards the bottom.
Now you're going to do the whole thing.
He doesn't give a shit.
Scott, are you kidding me?
This guy hates soup after me once.
He doesn't care.
I eat Burger King.
Is that true?
Yes.
He ate a bisque from Disneyland after me.
I don't remember.
Yeah.
Where were we?
We were at Disneyland and there was like a bisque I was drinking.
And I remember like, did I get two of them accidentally or something?
Maybe I drank a little bit.
I was like, I'm full.
I can't have this.
And I go, do you want this?
And you're like, yes.
And you started drinking it.
Oh yeah.
Because I want to try the bisque.
I was trying to decide.
Yeah, that's an odd part of bisque.
I guess you would eat soup, eat a bisque.
But it's liquid.
So you do drink it.
In a yard.
You slurp it.
Yeah.
You got the tall boy.
If you go to Yard House over here in downtown Burbank, you can get a yard of tomato bisque.
On the seasonal menu.
You want a lager, you want a bisque.
Two half of Weissens and a pint of bisque.
For my girlfriend.
Thank you.
This is so great.
You really have horrified the podcast for the first time in this or any of the Octobers.
Because now I'm covered in goo.
I know.
You really went for it.
I'm covered in weird sticky fluid.
You got to lick your fingers.
That's the only solution.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Mouse goo.
That's gross.
This is great.
You did it successfully.
And this is the sort of thing where maybe in a maze you would end up with something sticky
on you and you just have to imagine what it could be even though hopefully it just preserves.
That's true.
There have been a couple mazes this year where there were sticky things.
Sometimes I feel like it's accidental.
Like it was painted and like the paint shouldn't be the paint they used.
Or those things that you have to like the viney things you have to go through.
They have like a siliconey like then there's something like a little sticky about that.
Yeah.
They use the wrong polymer or something.
That was my favorite maze.
Dr. Polymer.
So basically you because Jason we can believe or him or not when it comes to the knees
and the anxiety.
Well the knees are real.
It's clear to me so hard.
Well the knees are real and Mike has known me since 2009.
So he's seen the spikes here and there.
I'm just attacking Jason.
It's Halloween.
I'm just attacking him.
There could be more gooey things all over you.
You never know.
The people around you are joking in the way that you worry everyone around you actually
thinks about you.
Scariest Halloween of all.
The scariest.
Yeah.
I'm not making any progress on this.
You needed somebody to do a haunt with you.
You needed a haunt.
And you didn't want it to be your tiny daughter.
Yes.
No.
Not yet.
Next year.
Yeah.
Rope her right in.
When she can hold her head up on her own.
That's when the baby.
When she can smile she'll be able to see the brand new smile maze.
That's right.
Yes.
It's teaching so many babies to smile.
That's right.
You found a fray.
You guys did this trip and I haven't heard anything about it.
So you did not scary farm.
We did not scary farm together.
Yes.
We separately did Halloween Horror Nights.
But yes we did scary farm.
We did it on opening night.
It was very fun.
A very fun time.
I felt very VIP.
I got to be part of the media elite.
Full disclosure.
We were part of the media elite that night.
My friend Bobby who I brought along was not.
Well yes.
We felt bad we only had two VIP passes essentially that allowed us access to all the hottest
areas of the park.
And I'm not trying to brag here but you know when you get when you're at the media elite
like we are.
Yeah there's going to be some steam trays set out for you.
And yeah you're going to get like as much of those somewhat boiled potatoes as you want.
I had some mac and cheese balls.
And they had an ice luge.
Luge that was in the shape of some sort of gremlin thing and then they would pour your
drink down.
Wow.
And the drink we agreed if we're allowed to speak disparagingly about the hand that feeds
us.
Well we want to say thank you for all this stuff.
Never mind.
Sorry.
But then we can say the first drink you had I think is where you're going with this right.
The first drink you had was maybe the sweetest thing anybody could put in their mouth.
Yeah.
I have since thought about how grateful I am that you knew what I was talking about
because there is a smell in LA that's only in LA buildings like interiors that's like
a sweet mildew.
In my mind I'm like it's probably asbestos.
But it's all over LA and it's like in if you go to like a meeting on like a lot or like
the Gaylord apartments like those old school LA places it's a sweet start clocking in America.
Okay okay.
Which lot what lot smells like this if I ever go on a lot again.
In my mind it's Paramount.
You know it's any place that has the sort of old school 20s.
20s.
Yeah.
Okay okay.
Not some sleek fox situation.
Yeah.
Yeah okay.
It's a very specific almost like mothballs.
But the drink it tasted like that.
Yeah.
That one wasn't as good.
The other ones were good and the beer was good.
I went to this weird tasting event there and I didn't stay around long as I had something
else to do.
So I quickly consumed a drink that was a in a syringe like it was kind of like that like
preserves or mouse goo in a syringe and it was unclear.
Well either you could like shoot kind of straight from that or pour it into your drink.
It was this not available.
It's only I have the syringe drink.
This sounds like a bachelorette party or something.
Or a hospital.
Or a syringe.
Or a bachelorette hospital.
Yeah.
Yeah maybe I wanted a sort of covid fugue that I'm not.
Sea stripper nurse shooting shots with a syringe into your mouth.
No we didn't see anything like that.
No these were the concoctions of a mad scientist you see.
And I kind of liked it for being like a fruity drink.
I didn't I didn't mind.
It was on the sweeter end.
But yeah I don't know.
That was at Knott's Berry Farm?
Yeah.
Was that in the Johnny Rockets?
No.
Well we buried the lead because that's where the VIP party was.
We were rocking and rolling.
That's right.
They were not playing rock and roll music though unfortunately.
What?
Mike and I did the Lindy all night long.
Yeah.
Despite no rock and roll we were doing it just to try to keep the spirit of the restaurant
alive.
And they weren't serving the regular Johnny Rockets menu sadly.
So that was a bit of a bummer.
I said this and I mean this in the best way.
And we've all been to Knott's events and they're nice enough to have us.
Knott's events always feel like your grandma's church is having an event and you're invited.
And there's a lot of stuff there to have and it feels very like home.
Everything feels very homemade.
Does that make sense?
The park in general I think feels very like you know homey and quaint.
Yeah.
Like your grandma.
Right.
Like your same grandma.
Like my mom's place.
She's very kind.
She owns a lot of roller coasters.
She's an unampeded mean.
She's a billionaire.
She lives in the desert.
I go to Winnapark and I feel like I'm back in Upper Darby.
Yeah.
Yeah so we got to do that.
Full disclosure we got to skip the lines.
This is the perk of being theme park journalist podcasters slash influencers.
Yeah geez or just hanging with them.
Boy.
On top of the world.
I know.
Well I've been calling myself a theme park influencer ever since then.
Just keep saying it.
See what doors open.
Door to this garage.
At least that one.
One door could open.
Did I have like some sort of swagger in my walk like look at this.
You seem like a cool kid for sure.
Yeah I was.
But like did I feel full of myself a little bit because I was like come on look at this.
Look what we've done.
Oh yeah.
No I was I was.
I was.
How charming was that.
Was that Willy Wonka whisking you around.
Was that what it was like.
It was it was it was incredible.
You were.
Yeah I felt like your child.
Thank you.
All right great.
Wow.
Yeah.
You were a movie star and my dad at the same time.
Okay that's good.
Yeah.
Well I'm very far.
I mean obviously I'm in father mode right now so.
That's probably what it was.
We did we did every maze.
We did every maze which was great.
Not repeats.
Yeah.
Not usually has like one or two new ones and then repeats and then they'll freshen up the
repeats.
So so the first time we ever went down to nots we got a behind the scenes tour of the
depths and dark entities.
Yeah.
The lights were on and those are still there.
And those I feel like they last for like fourish years.
So these could be the end of the last year for that.
So you all did that.
Well with the lights on.
Yeah.
Is that weird.
It was fine by me.
All good on my end.
It's like if you walk around the place set with like all the work lights on.
Were they scaring you though or were you just.
Oh no no they were just telling us how they did everything and how stuff worked.
And that's already what 2018.
Yeah.
So that's four years ago.
So so those are like the stalwarts now of the night.
But Charles have you been to you've been to scary from before.
Let's let's let's do this.
Haunt wise history with Haunt.
How long have you been doing them.
Oh man.
I love Haunts.
I've been doing them probably since high school I guess.
But even in high school and junior high my friends and I would set up a haunted house
for trick or treaters to walk through.
Oh wow.
And we would put a lot of effort into it.
So that was it.
So it's been it's been in my blood from day one.
What was do you remember like the haunted house themes or anything you would do.
Well we lived I lived I grew up on the border of Texas and Mexico which is very subtropical
so it's a little like Florida swampy in that way.
It's very wet.
Oh wow.
The theme was plants like every year you had to work with the foliage.
But the plants were mutant plants or just we would just sort of like put cobwebs on
everything and then jump from behind lots of plants in the house that I had the house
that I grew up in.
There was multiple doors that you had to walk through before you got to the front door.
A lot of opportunity for scaring.
But I think I maybe I told this the last time I was on I can't remember but my number one
haunted house story is that in high school I went with my cousins and my mom to a haunted
house on the border and they all went into the next room and some scare actors pulled
me back and they pulled me to the ground and they pinned me down and then like more scare
actors came around and they just took my pants off.
I mean you're not supposed to be doing that.
It's an assault is what.
They just kept yes ending that energy until they realized they had crossed the line and
then you could I saw them kind of be like oh and then I just like hoisted my pants up
and like ran out and then my mom was like they took my pants off.
She was like oh no.
They just got so caught up in the and why why you.
Well.
God.
Look at me.
All right.
I see it.
Jesus.
That didn't put you off haunts forever.
No maybe it fueled my addiction.
Chasing that high.
I haven't found it since.
You know not I love I think I've been there for years probably.
I think this is like maybe my fourth year of going.
And I think this was the year that I got a little bored with it.
But I still treasure it and think it's very special.
Yeah well that's a that's a larger I feel like topic because these both knots and horror
nights and maybe you won't feel the same about horror nights but there's like eight ish nine
ish houses.
It takes a lot of time to do it.
You know if you have like your front of the line passes and by I think we said by the
eighth or ninth time you're almost looking for like someone to like punch you or something.
Totally.
Or my mind I'll just I'll be like I need to send that email and like things will just be
jumping out at me and then I just get into a trance.
This is what I've said to my close before I go that first one is going to be bad.
You're going to be like I'm never why would I ever do this.
This sucks.
I don't want to be scared.
I hate it.
The second one you go OK it's not as bad.
But I like the eighth or ninth you are just kind of like zombified like hey we go OK look
at that.
Oh yeah there's a clown that's yelling at me OK.
Hey you're right.
Anyway none of the next one like yeah there is a feeling by the end of that where I think
your brain has learned like no one is going to attack me.
Yeah.
Right.
And it's also you're exhausted because it's midnight.
But Charles never learned that.
You did.
No I was attacked.
I was attacked Mike.
Well it wasn't.
That keeps it alive for you.
You don't believe the victim.
I don't think that is what I said.
It wasn't look it wasn't the nuts scary farm character Mesmer doing it.
It was something else.
It wasn't one of these beloved I nots I.
Coodles.
Wasn't Coodles from Horror Nights.
That's not Coodles.
Coodles.
It was not Coodles.
It wasn't the ghost town resident with supernatural the conductor.
Are you speaking of the conductor.
I believe I saw that her name is Sarah Marshall.
Oh Sarah Marshall.
Yes we saw we met her.
We'll never forget her.
We did not forget Sarah.
What is it that name.
That's crazy.
I don't know but it just says on the like it's like oh oh wait I saw that too.
Wait where was that.
That is the last.
OK why am I it's Grimoire.
That was in Grimoire.
That was a new maze and the character's name in Grimoire for some reason is Sarah Marshall.
I don't know if they didn't know.
Any other name almost I mean not Annie Hall but like most other names.
It sounds like an old noise name.
I don't know.
No I didn't Google it.
Who cares.
We're putting it up.
Yes Sarah Marshall.
I mean we I guess we yeah we could talk about that.
That's Grimoire which is the new maze.
We did it like one of the last ones we did it.
That's their big Kahuna this year right.
That's the big unveiling is Grimoire.
Yes because the other new one is like Bloodline.
That one is like they give you a gun which is actually we did do that's the only maze you did.
Yeah this is the newer version of Infected.
Oh that's right.
Yeah I like the idea of like putting like a kind of fun gun and it's like a zombie or you're
shooting but this is my feeling with a lot of rides that you have a gun on.
It's too much.
Too much going on.
Yeah and they didn't work.
And the guns didn't work and like it's not a satisfying thing to shoot it.
Yeah.
Because people are just they're getting close to you already and they're not going to like
kill themselves to throw themselves against a wall to make it feel like you're actually shooting them.
Yeah and I didn't know I was just shooting all the good people and I didn't it took me
a really long time to realize that I was shooting the people helping me.
Yeah like a steampunk bartender you were lighting up.
Of course I'm going to shoot a steampunk bartender.
This is annoying.
This is an annoying aesthetic.
I would love to shoot a steampunk bartender.
Way more than a zombie.
You're trying too hard to have an identity.
One too many Tinder dates end with so I'm a steampunk bartender that's my gig.
Goodbye.
And that was another one I think we did at the end closer to the end and I was just like
this is too much and then the score isn't satisfying.
It doesn't even tell you like wait for your score.
So it's like you weren't paying attention.
I watched the video YouTube of it before this and I was like oh this actually
makes it actually better than it was in my memory.
Yeah.
Because my memory was just like I got to pretend to shoot these people and.
It was a big line of people too.
You just felt like you're in line with a gun just sort of walking through a line but
Grimoire was really weird because it was kind of a Stranger Things camp like teens at a campfire
and I mean you know the SoCal actor element of it's very engaging.
Like there's a lot to think about there with like you know all these 20 year olds
like playing teenagers and like you're just making like direct eye contact with
four feet away and they had a fake campfire and then the girl the lead girl read from
a book I think called Grimoire.
Grimoire is like a book of evil essentially and I guess various lore I guess and she's
lip syncing the dialogue and it's a very I'll say the word intimate kind of spot to be in
and I for a second I thought this was going to be the best maze because there's like people
she's like dressed like the Pokemon trainer.
What's the name of the main Pokemon trainer?
Misty or Ash.
I think it's Ash she's dressed she was dressed like Ash she's got big baseball cap and she's
got big book and she's like doing the real like come on everybody type acting and she's
pretending she's doing the lip sync and then yeah something happens and she says something about
the book and then lights or whatever and smoke shoot up and I remember going this might be the
best one.
It started really promising and she's lip syncing to a track that's extremely loud.
So loud.
Is just booming unnaturally loud everywhere.
You're close to her yeah.
And then other people would be kind of ad-libbing or they decided later that they should like
have more lines but there wasn't a track and it was already too late or something so there
would be like her that would be like we have that would just be so and then somebody else
would be like it was just like this completely like what the mix was off.
I was off to say the least.
I watched that video and I think the reason her track is recorded is because an effect
has to hit after she reads from the book.
Maybe I think there's like some fog or an explosion or something that happened.
I think what it is is that all the kids we don't see Sarah Marshall again we don't forget her but
we don't see her again.
She's Sarah Marshall I believe because they're trying to find her.
They remember her but the other you see the other kids later.
Now they're played by different much older actors in my memory.
It's like you saw the kids before and then you see them later and you're like then looks like
that guy aged 15 years since I saw him at the campfire.
Look you gotta have some dupes and you gotta do 30 minutes on 30 minutes off.
Yeah yeah of course.
You gotta just match the best you can.
But I think that's why the recorded track is because they have those people all
trying to sound the same.
You can look different but don't you ever sound different.
No if you sound different it will give it away.
So but you go through like a really like weird like 20s or 50s pastiche before that which I again
I'm watching the video and I go oh that was all really cool and then you go through like a fox
hole I believe.
Yeah you go through like a black and white house.
Like then you go through a closet then you're like in an army fox hole for some reason.
Yeah and then you're in like paths of glory all of a sudden.
And then Jason you're like this you go into a rations room with a bunch of cans of soup.
There's just a big room full of like not Campbell soup but it is like the logo it looks like Campbell
soup.
Is anyone eating any of these biscuits?
I don't want to be the first.
Somebody else try.
Is the VIP wristband get us these?
Can I get a couple?
You get tackled by a scare actor for trying to rip one of the cans off of the.
Sir.
And it's all that's all actually pretty cool and then you go back into present day
and then there's just many rooms of going through the forest trying to find Sarah Marshall.
Yeah.
And you can't find her.
We didn't find her.
And you do forget your goal.
Absolutely.
You forget Sarah Marshall but you do forget why you care.
There's a Buena Park actor yelling at you though later but you still don't know what you're doing.
And it's that very classic maze thing which I realize they all almost all have accepted six
flags.
They almost all have this thing where people are like come on come on and it's just like
it's just like rushing you like airport stress is like yes that's how that's how a lot of them keep
the tensions high.
Yeah and well and also the built they built in keeping it moving because you got to get a lot
of people in and out here so for some reason all these are all very urgent.
I think I've said this probably twice on the show at least by and I didn't do this because they
did a WB like Horror Nights on the Lot a couple years ago.
That's fun.
And they did like an Arkham Asylum Batman one and there was a room in the video I was watching
where Joker has to do like he has to yell and do his Joker shit but also he has to move sure
the line is moving and then anybody else wants to control the line too he's like hold on one
moment and then he does this whole thing and then like he's like checking checking to make
sure the whole group is ready and then he's like all right right this way you know like they
couldn't get a second person.
And this is a Joker's assistant.
Yeah Harley Quinn couldn't have done that so yeah it's all it's all built into like ride capacity
or or haunt capacity is the the narrative has to move because we got to get people in and out.
Yeah Grimoire was a new one the first half that's my review the first half I feel like is great.
And I think it's an unfinished story if I remember correctly they kind of just
they're just like okay go go out.
Yeah they end and like she's gone the book took her.
Yeah she's dead I think.
Yes she's gone Sarah Marshall's dead.
Huh yeah well I guess these things aren't supposed to have happy endings.
No it's really sad actually.
Because you're seeing the book through the ages like the book taking people are possessing
people I think.
Yes because they keep like there's somebody will come out like somebody cooking something
in a kitchen and she'll have like the book and the book is glowing and everything else is black
and white around you which is a cool effect.
It's painted black and white and they're like wearing like gray makeup and like black and white
clothing.
I feel like if they can punch up that second half next year.
Yeah.
We may have.
A go picture.
Yeah and it can make it to the four year mark.
Is that the longest these things go or is it.
I think around.
What's the Kenan of.
I know.
The origins one right.
No origins is newer really origins was 2019 I believe.
Dark ride I think last year dark ride.
Yes that's the oldest one.
You can feel that feels old.
That one does feel that's the weakest I think.
It's OK it's not bad but it's not it's not that scary and it's not that interesting.
Yeah I feel like the clown room at the end is like kind of fun but not not as fun as
like killer clowns at horror nights.
It's a fun idea to just walk through a dark ride is a fun idea but it doesn't really always
feel like you're doing that.
So I think wax works has a similar tiredness to it too but there's something
just very charming about wax works for me.
Wax works Dr Scratch I believe is the character's name and he like it's a you're in a wax museum
but he's also taking people and turning them into like horribly disfigured wax creatures.
At the end you see like depending on if people are on their shift or not people are in like
the vats of wax like crawl like calling out to you.
I don't think we got that because I was watching the video earlier today.
I remember a couple of times we going through the mazes and I go like there's a couple
of people called in sick today.
There was that and then a lot of the things that had been working before weren't working
where there'd be like a big hand that comes out and grabs you.
Yeah yeah and I was sort of waiting for the big spectacle moments and those it did feel
like this year maybe it was just opening night and it takes a second to sure get the show
on the road but it did feel a little like there was a dip for me but maybe I'm just
getting desensitized.
I did that I did I did Fright Fest I went to the Magic Castle.
Wow.
I had a frightful month.
Yeah and Horror Nights and so I'm just sort of exhausted.
Yeah yeah yeah well you've lived at like scream decibel I guess for I guess less so
the Magic Cast unless I don't know are people screaming at you?
No that was that was delightful.
Yeah that's just a calm nice time.
I will say the my favorite one of Knott's is Mesmer which is when we did first.
Yeah I'm having a hard time remembering it and I was thinking about you saying that
it was your favorite and how for some reason it's blended for me.
Mesmer it's a lot of like you go in a circus tent and then there's a room that's got like
different shaped clocks like grandfather clocks and it's all tilted it feels like a Batman
Villains lair or something versus the other like it feels different.
Yeah.
It's got a mood it's got an atmosphere to it that and it's all like disorienting you.
Versus just like pummeling you with Boyna Park scares.
Right right but the yeses.
The industry term yes.
So I've got that one's a new I think that one's like two years old but I feel like that one is
the best maybe which is because I was the freshest also that's also very possible.
Mike let me ask now that you've been going for a few years now.
Yes.
How do you decide where to start do you start with like what's closest to the entrance do
you start with what you're most interested in like.
Well Jason this year I'll tell you why we started with Mesmer is because it was very
close to the Johnny Rockets.
Johnny Rockets proximity and you want to like you hope that I guess in this case there was not rock
music playing but in another year you might hope that if you're a little afraid that maybe you
hear rock around the clock it is like you can kind of like tether to that.
A Bobby Boris Pickett cover of rock around the clock or something.
Okay sure sure sure yeah they should there's they should fill it with spooky rock.
That would be a great idea.
They should there's a lot more depressing than someone whose mental health relies on
orienting themselves with rock around the clock.
They're just giving us some rock music.
Ah there's also that's the second year I think of the roaring 20s area.
Yeah that was nifty I like that.
Which you would say nifty.
I was that I really stopped.
But it's the right word for it.
I did.
Oh your instinct was correct.
It was cute.
There's like like evil news boys this is why I said this last time Jason this is your this
is outside too you don't even have to go into a scare like into a maze this is just outside.
This is the roaring 20s scare.
Goring.
I said roaring I said it wrong but yeah you got like your evil news boys.
Yeah your evil flappers.
Yeah little jazz band playing up there giving it it's all.
This jazz band sounded great.
I it didn't sound that evil to me honestly it just sounded fun.
Well that's the trick.
But there's fun music I've made me music isn't always like the haunted mansion you know.
It's that's true.
Ghosts like ragtime I guess is what I'm saying.
They've established that they don't need to they ghosts are fun they don't need to just listen
to like screeching on a on a chalkboard or something.
Ghosts yeah ghosts like screeching on a chalkboard but they also love an upright bass.
They really do this is seems very associated.
It is true that it seems like what for some reason I don't know if the haunted mansion
started it but is can somebody point to the first piece of pop culture where an upright
bass was associated with ghosts.
Well when what were ghosts before the 20s I guess they were Victorian but before that
you know it's kind of like how teenagers didn't exist till the 50s like ghosts didn't have
a brand until right right right didn't have a musical identity.
They were just ragtime era.
They were just insane peasants that with no outlet with no way to express themselves
from beyond the grave was there they found jazz was there an origin of like ghosts being
fun were like ghosts like represented you know sadness up until a certain point when
somebody was like well what if we just like pretend they're just having a party.
I don't know the answer to it.
Is Disney part of this they I don't want to say they invented it but certainly and there
was stuff before the haunted mansion but like I do think of like the skeleton like the early
Walt cartoon the skeleton dance.
That's kind of like a late 1800s like the whole like mysticism movement made like magic
tricks and like the macabre of really popular in the late 1800s.
Oh yeah yeah that's true.
Like Bella Puck like skeleton person.
Oh sure.
And then you could like have fun with somebody who has access to beyond the grave or like
plays with your expectations.
And stances and huh huh.
There was also a tradition of reading ghost stories at Christmas time.
Really?
Yeah that Christmas Carol is a ghost story.
Right right right right.
Because Christmas was miserable until like 20 years ago.
Yeah until the Coca Cola.
Coca Cola.
A couple years before we were born.
Yeah.
And we're all 18 just to do the math.
I toured one of the this big old DuPont mansion in Delaware.
That's like a museum now does like historical exhibits every Christmas of like what is
Christmas like over the years.
You would go through different rooms and floors and they're like and so this is the 1800s.
This is 1910s 1930s 1950s and like the older ones are like the Christmas tree was often
decorated on Christmas Eve with candles.
It was not decorated sooner because you could only fill the candles for one night and you
had to blow them all out lest you burn the house down.
Yeah makes sense.
So that was Christmas.
That was Christmas Eve.
One day of an extreme fire hazard.
Yeah and then yeah and then there's poppers.
I love poppers.
Yeah everybody did poppers.
The British poppers.
I'm finally listening.
No.
The ones that you like pop and have confetti and like little paper crackers crackers.
Okay so you're saying capitalism has made everything fun really is what we're saying.
Yeah and they've injected some things really.
It's not wrong.
It's not completely wrong.
Yeah it's uh what the whole show is about.
We celebrate the good stuff that capitalism that's right leads to.
That's what the thing on the apple podcast says.
Poppers startups nowadays.
So yeah nots overall it delivered uh it's not it doesn't give you every year when you try to
talk about it since there's so much stuff that's like very similar or the same it's like I don't
want to go over the depths again because I've been there every listener knows my feelings on the
depths they know.
I'm not sure every host remembers your feelings on the depths.
You remember the my favorite part of the depths is that they do this really awesome thing with
like a laser when you're walking through like fog or like it's supposed to imitate fog or water.
So they put fog then they kind of put this laser that makes it feel like it's only chest level
and then there's people kind of putting their like fins or they're like sea creatures putting
their like arms up above.
Fins to the left fins to the right.
Well that's why I like the depths a lot.
Like the only bait in town.
It's very successful at what it's pulling it looks good.
It looks it's like one of the best effects that I've never seen anywhere else.
Yeah and every time I see it I think about how I was in this play in a community theater.
Oh actually this is a high school play where it's called the Diviners and it's a play that
only high schools know and I played a preacher who has to like go and like save a boy who's
drowning and the director just wanted me to like jump on the floor of the stage and just
like pantomime swim and it's supposed to be the most upsetting climax possible and people would
just fucking laugh every time I would jump on the ground and start swimming and I think about
that every time I see the depth I'm like if we only knew about this not technology in 2005.
That could have been doable for high school maybe.
A lot could have been doable in my upbringing that I wasn't given.
You have a long improvement.
This is not that high on the list ultimately.
Capitalism could have made it more fun.
I felt a little like Knott's is getting stale to me as somebody who goes but at the same time
I've been going to Six Flags it made me think Knott's is so special.
It really made me think like they really Knott's has a soul at the end of the day.
It's a weird soul and it's a makeshift soul but it is a it does have a soul.
For sure yeah yeah and it's got the like a they've got a voice that's consistent.
Now I have not been to Fright Fest.
I don't want to go back to Fright Fest without Anthony Gio.
Yeah.
Basically that's when whenever Anthony wants to go and do Fright Fest because we did Fright Fest a few years ago.
But I want to hear about Fright Fest.
Yeah yeah please.
This is my first one.
I mean I went to Fiesta Texas into Six Flags over Texas growing up to those Fright Fests but this was
I had never been to Magic Mountain before so this was my first.
Oh at all.
Yeah yeah and I don't think I can do roller coasters anymore.
It was really rough on my body.
Which ones did you do?
I did basically all of them.
The one that screwed me up was the Viper because it's like a loop and then a corkscrew and that was too much.
Yeah it was too much but then my friends went on Tatsu where you dangle and you face down and I said
I can't do that with you.
That's actually weird.
That's too scary.
I love it.
This is too scary.
Really?
I've only done it once but I thought it was thrilling.
This is what's funny about this is that he's the brave much braver than us when it comes to stuff like that.
What does it mean?
Are you asking him or me or?
You.
Oh I don't know I just thought I mean that one was fun because I this was like 2007 something like that.
I just thought it was so unique because you load into the chair like you're sitting and then it
like swings you up so you're facing down and like flying.
It is unique but it scares the shit out like the idea of it scares the shit out of me.
It's actually scary because like you can die.
Yeah it behooves them though to keep their guests alive as much as possible you know.
That's what I always.
I think I came to that conclusion around like 11 or 12.
Sure you're not wrong.
I think like that there's the separation of scary rides and haunts.
Jason if you can get over anything that's scary about a roller coaster then you get
the fun part that you enjoy.
Yeah.
I feel like with a haunt I don't think you there's enough in it for you or me
like so we get over the fear and then what am I am I going to appreciate the the theming.
Yes.
That's what that that's what is in it for me.
I think so.
Okay.
I like the theming I also like the world of horror like media and fandom and it's all very
a piece with like theme park fandom and comic book fandom.
Yes.
It's a similar language.
That's what I guess because we both did not we were kept away from all this as children but
we're comic book kids.
Yeah.
Now yeah you're like oh it's all the same.
And when it's really pulled off to I mean not to skip around but with horror nights
too where you're just like oh this is a fully realized idea from beginning to end it's
elevated and even though it does feel a little corporate or something there's still yeah
you're just like wow you really pulled this off and I got in the middle of something and
it felt real to me or you know or the idea of it felt real to me.
It's interesting because you're like certain ones like Mesmer for instance you're like kind
of impressed that it's not doing the same thing as every like all the other ones.
It's similar of course but it's not quite they're like doing a few things that are new
but then like to jump around horror nights there's a Halloween maze.
And they pummel you with I love it.
I love it.
I don't I think I've been I've never been pummeled more with like people jumping out at you.
There's a spot at the end I think I think that I'm remembering this right.
There's a room with like eight Michael Myers right and like half of them are real.
There's so many Michael there's probably 40 Michael there might be that many maybe actually
and then the last stretch of it there's just Michael Myers coming out of every window at
you as you try to leave.
Wow very body inclusive like all shapes and sizes.
Sure yeah not at all.
So like by the end you are like even if it's your last maze you come out of it pretty impressed.
Yeah you're like they got me and it's classy too and also the I mean not to be rude but just
like the it just feels like horror nights is sag.
Everyone is just you know a groundling.
Sure there's like a certain level where like the wigs have a little more patina
and everyone's really selling it but Six Wags was I mean these people they don't want to do it.
I don't know why they're doing it.
It's parents making them get a job.
I guess so.
That's on the billboard at the entrance.
I don't want to do the work today.
That's what we found when we were there is that very few employees wanted to do it.
We kept joking about it because it's so many I mean probably a hundred times somebody would
be like boo and then there'd be a moment where they'd be like and it was just it would be this
like apology energy that was like no no it's okay like it kind of worked like you want
and it's so everything at Six Flags the sets were kind of good the sets were good but then
there was one one at Six Flags called Aftermath 2 Chaos Rising because we're all so aware of
the first one and how the chaos needed to rise.
How could they do another Aftermath?
The chaos would have to rise or something.
Then it's gonna leaven but that was these huge set pieces with really tall
towery you were you were basically in Children of Men essentially and so you were like walking
through burning buildings with real flames and it was it was really like the the production
design was amazing but then the actors were all like victims of this chaos whatever it was so no
one was coming for you everyone was just like oh oh no like you just keep walking by people being
like that way.
Hey!
It's like being like walking you're like outside of a high school nurse's office.
Yeah it was like hour 13 of like the Capitol riots it was like everyone was basically disbanded.
It got mazed.
And this is like right after the head of Six Flags is like you know we're changing our image we're
not just gonna be a babysitter a place where you can just drop your kids off and I'm like
do you know what parks you run man like you're changing like you're gonna have to inject a lot
of money and a big change in like your whole vibe if you don't want to just be like the teenage spot.
Yeah I know that's the one Six Flags across the board every house had that kind of Rob Zombie
what's the zombie show the The Walking Dead like where everything is just a little
MAGA.
It's just like ah dang that's not my favorite thing about Halloween ultimately that's not the
aesthetic I think about I love a gothic I love a spooky yeah.
Was there the Haunted Mansion like ripoff one this year?
There was yeah.
Okay because that a lot of them they keep around.
Yeah I liked it okay yeah that one was okay.
Well they had one where people were flying over you a lot and that was
cool where they were in these harnesses and they all felt like trained enough in this thing.
The highest compliment you could give.
It was satisfactory training provided.
Yeah they did this thing where they would lunge at you and then they were on bungee cables so that
they would get really close to you and you thought they were going to hit you but then at the last
second they pull back and they somehow felt confident enough to understand the distance
There was some horror nights that had like a bungee yeah I feel like sometimes you see the
bungee when we did Delusion there was bungee like the rock monster punched somebody and they
bungee like shot them backward.
Yes so Trumpy about just saying and they had bungee and there we and we love bungee.
The thing with the haunts they gotta have more bungee they don't do bungee.
Did you do Twisted Colossus?
Yes I did Twisted Colossus.
How was that?
I liked it I liked it but god I missed the days where I could get on a roller coaster and feel
abandoned every time I was like this is I have to be on high I don't know what I was trying to
monitor but I was like I must be on I must be on Red Alert.
Yeah you want to feel free when you're on it not like worried.
I was looking at every screw I was passing on all of them so.
Okay because that's I gotta get but that's that's another Minotaur for me is getting back on Twisted
Colossus because I did it once and it crushed my genitals and I would just.
Who needs you to do this?
No one I I'd say don't do it.
I have to do it.
Seems like you're better off not.
No I'm gonna do it.
I don't want your genitals to get crushed again Mike.
That's not gonna happen again.
Yeah that's I can fix that.
Unless you like it.
You have a daughter they still work it's fine.
You did reproduce post-test to Colossus.
That is a good point.
I think you should freeze sperm and then go on Twisted Colossus.
You can freeze sperm out of six flags too.
Yeah at that Johnny Rocker.
So yeah I gotta get back on Twisted Colossus because it was crazy and fun but like it felt
I felt insane on it.
It's like there was a panic another anxiety attack happening to me.
I think that one was correct.
I think you were right.
I'm worried you're gonna get over this fear and then that'll be the time that Twisted Colossus.
Claims my genitals for good.
I hope not.
Again as we discussed Jason we love we all love when we can dock each other's pay
and get more of the money but I don't want your pay docked permanently due to your death.
No this is Twisted Colossus is good.
It's just that the whole situation was bad.
The employee leading up was not the most helpful person when we were trying to give him
our plastic souvenir glasses and he wouldn't touch them and he said you gotta get out and
go and put them on that table over there and we had to get out after being loaded on feeling
like the ride was gonna take us like without like somebody's gonna step on it as it shot away.
Charles the Six Flags teens this did you sense more of a vacantness or a hostility due to them
not wanting to be is was it more of like lost eyes or like open mouth like gaping yeah yeah.
Yeah if there was I mean I'm sure there's all kinds but it was it was the look of people who
have done no self-work which I guess is teens but there was there was a there was like a I don't
know my place that was like that was the energy.
It just sounded that they that they scared and then like recoiled a little like how can
you have the confidence to scare when you're clearly not like that that's that's very difficult.
Yeah that's that requires the most confidence in the world maybe that's who this is whose pay
should get docked if we're deciding. He didn't commit no one committed. I do want to say if Mike
dies I happily will do a Mike impression um on the show forever. Oh sweet okay cool like how
Rich Little did uh the pink panther after Peter Sellers died um he dumped half the movie.
I'm happy to do that. That's that's thank god because the backup would have been a James Earl
Jones AI situation and that sounds expensive so the guy sounds good you know uh I'll go along
with that plan but I would like to hear Rich Little try his hand at an impression of me.
The only thing I could ever do to impersonate you is funny. Funny funny funny and fun.
I've heard funny. Is that like my Chicago accent? Yeah that's interesting. Oh I've never caught
that but it sounds familiar. And if Griffin Newman now I'm really jumping around if Griffin Newman
is listening to this episode something he says on blank check is fundamental. Start clocking.
You could is a drinking game. This is coming from someone who has no friends just podcasts so
you sit and listen. They did that one again. They did that one again. That's the hook so mine is
the hook is like funny so like Rich Little. Same root word as Griffin. Yeah right it's funny and
fundamental. Yeah maybe just listen to everybody's F you I mean somebody's has to be fucked. Somebody's
has to be however they say fuck. Yeah listen for Jason's fuck and that'll be the key. The only thing
I'll say about anyone doing impression to me is I don't want it to be nasty like that Phil Hartman
Frank Sinatra impression. I want it to be nice like the Joe Piscopo Frank Sinatra. I want it to be of
respect. I want it to be loved. He loved because he loved Mike. It came from a place of love.
That's a five timers. I was talking about Joe Piscopo's kind Frank Sinatra impression. That's
for sure something. It was funny. It was fun and it was funny and fundamentally. Is that kind of
griffin-y? Sorry. Fundamentally. That's what he like. It's probably like super pronounced. Yeah
totally. He hits the syllables. Yeah wow. Well try it at home kid. Now you know you have a guide
for doing a griffin-numinum impression. Did you see any antics of teens that weren't working there
because when we were there we saw a teen put his mouth on the fog machine and suck a bunch of fog
up and then spit it out. No I didn't see anything too crazy but I will well there were girls that
were screaming in a way that was like oh my gosh. That was with us too. Yes that's happened there
with us too. You were like it's a little performance. I know there's something where I'm like it's a
little bit too much. If it's not a performance then something's up here because you shouldn't be
screaming this loudly. Yeah no we had that too. We had exactly the same thing. Did you drink a
beer in the little pen they make you sit in by the giant rockets? My friends did. I've been trying to
drink less. My friends drink a beer. In the pen. In the little pen and I will say the one thing
teen wise I did feel was that I went with like all me gay guys and I was like well we're just
gonna get killed. Like there's just it just felt like one of those things where it's like we had
a comment. We went to Magic Mountain. We went to Valencia and we should have known.
It's basic math. I don't want to forget though that the most exciting thing that happened to
us at Not Scary Farm was the moment that this clown walked up to us and started heckling us.
Yes yes and teasing us and then she walked away. Teasing both of you so it wasn't about your
orientation. No no no this was not and I used the word preference. That's what I'm saying.
It's okay. Oh shit fuck I've never been in this scenario before okay. I can tell you.
Preference preference okay. That is a great trick to play on straight people.
On orientation preference. I'll get them in a garage. It's a forced choice actually. Get them talking.
Scary.
Scarier than an eye in a Knott's Berry jar of preserves.
Don't use orientation as the keyword to do an impression of me.
So we were generally heckled. We were heckled as a group and then she she walked away and then this
janitor came up kind of seemingly out of nowhere. Yes. And was like like a materialized. Yeah it
was very magical. A magical janitor came up and was like man every year that clown gets sillier
and sillier. It's literally the funniest thing you could say about a clown.
He had like the like it was like the Wingsworld 2 Charlton Heston like far away look in his eye
like that clown like oh boy. Bob Hoskins Schmee like yes yeah. Look at that. It was so like he was
so delighted. Yeah yeah. It was one year I thought he peaked and then he showed me.
That is maybe the best character interaction we had all night. That of my year. Yeah sure. That
was the best thing I heard all year. How were the sliders this year? Did you see any sliders? The
people sliding on the ground. Not the burgers. I assumed you were asking about burgers yes.
No but I did have like they had a carving station where I had some turkey or something.
Ah that Halloween. Like a grandma like a grandma's church thing where you're like they have a carving
station here like multiple carving stations which yeah they give you a big like tri-tip or whatever
they got. Yeah my gate like a depression era orphan. Yeah I also I like immediately I lied
because your friend couldn't come in with us because we want to break the rules. I didn't want
to get in trouble. But I immediately I was like oh yeah we're gonna be there in two seconds.
Like you turn around and I have two plates loaded up of food. I'm getting like 10 boiled potatoes.
The whole English breakfast. Yeah the sliders is you're talking about the people on their
the slide on their knees and scare you. Yeah. There were a few out. Less than usual though right? But
I feel like it was less than usual and I don't want to say it's because because they've been
doing it so long at this point but it's got to be just hell on your knees. Yeah. There's no way.
There's no way you could come back next year and do it again. Yeah when we were at Six Flags
the opening ceremonies of Monsters a guy slid right out in front of everybody and made a bunch
of teenage girls shriek and then we heard him stand up and go oh like we heard him grimace
that he heard himself opening night first scare of the night. And I have to imagine that happens
a lot because these people are sliding like crazy. Be honest those are your least favorite. The most
like you don't like are you most scared of those scares? I feel like that's when you grabbed my
arm that one day. But I think that is very impressive. Okay. So I don't know that might
bounce out then. So you go ah and then you go ooh. Ooh. And that's how you hurt your knee was
as a slider. I was sliding yeah I was raw dogging sliding. I didn't know paths. During the summer.
That's what you can't do. Yeah it can't with the asphalt's 80 degrees and the sun's beating down
you're not supposed to just throw your knee at it. Jason there are no summer sliders we keep telling you.
Well yet. But for some reason sparks did come out of your knees. Yes. Can I ask the wait let's Scott
you actually watched the video now that I'm thinking we just recently did a Patreon episode
about the musical Starlight Express. Is there sliding in Starlight Express? Oh geez. I couldn't tell you off hand.
I feel like a lot of stuff happens. There's a little bit I think. Could be. There has to be sliding in Starlight Express.
It's probably accidentally sliding a lot. That's true. But is there Starlight Express? It's gone for
ever and ever. So I don't know. It's still playing in Germany. Yeah they built a private theater that
is just for this that the town financed because they love Starlight Express so much. Wow. There's
a documentary on the sliders. Yeah. But did Starlight Express did they actually invent sliding?
Not Scary Farm predates Starlight. Right but did sliders start with Not Scary Farm the first year?
I think those sliders seem pretty proud of their sliding. That they started it.
But I think a lot of because there is sliding in a lot of these things and I think there is
speculation and argument over which one of the I think it's from Theme Park World but I bet there's
a guy out there who's like I know I'm the first slider. It feels adjacent to on Letterman when he
had that woman that would just like drill her stomach with like sparks would fly out of her stomach.
She had a metal. She was an ongoing theme in the show. I bought this woman up on the show before
where yeah she would have like a metal outfit and it would spark. She would just spark because she
was hitting herself with like some sort of power tool. Something that would create sparks and she
would just like. Yeah. And it would happen whenever you'd go to commercial and they're like the band
would play and then this woman would come out and just like spark her stomach for no reason.
It would be a sort of a celebration. It feels like that. Like a late 90s discovery. Yeah but yeah.
Not as I feel like yeah there were only a couple sliders. So there was still a lot of people with
like a soup can full of change. Yeah. That's an old standard which like allowed like to rattle it at
you. They had canners. There's plenty of canners. They had canners yeah. Canners versus sliders.
My favorite Shakespearean situation.
Dynamic. I would like to try sliding now that I'm thinking about it but it's probably not a good idea.
Yeah no go for it. Why not? You only live once. What was it? Is it just like knee pads? Do you remember?
I mean I would love to watch the training montage of you getting into sliding because like the
whatever guy you found would go like oh just knee pads huh? That's what you're thinking. Well
go ahead and try and you get your ass handed to you but then slowly but surely you become better
than him. We will try and whose injury will get blown out first? My knee or your reoccurring Achilles
tennis injury. My tennis. Well they've healed since I haven't been playing so those are doing
alright right now but we'll see when I'm sliding for sure. When the Civil War does happen,
sliders everyone half of America will become a slider. There's just gonna be so much of it
everywhere. It's gonna get weaponized. It's inevitable. Yeah. But just duct taping washers.
You don't think half America's accidentally already duct taping washers in their hands as we speak?
Because if they take guns away what do we got? Sliding. And we washers. And if you can't slide
the children will just shake a heavy can around. But the fourth world war will be fought with washers.
Six Flies you probably won't return to maybe. I mean I just love being at a theme park so if
somebody wants to go I of course I'll go but um Universal I mean I don't know do you want to
talk about Universal? Yes. I loved it. You had a great time. You guys not go to this one together.
I thought a lot about Mike though. Oh that's nice. Wasn't the same there. Did you think of me?
I was thinking of you. That's nice. For sure. No I swear. But that felt a little like stiff
like thinking of like that seems like passing or like not without not with a lot of like feeling.
I'm talking about like powerful adoration. Oh you're talking about.
I mean I don't want to lie. I don't know. Have you seen the lake house?
No. It's much too bad. Are you talking about a generic lake house or the
the hunter race? Talking about the lake house Mike and I are gonna buy.
I was talking about the movie. I mean I'm into the lake house uh buying it that is uh but I I want
to shout out real quick the Margaritaville interaction I had at City Walk before because
this was what I was high about the whole time. I told Jason this already. I was sitting outside
by the fire pit at Margaritaville waiting for uh two friends to show up and an employee of
Margaritaville rolled by and he said hello Mr. Carlson congratulations on the baby. Welcome back
to this sector and he kept rolling. He kept walking. Whoa. Wow. And I was like wow. This he
never came back never talked to me again. Whoever this was good work sir. Geez. Wow. That made me
feel great and crazy at the same time. Very Truman Show. Sure. Yes. Whenever the actors are
trying to get messages to him. Yes. Yes. So I was congratulated on the baby but then also a City
Walk saga reference thrown in. Wow. Yeah. Really. Like a king. Yes. I did feel like. You were a VIP
somewhere. No one was there too so when I kept when I told my two friends they were like uh okay
that's cool. I was like no no no but you did you hear what I said? I said sector and sector is a
reference to when we did. We did 19 episodes about City Walk. They like it and they still talk
about it and they say the song. He used our linguistic choice. What? What? He used our language.
He used our linguistic. Oh sure. Yeah yeah. He used our term. Yeah. Our term. Like speaking Navi.
So I was uh obsessed with that interaction the rest of the night is what I'm saying.
Yeah. So your brain your mind was occupied. That's what I'm saying. I was occupied. I
like I can't I feel like I brought it up later in the night too even like just like but you
guys saw that like or you heard that that was cool right and they were like yeah it's cool or no I
ran into my my sister came later and I told her about that and she was like oh oh yeah.
Oh I had a lower key version the other day at Avengers campus. I was at the pin bar and someone
popped up and said hey I like the show can I get a picture and then they just disappeared as quickly
as they appeared and then I drank a beaker full of hard seltzer. Did you say no to the picture?
No I said of course you didn't have. Oh okay. Yeah. Why are all our fans running away?
Makes it harder to prove. Yeah. We need to take a picture to prove that it happened. Well they're
athletes. That's why. Oh. I just figured it out. Yeah. Oh wow. I had a plastic test tube of
hard seltzer with an obscene amount of boba in it and no straw. I looked around and no one was
being given a straw so I just ate a few mouthfuls of boba at the end of the drink.
I have a question. How many of our listeners have ever listened to this podcast while doing
the battle ropes? The two big ropes that you was like do this. Like how many people have ever
listened to podcast the ride while just ripping on those battle ropes at a gym or in the back
your backyard or something. There's wrestlers who listen. Could be a wrestler. There are a few
wrestlers who listen so I guess that is possible. It could have been the wrestlers. Charles do you
do the ropes? You're in good shape. Would you do the ropes and listen us? Thank you for saying that.
I absolutely would. Have I know. That's too much to ask. I think there's a bigger question of has
anyone ever listened to a podcast while doing the ropes? That might just be the case in general.
Yeah, Rogan. Exclusively Rogan. You're right. I take it back. I wasn't thinking that way.
And then everyone everywhere like they go like damn social justice warriors.
Right. Yeah. I was thinking of like POOG. What? POOG it's Caperlands podcast. I was thinking of
rope people would not listen to. Rope people. Rope people. There's some doughboys listeners I bet
who do the ropes while they listen to doughboys. Yeah, they live vicariously because they should
not be eating that. The food they cover. Oh I see. Yeah. Yeah. You don't think they roll a McDonald's
and then do the ropes to get rid of the excess. They earn the McDonald's with the ropes. I guess
that's true. By the way thwarted earlier from getting an adult happy meal. Oh yeah you waited
too long. I waited too long. Huh? Who thwarted you? The app. I checked like 10 in the valley.
There's like 10 close by. I was at McDonald's Monday morning at 10 38. You were. You
texted me pretty early. You rope dropped. A grimace toy. Now this is our ropes. It was you
rope dropping McDonald's adult happy meals. That's correct yes because I wanted one of the
the new weird toys that look like it's melting. But it says until the end of the month so I'm
assuming they'll restock at some point. It's a good question. I don't know if they will. There's four
different weird toys. Do you guys know what I'm talking about? I've not looked up what the adult
happy meal toys are. There's I it's I don't know what it is something called cactus plant. There's
some sort of like art designer McDonald land toys with grimace, hamburger, birdie, and then a
character I've never heard of. Not Ronald. Oh wait where they have the multiple eyes? Yes multiple
eyes. They look they look scary. It's like a street wear collaboration I think. It's like when
a unique low was doing like sesame street clothing but they had like X's over Big Bird's eyes and
you're not sure why but like it's cool I guess. Okay. So I got a grimace with four eyes. Well
since we're talking about this sort of thing you as you guys you went to Horror Nights.
Did either of you collect all the custom NFTs to show your Horror Nights fandom powered by
Hyper Mint? I have a few of them. Powered by Hyper Mint by Moon Pay?
Oh I'm seizureing from those words. I would have gotten on the moon on the website you see this
graphic that says ready player me create your avatar. Ready player me? You could get so the
Horror Nights thing this year was that you would scan and you would get an NFT for every maze.
I will say this I couldn't find the QR codes for a lot of these mazes so I ended up with maybe two.
How did you know this? I didn't see any evidence. You asked a good question. I heard people talking
about NFTs and now you're that's I understand now. I'm trying to remember how I heard about it. Maybe
Instagram or something and I got very like oh man I'm gonna get all the NFTs and then I got two of
them and forgot and then there were signage was not clear. There's also a limited drop of
$185 Universal Monster hoodies. How much is it? $185. Do they look cool though? They look all right.
You can kind of see them. The McDonald's this is a trend because the McDonald's adult happy meals
also coincide with a website where you can buy like $60 McDonald's shirts. Hip like art McDonald's
shirts. So McDonald's is really doing it. Yeah some of my favorite artists work for McDonald's.
That's it's always been the case but now more than ever. Sure freelancers. Is capitalism doing
good stuff? That's again. Art jackets. And the uh now now this is not a hip this is just a classic
they're bringing back the the buckets. Remember the bucket the classic McDonald's buckets.
I'm not gonna make the same mistake with the buckets. What mistake? I slept I slept on the
adult happy meal. Jason wanted one of the toys. I was going to Disneyland the next day. I was like
I should not eat a Big Mac value meal. A Big Mac adult happy meal. Could have gotten nuggets.
Could have gotten nuggets. Yeah it's like a 10 piece nugget. That's way too many nuggets.
Put them in the freezer. That's true.
So yeah the buckets are coming back which is fun. But yeah I have grimace. Fun. Fun. Oh I said it.
I think listeners should take 10 shots every time you say fun.
10. Let's see what happens. Let's see what happens to that Patreon. Yeah.
Oh no all our pay has been docked. I don't know you know if the credit cards keep renewing then
oh that's a terrible thing to say. You know it's weird a lot a bunch of our listeners died but the
credit card kept renewing. And they had no way in their lives to cancel the credit card.
And people thought they were alive because they were paying for this Patreon for years.
They're probably fine. All their OnlyFans and Podcast the Riot Patreon just kept
clicking away. I'm getting concerned that they died. Somebody check somebody log into their Patreon.
They always give someone your Patreon passwords in the event of your death. And your OnlyFans
password. And your OnlyFans. Yeah. You take out life insurance. Send us your OnlyFans passwords.
We're gonna isolate that clip.
Next week on Podcast the Riot. Send us your OnlyFans. Password. All right so what horror
nights? Highlights? Yeah. Stuff you liked? Well I'm trying to think yeah the NFT is kind of a bust.
Wasn't so fun like I thought it would be. Fun. Fun. The big kicker do you want to just go right
into the big picture? Sure. Do you want to work your way into it? Is the kicker what I think it is?
Baby you better believe it. Is it the weekend? Yeah. It was great. I wish you could see the
I wish you guys could do the weekend at the very least. It was fantastic. Because I love okay so
what I love I've said this many times on the show. I like a loud douchey pool party where the music
the bass is hitting and I love the outside of the weekend's maze because they're blasting it as if
it's like a Vegas pool party. So do you get this any better than we do? We've never understood why
you like this. I actually I hate that but but I get but of course I can access the irony you know.
I don't even know I mean there's irony there but I don't even know if it is irony. I think I was
trying to analyze this too because we've tried to figure out what it is and why I like it. I like to
go to almost any concert doesn't matter if I know I won't pay necessarily but if it was free and I
don't have anything to do I'll go you name the band I'll go. Okay the Beatles. I'm there. I'll see them.
Okay a Beatles tribute band. I did it a month ago. John talks about himself. John talks about
John's death in the third person. Yes but also when we're talking about Transformers a ride that
pummeled you I think I there's a I have like a sensory like I like a lot of stimulation. I like
to check on the phone. I have all these alerts. I think my brain is better when it's getting hit
with a lot. You're a fast boy. I'm not saying I'm a fast. Oh a new term. I am a fast boy but I think
it's probably like to try to keep the bad thoughts out or something like keep it away keep getting
pummeled with stimuli and a variety of stimuli so I don't have to like sit with myself for too long
and I think it extends to like Transformers getting the shit kicked out of me on that ride.
A part like a pool party where you're just music is unbearably loud. I don't want bad thoughts.
I'm a fast boy. Stimulate me. Yeah. Sounds like an awful club song. I don't like bad thoughts.
No we're gonna sample that and make a beat out of that. If somebody in the audience could sample
what Scott said and I think it's done now. I think it's already been done. I think that would be
a good point. I'm gonna run for president. And then if it ends with Jason saying send me your
OnlyFans password that'll be the end of it. We gotta go picture. I think we'll have a hit on our
hands. So I think that's what it is. I think that's it. Again I would not do that like three days in
a row at Vegas but I like one couple hours there. I mean I don't have an opinion about the weekend
at all. Like he's somebody that's not really in my consciousness but then when I was waiting in line
I was like oh wait I actually like all these songs. The songs are all pretty good. I don't go out of my way to listen to them but if they're just on yeah I'm like oh yeah these are
yeah I'm like but the the vibe of it was pretty like chic for a haunted house and it was it was very
VH it was very like MTV movie awards. That was the energy of it. Yeah yes that's yes like yeah because you
would see like in a big big elaborate stage picture for a performance with like dummy weekends or
something and there was like full of the maze was full of like fake weekends and dead weekend. Little
Richard weekend looked a lot like Little Richard. The hair especially. It was a weird like this is actually
Little Richard. They bought like last minute Little Richards and we're like yeah this will have to do.
And it's like that you go into like a club room and there's like a lady dancing and then she
gets her throat slashed. It was just I didn't know what to expect. I was like the weekend that's
going to be my least favorite room because who cares. I mean thing because who cares about this
you know this just feels like America like this is just America. See this is where we're different. I
heard weekend maze I go it's gonna be my favorite one and I was right. Well because I couldn't even
imagine what that would mean you know that so but then the fact that it had this sort of 80s like
it felt like a clubby like 80s music video. Yes that is what it was. With lots of lasers and your
lots of mirrored things. A big casino like a big slot machine all of a sudden you walk in there's
a big slot machine like evil slot machine. It was so elevated for a haunted house it looked so good
and then there was a whole plastic surgery. There's sort of like an LA nightmare too like a lot of
there was a woman that was like carving out a man's face and then being like he's so hot and just kept
saying he's so hot over and over and over and I was like all right kind of this is kind of cool
actually I like this. So that was good delivery. That was very good. Horror nights the lorry the
Jamie Lee Curtis groundlings edition was great. Got some equity people in there you know some
sag people. The big highlight too for the weekend maze is that you go in the Super Bowl rooms you
go through the Super Bowl maze mirror rooms with the jiff we've seen the jiff of the weekend
where he's like lost and putting his arms up. Yes okay and it's so fun to be in the Super Bowl
room. It's about is it the most iconic moment or is the most iconic room because there was the Dr.
Dre Snoop Dogg when they had rooms like there's little set pieces. You're asking what is the most
iconic Super Bowl room? Yes that is what I'm asking. Because there's been a couple of these lately.
Yes that is not Timberlake because he came out of a room and it was it was boring in there.
You're right. He's at the bottom of the list. Was Katy Perry in a room at the Super Bowl?
She had the shark we know the shark. She must have been in a room at some point in her life.
That's true but on camera in the halftime of the Super Bowl I don't think so.
Aerosmith and Britney Spears and in sync no rooms just on stage. Rooms are new rooms are in the
less Super Bowl rooms are in the last four years. Yeah Prince was not in a room. Springsteen not in
a room. We didn't have the technology you could only film from up above. Yeah this was this is
the first I guess I was excited because it was like it's not just you're going to be in a room
you've seen a movie now you're seeing a room that you've seen on the Super Bowl. Yeah so that's what
is exciting about it for me. A different type of room. Yeah a different type of room. I feel like
the room hit you harder than the room hit a lot of other people. That's possible. Jason what did
what did you think about this room? I thought this house I thought. No no no the I mean the
weekend. Were you ever like the room? I clocked the room. I did clock the room. I remembered it
from the Super Bowl. His other big performance summer 2020 he did the MTV was it the I think
music video awards and he likes the video music awards video music awards VMAs and he
takes the year was kind of um he was on the top of this building I looked it up it's called the
Edge it is a hundred story skyscraper in New York and he was like stumbling around like the the
helipad and then a helicopter was also circling him in the air there wasn't a ton of new items
in the summer of 2020 there wasn't a lot of new media so it was just like oh yes I don't even know
what this is I've not seen this oh it's great okay go home and watch it he's always on top he was on
top of the Hollywood sign with Lana Del Rey too right wasn't that I think that yeah something like
that he's gotta get down I also heard uncut gems with the weekends and is he in the gyms isn't the
way at the weekend in uncut gems that's Adam Sandler oh I said the star oh yeah you idiot
yeah it's the weekend am I crazy audience is gonna tear you up for that one dude I could see how you
thought that though I forget where where I heard this I feel like I read it a couple of places at
this point but like the opening night uh someone went through the maze and when they came out like
someone else was like hey you know that room where there was a few weekends like stabbing people or
something uh one of those fake weekends was the weekend sure like that was actually him yes weekend
he's having the like the thing with Sandler's girlfriend in uncut gems in the bathroom
oh okay with Julia Fox Mike I knew that I was playing pretend that was a trick you were in it
it was that was a haunt for you oh I'm scared I was scared I was being gaslit yeah the weekend
that was the highlight I mean the after our hours bar did you go did you see it what's the no what's
the after hours so they oh above Jurassic world above Jurassic world we so yeah I couldn't even
look at it was so busy it freaked me out I got really excited because they had turned it into
like a neon red bar of some kind which of course it wasn't anything that special but they called
it the weekends after hours bar so I that was enough for me we I was like yeah let's go run
up the stairs the line was yeah it was crazy insane did you get in no well because like there's no
time to do anything else yeah so literally I was like I will wait for this but the problem is we'll
run out of time I saw a few videos of people who would go on and recorded houses and stuff on media
night I think was the ordinary adventures one day they were like the wait for the weekend bars 90
minutes it's about there was like the longest wait for anything yeah but they did bring pizza fries
out to Hollywood oh I didn't even know that yeah this was a thing that people were talking about
this is a Florida thing it's a Florida thing we hadn't had before it is french fries with
marinara sauce and mozzarella and pepperoni and you could get it at the after hours now yes and
apparently was only at the after hours bar this year that's also such an inconvenient like the
balcony of the Jurassic Park restaurant it's not the easiest like crowd flow location yeah that's
true but it's a great location oh great location like it's a beautiful dress patty I would get
married there yeah you're absolutely right it feels like it's a little bit of Hawaii paradise
yeah right and right in born LA right I really like it I don't need to go there do you know any sort of
girl boss-esque scientist who could perform the ceremony someone who's seen murder yeah
it made her stronger would love to go back to our old place of employment someone who adopted a
cloned girl and moved to the forest with her old co-worker the terror tram oh we gotta talk about
that's maybe my second favorite thing really I didn't they could have been it could have been
they could have fleshed out more but I really liked yeah the nope area was amazing yeah that
was really cool but then you're going so the terror tram it takes you if you don't I mean
you were a tram and I worked the terror tram when I did I've never been to a
haunt just as a attendee but I did drop people off to get scared well when they drop you off
you this time around you walk through a lot of just kind of like it was weird how low quality
a lot of it was there was an area that was just cutouts of like cats just pictures of cats and
then there were people dressed as cats scaring you and there was just a track that was just like
like over and over and it was like this is not the horror nights I love and then you get and then
you get good coodles and you get to this I mean it is it's incredible that you get to walk through
the psycho motel it's just incredible that you get to like that feels that's awesome that you're
able to just walk around so psycho motel so yeah you get on the tram it's like a normal like tram
that they do for the tram tour where they show you the movie the magic of the movies
but they've got new video and they introduce you to a new character
that they put that they say is like an old universal character I think they've perhaps done
it before this character has been there before I was googling and there seemed to be a history
in a way that made it seem like this is not all new to the internet okay so I apologize
coodles is presented by Eli Roth as well oh from the twisted mind of Eli Roth for the visionary
the dark visionary mind to be like all right uh so there's a clown named coodles scott I don't know
if you this is this a little do you want to look him up maybe see if you would find him scary
but like coodles they're like oh he was an old clown around the this was he on the set or was
he in the tram he was like the fun tram mascot I believe they're talking about something like that
oh they're reaped they're presenting it like in the 60s or something there was this fun character
yes okay okay gotcha um and then he likes to he like went missing and he started killing tram
operate tram tour Scott and Allison mm-hmm those were their names because my my tram lady was like
and if we see Scott and Allison and yeah then they dump you right in front of the start of a maze
and there's coodles was right out there I thought they were gonna hide coodles but they don't he's
just they don't hide coodles yeah yeah he's just waving to you and then you pretty quickly walk
like through the Bates Motel yeah up to the house uh Bates house I guess I always think about how
crazy it is that there is a house like just on top of the hill that looks down at that war of the
world's plane crash just the back oh yeah if you look out the back yeah yeah just see somebody lives
there yeah I mean it's amazing yeah that's your view and then at one point in time probably the
owner of that house had just like picturesque yeah you with the valley and then back we'll go
one morning to a plane crash oh god it's been smoking every day since smoking plane crash uh
so yeah you walk through the Bates Motel you're getting scared coodles like there's many people
playing coodles spoiler alert uh you're getting scared like people coming in and out of rooms
like that's all pretty fun and then you walk up and they ask you do you want to take a photo
with Norman yeah I saw some people doing did you of course I did I love to take photos with
characters uh and they give you a very specific instruction that I did not hear they said do not
kiss Norman and I said hell no I'm kissing the man on the lips and I gave a bugs bunny style kiss
I grabbed his head uh they said do not do not step on the stairs I did not hear this
I walked like next to Norman almost on the stairs and Norman Bates in character goes don't stand on
my stairs wow and I go oh Joe I'm so sorry I'm so sorry but then he stayed there of course and
took the photo so and and I could feel why because the steps are not like they feel rickety I don't
know why they wouldn't make those stronger I don't know why they wouldn't fix it but it definitely
felt like you you were like it could break right through that's probably why that'd be kind of fun
if you broke fantastic if I spoke with broke the psycho house if it all collapsed off of yes like
how's the guys like boltergeist imploded like boltergeist leaving only you standing like it all
collapses perfectly around you uh-huh whoops so you get to meet Norman and take the photo with him
which for horror nights he really should be attacking you if I had a gripe I understand
it's fun to take a photo with him but it should be like you take a photo with like mother's skeleton
right he attacks you earlier yeah it's also you he's one of those characters where Anthony Perkins
is just so Norman Bates that it's not an interchangeable it feels there's something
about how he just looks like a realtor or something there's just something about him that
didn't look let me find the photo let me see how what the like how the likeness I mean I don't know
who you got but my Norman my Norman was a little is that why you didn't take the photo because
you're like this doesn't feel right yeah it's it's amazing they do find a good amount of people
to do that it's really specific I mean he's kind of just a guy but like I don't know I've seen way
better slender pale I wonder if they have like a lot of wiry game in who moved to LA need a job
some six foot five are you going through your roly dex who do I know who do I know who could
be a couple someone else I'm trying to think somebody help me out here who did a little
David Schwimmer perhaps a little oh well no you know he's actually he's not bad that's not that's
not the kind of guy how many knives do we give him on the norm and looks he gets eight knives out
of 10 he looks like somebody I know supporting cast member he's got the pomade like hair like
yeah yeah yeah my guy was like a Dylan Baker type it wasn't wasn't the same uh-huh a Dylan Baker
character yeah would work with that happiness house yeah when are we gonna have the movies we
want no john luvitz's corpse oh no he was so sad the ladybird house wow house we can hear them
fighting but also making up and getting along gummo ride it out ordinary people
colon in ordinary people ordinary people rising so then you go from the baits house you go to war
the world set and I can't it's that's before the cats I agree with you the cats part is very
confusing yeah the cats and then bats and then you and then you walk down the hallway that has
pictures of bats and then there are men with bats yes they're just like yeah yeah so you're just
making any connection okay I don't yeah I like that we were that we were outside I think I was
like you know it's a nice night it was a nice night my night was less than nice but then you get to
you get to nope land and that was amazing it's the whatever that's called the town yeah it's the
like Jupiter's clam yeah yeah and it's all but it's it's it's nope mashed up with the us
the us care like the us jumpsuit people are out with the scissors because you can't really do
anything with like nope is about looking up in the sky you know right scare people for those
creatures are pretty delicate and hard to reproduce in any meaningful way really pull out some stops to
make a spaceship yeah complicated with the shots even just from the trailer it's all open spaces
and pastures and mountain towns and yeah so good move they yeah they put the us and us was one of
my favorite mazes whenever that was I loved the us maze and also I think was was Jordan interviewed
on the tram too before I'm trying to think they showed a clip of the month the zombie monsters
which yeah also they promoted zombie monsters on the tram oh interesting um and maybe there was
like an interview with Jordan there was like a cut up featurette of him talking about all his movies
yeah yes that's right energy yeah so what I really want to talk about is my pal rob zombie and his new
passing the torch I'm retiring I know I had a good run there but I I know it's not getting
better than that no one can fill my shoes like did they ever do this I'm asking more questions
I don't only answer to uh did they ever was there ever part of the terror tram where they took you to
the monster's house which is on the wisteria lane it's a little far yeah wait because then you're
hoofing it up yeah the hill that's the hardest part to walk and you got to dress it up but you've
got to redress it like the monster's house yeah do we know maybe move it and rebuild you should know
this which desperate housewife lived in the monster's uh this was literally my audition and
I don't oh no it was so hard for me every time I'm sure I've said this before but just like
remembering and then and then the blue house is the home of brie played by marcia cross is that
one right did I get that right yeah I don't know that the details are right but marcia cross was
the actor there was who played brie or was just on the show what's that was terry hatcher yes terry
hatcher is one of them I don't remember her but this was all required there's things as a tour
guide that you can say if you want but they like really cut a deal with desperate housewives you
have to say all of these names the actress and the character and and the house and god I like I would
just melt down having to remember these five names of a show I don't watch anytime I was on the tram
that would usually felt like there was a little bit of a buzz every time we go down with stereo
that felt like for a while that was the draw yeah oh wow okay this is the golden girls house too is
that there no that's disney that was disney world for a while even though it was really weird
because the golden girls predated the theme park so like wait a minute why is it here they built
like a fake golden girls house yeah for the exes in the house because it would have they make the
show if they didn't have this there was other shows that were well wisteria lane I can't remember
them scott you should know all of them of course uh animal house might have been the monsters house
too the monsters house was repurposed yeah yeah it was I know that for a fact I know that and then
they were also I was there when they were this is another story I've told before uh they were they
had built a new house at the end of wisteria lane for the mockingbird lane pilot for the singer
fuller monsters jerry o'connell show so I was they were like and now we're building a new
monsters house for this new show called the mockingbird lane I have no memory of this
I was like it's come up it's only come up a lot of times lately we just keep we just love the
look we're all big brain singers it's obviously you want to talk about it as much as possible
I just I'm sure we've talked about I just wanted to know which desperate house wife
lives in the monsters house that's all I want to know that's why I asked the question
and if you could walk into the house on a trip to her tram that would be fun maybe if the zombie
movie is popular what's the zombie movie the rob zombie monsters movie you tell me you all would
know more than I do it was in the top 10 what else I don't think there's any more green lights
left in LA after um that movie well they moved in the croatia where they shot right right do you
anybody can film whatever they want as long as they go to croatia there was a uh I'm trying to
think just other other hits real quick uh they had an they had a few more like original may
usually it's all all ip they had an original I should look up what the name of it the hotel
one I like that one which is cool and they had like original characters yeah and like it was very
tower of terror like very old time hollywood serial killer who kind of looked like two-face
and he would uh just attack you in every room I have his name somewhere let me find it sorry
I'm trying to think of I'm busy I'm still trying to find out who lived in the monster
I'm also working on that everybody's looking up shit we gotta be here we gotta be present
I'm putting this down Dan you can look up what you want I'll find it later this is for me I'm
pulling myself out of this I'm looking everybody back in the eye not gonna we're all looking at all
of us glued to our that's fine when you get when you we do the when we do the episode where you
do the whole tour you will have to have that piece of information oh that I am gonna feel the same
pressure I felt in 2006 and then uh like it's still right now in my head one of the names is
Paula and I don't think there's a Paula on Desperate Housewives that's Paula D her
brief sitcom was filmed can we punch this because we've been teasing this for years that scott's
gonna do the full tour as an episode can we just get one of our friends who are currently working
on the lot and just we just jump in a golf cart and we just shoot a video of you doing it on a
golf cart for us sure that would be that's hey that's I'm there it's up to one of our lot friends
okay how good of friends are they you should yeah I think I think we can do it the whole tour
I think that's cute that's that's content that's nice that's what our tough athletic uh listeners
want to hear that's what them while they're doing the battle ropes that's some rope damn scott's
crushing these desperate housewives facts it's really motivating me to keep roping
so I'm still trying to find the uh the name of this there's like a there's an order the killer's
name is really fun and I've completely lost it so somebody's got to say well I don't know what
else to do because I didn't go there somebody else is gonna have to say something else it was great
I love I love haunted houses when they feel like real places and it felt like a real hotel like
you're that's what I liked about the us it's like you're in a living room yeah and especially when
there weren't people sometimes there'd be no scare actors in the room and you'd just be walking
through yes you know an open house and you're just like this is actually the scariest thing
the universal um hotel house that is where the walking dead used to be yeah we say that yeah and
man these lines at universal are out of control I don't know how people I was I we bought the like
express passes and I feel like people who didn't buy them only did like three things it's or you
just or you have to commit to it's we it's after hours bar and then you got yeah you have to do
yeah if you don't have the express you have to like get there either early or like stay pretty
late because if you stay pretty late everything gets the wait is at midnight though right not too
okay well then yeah maybe you can do it okay I finally have the name uh it is maximilian de vil
which couldn't be more on the nose that's definitely the first kruella's brother it's
kruella's brother maximilian de vil oh you know what's good I guess we don't ever point at me
I'm so sorry I got too excited no this now this is a how to do a mic compression it's a lot it's
the eager points there's a lot of that it's usually yeah your point it's usually it's and
it's usually yelling about a 60s sitcom or about like a soda that Jason hasn't had yet and he's
like I'm gonna have it tomorrow you gotta have it today well Jason will give me a point back
Jason you guys get in a lot of point we get with Jason that's what the listeners don't know
oh yeah I was gonna say oh okay am I the the did you do the death eaters oh walking through
harry potter yes yeah that was the highlight I take it back that was my favorite thing of like
all yeah it was up there with the weekend for me because they do like scary like death eater
people with the wands and whatever and there's all this like green laser there's a lot of smoke
you walk through like the back of diagonale or hogsmeade whatever it is and suddenly there's
like all this smoke and then there's all these death eaters and there's somebody doing like a
big performance yeah they've all got wands it just I felt I felt like I was in harry potter
it is it is good and it's not like nobody scares you yeah like nobody jumps out really but they're
like in like a little corner and like smoke is shooting up and the green is there and you can
just like hang out and it's like a very good atmosphere it just reminded me how much I love
harry potter I hadn't connected to that love in a while sure any reason yeah no just a preference
okay all right um to answer your question how do people just get to the I think if you uh really
want to do this and you want to spend two hundred dollars for one night you can get a frequent
oh yeah freaking fear or an ultimate fear pass and the ultimate fear pass you can go every night
of the month yeah and the other one you can go you only have 27 nights you are able to go how
much is the ultimate fear pass and will you do it with me next year and get the ultimate fear
pass it's 329 okay hopefully it doesn't go up too much next year when we do it
and we'll go every night oh yeah we have to so it's a different between it says up to 27 nights or
up to 33 nights so you're really only getting another week okay well next year we'll do it
and you guys you only have pizza fries for 27 nights in a month well that's your super size me
I'm trying to think what other real quick well uh mazes uh killer clowns was back
yeah we did that before scarecrow one I don't know oh yeah yeah but it was yeah the one thing
I liked was the birds poop on you you walk through yeah there's a bunch of birds and like waters
you get shit on yeah it's good did you guys see this giant crow creature like bird creature
with a top hat on stilts that was like yes skulking around that looked pretty cool you'd like you'd
have like that crow we uh crowena why you just you didn't even have to look it up you just had
crowena hold it sorry I almost forgot there's a very aggressive uh like flames that shoot out
when you're on like the main drag of universal which I like they're like blasting some sort of
like metal music usually yeah it almost feels a little like the wrong tone for it I agree I'd
never like metal ever but especially that's the side of Halloween that I'm like no no like yeah
like I mean it's like slash is wailing on the guitar I think that's what it is at least in
previous years it's been slash it should it should be like Danny Elfman energy in that area
like it should be like you know you should feel like welcome to the world of movies rather than
shredding on guitar lately have you seen this he's shredding looks like a pro wrestler yeah he's on
the battle ropes he's playing at the bowl in a couple weeks yeah I'd like to see that he has
bright flock like a like what is it shock red hair is that the word shock flock what is it shock
shock is a flock of red hair like several redheaded birds yeah yeah a few birds on his
head so he's got red hair he's very vascular he's so very baby and jack yes yeah wow he's doing the
not drinking water for like 24 hours to get vascular he's like playing like the simpsons theme
on like rock guitar or at least somebody in the band is rock guitar yeah you or as most people
put it guitar well you can play jazz guitar you can play rock guitar you can play prog rock
he did coachella and and there was the simpsons they started with the regular simpsons and then
they rocked it out but it was a metal simpson good for him so yeah he's playing the bowl in
a few weeks I'm not gonna go to that I'm scared he's gonna jump out and he is eat my face he
looks like a zombie now frightening but and again then he does like uh oh and go boingo song at the
end I take back that he looks like I would love to work with him he's a legend absolutely
I mean it really solidified in my mind that I just love horror nights horror nights is how I feel
about universal where like even though I've been a million times I still am transported to the movie
magic world and nots has like special it has like special diy like the whole if the whole town comes
together we'll pull it off like energy yeah yeah and then six legs just felt like like a coke
commercial from 1992 1992 it's the same coke it's the same pallets of coke the same machines
mrs taz is in the commercial with a bikini yeah you were helping you were helping build the
confidence of some very scared you were actually you were the scary element by just being older
than them and walking past them so you really helped them overcome their fear
they're already confused because all the fixtures and buildings are sun bleached everywhere they
turn they haven't seen a sherman williams paint paint store in their life uh uh real quick before
we go the biggest thing that I realized the night of the nots event was that there is now
a taco bell in the walmart by the portillo's in pointe park and this is very exciting to me
but you didn't get taco bell no you just hung out there I just was I stopped in the walmart
you cruise because we I this was if anyone saw this tweet this was true that I just I hadn't seen
my phone in an hour I went and looked at it and there was the text exchange oh my god has the
taco bell in the boyna park walmart always been there no response from us no it's new
you answered to yourself yeah yes I said wow it's new this is like all right straight to
twitter this is such a mic encapsulated this was not I was not being performative at all this was
literally just my reactions in real time and then scott posted it without my consent my consent to
twitter uh you know thought about asking but uh I'm not upset um I was excited to learn that there
was now there was something in there before and I forget what it was what I think it was a subway
why do you know what was in the walmart in pointe park I know there's I know there's things you like
in pointe park like nots berry farm the pirate show but the walmart is a walmart well yeah
statistically it's likely it was a subway in there most of them have subways in there I just have not
seen a taco taco bell in a walmart before so I was excited by that it's just that those brands
walmart x taco bell in x pointe park how was the energy was everyone excited it was not well
people were not there like they had the key they had the new like ipad system for ordering
but people were not ordering there hang on you went in but didn't get food from there well we
were going to nots and I knew there was some vented to johnny rockets but why'd you go in
just to see it I had to go to use the bathroom I know anyway and I also went in to check for the
toys yeah oh but I did I think I went in there mainly to use the bathroom but also I have to
check the toys and I did get something from my friend I found a mummy toy that he was looking
for tom cruise mummy no they don't do this okay no one's done those so you got an elizabeth moss
invisible man toy from another world one of the last new releases from the old world there are
rob zombie monster toys coming though and I have one of them for the rest of our lives yeah forever
10 a year we're all gonna get gifted them so many times well charles what's a what takes the cake
then it seems like universal is the winner overall it feels unfair because they are the most financed
entity but yeah it just doesn't it just I loved it I really loved it and uh everybody had fun
it was pretty funny in a very fundamental way I'm so curious I really this I I say all I know is
that I say pants also instead of like pants funny pants welcome to my world it also it really sounds
like a guy it's funny it's funny because they sound like one of like this like the
goring 20s characters I feel like yeah funny pants yeah Chicago was the birthplace of the 20s
those clowns pants get funnier and funnier and funnier every year um well so happy to have you so
I've been having back after all after all these years uh so happy to have you back charles
Rogers you survived podcast the ride uh let's exit through the gift shop is there anything you'd like
to plug I'd love to invite everyone in America to come see what I'm developing
on my laptop and google docs okay so if you see if you know what charles looks like and you see
him somewhere then you're you're fine with everybody over that shoulder yeah if you see me type type
typing in a cafe peek over my shoulder yeah if you're by the cow if we be on hillhurst
trying to get the green light you can just watch search party while you can
yes it's now we know all our listeners are so fast hurry up and read hv o max make sure you
watch it and it's true I've told you this this is speaking of speed it is the fastest I've ever
watched anything like as soon as I am eight times I better get the gist of these thumbnails so I can
bring it up uh oh yeah there's my friend oh yeah yeah all right so if I run into these people I
can say I saw it uh no I love the show so much just devoured it and that's the thing since you
realized you made you did a ride sequence if listeners if you haven't already watched
search party and you need an in that's true yes that it would you you that's a real dream come
true to get to do like a shot in a super elevated oh wait oh well I mean there's all oh my god
there's all of that but there's also which wait a minute we talked about the park is that the
the long island are we allowed to talk in the gift shop like this yeah we can we can meander we can
void her in the gift shop um was that at adventure land or where did you that was adventure okay okay
that's right because we talked about that with john gabris big like storied history of stuff a lot of
shooting done at adventure land yeah a lot of stuff is shot there I walked through I mean it was
fun we got to we got to have the roller coaster be active for the shot we like for like the master
shot so we got to run it for like 20 minutes and then like pa's wrote it just wrote it over and over
oh cool just for that shot yeah so that was that was cool wait yeah so I mean that's like
because we talk about all the time about things that film and theme parks yeah how would it how
do you feel to like have it it's yours for I don't know how long you were there well first of all it
was supposed to be called the happy place but um it was supposed to be like disney world but then
because of clearance issues there is a happy place in universal studios in osaka there is like
an area or something called the happy place and it did not clear so we had to call it merry merry
land which I was just like it's not nearly as meaningful um for the story and then it just
kept getting notched down from like I think we're gonna shoot knots very far I think we're gonna
like do like a day in southern California and it just yeah I mean like everything was search party
it all just that was like I guess we're just shooting in New York again but you set the bar
high and hopefully you land somewhere yeah exactly yeah so then we went settled for adventure
adventure land and uh yeah I mean it was fun we made up a fake uh fake theme park I was the one
I meant was the Jeff Goldblum the like the journey to the center of the year I mean I guess that's not
technically well it's it's like a reveal I guess but that's like extremely theme parky yeah yeah
in the that was green screen on the out you know like through the windows and then the reference
I gave the art department was um the back to the future ride when you're going through the canyon
of like through the volcano oh yeah yeah like everything prehistoric before yeah dinosaur
when you're in like the rock world a little bit because all your whole cast and Jeff Goldblum
who is tunnel Quinn that's so good uh you're it's a it's a descent into the center of the earth or so
yeah everybody and then he pulls the rug out from under you and he says it's just a ride made out of
centrifugal force and a bunch of heaters it's all the build up to a a restaurant yeah ultimately
much like mars 2112 yes this is our name very much circling back to Jurassic world that scene
that they eat dinner at is very like based on the Jurassic Park scene of them all eating dinner and
that and we did like projections like how the oh right oh yeah yeah projections in the room when
it's all like calm and logistics after like so your minds have all just been blown and now you're
you're doing Jurassic homage stuff with Goldblum yeah you ultimately just realize you want to do
everything you like as a kid that's the meaning of life yeah yeah i feel like not everybody did
not everybody is like i have resources let me do little kid shit so yeah congratulations well we're
all doing it on different scales i got that adult happy meal on 10 people are jerking off in their
cars the little mermaid lunch boxes so everyone's doing it on some level
so cool
and you're still you know you said that your interest in haunts began with doing them yourself
in your house and now you've come to a house and put goo on us which i'm still finding on
i just i like about 15 minutes ago i found a preserved pocket i didn't know about
secret scares after the fact uh anyway so thanks for thank you all thanks for being here so happy
to see you again and uh oh you can find us on all the socials at podcast the ride uh haunt cast the
fright merch is available in our t public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out
podcast the ride the cemetery gate or get one more bonus episode on our new tier which might have been
named by now i don't remember where i want to workshop that on the okay in the episode you'll
find all that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride um so still like haunts yes all right
that says it all that says it all yet fun forever dog this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by mike carlson jason charredin scott gairdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex
ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever
dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook