Forever!
Dog!
Warning! The following haunt cast is part...
Playful Spooks have interrupted our yearly tour.
A pranky spirit has detained us and demanded an entire episode to himself.
Kindly remain subscribed as we explore his legend, his triumphant return, his hat,
and an even spookier ghoul named Jared Leto.
Please enjoy your two-hour intimate look at the Hat Box Ghost.
It's Haunted Mansion 5 on Haunt Cast The Fright!
Does everyone know what to do?
You fucking don't, you don't again, I'll do it.
Seven weeks! No one did, I'm the only one who does the assignments.
I remember what we're supposed to do at the top of the episodes, and this one's important, guys.
I think you really let JC down, not Jesus Christ, James Cameron.
Because we need to honor that it is seven weeks until Avatar, The Way of Water.
And...
Here's what I'll tell you, I got in the car and I said, you know what you're gonna do?
I swear I'll listen to the end of the episode. I swear this is true.
I got in the car and I go, I'm listening to the end of the episode.
I got distracted by something, I started driving, I said, oh, Chromio has a new song.
And I completely forgot to listen to the end of the episode.
You'd rather listen to that than your own voice, definitely.
No, I understand in general, but I was leaving and I go, the last thing you have to do for research for the episode is listen to the end of the episode.
Completely lost it. Listen to the new Chromio song, which is good.
Great.
And then I fucked up. This is what happened. My name is Michael Carlson.
Well, no, it's not. It's Michael Norrell.
Michael Madson.
There, I gave it the oomph.
Thank you.
I'm Scott Grave Digner.
Yeah.
Oh, there's Jason Skeleton.
Yeah, I'm here. I was just mostly focused on like, all right, leave a little early so you can get a cup of hot coffee.
It's too cold. Too cold this morning for iced coffee.
So, you have iced coffee in the fridge, but you gotta go somewhere for hot coffee.
I've been thinking about this for seven weeks.
Yes, and partially because I think in the time since we, since the last episode, and this is our yearly Haunted Mansion episode, or will become that after some Avatar bullshit.
But last year we were just like, well, with the yearly nature of this podcast, like that's a year is a long time for stuff to happen, for seismic shifts to happen.
And it's been a long, long wait for Avatar 2, for any of these avatars to come out.
It's the only franchise that moves slower than our yearly Haunted Mansion podcast.
Right.
And, you know, in that year, I think I've, I think I got blue-pilled.
Really?
I got Avatar-pilled. I think much more so than I had been. I think I was starting to go that way, because that's my thing with the whole thing is like, I think the people, I think the people choosing Avatar and choosing to want to enjoy Avatar are the people choosing fun.
It seems like more fun on that side. And Mike, you were ahead on the curve.
Yeah, thank you.
With this. You were the only, you were the first one, I'd say, on this show.
On the show, yeah.
We thought it was inexplicable that you had the reverence for the mighty Akron.
You invented this phrase to tribute this franchise.
And that you brought the spirit of Civico.
And you never lost it, and that includes last year when we said, do we think it will be coming out? We were within weeks of this episode. You kept the faith. I thought there'd be a delay.
Right, because it's been delayed, what, a decade at this point? Avatar 2?
2009 was the first one.
Yeah.
Yes.
So thank you for that. That's a badge of honor, I guess, in a lot of ways for me to wear.
I believed.
I thought this was the year for sure, and it is. I mean, there's no way it's delayed at this point, right?
At this point, no, it's the big, like, Christmas release.
They made Tony the Tiger that I saw Frosted Flakes still. I haven't found the actual serial yet, but they wouldn't put out a serial with a tie-in to Avatar unless the movie was coming out.
Yeah, unless they were pretty certain.
And then, someone-
You can't reel that back. There's no way to pull that back.
We've gotten multiple pictures of it at this point, because, like, the first one we were, like, briefly-
We thought it might be a joke, yeah.
It's real, it's a Photoshop, but then someone sent the big display from, like, Sam's Club or Big Lots or something, and it's like, oh, that's real. That's in real life.
Yeah, confirmed.
Tony the Tiger Avatar box. That's so- there's no going back now. We are full speed ahead to Avatar the Way of Water, and thus, we, as a unit, as a podcast, need to act, and so we are, and that is why this December, Podcast the Ride will present Feliz Navidad, The Way of Winter, a Yuletide celebration of all things Avatar.
We're figuring out what that's going to be exactly, but we're going to- there'll be at least several things celebrating Avatar, Pandora, the world of Avatar, at Animal Kingdom, and anything else that seems relevant.
I think we're open to ideas, if there's sub-sex of Pandora world, if there's things- look, I think we've all spent, regrettably, little time in Pandora.
At least I have. I've only been there once. Mike, a couple times. Jason, I forget.
Twice?
No, I was there, I think the first time with you guys, and then I was there with my family around this time last year.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, if there's- I mean, you know, there's big stuff we got to cover, but other- maybe- and you guys might even know, are there little elements of that Pandora culture that we have not hit?
There's the bowls.
The bowls.
Yeah.
It's a Thule Canteen.
That's right.
Well, that could be it.
We could talk about the bowls, because I've had a couple bowls.
The popping, popping bubble, the boba?
I'm not a big fan of it, but we can talk about it.
Okay.
I tried it, yeah.
The popping, the popping bubbles.
We can talk about the floor, like the floor, or the- I should say the ground with the colors in it.
Yeah.
You know what I'm talking about? At night, it gets supposedly, like, gets very colorful. It doesn't get as colorful as I kind of said it would, but it's still interesting.
I haven't been there at night.
What?
The timing has never worked out for me to be there at night.
So I'm missing a big part of it.
You simply must go at night.
Let's not forget the other big part of it.
The bathrooms halfway through the line of Flight of Passage.
Oh yeah, good point.
And we've only done the line.
The episode we did about the ride was not about the ride.
That's true.
It's just about the line.
So we could still discuss the actual ride of Flight of Passage.
I mean, I don't know.
It seems to me like bathrooms is going to take precedence over the ride.
Well, that's, you know-
People know us.
You could make an argument that we should have done just the office with the big tank.
That should be its own episode.
Sure, yeah.
With the Unobtanium and the little, whatever, that little illusion or what?
That's not an illusion.
Is it floating like on Parker Selfridge's desk?
Is that a blue pill?
It is Parker Selfridge.
I believe it's his desk.
No, I don't think it is.
No, it's not his desk.
No, it's set way after.
In the time when Parker Selfridge was alive and on Pandora, we don't know what's going
to become of him in way of water and seed bearer.
But it's like that little illusion where there's like a magnet or something, I think, under
it's making the Unobtanium sort of move around or a different-
It's maybe just not even Unobtanium.
Maybe it's some sort of a disease or it's a COVID disease or something.
Something.
It's in a little jar.
That was the initiative.
So it got released from a lab on Pandora.
It's possible that COVID came from a lab on Pandora.
It's like when you're-
Dr. Augustine's lab is where the origin-
Not enough people are going after Dr. Augustine.
People didn't realize that that's actually the place.
That's the lab theory.
That's my lab theory.
No kidding.
I don't remember if Dr. Augustine, now I don't remember.
Actually, I think I forgot too.
Dr. Augustine's Sigourney Weaver, right?
Yeah.
And Dr. Ogden is the right exclusive.
All right.
We're embarrassing ourselves again here.
It's Dr. Ogden is the office in the line.
Flight of Passage could be the first ride where we do Flight of Passage 2.
Like in big fights, in boxing or wrestling where it's like two people meet again.
Yes.
Well, I still think we-
See, you guys are salivating for twos.
Let me tell you behind the scenes-
Oh, I wanted to say-
I always want twos more than anything in the world.
Indiana Jones and E.T. too.
Indiana Jones too.
I'm waiting for-
I'm so excited to do twos for things.
But yes.
I feel like Scott is the lone holdout of one.
I want to do twos yet.
Seems to say, new things are fun.
Aren't these new?
New things are good too.
Battle with Ogden and Mansions.
We ride these things for a reason because it feels good to go home.
Nothing else to do also.
And we haven't even talked about three.
Sometimes the rubber match is the most exciting one.
That's true.
You're right about that.
That's right.
So we'll brush up.
We'll make sure we get the right names for whose lab is which.
Well absolutely.
It's been a long time.
We will get our act together.
But truly listeners, if there is some subsect of Avatar, Pandoran culture that we need to hit, let us know.
Because Feliz Navidad will be here before we know it.
Okay, great.
That's very exciting.
Yes, Jason?
Let me ask you a question.
All right.
And I don't want to spoil if a picture is coming.
But you sent us the Disney shop.
I didn't buy it.
You didn't buy it yet.
What are you talking about before you answer the question?
Someone finish the sentence.
The baby Navi Halloween costume.
There's a Navi baby costume I found on Shop Disney.
And I realized you've moved.
I don't have your new address.
And I was like, oh, I should buy it and send it to him.
And then I was like, oh, will it arrive for Halloween?
I think it was for a bigger baby.
So I was waiting because it wouldn't be ready for Halloween.
Okay.
So yeah, maybe next year when everyone says like Avatar,
like Double Fever or something,
because we're going to be so jacked up after a wave of water.
They're going to be ready for the Seed Bearer.
What's the next one?
Seed Bearer is the next.
Yes.
Is that right?
And we will be addressing in 2024.
That's in two years time.
I was thinking how with these yearly episodes,
it's funny how by it being at the very end of October,
we are now I think perpetually tied into a couple things.
Election fears.
Oh yeah.
We got midterms this year and we want this to go well.
We want Herschel to get in.
Very nervous that our boy isn't going to take it all the way like he did on the football field.
We are.
Yeah.
And we're rooting for Dr. Oz.
We are also agents.
Yes.
Memet.
What's his name?
Yes.
Memet.
We are also on the payroll of Turkey.
We are also secret.
We are agents of influence from Erdogan.
President Erdogan.
You stumped me.
I, I, Memet Oz has like very close relations with the country of Turkey and everyone's like,
that's not great for senators to be super close with other countries.
It's fun.
Look, I've only just learned about this man in the last six months.
I don't know about any of his previous dealings or I've heard something about a television show he had.
I don't know.
All I know is that he's a salt of the earth, Pennsylvania guy, just a real, the most regular Pennsylvania boy, which you should root for.
I am rooting.
I'm hoping he shows up at the world series.
My beloved Phillies go into the world series.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, that'll happen between now, right at the beginning of the year before next year.
Congratulations.
The day this comes out.
Okay.
Yeah.
So, so there's a lot.
Would you finish your thought?
We also have to, we're locked into haunts.
We're locked in a haunts recap every year now.
I'm just saying there's always, I think there's, there's some stuff coloring these haunted mansion episodes.
Yes, that's true.
There are fears about how elections are going to go.
And in 2024, God knows what the fuck will be happening then in terms of the big election.
And we're also going to be really nervous about is the seed bearer of the same high watermark as the way of water.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
It's going to be a rough episode.
I'm happy we got a minute.
Like, you know, cause this fit, like, like, remember how we felt in 2020.
That was crazy.
Yeah.
This, this one feels like at least, you know, there's, there's bad stuff going on, but like, at least we can take a breather on all that seed bearer stress.
Exactly.
Yeah.
The seed bearer that we can call.
And we know way of water is going to rule.
So we actually, we should take a nice deep breath, nice deep breath of water.
Let's all breathe in some water.
Breathe in some water.
Speaking of, there's someone here who that last year, this title could not apply to you, but this year it can.
We have our very own seed bearer.
Carlson, the seed bearer.
We say seed bearer.
Does that mean that you had a child?
I think so.
I don't know what it does in the film, but doesn't it?
I mean, it makes, you know what I was talking about.
I do.
I'm a father now, a seed bearer, if you will.
What should the woman be?
I was going to say the woman's probably the one who has the uterus is the seed bearer.
She bears, Lindsay is the seed bearer in this instance.
She'll be thrilled to have that title applied to her.
Yeah.
You're the seed bank?
The seed bank?
The seed shooter.
Is that the Prince song seed shooter?
Or no, it's a, oh yeah, he wrote it, sex shooter, but it's, that's a, is it Vanity or is it?
Apollonia 6.
Apollonia 6, thank you.
Yes, so that's true.
That's a difference from last year.
More of like a seed factory, I think.
Yeah, that's, yeah.
Oh man, yes.
I mean, I guess it's all student.
If you're lucky, you're a seed factory.
Yeah, yeah.
And you're a salt of the earth.
I'm a lot like, who's called a factory guy?
Dr. Oz is, yeah.
Look, I'm just a humble man with a seed factory.
I'm just trying to keep my seed factory in order and Brandon gets in the way.
Brandon wants to shut down the factory.
But anyway, big, big jumps.
These, I just think we need to track some of these things.
There's one other thing in the re-listen, and I'm sad you guys didn't get to hear this,
in checking out Haunted Mansion 4, something strange happens in it, which it is the first,
not the first time, but it is the first reprise of the endless Lake Nona argument.
There was the initial time that it came up and Jason was mad about Lake Nona,
and then it comes up in Haunted Mansion 4, and the strangest thing is it is clear as day.
You fully say, oh yeah, I got confused.
I confused the housing development, I confused the city with what Disney's trying to do,
and actually misspoke and I apologize.
You're saying it's resolved completely.
Completely resolved.
I admit my, yeah.
And then in May, it became the biggest argument in the history of the show.
I don't know what happened between October and...
I don't know, yeah.
God knows, God knows.
I'm just lost at this point.
Yeah, I initially thought it was just like when a real estate agent makes up, you know,
this is the cool new neighbor, oh well, everyone's moving to Franklin Village in Los Angeles,
you know, just makes up...
Well, that's not a new, that's been around for...
He's saying it as an example of his name.
As an example of marketing.
Yeah, it was around for a while, so I thought, I didn't realize there actually was a Lake Nona...
A thriving community where many listeners live.
Apparently.
I have...
Numerous wrestlers who can hit me with chairs.
I think if we wait a couple months, maybe we can get it going again.
We can just turn it over?
Think if a couple months go by, we can wait and do it again.
We forget all these things, we forgot Augustine and Ogden and we'll forget.
So embarrassing.
So that we can reprise...
This is somehow I'm less into doing part twos of episodes and more into just the arguments coming back.
Oh yeah, full argument episodes, yeah.
That's a good idea.
Man, people are probably wondering when we started actually talking about it,
about the mansion that is, I have some ideas, let's do it at the end now that I'm thinking about it.
Sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
I have a couple things I want...
Like different anger mating threats for all of us?
No, no, no, no, it's more mansion related.
It's you and I being punished if we don't do things right.
Interesting.
So we'll do it at the end, we'll do it at the end.
Oh tantalizing.
Okay, well you know, you're right.
Let's move things along and let's officially get into Haunted Mansion 5.
Here we go.
And folks, if it wasn't clear already, this is like when the ride stalls.
This is like when you get stuck and you hear the announcement about playful spooks have interrupted your tour.
And we are stopping in the place where you the most want to stop.
In a ride that stops on almost every time you're on it, what would the Omni Mover, it all has to stop if there's any issue in the load or the unload.
And we are stopping our tour right in front of the Hatbox Ghost.
Oh baby, here we are.
It's all Hatbox Ghost.
This is the app we, yeah, when we negotiated the terms of these episodes, this was very important I think to us to have an episode just about...
To you.
To me specifically.
Well, Jason, what about Jason?
Well, I remember there was a lot of hubbub about the Hatbox Ghost when he returned and they were kind of like, you know, really ramping up like the mystery.
What happened?
Was he really there?
Was he removed?
He's in the children's record about the Haunted Mansion and these drawings.
Did anyone see him?
And then like, so yeah, I think I agreed that like, yeah, we can dedicate to this guy.
The most popular ghost, I think.
The most popular happy haunt.
Yes, on the ride.
Could be.
There's the most story to it.
And hey, look, I mean, I had to wrap my head around it.
I had to like, K, I guess.
But you know what?
We've done, we've certainly done tributes to single characters.
You know, we've done botanicus.
We've done the dirty footed pirate only from Pirates of the Caribbean.
And, you know, if anybody deserves it, it's the Hatbox Ghost.
Yeah, sure.
It's Hattie, which I've seen.
I saw a number of places just referring to him as Hattie.
I'm anti Hattie.
When I started hearing that, I was like, that is cutesy.
I don't like the sense.
You know, I guess tell today we're talking about old Hattie.
It's a little familiar.
It's a little presumptuous.
Old Hattie.
I am not a fan of calling him old Hattie.
Thank you.
I don't like that.
I mean, I think this would come up and then I would just get like,
Oh, right.
What?
What do you mean?
Hattie over and over.
I mean, I'll call him Hattie on the episode because we're going to say his name a lot,
I think, just for variation.
Short hand.
Yeah.
But yeah, no, it's not my hatbox ghost is the way I like to refer to him.
The proper, the full, full formal name.
And look, I also, you know, I've had my issues in years past where there has not been like
maybe the momentum that we needed to actually start talking about things on the ride.
Yeah.
But I think that's the thing on the ride.
And I, by stopping and focusing on just one character, this is now,
we're now at the least in the realm of the thing that I'm fearing on these episodes always,
which is no, no, no, stop, stop, stop.
Right.
Like, well, there's no way.
Look, we're stopped.
I assume we, this will be, unless you're talking about twos,
we might fall right into hatbox ghost two before you,
but the sooner we get to it, I guess.
Well, I don't, I will say a lot of the mystery has since been said.
The mystery has since been solved.
Like a lot of like, what is he, what happened?
And he's been back for like seven years now.
And so I think we're, we're good.
You know, I think a lot of the young men is that do you not?
Jason, no, no, no, I've got plenty of Jason.
Are you feverish?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean?
Enough has been said.
We haven't even done the episode.
We don't know how much we discussed.
We could do a second one.
Are you crazy?
Well, I, I, this was the, the, I want to imagine year where I'm like,
well, this is kind of an open shop case fellas.
But I want to explain the case.
I want to talk about the case.
Yeah.
There's a, well, there, there's a bunch here.
Chronologically, where we have finished last year, we exited the attic.
And that is the point where in today's times you enter sort of a,
you know, kind of a void, kind of a like amorphous zone.
That's not like a clear.
It's basically exiting the mansion.
You're falling out of the mansion.
Yeah.
Well, technically not yet because the ghost is right before,
right before you fall the turn away.
And we were not going to talk about the turn that the, the turn.
Well, no, we can talk about when it turns to face the ghost.
We can talk about the, yeah, the doom buggy turning to face.
And I guess some of the, cause you can see them for some of the descent,
but only some as soon as you can't see the ghost anymore,
that is next year's territory.
But just chronologically it's we've exited the attic, but,
and that's, and we,
so we're in the zone where the hat box goes lives today.
And as Jason said, has since 2015,
since this legendary character was brought back,
but his place in the ride itself or so people believe,
and it's all a little ambiguous, the history of,
but like presumably he was in the attic.
He was where the bride was.
Okay. Yeah.
And the bride was over where the piano was the harpsichord or,
Oh, that's what it is. The bride was in a different place.
Yes.
Okay.
Because you kind of, you rotate,
I believe Tony Baxter was the one who said you for years,
you would rotate towards nothing for a second,
because that was where he was where the bride would like,
put your focus onto where a certain item was,
but there wasn't really any.
Yeah.
And now the harpsichord I believe is there.
Is it a harpsichord or a piano?
I saw it referred to as a harpsichord, but it could be.
I think it's a piano.
There's a piano earlier in the ride. Isn't there?
Yeah. Well, there's a, there's an organ earlier in the ride.
Victor Geist is playing the organ earlier.
Are you talking about someone else?
Isn't there another piano?
Probably another piano.
Okay.
But there, you know,
what do you think of it as a piano in the attic?
The one that the shadow is playing?
Yeah.
I would, I, I want to say that that is, I don't know for sure,
but I would want to say that that's like a tack piano,
which, which, which is the like jangly.
Yeah.
I forget how you give it the tack effect, but like it's, it's very,
it's very specific type of noise.
Like, yeah.
So yeah, that's where the bride was.
And he was, yeah, he was in the, he used to be in the attic.
Yeah. And the assumption being that that's the bride.
That's the groom.
Yes.
And his head is set.
The way the effects should have worked was that when her heart beats,
his head disappears.
And then reappears on the next.
Is that right?
Yeah.
They were like a kind of a.
It was supposed to be synced.
Wow.
With the heartbeat.
Oh, interesting.
Wait, and just to fully, I mean, I think listeners know,
but the intrigue in what was cool about this character and is cool about this
character.
He is a, a ghoulish figure.
Who, depending on when you see him, but possibly.
He's got a skeleton like head.
On the, in the place where a head should be.
And then there is a magical vanish and his head.
Moves magically down to his hat box,
leaving nothing where his head should be.
And this happens back and forth, back and forth for as long as you're,
you're looking at him.
And it's just a cool idea.
It's a cool, it's a very cool.
Illusion as it's done now and probably was intended to be a very cool illusion,
but it didn't quite work out.
It worked.
They said it worked in Imagineering with like controlled space,
but then when it was in like an open, a little more open area,
it just didn't work.
You could see both heads, I think at the same time, or it was just,
it just didn't look as cool as it did when it was in Imagineering.
It did not cool on site.
They build these things.
It was, it was built at the Glendale facilities and they build,
they make these things in these little cubbies and with like curtains that you
can pull on and like really control the environment.
But then everything else gets installed and you see it in context.
And I think you were also,
I think maybe the guests were so close to it that you could very easily see the,
the shifting of the lights and wow,
wherever they were actually doing that effect.
This is, there's a picture of Yale, Gracie, like fiddling with it.
And one Imagineer who kind of researched the Haunted Mansion said like,
oh, that's a test model.
That's not in the mansion.
This is supposedly the lone picture of it in the mansion that Doombuggy's found
this a while ago.
This is re, but a recent uncovering.
Recent uncovering.
And there's some very grainy.
Also recent.
Recent like super eight or 16 millimeter footage.
Yeah, there was a debate whether the ghost figure was actually on the ride or
not for decades.
Yes.
This is the lore that we're getting why there's a little more here than just,
he's a cool animatronic is that it became like, you know,
essentially almost at any point that you'd went on this ride from 69 to 2015,
when they did a new version of it,
you did not see this character that have boxed ghost unless well,
this is what was murky.
And I didn't, I never knew any of this or tracked any of it that like, no,
sometimes you hear, no, it was gone before the ride even opened.
But then internet discussion starts in the nineties and people are like, no,
I saw it.
I swear I saw it.
And other people say that's impossible in the chronology.
But, but people had, so it became like, well,
is this a Mandela affected situation or not?
Did people see it or not?
And I think it was pretty not, you couldn't track easily.
Tony Baxter claimed to have seen it. Right.
Tony was like there in the first week and he claims he saw it for sure.
And people, they ran through the mansion.
He said there's a video where he's going through the mansion.
I'm sure you've seen part of it. At least he's talking about like,
they got to go on it like for two straight hours when it opened.
Yeah. Hours and hours worked at Disneyland.
He's an employee and now legendary imagineer was a, an employee doing,
I don't know what, at that point,
I think he was not ice cream scooper.
I think he moved up from that at that point,
but he was something else. I don't know where he was in the park at that point.
Yeah. And so it seemed eventually confirmed.
It was there for cast member previews, maybe some soft openings,
but like a month or less it was there. And, um,
well, you know what? Hang out. We're, we're jumping to like,
this is the like, the, the like sleepy real stuff about it. Yeah.
The legend really, what was propagated for a long time was the idea that
this figure was so scary. Yes. This effect, uh,
so like shocking and important that it was too scary for the ride and had to be
pulled before really guests started to get to go to letters about this and
complaints at city hall. And they were like, we got to yank this.
It's far too terrifying. Even though, uh, I,
I saw something where it's like, well,
that head sculpt is also used a version of it is used on the hitch,
the one hitchhiking ghost, one of the hitchhiking ghosts essentially has the
same. Yeah. Yeah. Yes. So it's a very familiar looking character. Um,
but this, so anyway, you've got competing lore of like, oh no,
I think it just maybe didn't work out right versus no, no, no.
This was the scariest thing you ever could have seen. And, uh,
which is, you know, more exciting mythology, but also how, you know, look,
it's a, it's a scary effect. It's certainly very creepy and very off
putting, but like how could,
what version of that is so scary that guests are that adults are just like
scarred. They have to go lie down as soon as the rides over.
It's like terrifier too. Uh, right now it's just happening.
There's a grossest core movie with a clown. You know what I'm talking about?
No, I don't know. There's a indie clown movie. That's the,
the sequel to a movie called terrifier. And it's a really scary clown.
And it's making people throw up and pass out in the theaters. Oh, it's so gross.
And it just, I always get like, I watched a clip, someone posted of it.
And it is, it's scary when the clown knifes you in the face,
but like does a vertical slash on the face. That is kind of scary.
But then like the further shots, it's like, well,
you can tell that's not a hand. You can tell that he's ripping apart.
I think you should watch it and report back. Oh, I should. Yeah. Is it strange?
I haven't seen it. The first one is, but the second one's in theaters and it's
cleaning up. People want to go see this and pass out. Oh, okay. Yeah.
So I mean, that's probably also partly legend of it. Yeah. Like, oh my God,
if people are dying watching the movie, but also I do think it's super gross.
From what I hear like fifties kind of like the tingler type. Yeah.
Gimmickry that imagine a film so scary. Yep. Which is so this can't be.
That's the hat box ghost in 19. That's the hat box ghost.
Maybe times were different. Maybe somehow this was so, and after all the,
all the buildup, which we went over that this like there's legend kicked into
this ride before it even opens that years pass and that meant that building is
standing there with no label, with no sense of what it is.
Like what, and then like, is the, is the ride itself so scary that they refuse
to even open it? Yeah. Or is the building haunted? Like have people died working
on it? There is all this crazy lore and I think it all really crystallizes in
this character. It's an accidental perfect situation of like lore and then
it all converging like probably in the night, like yeah, nineties or something.
Yeah. I don't think there, I don't think there was a place for the, the myths
and the legends to gather pre internet. No, no. Like this must've been way less
of a thing in the, in the seventies, eighties. Yeah. You would have to talk to
a bunch of weirdos in person to get this stuff. Yeah. The letter column of E
ticket magazine was only so big, you know? Yeah. I do want to give credit to,
I think, you know, with the technology they had in the later sixties trying to
sequence a beating heart effect with like a black light coming up on a face and
then a tiny spotlight coming up in a hat box is an audacious idea. Like it is
crazy at that. I'm sure would be difficult, a little less difficult with
technology now, but like that is a crazy effect to try and do. And I think it
wasn't just people were so close. There was just too much ambient light in the
attic that it didn't get dark enough in the way that in a room full of blackout
curtains, it probably was dark enough for the effect to work. And I, it's so,
it's crazy that it is back now where I feel like the attic is only brighter. It
has only gotten brighter as technology has made lights brighter, but they're
doing it in a different way. Like you have to, I mean, this, like from the
photos that you can see of this Imagineer, you know, Gracie working on it,
it is like, it feels very much like the ballroom dancers, the, the, the ghosts
who are very like, yeah, right. Like the figure seems delicate to me, right?
Whereas now it's sort of this digitally lit, you know, you have the, the control
over it in the way you would the stages where they shoot the Mandalorian, you
know, you can like really accurately dial in level of brightness, but it's just
dim enough and it is kind of impossible to do in this analog way.
Here, by the way, this is actually, I think more terrifying. These are the
schematics of the original guy.
And now what you're showing us is like, this was some proof that it did exist
because there's also the question of was it ever there at all? And this is like
from a manual that proves, no, no, no, here's the framework of it. Like they
made blueprints with like really, you know, super detailed of what all the
parts of it are.
Yeah. And I, I, there was also a rumor. I hadn't heard this before, but in some
Jim Hill podcast or article that the link doesn't work anymore. He said that
Mark Davis said that I think the hat box ghosts became one of the Eagles in
America sings. I think the actual animatronic became this. And then other
people in line were like, I'm sorry, I'm afraid that's not probably not right
because he's just a bunch of tubes and a head, like tubes and metal rods in a
head, which makes the drawing that you're showing us very unsettling, but
because it's very, it looks very Mars attack alien where there's a creepy
skull. And then the only thing he's, he's just, he's skeletal. It's like, he's
just a tube man. It's those are incredible drawings or schematics.
I mean, this on its own unintentionally is like an awesome piece of art. Yeah.
Yeah. It looks like an old, like a, like a 1800s, uh, weird outdated medical
textbook. Yeah, for sure. It's this I, I'm trying to think when I learned of
this, it's probably it's at least I really only learned about it maybe a
decade ago. I think, did you know about this when you were younger? Cause you
were a little more into the magazine stuff. Not really. No, no. Yeah. This,
this kind of snuck up on me. So this I think is a perfect story because people
want to imagine Disneyland is real and alive and it's a fun thing to say that
there's some like actual mystery when it comes to this place and it's the best
version. I can't think of another story like this. That's as fun as this, like
there's all the different rumors you hear about Disney, the dark ones, uh, nobody
dies on property, whatever that stuff. But like, this is like the most fun
version of like, well, I don't know. Maybe it's blah, blah, blah. Maybe it's
this. Maybe it's like, this is the most fun before they brought it back and
before it was sort of recorded history. Like the most fun way to like speculate
of like some little fun, real, maybe it's real. Maybe he went away. Who knows?
You're saying this is more fun than the lamp. The lamp in our house. Well, the
lamp is the new hat box ghost is what I think now we can discuss the lamp and
did the lamp change overnight and didn't Walt actually ever see this lamp? It was
the idea. Did he ever enter it? Was it a type of lamp that they made when Walt
was alive? Right. Yeah. It's magic lamp that kept burning through the pandemic.
Walt said, if there's ever a pandemic, give people the lamp. They need hope.
Then the lamp. Yeah. So the lamp is the new ghost. But in a pre lamp era when we
needed some excitement. Because yeah, I mean, I never had actually tracked. In my
head, it was just, yeah, nobody's really sure if it was there or not. So before I
knew the timeline, which was interesting. And some of the lore and the
mythos comes out of the fact that, like I said, as soon as, you know, by
September 1969, like the second month of operation, for sure you go on this ride
and there is no hat box ghost. But if you were a nerd for this stuff, following
this stuff, looking at any ancillary media, you might have been like, where's
that ghost? Yeah, sure. They used the ghost. The ghost was by I saw an
advertisement with a cool like line drawing of him. And then there was this
record slash book. Like the record is a reading of the book and the hat box
ghost is in that. So he's in materials that exist outside of the right, which
might might have made people think he was in it. Like, no, I remember him
because there's that hitchhiking ghost that looks similar or he's in the record
or whatever. Like in my head, it was possible that it was never available to
the public to see and people were just conflating all of the stuff. Yes. And I
think like there's a lot of interview before when it was just like a Guillermo
del Toro is going to do a new non Eddie Murphy Haunted Mansion. He was the one, I
think, who really sort of brought up a lot of like, oh, it's about the hat box
ghost. If you don't know what that is, that's this thing. And he probably had
the record. He probably had all of it because he's got a house full of concept
art. Yeah, but he's got him saying he has probably a house full of like old
shit. I mean, he does have a house full of shape. He probably like has the record
and stuff enough to like have found the still kind of seldom examples of hatbox
ghost being talked about. Here's a quick clip just to play it of which I'm mainly
playing because it's Thorol Ravenscroft, my favorite voice, who's also one of the
singing bus. This is just his quick his mention in this storybook slash record.
He was a cloaked figure with an evil grinning face. A hatbox hung from his
hand. That's that. OK, it's not much, but if you're like that could the with the
attached image that could linger with you as a kid. And you might be like
somebody might have heard this in 1970 and then not gone to Disneyland until the
80s and thought, where's that go? Where's that hatbox guy? Well, it brings up a
good question to me. Is he the most popular ghost if he's he never got
removed? Is it is so much of the fun of him? Is it because it was decades of
being holding of withholding the ghost? You think he is now for sure? I know
legend. There was no legend. Do people care about this? Is does he become
because I was wondering, is there some world where he's sort of like the mascot
of the ride in a way ahead of the hitchhiking ghosts who now sort of if you
need to like represent it abstractly, who are you going to meet in there? It's
the hitchhikers. Maybe Lyoda. Yeah, I guess Lyoda is after the hitchhikers. But
yeah, hatbox ghosts might be taking the lead. But I'm saying does he take the
lead if they just use that original robot that when those pictures and it's a cool
effect and it works. But does he just become another one of the of the ghosts
and hitchhiking ghosts still are like kind of the big thing because people are
like they followed me home. They were in the mirror and interesting. You know what
I'm saying? Like he doesn't now he's been so showcased and now his robot is much
better than the other robots and he looks very cool. The only one who got one made
got a very cool robot and legend. He's a legend now because of that. Yeah. Is he
the legendary? Does he have his own podcast? The ride Haunted Mansion episode?
I don't think he does. Yeah, I think part of the story is important context
because it wouldn't have been as cool even if that if they're sort of like if
they'd figured out whatever the 60s jankiness was it probably would just be
as fine as the some of the stuff in the ballroom. So he would I'm sure
people would like him but I didn't have a few decades of like Chinese democracy
buildup. Very good comparison. Guns and Roses a long-waited. I think hatbox ghosts
delivered a little better than the eventual release of Chinese democracy. I think that's right.
Guns and Roses that has been out for 10 years I think. That's right. Yeah. 10
glorious. We all we revisit it each each Christmas season with our loved ones.
You know what it really if I could do another pop culture analog because it's a
character in a highly anticipated property who's it was far enough into the
like as far as anybody knew this guy's in it so he's in the artwork in the case in
the metaphor I will make that I'm talking about a character who there were
toys made of like this guy get ready to like this guy I think the hatbox ghost
is the constable Zuvio. Yes. Haunted Mansion. You don't know if you maybe we
should still do a glossary of Deep Star is Curious but this is who was supposed
to be in the initial in Force Awakens. In the first line of Force Awakens toys
that came out before the movie one of the characters was Constable Zuvio. A very
intriguing name like hatbox ghost. Yes. Like a constable. He's maybe in a trailer
I forget but people were there was a lot of constables Zuvio buzz before that
movie came out and then if you saw Force Awakens he's not in the movie. Don't
know where my friends friends of mine such as Buzz Buzz made a video for
Funny or Die that I liked which was like let's make something about everything
like everything that's going to we think is going to be on Star Wars based on the
seven things they've said and the great Josh Fadim plays Constable Zuvio maybe
the only on screen constable Zuvio. Oh wow good point. I think so. I mean he played
he's like kind of a high jinky guy falls over a classic Zuvio lie which I if his
Zuvio was in the movie I might like the movie more. Dave Filoni come on get Josh
to play Zuvio on one of these. Yeah. Josh Fadim not Josh Gad. No no Josh Fadim yeah.
Has Gad not had enough. Yeah no I mean I wasn't but you put Gad somewhere else I'm
just saying for Zuvio. I was just wondering when you talk about casting and nerdy properties
and you say Josh I go right to one place. I hear you. Make Josh Gad a different constable.
A new constable. That's what we want. Fadim is Zuvio. A bunch of brothers who are constables. Yeah they can be in the same
scenes together. There's a historic precedence with that with Star Wars 2 because the lead up to
episode 1 there were two two big lead ups one was Samuel Jackson is a character named Mace Windu
and I think he has less than 10 minutes of screen time in episode 1. That's true. And then the other character
who I think you could send proof of purchase away for and get it. I Mike you might know his name he has
like a cone head kind of head. He's on the Jedi Council. He's in it right. Yeah he's in it.
Why can't I think of this guy. He has a cone head. You could send away for this action figure and they were Dark Horse
comics also had like a four issue series so everyone was trying to read the key. Ki-Adi. Ki-Adi. Yeah.
I'm sorry Ki-Adi Mundi. Is that right. Is it. Is this guy's name Mundi. Oh wow. You're right.
Is it Mundi. I don't know. I've never heard it pronounced. I'm going to say this is wow. Star Wars is a Mundi.
Maybe there's a Clone Wars episode where somebody says his last name or his full name. Not as disappeared as Constable Zufio
but him and Mace Windu like leading up to episode 1 those who are the little like and these guys are coming get excited
and they're barely in the movie. The whole Jedi Council is doesn't have much to do. The whole Jedi Council Mace Windu gets much more action in the second and third.
Yeah and he gets to talk to Yoda at least. Yes. He gets like one on ones with Yoda at the very least but yeah Mundi doesn't get to talk to Yoda.
Oh man they don't give Mundi anything to do. Poor Mundi. Yeah at all is not. Oh man. Hey it's the light side and dark side at the World Series this year.
The Phillies versus the Astros. That's right. Jason versus Mundi. I don't know who to root should we even know. You know what actually I do.
I had no opinion on the matter until last night seeing Ted Cruz front and center. That's right. By no one played.
So I'm going Phillies for that reason. And who was front and center at the Phillies game? Star of Top Gun Maverick, Miles Teller from Downing Town, PA.
Everyone had a great time at the Maverick. Miles Teller, someone who I've tolerated for at least three weeks. And he's Jason's guy now.
He's my guy now. We were talking about like I don't know he was pretty chariot. Top Gun Maverick at SNL. Then he's at the Phillies game.
Yeah I know. He's kind of good on SNL. I can't believe I'm saying this. So Avatar and Miles Teller you've come around to.
I'm Miles Pilled. I haven't watched the Godfather TV show. That looks excellent. I love the scene chewing. I love Feud, Betty versus Joan.
That mini series is so great. I don't think those are comparable though. I don't think it's as good. I mean yeah I don't think he's it's probably delivering like Jessica Lange, Susan Sarandon facing off.
Yeah yeah we'll see. We'll come. You know in three years that'll be all we talk about is Teller on the offer.
But anyway back to the Zuvio of the mansion, the Hatbox Ghost. Here let's talk a little before we get even dive back into legend.
There's things about this character that exist regardless of form, regardless of if he's drawn on a book or in a figure that got removed or the figure today.
I mean just that the effect is cool. The box is cool. That he's like hunched over. There's a lot of character just to the way that he that he holds it.
Like he's holding it in a mischievous manner like I got something here and we know that he's maybe not the best with walking. He's got his his his like crooked cane which has a more specific term but I'm not because shalali.
Is that right? Well that's like a claw like that's a thing you beat someone with. I guess you would use a shalali if it's big enough as a walking stick.
I think I saw that word applied to unless I'm crazy. But you know it's at least a cane. He's got a gold tooth. That's a distinct facet of him.
He does seem to have more person that I will give it to. I didn't want to completely take away what is interesting about him but he does seem to have some interesting things about him that really stick out more than some of the other ghosts.
Yeah. The kind of his is like asymmetrical eyes which maybe they aren't exactly but it's just the way the pose is where one is wide and kind of frightful but the other one's more furrowed and shriveled up like it's a you know it's an off putting facial pose for sure.
Yeah. The doodles of him for the kids records and kid stuff can also you can make him cute. Like he's cute. He is cute. He's pretty cuddly and he's got kind of like a shock of fuzzy hair. He looks like kind of a Hanna Barbera guy in that version.
Oh yeah almost. Do you think even before we start talking about like what we think do we think we should maybe get into sort of this history of hats in general?
Because I looked up some interesting stuff about you actually did. Yeah just a little bit. I mean I did. I didn't listen to you. You were going to find a way to screw me. Well I just don't screw. I mean I didn't listen to the episode but I did look at I did watch a video called World Hat Story 101 about the top hat.
Well I guess we better. Hat of the modern man. Oh. I mean Jason do you know anything about the top hat? Um I know it used to be very labor intensive and the phrase man as a hatter comes from like mercury used to be used in the blocking process.
That's interesting. I know you're doing this to needle me but that is interesting. Well people hadders had mercury heads. It's also interesting the top hat sort of replaced the sugar loaf hat you know because that's more of like kind of a pilgrim hat type hat.
Which would you prefer Jason? Sugar loaf? I just need to I'm going to double check a sugar loaf hat before I make a decision. I can't picture that off hand myself either. Just Google sugar loaf. Um but then also yeah there's obviously it didn't completely. Should he not put hat in? Just sugar loaf will do it? Sugar loaf.
What is it? We can talk about sugar loaves too. That might be for its own episode about sugar loaves. Sugar loaf seems like the transitional point between like pilgrim hat and like 10 gallon cowboy hat. Yeah yeah. It's kind of man in the yellow hat. Yes exactly. So he was sort of a throwback as well.
The top hat John Heatherington is the presumed creator of the top hat who was an English haberdasher. And it was first worn in public in January 1797. Wow. So it's an old thing. This is what folks this is the Met Gala of its time. People were like are you crazy? You're not wearing a sugar loaf hat?
But soon enough it becomes the norm. That's right. And it was still it was like a wealthy thing. You know this is a it's always been a fancy hat you know. Mr. Monopoly wears it and I think people like the Mr. Monopoly of the 1800s would wear it as well.
So this suggests again we need this history because it suggests something about the character of of the hat box goes to be able to analyze him thoroughly. Are you are you saying like in a socio economic fashion by him wearing a top hat and by even you know what by having a hat box because that's a whole I don't know if anyone has the history of the hat box.
Well God forbid. But you know because that's I was thinking like do you guys anticipate in your life ever owning a hat box. I could see Jason having a hat box. I was I did write down like do people know about in the modern age you people learn about hat boxes from this character this attraction.
You know because I think you know upscale if you're buying like a real hat like a blocked hat men or women's hat you still get a hat box. But like how often do you do that in your life nowadays. Once or twice for some people if ever. You know has anyone ever gotten a purchase a hat not that not like a cap right.
A hat that requires I've never I don't think I will ever be commissioning a hat to be made to my specifications. Right. Yeah I think if you are going to a place where you're getting like a fully from scratch like made fedora or cowboy had 10 gallon hat you might still be getting or like high fashion like if you're going to Neiman's or Bergdorf's or stuff you might be buying something that comes in and because the pair of hats is a hat box.
Comes in and because the packaging is part of the luxury. You know Bergdorf's a regional inner heard Bergdorf. That was the place that that's the fancy department store whose restroom used in New York. Bergdorf Goodman's. It's next to the Plaza and Central Park.
Is this like a am I supposed to know that when you used the restroom that story. I told this story when we were in New York because I went in the Plaza we wanted to see the lobby of the Plaza Hotel and most of it is like blocked off for non hotel guests or if you don't have a reservation.
There's so many people trying to retrace the steps of Trump. Yes. That's right. Like we can't so many people they're trying to recreate people are getting down on their knees and a little knit cap and another guy in a big coat pointing the way to go. Yeah.
Yeah. So if you are you never owned a top hat in a serious manner. Right. No. No. No. Not nor have I though I do kind of want when I turn like 40 I'd like to start wearing a cowboy hat but I think it might be too much.
Can I actually looked up the I can't believe I'm staying on inventor of the top hat but I looked at John Heatherington is just such a name I wanted to see more and this is I'm confused by what I'm reading this is Wikipedia and I don't know if what we're talking about is the top hat but there was an incident with this guy.
Oh yeah yeah I saw this yes in 1797 he was charged with breach of the peace and inciting a riot. Yes because he'd appeared on the public highway wearing upon his head what he called a silk hat which was shiny luster and calculated to frighten timid people and the officers of the crown stated that several women fainted at the unusual site while children screamed dogs yelped and a younger son of cord wiener Thomas no not core.
Poor son has he not had a difficult road enough. It was thrown down by the crowd which collected and had his right arm broken. So there is a this is I thought this was interesting because this is like the legend of the half box goes.
This seems like bullshit doesn't it. A guy wore an experimental hat that made women shriek dogs yelp and it was as bad as arm broke.
It was a hat that was a few inches taller than a normal hat and it's slightly different just slightly different shape and it caused a panic and a riot. This seems like a made up story does it not.
In a time where people. Yeah it's also look Wikipedia is saying oh look in the Wikipedia the common form of the story has reproduced in many then subtitled put in by Wikipedia which books many which books.
Yeah it seems great and also like a slightly taller hats wear a powdered wig like a normal sane person kill him kill the demon kill the boy and the younger cord wiener Thomas.
It's so this is yeah this is exactly like the half box was the legend of the top hat is filled with like oh was it the scariest moment when people saw it to a people not able to handle a hat that was double the size of normal.
Specifically when I look up silk hat it looks like the hats you know that opening shot in the prestige with all the hats just kind of like and you don't know what you're seeing but it pays off later. Oh right.
Could you show just that like one minute of film to someone from the past and they would just lose their minds. Look at all those hats look at all those tawdry hats. Yes they got to be institutionalized.
Also I according to that YouTube channel or initially it was usually like beaver fur was used to make a top hat until the decline of the beaver industry. Hmm. So then it was probably what a fine industry that must have while Trump said he was going to bring back the beaver industry but he didn't.
I believe beautiful beavers. We love them they're making dams we can make hats out of their fur. He if he went on TV was talking about beautiful beaver. That's the way the late night hosts would have a field day and it would have sunk his career certainly for a presidential candidate to be so
wanting to see beautiful beavers. Yeah no that would have sunk him for sure. I think became very popular be some sort of fur or pelts that were easily acquired in America became very popular in France to wear beaver to wear like yeah items maybe of beaver and and so like an influx of money into the early America.
Yeah America's founded on the beaver industry. Yeah I wish we were like grinding up beaver bodies but it was yeah it was it was really awful whatever it was without knowing any details. Look back in the past you were either being scared of hats or you were grinding up beavers.
Yeah the truth one or the other. It sucked. What kind of man are you? Beaver grinder beaver or a hat shrieker. 50 percent of the food you eat it's got bugs in it and they're not supposed to be there.
Some people you can call a top hat a high hat or a topper which I like that. I think that's a cute way to call it. I got my topper here. Topper. Yeah. So I think this is all important context for the character of the hat box ghost to know where he comes from and what he's all about.
I don't I should disagree with you and yet I think maybe it does. I think it does. Yeah because if he's dealing in it just implies he is a fancy ghost and this is a ride full of fancy ghosts. That's maybe it. There's some status throughout this.
There's also speaking of Wikipedia like barely sourced things. Some one of these Disney fandoms which are always pretty shade Disney dot fandom dot com had the the tidbit of info. He was a milliner though this has yet to be clear in the attraction itself.
Okay so he's not then. So you made that up. So it's bullshit then. There's a lot of that on these Wikipedia. Well here it says he's this and here it says he's like it's it's not really until we see the Jared Leto movie which was will be definitively what the hat box.
He's playing the hat box ghost in a movie next year which I guess that's a big thing between the years. What you what what date does that come out. I'm sure it's before.
No let me throw this out. Should we delay next year's Haunted Mansion episode to fully just talk about the Haunted Mansion movie. Oh man. I'm not saying we do. I'm just throwing it out. No by precedent by precedent. Okay. We have we did the Eddie Murphy movie.
On the second day and sit alongside these are not the same track. Okay. I cite precedent to say please can we not. Okay we only do a beleaguered second. I'm imagining you wearing a beaver top hat when you're saying this because you're saying precedent like an old timey judge or something.
I say precedent. Hmm. August 11th 2023. Hmm. Interesting release date early. Yeah. A little early trying to make early for Halloween but like just the tail end of like summer started to taper off like August was very grim for movies.
Well past summer you can make an argument though that people are starting the Halloween season earlier and earlier every year. So that's appropriate. Well in Christmas I saw some Christmas is already here Jason. I saw a post about like oh Universal Studios Hollywood when you walk in the entry where there's already garland on the fake New York like for Halloween and there's a week left of horror nights and they've got like Christmas decorations.
The snow is on the castle at Disneyland. Yeah. Yeah. And oh I never mind. I won't talk about that. That's about my annual pass that I can't renew now. Oh you probably can't either. Oh I can't. Yeah. Unless you did it. No Jason did it. Jason's the only one who has a magic key right now. Didn't you have like a there's no grace period. There wasn't a 30 day. I don't believe so. And I might have been past that as well. We're locked out until they decide they allow us to buy another one. So fine with all this bullshit. I'm fine. I mean I'm annoyed.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm annoyed. It's been annoying there. It's just annoying to me if they never release them again. And like well again they did last fall knows what they're going to do. Yeah. It's all over the place. Next year. We'll know. We'll have such a pile of new frustrations and confusing kids. It's a it's a not it's not a magic key anymore. It's a pixie dust pouch. So make sure you have your pixie pouch. I'm sorry you don't have enough dust in it today. You can't get in. Well when pixie pouches are
announced at least that'll give us a chance maybe on the ground floor again. So I'm all for that scenario. Yeah. As long as we can be opening day of I I'm not sure which way to go if we because there's stuff to talk about with the movie with the movie. But do we stay on kind of legend. Sure. Well should we talk about the return or do you want more? I've got a little stuff on what actually happened. So look you know let's
go back to the legend surrounding it. Did they pull it because it's too scary. Did actual guests get to see it. And what seems to have been pieced together is it was around for employee previews where Tony Baxter saw. He was like one of the only sources on any of this. Yeah. A little while. And he says well it's very possible that they could have also been like soft opening previewing it for guests and guests saw it then. But there's only this very mild window where it could have happened. And over the years through the 90s as the story is coming like it took forever. But this site doom buggies
tracked it and a picture was found of it in context and a brief as a pruder esque video. Yes. Or you got to really know what you're looking for to see it. But so this there is proof that it was around for guests for a couple weeks.
So then what why did they what a weird like not clean way to pull it's around for guests a little bit. The true story here I looked a little further into Yale Gracie who I'm sure we talked about in the first year or two. But I had to as with Dr. Augustine and Dr. Ogden I had to refresh my memory. And I'm sure we talked about him in the context of what he did for the mansion. But all their Disneyland stuff he basically he was the special guest.
Special effects guy. And that's a really particular thing to be the special effects guy in the 1950s and 60s. That's where you're using like weird Houdini magic. Yeah. Houdini magic to like it's it's all like it's it's practical effects to like the popularization of Pepper's Ghost.
Of anywhere in the mansion but still used today and raise the resistance and other stuff. And then comes from this guy because he was looking for theatrical effects that could have worked you know 100 years ago. Yeah. And they can still wow people in the park today. The let's see he worked on the lava in Peter Pan's flight.
A little subtle touch that had to be cool and look real and be done on the cheap. We were just talking to the doughboys about the Blue Bayou restaurant and something we really lit up at. So it's such a big part of the ambiance there are the fireflies.
Fireflies. Yeah. Bye. That's this guy. Wow. He did those which is like still what a huge part of being. That's like what you that's why the hassle of getting into the Blue Bayou is this subtle thing. And he used to guy used to complain about like
People trying to recreate stuff he wanted to do in with new fangled ways of doing things. And he's like no there's one way to do it. There's one way to do these fireflies whenever they try they mess it up. He was very particular. And I think people
Imaginers today are still like oh yeah this guy was he was right on the money but everything. He was a genius. Yeah.
Fire in pirates is this guy. And there's a really cool photo of him holding a pipe behind the fire. Oh wow. Like looking real like just like cool villain with the awesome orange lighting hitting him from behind.
So anyway guy truly pioneering like so important to the history of theme parks and he's working in spaces nobody's worked in before. So he's not always going to get it right. And this is a thing that he didn't quite get right. As we said it worked in one environment but not in another. And the reason it got pulled is because he said I'm pulling it like it's not like anyone. There was no superior saying yeah you screwed up. Yank the hat box goes.
He was not happy. It drove him mad. He pulled it out himself. It was like Axl Rose hearing the first go at Chinese democracy and saying this these songs aren't good enough. I have a standard. Yeah. I need them to be as good as appetite for destruction. Yes. And then and he then he held to that standard and we can all we're all humming them in our we all we all know that's right. We needn't do it on microphone. He just couldn't take it anymore. And it stayed on the table. It was a very good song.
But on site he had like kind of a sort of a bungalow office at Disneyland and it was just sitting in his office like taunting him like the raven. This kind of adds to it too. I never heard any of this. And it just really bugged him. And then it started getting stripped for parts not Jason as he said it's been debunked that he became the eagle in America sings.
But he did like because it's translucent parts and like it got like robbed for various parts for the graveyard scene and for different characters in that. So that box goes really like disintegrated. It's like became you know parts of 12 characters essentially. And and it bugged Yale Gracie and he wanted to get it right. He never got it right.
I say also you're Gracie sounds like a great guy quote Mark Davis great engineer. He was a great guy. I never drink a Manhattan without saying and his wife Alice and I agree on this. Here's to Yale because that's all he drink. Love it man. My favorite is a man and guy.
I think he also did like martini lunches like on the Disney line 24 7. Awesome. Great. Drunk magic man. He was a perfectionist who didn't want to put stuff in the park. He didn't believe in. So that's how great. So really what happened is the guy who really wanted to bring this illusion of life couldn't do it which makes the 2015 reprisal so much more dramatic that it was like piecing together the dream of this this cool Manhattan drinking pipe smoking guy.
Wow. Yeah. So it's almost like thinking of I mean it's not quite the same because the Yeti is still in Expedition Everest and it's not working but Joe Rody has left the company at this point but he had vowed for years he's going to fix it going to fix it now he's gone. Whatever happened he's with Richard Branson in space now. But maybe like somebody will have to do it in 30 years and finally fulfill. Yeah. His wish is to make that move again.
They have to know that it's not going to move the needle attendance wise but if they can ever crack it all the nerds like us will be so oh my god the Eddie were it will be like in a certain subset it'll just like be a real like wave of excitement. The imagineers know that now. Well we ever have somebody who would rubber stamp green light that project for money again who wants to do something just because it's fun for that for the park and not because it's going to move the bottom. Well isn't this. Hey look isn't the 2015 have us.
Ghost and a lot of other things they were doing back then kind of a sign of sign of the times of those times in a good way. It's not shape back era where like I don't know what's more. Let's do bands here like what more what money adders can we throw in.
Right. You know this is like when that box goes got to come back it was such an era of like we don't need to do this but it'd be cool if we did it and it would make everybody happy if we did it. Yeah.
And it's funny because the 60th anniversary that 2015 it's fun when companies like this contradict themselves because there was a video about it like he's back on the Disney parks blog and they made a they did a post and they had a little video talking to a bunch of imagineers and they're like we thought it'd be cool to bring back for Disney's diamond anniversary you know diamond celebration.
That was what they called the 60th and you know you've taught me guys I know the diamond but there's also a USA Today article from that time where the like lead on the project was like yes it's just kind of happy coincidence that it's lining up with the anniversary.
We didn't do that on purpose but then there's also a video with a different imagineer going like as part of the diamond anniversary. So they have to fit the narrative the narrative fits whatever it fits. They didn't mention the narrative that is like well they didn't really do a bunch of new stuff for that time.
The anniversary pretty much just I'm with you I'm haunted by that anniversary not doing as much as we wanted it to do. Yeah there were supposedly so many things going to be announced didn't happen didn't happen. Yeah. As far for the course. Yeah point. That's true. But so yeah 2015 it comes back. I tried I learned a little about why that happened.
Like as a yeah I think it got grouped into the diamond celebration of course but OK there is a podcast called Tomorrow Society with very good interviews with imagineers about their craft the stuff we don't we don't know about.
But yeah we don't have to be funny but like this guy talks to a couple of people who are part of this project. Daniel Joseph is one and Ray Spencer is another and I especially enjoyed listening to Ray Spencer. This is imagineers name. I don't know. We tend to only talk about like it's hard to find even like you got to be really prominent like a Joe roadie for a Steven.
Know the name but Ray Spencer at the same at the very same time he had three projects going on. One was the redo of the Matterhorn. So like those screens on the lift hill now and the redo of the robots. Yeah very similar to this just like atmospheric didn't have to do it but the ride so much cooler because they did it.
Yeah it's it's modern and digital but it feels it's not out of place in an old ride. And then he also did the redo of Condor flats the Soren era area into Grizzly Peak airfield. Also very charming. Also a like just they didn't have to but better that they did it right.
It makes the toppings bar more fun. Jason knows sure in a better mood and maybe end up loading up on more toppings. This guy also probably the ultimate. They didn't have to do it but thank God they did it. Buena Vista Street. That was his big project and the red car trolley. He was very passionate about trolley.
Jason needs to know this. I mean I like this guy. Say his name again. Ray Spencer. Ray Spencer. Is the guy. His interview at tomorrow society was great. And you might think why can't picture this man. I've never seen him but you may have because if you go to California Adventure there is a place called Big Top Toys on Buena Vista Street.
And as soon as you enter there is a conductor. Have you ever passed by this. A guy in a red jacket and a top hat. And that is this guy. And like the old cone. The shouting cone like an old director would use. We talked about him. We must have at some point.
Yeah. Well come on. It might have been because my friends Tyler and Kia were at the park and they were like hey the park fan who's this. And I said I don't know but I'll find out. And I was happy to report that is an Imagineer who likes the circus and like strolls and did Buena Vista Street. And now I know he's part of that box goes to. So I got a good feeling about this guy.
Does he still work there or is he done. Fired probably like everyone else. I'm not sure. It might be like a consulting. He does stuff sometimes. I think he might like do stuff for Universal. Yeah. Anyway he brought up interesting interview. I won't just like recite things from the interview. But a couple of interesting things about the product. It was not just we're going to make the hat box ghost again and plop him back in. There's some stuff we got to be concerned with. There was not a natural decision of where to put it because do we like evict a preview.
This character and put it in the attic like it was. Or maybe we'll have the same problem. It won't really fit. And then they ended up carving out this little kind of cubby which I love. I love his spot. They also had to change the track slightly. That's something I didn't know about this. It is no they didn't just put a figure in because I'd never thought about this that the doom buggies it's not like it's a digital system. Right. Right. Pointing it from place to place. There's on the track itself there's some
mechanism nudging your car turning it for the way that they want you to look. And that spot did not exist for that box goes previously. So they had to reroute the track and change it to make you to see you get to stare at it for longer as we're doing with this episode. Sure. Yeah. And they did it. I think they change and correct me if I'm wrong. They changed it. There was a point where they were teasing the hat box ghost where they sort of just put up kind of like a flat with like a window or something. It was like a window and like hiding. That was a
It was up for a while. It was up for a while. I think they changed the track before but I could be wrong. I'm not sure if that's actually maybe they had maybe they did made it part of a bigger overhaul. Yeah. Just like one day. We'll just put that. We'll take the wall away and he'll be there. Oh that must be it. Yeah. Yeah. That's what happened. So correct me if somebody was kind of a digital window. I saw something about it's sort of a digital looking window and then it had one of this the owl stanchions from the line. Oh maybe. I don't remember. And then maybe something like it flies away or something. I think I've
been going a lot around. We were going and I remember seeing the window and we we were talking about like when is that going to come. It's got to be here. It's got to be the hat box because they didn't say who it was but they said something's coming to the Haunted Mansion which is really that was awesome. There was a tease on the ride. Oh really. Like that I'm saying this was a tease on the ride. Okay. Versus like oh they're putting a thing on a ride and then it's just there. This was like something's coming to the mansion. There's a different thing now when you would go on it like that was teasing it in the right. Like I don't
know. I can't think of a good example of like something new is coming to a ride but there's something there to suggest exactly where the new thing will be. I don't know. It's very it was very cool. It was like a trailer almost like you know things going to be. Yeah. It was like a real tease short teaser trailer and they they announced they did announce like a month before like the hat box goes back. Yeah. But it was before that where they were teasing some things here. Now it's new and neat. That's neat. Yeah. And yeah I remember
it's interesting because sometimes when you try to find like when did this start what's the opening date it's like well this was the previews for cast members and friends and family and that's this was soft opening and this is the official record day. This one it's pretty definitive on all the Disney like blogs and stuff. The company websites like May 9th 2015 he's back. You can look at him you see him on the ride. Gotcha. It's here. Yeah it was like yeah you're right Scott. It's the it was this
window if you can see that that's kind of yeah. Remember this. There's something with that owl. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But yeah it was like for sure you knew it was new when you went on the ride for the after like a refurb. I don't think I ever saw it in that era. That is pretty neat. What I remember now that we've talked about the kind of the how they put it together in the project just emotionally let me say I really I strongly remember seeing it for the first time. And when I say that I love the space that we
have where he exists in the little space they carved out for him. What I love is that it so well utilizes the high backs of the doom buggies where you're heading to something and maybe you see a little bit of glow but you don't know what and then suddenly it just kind of like whips you there and now you're very very close to this character with who has this whole mythos and is just cool regardless of any of that. It's a good reveal. Yeah. Because a lot of it is you're like a lot of the
pictures just looking at big rooms and you have to. Oh that's cool. That's cool. And you're looking at a million things at once. This is one of the only times with the intimacy. Exactly. That you want. This is that maybe the ultimate moment of intimacy because you only have one thing to look at the ultimate moment of intimacy like you can have as a person. Well that depends on who you are and what you're all about. You're not a seed factory. Well for me I am the seed. I am the seed. Like said like Walter
White. I am the seed factory. He's nervously riffing because he knows it was artificial. Too intimate. Too intimate. No not artificial. Yeah I'm trying to think is there any other than maybe the hallway but that's the thing you're moving pretty fast through there and there's no like real face to face with a ghost in the hallway. Yeah. Yeah. There's like there's a pivot point. You know what it's like is the the trolls in the maelstrom where you
head towards the trolls and then you turn from the central. Yeah. That you get to stare at him for a little while and then you go backwards away from. I guess that's Elsa also in the new but it'll always be the trolls in my heart. Sure. Yeah. Sure. The hit three edit troll three. Yeah. That's the three edit troll. Yeah. And then sorry if I'm good. I haven't done my maelstrom research over the fall. We'll get to that. We'll get to that before. But we'll do Indiana Jones to before maelstrom. No. No one wants that. They all want it. It's great.
They all want it. So yeah. So it is it is cool like it's whether you know any of the lore or not it is a cool reveal because you really can't see it coming. Yeah. It's hard unless you really are craning your neck around. Yeah. You cannot see it coming. And also you're in front of this now much newer looking robot that has a very cool effect. And I would I would be interested. I haven't pulled somebody who doesn't know anything about it but I would imagine you would that would be one of the memorable parts of the ride if it was your first time going on it.
Go like oh that was a cool ghost with the head. Probably. Now also digital newer. Last year my complaints were about the attic feeling too digital and current and I don't have those complaints about this. It's kind of like the the matter on redo or there's something about they just didn't.
It's like something about the like the dimness and the lighting and maybe I'm just influenced by listening to this guy Ray Spencer because another thing he said was they they were like we need to make the him special because he is special but not so special that he distracts like it is not like an aura of heavenly light on this character.
And that goes because that would be out of place. It is I think the dimness it's it like you don't feel the digital nature of it so much because it's done in this realistic moody fashion. I know it's not the same thing but it almost in the same way that like I feel like if they had made the Harry Potter queue with the paintings coming to life 10 years earlier those would have looked like screens.
Yeah like there's a perfect those absolute they look awesome and they still look great. Those those paintings come to life. If you look at them and they're static you think it's a painting like I was on it not long ago and it's like it looks great. Yeah. And like the same thing with this it's like within just a couple of years stuff like this can make the difference for how good the technology is and how timeless then it can feel because like the bride is dated. It's digital.
Hmm. What would you kind of feels 90s and it feels very 90s and I don't I feel like this thing could last for maybe the technology would get so good it would feel dated but this thing feels like it could last for 50 years and it wouldn't be you wouldn't go oh I know when that era what era that was made in. Yeah.
I mean I think you bring up a good point about the moodiness. He there is not a lot of I mean Leota talks she kind of has her own soundtrack and sound effects and such. But the hat box goes he's kind of like sinister sinisterly laughing at you and there's that like poof sound effect kind of when the hat the head for the transition between the hat box and that and the head.
Yeah. And it feels like copacetic with everything around it. It feels of the piece. Yes. Because you can by that point you can probably hear you know just you can hear a little bit of what's going on in the attic and a little bit of the graveyard that's coming up. So all these things just need to be ambient and fit next to each other and not be so overwhelming about other elements.
The other thing is you're looking at him for a while long enough like as you tilt towards him and then when you go backwards you're kind of guaranteed at least one disappearing reappearing. Oh yeah. They time it so you get. Yeah absolutely. And if it stops or if it slows down you could see it happen a couple of times. You know.
Yeah. Yeah. When you get stuck in front of him. Oh what a dream. The best spot. Yes. Yeah. That's where that's where you want to be. Never. I always kind of like when that ride gets stuck kind of wherever you are. There's no part where I like bummed or anything to like go this boring. Like I kind of look forward to the and I like the little playful spooks. I bet it's part of it to me. Yes. And it's not like getting stuck on Harry Potter where I start to get a little nervous. Sure. Yes.
I go we can be up here for a while. Yeah. Depending on where you are. That's that's happened a few times. I got stuck in front of one of those mentors. No thank you. Spooky. How many stories. How many stories up are you at that point. A couple. Yeah. Yeah.
At least two. Yeah. So if you get it if you're stuck in front of it for a while you maybe get a chance to stare at it and try to figure out how does this effect work. As we said Yale Gracie could not figure it out in just in a way just with lighting. I forget how much we said it was like essentially the idea. It's it's scrims. It's it was going to be some version of that. It's like the carousel of progress is an example where it seems like a wall but then the lighting changes or it's it's you know.
Transparent somewhat. And when you when you put a light in there now what seems like a hard surface was actually just partially transparent. You could look through it. It was something like that. Yeah. Yeah. They use it everywhere on stuff. They used it a couple of years ago at nots paranormal activity maze like where I'd be walking down a normal well lit hallway and then scrims they change the lighting on it and like it was hell. There were tons of characters. Yeah. Yeah. And you were like it was like such a great effect that still works. Right. It went from like a wall to like a wall.
From a boring hospital hallway to see the depths of hell. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Really cool. It's cool that you know grazing might be behind the use of that anywhere in theme but you might as far as I know you might be the first. So that was the idea was going to be a mini version of that. But it's so lighting dependent doesn't quite work. That's not really what it is today. Do you guys know how they do it. This is not there's not even really like debunkers or people really trying to say I figured out the hat box. Did you. Does it say in the interview because I did not
listen to this interview. No. And I don't think they like make up. I don't think they're dying for it to be said and figured out. I have theories based on my idiot brain. I have. Well and then what I have is like somebody's guess on Reddit. OK. Which take that with a grain of salt. But it might be. So I maybe have a solution if you don't want to know. Skip ahead. But Mike. Well I think it's all like sort of like L.E.D. based where like it
can like things can like literally like a screen can turn on and off. And the way that they've done it and I am not smart enough to know almost in the same way like Harry Potter where like something on the figure itself just looks better than like it masks that it's a screen.
It can turn on and off. This is my dumb opinion. I think it's something like that. Yeah. But then it's also like you are you have to really stare at it to register. Oh now there's nothing. Right. It doesn't look like anything.
That's why that's why I think it has to be turned on and off a bowl because you really I've looked you can't see it in the hat box when it's not there.
Well I think I think I watched the B roll of them like you know where they do that. They take footage of people programming it you know and they're narrating over it in that short video about the hotbox ghost being back.
And I think what my guess was from what I could figure out from this video the the head on the body that is a practical head. But it's like very basic and the head is the fate it's projected on it.
And then there's is there nothing in the hotbox. Is there just a screen in there. I think that's right. Yeah. Yeah. Because the other thing yeah the face obviously is blinking.
There's not that's not a robot blinking. We know that there's a projection of some kind or it's some sort of screen in it. So it has to be either or I think so you're saying you think Jason that there's some sort of like maybe black featureless head shaped item.
Well no it's white like imagine movie screen wrapped around like a mannequin face like your white movie screen.
So good to be a projection. That's the only reason why I'm like is it some like screen inside him that I'm not. But maybe yeah maybe projection is just can be so precise now that I never like sort of because I know other projection things you can kind of see a little.
Yeah. Once in a while it's kind of weird. Here's and skip ahead listener if you just want this to be magical and not here and this could be totally wrong because again I found it on Reddit but it makes sense to me.
Yeah. Thinking it through. I think Jason you're correct that there is nothing in the box and that that's maybe a subtle 45 degree pepper's ghost sort of like there is a little projector in the at the top of the box that's shooting this image of a face down at a weird angle that then conforms correctly to a weirdly angled screen.
The the head on the body. I this somebody believes I'll just read what they wrote and the use I forget the user it had the word wookie in it. Okay great. That's not full credit but it's something.
There's a thin piece of opaque material that gets pulled into his chest. So interesting. There's so it's a really it's a very light screen that like furls and unfurls and gets sucked back and then put back like back and forth.
Wow. It doesn't not make sense to me and that so it's saying it is a projection but it's just that the the screen pulls down and up. Yes when like arrives right on time like to the millisecond.
How interesting or the face to appear on it. So yeah. So yeah. Okay. So the way to project something would it have it would have to be a white screen because it wouldn't project on the face is gone and white but maybe it's more like it's it's a really neutral gray like a darker.
Right. So yeah that would have to be down obviously when it looks like he just has black.
There's a shadow like an empty space where his head was that's the effect. I think it's like it's a screen getting yanked. That's crazy. It feels like a cousin to me of that really cool effect in Tower of Terror Tokyo. Yes.
I was thinking when appearing and disappear where like you cannot be off by half a second. That was also shocking to learn how that was done because there's something that like disappears and I thought for sure it was some sort of projection trick but it literally shoots down into the ground.
Yeah. Yeah. Like just fat. It's like a fast thing. You can't gravity. Yeah. Fast. You can't see. So interesting. Regardless of what's happening. Even if this user is wrong about that. I think they're dead on about this.
The next part which is the subtle blue light that represents his head moving from his neck down his body is meant to draw your eye away from the rapidly disappearing screen for the projection and this interview with the with the imaginary I heard another piece of like something on YouTube.
They seem to be hinting at this that like it's happening right before your eyes and that it's distraction.
It's like a prestige. It's a magic trick. So if you're following his his soul or his essence which you're going to say that looks cool. This whatever like magical ambient light is moving. Look at that is the stress.
So if you go on it if you and you want to crack it you might just want to stare right at that head and don't look away.
Wow. I mean that is what I was trying to do when he first when I first wrote it in like 2015 but the theme marketing did work of like the hotbox goes back because the lines for Haunted Mansion massive to see this.
Yeah. Yeah. You trying to crack it. I'm looking at it now. Yeah. And I'm trying to see if I can see the top. You know what the lighting is on its side even for like watching a video of it because can't.
Yeah. It being in this dim spot and it's dim like even if I bet with all the lights on you go. Oh got it. But yeah I guess I'm wrong. I guess it probably is still a projection and there's not a screen in it but I can't really.
I guess there is sort of some movement on the head when it transfers. So yeah maybe. Yeah. It's still hard to tell even if you're staring at the head but it obviously is a video.
So maybe maybe you can tell more but it's a really great effect regardless. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's so cool. The fact that we don't really know and they have not really Lee and the people are not even dying to like catch them and like I know what they did.
It's really cool. And I'm not even sure but that seems like a start and amazing. They really pull off. It is one of the I think it is one of the neatest things you can see in Disneyland at this point within the rights just.
Yeah. It's really cool. It's really cool. And I've said I think I said this on one of the mansions or maybe everyone I'm not sure is that if they ever again this is never going to happen now because of the way decisions are made but I would love to see an overhaul of almost all the ghosts in this style because it still looks kind of old school to me but also it's so much more clear.
It still maintains this sort of spooky nature of the ghost but it's a lot easier to see and a lot easier to see the effects. So if you put the graveyard full of at least a few more prominent ghosts because I've said this before it's like the graveyard is awesome but I wish that if they would apply the new technology to some of the ghosts and really like spruce things up overall in the mansion.
Yeah. Maybe like spots here and there. I don't know if it needs to be addressed but there's some that are just kind of hazy. Yeah and I know like it's fun to kind of go like like squint and go oh I think this person doing this but like some of the some of the more marketable ghosts.
Victor Geist's your Constance Hatchaways you know. Yeah. Who what's the chandelier ghost. Pickwick. Pickwick. Thank you. Pickwick deserves an upgrade is what I'm saying. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So well there are you know that look there's upgrades come into mansions here and there.
I'm not happy about it. Yes. Well we talked about this when we talked about D23 news the Hatchbox ghost is coming to Disney World and Mike took the hard stance. Oh you don't want it. Not. They don't. They should. Not an unpopular opinion.
You think so. That's what I've been reading. I mean at least in our audience I don't think at the very least it's 50 50 if not more in tilted in favor of this opinion. It is kind of just like we put a seven year old animatronic we put a seven year old edition into the
Florida one which that that that is one of the best pieces of news they had. Right. That is a real sign of the times. We're putting an old thing in a place. Yes. And really done because of the movie I think they're presenting it as a thing. Oh look the Disney history finally coming to Florida.
But really it's like we're hoping this on a mansion movies a big franchise Jared Leto big star big character. He's the Hatchbox ghost. Let's get him in there because people are going to want to see that character once they see this movie. That's my cynical take is that they're presenting it as something for the fans when in fact they're like we got to have this with the movie before the movies out or who knows when they're going to put it in. So but you're you don't want you're not wanting to just like leave an empty space. Your argument is also I want to leave a seat at the table.
I want to see the table for the ghost but I don't want him sitting there. You want you're you're thinking you want them to get something that they don't they get their own version. Yes. I think that's more fun. I think that the lore of new character Disneyland Hatchbox ghost is fun. And I think it's I like that again we I think mostly in agreement that we like it being there's stuff that's unique to the parks on both coasts. Yeah. And I feel like this is what's more specific to do.
Disneyland and the legend of this character. Sure sure. So it feels to me like you know they're putting a hat box ghost over there. So you want the Florida Hatchbox ghost to have like a patchy beard and long greasy hair. You want the full 30 seconds to Mars. Look. Well now. Okay. Okay. You're making a little joke I think but I actually would. I am making a little joke. I think I would be more in favor of them modeling it after Jared Leto. No. Because it will be different. No. What?
That logic makes sense. But what. Come on. Because then it's different. If that just happened you would hate it. If it happened here. If it had like. We don't know what it looks like. If it wasn't this back and forth already established. I'm just saying I'm if you if there were two buttons one button is put the old the same thing that from Disneyland and what put the Leto one in. I'm putting the Leto one in every time in Florida. And I would do it without it with a clear conscience. Just with taking your daughter for the first time and going like and that's that's the answer.
That's not Dr. Michael Morpheus. Right. This is not a clear. This is not the fail son from House of Gucci. That's right. No. That's not a Gucci. Is it. It's wild that performance. It is. I like the performance. The movies should have been more nuts. That's my only complaint. Every character should have been like. My complaint is like everybody still do the voices they're doing and make the movie a full on comedy and I'm there. But it's not it's not as crazy as the
performances would suggest. Yeah. I you know it's as you say this that you would willingly give Florida the the letter letter. I would I'll tell you why this occurred to me. Well I mean I'll just say my my thought I was thinking about Leto stuff and I was thinking about 30 seconds to Mars and I was like you know if there wasn't Leto baggage and if and how about this if you had grown up with it I think you would love 30 seconds to Mars. That's an interesting thing. And when you say grown up.
How old if it had come out in the late 90s where you were all that shit you revere heard it then I disagree with that I think because I was OK. Believe it or not a couple of weeks ago I was listening to some of the sequel single excuse me singles of 30 seconds to Mars to refresh myself.
OK. This was I was on a run sometimes I'm all this is going to seem like I'm I'm complaining I'm allowed control of the YouTube once in a while when things are going on when things people are like wanting to focus on the TV. People were over Lindsay's family was over and like people are cleaning up or somebody's in the kitchen and whatever.
I'm I can then wield the YouTube. Hang on. What in the world you're so when everyone's distracted and chores are being done. Well I'm you get from all right Mike gets. I'm not trying to act like I'm I'm being persecuted or something. I'm just saying once in a while when like stuff is sort of going on and people don't want to watch a movie. Let Mike control the YouTube and it can be whatever we want.
Well mom is putting stuff in the garbage. Mike gets the YouTube. It's yes and I understand it because people like to watch TV they like to watch a specific thing. People don't necessarily like to go down YouTube rabbit holes like maybe we do. Maybe the three of us are now look I'm entirely YouTube rabbit hole. Yeah that's my favorite show. My favorite show is YouTube rabbit holes. Of course yes. And look you know I'm sure there'd be things you would see in my history and go you watched that. The one that I always think about is that YouTube
provided as the entertainment for Lindsay and her mom multiple versions of Sammy Davis Jr. singing Mr. Bojangles. Mr. Bojangles. I've thought about that ever since. Yeah I'm like how did multiple you finished one and then you were like no you should probably see this one from three years prior. I want to actually legitimately I want to hear exactly how that played out. God I don't even really remember exactly how it played out. I will go back there. I'm trying to think. You must. I have to know. I'm trying to think is like I'm sure we were watching some sometimes I
like. OK here's here's my strategy sometimes with when I'm YouTube rabbit holeing with a bunch of other people is I will try to at least get adjacent to some other people's interests. Very much like sometimes sometimes. Lindsay likes old standard. She likes the old crooner. She likes the old time music. She likes newer music as well. So she doesn't like so much like the 70 year old man in a dingy basement complaining about the woke belief. No she does not like that. Whatever you're
talking about she doesn't like it. No she likes those soundscapes that I like where it's like a Halloween party going on downstairs oldies playing from another room. You do. No I put that on if I'm like you know working on something or cleaning or stuff. It's like there's a whole YouTube channel of it and it's just like a still image and it's just playing like audio.
Mm hmm. So I believe this happened because I started putting on some old like old old crooner types and then we got into Sammy Davis and I was like you know what I actually don't know a lot of like what was the song. What were Sammy Davis song you know Sinatra's you know a little bit of Dean.
This was discovery. This was not like yeah I know the 76 Mr. Bojangles is the best Mr. Bojangles. Right. This was a little bit more discovery and like Sammy Davis did the Candyman and he did Mr. Bojangles which is a 70 song and I forget the band that did it.
It's not like an old standard but he like did it in a sort of an old style and I think he did it every show from that point on. So I was on a Sammy Davis kick at that point and I don't remember exactly why I ended up with multiple Mr. Bojangles performances.
You know it actually helps me to learn what I found that you were you were trying to learn about it. I found it so strange that you were like you had you've done one and then you got to do two more. It's really like sat in my head like a rock for years.
I don't know there could have been something more strange at play. I'm not ruling that out. Will you for the listeners rank. You don't have to do it now but at least on Twitter for anyone who's interested rank the Mr. Bojangles performances.
You know what a song I like there's a song that Sammy Davis does and Bobby Sherman. They both called Sweet Gingerbread Man which I really I'm a big fan of both versions of it. One of the credits and one of the Hawkeye Disney Plus's they have Sammy Davis I think singing Sweet Gingerbread Man.
Wow. One of the one of the that's an oddly relevant right. It takes place at Christmas. Yes. It's like fresh shot of the pan sweet gingerbread man. It's a very cheesy song but I like it a lot. It's nice. It is nice.
Can I tell you why I thought 30 seconds to Mars. Yeah go ahead. Because their most recent album is called America. I'm like that's like fucking all your like American American Wasteland. American. OK so here's my argument for why I don't think I would have been because 30 seconds I was listening to the singles and I was like oh this song. Yeah this is an unpleasant song like I don't know what it's like.
It's like very moody versus like something like My Chemical Romance which was the Black Parade. You know do you like any of that. No I'm talking about. No you don't know I'm talking about. I know a little. There's like a very like inspired by American Idiot album I think. And you're asking me if I know.
Well I don't maybe it's possible. You avoided it like the play. So this was more when I was older when I was 20 early 20s mid 20s and there I like I like those My Chemical Romance songs pretty good. OK. And I was going back through all of this stuff and go yeah what were 30 seconds to Mars songs and I was going through a couple of them like oh this is unpleasant. These songs are unpleasant. OK. And don't even have like a fun upbeat sort of pop punk thing. It's a little more screamo kind of thing.
You know very like kind of labored and like more intense and not as much fun. So I don't think so. That's a good question. You know what I say that not really knowing what the music's like at all. I'm not as big into like that screamo emo stuff from around that point and especially the singles which I still don't like.
I don't. Seems like not fun. They were on Conan one time when I worked there and I was like this is the worst performance I've ever. It's like they were like they were like six guys with giant drums who like with different color face paint swiped on. And it was one of those like oh Oh Oh oh oh oh.
One of those fucking chants that would leave you for like 15 years. I think maybe we're finally a little bit out of chance. Oh yeah. The Tejo. I was truly watching it on the monitors like oh people like the five we can play five to ten seconds of this.
this I think right before Jared Leto sues us. It's like really like no fun.
It's just really yeah there's just it's sort of I remember being on the radio and never
getting into it like you know an all-american rejects where I'd be like well this is a pretty
fun pop punk the ataris and anything where I would casually like it. I wasn't a big fan of either
those bands. You want some melody. What's a melody and I want a little the upbeatness and.
Well here to not stay in tangent land for too long you know this is all being said because of
Jared Leto. Well ultimately the character we're talking about this year will be portrayed on
screen by next year we will know. We will know what it was we will know how it went. Yeah. What are our
fears. I'm going to say fears. What do we think this movie is going to be like this this finally
we get boy. That's a good question. I don't I don't really know. I'm not sure. I'm more my concern is
that it's not going to be like as scary and moody as I would want it and that's not really a few.
A little concerning because it's very comedy stacked. Yeah. Owen Wilson Tiffany Haddish. I
mean I like this is a good cat. Look yeah I know I that is nothing but a tone wise. I'm thinking
they're going to lean more toward the graveyard and less toward the hallway if you know what I mean.
Tone wise I'm a little concerned they're going to burn off a lot of time like the Eddie Murphy one
did where it's like well I'm a real estate dad and I'm not around a lot because I got to sell these
houses but we're moving into one of that because this one already they're like OK the premise is
it's a single mother and her child. OK. And they move into this. It's like I don't I do not care.
Just show me this. I want to monster. I want a ghost party. Well look even the Muppets had to
reckon with how why are you in a haunted mansion. Yeah. This question has to be sure. That's true.
So yeah I would say that my my concern is like it we're still leaning we're going to lean toward
like family friendly not that it shouldn't be family friendly but it's going to be less like
atmospheric and there's going to be less of a tone like a cool creepy tone and mood possibly.
Well especially given that as was said earlier Guillermo del Toro was maybe was like for sure
was deep into development of it and who knows what happened or why that one didn't work out.
But I know that people were pained to discover that Jared Leto comes with a lot of
bad and maybe like there's been highly anticipated characters he's played before
where then what he did was kind of annoying or nothing. Michael Michael Michael Michael.
We all had so many hopes for what Morbius was going to be. But the like well so you know what
I had not put together is that this isn't so surprising but Doug Jones not our friend
Jones but actor Doug Jones was going to be Hapox. So I think that's a good point.
Hapox ghost in that version and everybody loves him as a creature in character. That's the next
out of the park anytime from from Mack tonight on. And so that that does feel like oh boy they go
from like culty always cool to uh to like a guy who runs a cult. Well who is a cult leader.
Uh huh. That's true. All that stuff is true. And if that is all the cult stuff aside you know I do
think I like his Mario voice in House of Gucci. I think there's a realm Mario voice. He's a very
nice guy in House of Gucci. I didn't know that. OK. He's you should at least watch some scenes from
House of Gucci. I think you'll know what I'm saying where you're like man this is right on the edge
of being something like I'd like to watch. I you know I like them in We Crash the show we've
worked on. Sure. I yeah I thought he was a lot of fun in that. But yeah it feels like I don't know.
Also I want to say I have mixed feelings about both of these people but like a road trip comedy
that pairs up Jared Leto's Adam Newman and James Franco's Tommy Wiseau. I just want to put let's
like merge together. Sure. Let's write a fictional adventure. Right. People can play them as long as
they play them exactly like those ambiguously foreign and strange positive oddballs you know.
They can pick up Joseph Gordon Levitt's Travis Kalnick because that is the Uber guy. The very
aggressive Uber guy. You would put him over Don John. Huh. In there. Oh yeah. If I could only put
one or Jiminy. If you can only put one Joe Galev on the boat. Yeah. I'm going Don John. Look you're
neither you are wrong. I was just trying to keep it in the realm of tech guy. I see I see you're
right. You're right. Well the only thing Wiseau already isn't and you know who you might want to
put in there is like an artist like the tightrope walker because he's like you know like let me show
you a world of fantasy. That's like a duel then like to sketch comedy characters. Leto and Levitt's
accent characters thrown together. I think one thing I if I was making a Haunted Mansion movie
this seems like an easy go to that I think no filmmaker would consider is trying to mirror
in the arc of the movie make the first half like the Claude Cote segments and then make the second
half of the movie like the Mark Davis segments. Sure yeah. Keep it dark and then make it silly and
yeah yeah. It seems like an interesting way to like get the tones the various tones of the ride
in there. Sure. But who knows if anyone's considering that you know. Yeah I think with
I think the answer with Leto you never know what you're gonna get so sure it's almost impossible
to tell. You might get a surprisingly fun performance or you might get a used condom in
the mail. I was gonna say for sure you're gonna use condom in the mail. That's for sure. He's gonna do
he's gonna have heads in a hat box. He's definitely handed out a bunch of hat box full of some kind of
animals heads to the cast. Oh yeah. I know that has happened. Yeah yeah yeah. Danny DeVito got a
fucking hat box with a head of a raccoon in it or something. Yeah that's so nice wow a hat box. Boy
Jared is a great guy but can't wait to work. Oh no. He's been he's made big strides in the actors
labor issues because now the animal heads and the use condoms that's been worked into the latest
sag contracts. The latest screen actor contracts. That you wait that you that you get them just for
participating. It's sort of like guaranteed now like you have to be paid to go do the pre-shoot
covid tests. Like you have to make sure you're getting you know something absurd in the mail.
It's gonna help with performance. Like you you're gonna give it a different bent if you're if
there's a real a dirty adult diaper sent to your home. A full diaper. Adult diaper. I forgot what
the things were. I was like what was this story again? And my I completely content wearing content
wearing. I completely went to used condoms. I forgot that right alongside this was anal beads.
Oh yeah. We sent people anal. Was this on Will Smith. On Suicide Squad. That's what this was I think.
Not Justice League. Because the Joker because something we know the Joker and something the
Joker would do would send anal beads in the mail. Yeah that's right. That's a good point. He would
serve as a just like a voluntary Spencer's Gifts sex toy employee. Right yes. He went into a
Spencer's and was like I know what I'll get. What are the most twisted items?
Yeah yeah. Culticide. His Joker is fine. I would say it was not worth the hassle. It was not worth
the anal beads. But it's fine. I mean I'm glad the anal bead industry was propped up for that
amount of time. I want to see the two Snyder movies. I want to see Justice League 2 and 3. I would
like them to make those. And 3 is the teased at the end of the first Justice League and is the desert
nightmare apocalypse. Yeah where Batman is in the big coat which is I think cool but makes no sense.
Batman's wearing a thick coat over his shirt over his Batman outfit. All right. And he's got goggles
on for some reason. Doesn't make any sense really I guess. He should just have goggles in his cowl.
But then maybe. Yeah but then Joker is there with him so they have to like sort of team up in this
in this future world. Sorry is this happening or is it. No there's still people are still
banging the drum on this. Which probably I guess won't happen but. It's the most unpleasant drum
sounds I've ever heard in my life. The Justice League movie is good though. The Snyder cut's good.
These all fall into like fell asleep before the ending for me. Suicide Squad, Justice League.
Well Suicide Squad. We have to cut this off. Suicide Squad the first movie is not good.
Yeah. OK sure. Yeah. Yeah. I don't doubt that someone who has any interest in any of it would
like the Snyder cut. I like Jason fell asleep very quickly but I do in any and all things. So
I've been a parent for a while now. As you've. Sure. The years have gone by with these podcasts.
No Baby when we started. There were no what? Childless Men when we started. Right. Two now.
And we're making our way out the window. The fall into the graveyard will begin soon. One bit of you
know what though Jared Leto this casting information gives us one crucial piece of information about
this character and maybe a good thing as we wrap up. The name. I don't think I knew the name and
maybe the name is purely an invention of the movie but it will become the name canonically
because there wasn't one before. The Hapbox Ghost. Do you guys know offhand? I'm looking through. I
have it here somewhere. Just you say it. I have it. The Hapbox Ghost's name is Alastair Crump.
Alastair Crump. I don't know if you want to say Alastair. Probably not. Alastair Crump.
Right. Crump presumably a reference to Raleigh Crump. An engineer. Which is confusing because
other things have called the Caretaker who is a character we'll meet soon next year. He's the
wobbly knee guy at the bottom of the hill. I don't think I realized that was the Caretaker.
He has been defined as being Silas Crump. So they're trying and I think the Haunted Mansion
movie the Eddie Murphy one had Master Gracie as a character and we've talked about Yale Gracie but
they're trying to get these guys names in wherever they can but a little confusing if there's already
a Crump unless they're tying it together. Unless the Caretaker is related to the Hapbox Ghost.
You know we should real quick because there's so many different versions of like yes the Hapbox
Ghost initially was the husband of the bride. Yes. Oh right. Because it's like and there's some
people that are like oh well he lost his head and the bride killed he's not the husband. She has the
head. But she was a victim of the bride and yes also maybe all of it because he has a lot of
hat boxes also. He's traveling with a lot of luggage. So it's like does he have other heads?
Is he maybe like the the sidekick of the bride in some way? He's been killed by the bride but also
now he's sort of teamed up with her and he's keeping all the heads of the headless people
that she's killed in these boxes. I would love kind of a characterization as like yes dear anything
you say dear. Exactly. Trailing behind her dropping the thing his head's falling off. So maybe that's
what it is and that's a fun idea. Huh. To to because because yeah there's different like comics
and things and everybody made up their own slight origin and again the Imagineers didn't put two
thoughts other than that looks cool put it in. Like we said all of pop culture today is adding
a bunch of shit to things that people did not think about in the 50s or 70s. Yeah. They thought
about their Minhatans and their martinis. Yep just like that was cool that's cool let's go to lunch
and get hammered. It hammered. Yeah. I one thing I didn't mention I was looking at the Jason Sorrell
book about the haunted mansion and the version I was looking at is an older printing 2004 2006.
So there's a lot about the Eddie Murphy movie in it and I was combing through the whole book trying
to find stuff on the half box goes and it gets one page and again this is 2004 let's say
and it just has the answer to the mystery like it's all there it just says like it's got the
Tony Baxter quotes he's the one who said like yeah you you would rotate you towards what is now the
harpsichord he says harpsichord that's where I came up. Oh god. Harpsichord from. Yeah. But he's like
yeah it didn't the effect didn't work because it was too much ambient light and you were too close
to it and it's pretty definitive in this book and this book is published by one of Disney's
publishing things and they bring Sorrell back to update it every few years I think the last time
was around 2015 2016. So I do want to get a hold of the newer one and see like oh have they expanded
it now. Yeah. Maybe no. Maybe not. Maybe no. Maybe they kept it a page as opposed to us who did two
hours this was a two hour about just the half box ghost and you know what we weren't wrong you weren't
wrong you were I never I don't think I ever said you could be wrong but I I you know this was the
right thing to do I'm glad playful spooks interrupted our tour and we stopped here for a while and hung
out with Alistair Crump Alistair Crump the half box ghost who we will see. We'll have a lot more to
talk about in regards to this character the grand marshal of the black parade. No no don't say that
he's not the black parade. Gerard Way. Oh excuse me. DC Comics editor. Oh yes. DC Comics writer and
editor. The music superstar who parlayed that into a career writing comic books. Yeah hey good for him.
Good for him. You know they played they played the we are young festival yesterday wearing their
black parade outfits and old men masks. Oh I saw that yesterday. Maybe they were just afraid the
winds were gonna kick back up. I think they're aware of it being like a nostalgia festival and
they wanted to comment on it somehow. That's actually a solid bit. Sounds also unpleasant to
play music wearing a thick rubber mask. Yeah. Although I guess like slipknot. Up there playing
the black parade dress like Carl Havoc you know. Who's Carl Havoc? Oh from I think you should leave.
They quote all the make up. Oh yeah yeah yeah of course of course. Speaking of obscure names. Yeah wow.
These are our characters. Yeah you pulled that out real quick. Carl Havoc. I know what that is.
Well you know and now we reach any predictions about next year. One I have is that because
it was said once how many more times will Gerard Way and the black parade be mentioned
between now and next Halloween. I have my fears. Do you want to get how here rate on a scale of
one to ten skulls. How what do you think you will give the haunted mansion 2023.
Oh my liking of it. Yeah and then we'll say our actual scores. Oh my goodness that's a really.
Should I be optimistic right now? I'm not. Three point three and a half. I'm gonna say six and a
half. Okay I'm gonna be optimistic. Are you going out of ten? That's what he said. Ten. Oh okay I
was gonna say three and a half out of five. That's not bad. Yeah that's a pretty good deal. Uh uh
hmm out of ten. I'll go eight. I'll go optimistic. Wow that's very high. You might really like the
haunted mansion. I might really like the haunted mansion. I mean precedent is if we're going off
most recent Jungle Cruise is not up there but like I have I have high hopes. I don't why. I can't
tell. Everything Disney makes is shit. I like Owen Wilson. I know it won't be a Pinocchio but.
I like Owen Wilson. It's kind of an oddball cast. You should say Danny DeVito. Danny DeVito should
play Pickwick. Maybe he is. Maybe he is. Oh man. Jamie Lee Curtis is Madame Leota. That's fun. I
mean that's great. She I feel like she's on a real run right now. Owen Wilson has had some fun stuff.
You're right. He's been fun. So I don't know. I'm going out on a limb. I recent movies I've not been
very fond of anything really. Yeah that's my biggest look. Even these little things are enticing but
remember it is a movie that the Disney company is releasing in the 2020s. And that is why I put a
three point five. It's not the heyday of live action like the million dollar million dollar duck days.
A brutal movie. Yeah. It's it's interesting. Jason though Jason I sometimes when you're your review
of a movie I feel like depends on just how your day had been. Because like sometimes you'll come
out hot with that Country Bear take and I was like are we watching the same movie. I was not having
good time during the country. I think you need to watch that when you're feeling better and you can
reassess it. I feel like I was in a pretty good mood when I went in. I just think that that still
to this day I'm still like what movie did he watch. The Country Bears is pretty good.
Well you need to get some real good little real good windfall something when something great
happens to you celebrate by rewatching. That's right. Is there a playlist of just two thousands
like going to bang out Brother Bear. We're going to bring out home on the range. Confessions of a
teenage drama queen. Confessions of I mean that's look that was never for me. Like I can't judge
that one too harshly. You never know certain ones you're like this is a movie I never cared about
and assumed was bad at the time and I've watched it now and it was better than any movie released
in the west. I mean that was during the pandemic we went back and watched a lot of like late 90s
mid 90s like high school movies. Oh yeah. And you realize how many like either journeymen directors
or writers or like really good sketch comedy ringers were writing and it's just like wow this
is pretty good. Someone solid was involved. Yeah. Well we will see that's maybe that's the big thing.
I can think of nothing bigger coming in the next calendar year than determining the quality of the
Haunted Mansion film. But Alistair Crump we'll see you soon. It was great to hang out with you for a
while and listeners you survived Hauntcast, The Fright, all of it. It is done and we switch back
to Podcast the Ride next week and you can find us on all the socials at Podcast the Ride. Merch is
available in our Tee Public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out Podcast the
Ride the Second Gate or get one more bonus episode on our new tier Club 3. You will find all of that
at patreon.com slash podcast the ride and yes. Here's what I'd like to say. Oh wait you had ideas.
I have an idea. I want to real quick and we have to do this quickly because I don't want it to
linger in our minds too long. Yeah. Maybe Scott it's your job. I task you with it. You need to
give Jason and I an assignment for next year maybe even the following year very specific very detailed
of what we need to do when the episode starts and if we do not do it we will be punished in some way.
Oh. We need clothing we need to wear. Things we need to say at the top of the episode and if it
does not happen next year we get punished and so we get put in the penalty box perhaps. We drink
the year old Donald Duck orange juice that Andrew Gressom. I mean I don't know about that one but I
would say I don't know. Bring to me these items three. Yes. So so uh off the top of your head what
clothing do you want us to have to wear when this recording starts and what do you want us to start
the episode off with and if we don't do it uh the punishment will be let's see um we have to listen
and review solo on the Patreon full 30 seconds to Mars album. You will have to listen to the full
one and then solo record 60 minutes by yourself. This is your you're charting a guaranteed path
to where you end up at the end going 30 seconds Mars. Kind of like it. It's possible but I'm
gonna not. You're trying to invent a rationale to get where you want to get. I don't I'd rather
review other things and say you know what I like this um and also it's probably not a good thing
to be like Jared. That's pretty good actually. Did you know he actually is good. I like him a lot.
Yeah yeah right yes. So only worst things. But maybe on the Patreon I will say yeah I can say it but.
Uh um here's well here's this is where the stakes enter. All right please add to what I just said.
If the if the task is not completed. Yeah. With each one a a cluster of robots becomes eliminated
from discussion in the graveyard. Now here we go. We cannot even talk about it. Real stakes. Oh no.
No this is but these are stakes Jason. Yes because I know you're gonna want to talk about it. And we
by the way both have to do it. Yeah. We both have to remember next year to do this thing.
Um and it can be a couple things. It could be sure like like we have to wear blue in the honor
of Avatar. We have to wear. I think it needs to be complicated. Uh um okay. I think the wearing uh
blue and I'm not just saying that because uh half my wardrobe is the color blue. Uh all right now
you know not to say blue. It won't be blue. That's not yeah yeah yeah. Um okay how about this. Yeah
it's it's two parts. It is a uh there's there's two reveals involved and I think I'm thinking
clothes because you sent me down that path. Okay. Uh this I'm giving you like go get these clothing
items like the dogs at the animal actors show. Um okay you you need to wear a hoodie like Jason
you're wearing now and that can be anything but at some point probably let's say right at the top.
You need to unzip it and and on your shirt whether that's written on your shirt itself or like a my
name is tag there needs to be written your favorite character from Avatar the way of water
in blue ink okay blue ink right right uh marker does matter that's it that's up to you. Yeah I'll
just make it like a ballot uh but but it has to be blue um and since we're talking about the hat box
ghost uh just bring a box of any kind and open it up and there should be a type of hat in it okay that
would be surprising maybe not that would provoke shrieks or that would break a young child's arm
okay but like you know because a filly's hat is not going to do it I know you might have a filly's
hat right um and uh unless you're so ashamed of how they do in the world series I mean just look
we're just proud they got there you know yeah it's a miracle I'm rooting for you as I said I'm on
your side due to Ted Cruz uh um so but yes like a where when it when the hat when the box opens
there is a hat where I'm like whoa okay yeah an unusual hat and uh the name of your favorite
avatar character in blue ink okay and this is when we start how you hit record on the podcast this
all happens yes welcome welcome to podcast the ride you do the whole intro and then you go and
here we go yeah yeah mm-hmm right and I'll say your names right and then you have a little
presentation to give all right okay fair enough and if not we loot we are not allowed to talk
about the hitchhiking ghosts oh my god instead of two high stakes that's pretty good good there also
though is the question of what even are we going to get to because I don't think we know now we're
back to we don't know the we don't the dividing markers we don't quite know where the haunted
mansion series goes so that's you know maybe we wouldn't even get to them anyway but still then
the next year we are not allowed to talk about you don't get to talk at all about the hitchhiking
ghosts that's pretty huge that's pretty okay well a big assignment then for next year listeners of
this specifically will talk to you in 2023 uh in the the great Oz and Herschel Walker uh rain
and uh and we will I guess land we what we will do is uh begin to descend down a series of uh we'll
pass by some scary trees if you want to hear about more scary trees go to the patreon something we
just talked about uh check us out on Doughboys too if you hadn't heard that I think that's out by now
and uh yeah so we will uh here's what all right we just the Hapox Ghost has just gone out of our
view and another doom buggy is blocking it and we are moving downwards backwards and we set the
scene for next year haunted mansion six beautiful forever dog this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey
ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever
dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook