Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following haunt cast may require working knowledge of Funko Pop executives.
You may encounter coked out birds, embarrassed dads, and exactly as many Hitchcock impressions
as you suspect.
It's the classic Universal Studios attraction Alfred Hitchcock, the art of making movies
on Haunt Cast the Fright.
Welcome, Foolish Mortals, to Haunt Cast the Fright.
I had a whole opening joke plan, but I just want to get cut to the chase.
We got a host who's excited to do Alfred Hitchcock for you.
Let's go, Mike Carlson.
He was chomping at the vid.
I did it on Mike a little earlier, but good evening.
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright.
And then I kind of lose it.
Haunt Cast the Fright.
It's past the good evening.
The good evening I have, and then it's gone.
Then it's over, then I go, it just goes right into my gruff.
That's, you know what, let me try to do, I wrote a little intro.
Let me try to do it like Alfred Hitchcock.
OK, here we go.
OK, OK.
Welcome to Haunt Cast the Fright.
A podcast about.
No number one, lose the clapping.
Sorry, sorry.
Scream Pox, hosted by two Disney deadies and one haunted doll.
My name is frightful, gnarled son.
You're still.
Oh, I mean, Alfred Hitchcock.
Hitch, they call me Hitch.
They called me Hitch, but my name's Mike Frightful Carlson anyway.
I don't know where the Hitch comes from.
Here, keep going.
This is great.
I actually didn't have a name for Jason Skeleton.
Welcome.
We've got two big Hitchcock boys here today.
OK, well, in that case, let's cut to the chase.
Let's get to Hitchcock.
Let's get into it.
I'm going with Scott Grim Reapner.
That's what I'm going to attempt this year.
But everybody, you know, punch up your punch up each other's.
You seem quizzical about that one.
Yeah, I was trying to think if I had done this one yet, should I try Jekyll Shriekenden?
I think I love it.
I think I've tried Jekyll.
Have you tried Jekyll?
I don't recall you trying Jekyll.
Jekyll and Jackal, I think, were the ones I kept trying.
Well, Jackal, you know, we like that.
There's only one Jackal, I'm afraid.
Sebastian Jekyll.
We're listening.
Yeah, we talk about the Sebastian Jekyll of Christopher Lloyd.
The character Christopher Lloyd played on UPN's series Deadly Games.
Of course.
That's on the second gate.
So stay away from Jackal, because that guy, he'll go right through these computer wires
and microphone hookups and suddenly he's in your head, man.
I do not want him to saunter into the room with his glass of semi-flat sparkling apple
juice and just get my ass, you know?
Yeah, and kind of like be sinister to you, but not really do anything that bad.
No.
That was our takeaway from that show.
No, not really.
His role on the show, which is only slightly longer than Alfred Hitchcock cameo in the
movies.
We got to cameo point, didn't it?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, first things first, welcome to Hauntcast, The Fright.
I'm excited we've begun this again.
You know, we're going to have some fun.
Of course, the Haunted Mansion series will step closer and closer as we step closer and
closer to the grave.
So, we'll set a similar pace, well, at a year-by-year pace.
That'll be the end of the month.
Mike has been out haunting again.
We're going to hear about some recent.
I know it's been a bit, you have carved out the time.
You're in a stretch of parenting where it's hard to get out, but you love haunts that
much.
You have made it work.
We've carved out like one thing, fun thing for me to do a week, which is go to a haunt.
Luckily, there's a lot of them.
It's fun seeing your daughter grow before your very eyes.
All that is magical and beautiful, but I'm just talking about extra curricular fun outside
of the home.
So, yeah, basically my only fun in that regard is haunts and then going to the toy section
at Target.
Okay.
You go for functional reasons, but then like, well, it's on the way.
You can't fault me for.
Oh man, do we need something?
We need something, huh?
We need, are we out of granola bars?
Oh shoot.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'll have you go unless you want to go.
Did you pump?
Because if not, I'll probably have to go.
It's so convenient, the baby section.
And I don't know what, sometimes I forget where it is and I have to walk through adjacent
sections like really close to it.
But if things was a babyish stuff in there like a toy.
Yeah.
Well, she needs toys.
I mean, she's a little child.
Oh, little children need toys.
That is a rule.
That is what Dr. Spock said.
Is that where is to the target toy section where you got this, this Kingo, my favorite
character.
Let me, let me update this for 2022.
My favorite character in fiction.
I know I got that at GameStop actually.
Okay.
Oh, gotcha.
And I won't lie.
It was on clearance and I said, you know what?
That's a really good deal for a, for a little Funko pop key chain.
So yeah, that's where, that's where I got it.
This was not a priceless.
This is not like lines out the door every day for, do you have a new second shipment
of Kingo yet?
Well, you know, it's a good question because like they make a lot of Funko pop merchandise.
So it could either be a limited run and then it didn't sell well or it sold very well and
they made a million of them.
So I'm not actually sure.
I would be interested to know.
I could talk to Funko president Brian Mariotti and see if he has the list or like of how
many they made for all these things.
You know the name of the president of Funko.
Yes.
Brian.
I have texted about this man.
Oh boy.
Dear Mr. Mariotti, I have a new beautiful daughter and I'm wondering if you can tell
me where to track down the young Sheldon variant where he's in his little docent costume from
when he worked at a train museum.
Yeah, here he is.
This is Brian Mariotti.
Whoa.
He is the chief creative officer.
Excuse me of Funko.
He looks like the John Cena of toys.
Yes, I think he is the John Cena of toys.
But yeah, you know, we know we have all these different guys on this podcast, right?
But believe me, the toy world is full of guys.
And yeah, this is what as soon as I heard the name and that you Griffin of time, like,
OK, this is this is an Eisner.
This is a trey.
I don't know in terms of I don't know his like ethics or what I don't.
Yeah, I don't know anything about that.
I just I'm fascinated by him immediately.
I haven't done any sort of deep dive.
But yeah, he's I follow him on Twitter and he might.
He'll know the answer to how many KINGO's were produced, how many KINGO keychains.
I don't know if you only do this with Disney executives, but let's try it.
Let's cut to the chase.
Can Brian Mariotti get it?
He looked pretty handsome in the photo.
Let's see him again.
Oh, there he is on the screen.
Oh, he's oh, yeah.
Well, this is kind of your aesthetic, Mike, which is like Rockstar, who peaked 18 years
ago.
That's kind of his vibe.
So this is what you regard as the pinnacle of male handsomeness.
That's true.
A lot of the toy guys, again, this is a different for a different podcast, but a lot of the
toy guys have a wide variety of aesthetics.
So yeah, he's got his own unique aesthetic going on here.
But yes, I mean, I think he's a pretty good looking guy.
He's got he's got a nice suit on.
It's got like a checker pattern or what would you call it?
Yeah, I'd wear that suit.
Jason, that suit screams I am about to con a like 10th round NFL draft pick.
18 year old out of 80 percent of their income.
That suit says all that.
That's what a suit can say.
That suit says that.
Shady, shady sports agent.
I say that's the suit of a man who makes dreams come true by producing high valued collectibles.
Oh, and now wait.
Now, Jordan has slid the screen over and now we're looking he's in front of a big C3PO
and he's wearing sort of a Bill Nye.
He's from the Bill Nye collection.
Yeah, so he's got a little bow tie.
Standing in sort of a feed, you might say.
What would the pocket?
A little.
Yeah, I'm getting a little young Sheldon with that boat.
Maybe that's why the show that the multiple.
Do we know how many Sheldon's all told there are Funko pops?
Yeah, yeah, because we know there's two at least there's basic.
There's classic and there's docent like stars in the universe.
It's unknowable.
Funko pop wise.
Yeah, there's got to be very so many different show and variance, I imagine,
with him in just different shirts.
Using the word variant at this point in this year to describe in this case,
it can just we've all used this word a lot and now we're using it to describe
how many Sheldon's there are.
It's funny because you say that because I'm equally on the COVID-19
Reddit where they're discussing variance and like the general action
figure collector where they talk about variance.
It's called a very you actively learn more about COVID than you have to.
I am. Yes, that's true.
I still am.
I'm like, well, I see you subscribe to different reddits.
And then it's sort of an aggregate of all the different reddits.
And so I've subscribed to it.
So when I'm scrolling through Reddit, I will learn about new
Ninja Turtle collectibles, and then I will learn about the bivalent booster
and how maybe that when are we getting the efficacy data?
You know, when are we going to know?
Because it hasn't had a full trial yet to know exactly how successful it'll be.
Do we have the Calabunga data yet?
Do we know how bodacious the new line of turtles are?
We do have that data.
And the answer is very the answer is highly bodacious.
Have we gotten to 100 percent?
Because I'm not I don't know if I'm willing to.
I don't know if I'm going to take the time to get the new Donatello
if it's not 100 percent Calabunga's rate.
Well, you should not.
Don't fear on this, because these are these are as perfect as turtles can get.
Shout out to head of NECA Toys, Randy Falk, a different guy
who I love, Randy again, Randy Falk.
But Randy is great because Randy looks like kind of a rock and roll guy.
He's he's like the you mean like the person we know.
But other toy guy we just talked about.
But a different type of rock and roll kind of guy.
He he he's like kind of like a cool like metal kind of guy.
He's a Vince Neil. He's got long hair.
I think he used to be on rock and roll radio, rock and roll radio.
Yeah, which I just that was just that's something that just came out on his
Twitter he revealed a few weeks ago.
Again, this is a different podcast.
Yeah, I'm doing a different podcast right now, and I want to go back
to haunt cast the fright.
You know, we have to.
Yeah, we're one premise of podcast within another premise of podcast.
So we'll get through it here.
But we're we're we're haunting.
The point is, you're haunting again.
But where do we kick this month off?
I think there's no better place to do it than with the master of horror
cinema's finest tour of frights.
That is, of course, Rob Zombie, who directed the new monsters,
which I believe by this point, technically we kicked off haunt
cast the fright with an episode about that on the second game.
We're recording this before we know before we know how good it is.
Yeah.
Well, I'll just say that there is a gulf as big as that fall
in saboteur of the Statue of Liberty on some of the movies I've watched lately.
I see. Wait, so that means you maybe have seen Rob Zombie's
monsters by this point.
I you'll hear you check out the Patreon and you can hear my saga.
With Rob Zombie's monsters, maybe that's by the time this episode comes out.
I will have seen all but the last 20 minutes because I fell asleep.
So Jason's saga is that he fell asleep or is the saga like you like lost your past?
We forgot your passport. No, no, I didn't.
Not a saga in like, oh, Mike's going out of town.
I wonder what a crucial thing is in another state.
You know, OK, got it.
But I feel like it's a long lineage of sagas that involve you falling asleep.
Yeah, that's a pretty standard.
That's what I call a saga.
It's not limited like the Skywalker saga that ended.
It keeps going and going and going.
But anyway, now that we've we since we've already covered
the master of horror, now we move to a it's, I don't know, a lateral move
or a lesser move to Alfred Hitchcock, who was a
was not just a character in that Anthony Hopkins film 10 years ago.
He was a real man. That's right.
And he made he made some movies.
There was a second Hitchcock biopic around that time, too.
I think straight to HBO. Oh, well, was that about how he was like a big creep?
They made a movie like that.
I think all of them mentioned that a little.
But I think the Hopkins one seemed like real Oscar baby.
And that's the bet when something is Oscar baby and then they do not take the bait.
No, that's always very funny.
It's there's there's a certain type of award season movie
where like everyone's like, wow, this performance is amazing.
They're definitely going to get nominated if not win.
And then you hear it's like, oh, how's the rest of the movie?
And it's like, oh, don't worry about it.
Don't ask that. He put the stuff on his face.
What do you want?
It does. Do you care now about what he does in the movie?
And if it's good, look at his face. It looks different.
Yeah. Did he try to do was the voice as good as mine?
Did he try to talk?
It might have been right in the same neck of the woods.
I don't I feel like I saw some of it, but I don't.
I might have been a screener.
No, let's talk about the man and let's talk about
the finest work associated with him.
The Universal Studios attraction, which like
probably the title, the main title, you would say, is Alfred Hitchcock,
the art of making movies, had a couple other titles.
But this was an opening day attraction at Universal Studios, Florida,
in 1990, closed in 2003.
And a great tribute to somebody who you guys say that you are boys
of what it describes.
Let's let's talk about your Hitchcock feelings in connection.
Sure. Yeah.
I mean, we were a big Hitchcock family for a few reasons.
One, the easiest of which was that when Nickelodeon
started airing the SNCC block.
Are You Afraid of the Dark was on?
Then it kicked over to Nick at Night and they followed it with
Alfred Hitchcock Presents.
Oh, they did a little horror tie together between the formats.
Wow, that's cool. Yeah.
And so we like that.
I saw a couple of
Alfred Hitchcock Presents recently on like MeTV or AntennaTV.
One of those channels where you're like, what is this?
But then it's like, this is pretty good.
Like they got interesting stuff.
And so I feel like that was one reason we like the intros.
We started watching the movies.
We like looking out for the cameos.
And then isn't this, by the way, this is sort of this is this is Eisner
before it is Eisner.
Guy talks to a semi charismatic,
semi bald guy introduces a special movie of the week.
Yeah. And I think the other reason, well, one Hitchcock movies are kind of
I didn't want to say they were that my parents knew there wasn't
foul language or nudity or violence, which were very verboten in the early 90s.
But murder is fine.
Murder and grand theft and that sort of thing.
My parents, I think around this time, were both big readers of like paperback.
Suspense novels like
Stephen King and Dean Koontz and and Sue Grafton and stuff.
So those were always around.
So I think we could all kind of agree on this. Sure.
We I didn't get to watch horror movies and watch a lot.
My parents didn't show me a lot of stuff, but my mom did love Alfred Hitchcock.
So even though I wasn't allowed, not allowed, just not even made aware
kept away from, I would say, most of the things I've talked about,
like Gremlins or whatever, she still liked the most
or horrifying snuff film that was Gremlins and Gremlins 2, which is a cartoon.
Yes, a literal wonderful show.
It's fantastic. Yeah.
She did like Alfred Hitchcock a lot.
So she would be like, well, you might be like nine or 10.
But you know, you could watch Psycho.
I would let you watch Psycho. Sure.
Because she liked the big she liked the main ones.
So I did see those and we watched the show on Nick at Night.
So, yeah, we like that. That was great. That was fun.
As a kid, I was scared by all of it, believe it or not.
For sure. Well, this it is like a the the attraction itself that there
and we'll get into what it was and everything.
But if you can imagine, there's, you know, a big section related to the
Shikah Shower scene like I do.
I remember as a kid that it felt risky or especially scary
to be like that. There are like a bunch of kids in the room watching the stuff
that is, you know, regardless of that, it wasn't actually bloody or whatever.
The scene is still very jarring.
And I think they I don't know how they conveyed this, but I think in some sense,
they tried to make this like designated a PG 13 attraction.
Like they kind of warn parents. Yeah.
I mean, you are seeing a live
depiction of a naked woman being stabbed.
Yeah. And they early before that, a 3D version
of the strangulation in Dial M for Murder, which is, you know,
thwarted by stabbing a man in the back with a pair of scissors.
Oh, OK. So yeah, all of that.
Yeah, that's all whether what regardless of what he's actually showing. Yeah.
Yeah. It's upsetting for a kid. Yeah.
I mean, I guess I mean, a lot of the rides would be upsetting for a scared kid.
But I'm trying to think, is there anything comparable like when Universal opens?
I mean, Jaws, there's blood, blood.
Yeah. Well, and when he gets like burn up, electrocuted, that is like jarring.
I think I would say a lot on the scale, at least certainly compared to Disney,
that a lot of the 1990 Universal was edgier, scarier.
I think that, you know, something maybe we'll talk about in the future
on a hot cast that that horror makeup show. Right.
With you, because that is the that is stuff from the fly in it.
And the fly is a very horrifying kid would not.
A young kid probably wouldn't or shouldn't be watching the fly. Yes.
So, yeah, they were they were obviously there's still a little more
comfortable scaring kids.
But yeah, back in the old days.
Yeah. Well, and this one, both suspenseful and a little scary and notable
among the opening day attractions, because it worked.
Sure. No. Yes.
The big ticket mechanical Jaws earthquake, King Kong fraught with problems.
But the shows that were produced probably for on a lower budget scale
that were clip reliant were more controllable than those did,
which I'm so fond of all of that.
We were debating about which one to do this year because there's that make
this the horror makeup show. There's murder.
She wrote. We'll get to all of it.
But I'm very fond of all of those.
Here's how movies are made from the early 90s.
It's interesting because this is I feel like this falls in with the Lucy attribute
to because it's like both of these people were dead for a while.
Oh, Hitchcock was dead for 10 years before this open.
So it's like these are almost like nostalgia attractions.
Yeah. That were opened.
I'm trying to think of like an equivalent.
I guess it's like seeing Max from the goofy movie dancing now
during these Halloween events or something where it's like that's marketed
just to the older people.
They're probably. Yeah, that must be true.
Well, at least some of the classic Hitchcock's probably now in 2022
or as old as Goofy Goofy movie.
Yeah. Yes. What?
Goofy movie 95. Yeah.
So yeah, we're getting almost 30 year anniversary of Goofy movie.
Talking about. Shut up.
All of you shut up. Max Max is a younger millennial.
Yeah. We're closer to Jim.
Max has a lot of gigs like he's he's doing a lot of gigs
and he does freelance graphic design and he is interviewed
in that business insider like good luck millennials.
You'll never have a home, you fuck.
Yeah, that's nice to see.
Oh, yeah. Thank you for taunting us.
Articles once a week.
And my my trending topics underneath that were like Disney World.
And it's like, well, yeah.
Yeah. Well, well, well, is it though?
Because this week we're recording this is probably trending.
I know. I think I saw it before.
I think I saw when it was just like it's lightly raining
and people are in long way, you know, there are nice.
Yeah, there is the like everybody's huddled in the hotel
and they're putting on nice little like skits.
The country bears are hanging out playing in the arcade.
I saw today. That's fun.
They make they make good things.
But universal, the the the walls got torn up.
But then the whole.
Yeah, the rest of the year.
They got to they got to clone a new one.
Yeah, I looked psycho is 1960.
So it's 30 years from psycho to this.
Wow. Attraction opening.
So what's the stupidest thing from 1992 that we can say?
Good question. 1992.
Like babies kids come out a little early.
Hudson Hawk a little before that before to
bad movies.
1992 Cool World.
Cool World. Oh, cool.
Is this interesting?
I think it's I don't like the movie.
There's an interesting aesthetic to it for sure.
Or like Encino Man Encino Man, which also is a fun watch.
But Encino Man is as old today as psycho was when Universal.
Yeah, but she was.
But I feel like the Hitchcock movies didn't never dissipate,
either airing on TV or like, well, yeah, early video store classic
and universal to as DVDs, Blue Ray.
They have never let these movies dissipate.
They re-release them so often.
A lot of the Hitchcock movies are on Peacock and the others are like on HBO Max.
So you can see a lot of the filmography.
Yeah, yeah. And because I'm dumb,
I watched Psycho because I hadn't seen it a long time in the lead up to this.
But then I was like, oh, you know what? I really want to see Psycho 98
and Psycho 2.
I'm like halfway through Psycho 2.
If you can imagine, I'm having some sleep issues as well
when it comes to Psycho 2.
But this is a I mean, we could deal with this more down the road.
But I've always wondered what those movies are.
And so far, Psycho 2 is a lot of Norman Bates working at a diner.
And so he has to keep picking up knives and it's triggering to him.
So it's a lot of him like shaking a knife and not being able to cut a sandwich.
I'm trying to think, is it somebody like Quentin Tarantino
has some sort of wild opinion that like Psycho 2 is better or something.
And I can't remember if that's right.
I think for sure the people say the old like Omen or Exorcist 3 is good.
I've said this before, where there's like certain beliefs that like some of these
there's like like outlier sequels because all of these feel like trash.
Yeah, real. Yeah.
Because like what else should be the story of Psycho?
But like I think there's at least some opinion that one of these psycho
sequels is good and I forget which one it is.
You know, two is better than I thought so far.
I haven't finished it, so I don't know where it's going.
But I'm like, you know, a solid Dennis Franz performance.
Oh, wow. What's your name?
Meg Tilley is solid.
I'm like, it is not as trashy and stupid.
I watched the trailer for four.
I got to do it sequentially.
I'm not. I.
So I won't make it to four for a while.
But I was curious about that because that's one of the weird universal Orlando
connections to Hitchcock is that, you know, obviously the psycho house
is on the universal Hollywood back lot.
But Orlando has or had the house in the motel from Psycho 4.
And you ask, why did they need to rebuild it there when it's in Hollywood
and remains in Hollywood?
And then it was we were talking, Jason, about how there was that creepy
corner of the park, yes, where it turns into there's like a there's a weird
off park hard rock cafe, but you have to pass by the unsettling
fake psycho house to get there.
This I remember crystal clear standing looking at the psycho house and
that part of the park truly seems like looking back, I was staring
at a giant Rubik's Cube.
There was a hard rock park, very interesting building.
There was like shaped like a big guitar.
Yeah. And you could enter from outside the park or inside the park.
For some reason, something we love. We always love that.
Yeah. And I just we just blew right by it.
Like none of us.
We were more interested in the psycho house set.
My family and had no real connection to the hard rock cafe.
That would be your adulthood.
That would be a large part of a large part.
I mean, every time I go to a city, I get the shirt or and I get a pin.
I got a Jacksonville.
Yeah.
So it holds a weird place in my memory, which I think this show in general does,
because there is a gag, the gag at the end with the mother, the two Norma's.
I remember that clear clear as day.
Yeah.
Do you mean Norman or do you mean the mother?
No, the mother.
When there's two mothers at the end.
OK, yeah, right.
I I never forgot that.
Like when I went back to rewatch this, because there's a lot of versions of it
on YouTube, I was like that happened exactly.
As I remember the thing that I misremembered about this show
was that the Statue of Liberty thing is just when you're leaving.
I thought that was part of the finale, too.
Yes, it was part of the show in the little mini version in Hollywood,
which it gets confusing because we covered some of this a little
with the special effects stages with Carl Tartt a couple of years ago.
And I don't know what we covered in that.
So there might be repeating.
I'm not sure these micro versions they make us figure out.
And let's add to that complication, Psycho House off the table, its own episode.
Yes.
It's micro topic this, which includes also Norman Bates attacking the tram.
And by the time we do that, I will have watched all four psychos.
I'm pretty excited.
Yeah, we'll all do it.
All five, including the.
Oh, if 98 counts.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yes.
Show.
How long would that run?
Oh, boy. That round for a while.
Yeah, I didn't watch that either.
And then, yeah, I mean, there's going to be a little
There's going to be a little Psycho House Bates Motel talk on when we talk about Horror
Nights because they put up a whole thing around there with a new original universal character.
They add.
Yeah.
So there's a whole new mythology that they've built up.
It doesn't really fit with the Bates Motel, but they're repurposing those sets for this.
That's some of the coolest, like in the little bit that I've done Horror Nights, that you get to walk
right up to the set.
Yes.
So great.
Yeah.
You walk right by the rooms at the Bates Motel, then you walk up in front of the house.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
And I got to use it.
I won't say I don't say why, but I will say I got yelled at by the Norman Bates.
But like for a real reason.
Like more by the actor, you're saying?
Yeah.
The actor knew I was doing something I shouldn't have.
Not it's not crazy, but I'll say what it is when we talk about it.
Mother does not approve.
Yeah.
Before we get to the attraction, I wanted to talk a little about the Universal Hitchcock
Association and what made it like now Hitchcock is one of the big franchises that they can
bring to Universal Florida when it opens.
So Universal produced the TV show Alfred Hitchcock Presents.
So the famous silhouette and the music that was always under Universal.
He had a bungalow on the lot.
That was a big thing.
You always pointed out as a tour guide and no matter who's in there, I think it was
whatever Mark Platt productions is when I was doing it.
The silhouettes on the side of the window.
So it's like it feels like part of the Universal Hollywood DNA.
And he filmed a lot of movies there.
Like the birds, I think, filmed a ton on the lot.
Saboteur, I want to say, or at least Saboteur was a Universal movie, but not all of them
were Universal movies, which is what's a little confusing that Psycho, which you now associate
very hard with Universal, was made by Paramount or maybe he made he might have made it on
his own and then they and then Paramount distributed.
Yeah. So it's a little confusing.
Why is there so much Psycho and it's on the lot?
So you really associate them.
And I believe it's that like so Hitchcock made movies kind of everywhere, but then it
consolidated at Universal at some point like his production company.
He basically he sold Universal a bunch of movies that they did not make.
Rope, Rear Window, Man Who Knew Too Much, Vertigo, a bunch of other ones.
And I believe Psycho and he did this in 1964.
And in doing so, like in exchange, he became the third largest shareholder in MCA, the
parent company of the universe.
So like major, major deal.
I didn't realize he was so invested in it and probably the family still.
I who knows, but like at least in 1990, it was like, well, Hitchcock is like super
intertwined with this company.
Yeah, we need like, yeah, he does.
He didn't get the Spielberg deal or anything, I guess, because it wasn't the theme park
yet, really. But the Spielberg deal and that he was like that he still like makes money
from the park. Yeah, somehow.
Yeah, but me. I don't know.
That's be interesting because there's still stuff of his who knows what exactly the deal
was when you sell all of it.
And does it still?
Well, I mean, they still are.
Right. So like the franchises they still own in the movies and they're on Peacock, like
Jason said. But yeah, does there any when you retire the ride to those benefits?
All the yeah, all the everyone standing at all the old rock and roll guys are signing
these big deals now for their whole catalogs.
But some of them have different like some of them are just a blanket signing over their
catalog for a bunch of money.
And then the whoever buys it can do literally whatever they want.
And then some people are like selling Neil Young is like half sold his and he still gets
like kind of a say. OK, what's going on with it?
And maybe is when he dies, the estate will.
So I wonder, like all these interesting deals straight to commercials like we've been
waiting so many goddamn years to Ohio.
We're going to embarrass the hell out of him from beyond the grave.
Cortez, the killer in a Chili's commercial.
Cortez, the killer fajitas.
Old man, take a look at your life.
Is that him? That's yeah.
That's him just over an Applebee's commercial with like check out Father's Day's
Bud Light special big Bud Lights for three dollars.
Take your old man's had a look at his life with.
That's what's going to happen.
Some chili peppers.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, these are clearly big ticket items.
All these live. It's a little scary, like watching everybody cash out.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Bob Dylan cashed out for what?
Like 500 million, like something 500 million or something, I think.
He was one of the first ones I feel like was high profile.
But yeah, they're all cashing out right now for just an insane sum.
So like a horrible corporation can use these now for the rest of time, I guess.
Don't know. One of them should sell the catalogs to Universal because we know what happens.
Oh, yeah. Universal has all the musicians.
Oh, master recordings. Oh, yeah.
Sorry. I just have to mention.
Get well, Jimmy Buffett, whatever happened.
He had to postpone concerts for like six months.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, got well, Jimmy.
This will that would if anything happened, God forbid.
Suddenly you get the heaviest podcast, the ride.
I don't think we've ever done a one a 90 minutes of solemn.
Oh, we will.
Suddenly, it's the most solid.
We'll edit out the jokes if there were even jokes.
Well, we'll we might try jokes throughout and then you kind of like snap at us like, hey,
cut the shit. Not today.
Not today. Or, you know, maybe I'll just do that one alone.
We've never done.
I know. 90 minutes alone.
Just need to work some thoughts out.
So, you know, he postponed some concerts, I think, till March, Vegas and March.
So I guess we got to March.
Well, we're going to go back and celebrate the return to the road.
Welcome the king back.
Yeah. Hopefully, Deuces are Wild Tour still happening then, too, because Deuces.
You know, they're not Steven Tyler's out of rehab back back in Vegas
for the Deuces are Wild Tour.
Is it currently happening?
Currently happening. Yes.
Oh, boy. I'm so sorry you're stuck with your daughter.
Right. Right now, I'm trying not to get COVID again.
So probably not the pit at the Deuces are Wild.
Las Vegas Aerosmith Residency is the place I should be.
But, you know, she can get vaccinated at six months.
So maybe the day after.
All right. And shot. And Mike takes off.
That's right. I'm going for like a month.
Needle ignition. Hey, this is good.
It's fully strong two hours later. Right.
No, sir. Two weeks.
It's like, I can't hear you. I just heard two.
Got to get to a Bob Hope Airport.
I'm on the phone. You can hear in the background.
I'm back in the saddle again.
Over the over the sounds of your weeping.
Yeah. I'm here.
Talking about music, I was surprised in this attraction that they don't.
I feel like music is a big part of Hitchcock movies,
the psycho theme, the North by Northwest theme and the vertical vertical music.
And I feel like usually they mention nowadays
if they make an attraction like this, they they toss a cursory
mention to a collaborator.
But I didn't see any of that or no mention of Saul Bass's famous title
sequences, the defunct land on this shout out has the Saul Bass,
the defunct credit likes all that.
Yeah. Right. Yeah.
He's based. The family said no.
It was about one man about the family.
Fuck off, Bernard. Fuck off, Harry.
He didn't write these movies.
Yeah. Yeah. We don't hear about writers, really.
The I mean, I get what I was driving at, maybe with like so big things
happen in 64.
One is that merger and he owns a bunch of the company now.
And the other thing is that the Universal Tram Tour opens in earnest.
Like there were ways to tour the studio, but the trams and the big pink
glamour trams, that's new in 64.
And think about a time before Jaws, before Earthquake, before any of that.
What is the biggest thing on that tour?
It's the psycho house.
So that's opening day attraction on the tour, which probably cements
psycho as being iconic.
And it's also like the beginnings, I think, of the Universal brand,
where it's like this is like current recent relevant movies were made here.
You recognize that set, you know, it's so well.
And it's a big director that you a regular person know, like, you know,
with the association with Spielberg or Ron Howard or whatever.
So I feel like Hitchcock and Universal Studios in Hitchcock being so married,
it really like that's what Universal becomes a little bit.
And a big another big step in that,
I feel, is the brief era where Alfred Hitchcock became
not just associated with the brand, but the face of the brand.
Yeah, this is one of the big things to talk about.
I think we were excited to talk about.
Don't know when sometime in the mid 70s, but he at least for one commercial,
I couldn't find if there were more.
Do you guys find like you saw the one?
No, I saw the one.
Yeah, I don't know if there was more.
I always thought there were that he made a bunch of them,
but there was only this one that I could find.
So he was like he was a Colonel Sanders for a minute.
It's fantastic.
For Universal Studios, you know, like he's he obviously liked the spotlight.
He liked being Mr.
On camera. Yeah.
In the same way that any of these people, even though you'd be like,
oh, well, they're just behind the scenes when you get older, you go,
well, they're they loved it.
Like he he was in every movie.
He did cameo in every movie way before Stan Lee was doing it.
You know, way before Tyka, my law or fight.
I wish Hitchcock would have rift a little bit.
But if Hitchcock could have ripped,
if you could have mocapped like a court like character from Ragnarok,
like Thor as a very slow talk, slow speaking Englishman who's with him.
So that just happened.
Awkward.
It would be funny.
Is that even a thing?
It'd be funny to see.
Oh, hold on. Sorry.
So sorry. Sorry.
No, please. No, no.
You got to go. OK, OK.
Here we go.
It's good for fly.
They see you know, I had to say it.
I had to cut you off.
Sure. No, that's fine.
I was just going to say a very stoic like Jolly Thor, like with the,
you know, Apple on his head and like the knife throughout the knife,
like being thrown right next to his ear.
Yeah. Like in some of those gags.
Oh, so let's let's get to this.
Let's see Alfred Hitchcock himself extolling the virtues
of going to Universal Studios Hollywood.
Good evening.
Welcome to Universal Studios, where you learn Hollywood secrets.
Music. Fantastic.
And now you'll learn the secrets of the six million dollar man
and the bionic woman on the Universal Studios tour.
So a lot of that when there was just music playing,
we're cutting to all the fun, you know, the kooky characters,
the cowboys and jaws with the big insane teeth, the jaws used to have
and Frankenstein.
But then the the meat of it is that and promoting the new.
Yes, I don't even.
The six million dollar man feels like a different universe than Alfred Hitchcock.
Oh, yeah. And say those words.
Yeah, it does. It feels like he because when you're a kid, you
I've said this before, I you're confused even maybe about like exactly
the like eras these things were made.
Yeah. But Alfred Hitchcock feels like a hundred years before
the six million dollar man.
So it's funny to see him because you're like, oh, yeah, he was alive
until what? 1980.
He died in 80, but he directed a family plot was like 76.
Yeah. Like a handful of movies in the 70s.
He had some less good movies.
Those. Yeah, I don't.
I don't think those are as well.
I've seen family plot like ages ago.
I feel like I at different ages, I would get into different Hitchcock things.
We watched Psycho when I was younger.
When I was in high school, I watched Vertigo in college.
It was like North by Northwest and Shadow of a Doubt.
And then Rope. Oh, and film school.
People were obsessed with Rope.
Yeah. Right.
Worryous of notorious.
I haven't seen it. There's a handfly.
Oh, you would love that.
I yeah, I want to see that one.
Also, James, Jason, your guy.
I love Claude Rainey.
Guy is Claude Rainey.
Hitchcock started so long.
He started in silent films, but also he made the 1935 Man Who Knew Too Much.
And then he made it again.
He made it twice with Jimmy Stewart.
I've seen one of those.
I think I've seen the Jimmy Stewart one.
And when I was listening movies quickly, did I say man who knew too little?
Does anyone have? It's very easy.
I like that is again because I'm stupid.
That might the Bill Murray movie might be more on the tip of my.
That might have passed.
Maybe I'm wrong, but maybe in half an hour ago, I said man who knew too little.
And nobody called it out.
I'm a little sleepy, so it's right by me.
Well, check the tape. I just oh, I boy.
Well, hey, I caught it.
I owned up to it if it happened.
Look, the lifeblood of podcasting is going
calling out when someone mixes up an aphorism or going,
how do you say that word?
Say that again.
We've done it to you.
Yeah, I see you every single episode on other shows.
So it makes me feel a little better.
Junker not chaperone.
I chaperone.
I'm talking about when I am not the only one who says I think that's a reason.
Some of it is like, yeah, like a regional thing that I've just never heard.
But yeah, anyway, no, that happens all the time.
Yeah. Oh, excuse me.
What did you mean?
You motherfucker. I'm getting your ass.
What do you mean?
You call it a Hasek instead of an Ottoman. Yeah.
Destroy him.
You got I think you said you did that to me in like 2010 or 2009.
We were like doing an improv scene.
You're like, what the fuck?
In the scene. Literally not known.
Yeah. No, you need to know to do an improv scene.
If you suggested an item that I'm not familiar with, it was never.
I was just a thing.
I think it was just an old timey phrase, a word that stuck around in the family.
And it wasn't until I was much older.
People were like, what did you call that?
What was the word? Do we know Hasek?
Oh, that was that Hasek was in an impasse versus Ottoman.
Oh, that was a real thing.
Yeah. This was this like happening.
I never forgot. Yeah.
That happened.
Let me go back to the Jordan.
Can you pull up the video again?
I might make you like, OK, you well, you have one of the frames.
The hop ready that I yes.
So well, first things first, hearing him say it is weird as it sounds to us.
It's clearly weird for him to say this six million dollar man.
Bizarre word to stress.
Yeah, I hate to cut you off, but it's a guy's like,
well, let's see what Gilligan and the Skipper are up to.
Like it doesn't it feels like he shouldn't be associated with the trash of TV. Yeah.
Is he a love boat?
Is he? Yeah. Is he like, I am wrong, but I could be wrong.
I am the cruise director.
Activity start every day at 8 a.m. on the Lido deck.
A couple is having quite the marital issue.
It will take a lot of drinks to.
So what's the bartender's name? Isaac. Isaac.
Get on it, Isaac.
I know that fact.
I know you are basic geography.
Do you have my back on that one?
So the frame that we're looking at for people who are just listening,
he is like flying and he's clearly flying in this like theme parky
where an effect that they can replicate very easily in front of an audience
where you fly by just standing straight and then the camera moves you to the next place.
So seeing this very stilted hitchcock flight is so funny.
And then when he lands, he gives this look.
He immediately breaks commitment and looks off frame like, was that it?
Can I stop acting like a fool?
Look how defeated he is.
He does. Well, I think he likes like talking to camera and being on camera,
but he likes that genteel nature.
And I think he felt stupid doing what they made him do.
I think he probably did.
But on some level, he still wanted to be a star.
Yeah, I could be super.
I hear they're making a new Superman.
I'm Cal.
Christopher Reeve is no match for me.
Yeah, I know I'm on death's door, but if they just let me screen test.
I'm an ailing old creep, but I could be Superman.
I think Universal probably owes a lot of.
I feel like Universal rides with like a little bit of bodyness
and a little bit of darkness when they work best.
Like I'll toss out like the fake mummy, you know, unloading sequence
and the rumors and the fire, I think are of a piece with like
kind of the comedy in Hitchcock.
Does that make sense?
Or like the comedy and like that his intros and stuff
and like his weird little darkly funny or darkly funny.
The check movies are horny.
They vary horny.
He's a British guy who nailed the American it's like can
can regular people be pushed to do evil things like murder and also
what are they like when they're dangerously horny for blonde white women?
Like he got our ass like he got the Republican Party platform.
That's true. 22.
It was also he was living it because he was freaking out.
What's her name?
Are freaking out is an understatement with Tippi Hedren or something.
I think. Yeah, yes.
You said I so he had been doing Kim Novak, even everyone.
But his movies are all yeah, like his movies are all the what you just
like the the universal playbook body.
Yeah. Violent.
It's anyone called Hitchcock's movies.
Body.
Yeah.
Well, again, Jason said I let it slide, but I'm like, we just say body now.
He said without being stopped.
He body.
I said body for you there.
What would you when Jimmy Stewart in rear window is discussing the brazier
that what's your name is working on?
You would call that a little body.
Little body.
The body is joke.
North by Northwest, which I like in college.
Even even I at the time of like a freshman college is like, come on, man.
There's that so many gags of him going to kiss the love interest.
And then a train goes into a tunnel.
This happens multiple times in the movie.
I see. I see. I guess that I got away with it
because trains are like the third lead in this movie.
I just I swear the two of you are double handedly
keeping the word body alive in this century.
Yeah, I think this word is retired if not for you two guys.
I wonder if Hitchcock ever said it in one of his intros on the TV show.
It sounds like a word he would say.
It's of his era.
Maybe that deserves a good I was looking for his appearance
to see if he was that he was on like What's My Line and stuff.
He was on like talk shows.
He's on some weird. He's not going to.
They're guessing him immediately on what's my.
You think he can't do a voice?
You think he can't hide that voice?
My name is your Alfred Hitchcock.
It's Alfred Hitchcock.
I work in an entertainment sector.
Hitchcock, get out of here.
I'm interested in murder.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. All right.
We know who it is. Yeah.
Do you have you considered bleaching your hair?
I do see a headline, Alfred Hitchcock's body game with the vertigo.
So somewhat people have associated Hitchcock with bodyness before.
A hundred percent.
Look, their movies are a little body, a little body, I would say. Yeah.
Would you agree they were a little bodies?
I think so. Yeah.
Sorry, new listeners.
We're sorry we lost you.
Yeah. So if you've turned it off now because of all the body talk, we apologize.
What were you going to say? Oh, you were looking up cameos.
Oh, yeah. Just saying I didn't see him on Love Boat.
I just saw he was on some talk show.
You know, a Tom Snyder show he was on, but he did not do like a guest spot.
But this silly him flying around is really funny.
Oh, boy. There's a billion dollar man.
I wish there were a ton of these and I wish he was still around today
to talk about her new things on the universal.
Oh, we all have to make sure to vote.
Covid boosters are available in the city.
What? Walking by Vailen,
the Covid boosters by Vailen.
Check out the new universe store with custom items
from all three pitch perfect movies.
Is the song when I'm going back pitches?
Yes. Albert Hitchcock doing the cover.
Albert Hitchcock singing cups when I'm gone.
When I'm gone, you're going to miss me.
You're and I'm gone.
But then it's like the slow clack,
clack, clack.
All right. Well, that song is 48 minutes now.
They should just have an actor play him.
Why are they not doing that?
Let's just have an actor doing playing him on the commercial.
It would make so much sense to have a walk around Hitchcock in Universal Studios.
They never did that. They should have.
Yeah. Because Lucy, you can I don't I haven't seen Lucy walking around lately
at Universal, but a couple of years ago, there was a walk around Lucy still.
There was a Charlie Chaplin.
Yeah. Was there a Groucho maybe at some point?
Oh, maybe. I'm not sure that would I guess.
He I guess he seems more famous than Groucho,
at least more in the modern sense.
I could be totally wrong.
But Groucho was a performer.
So sure. Yes.
And he did a lot of TV later.
And that's the old Groucho old Groucho.
He was a totally different guy.
Also pretty can't talk about old Groucho.
Oh, man.
He did enough groucho.
Gilbert got it on the billboard Groucho impression
where he was just like so slow by the end.
He was like such a fast talking guy in all the movies.
And then he was just so slow on like Johnny Carson's like Jerry Lewis.
Like that's that other era where he's just like a different person.
Mothball. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I understand your age, but then people like live in that for decades.
Yeah. Slow version of themselves.
It's wild this way that can swing, because like I feel like Orson Welles
sounded the same forever.
Mm hmm. The 30s to the 80s.
You know, Orson Welles should have done commercials for Universal.
Gee, like there is a theme park, California theme park.
Now they've screwed me on a couple pictures.
So I'm going to be up front with you on that.
There's still you just find so much weird Orson Welles stuff like you.
He's like this talk show that he did.
Have you ever seen any of that?
We're never getting out of this episode.
I know. I'm sorry.
Say what is it? Go, go, go.
Orson Welles' talk show that didn't really work
where he's like obviously drunk.
And I think Jim Henson was on an episode like fascinating old Orson Welles clips.
He had his own talk show. Yeah.
I don't remember that one.
Some of it's on YouTube.
I forget if it's just the pilot or if there's more.
There is a pilot for like a Twilight Zone
esc Alfred Hitchcock presents esc show he did that is so cool and weird.
And I forget what it's called, but it's really good.
And it's out there.
I forget if I'm mixing up with the was Jim Henson or not,
but for sure it was the Orson Welles show.
And he's got a big Bert Reynolds on one of the episode.
They're wearing matching suits and shirts.
Big open black red.
That's weird as hell.
Yeah. In front of just giant photos of Bert.
He doesn't have a desk or anything.
It's sort of like what was Merv Griffin like that or like a daytime talk show.
Why are they wearing the same?
I don't know if they mentioned it.
I can't remember.
Was it on purpose or does that just did everyone just wear blazers
and then red butterfly?
You got to go home and watch this.
You're showing a very intimate shot with a spotlight behind him.
It looks like a frame from the Brady Bunch variety.
Or like it's Lauren Sanderson singing a ballad.
Days recording days after Johnny Knoxville show,
they did a jackass episode of Family Feud and Johnny Knoxville
wore the same suit that Steve Harvey wore.
Yeah.
Oh, that's fun.
So I don't know if that was the gag or that was just an accident.
Everybody in the 70s had the open red shirt, red dress shirt,
and then a suit jacket.
Yeah, could have been coincidence.
Anyway, point is Hitchcock incredibly tied to Universal Studios.
So by the time Universal Florida opens 1990, you got to get him in.
And we get this show.
Again, Alfred Hitchcock's The Art of Making Movies,
but alternately called The Art of Alfred Hitchcock or Hitchcock's 3D
Theater.
There was a 3D component of this.
There was a 3D film that you watched that was one of the scenes of it,
which I believe, somewhere saying, this
might have been the first 3D movie on Universal property.
So you have this to blame.
Like a dealer giving an 18-year-old a taste of cocaine.
It's going to be a hook for life.
Are you crazy?
Of course.
And it was replaced by a 3D movie as well.
One of the finest.
Yes, this is the space for stellar cinematic achievements
because it gave way to Shrek 4D.
To Shrek 4D.
Shrek 4D, Shrek, and Donkey R.
Somebody once told me the world is not your roadie.
What is it?
Roadie?
Somebody once told me the world is going to roll me?
It's going to roll.
I thought it was the world is not your roadie.
That's what I was about to say.
Oh, no, that's not the lyric.
OK.
This MF said this world is your roadie.
Go ahead.
Get his ass.
Blast me.
The world is not your roadie.
But in order to go in order through this attraction, of course,
outside, you're looking at the famous silhouette.
In thinking about the silhouette, I was like,
if someone drew my silhouette and that's how it looked,
I would be furious.
This is what you think of me.
I do have kind of big cheeks, so I
would be concerned about that.
It is like the joke of like the Simpsons joke where Lisa gets
the caricature drawn of her on the boardwalk,
and it's just like everything, like all the features,
or everything that you would want.
She thinks she's ugly because of it.
Oh, all the insecurities.
So it does seem like perhaps that is.
But I think also he's got some say.
I bet he likes it.
I think he likes it.
He probably likes it.
Hitchcock likes it.
I wish he was alive just so we could ask him,
what do you think about the big Ted statue next to your silhouette
on the bungalow?
Is that what's there now?
I think it's either Ted or it might be like the Hasbro.
Like Hasbro might have taken over that bungalow.
Oh, there was a Mr. Potato head at some point.
At some point, there's a Mr. Potato head
next to the Mr. Potato head of 20th century American film.
I think you'd be proud of everything that's
been made on the Universal lot for the many years since his
pat, you know?
I think Hitch should be proud.
When I want to relax, I just put on my HD DVD of Evan Almighty.
That's the one I went to too because my first summer
as a tour guide, it took over everything.
It was all over the lot, and we had to talk about it so much.
And then it came out, and we had to talk about it so much.
Yeah.
Psycho, Strangers on a Train, Evan Almighty.
There it is.
Oh, wow.
Hey, Jerry Fett.
There's the Hasbro bungalow.
Wow.
I didn't make up a Mr. Potato head, which
is weird because Mr. Potato head's at Disneyland, as we know,
or California Adventure.
But he's owned by his movie rights for his own solo movies.
Well, and remember, Scott and I stumbled upon the Potato Head
Kids recently as well, a cartoon that I did not know existed.
Yeah.
You haven't watched it since?
Believe it or not, I haven't watched it since.
But there was a cartoon where Potato Head had a bunch of kids.
Wow.
Like in the 80s.
Then they all look like turds.
Oh, I remember this.
Yeah, I kind of remember.
See?
The turds of this.
The turd kids.
Oh, it's that turd kid show.
Anyway, you get inside, and there is a, I remember the lobby.
I remember the lobby very strongly.
There was this big collage, not just a flat collage, but very 3D.
This is like, I had to be there to remember.
But I have this faint kid memory because I was scared by it.
It was like black and white with hints of color.
And then there's film reels with all the names of all of his movies,
but then kind of like surreal, grotesque stuff.
Here's big chattering teeth or a big spiral swirl
or big handcuffs and a big crazy hand.
This was neat, I remember.
And I remember thinking it felt very Nickelodeon.
And then I was looking into it, and this sculpture collage,
whatever you want to call it, was made by somebody
named Diane Stapleton, who was the art director of Roundhouse
and Wienerville.
Wow.
So I guess worked in Orlando.
And so like, yeah, because it felt like that double dare aesthetic,
like a big crazy moldy hand where you felt that somebody just
made it themselves.
Cut me off after 45 seconds here, but I saw Wienerville live.
I saw Mark Wiener perform live at a racetrack.
A racetrack?
But that's too far away.
Racetracks have terrible vision.
I couldn't see very well.
Visibility.
But if you know what Wienerville is, it was a weird show
with a guy who put his head through a little hole,
and it would make characters look like they were tiny.
Yeah, I liked it.
It made me a little anxious.
Yeah.
I think I bought into it too much.
You thought it was real?
Well, I was like, they're going to turn the Studio On members back,
right?
They can't just leave them like that.
How old were you?
Too old, Michael.
You know what he's talking about?
Too young to watch Psycho.
Too old to believe the logic.
He puppetified people, you're saying?
Well, you would be standing up, and then it
would look like you were shrinking down to puppet.
Because you'd put your head through a hole
to make it look like.
Put your head through a hole.
Like this.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Wienerville, of course.
But they would say so much, like we're going to Wienerfy.
Probably not that.
It was Wienerfy?
They would turn you into, we're going to turn you into a thing.
And I'm just like, oh my god.
Was it Wienerize?
The word Wienerize is like, smirking out
of the distant recesses of my brain.
Impossible.
Well, we'll do a Wienerville episode.
Again, I don't want to get off, again, too many intangents today.
Yes, so to get in, anyway, I just remember,
I remember this entire thing, by the way,
just being so moody, feeling very adult.
I probably saw it when I was nine years old.
And I felt, I was just like scared by all of it,
but also impressed by it.
And I love, I think in both the Hollywood, the mini version,
and the bigger one in Orlando, I think they did a good job of like,
here's a little film school lesson that theme park tourists can access
and go, oh, that's cool.
So that's how we did it.
Yeah, I did not see this.
I didn't go to Universal till I was older.
We were still like brand loyal for some weird reason
if we went to Orlando.
Even though my mom loved Alfred Hitchcock,
it wasn't like, oh, there's an Alfred Hitchcock,
we should go over 25 minutes away to go to this thing.
So I'm seeing it all for the first time.
But we would have gone nuts for it, I'm sure, if we had seen it.
So you didn't see it in person or maybe later?
No, I never saw it.
I just never, yeah, did not see it in person.
Do you see this in person, Jesus?
Yeah, a few times, I think.
I was surprised that it stuck around till 2003.
It lasted 13 years because I could not remember
seeing it in high school.
But I can't think of, I feel like 2001 or 2002, my family,
me, my dad, and brother would go stay at the Hard Rock
and do Universal for a few days and then just drive over
to a couple days at Disney.
And so we were at Universal for a while.
And I can't imagine not seeing this
I was there for a couple days.
Yeah, I think I went and it was still kicking
when I was like 14 or so.
Yeah, and I don't know, held up, cool.
And here, we're getting towards, you
talk about believing things like Jason and Wiener-rising.
Feel free to call it anything that you liked in the 3D movie,
which he says something at the beginning,
this is the best of Hitchcock.
And then you get a big pile of iconic moments,
or at least the ones Universal had access to,
which is most of them.
But they build up that Dial M for Murder was shot in 3D.
And it had never been screened in 3D
because 3D was kind of a trend that had lapsed at that point.
So they only, they theatrically released the flat version.
But this 3D print existed.
So I think that the guides or whatever
would say here for the first time,
even though it's done every day in the theme park,
you get to see Dial M for Murder the way it was shot.
So that's what this big montage builds up to,
which you were describing.
It's like, so there's a strangulation and the?
Yes.
Well, first off, it is a long montage.
And I think at the time, seeing little set piece
moments from movies was a bigger pain in the ass
to track down all these movies.
So it was more novel to see them all again,
even if you get them in syndication or.
And then in a nice theater, too.
In a nice theater, good quality footage.
And but there's a couple things I really like going on here.
There's the Dial M for Murder 3D,
which is wild that that is just in there.
But then pretty much the main 3D thing
seems to be setting up the birds joke.
Where.
Because it gets cut off.
You don't really get to see the full ending of Dial M
for Murder.
Yeah, yeah.
And I got to say, there's another trick in there
where he says, it's time for the main attraction.
Put on your glasses.
You know, put on your glass.
So they show a bunch of shots with characters
in glasses in Hitchcock movies.
But when he says it's time for the main attraction,
there's like multiple shots from the birds.
So they tell you what's coming.
You just don't know it.
It's like a little secret trick.
They subliminally remind you the birds are coming.
Yeah, because what it builds to is
that you're watching this 3D movie,
and then it starts to sputter out.
Is there like that sound kind of pitch bends?
And then the film burns out, and there's just nothing on screen.
Or wait, well, I guess the big thing
is there's like a giant rip all of a sudden through the screen.
And then it becomes birds chaos.
The bird, the famous birds take over this space,
and you see back to what's behind the screen,
which is this big kind of implied sound stage sort
of space.
And yay, speak of the day, Gremlins 2
was just brought up, the other prominent thing,
where film breaking happens.
I would always buy this.
It would scare the hell out of me any time.
I mean, still, like it is a very like,
apparently the projectionist the first time this was screened
thought something was wrong.
Like he bought it.
So this is great.
In a 3D movie setting, the film burns out,
and then a bunch of animals attack you.
It was like very chilling to me.
I loved this thing.
Yeah.
And Kevin touched on it in the Defunct Land.
Like Tippi Hendren's daughter bought it when she first saw it.
She was like, oh, fuck.
She was startled.
There's also very funny that once the screen rips down
and there's the fake sound stage behind it,
they do some classic 3D, this girder is coming right at you.
This pipe is coming right at you.
Yeah, sound stage stuff.
A big old pipe.
Yeah.
It gets a little silly the longer.
I think it's very chilling when it starts.
And just haunting, seeing these birds kind of slow motion
fly towards you, which was, I'm sure,
a big pain in the ass to shoot.
They showed in the Animal Actors Show,
you've got to get a fan out to keep them
into where you could focus on it.
But then, all right, what would a bunch of birds
really make lights fall and then the lights spark
and people fall off ladders?
I guess birds are like, in the movie, the birds,
they're throwing themselves into the foam booth
and killing themselves.
Yeah.
So I guess if they're hurling themselves at lights,
I guess it could maybe knock a light off.
They're not like special birds in the birds, right?
There's just too many of them.
Yeah, what is the plot of the birds?
I don't think it's ever just, it's like.
It's not?
No, there's got to be a reason.
They didn't like fly by an overturned truck that
had a secret cocaine shipment in the undercarriage.
Are the birds on cocaine?
That's what I'm asking.
I'm going to Google, are the birds on cocaine?
The birds.
1964 on cocaine.
No, it's not like a modern film where it's like,
how did the monsters get spot?
Or like, how did Herman and Lily meet?
How was Herman created?
I don't know.
Well, if there was a scene where the birds all snorted cocaine,
it was cut.
And they didn't bring that back for the theme park version.
Keep talking.
I'll find it.
Well, yeah, it gets so silly what happens.
Like a fire starts and the lights are crackling.
But then that turns into fireworks.
And so then it's like nice magic of movies, fireworks.
And the final bird that flies up towards the camera
morphs into the famous Hitchcock silhouette,
which has a confusing message to me.
Like, Ben, the bird was hitch the whole time.
It was a big pain in the ass.
Caused chaos wherever it went.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kind of like pecked at people.
Me with them.
Oh, wow, Jason's right.
There's no real reason.
It's like North by Northwest.
They're like, we've got to get the documents.
Clown on me for saying that was wrong, now.
You fucking asshole.
You thought the birds were a spell?
You thought there was like polluted water or something?
That's a cool thing about it.
They don't know.
I don't know.
Something's happening with birds.
I think executives were nervous about it.
Like, there were multiple things where it's like,
how are we going to film this psycho book?
Like, how is he going to do this?
I believe in early marketing gimmick of like,
don't learn anything about this movie.
Just come see it.
And I think the first round of crowds who saw it were like,
holy shit, like we're freaking out.
Because of the twist, yes.
Well, the twist and also like that music sting
with the shower sequence is very jarring the first time you
see it.
And the character, spoiler alert, killed off.
Yeah.
Who's presented as the protagonist.
Yeah, that was crazy.
That was one of his big twists.
It's like the start of Executive Decision
where Steven Seagal dies really quickly.
Yeah.
Have you ever seen Executive Decision?
No, I haven't.
Oh, you'd love it.
Oh, man.
Kurt Russell.
Oh, I just watched Breakdown for the first time.
I've never seen that.
Breakdown, really.
You should check out Breakdown.
Well, this confirms I'll keep going into Kurt Russell.
So included.
I've never watched Backdraft for all though.
Didn't watch it when we did it in the first.
I haven't either.
I could not remember if I had ever
seen the ending of the movie.
I could not remember if I had ever seen the ending of this.
So we watched Get Out the other day,
which does feel very hitch cocked.
He's Mr. Universal now.
Yeah, Jordan Peele's Mr. Universal.
He kind of took the spot.
He really did.
With the set next to the psycho set.
Yeah, the current director face, I guess.
We walk through again.
We'll talk about it later.
But when you're walking around, you walk right through Nope
slash Usiverse.
Oh, this is a good chance to talk about it
because we didn't really talk about the Nope set that
got added to.
Yeah, so we'll talk about it in the Horror Nights.
Great, great.
OK, OK.
Yeah, you walked through a big one.
Walked through that.
Well, let's move over to the psycho room
because that's where you're at.
After you watch this montage, you
try to get the birds out of your head.
But then there's more horrors awaiting you
because there's an indoor set, an indoor version
of the psycho house and a sputtering Bates Motel sign.
And this is kind of a combo of clips and demonstration stuff.
But I think it kicks off with Anthony Perkins himself
in walking out the door of the iconic house, welcoming you in.
And then the mother from upstairs yells, no, I tell you,
they won't be feeding their ugly appetites
with my food or my son.
In a psycho rewatch, this struck me
as one of the sillier elements of the film,
that the mother is a cartoon witch.
Yes.
No, boy.
They really could have made that a reasonable older lady's
voice.
It also is not a voice that I can imagine Norman Bates doing.
Right.
That's a crazy.
He's like the master of, he's like Terry Fader.
I was going to say Mark Weiner.
I was going to say another.
The great puppeteers.
Yes, that's true.
I mean, I think people, you would probably argue that the first,
up until Janet Leigh getting killed,
that's the best part of the movie,
is that whole sequence where she's on the run, checks in.
It's so suspenseful.
All the driving.
All the driving, all like checking in, Norman.
And then the rest of the movie is like good,
but the tension's sort of a little bit gone there.
Yeah, yeah.
Obviously, there's still a twist coming at the end.
There is the scene with the private investigator,
who in the remake is William H. Macy.
Detective Arbogast?
Arbogast.
That was my favorite part in re-watching it, was the boy,
whoever, I know the old actor is Viggo Mortensen in the new one,
but getting out of the car and Arbogast being mad at Arbogast.
Arbogast, whatever.
Also, there's a Ted Baxter cameo at the end of the first cycle.
What?
Is he one of the guys in the?
He's just working in the jail.
Wow.
I don't even know if he has a, he might have one line,
but he might not.
I never knew that.
The overhead shot when the detective walks up the stairs
and they shoot it overhead in the hallway,
and Norma just full speed runs at him.
Yeah.
It's terrifying.
Yes, that's terrifying.
That rivals the earlier stuff.
Yeah, I'm not saying it's bad.
I'm just saying that first shot, it's almost like, what,
Wally, where the first part of Wally is like a little bit.
Yeah, well, I think the second one got me as a kid.
I'm like, oh, they're not going to do that again.
And then they do, and it's such a disorienting angle.
And then it's kind of cartoony how he falls down the stairs.
That is the, that does not, that didn't age as well.
I watched the making of the Gus Vansant 98 Psycho,
where William H. Macy's talking that out with him.
And like, well, because I remember in the first one,
it looks a little silly.
So we're going to do it a little better.
And Gus is like, no.
No.
No, no, no.
It's still special effects.
Shot for shot.
Oh, so we're going to kind of, OK.
And you could tell Macy's like, your funeral,
but I'm getting a paycheck.
It reminds me of in The Batman.
The, that's still, the Robert Patton said Batman.
There's a scene where the Riddler like just brains a guy
and he just runs full speed at him and goes, ah,
like he's in a dark apartment.
And it's just the most unsettling thing.
And I was watching it in the dark alone.
And I was like, Jesus Christ, is the whole movie
going to be like this?
You got afraid?
You were afraid of the Paul Dano?
No, he just does his guttural scream.
I'm trying to remember.
I've seen it, but I can't remember what part you're talking about.
I think it's the mayor.
I think it's when he, I think he's watching the news.
And then the Joker, or the Riddler just silently appears
behind him and then runs full speed at him.
Oh, I remember that scene, yeah.
And it's terribly unsettling.
And that they don't do again in the movie, I don't think.
In The Batman.
Right.
Yeah.
Modern masterpieces, modern itchcock.
I liked it.
It's very long, but I liked it.
They try to do a lot of, it's a few
movies.
It's a few issues of a comic book.
So this thing, you're like, then you're kind of bouncing back
and forth, like you get a, it's a great, it's a classic early
90s universal walk and talk.
Hi, I'm Anthony Perkins.
When we did this, we went da da da.
He's very good.
It's great to see him in this video.
And nice to see him in sort of like, you know,
genteel Phil Hartman like, you know,
being that he's iconically such a creep.
Although he's like, he has his own like charming.
That's actually a mistake of the Vince Vaughn thing
is that he's like weird and ticky and tucking his shoulder
the whole time.
And whereas like you could see how original Norman Bates
would kind of lure you in.
Yeah, because he saw like he seems wholesome and innocent.
That's what Norman Bates charm was.
Had a hard life, Anthony Perkins.
Put himself in conversion therapy.
Whoa.
I did not know that.
He was not.
He was gay.
He was actually, Stephen Sondheim and him worked together,
I think only one time.
But he was kind of Sondheim's muse for a while.
And they were very close.
But they made this movie called The Last of Sheila
that I watched a few months ago.
And it's awesome.
It's like a whodunit kind of movie.
And it's got James Mason and like a very young Ian McShane.
Like it's in the 1970s.
And you're like, I was like, who is that?
They're so familiar.
I can't place it.
And it fucking Ian McShane.
Wow.
But yeah, Last of Sheila.
Check it out.
That's a great movie.
Huh.
But yeah, he's like super like dapper Sherman.
And you got to like the real guy playing the,
even though he passed away not long after this.
Right.
Just was sick of the sad life.
Early tragic AIDS death.
But he fit this in.
And I like seeing this in the Hollywood version.
They repurposed this part.
And this is where you get between him and the in-studio crew
who are going to recreate the shower scene for you.
You get great, legit good, like classic universal factoids
about this.
You get a little mini film school, which I liked.
But this Hitchcock stuff was gone
by the time I was a tour guide.
But it was always recommended as like, hey,
if you get stuck by the psycho house,
you can go into these facts.
And I like the classic facts.
The blood was chocolate syrup.
Well, this isn't a fact, but the joke,
the scene that drove thousands from the shower to sponge baths.
Kills.
Every old VHS rip of this online, that joke kills.
You could get stabbed doing a sponge bath too.
That's true, yeah.
It's still in the tub.
It's not the shower part of it.
Yeah, you can hide razor blades in that sponge.
Oh, god.
That's horrifying.
Yeah, scary.
Jason, stop.
Secret blade.
Stop it.
The twisted mind.
This seems like some twisted idea out of the asylum that
is Blumhouse.
But then you, the legit cool fact, and probably the main thing
they're demonstrating, is that the knife never actually
enters the skin of Janet Lee.
And that this is all done, it's really left up to your imagination.
You fill in the gaps.
And that's cool.
And it's cool that they take you through the angles,
and they recreate some of the angles,
because this is the epitome of perfectly chosen, whatever it is,
these 15 shots or whatever, and what poetry they are.
And the only appeal of that 98 Gus Van Zand is like,
well, it'll be interesting to see the shots again.
Even though he put in weird that there's psychedelic shit
when her eyes kind of, it's not good.
It's so not good.
It's like, yeah, the same thing.
That's the only appeal of when Weezer did the Africa cover.
It's like, we may as well hear the music again.
I would, yeah.
Yeah.
I think I would still like, I had more fun watching 98 Psycho
than listening to it.
I never made it all the way through, because that's sacrilege to me.
Right.
Some good actors.
My Hitchcock is there.
You got some good actors steering that ship.
Well, what you end up with is a scene, the very last scene,
has Philip Baker Hall and Robert Forster, greats, who have passed on.
You're like, wow, they filmed together.
And they refilmed that shitty end scene where everything is over explained
to you, and it maybe only confuses things more.
So you're like, is this the only time Forster and Philip
Baker all were together?
Was this crap?
That's a good question.
I think that was, yeah.
But they're not even really in the same shot, even.
So anyways, like this demonstration.
And then did you guys find the trivia about the Janet Leigh
in this show?
Who played her?
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
No.
We got a picture.
Jordan, do we have a photo of a woman in skin-colored shower suits?
Cheryl Hines.
Young Cheryl Hines, apparently fresh out of University of Central Florida.
Oh, that's Jane's alma mater.
Whoa, wow.
And then went to work at Universal.
Yeah, and also worked at Universal.
That's the pipeline.
Crazy.
Yeah, well, there you go.
Well, she can look at Cheryl Hines as the path from Central Florida
to Universal Orlando, too.
And then, yeah, she's with an anti-vaxxer.
Now, are you talking about Cheryl Hines' real-life husband?
Is that what you're referring to?
Yeah.
I've kind of heard of Robert Kennedy.
Robert Kennedy.
Junior.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not the first.
I mean, the first one might, you know, they might still be alive.
Well, that's a different thing.
Yeah.
They're all still alive.
All of them.
They're all alive.
All the Kennedys are alive.
There's one more photo.
Let's just put it up to say we did.
See?
Look.
Yeah, there it is.
In the press kit.
She said it was a bizarre job.
You're taking showers in fake nudity in front of tourists every day.
And then, like, I couldn't find video of her doing it.
But the other, it's a weird, like, little mini scene within all this,
if you watch the video, where, like, she's mad at the crew.
That has to recreate Psycho every day for some reason.
She's, like, complaining at him.
Yeah, all of that.
It sucks.
Because, again, I had not seen this in person.
So I'm watching the video, and Anthony Perkins is there.
And you're like, he's hitting the right mood.
It's a little scary, but it's a little informative.
He nails it.
It's good to see.
The music is good.
Then it's like, hey, here comes the performers.
And you're like, oh, god.
These Orlando guys in, like, shiny jackets.
Kind of like the Carl Wilson jacket I like.
But it has the silhouette of Hitchcock on the back.
And, like, yeah, I don't care that the fake director and cameraman
and fake Janet Leigh aren't getting along while doing this.
And she's like, why do you think I'm upset?
Everyone's just going to be looking at me and saying,
Janet Leigh looks better.
And you're like, why is this weird, like, they're having, like, a domestic dispute?
Yes.
There's one version I saw online where there's a lot of jokes
between her and the director, like, is this about last night?
And then it's like, oh, it's cold in here.
And he goes, like, yeah, just like last night.
And I'm like, this must be the chunk of lines where they said, like,
you can improvise.
And that improv would go on to surf her well later in her career.
Yeah, sure.
That's where she learned.
It's not necessarily the performance fault.
I'm sure that's sort of, like, the directive they were given.
But it's completely, totally off.
Yes.
Like, what the mood they've set up.
And now you're just getting, like, bickering people you've never heard of.
And it's like, it just doesn't.
That's the one drawback.
That's the one thing I don't think I love.
I would agree.
I had no memory of it.
It's a well-designed room.
It's a great little sequence.
This bickering does not match.
When you're talking about a director known for, like,
just a sparkling dialogue.
Yeah, tightness.
Yeah, interesting filmmaking.
I will say that, like, so after they show you both sides of, like,
how they shot the scene, and then there's, like, a switch at some point
where one of the crew members puts on the dress and, like, the fencing face.
Oh, yeah, whatever, like, shadow face they have to put.
Yeah.
In Andy Bergen's one, I believe he says,
they had to blacken the stand-in's face.
And I'm like, oh, they would have massaged that line nowadays.
That doesn't sound great.
Different verb, perhaps?
It's just a mask.
So, like, at some point they swap, and then that mother starts, like, going after the director.
You think that the audience volunteer has lost it and is starting to stab everybody
and chase them around the set.
But then there was a little fake-a-roo pullback of the curtain,
and it was the director of this little show did a little change.
It's a great gag.
That, I think, is totally correct.
Well, that's their true, they're already, like, feeling the,
we've talked about it, Universal's basically shifted almost completely around the, like,
making of a movie and showing how it works.
And we're just doing it now.
You're just in it, and it doesn't matter.
We're not going to be behind the scenes.
But you can feel already there's a pull of, like,
we should give everybody, we could just scare them more.
So they throw that in there in between.
It's a little...
You get a little...
Whatty.
Oh, well.
It's a little outrageous, you know?
There's a shower happening.
Something goes wrong.
A class, an early example of something is going wrong in this presentation.
That's true, yeah.
So, yeah, this is like a superstar television at MGM Studios a little bit,
where you get the person up, and then there's a little, there's hijinks.
And it's got a lot of the stunt show features of, like,
fake person that you think is a person from the audience.
And kind of making a fool out of the, like, even the reveal of,
hey, look, your dad's dressed like an old lady now.
Yeah, right, exactly.
This is another one.
Humiliate Dad wins every time.
And this was a hallmark of the 90s attractions.
Dear Penthouse Forum, I was cucked by the Universal Studios Florida resort destination.
I was made to look a fool.
Is there any, we've said it before,
is there any attraction now that is humiliating dad?
That's all about humor.
I don't think, I mean, other than, like, just the start tours or something,
but not specifically.
The only thing you can do to humiliate him, I guess,
is buy him, like, the grumpy shirt that says, like, I'm an asshole.
I'm a grumpy asshole.
I gotta get one of those now.
Less attractive grew.
I gotta get some of these shirts now.
I realize now I can buy them and wear them proudly.
Oh, finally.
Full dad shirts.
Like, the Donald, we've talked about this before, they sell dads,
the Donald shirt and grumpy, because they're both jerk characters
who don't want to be at Disney World or Disneyland.
Are you gonna be able to, like, settle into that type?
You have, there's hours of you on record saying that you like being at theme parks.
Well, I'll try.
Maybe it'll feel too weird and I'll have to remove the shirt and buy a different one.
You have started drinking coffee in the last year.
That's true.
You can get the grumpy, like, don't talk to me until I've had my morning coffee, you know?
Okay.
I'll do that one.
Start doing it.
You've got a whole new world of t-shirts ahead of you.
You gotta size up.
You gotta size up one or two sizes with those ones.
They need to look like a fucking sail on a sailboat.
Those grumpy.
Thick, Haines beefy tee, thick beefy tee, but like two sizes too big.
Dads are so humiliated in the theme park shows to have to wear a dress,
but their t-shirts are big dresses.
That's true.
They don't even put it together.
They don't even know.
You're in one.
You changed one for another one.
A shirt with like an angry looking stitch on it that says,
like, my kids don't give me a minute's peace.
It's a real, the next step will be if they can customize,
put my children's names in this angry.
Ohana means family.
Family means don't wake dad before 10 on the weekends.
I need shirts that keep going to the back.
There's more complaints on the, here's some other gripes I got.
When my wife looks me in the eyes, the fire is gone from her vision.
That's just got a very cold looking Merida on it.
Crust arms.
Okay.
We've talked about Hitchcock being bad to the actresses.
And this is, and we talked about these often repeated bits of trivia.
This was for sure a thing I was supposed to say as a tour guide or that I could say
that like, you know, part of one of the things that made it so unsettling
and it made Janet Lee's performance great was that Hitchcock would change the temperature
of the water without telling her that it goes from warm water to ice cold.
And then that caused terror and shriek and surprise.
Yes.
But I watched some DVD making of the shower scene where Janet Lee denies this and even calls out.
She says, now I don't know what they're telling people on the universal tour,
but let me just say this for the record that that did not happen.
They never used ice cold water.
And in fact, that was very well taken care of because it was extremely,
like she describes it all, how like, you know, the final shot is her dead with the,
like starting from very as close to the eyes you could possibly get and the water's still running.
And they had to do that so many times because like it was manual focus.
Like there was no way to like keep the focus.
So like she's there slumped over for hours and she said everybody was a gentleman,
except for the crew members way up in the rafters who she said,
I think they brought more crew members in to look at me every day to ogle.
Interesting.
I wonder, I sorry, I wonder how many people would object to like if they went through,
just like watched you do your tram tour speech.
Would Paul Giamatti have had an objection of the big fat liar portion or something?
Like, because I wonder how much like movie fact is not fact.
There's a lot of, you know, when I said he was very verbally abusive to all the children,
I don't know why I went out of my way to say that this character assassinate Giamatti.
Yeah.
I mean, a lot of, yeah, a lot of the Hitchcock stars, you know, older stars make appearances
like in this attraction or at least like, yeah, that story about
Tippi Hendren's daughter, which I do, which could be Melanie Griffith.
Oh, right.
I don't know if she had a sister.
I just saw the phrase, uh, Tippi Hendren's daughter.
So the line is Tippi Hendren, Melanie Griffith, Dakota Johnson.
Wow.
What a lineage.
Yeah.
And then they were all, that was the family that lived with the lions for that weird movie.
Yes.
Roar.
That was way worse than anything Hitchcock ever did to anybody.
Yeah.
And they chose it, I think.
The, um, old Jimmy Stewart is really something in his post-show segment.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they got Jimmy Stewart.
Old Jimmy Stewart, again, on talk shows, fantastic.
Really good.
So slow, you read a poem about his dog.
Jim Carrey did it, I think he did that on Saturday Night Live, that is a bit once.
Yeah.
Or Joe Pesci show, was it?
Oh, yes.
I think it was a Joe Pesci show.
Oh, okay.
Hey, speaking of anti-vaxxers.
But in a theme park context.
Not Pesci, Pesci used that, we don't know.
No.
In a theme park context, so you've got the Statue of Liberty scene from the saboteur,
a carousel, which I think is strangers on a train, but there's also a carousel in Shadow of a Doubt.
And then you have a city, like, you know, apartment buildings from rear window
that you can stand with binoculars.
And Jimmy Stewart is telling you, did you find the murderer yet?
They might have found you.
Like, I was like, that is insane to think about six-year-old me with binoculars going like,
there's a lot of things going on in these apartments.
I hope the murderer doesn't see me.
You're looking at murder and there's women in their underwear instead of that?
And that's a body sequence.
There's a rear window.
Oh, speaking of Brian Marriott, Funko is making a rear window board game, I saw.
What?
Yeah.
Funko is in the board game space now.
I like that you still chose, you didn't say speaking of Funko,
you said speaking of Brian Marriott.
We were a long time ago.
Three hours ago.
Look at rear window board game.
Jason, look at this.
Wow.
Yeah.
But wait, it's the actual, like, poster art and stuff?
Okay, so they're not Funko-fied.
It's not a Funko-fied.
Oh, right, right.
No, no.
There are Funko games.
I have a Seinfeld Funko game as well that I haven't played yet,
where there's like Funko-fied versions.
And that thing I got you was Funko as well.
You gave me the full, yes, the Seinfeld set in Funko, which is so awesome.
Thank you, Brian Marriott.
This last room, I liked so much.
This crazy, surreal, as with the opening collage or whatever,
that here's like a bunch of, like, wow, there's a rear window and a carousel
and a big Statue of Liberty torch all in one space.
Like, that felt like being in Hitchcock's mind, where here's big icons.
Yeah, that's great.
Yeah, yeah.
That's almost like Batman.
Batman in the Batcave in certain versions has, like, a big penny,
big two-faced penny and a big dinosaur.
It's like stuff he's collected and it feels like this is the same thing
Hitchcock's, like, artifacts from the movies.
Yeah.
And it bled into, like, the Bates Motel, like, a gift shop as if it was at the Bates Motel,
which is also a pretty good gag.
And yeah, that Bates Motel, I mean, they still sell Bates Motel stuff here and there,
but I remember after it closed, a bunch of it showed up at the, like,
there's a store in the New York streets, and I'm not sure what it is right now.
A few years ago, it was, like, Irish stuff, you know?
And before that, and maybe at the same time, it was all the clearance merchandise.
And so I remember going there and being so excited that day.
I was like, I'm going to get a Bates Motel keychain.
It does say Lisa on it, but it's also $2, so I can't be too picky.
You bought not your own name.
Yeah, I bought not my own name.
Yeah, I was a cool guy in high school.
What do you want?
Did you, like, show it off, though?
Because that is, like, ironic to not have your own name on a keychain.
Yeah, I think that was part of it.
That was a very funny gag for 17-year-olds.
Like, look, I got a keychain with someone else's name.
I think it was too, I think it was rectangular.
And I think he ends were metal and pointed.
So I was like, this isn't practical as a keychain, but I'll keep it in my little souvenir box.
When Kmart was going out of business, we went there every week, a couple times a week.
And I remember I bought these, like, yellow sunglasses.
And I was like, you know what I'm doing now?
I'm wearing these every day 24-7.
Yeah.
This is my thing now.
And yours was the Lisa keychain.
Lisa keychain.
Me and some friends were, like, walking through Sears once they had clearance, like, socks,
like, teen socks.
And we were like, let's get matching Hottie Patrol socks.
Oh, wow.
That's too blotty for me.
Hottie Patrol socks, Bates Motel Lisa keychain, and you in yellow sunglasses.
Everybody's in their best.
I mean, we've got a couple of fucking quarterbacks right here, a couple of prom kings.
No denying that.
Look at this motherfucker.
He can't even say he's denying.
He fucked up.
I'm sorry, everyone.
No, this is gold for misspeaking.
Classic misspeaking.
There's one thing I want to go back to.
I know we've been going forever, but I can't let the episode pass without bringing this up.
This is back in the Psycho sequence.
And this is one of the things that Anthony Perkins talks about, where he,
this is a quote that he kind of, like, interrupts the live demonstration.
So he can give some expertise, because he was Norman Bates.
And he says, well, he wants to say a little of what made that original scene work.
And I think it goes on to make the point that the knife never entered her skin, and here's why.
And in setting that up, he explains how this could have been a lot more grisly.
And what he says is, you see, Psycho was based on a real murder case.
Years later, they made a much more graphic film based on the same case.
It was called the Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
But Hitchcock felt the violence of the crime was just too horrible.
And thus, you know, it was tame, and the audience fills in the gaps.
I was like, I never heard of this.
The same thing as Psycho and Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
Now, so all right, let me figure this out.
And here's the big crazy reveal.
There's a fella named Ed Gein.
Oh, Ed Gein, yeah.
You know Ed Gein.
I know Ed.
Yeah.
You're a good fella.
The Butcher of Plainfield, the Plainfield ghoul.
Sure.
I didn't know any of this.
The same guy, there's elements of Norman Bates and Psycho,
Leatherface and Texas Chainsaw Massacre, and Buffalo Bill in Silence of the Lambs.
Wow.
Like real things pulled from this one, got one man is all of these monster, like lawn chaney, but real.
Every monster.
Now I'm going to, you've heard a little about Ed Gein.
I'm sure that, I didn't know any of this because this is not my area, true crime and stuff.
I'm sure there is a podcast, this is probably a podcast that's all about Ed Gein.
Well, I want to know what does Ryan Murphy have to say about Ed Gein.
Now I'm going to put a blindfold on and throw a dart at a dartboard, starring Adam Devine.
Okay.
Hey, okay.
It's Ed Gein.
All right.
Netflix limited series produced by Ryan Murphy starring Adam Devine.
Money please.
I think maybe I saw that there's something from an American Horror Story that's also Ed Gein.
I'm sure.
So yeah, he might have beat you to it.
But just in wrapping my head around Ed Gein, okay, so Middle of Nowhere creepy house,
incredibly like crazy, crazy religious mother.
Sex is evil and women are instruments of the devil.
This was instilled and things don't get too crazy yet.
I was going to say this is the way all three of us were raised.
And we haven't killed anybody yet.
We haven't done that.
So this is so far it's okay.
But anyway, then he like, he might've killed his own brother when they were younger
because there was a fire and he went and told the police,
my brother, I lost him in the fire.
And then they came to the fire and said, well, what happened?
He said, oh, he's right there.
And why do you know now?
So maybe Shadely killed his own brother and then his mother died.
He put the word mother on the tombstone.
So that's real.
And then so the fixation with mother and wanting to dress up like her, that's a real thing.
Then you go to Texas Chainsaw Massacre, which I've never seen.
I should see it.
But I'm told that there's furniture made out of human skin and bones.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, I believe so.
All right.
So that's this guy.
He did that.
He made furniture out of skin and bones.
And then to bring silence to the lambs in, the woman suit, the skin suit.
Right, right, right.
That is him.
And that's him trying to be his own mother.
Isn't that weird that Norman Bates and Buffalo Bit, two of the crazy,
and that like they just didn't go crazy enough.
It wasn't just a wig.
This guy fucking.
I like you're delivering this as if it's the same way we're like,
and you know, imagine you're Claude Coats.
He was the guy of the Haunted Mansion who actually added some of the dark stuff.
And he was also Snow White's Scary Adventure.
You're like, whoa, I didn't know.
I only have one tone.
I don't know how else to do it.
I mean, I would have done it the same way.
When tragedies befall me in my life, I'll be talking in the same tone.
I'll be nervous laughing because I'm losing my, I don't know what else to do.
So I came out and there was a screwdriver in each one of my tires.
And I don't know who did it or who I've wronged.
And fun facts, the manufacturer of the tires was.
I guess a Goodyear tires, but it's like, you know, an always ready screwdriver.
And, you know, they're owned by the same parent company nowadays.
I just I just I also want to add, I just purchased a leather face neck,
a toy from Target for a friend of mine.
And that's true.
I did it a week and a half ago.
So now, you know, the toy was inspired and I would say,
wait, sorry, Brian Mariani.
Yeah, Brian.
Well, that's Funko.
OK, OK.
Andy Falk is NECA.
Oh, sorry, NECA.
So, OK, well, I'd say, well, you know, I'll throw it out to Brian or Randy.
When is the when's the tribute to Ed Gein?
We pay tribute to the to the the fictional monsters.
But where's Ed Gein's?
I'm sure they're working.
He wrote all Hitchcock didn't think of any of this shit.
Ed Gein did it.
Yeah, right, right.
I go in that there was a thing that stuck out to me from this.
Who is the oh, God, I forget.
I didn't write.
Is it Shirley MacLean is talking at some point?
Yeah.
And the yes.
Yeah, she describes a lot about the TV show.
I yeah, I did.
She at some someone in one of the narrations discusses that he's like,
you know, and of course, Hitchcock movies usually have a big ending
or a plot twist or something.
Whereas Hitch would say, I I'm worried I got the word wrong.
It's got to end with a smacker.
Yes.
And I was just like, I don't remember that one that I forgot about.
I don't know.
I've never heard.
I heard I saw the video, but I've never heard that if that somehow I might have missed that part
in the montage or missed that part in the post show because I feel like if I was a little kid,
I was like, do you know that Hitchcock movies end with a smacker?
Like I would have been really just insufferable talking about smackers.
That I mean, it's a good philosophy.
We should incorporate that word.
And if we're on the way out here, let me try to end with a smacker.
Jordan, there's there's two videos that I haven't shown and they have the same title except one's
part one, part two.
I think maybe skip.
Oh, we already saw.
OK, no reveal.
I was gonna see if we could surprise you guys with who's going to but let's this is a smacker.
Nonetheless, yeah, this is let's bring some more great kid.
Now that we've tied together Buffalo Bill and Leatherface and Norman Bates,
let's bring another character into it via a Universal Studios Florida promotional video
from the late 80s telling people what was going to be there.
Let's just play and see.
Good evening fellow tourists.
I was on top of these stairs.
But the second murder took place.
Master, let's cause it because the listener can't know what's going on.
Oh, that's Sebastian Jackal actor Christopher Lloyd.
You may know him mainly deadly game.
That's the character he played on UPN's Deadly Games.
But he also played the character Doc Brown.
And there's I don't think we've really talked about this that Doc Brown runs around
and sees all the he travels to the future of 1990 to see all of the things that are
going to be at Universal Florida, which brings him.
We got to cover every bit of this, but he ends up face to face with all this crazy other
iconography.
But here he is snuck up into the psycho house where Alfred Hitchcock is talking and explaining
how he shot the scene.
And then very strangely, he says master, which is I get what you're saying.
He's a master filmmaker, but it's weird.
Yeah, it doesn't feel like something Doc Brown would say.
Master of suspense.
No.
Why would yeah, why wouldn't you just say the master of suspense?
Master.
Yeah, I know it's odd.
Really weird.
But then we get a little more into the Doc Brown voice, I'd say, with what he says after
this.
Weird, weird little mini Doc Brown monologue about why Hitchcock's a great director.
But then if you could pull up the other video, this is a smacker.
Imagine just imagine watching.
You think you're watching the end of Psycho and then you get this.
This is the scene where this is Vera Mile, right, is walking up to what she thinks is
Norman Bates' mother in the room with just one light.
And this happens.
And the chair turns around, but it's we know it's going to be a corpse, right?
It's Doc.
Wait, stop, pause it, pause it.
Doc Brown is Norman's mother.
Yeah.
Twist, but then further twist.
Then it cuts to Doc Brown regular at the door watching this and he gets scared.
Right.
So this is like a trippy.
This is like Doc Brown's having a nightmare.
He's seeing himself as Norman Bates' mother.
Or he's he's messed with the time stream so much he's actually running to himself.
Which we know he's not supposed to do.
They do all the time in the movies, but you're not supposed to do that.
Yeah, well, OK, so he's being cautious.
If you see yourself, get out of there.
Yeah, because also he really probably didn't know what the hell, what happened here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
This is beyond this is more like a being John Malkovich, like some surreal.
Why is my face on this?
I don't know.
There's a little tale more to then some people come in and remove the grandma or the mother
prosthetics.
Yeah, so this is great.
Well, I think we did I think we did a little of this on the fake Doc Brown episode, perhaps.
Yeah, or a different maybe a different one.
But yes, this is such a weird.
It also like isn't necessarily the character of Doc Brown.
He seems to love the magic of the movies.
Well, check this out.
This is the rest of this.
Nothing more magical.
Makeup cosmetic beautification.
Wrong.
Horrific mutation.
Live horror makeup show with a secret of horror unfold before your very eyes.
Whoa, it's two attractions.
Yeah, yeah.
Then he ties it to the horror makeup show, which we'll do down the road maybe next year.
You know what?
This is one where I would we've said we've criticized this before,
like on the Benicio del Toro opening of Guardians of the Galaxy the Ride.
This is maybe one where you don't you want him to like suggest that he's Doc Brown,
but not be Doc Brown, where it's like I'm Christopher.
And like he's acting like a little like Doc Brown, but you don't want it in continuity
because it doesn't make any sense that Doc Brown loves movies.
I don't know.
Well, he loves Edison and Edison had a lot to do with early movie technology.
I forget what exactly, but no, he would love all of the and the knife ever never actually entered
revolution rope.
It's all one shot or so.
The magic of the movies would have you believe I just I use the time machine to go back
and see that first screening of the train coming right at you so I could see a whole crowd go.
Everyone jumped away.
They thought I was real.
I've been proven wrong.
You're right.
It should be Doc Brown.
I just wish there was movies.
Yeah, I wish he just had talked more about the movies he loves in the back to the future movies.
I'm sure he will in Back to the Future 4 through 6.
Sure.
That will happen as soon as Zemeckis pass away.
Honestly, maybe before.
Well, who knows?
Anything's possible.
I was kind of hoping this that reminded me of another universal video that we haven't
done, but I feel like we have to do an episode on the John Forsythe souvenir video you could buy.
Oh, yes.
For like $40.
And I think there was a Florida one and a Hollywood one.
So if you want to talk micro targeting.
Yeah.
Yeah, both.
Oh, God.
Well, I would love to.
I love those so much.
Movies are the wizard's wand.
We've brought it up in bits and pieces.
Yes, let's do that soon for sure.
But I checked that for interesting clips.
And can you imagine that how they addressed this was John Forsythe, who is an actor on
Charlie's Angels, by the way, who's very...
I only know this.
Charlie's Angels.
Farrah Fawcett's luminous hair.
So I have the poster in my garage.
What can I say?
I'm a man.
Could you dye it a little more platinum?
I was going to say, if you can imagine what John Forsythe did in that video, as we've
been doing the whole time, is walking up turning profile and saying, good evening.
Nice.
You can't resist it.
We couldn't resist it.
No.
We had to do it the whole time.
And he made all these great movies, but what we're going to know him for...
This is what I'm saying.
He's going to feel like a theme park character in 100 years.
He's a guy who said, good evening.
And he was very retunned.
That's all we'll know.
He was like Shrek.
Like Shrek after him.
He's just laying there.
This is the space where the big bulbous characters live.
The ogres.
Shrek and Hitchcock.
Psycho, North by Northwest, Vertigo, one or two others might sustain.
But then the perspective will be like, you know who directed those?
The Good Evening Guy.
That guy.
I thought he was just from commercials.
Made movies too.
They're going to look, he's going to be deep faked before we know it.
And he'll be in stuff again.
And he'll be doing intros and there'll be a new Alfred Hitchcock hour.
Sure.
Or whatever it was.
Let's get him on the show.
We could get an AI Alfred Hitchcock saying like, sign the Change.org petition to bring back Shrek.
Forever Dog's making acquisitions lately too.
So Brett, if you're listening, could you acquire the deep fake rights to Alfred Hitchcock?
And have we have his likeness rights and we can do a podcast as him.
Well, that'd be a big boost for Forever Dog.
Alfred Hitchcock presents the podcast.
We'll do it.
But you know, why do the deep?
If it's just audio, why do the deep fake?
Well, we have video here.
Yes.
Oh yeah, true.
You want maybe the whole thing.
But if you need a little help filling in the voice, we got Mike to do it.
It's like 95% of the errors.
It's pretty close.
It's kind of an easy one to do.
It's kind of a satisfying.
Don't cut him down like that.
Well, no, sorry.
Difficult to master.
The master of the master of suspense.
I'll be, master!
I'll have mastered it by Tuesday.
Oh, so it's too late.
The episode's done.
Oh, well, but when I do this podcast on Forever Dog, the official Alfred Hitchcock podcast.
Yeah.
Is it really him?
Did they reanimate?
Did they dig him up from the grave like Ed Gein would do with his bodies?
No, no, no.
It's a modern mimic named Mike Carlson.
I'll wear his skin if we don't get the deep fake rights.
If it's still around.
I don't know that it's around.
I would have wanted that.
Where my skin?
He's probably buried 10 minutes from here.
Probably.
Let's go dig up.
I looked it up.
He was buried at sea.
What?
Isn't that weird?
Yeah, ashes at sea.
Well, we got to get his ashes, put them back together.
Jason, get your sailor.
He loved making lifeboats so much.
Jason, get your sailor boy outfit on.
We're going out to sea.
All right, Mike, get your giant t-shirt with Stitch on it looking pissed.
All right, great.
Don't send me on a recovering ashes mission until I've had my coffee.
Mike, you say it last.
You got to do it as the man.
Oh, oh, oh, yeah.
I was like, what is he talking about?
You've survived.
Podcast the ride.
Right as Jordan pulls up a picture of a Hitchcock.
Funko.
It all ties together.
It connects.
The circle has been looped around too.
What's the word?
Someone roast me for not saying the phrase correctly.
So yes, you survived.
You could find us on the socials.
Marriottie's Funko Pop.
There is one of him?
Yeah.
That's a lot of-
Who's Becker?
Is he another Funko part of Funko, I think?
I think he's another guy.
Presumably.
To fucking be these guys, you've got all the Funko plastic that you're ready.
You could do whatever you want with them.
There's a Jordan Blum Funko Pop too.
Oh, sure.
They got the director series.
These guys would be Ed Gein's now.
If they- Ed Gein had to resort to being creative with corpses and skin because that was all he had.
If he had a bunch of plastic like Marriottie, maybe he would have made some great toys instead.
Yeah.
I think it's- yeah.
It's a real shame.
Anyway, you know what's not a shame?
The great bonus material that's available on our socials at Podcast the Ride, the merch in our T
Public Store, including for Haunt Cast the Fright.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out Haunt Cast the Fright, the Cemetery Gate,
and the as yet named Club 3.
We've got to spookify that.
You can get one more bonus there on our new tier.
You can find all that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And thanks to Jordan Black Cats.
How about that?
Spookified.
Pretty good.
At Forever Rabbit Dog for producing this episode.
On the second gate, Munsters 2002.
Coming up on Club 3 is voted by the audience.
2022.
What'd I say?
2002?
Fuck.
I'm gonna-
Got him!
No!
Don't roast me!
Wrong year, moron!
Let's end it before I fuck it up more.
Wrong year.
Damn it.
So much roasting.
You end it with a smacker.
Bye.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehm,
Joe Silio,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team,
and liking our page on Facebook.