Club Three.
Lazy Club Three, start here, no pressure.
Jason, hi.
Mike, hi.
Hello.
You know, let's like ease into the pool
because we have our work cut out for us.
This is the most, you're gonna hear a lot of me going like,
and what does this say?
What are my notes?
What does this even mean?
Why did I write this?
It's there, it's sprawling scene notes.
You almost went into the Biden right there.
Yeah.
Biden explaining Kingdom Hearts.
On a Patreon episode.
I, I got a square gown, square jeans.
Goofy in a ship, he's in a ship.
Mickey doesn't live in, he doesn't live in suburbia.
He's not wearing the pants.
He's with Zorai, red shirt, polo shirt.
He's in Traverse Town.
Okay.
I grew up in Traverse Town.
I took the train from Traverse Town, Washington, DC.
I used to live.
Folks in Traverse, you could buy things at the store.
You could buy things for some sin.
How are we?
It used to be red and green.
You'd buy the, you'd do a Louis, right on the shop.
They wouldn't be there.
People turn in Harless foes, they're turning in Harless.
They're not Harless, Harless.
Harless.
This might be five years of doing this show.
This might be the most I've ever been like,
ah, I am in over my head.
That's completely right.
We are talking about Kingdom Hearts.
That was the suggestion.
I'll go into some of the other Club 3 things.
But what you reminded me of is something
that I wanted to say right up top.
That the general suggestion was,
we wade through Kingdom Hearts.
I think the audience knew that we are not
previously familiar with it really, unless I'm wrong.
But there was also something that people threw out
when it won the poll was maybe a video game
and seemingly Kingdom Hearts enthusiast,
Matt Apodaca, could join the guys.
And the only reason Matt is not with us
is because I think you want the over in over your head.
We don't wanna guide.
We wanna be in an unfamiliar world like Sora
going through the realms of light.
Trying to piece together what's going on.
I hear you.
You don't wanna guide like,
I guess Donald and Goofy are not guides somewhat.
They haven't been in any of the places either.
Yeah, they're fresh too.
So yeah, I think that's right.
I'm also intrigued by the listeners.
Do they,
what do they think this episode's gonna be like?
Cause like,
do they think like,
oh, I know Kingdom Hearts very well.
It'll be funny to watch these guys struggle through it.
Or are they like, oh, it's so ridiculous.
Like watching some kids who don't know how to swim.
Just swatting and swatting around and getting nowhere.
Only getting deeper and deeper.
Yeah, I guess maybe that's what they're looking for.
I mean, look, they're just looking,
I guess we're the professionals.
They're kinda looking to spin gold
with anything that we get thrown.
So, you know, look, I'm up to the challenge.
I hope you mean spinning earths.
That's what we're gonna be spinning a lot of today.
I, you know, I'm not opposed to
convoluted continuity or lore.
I was walking around the other day
and I saw like a tweet.
I was looking at my phone.
I saw something about the X-Men and I was like,
oh my God, I've been reading X-Men comics for 30 years now.
It's like second grade.
That's true, yeah.
They're like extended family members.
And if you ask me to explain, there would be,
there's some goofy bullshit in there.
Sure, yeah.
There is some really convoluted stuff
and some stuff where it's just like,
the young X-Men traveled through time
and now they're on the regular X-Men.
No, there's some stuff that sucks here.
In their mix with all the like different stages
where I was like, and this was really cool
when I was this age and then this happened at this age
and this person came on board.
So you haven't spent 30 years with Kingdom Hearts.
I haven't spent, no.
You could spend what, 20 years?
It's been out for, yeah.
The first one came out 20 years ago.
Happy 20, Kingdom Hearts.
PlayStation 2.
Yes, that was when I knew I was in over my head
because I was like, oh yeah, there's been three Kingdom Hearts.
I remember my brother was really into those games.
No, no, no, no.
And I looked it up, oh no, it appears
there's been the 13 games if you count.
Nintendo DS, Game Boy Advance, mobile games,
browser games that are no longer available on browsers.
Yeah, and look, we're gonna limit it.
We're gonna put up some barricades
because the madness has to stop at some point.
Before we get into that Club 3 business,
I wanna mention, because look, first of all,
this was the stats-wise biggest mandate we've ever received.
48% to 21.
This demolished.
I couldn't believe how well Kingdom Hearts,
we got hit by, we all got smacked in the head
by a very powerful keyblade.
The runner-up though, just to mention it,
and I like to read the full thing written,
and this is from Shane Cannon,
who gifted us Garfield Eats and also the pros
that made Garfield Eats so fascinating
because he spit out the whole story, very contained.
And I think a pretty good effort by Shane Cannon here
as well, this is the runner-up.
Please discuss the 1999 Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade
featuring Lou Baga, Verne Troyer on an Austin Powers
Spy Who Shagged Me-thiefed float,
an Ask Jeeves float, Rudy Giuliani,
and a special performance by the Bacon Brothers.
By the way, that's just a smattering
of when you watch the actual opening as they did.
That's just some of who gets mentioned at the top,
which at the time the person doing the announcements
was Don Pardo.
It was a rare outside of SNL in the 90s,
Don Pardo appearance saying, Lou Baga!
Something he never got to say
because Lou Baga didn't do SNL.
Those snooty bastards didn't let Lou on.
So that will carry over to the next round.
I'm not gonna say the whole thing again,
but the 1999 Macy's parade, this is very intriguing, right?
I was excited when this showed up.
I think we were all like, not rooting for this over,
but if it had landed here, would have been exciting.
So it moves on to the next month,
and that might be weird because it's November now.
Are we really in December going to do a Thanksgiving parade?
But Christmas parade.
Yeah, sure.
There's a parade.
It's the holiday season, I think.
That's not so far removed, I think.
And what does the Macy's parade end with,
but an appearance from Santa Claus.
The big man himself.
Who never hosted.
Santa never did it.
Alec all the time and never Santa.
Yeah, you know Santa, he did mad TV.
It was more his seed.
We had him on Fridays once, and it didn't really pop.
So I guess, I think this very well could carry over.
I actually think it does make sense for December.
So if your heart is in the 1999 Macy's parade,
feel free to vote for that.
But this brings me to December.
That is the next club three.
We've never done a holiday.
So I would say the encouraged areas for your suggestions,
which we encourage you to post below in the Patreon app
or the webpage, something holiday oriented would be great.
Look, we love our parades and our Christmas specials.
There's a lot of odd amenities in that realm,
but also there might be rides or seasonal attractions
we don't know about.
I think there's a lot of possibilities.
Yeah, there's the we wish you a turtle Christmas,
Ninja Turtles movie that is something I didn't even know
existed until a few years ago.
I don't wanna say you vote for that,
but I'm just saying if somebody wants to throw it
in the mix.
We can always campaign.
We can see we can nominate.
I'm gonna toss this out in the vein of the Macy's parade
that everyone's thinking like, oh, Christmas and Hanukkah.
Don't forget about New Year's.
Cause I'm sure there's a lot of weird New Year's
specials and ceremonies, you know?
True, true.
Don't sleep on New Year's.
Don't sleep on New Year's, especially because some
of that block on local affiliates is usually a local
fireworks display or something.
I mean, like the, you ever watched the Jamie Kennedy
disaster?
That's one of the best videos.
There's an amazing cut down of a local affiliate LA,
Jamie Kennedy hosted in front of the Chinese theater,
a New Year's special that went horribly awry
and where they didn't really have security or control over.
There's just like, just absolutely, I was gonna say wasted,
but I will say hammered people.
It's like insane how fucked, it's the most fucked up people
you've ever seen on TV and right towards the end
a fight breaks out.
It's so, and if you can imagine that Jamie Kennedy
is not the consummate broadcaster to maintain control.
He's not the art link that was needed.
So that's a good one.
I think you're absolutely right.
There's a ton there, but also don't forget,
we've announced our theme for some of December's,
I mean all of December, but it would fit in the realm
of the topics to do something avatar related
because we are celebrating Feliz Navidad, the way of winter.
So if there's some particular facet of avatar,
Pandoran culture that you think belongs on club three,
I think that could be possible as well.
A lot of choices, a lot of options.
Yeah, yeah, so get creative, get a little creative writing.
Yeah, do some work.
Yeah, yeah, it is a work for us.
So that's it, and I think I maybe,
I wanted to take a little time with that
just to talk about something that isn't Kingdom Hearts
before we launch, before the journey begins.
You know, Kingdom Hearts has always,
it feels like when you're a passenger in a car at night
and you kind of see, maybe you're a little tired
and you kind of see little streaks of light
or buildings kind of lit up out of the corner of your eye.
Like I remember Kingdom Hearts always being around
and I knew it had a very passionate fan base
and it was a huge hit multiple times over.
Oh, continues to be.
Look, there's no disputing of that.
It's just not anything we've ever, unless, am I mistaken?
Do you have experience with Kingdom Hearts that I don't know?
I don't have experience.
I think that I'm the biggest gamer of the three of us.
Yeah.
And I'm not a big, I'm not an insane gamer,
but I still, I have the Switch, I have a PS5, I had a PS4.
I will play if Mario Galaxy when that was Wii, right?
No, the new one was, I can't think of Mario Odyssey.
I played through that, I played through new Zeldas.
Yes.
I play wrestling games still, but I'm not like constantly,
I'll do like a month where I'll play a game
and then I sort of won't play video games for a month or two.
Like I'm not consistently gaming.
Not always playing something.
Yeah, I have video games that I still like.
A lot of stuff is just unfinished.
I like those, Batman Arkham games, I still like.
Those are my dream come true, those games, how good they are.
I have not played Gotham Knights, supposedly not as good.
But those games are amazing.
I told the story when you lit a horse on fire during Zelda
when we got it five years ago.
We did tell that on the show.
Yes.
Okay, I have that in my note.
No, no, I wasn't gonna tell, I wasn't gonna build.
Get ready for a tale, everyone.
I couldn't, we talked about that somewhere recently
and I couldn't remember if it was on here.
Yeah, you stripped Link's clothes off,
you put him in his underwear
and you immediately lit his horse on fire
and the horse were sent running
and Gio and I were laughing more than I've laughed
in like a decade, because we didn't know that was possible.
Kind of not intentional.
No, you just sort of, you mashed buttons,
his clothes came off, the horse was lit
and it ran and we were laughing so hard at it.
Before that, my big video game,
I think that the games I was invested in before that
were like Max Payne 2 and Grand Theft Auto Vice City
and that's coming up on like 20 years for both those games.
Right, and again, Grand Theft Auto, all pandemic,
I was playing with Susser and Gio and her friend Tim.
So yeah, so I'm playing games.
I will say this about Kingdom Hearts.
I was always excited about the idea of it.
I think because it's like kind of an RPG,
even though it's not a straight RPG, like Final Fantasy.
I never played the Final Fantasy games,
which are classic games that everyone should play.
I just never got into those
and this is made by the same company
and a lot of the same people.
Silver Juno Square.
Yeah, and there's so much in common.
Cloud shows up from Final Fantasy 7, Cloud Strife.
I know the names.
Sephiroth shows up, one of the bad guys.
But I'm just saying like those types of games,
I didn't really play very much.
Zelda was a little more action oriented than some of them.
I think that's why I was more with Zelda,
but I was always a Nintendo kid first.
So I was always like, oh, Kingdom Hearts,
I'm gonna get to this one day, much like Yellowstone.
I'm gonna get to Kingdom Hearts one day.
I played Epic Mickey.
I don't know, were you around?
We would play, yeah, we would play a little.
So Epic Mickey was in a similar way to this
where it was like, we're gonna take a bunch of,
you remember this?
Yeah.
We're gonna take a bunch of Disney stuff
and sort of put it out in one big universe
and Oswald, right when they got him back.
Oswald is a villain, that's cool.
Yeah, and so we played that.
That game is pretty good.
Not quite as-
Just as great as I wanted it to, yeah.
I thought it would be like jaw-droppingly.
Yeah, then there was art.
I'm sure I've said this many years.
I think we talked about this years ago,
but there was art, promo art for it,
that looked incredible.
Looked like cool and stylized dystopian versions of things
and like return to Oz,
but it's the Magic Kingdom or something.
And you're like, this looks awesome.
And then it sort of ended up being a big cartoon game,
which is fun, but not quite,
it didn't quite live up to the promise
of what it could have been.
Sure.
So I did play some of that, but yes,
Kingdom Hearts, for 20 years, I've said,
I gotta play this game.
I'm gonna get to this one day.
And you're being made to.
And I bought the game three weeks ago.
Wow.
Three or four weeks ago, I bought the game,
which has like many, many of the games in it.
And I said, oh, this is, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna be the guy that plays the game.
So I'll have that perspective.
Yeah.
And I'll get, and you gotta go,
I'm probably not gonna be able to beat it
cause it's a long game,
but I'll at least have some time with it
and I will have some perspective.
Here's the thing.
Having a child,
it's not the easiest thing to play video games sometimes
when the baby is very young.
Also, I said to myself,
I'm not going to look at strategy guides.
I'm gonna just do this.
I can do this.
Cut to a couple of days ago where I go,
I haven't gotten out of fucking Traverse Town.
How have I, I've spent so many hours,
I feel like playing this.
I'm still stuck in the first like 5% of the game.
This is where you are before you get to go
to like the real places.
This is the like gathering supplies place.
So I'm playing this like a couple of days ago,
holy shit, I haven't gotten anywhere in this game.
I haven't done anything here.
I go, I've been playing this in like little pieces
for like two weeks.
Oh my God.
I've barely done anything.
Mike, you are describing,
I ran into a similar problem where I was like,
okay, I know how to get a grasp on this.
I'm gonna go to YouTube
and I'm gonna type in Kingdom Hearts Explained.
And after watching five Kingdom Hearts Explained videos,
I went, oh no, this might be harder than I thought.
So then I tried to find play through videos
and my options were, do you want a 10 hour one
or a 20 hour one?
And I was like, oh no.
Yeah, I was watching the 10 hour one then
to sort of catch up with the rest of it
because yeah, I was like not getting very far.
And I was, again, I should have gone
to strategy guide immediately.
Cause I would sort of play for 45 minutes
and go, I don't know which way I should go here.
And then I would kind of, I would miss a doorway
or something, which is where you would push
the story forward.
Cause like Donald, I don't know,
we should start at the beginning,
but like there would be certain things
you'd have to trigger going on.
And I was like very casual about it.
I go, it's okay, you'll do it at a certain point
and you'll figure it out.
And then a couple of days ago I go,
I barely play this game, I think.
I think I've just been roaming around this town casually.
What's going on?
I watched, I tried to look at videos
that like IGN had done
where there was another company called Giant Bomb,
which I was like, okay, I know I've seen Giant Bomb videos.
I kind of know what this is.
And so I watched it and it's these two guys
worked for the company and they're like, yeah, all right.
We're finally gonna try Kingdom Hearts.
And I scrubbed through like a while in
and they're like setting up the control options.
And I was like, oh, this isn't working either.
I spent so much time on the island.
There's an island to start out in the game.
I realize now I spent like days on this island.
The way this episode's gonna go, we aren't careful.
We're gonna be on there, we'll do two hours
if it's only on the island.
Okay, here's what's gonna make this doable.
Guys, here's the assignment.
Well, this helps a little bit.
And this is from Alex Tucker.
Thanks for the suggestion.
Alex, congrats on winning the poll.
We need an episode of the boys trying to figure out
the plot of the first, first Kingdom Hearts game.
Please, boys, it's so confusing and nonsensical.
Donald is a wizard.
Yes.
Well, he's the Grand Mage, she's the Grand Mage.
And Goofy is the head of the Royal Guard, I believe.
Okay.
For King Mickey.
Yeah.
Okay, what I'm getting at here, first game.
He's limited it, so let's cut any expectation
that we did anymore in the first game
because there's plenty in the first game.
Yes.
I was curious about everyone's strategies.
My strategy ended up, I found a mirror,
a helpfully breezy four hour 38 minute cut scenes.
Yeah, that's good, yeah.
I, guys, let me say this out loud for the first time.
I hate the phrase cut scenes so much.
Really?
Because it sounds like deleted scenes is what it sounds like.
Now, it took me so many times going like, cut?
So these were cut from the game?
No, no, no, they're cut, like edited.
Oh, interesting, I've never even thought about that.
It's always stuck, it's been like a bristle
in my brain for a long time.
Did you ever read, like when you were younger,
did you, like in the same way that we all,
I think, read Entertainment Weekly pretty religiously,
I found a bunch of my old Entertainment Weekly's
a couple days ago, did you ever read like Nintendo Power
or any of the other different gaming magazines?
Not like, to recreationally, if it was like something
specific that I was, and I'm like the least gamer,
by the way, I'm like, I play the new Mario carts
when they come out and that is all.
Doctor, you're a Doctor Mario fan though?
Yes, the original 8-bit Doctor Mario, correct.
Okay, that's something.
Yes, that was a big relaxing wine habit for a while.
Yeah, nothing since the Wii U for me, no Final Fantasy.
So any Final Fantasy familiarity of characters,
not gonna help me out, I don't know what any of this is.
So we're all going in a little blind,
but all we have to do is the first game.
That's it, that's it.
Unfortunately, a lot of the explainers I saw
were going in chronological order where you have to,
okay, well, you have to go, this game takes place
before the first game.
No, out, it's out, it's out.
You can tell us anything that you found interesting
from that, however, it's gonna get dark,
we're gonna wanna be out of here.
Yeah, I gotta say, the best video I saw
and other people, I guess, agree,
because it has 1.9 million views.
Can't argue that.
But it's called, where did it go?
Kingdom Hearts, but there's no context.
And this is what I, this took a while to find
because the parts, if you just Google
Kingdom Hearts funniest moments,
that doesn't give you what you want.
I wanna see-
There's nothing funny in this entire game.
I want-
This is the most humorless drag ever.
I wish something funny happened.
I wanted to see the two second moment
where a ladim runs by and goes,
oh, hey, Sora.
That's what I wanted.
I wanted to see, oh, in one part,
you can push Winnie the Pooh on a swing,
and if you push him hard enough,
he flies over the 100-acre woods.
Whoa.
That is my interest.
Oh, that's cool.
I have a video I'll play towards the end,
which breaks the rules a little,
but is, I think, worth it based on some things
we've addressed in the past.
So, do you have a starting place?
Maybe.
Okay, Basics 2002, 20 years ago,
made by Square Enix, the makers of Final Fantasy.
Finally, the Disney universe
and the Square Enix universe collide.
So, it's a chance, it's merging Disney stuff
with Final Fantasy stuff, and characters
are very at peace with the Final Fantasy universe
and vibe.
Let me, I'll say one more thing before I do,
which is maybe my previous familiarity
with this game series.
This is the only way that it had come across my desk before,
which is that in early days of YouTube, 2007, 2008,
that I would sometimes be looking for a song,
and I would find not the music video for the song
or a clear version of the song,
but rather an AMV or anime music video
that takes a song and cuts Kingdom Hearts footage
to the song.
And this, so my only awareness was from the,
and I'm like, okay, what can I glean from this?
All right, it's like, this game is about
12-year-old waif nymphs with perfectly spiky hair,
and there seems to be a lot of angst involved,
and then it's always, here's what, okay,
because I started thinking, like, what,
I was just typing in, I was like,
I think I get a sense of the kind of song
this stuff's edited to, and it'll be like Evanescence,
Lincoln Park, Nick, yes, for sure that,
there might be a hundred of those,
or like Tattoo, anything of that,
and that neck of the woods.
And then just footage of like longing and reaching
and grasping, and like with these characters
who are like mainly very anime-looking characters,
but then sometimes like Sebastian the crab
will eek in there.
I don't know why.
Like, this is not knowing the context,
I'm like, wait, so how come, boy,
it seems like these people are really going through a lot.
Why is Dewey there?
And these things always struck me so funny.
It's like, actually, here, let me do, let's do a challenge.
Can you name a song that you think is sort of in that,
in that realm?
Here's what I get, Evanescence,
Lincoln Park, Tattoo, Nickelback.
I also, I looked up some Trident Trees.
Puddle of Mud.
Oh, Puddle of Mud, that's good, okay, okay, yeah, yeah,
let's see, all right.
Puddle of Mud, Kingdom Hearts.
Is it Band Seether?
What about the band Seether?
Oh, Seether's gonna be good, here, I'll do that one.
Kingdom Hearts, AMV, Seether.
What was Seether?
I'm trying to remember.
World Falls Away.
Yeah, World Falls Away, there's so many, there's so many.
What was the first idea, Puddle of Mud?
Yeah.
I, these things, basically, I would, yeah,
so a lot of Puddle of Mud, so much Puddle of Mud.
Here's Kingdom Hearts 2, the Puddle of Mud Blurry opening.
So I would stumble across these,
and I would equate my feeling about it to being like,
you know in The Simpsons, in the Burlesque House,
when Grandpa walks in and he's whistling
and puts his hat and coat down,
but then sees that Bart is the doorman
and then just keeps whistling,
and then grabs his hat and coat again and keeps walking?
That's me with like, all I know is this fucking,
you know, hate to say it, but American idiot,
mashed up with 21 guns, mashed up with these waif nymphs.
That's on the second level.
I don't want any part of any of this.
So that is my backstory, so that's all I know.
I knew that it's waif nymphs,
and I know that sometimes Jiminy Cricket is around.
Yes.
If I can bring us into the very recent midterms,
the Kingdom Hearts midterms connection.
Oh yeah, I saw this, yes.
Did you see this?
Uh-huh.
This was so bizarre to be reading about Kingdom Hearts
and reading about midterm news at the same time
and see the crossover.
Maxwell Alejandro Frost, the first member of Gen Z,
elected to Congress, had tweeted,
I haven't played video games in years,
but I'll always remember how awesome Kingdom Hearts is.
Bizarre coincidence, really strange.
Member of Congress was a Kingdom Hearts fan,
and we defeated a real world, what's his name?
Ah, shit.
Zeena.
No, who's the actually worst one?
Arson with Ansem.
We defeated a real world Ansem, that being Dr. Oz.
Right.
Yeah.
Take that.
The Heartless, AKA the GOP, huh?
Okay, so let's, all right, that said,
we've all established our connection to it,
so I was kind of dreading having to get into
actually experiencing this.
Yeah.
But now I understand the game.
I have a full grasp on the game,
and I can tell you what the game is about.
The game is about zippers.
It's about characters with clothes with complicated zippers
and in places that zippers are not normally,
zippers on hats, maybe zippers are on pants,
but they're on like the knees,
or they're like, maybe it's on the crotch,
but like all zigzag.
And to a lesser extent, complicated belts.
Complicated belts are also a part of Kingdom Hearts,
but I would say zippers more than anything
is the theme of the game.
That may, yeah, that's the main takeaway for you, at least.
That's what I got out of it.
Chain wallets, kind of.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's kind of, it's a very chain wallety game,
and all that music is kind of,
maybe you'd put that in the genre of chain wallet music.
That's 100%, yeah.
Those are fan made though.
Again, I don't want people to be confused.
Puddle of Mud is not in the game.
No, no, no.
No, no.
That would be very funny.
Music's great, honestly.
Music's nice and pleasant.
But Sephiroth, occasionally voiced by Lance Bass.
Sure.
I know that.
Oh yeah, you got a music connection there.
Yeah.
Okay, so, but basics.
You play the game as Sora.
Sora is the main waif nymph.
He is played by Haley Joel Osment,
who's having a big 2002,
because he has also voiced Barry Barrington,
the star of the Country Bears movie.
Jason, would you like us to talk about this
for 20 more minutes, or should we keep proceeding?
Look, it's been long enough.
I'm ready to revisit.
You know?
All right, good.
Please just don't make me look up the difference
between Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep
and Kingdom Hearts Coded.
No, no, this will not,
we have not been given this assignment.
We can't do it.
We were forbidden.
We'd love to do it.
We can't do it.
You know what?
That's fine, because Kingdom Hearts Birth by Sleep
turned out to just be a dream that Tigger was having.
Is that true?
I today was like, all right,
I'm gonna refresh myself with some Kingdom Hearts stuff.
And the first thing I watched, rewatched a video,
and they're like, and that game didn't really matter,
because it was just a dream in Tigger's mind.
I was like, God damn it, come on.
Tigger gets to have an entire game dream?
It's like his Starlight Express.
Oh, that's right.
So, Sora is a cheerful teenager
who lives on the Destiny Islands
and has been best friends with Riku and Kairi
since childhood.
So, there are three waif nymphs.
Three, they have perfect hair.
Their hair that would poke your eyes out.
It's so spiky.
They're all four foot tall,
and a foot of that four feet are their eyes.
Their eyes are very big.
Three youngsters who live in a little paradise
and yet really wanna leave the paradise
and go do other stuff.
Yeah, they're restless.
Yeah.
Yes, because their circumstances change a lot.
Quick notes about Riku and Kairi.
Kairi, female character, played by Hayden Panatier,
who was, of course, in the 2000 Disney film, Dinosaur.
She plays Suri.
So, Hayden plays Suri and Kairi, not Sora.
Suri is not Sora.
Riku, the other boy, is voiced by Seventh Heaven's
David Gallagher, who was the blonde-haired kid
on Seventh Heaven who would run a foul
of light marijuana use, or in one case,
having to huff paint or being tempted.
No, I think he did huff paint.
I don't really know.
I should watch the full episode.
But here's what's crazy about this.
For some amount of time, spoiler, I guess,
a villain of this guy, a major character in this game,
voiced by David Gallagher, who at the time
of the release of this game, had the locker next to mine
at my high school.
I went to high school with this guy,
which everybody thought was really funny,
because this Seventh Heaven, I mean, Seventh Heaven's insane
if you watch it now in general, and he probably had
the most insane stuff to do.
So, I feel bad about it now, because it was kind of
that ultimate, like, you know, oh, boy,
that guy thinks he's so big because he's on Seventh Heaven.
Does he?
Has he ever indicated that he thinks he's so big?
Or have we applied that?
Is he a regular guy who everyone in this high school
is being terrible to?
I don't know, I don't remember.
Guys, that guy spoke to him twice and he seemed fine.
But anyway, it was a good situation for me,
because he was always off filming Seventh Heaven,
or maybe in some cases, VO sessions for Kingdom Hearts.
And you know, you have that double up with the lockers.
I never had anybody below me or above me.
I had plenty of space when getting my books,
because he was never around.
It was essentially like an empty locker.
Thank you, Kingdom Hearts.
Kingdom, I thank you, Kingdom Hearts,
for sending him on these journeys.
These incredible journeys that gave me locker room.
That's great.
So, I was flipped out that David Gallagher is part of it.
So, yeah, they live in paradise, but they wanna explore,
and maybe they've done the math that there's only one Kyrie
for the two of them, so at some point,
dating is gonna get difficult.
They're gonna have some difficult choices to make.
They're competitive.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can sense these guys are not good.
There's a race you run on the island.
Oh, see, this is what you don't know.
I only watch scenes, so I don't know what's going on.
You can maybe fill us in on only that scene.
I spent a lot of time on this island,
and there's a race between the two characters,
sort of for the affection of Kyrie.
Okay. And I lost.
Oh, shit. I lost badly.
Oh, you lost Kyrie.
Yeah.
Riku, you bastard.
Yeah, and when you're on that island,
you have to gather a lot of stuff for your journey,
including fish and some rope and some water,
and this took me forever,
to the point where eventually I did have to look up
where you get the rope, where you really find the rope.
If you wanna go to a fantastical world and find rope,
Kingdom Hearts is the game for you,
because, look, they don't know that they're going
on a crazy journey to all the Disney worlds.
They're going on a raft journey
to see what else is out there,
but then there's a big invasion
and a bunch of scary monsters show up,
and these we find are the Heartless.
Yeah.
They are kind of pitch black, jerry guys who are,
we don't know everything about them at first,
but they seem like pure evil.
They're bad news, clearly.
I hate the Heartless.
Oh, you said it. I really hate them,
and it's not because of whatever their motivations are.
It is because fighting them is the most monotonous thing
you can do, and they keep respawning,
which is a big pet peeve of mine in video games
when character, not all the time,
but if things respawn, meaning that they keep popping up,
when you defeat a bunch of them, you leave that area,
you come back to the area, and then they're there again.
That's always kind of annoying to me.
I always liked it better when you would defeat enemies,
and if you go back, they weren't there.
Yeah.
Because this is a hack slash game for much of it,
and then it has role playing elements.
If I had heard more that it was hack slash,
I probably would have gravitated more.
Exactly.
I think I thought I was more into hack slash
than the RPG elements.
Yeah.
Meaning it's like a weapons oriented game.
Yeah, you're fighting sort of more than
sort of turn-based RPG games, which were very much like,
especially in the early days,
you were kind of solving problems via text.
It was almost like Dungeons and Dragons in a way,
where it's like hit points,
and it was not necessarily an action oriented game.
When they made a Super Mario RPG game,
and I didn't know what it was, and I rented this,
this was one of the most angry I ever was as a child.
I was gonna say, I bet you didn't know.
I had no tolerance for this.
What do you mean?
Why am I picking items?
Then I just go to a screen.
I don't get to jump on the Koopa.
I have to pick something,
and then there's nothing satisfying that happens
when it hits him.
This is the opposite of what I want.
Yeah, I was not into that game,
even though for people who like RPGs, it's a masterpiece,
the other ones.
Paper Mario is sort of in between.
Paper Mario's sort of got some RPG elements,
but is a little more action.
I didn't play that one as much, but yeah.
This one's hack and slash.
It's more fighting, and I'll say this.
This is a video game thing, and maybe the future games.
I did not find any of the action in this game
fun or satisfying.
Wow.
This is the perspective you can bring.
I just watched video.
For all I knew, maybe the gameplay is great.
It might be to people listening, but you didn't like it.
There is something so, you take for granted
playing almost all the Mario's, the regular Mario's,
and the other Mario's.
You take for granted the important controls are,
and how satisfying it is to just do
the basic things in the game.
Even playing the 3D Mario games,
playing the 2D Mario games,
there's something so satisfying about jumping on the Goomba
and the Koopa Troopa's heads,
bouncing from things to things.
There's a rhythm to it.
The sound effects are perfectly chosen.
You really feel like you're doing it.
You feel like you're doing it, but then there's also,
there's a lulling almost effect to it,
where you kind of crave doing it more.
And if you play video games that feel like
they haven't figured out that sort of,
they haven't figured out their version of a calm,
or not calm, but a fun, satisfying version of it,
it is monotonous, and it isn't as fun to make your way
through maybe the slower parts of the game.
This is the case with this.
I have my big key, and I'm swinging into these things,
and there's not a ton of precision to it,
and it gets very boring, very fast,
and there's a lot of these characters everywhere.
The whole game is the heartless.
If you didn't like this at the beginning,
you're in a lot of trouble.
You're in a lot of trouble,
because they're everywhere, they're in the town,
and I went, I don't know about this at all.
I don't think the story could maintain me
playing the whole game like this.
Now, maybe they figured out more.
I'm sure the controls are different,
and maybe more satisfying in the future games,
but the actual action of playing, I was like,
I don't like this.
I would stop playing this if it wasn't for work.
Are you?
This is your work.
Did you get to a point where Goofy and Donald show up?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
I got to that point, but it was,
or again, early in the game,
and I fought a lot of these characters.
I fought a lot of these little characters
in an unsatisfying way.
Video games, and I'm not an ex.
This isn't, how did this, what is it called now?
Get played?
I'm not this guy.
I'm not a pro gamer, but you take,
when you see a game that's figured out
its controls like the Arkham games,
the Arkham games are amazing.
I don't know if you, you know what I'm talking about,
Scott, these, these.
I haven't played them.
The Arkham games figured out a system
now that it's been copied by almost every superhero game
that's come out after the Spider-Man games.
The most satisfying way to fight is Batman.
There's a rhythm to it.
It sort of like time slows down a little bit,
and you lock on, and you can do these massive,
crazy combos fighting like eight guys at once
versus Batman Forever on Super Nintendo.
Pretty boring, pretty bad controls.
That was a game I couldn't figure out
how to get out of the first room.
Yeah, I mean, it's a bad game in general.
There's obviously much better fighting games,
but even when you play the old turtle games
on Nintendo or whatever, you're like,
okay, we've got, you get the point of it,
but there's so much variation on like the fighting system
for the Arkham games, and you get,
you add like gadgets to it.
You add moves to it.
There's like skill in like building up hits,
where like if you don't get hit, you build up more.
So there's so much variation on the fighting,
and it's almost endlessly entertaining.
You can fight, you can just head on punch people
and beat them up, or you can hang from the rafters.
There's so much, like, I only start,
I start to like get very tired in my old age
if I don't immediately enjoy the controls
and the actual action of the game.
I am realizing, for Genesis,
I played the Batman Forever game a lot,
because I was trying, I was like mesmerized by the,
I will say hostile aesthetic.
Oh, it's unpleasant.
Yeah, yeah.
I have it for Superintendent,
I have it if you wanna play it.
Oh, I do.
I just could not stop looking at it,
and I think it was just cool to have a Batman game,
and I'm pretty sure I found it in a remainder bin
or at a used store for very little money.
So that was a big part of the appeal.
I dug through those remainder bins,
because you would find weird stuff.
I loved the 7-Up game, where you played as a spy.
It was so fun.
That game was fun.
Batman Forever was like similar to Mortal Kombat
when it came out, it was very innovative,
because it was like kind of,
they had recorded human beings, basically,
so it looked a little more real, quote unquote realistic,
versus Street Fighter, which was purely animated,
or whatever the term would be for a video game.
And Batman Forever felt like Mortal Kombat,
but I feel like it looked worse,
and it played badly.
They shot real people with the lost highway filter.
The stuff that people say is like,
oh, that's David Lynchy,
and it's always the most basic surface level reading.
The weird stuff, that's where the Batman Forever was like,
people, but kinda.
And I don't know the making of it,
but yeah, you could be fooled into thinking
it looked good maybe at the time,
because it looked a little different than things,
but playing it was, you'd have to really like,
be honest with yourself and be like, this sucks.
Yeah.
It sucks for a lot of reasons.
Well, let's keep plowing, because there's,
I know we get so excited when there's anything else still,
oh, I know something we can talk about for 50 minutes
that's not this, but the sooner we get it done.
Yeah, you're right, you're right, you're right,
we gotta do this.
So, all right, the Heartless, all,
and then it separates this group of three friends,
and Sora, in the midst of this, ends up with his weapon,
the Keyblade, it's a big sword that is also a key,
that also has a dangly with a Mickey Mouse ear on it.
We should also say Sora is like,
kind of Disney bounding as Mickey.
Yes, yeah.
His outfit is like, the color scheme of Mickey.
Red shorts, yellow shoes,
because they think they wanted Mickey
to be the main character,
but then Disney would not allow violence to be happening,
administered by the characters,
which factors into the rest of it.
That's 30s Mickey, where he's like,
picking up cones left and right.
Where he's hunting and poisoning people.
You know, when he was in the comic strip,
read by like 30 million people a day.
Also, the violence in this game is a guy swinging a big key
around some little clouds, like little dark clouds.
Like it's not.
Yeah, I would not call this a particular.
It's not like Mickey in an Arkham City game,
where he's pounding the shit out of like,
prisoners skulls on the ground,
like driving their necks into the concrete.
Like that's not what Mickey would be doing in this game.
So I don't know.
It's all fairly magical.
And we're purely, it's like, island and keys and magic.
And then all of a sudden,
22 minutes into what I was watching,
probably longer if you, much longer if you played it.
Now suddenly look, it's Cinderella Castle.
Why?
And now suddenly we're with Donald and Goofy.
And briefly at the beginning, Minnie and Daisy.
Yes.
And we don't really get why.
I would say that the why of the nymph waves,
plus the Disney characters,
I don't think there is a why.
It just is.
No.
They're together.
That's kind of a thing I always appreciate
about Kingdom Hearts, is that they played it straight.
If they're under the sea,
if they're in the Lion King or the Hundred Acre Woods,
like you just accept it and you move on.
Well, like a Mickey's Christmas Carol,
which obviously that's a famous story,
but it's like, there's no like, here's how they got here.
And I don't think, that actually I think doesn't show up.
Three Musketeers Mickey shows up in one of them.
But yeah, like even the Ghostbuster short that we all like,
it's not like there's some backstory of why,
why are these guys doing this?
Wait, you mean the Mickey cartoon?
Yeah, the one Donald Goofy and Mickey are all busting ghosts
in that old cartoon, which I loved as a kid.
But it's not like there's any, like what, why?
Yeah, I guess you don't want that, but I still am.
Oh, it's confusing as hell.
I think it's jarring to go to and that, wait, okay,
Donald is a wizard.
Goofy's a, he commands a guard.
But it is, it's just a little more,
it's a little weirder than those other setups.
But I'm just saying there is some precedent
for these characters to just be all of a sudden
the reality of what they're doing is just given to you
and not explained.
Yes, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But this is maybe the weirdest scenario where you go,
wait, what?
I would say so.
They get, they're wondering where the king is.
Yeah.
I mean, I think if you're playing the game,
I think the reveal is after a very long time,
the king is Mickey.
Yeah.
But we might as well just say Mickey is the king.
Yeah, you know it,
because everyone refers to him as King Mickey.
They do say King Mickey earlier,
but there's a little tease of like who he is.
Uh-huh, right?
Well, he refers to, in his letter, he writes to Minnie.
So you're like, well, if he's talking about Minnie,
then probably.
Seems likely.
Yeah, I just know it's like a moment
when then he shows up.
Right, right.
I don't know, I haven't seen all of it, so I don't know.
I guess I just meant in people making videos
about Kingdom Hearts.
Yeah, that's fully- Everyone's on the same page.
We're calling him King Mickey.
Yeah. Yeah.
But I think if you play it, it's like, oh shit,
like at the end of Star Wars, Hullabaloo,
whatever the fuck.
Yeah.
Fuck Mickey.
Well, that's a little more exciting.
Well, that's the most exciting thing that's occurred ever.
Because he dances.
Through a letter, they discover that Mickey left in a hurry
and left them orders to travel the worlds
and find a certain key.
So Sora got a key, and I guess the key came from,
no, it didn't come from Mickey, he just knows it's out there.
So Donald and Goofy go find a key.
It's somewhere in the worlds.
What are, are we on planets, or are we just on-
We are on planets.
It is planets.
I think, because they get in a ship.
Because they're in the ship.
Yes.
Oh, the gummy ships.
The gummy ships.
They're in a gummy ship.
They travel, so, I mean,
this would be a little more to be said, I guess,
but mainly Goofy and Donald travel from world to world
in a gummy ship.
And I saw that in a Wikipedia, and like,
oh, so this ties in gummy bears.
No, no, it's a gummy ship.
Is that because it bounces?
Like, gummy berries make you, no.
It is called the gummy ship.
Why?
Because it's made of gummy blocks.
What do gummy blocks do?
I don't, what do you want from me?
Stop it.
Stop the third degree.
Do you feel the same way?
What's gummy?
Why is it gummy?
I don't know.
I have probably, out of three of us,
watched the most anime.
And I have, when I was young,
I watched a lot of hours of Dragon Ball Z.
And that takes dozens, in some cases,
maybe hundreds of episodes to like,
wrap up a storyline.
So, I'm willing to suspend some disbelief.
But I found this all very perplexing.
Looking at it from the outside.
You did too, even with anime.
You still wonder why.
You wanna know why it's a gummy ship?
Yeah.
They just like, I don't, yeah, is it like,
I guess, because Chip and Dale maintain the gummy ship.
Yes, they launched the ship.
They launched the gummy ship.
Chip and Dale get them already on the gummy ship.
Yes.
But it's not like it go,
like it's not.
It's just a ship.
It's a ship.
It's sort of normal.
I guess it kind of looks a little more like,
it could be gelatinous.
Yeah, but I don't think,
when you see the inside,
I think it's all just normal gear.
Yeah, so.
And by the way, we're in like a fairy tale realm
with castles, but then we got a rocket in play.
Well, also the game there turns into like,
an actual like, kind of Star Fox or something as well.
So you do get to like, shoot from the gummy ship,
which changes the format of the game.
You fly the ship. In between those levels.
Yeah.
And it also looks different.
It looks like a completely different game.
Cheaper too.
It's a 100% different game.
Scott, let me try and get you back on board.
And I'm going outside of the first one,
but did you know that Kingdom Hearts Coded
starts with Jiminy Cricket trying to figure out
what happened to his journal?
I cannot imagine higher stakes.
Jiminy Cricket's journal,
this bad guy, he controls the destiny.
He's the conscience of characters.
He's got to know where his journal is.
Where all his inspiring thoughts are.
Is it a dream?
Ideas for songs too.
That's a good point.
Is it a dream at the end? Do we know?
Unclear.
Jiminy, there's a weird part of in the cut scenes,
it's like, okay, so Goofy and Donald,
you have to go into the different worlds
and find the key blade, okay?
And guess who's coming with you?
Someone to record all of it.
And it's Jiminy Cricket.
And then as far as I can tell,
Jiminy Cricket doesn't show up again for hours.
He's not around?
Way later.
And then he shows up and seems to know Pinocchio,
but he's not in Pinocchio world.
He's in Kingdom World.
Here's what I'll say about this in general.
I don't know that all the famous Disney characters
are utilized to their full potential.
You mean they don't exhibit any qualities
that are what you expect out of them?
Yeah.
Because in theory, you go,
oh my gosh, all the characters are in this.
This is awesome.
And then it's basically like,
you're walking by a statue of them at the Disney store.
Yes.
Yeah, like what, you know, I've always wanted to know,
what if Donald and Goofy weren't funny?
What if they talked and just said like,
but the keyhole is gonna open.
We don't have much time.
There's something,
did Donald say something about
smiles powering the ship or something?
Not sure.
I think he said something about like smiles.
I was trying to do the Donald again.
I still can't.
I saw a.
That was the best I can do.
You have two words with it.
I saw a cut scene where Donald said to Goofy,
oh, what do you,
oh no, that's Mickey, shit.
Oh, what. That was your Donald.
Yeah.
Oh, what do you know, you big Palooka?
That's pretty funny.
That's pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's some, I mean, they're trying,
Donald and Goofy have some spirit of the character,
at least, like it's Bill Farmer doing the voice.
There's a big thing about the whole thing.
It is big voice central.
It's real voices.
It's Bill Farmer.
It's Tony and Selmo and throughout,
I don't know if we should reveal characters.
Oh sure, yeah.
But like, I mean, whatever, we could say them as well.
But it's like, it's pretty stacked in line.
It is like, this is another venue to hear
in some cases, it's like,
it's a voice of Alice in Wonderland.
Yeah, right.
From the 50s, but now in this video game.
And again, saying exposition.
It is nothing but. Yeah, not a fun use.
Just like, just get you from point B to C.
Pretty much.
Does this sound like it's in Mickey's voice?
This is the letter he sends to get the plot going.
We need that key or we're doomed.
So go to Traverse Town and find Leon.
Which they do.
Then Goofy at some point in this says,
well, we gotta protect the world order.
Yes, that's, I wrote that down.
It's like, what?
Seems like something Goofy could wrap his head around.
The world order, Goofy.
That sounds like some Alex Jones conspiracy.
Yeah, that's a bit.
Well, figure out who you're not allowed to criticize.
And Leon, is the character from Final Fantasy VIII?
You're asking the wrong people.
I'm reasonably certain when I was looking up other cameos.
What do you know?
I know that he's David Boreanis.
It is all of the most dynamic voice, pure voices.
David Boreanis, David Gallagher.
What voices are more exciting than this?
From the doll, all the all stars of the WB circa 2000.
I know Boreanis' voice anywhere.
Final Fantasy II, Leon, it says is from Final Fantasy II?
Geez, well, they're coming from everywhere.
Eight, two, what's next, seven?
Oh wait, the character Squall Leonhart from Final Fantasy VIII,
who is known as Leon in the Kingdom Hearts series.
There we go.
So that's what you're talking about.
So Leon is Squall Leonhart.
Squall Leonhart.
Great.
There's a lot of knots out there, but this one is.
He is Leon.
So it's like, if Jason were in Final Fantasy II,
then it would be like, I'm trying to think Jason Hart,
Rogue Jason Hart. Jason Patch.
You might know Jason from Final Fantasy II,
but Rogue Jason Patch is the same character
from Final Fantasy VIII.
Great.
So yeah, so Donald and Goofy,
basically they use the Gummi ship to go to Traverse Town
and they find Sora who's drifted there
from his destroyed world.
And they realize that his key blade is the key
that the king, Mickey, ordered him to follow
and the three become a team
and they begin wandering together.
Okay, I hate to stop in the middle
of that riveting sentence you just said.
Please stop as many, let's all stop a lot.
The aesthetic of the Disney characters is sort of similar.
Like they're wearing, like I would say, like very,
not steampunk, but like futuristic-y versions
of their own outfits, not dissimilar to some of the outfits
that you would see at Tokyo Disney,
see the characters that Mickey and friends wearing.
Oh yeah, like fancy colorful royal clothes.
Yes, but yeah, like they feel like a little bit different,
a little future-y or something.
It's still their color schemes.
Like I said, it's complicated zippers.
Donald has a zipper on his hat.
Goofy has boy band pants.
He looks like he's in SYNC's pop era.
Which was happening at this time.
Right around this time.
But it's future, everything's future.
It's a little bit futuristic too.
It's like a futuristic Cinderella's castle
and that's why they're in like a spaceship and whatever.
But then also like there's a lot of gears around as well.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of gears.
So there's some steampunky type things.
Staffs and chains.
Stuff you could render in a PlayStation 2 engine
and then really embellish in like covers and guides
and supplemental material.
Oh, they look immaculate in those forms
and then everything's just really pointy.
A little more simplified.
It was sort of, I remember when Final Fantasy VII
was at its peak and the cut scenes looked so cool.
And when you watched actual gameplay,
everyone was real tiny.
Like everyone was real little.
Yes, you're right.
And I, as a 12 year old was like, what the,
what is going on?
So many times it would be like you get excited
because of the cut scenes you would see
and then you would see the game and you go,
well, the cut scenes look a hundred times better.
And I remember just, I don't remember what the first one was.
Maybe it was a Resident Evil or something
where it was like the cut scenes look as good
as the gameplay.
And that was like, holy shit.
Wow.
They finally did it.
It's like recent Kingdom Hearts.
It almost is like, it's pretty even between.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
I'll get to recent.
I'll get to it in a couple of years with this rate.
False promise.
At this rate.
You're gonna go, you're gonna play all.
You know what I wanna watch?
I wanna watch Tulsa King, which is the Stallone show
in the set in the Yellowstone universe.
Oh.
I didn't realize that.
I believe it's in the Yellowstone universe.
Wow.
There's a Harrison Ford, like spin-off
Yellowstone reverse, I think.
And I believe Tulsa King is in,
which is Sylvester Stallone as a mob boss going to Tulsa.
I believe, sorry if I'm wrong,
I believe it's all in the Sheridan verse,
the Taylor Sheridan verse.
Careful.
We're gonna get real confused
if you start using that a lot.
Not the Jason Sheridan verse.
Oh.
And not a not.
The Taylor Swift verse, you can't do Taylor.
No, no.
That's a different thing.
So many Taylors that are,
she plays all of them in that commercial.
How do you keep those straight?
She's the problem and she had versions of her in the video.
The scary one who wore black.
I haven't gotten into that.
Reputation.
I don't, I haven't gotten into the album
as much as I did gotten into Evermore.
I don't think it's as good as Evermore,
but there's some cooks in there.
There's so much to get through.
But I'm flirting with the idea
of just starting at Tulsa King.
Next, cause this comes out next.
It will, this is, it'll be out by the time this comes out,
but I'm flirting with the idea of it.
But I know by the way,
I don't remember where I started with this thought.
It's gonna be a lot of those.
We don't remember.
I thought you were gonna just keep.
You were in Traverse Town.
I don't remember where I,
look, I haven't slept that much this week.
You get so excited when any other words pop up.
Tulsa King, Tulsa King.
Oh, Tulsa, interesting.
Oklahoma, I saw the Oklahoma City Thunder.
Did you know?
Basketball's fun cause the guys fly so high and they dunk.
And one time Michael Jordan was in Space Jam.
We'll do anything, anything, but we have to, okay.
How much further do we have to go?
I don't know.
We were barely started.
I know.
But I guess it's, we have to define what the plot means
because the plot doesn't mean we have to talk about everything.
The plot is, look, the worlds, they just go to the worlds.
It's our choice what we say.
The main thing is Donald is a wizard.
Goofy is a Royal Guardsman and they find Sora,
the Wapethnimp from the island.
And he once needs to find Riku and Kairi, I think.
And he has the key blade.
And the key blade is going to come in handy.
A, for smacking people and heartless.
And B, because there's key holes
and the heartless travel through the key holes.
And we have to seal the key holes.
And we need to say the word key hole as many times
as possible to where everyone's wondering,
why does key hole sound so weird to me?
And it's not until three hours through this, you go,
oh, cause it rhymes with pee hole.
So that is why key hole has been just like,
wow, just bumping against my brain this entire time.
So the more you hear like, garsh, the key, seal the key hole.
I, you know, you do,
you're putting that into my head for the first time now.
And now my world will never be the same.
Can't unhear it.
Wow, really?
I'm hearing of this for the first time.
You're telling me this for the first time.
Well, the heartless, they've done a lot, you know,
and they, I think I'm very sad to hear that the,
the key hole has been sealed up.
And it's very bad what we've done to those heartless.
It's bad what we've done.
What we've done is very bad.
And don't even get me started on the nobodies.
The nobodies don't even come to play in this one.
Can someone edit the video,
I forget what you're Kingdom Hearts,
the video where Goofy dies in Kingdom Hearts
with the Trump reaction.
This was another thing.
This was also in the air recently.
This went around where someone's like,
hey, this happens in Kingdom Hearts.
And it's just Goofy just getting domed by like a giant rock.
And then Mickey throws off his cloak and pull,
like does the Arthur clenched fist
and then pulls off his cloak and he has a key blade.
I've got it.
It's not from the game, but we need,
I think we need this as sustenance for the rest.
So look, Mickey doesn't,
you don't really get to see a lot of Mickey
in Kingdom Hearts one,
but this is in Kingdom Hearts two and it rules.
It's a bit of a long one, but I think we all need it.
So I guess we better all pull together
and finish this battle for good.
He looks like Darth.
Yes, your majesty.
He looks like Darth Vader, but he's good.
Right.
And then a big, then up above a cliff, a big rock falls.
Look out.
Dives.
Bean trying to save King Mickey.
Don't know, don't know what that.
This is not happening.
Getting to see the moment of Donald watching Goofy's death.
Going through the denial stage of grief.
And then you get this.
I think this is the main reason we've been sent
on any of this because we really liked
Agro Mickey going, oh yeah.
Guards in the Splashtacular show.
And this does not disappoint, vengeful, violent Mickey.
They'll pay for this.
He looks so mad.
Keyblade.
And then you just, at the end of it,
they just linger on dead Goofy.
I think he turns out to not be dead, but it's all,
I mean, that's worth the journey,
but it's not in this game, guys.
It's in two.
We're in one.
In one, we have to go meet Leon and Areth.
I don't, I just don't have a lot of notes about this.
What's important to know about Leon and Areth?
Anything?
If no, if it doesn't occur to anybody
in the next three seconds and we move on.
We can move on.
Great, okay, so the thing is,
once we get past Traverse Town,
then you start going to different worlds
via the Gummi Ship.
And the different worlds are all different worlds
from Disney movies.
I don't know if there's a set order,
and the one that I watched, there's Wonderland.
We go to Wonderland, real voice of Alice.
There's so many, you have a century
after doing the voice of Alice, incredible.
But it might be more fun if it wasn't like,
then you end up in like a sham trial
presided over by the Queen of Hearts,
who needs, ends up being like,
bring me evidence of Alice's innocence.
Four pieces of evidence,
but one will be tricky to find.
So now you have to wander,
wander Wonderland looking for evidence.
Yes, I know, I watched this part.
I didn't get here in the game, but I watched this
and I felt like, oh, that it's gonna be as monotonous
as finding the fish in the ocean.
Boxes, not even, I don't.
They're so, oh, God.
It was so boring and I was so,
and I know I'm spoiled by modern games.
Like the last Zelda,
you get all this different fruit and vegetables
and you can like cook up different meals
and it gives you different things.
Like there's so much and Alice is like,
oh, you gotta go and find some fish.
Find the evidence.
I know it's old. Alice in Wonderland, Alice,
you know Alice in Wonderland,
who goes on the crazy adventures in Croquet.
And no, now it's a trial and you are,
I know you just got here, but you're her defense attorney.
The read. You need to go find the evidence in Wonderland.
Ignore the magical creatures you see.
You are looking for boxes of evidence.
Box of evidence.
And the land, when you're walking,
like you're traveling,
and again, this is the limitations of the graphics.
I am sorry, but it looks like you're going to some,
like you ever go to like a kid's birthday party
at like some sort of family fun center.
And there's like, they got like trees painted on the walls.
And it's just like, yeah, I can tell
they put some effort into this,
but there's not a lot of theming.
That's what it feels like being in the Alice in Wonderland
world in the game.
There's not a lot of excitement that you're there.
You see the card, the card guards, whatever you call them.
Well, you get to see the Cheshire cat who does not speak.
There is not a voice for him.
Some characters are just thought bubbles.
And whoa, the Cheshire cat.
Wow. What does the Cheshire cat do?
Well, he does appear in the magical way,
but then you get to see him talk to Sora, the 12 year old.
And the dialogue is this.
Now he can save Alice.
Don't be so sure.
She may be innocent, but what about you?
What do you mean?
I won't tell, but I will give you something.
And then a full frame thing says, attained the power of ice.
What?
Why have ice?
Why is that gonna help?
Worse.
I'm at trial now.
And then you do present evidence.
And then she just says off with your heads anyway,
because you're being insolent for having found the evidence.
The thing you told me to do,
but then you get to fight the cards, which I like.
I like that you get to see Donald fighting the cards.
Yeah, I like that's good.
It's still the same play mechanics.
So frustrating.
But at least it's the cards.
Like it's not like you fight cards the whole game.
At least there's some novelty of like,
oh wow, I get to fight the famous cards.
Yeah, it's one of them to fight the cards.
You get to see them really swing those spades down.
Yeah, so Donald and Goofy are fighting with you
alongside you.
Yes, they don't, you don't have,
don't control them.
You're only Sora.
You're Sora.
They have, and they can't really fight much.
They can't be violent because this is Disney.
Right, and this is my number one thing I wrote down
when I'm watching this.
And I'm like, if I was a kid, I'd be like,
I want to play as Donald and Goofy.
I don't know Sora is.
This is my complaint about like all the focus on like,
you're the superhero.
And I'm like, no.
No.
Just make me Spider-Man.
I want to be Spider-Man.
Yeah.
I suck.
I'm nobody.
Didn't Walt Disney learn this 50 years ago?
It's exactly the same lesson from the Dark Brides
that they had changed.
I just want to see the main people.
You're Alice on the journey, or not Alice,
but you're Snow White on it.
And it's like, no, they want to see Snow White.
They know they're not Snow White.
You get to see Goofy hold a shield next to you
while you fight as you, Sora.
I like that idea, but I want to be Mickey fighting then.
Yep.
No, no Mickey.
Mickey is the king.
He's away.
He's dealing with the heartless problem.
Isn't that what I'm doing?
No.
Well, it is, but you have to do it in your own way.
You have the keyblade.
Mickey's got to try to find another keyblade.
You know, he's busy.
Mickey is busy.
It was.
He's like the Marvel characters.
Like the Marvel characters.
They've got other stuff to do.
Busy.
If you like the characters, if you like,
and I forgot the main characters in the game.
Sora.
Sora's the hero.
I'm sure plenty of people like Sora.
I don't dislike Sora.
Don't get me wrong.
But if I was a kid, do you remember the thrill of playing?
Did you play X-Men, Mutant Apocalypse on Super Nintendo?
No, I played Clone Wars.
On Genesis.
Yeah, the ironically named Clone Wars.
The thrill of being like Gambit,
one of your favorite characters.
The thrill I felt at the time when you go,
oh my God, they're making an X-Men game.
I'm going to get to play as one of my favorite characters.
And the disappointment I would have felt at being a kid
and going, wait a minute, I'm not allowed all the,
wait, how many Disney characters are there?
All of them?
I can't play as any of them?
They're all next to you.
What?
Everyone.
I get to know what it would be like to be near Donald.
I would drive me absolutely crazy.
You were saying you are not excited in later games
that you get missions from Yen Sid.
The wizard from Disney backwards.
Yeah.
Okay, that's a, yeah.
I'm sure if I was a kid, maybe I would have played the game
and I would have liked it and then I would have fell in love
with all the original characters.
We like original characters.
I like that they made new stuff out of it.
I do like that, but purely first, like a first impression,
especially if I was a kid, man, I would have been bummed.
I like later on you fight Maleficent.
Sure, great.
Henchman is Pete, big Pete.
That's funny.
Is he in this one?
I thought at the end of this one.
I didn't see him in this one,
but I didn't watch everything.
There are slight differences in the American and the channel.
I don't know if that's that, but I read it
because I played like what's called like the final mix
or something of the first final final final fantasy.
I'm losing my fucking mind.
Here's what, I'm very interested
in what you're about to say.
However, I have to go to the bathroom
and I've never done this in an episode.
I would like you to keep going,
say whatever you want to say about any of this
and maybe try to get to one of the other worlds.
You know what, so this, I'm gonna make this
a real time bathroom trip.
Here's the problem is when you probably saw me on my phone,
I was trying to figure out if the Tulsa King
is in the Yellowstone universe definitively.
I'm not gonna, you need to close this out before I leave.
You need to get back on Kingdom Hearts
and stay on Kingdom Hearts until I come back.
Do you hear me?
I do hear you.
But finish what you're saying about Tulsa King, that's fine.
All the articles refer to it as the Sheridan verse,
but I don't know what that actually means.
So please don't have a verse, Jason.
I don't know if that means that it's in actually canon
that they're in the same universe
or just means in his like media, his TV empire.
So it's unclear.
I hope it is mixed with it
because I do think I'm gonna try to start with Tulsa King
in the Sheridan verse.
Work your way back.
Maybe work my way back.
Because Yellowstone, I know is premiering soon as well,
the season five.
It's the same logic of like,
okay, there's a new comic book starting.
It's a spin-off from this big complex book.
Correct.
But this is a good jumping on point.
Yes, perfect.
Well, Scott, as you are.
Okay, you have to talk about Kingdom Hearts
the whole time I'm gone.
Make some progress.
If you wanna get past Tarzan world entirely,
you have to promise not to do a tangent.
You have to, I wanna come back when the door open
because I know you might trick me
and talk about something else.
Okay, okay, here's.
Talk about fucking Randy Gerber or the new guy
or Green Day.
But I'm gonna open that door
and if the sentence I'm hearing is not about Kingdom Hearts.
That's fair, but I will say this right before.
Green Day has its own coffee I just was made aware of.
No, back on track.
Well, you're here.
I didn't break the rules.
But if we break the rules, I might.
No, I have to pee.
Let him go, let him go.
I'm just saying.
If we break the rules, a couple more ghosts
we're not allowed to talk about
in the Haunted Mansion episode next year.
We can put that down.
All right, yes, real punishments, good.
Okay, talking.
Checking ghosts are not allowed.
When I open the door,
the sentence had better be about Kingdom Hearts.
All right, fine.
You could jump three worlds if you want.
There's nothing that I need to be here to say.
All right, I'm going to the bathroom.
Go to the bathroom.
I have to pee too, but I'm gonna hold it for the rest.
All right, Jason, Jason, what's the next world?
Is it Hercules world?
I'm trying to find.
I also wonder when I believe it's Hercules world.
I think so, yeah.
Okay.
So it gets flicked by Hades at some point.
Just for the listener for the context,
as we're recording this, it's about 5.15.
Daylight savings time has happened.
So the sun is setting and I'm starting to get cold.
So that's probably adding.
Yeah, and there's a barbecue in the distance,
but we're not allowed to talk about that.
You see Danny DeVito's character from Hercules.
Here's the thing about the game that is funny to me,
especially now seeing the first,
the cut scenes of the first, the 20 year old game,
is that there's an awfully long time in between dialogue.
So do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, kind of.
In a very funny way.
So it'd be like the Danny DeVito,
which I don't believe it's Danny DeVito
doing the voice of his character.
And I can't think of the character's name.
He's the shorter, you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, I do.
You're looking at me like you've no acknowledgement
of what I'm talking about.
Because I'm trying to think of the character's name.
Okay, I just wanna make sure you're on the same page.
So keep talking and I'll find it.
Because there's like some,
I feel like somebody started up a barbecue grill here
and I'm inhaling fumes.
So there's like a pause.
So basically like how the cut scenes will work
is like goofy, be like,
gosh, we gotta protect the new world order.
Beat, beat, beat.
And then somebody will go, yes.
And this happens over and over again.
And it's obviously, no, it's an older game.
So they're not rendering, they're not making the game.
So it's like moving at a blistering pace.
But it's funny to watch everything
because you feel like it's in slow motion.
It feels like you're in molasses.
And boy, is it slow moving.
You know what I'm talking about, Jason?
I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, I was amazed there was as much dialogue as there was.
Because there's also captions.
There's text on screen, right?
Yeah, there's captions.
And some characters have captions
and then sometimes it's all dialogue from the characters.
Sometimes it is just straight up dialogue
from the characters and it can be inconsistent.
I mean, like a lot of games are very inconsistent.
And then even the Nintendo Zelda still uses text captions
versus using actual...
Danny DeVito is Phil.
Phil, thank you.
Phil Octetes.
So Phil's like, ah, we gotta move this block.
Beat, beat, beat.
And then someone's like, yes.
There's that long of a pause in between some of the dialogue.
So it's funny to watch it sort of as a movie
because especially video games
where cut scenes have gotten so cinematic.
Obviously, again, 20 years ago,
I know when the newer cut scenes are, I'm sure, better paced.
My video, this kind of inspired me.
Like I started poking around on the Steam store
and it's like, oh, maybe I can get a newer Grand Theft Auto.
Maybe I can get such and such indie game.
You should have been playing with us over the,
you should have gotten a PS5 or 4 and played.
I know.
Well, that's at the start of the pandemic, James.
Like, why don't we get a Nintendo Switch?
And I'm like, how long is this gonna take?
We don't need to get a Switch.
So egg on my face.
Yeah, you should, because there's Switch.
I should have gotten the Switch version of this,
I think in hindsight,
because I got the PS4 version of all of this.
And the Switch, you can play a Lion Down.
Oh, that is true.
You know?
Yeah, I don't, oh, he's coming back.
Do you want to jump to the end?
Jump.
All right, what's happening?
All I would say is that as far as people,
when they would play, 20 years ago,
I'm green with envy of the day that people played.
You motherfuckers, you got off to fuck.
There was no, no, go back and listen.
We were talking about this the whole time.
We were looking.
Go back and listen,
because we don't want to give up the ghost.
I had the Hercules Wikipedia open,
because we couldn't remember that.
I made a good point about how the cut scenes
were very slowly paced.
So we're like, gosh, the New World Order,
we have to save the New World Order,
which is not what he says, but the World Order.
And then it's beat, beat, beat.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
That's how all the cut scenes are.
And that's what we were talking about most of the time.
Well, I went in right at the moment
that my son had come back from a play outing.
And he, I came in and he burst out and said,
dad, dad, he was one of the happiest
I've ever seen him see me.
And I'm like, I have to go.
I'm in the middle of the Kingdom Hearts episode.
You facemasked him.
And you said, not now.
Not now.
My real friends are Riku and Kairi.
Vaunted over him.
We are not friends anymore.
Do you want to jump to the end of the cliffhanger?
Sure.
Of the game?
Oh yeah.
Oh, well, they all get reunited.
We're going all the way to the end?
That's great.
Oh, I don't know.
Are there other worlds that you felt the need to discuss?
Well, there are other worlds.
As far as do I need to discuss them is a good question.
I'll say this, early on in the game,
there's a section where you're going through,
it's kind of when they're teaching you how to play the game
and you're going on these great glass floors with like,
it almost looks like stained glass with famous Disney
characters.
And I'll say this, I like that.
I think that looked cool.
Just from cinematically, visually, it looks cool.
I know they've remastered these graphics.
But I did like that part.
That gave me a little hope for some interesting use
of the iconography of the Disney movies.
What do you think of this?
Go ahead, Jason.
Oh, I was going to say, the logic of like,
these seven Disney princesses or whatever number it was,
they each represent part of shards that you have to,
you had to save them to get there.
You just quit.
Keep in mind, at the record show,
that sentence began with, I think this is interesting.
I don't know.
Quit, your brain quit on you.
Your brain got out and drove away.
It's like a real Homer Simpson.
You got to the word shard.
Oh, Homer Simpson, you say?
Well, do I have a clip for you of a different character?
No, wait.
What happened?
Your dearest wish is granted.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Aladdin, congratulations.
That, of course, is?
Alien race.
Patience, my fine brother.
Fake genie.
That's the genie.
That is the genie.
It is not Homer.
It is the genie.
Otherwise, it's a stacked, because like so many other.
Billy Zane's in this game.
There's a lot of big ones.
You go to Tarzan World, and you get the voice of Clayton.
Clayton from Tarzan.
You got to see Clayton.
You could go anywhere you could in the Disneyverse.
You would have to see Clayton, and you
would have to help Tarzan help the gorillas.
But I didn't know what Clayton was.
That's Brian Blessed, and he's the voice of Boss Nass.
So you get Boss Nass in this game.
Now I'm back in the conversation.
Anyway, Jason, you were saying about the shards.
Yeah, Jason, what were you saying about the shards?
I know they all get reunited.
Everyone gets reunited at the end,
but then Mickey and Riku have to stay behind a big door.
Yeah.
You have skipped truly all the way to the end,
and I'm fine with that.
I watched other stuff.
But if that's where this is going, I'm happy to not.
I'm more than happy to not.
I'm just shocked by you of all people going off.
Yeah, he's the one who wants to say.
I've never seen this big of a skip from you.
This is all I.
Well, you said video games are kind of in panorama.
I will say this, Scott.
Really briefly, when you were gone,
Jason mentioned how cold he was getting.
That's the wind.
Because the sun.
The sun was setting, and we're all getting cold.
That's part of why I went in.
I got a sweater.
I'm fine to not talk about any of the things.
I think we need to at least run through the world.
Yeah, let's name the worlds.
We don't need necessarily see or speculate.
Not speculate.
Talk about them at length.
But we owe it to at least acknowledge
the different lands you go to.
And hold on, let me find them.
Oh, come on.
Well, you see fake genie.
It's one of these consortium of villains things,
where there's the heartless, right?
And then there's Riku, who becomes
under Maleficent's spell.
So Riku's kind of a villain.
But then it turns out that really, it's not
Maleficent's spell.
It's Ansem's, right?
Ansem's spell.
Maleficent is being controlled.
So I guess they left it open so she could
be a good guy in the Maleficent movie,
the Angelina Jolie Maleficent movie.
I saw that for you.
I don't think they were thinking about it.
I'm just saying, well, it makes sense to my brain.
I'm not sure this is canon in a lot of ways.
But why couldn't she just be bad, then, is what I'm saying.
She's a bad guy.
You get a bunch of villains all in that classic.
They're all like, oh, those meddling fools.
Which I love.
But one of them is Captain Hook.
And I always find it odd when Captain Hook is like one
of the, like, oh, it's all the worst villains.
There's Captain Hook.
Because he's like a boob.
He's an idiot.
I'm not scared of Captain Hook at all.
At least not that Disney one.
He's a numbskull.
I was turning into you, Scott.
The pan in this is really grating.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
I was watching this like, I dare these guys to tell them,
that's good.
I like what this pan is doing.
I don't think anyone likes this pan.
Wait, I have a line of dialogue.
It's like, goofy.
Who are you?
Pan, I'm the answer to your prayers.
You are the answer.
No prayer could be answered by you, Pan.
My greatest prayers that you go away.
I don't look.
I'd love to say I love the pan.
I don't love the pan in this.
But what do you think about the Little Mermaid
world and the dialogue?
Where is the keyhole, daddy?
It's in your grotto.
I do like that.
I don't know about that.
But now that you put P-hole in my head.
This is another awful part.
You go to Little Mermaid world, and everybody
changes a little bit.
Now, some of the changes I like.
Is it called Atlantica?
Yeah, that's not what it is in the movie.
It's not that in the movie.
Atlantica is made up from old cloth.
All the goofy, they become sea creatures, right?
Yeah.
Goofy becomes a turtle.
I like looking at Goofy as a turtle.
Yeah.
Donald is an octopus.
And Sora is a mer-boy.
He's a little mer-boy.
And I don't want to see Sora without his shirt on.
I'm not one of the people making the AMVs.
This is too young of a character.
Well, Jason did it to put Link.
And Link's a young guy.
Jason stripped all his clothes off in Skyward Sword.
I don't know if I intended to do that.
I think I was trying to access the inventory.
It was in his underwear.
Yeah.
So no, he's a mer-boy.
He's a little mer-boy, which, look, we all
want to be little mer-boys.
But it's impossible.
I tried to go to the seats.
Like, watching all this stuff, I was like, all right,
maybe I need to give video games another shot.
And I went to the Steam store, which is, I thought,
cross computers.
And the system requirements were all in Windows.
And I'm like, well, I guess I'm fucked.
I don't know what's going on.
Tell me the story while that was going.
Did we say this?
Someone cut me off.
I didn't think I finished it.
Well, maybe you didn't finish the thought.
Yeah, yeah.
This was about to be said.
This is possibly, it was not said,
but this was almost a five-timer within an episode.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
We recorded an episode before this.
And I have not.
The sleeping again.
Yeah, the sleeping's not good.
This is also, we have had the most,
we've been buzzed by the most planes and helicopters
we've ever.
Yeah, we've stopped.
If you think we're frustrated, we've cut it off.
We've had to stop and restart like seven times.
It'll be seamless.
I think Jason had the right idea.
The stories that they go to different worlds.
Atlantica, Monstro.
I have a clip of Monstro.
OK, go ahead, please.
This kind of tells you the tone of it
and what you get to see all our favorite characters do.
They find you're in space in a gummy ship.
And that gets to all.
Monstro's in psychedelic space.
And then you end up in his stomach.
And this is a scene between Geppetto and Riku,
who is holding Pinocchio like he grabbed him.
And he's holding him over his arm.
Pinocchio.
Please give me back my son.
Sorry, old man.
I have some unfinished business with this puppet.
He's no puppet.
Pinocchio is my little boy.
He is unusual.
Not many puppets have hearts.
I'm not sure.
But maybe he can help someone who's lost theirs.
Wait a minute.
Are you talking about Kairi?
What do you care about her?
And he walks off to the unfinished business
with this puppet.
That's the best part of the whole game.
I don't know what he's going to do to him,
but it doesn't seem good to me.
Yeah, I know that Geppetto is a real suss.
What do you want with your wooden son, old man?
Shut the fuck up, you old shithead.
I'm Kairi.
I do whatever I want with any little wooden boy I find.
I'm taking this puppet back.
I don't give a shit, old man, what you say to me.
I have perfect hair, and I will dramatically kind of
toss it back several times.
I'm so wispy.
I could do anything I want.
I'm going to give this little wooden boy his own head of hair.
Real hair.
Gertner's lucky I'm not using the locker under him.
If I stood up one time, I'd stab him right in that dirty chin.
That wooden boy, Scott Gertner.
That little wooden boy, we have unfinished business.
Put him under my arm.
I'll carry him away.
No, David Gallagher, no.
That's my Scott.
Not today, he's not.
He'll say no, saying whatever he says, like, no, old man.
No, man.
He's also, I don't know if they really conveyed the stakes of it to David,
because it's always like, plead.
Wait here, I have one more.
This is another one where the character, the famous character who we have feelings
about, the emotion is not really matched between the character and Riku.
It'll be a reveal for the listener.
This is towards the end of the game.
No help from the heartless.
So tell me, how'd you get here?
Hmm.
I simply believed.
Nothing more to it.
When our world fell into darkness, Belle was taken from me.
Who is the beast?
I would find her again, no matter what the cost.
I believed I would find her.
So here I am.
Sorry, hang on.
She must be here.
I will have her back.
Take her if you can.
Nah, I don't think so.
There's this lame jump in slow motion.
The beast just misses once and that like fells him.
So now we have like, all right, wow, it's a Disney, it's a video game where all the
Disney characters, well, what if the beast, what if you could play as the beast or
watch what he would do, like ripping somebody apart?
Like he'd probably make mincemeat of a wispy 13 year old with an attitude.
What if I could watch him do that?
No, Riku took one step backwards and that's the end of this 600 pound monster.
They make him look like a fool.
He's a fearsome beast, no longer.
Tricked me.
I slipped on a banana peel.
No way, you furry asshole.
Nice try.
I don't think so.
I made you look like a fucking dick.
You old, you fucking moron.
Trash shaving.
Eat my shit for a ball.
If we're sharing clips, this jumps ahead to a future game.
I guess Kingdom Hearts 3.
Woody and Buzz show up.
Oh, great.
Yep.
And yeah, I don't know.
I just thought that Woody was pretty funny here.
I sense a Jim Hanks.
Jim Hanks.
Well, that's sort of the main.
Whatever you're talking about, I don't care.
Put Buzz back the way he was, then get lost.
Or else what toy?
Yeah, I am a toy and a friend.
My guess is no one's ever loved you before.
Who's he talking to?
Because you know nothing about hearts and love.
There's another good line read coming.
You can't.
Okay, so the pacing is just as bad.
There's a snake in my boots.
You can't and you can't mess with me.
I rewound it so many times just to hear you can't keep us from Andy.
Like what?
The voice drop man.
Yeah.
Hearts are where love comes from.
What does he say?
Can you play the first part with Woody again real quick?
Yeah, sure.
Because it sounds like something John Taffer screamed at the manager of the Scottsdale improv.
That's also very funny.
The reason I clipped it initially is just because like, wait.
So in this video game, Woody tells a character he's never experienced love.
That's the line.
Yeah.
Whatever you're talking about, I don't care.
And get lost.
Or else what toy?
Yeah, I am a toy and a friend.
Something you'll never be.
Now clean this shit up.
Wait, wait, we'll go back to that one.
You're over boring.
My guess is no one's ever loved you before.
That's it.
Yeah.
The Scottsdale Arizona, he goes like, there's a literally line on that episode of Bar Rescue where he goes, this is why your wife left you.
No, this is why no one's ever loved you before.
No one's ever loved you before.
That's it.
Seal the keyhole.
And I had to work so hard.
I watched like 10 videos before I found one that is just clips of Disney characters saying weird things.
Oh, stiff.
None of them talk like them.
So it's all like they're so serious.
Everyone's so serious.
It's kind of when you look into other like niche fandoms and stuff and you're like, oh, what are the memes?
What do you guys think are funny?
And then you're just like, I can't I can't understand a lick of this.
I don't know.
This is something that's in my notes.
King Mickey used the gummy ship to visit Ansem the Wise in Radiant Garden to discover the reason why the worlds were disappearing.
Both Ansem and his apprentice Xehanort were fascinated by the gummy technology.
It's Mickey Mouse.
What is this?
But he let go of our ship and then he sings a song.
The description of that, though, at the very least, could be fun in another context.
Maybe.
Yeah, I feel like I would love to go back and play Epic Mickey now because I think I would go like Epic Mickey is like so exciting compared to this.
Some of this Kingdom Hearts stuff.
You mean the game where a man named Sid angrily chewing like a straw stalk makes character makes goofy.
Find a book for him.
I'm sorry. Deliver a book for me to an old man.
Yeah, that's a long thing that happens.
And Epic Mickey does not have dialogue, right?
You mean like voice acting, voice acting, isn't it?
Just text.
Yeah, I think it's mostly text.
I could be wrong about that because I was so weird to me.
I think when I was at your apartment once and I was playing it and I was like, why are none of these classic cartoon characters talking?
Well, but there's also newer games.
Like I said, the Zelda like still has a lot of text.
Yeah, like they can't do voice acting in this one.
I mean, I guess it's now built in.
It's baked into the game or whatever.
But they had to figure out how to set the course.
They have to the designers.
Miyamoto is working on the horse on fire effect so much they didn't have time to record dialogue.
Mario. Yeah, Mario still.
I mean, Mario has a still as Charles Martinette voice lines, which we will not see in the movie, which is good.
Real.
I want to see the stars of today.
I'm hip.
I want to see all of the comedies hottest talents.
OK, what do we have to do to get out of here?
Did I say all the names of the world?
We have to.
I guess we don't have to.
We have to do is say we don't have to.
The mission was to say the plot.
I'm just going to say some things from Goomba Stomp dot com.
Go for it.
Yeah, I think will they go.
You go to the world.
You're sent on missions.
What the it's sealing the keyholes.
That's what you're doing.
Yeah. The point is you go to Ariel.
You interrupt the events of the movie like the now the drama with Ursula isn't about the voice and Prince Eric.
It's about you being there.
Yeah, kind of the same stuff happens.
You fight Ursula and then the fight causes the keyhole, the seal and the more kills you seal.
Maybe the heartless won't come out anymore.
But then it all ends at Maleficent's home, which we know is hollow Bastion.
And that's where you they confront Riku who and realize that Riku is just under the control of Ansem Billy Zane and more of Billy Zane.
Ansem comes out through that and you realize that's why Riku got so muscly and why his shirts started to change.
That's why he started having so many wardrobe changes because he's as flashy as Ansem.
But so Sora wait Riku says let's fight without your precious keyblade and Sora realizes that his strength is in his friends and not in the weapons.
I don't need a weapon.
My friends are my power says Sora something that people probably were very emotional about and made some very serious Linkin Park music videos about.
But to me, I don't know what why this matters.
So then Ansem shows up.
The sea says it is I, Ansem, the seeker of darkness.
And they real I don't know.
Some say anyone else say anything.
I'm just trying to try.
I was trying to do the assignment moved by Sora's spirit any time always moved by Sora's speech golf goofy, golfy, golfy and doogled return to Sora's side.
And so does the keyblade.
Riku is defeated only to be stopped by a man named Ansem.
He teaches the kid out to unlock the darkness in his heart and becomes stronger.
Oh, I guess what Goomba Stomp dot com is telling me is that Ansem and Ansem the wise are two different characters.
Good.
I know that's what becomes over 12 games.
Multiple characters are VR simulations of the actual characters or dreams characters have or time travels.
Yeah.
Tigger dreams.
Or you're just a part of a Tigger dream.
So anyway, they get with Maleficent and defeat her.
And then they and then they you find out that Kyrie, one of the friends from the beginning, is the last princess of power needed to unlock Kingdom Hearts, which is a place.
Yeah.
Did you know that?
Not before I started doing this.
This name the whole time.
I assumed Kingdom Hearts was what all the characters were.
Sora and Kyrie and Mickey and Pluto.
They're all Kingdom Hearts.
It's a place.
I thought they were trying to acquire Kingdom Hearts.
No, no.
Kingdom Hearts is a place and seemingly like mainly a door.
But shards there.
But about the shards.
The brief form the X-blade.
And then one character turns out to later be a blade.
Uh-huh.
We're almost there.
Uh, Sora.
This Ansem shows up and somebody references that a keyblade that unlocks people's hearts.
And he says a keyblade that unlocks people's hearts.
I wonder.
And he unlocks his own heart by stabbing himself with a keyblade.
And you think that Sora is dead and magic bubbles shoot out of his heart and the bubbles fly at the different princesses such as Belle.
Someone who Sora has never met and his friend Kyrie.
And I don't know.
Then at some point Cinderella says we've been waiting for you keyblade master.
Sounds like Cinderella to me.
Anyway, Sora's sacrifice saves Kyrie and he only has to be dead for a couple minutes.
And he is back.
And then but then their home disappears.
The island from before it goes away.
Destiny Island is gone.
And Kingdom Hearts is a place.
I said that.
Look, honestly, I don't think my notes are going to cut it.
I don't know if I.
If you go to Halloween town.
That was a while ago.
Oh, sorry.
I do like that there's an eyebrow for Christmas stuff and it's the voices.
Like, look, we got to get we got to get to the end.
Sorry.
But behind the door.
So, yeah, Kingdom Hearts is a place and Ansem opens the door and he thinks it's going to be a world of darkness, but it's actually a world of light.
So jokes on Ansem.
This all means something to someone, right?
Yeah.
People are still listening, right?
Is there anyone listening that's like a big fan and are like, this is blasphemous?
Well, we're doing this is a great.
Yeah, either if you're a fan, we've made you mad or if you're not a fan, you don't know what we're talking about.
And hopefully you're at least enjoying the madness and hopefully you're somewhere warmer than we are.
It is cold out and there's somebody who's running like a barbecue grill and I was getting this wafs of like smoke in my lungs.
There's a gas.
I have a fire.
We should start recording this by the fire pit as we head into the winter months.
But what was the twist ending you were talking about that we should have listened to you and just ended?
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Mickey and David Gallagher.
And David Gallagher, I believe, have to sacrifice themselves and stay behind the door behind the door.
They closed.
We're keeping the siren.
Yeah, we're going to.
No more stopping.
We've got to wrap this for me.
Jason called 911.
You just greatly called the emergency button.
If you call Lyft Amp.
There is there is an ambulance missing foul or yeah, fouls in Los Angeles called Ambulance like and I have no idea what it does.
Yeah, I don't know how to find out why there's a hip ambulance.
Why is there a lift of ambulances?
Ambulance.
King Mickey shows up and sacrifices himself.
So you don't.
Sora did not find all of his friends and Donald and Goofy briefly found Mickey, but now he's gone again.
So the goals of the game were not met.
No, some of them were not all much like the episode.
We didn't explain all of it.
We did as much as we could stand and and it ends in kind of a here we go again way where because they haven't found anybody.
So it all moves to Kingdom Hearts 2, a game where Goofy is hit by a rock and briefly dies.
Right.
Now, if you're wondering if things pick up and get a little more exciting because of Mickey's presence, here's a random clip from Kingdom Hearts 2.8.
It's time with this key and Sora's in the realm of light.
We're going to close this door.
Now all we need is Riku.
Hey, Mickey, my friend is telling me funny stuff.
Here's more funny stuff, he says in Kingdom Hearts 3.
Exam when Master Xehanort made his grand return.
That's the Xehanort I remember.
Wow, man.
Mickey, you remember a way different Xehanort than I do.
He's I don't want to know anymore about these.
Well, Captain Jack Sparrow shows up at one point.
Oh, baby.
Alert inside the magic.
I'm sure they know already.
They play it every fucking night.
One of the one of the writers at Inside the Magic made their own patch for the game where Jeff Beck gets added to the character.
That's the Jeff Beck I remember.
Wow, my favorite blues legend.
So then also here's something else to know about too.
And I know we're wrapping it up, but you got to know.
You have to know that in two, you're not Sora, you're Roxas.
I don't know.
I'm not saying that right.
But he's voiced by Jesse McCartney, you know, did I know if both.
So which is probably this probably a Kingdom Hearts mashup of and if not somebody should make one.
There's questions online about why does Roxas look like Ventus?
I couldn't tell you.
I don't know the full story about that.
But Roxas looks like Ventus and he's not Sora.
But you don't know why you're watching Roxas and not Sora.
But suddenly Roxas has a realization that he's supposed to help Sora, someone who he's never met before, and that Sora has been asleep for the entire runtime of Kingdom Hearts 2.
I am going to sell the games I bought.
Hey, reach out to Mike.
No, I'm going to GameStop tomorrow.
I'm selling the games.
Well, that's a real insult to injury if you're giving games.
Wait a minute.
There's what you would you still want to sell them after you hear this?
That while sort that since the end of Kingdom Hearts 1, Sora has been napping and Donald and Goofy have been waiting for him to wake up from the nap.
I have Miles Morales Spider-Man PS5 game I haven't finished and it's a good game.
And it's been sitting there.
I need to finish that.
There's a lot of games I should finish.
But Mike, it turns out the master doesn't matter.
What?
That is a phrase I had in my notes and I don't know what it means.
Yeah.
And also it turns out that Ansem is not who he says he is.
He's not Ansem.
He's he's Zen or so Ansem is Zen or every time you say Ansem, I think of Ansem Williams from Happy Days.
That's nice.
That's a nicer thing to think about, isn't it?
Yes.
Sit on it, Pottsy.
And that's a phrase I keep.
Sit on it.
I think of Ansel Elgort.
Does Disney own Happy Days?
Do any of the Happy Days characters appear in Kingdom Hearts 2.75?
They should show up in 5, I think.
Yeah, Donnie Most is in 358 over two days.
As the actor Donnie Most or as his character Ralph Malf?
Oh, no, they find Ralph Malf and he says, we have to beware.
These Heartless come from Organization 13.
All right.
Do you want to like Jitterbug or something?
No, no, I don't.
There's too much to learn about the nobodies.
Can't Square Enix make a combination Final Fantasy Happy Days, can't we?
Make a new set of characters and they interact with a Happy Days universe.
That was in Laverne and Shirley's as well.
So you can have all the different of the sitcoms.
And you get to find out whether you're Shlomozzle or Shlomozzle, you know?
Yes, you can.
You can play as Shlomozzle, but not Shlomozzle.
So that's computer controls.
Sora and then you're flanked by Laverne and Shirley.
Fighting different characters.
On the beer line.
Hurry, fill the beers.
It's the only way to help Kyrie.
Not like root beer dapper.
Fighting Lenny and Squig?
I guess they're your friends, Lenny and Squiggy.
No, Squiggy's been inhabited by Ansem.
It's not the Squiggy we know.
An early moment that threw me for a loop where I was like, oh, let me read about Square Enix.
And it's like Square Enix is also known as Square and Square Soft.
Now, the reasons are because of ownership.
And I was like, oh, no, the ownership says ban us again.
Audience, if there's something that we didn't do that you would like us to do, we're all ears.
But this is as much of this as we could do right now.
Please let us know.
I spent a lot of time playing the game.
I don't really tell people that.
I did not half-ass it.
I was sitting down playing this game and realized I wasted so much time in Traverse Town and on the island, on Destiny Island.
I couldn't have been spending in Tulsa Town.
I watched so many compilation videos that had millions of views each.
Yeah, you're right. It is a town.
Millions of views.
I was like, oh, what?
The music's nice.
I was listening to music.
Before I sell the games, I will do a quick run through three, see if maybe the gameplay is more pleasing to my hands and my brain.
Look, my guess is that why we were given this assignment was to torture us.
I think so.
So I think we did do the assignment.
We definitely did it.
If that's what was being thought here.
But if not, and this is a pile of nonsense, then it's in your hands now to pick a topic that you want to hear more because next month is Christmas and Christmas is a time of rebirth.
And we can all start over and forget about Ansem and Xenorth.
Isn't Easter the rebirth?
They all are.
It's so important.
The child is born.
They're all wherever you want them to be.
But not rebirth.
That's first birth.
Christmas is a time of first birth.
But for now, I think this has to be it.
You survived podcast the right and thank you for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved our podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
Do you want to take one more guest on an AMV like here for a song to go out on?
Alien Ant Farm.
That's a little too much fun, though.
It could be, though.
I don't know.
I bet some of it.
We got it.
All right.
We got out with with visual help from Riku and Kyrie.
Definitive version of the song.
I if I understand, it's over footage like I saw Pluto for a second.
You and Riku never came home, so I came looking for you.
They spun the visual image around.
That's great.
To quote the song, ow.