Forever.
Dog.
Warning. The following podcast may...
Look, there's no other way to say it. It includes bodiness, okay?
I'm so sorry, but it does. It's very bawdy.
Specific bodiness may involve caught pieces, cleavage horns, ye olde sex toys, and an odyssey through Jason's bladder.
Johnny Pemberton leads us on a Rye-Bald Expedition through the world of the Renaissance Fair on Podcast The Ride.
Huzzah and good morrow! Welcome to Podcast The Fair, hosted by three good lads who doth taketh interest in horseless buggies that toss ye hither.
I'm Scott Gertner, that's the end of that. I was joined by Jason Sheridan.
Difficult to sustain for long periods of time.
The entirety of the podcast will not be done in such language, unless somebody wants to try it on their own, but I'm stopping. Mike Carlson.
Hi, yes, and thank you for stopping it before you got to me, because I was really like, okay, how am I going to do it?
And everything that popped in my head was definitely like saying stuff in a pirate manner, but more positive, like, are ye mateys?
And I was like, that's not it. That's not the way to do this. So thank goodness it stopped before I was put under pressure.
It's not an area that we're prepared to speak in for a very long time.
I was thinking about this how, like, there's sort of a through line between what we're talking about today, Renaissance Fairs, and like areas of nerddom that I don't think we have.
I feel like among the three of us, there is not Lord of the Rings and Hobbit so much. Right?
Unless we just never come up. For me, at least. Game of Thrones. Does anybody do you even watch?
Is this somehow an area that eludes all three of us nerds? It's not my scene.
Well, I did see like every Lord of the Rings and Hobbit movie were usually Christmas releases.
So that was like between Christmas and New Year's. Oh, we'll go see this. And it was a very pleasant experience.
You're not a fan of those as much as you are as a fan of Christmas pleasantry.
As much as like, oh, we'll go to a movie and then go out to dinner. You know?
A fan of dinner. That we know. That's been established.
Any sort of medieval fiction you're happy as long as there's an Applebee's afterward.
Yeah. It's like, oh, I wonder what I'll get at Romano's macaroni grill after this. Probably the same thing I always get.
You're zoning out while Gollum is like trying to grab the ring and there's a big climax.
Yes, I am just imagining the ring has been replaced with like meat ravioli.
An onion ring. Oh, an onion ring. Sure.
Jack Daniel's barbecue sauce. Jack Daniel's sauce. On pond pasta.
It's not. This is one of those where I feel like disappointed in myself that I haven't watched Game of Thrones.
That I'm not that into like the castles and drag.
I like dragons, but I'm not so into it. So it feels like I've let people down.
Imaginary people down are upset by me for not having some like intense fandom for this type of thing that feels so adjacent.
Because maybe this maybe I'll get there because like I'm trying to be a little horror boy.
I'm trying to get into all that stuff recently. I just got through the third Freddy Krueger movie.
Which is very exciting. Right after Halloween. Great.
Look, there's a baby and sometimes Scott, something you said where you had to get through movies in chunks.
That is very true with our baby as well. Yeah, I'm going so slow.
Dream more. 90 minute movies take three days.
So it's nice about this. You can sit down and do a 90 minute experience that can't be interrupted.
Unless somebody needs to pee or something. But let's barrel in because now's the chance.
If anyone's mad at any of us for not being into anything medieval adjacent fantasy adjacent.
Let's start figuring it out because this topic I feel like is a no brainer.
I can't believe we haven't done it. And it took our excellent guest to bring it to us.
A Renfair fan. And when I asked about credits, he encouraged the instructions were to go to your Mozilla.
Type his name in and don't worry about spelling it right. And hopefully there's an auto correct.
So if you're if you want to know more, then go to Mozilla and type in Johnny Pemberton. Hi.
Hi. Huzzah to the tipper. So the what?
You already lost me on one. What's what was that word? Huzzah.
No, the other one. You said that to when you're at Renfair when you when that's what they say to you.
The workers, when you tip them, they say, Huzzah to my tipper.
Huzzah. Oh, I just feel like this sort of like this weird thing when you take Renfair out of Renfair, it feels a little like cringy.
Oh, sure. Yeah. When you're not in the garb and when you're in a modern studio, when you're in a very well lit place.
Yeah, yeah. Where everyone's moderately clean and there's no indoors.
There's something about Huzzah to the tipper that you shutter as it's. Yeah, it's like a little bit.
I think I figured out you guys blind spot, though. Oh, really? This whole thing.
Listen to your you know, your your opening introduction discussion. Yeah.
Is it possible that you guys don't smoke a lot of weed? Not so much.
Not so much. Jason, not two of us, not two of us. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, not in a while. Yeah. Yeah. I think that's what it is.
Huh? I think the fantasy stuff, all the people I know who have been super into fantasy stuff are stoners.
Ah, huh. I think that's it. Yeah. I got into it around 30. So I'm a cool guy.
OK. So was it not till then? I guess I didn't realize your time.
In my later 20s, like I tried edibles and they're very intense.
Oh, yeah. And so I've gone backwards to the weaker stuff. Gotcha. Yeah.
Interesting. Why do you think there is that correlation? Why is it a stoner experience?
I think it's like you get lost in the experience because for me, the whole Renfair thing is you go and you get to kind of like time travel a bit.
Yeah. And that's very conducive to being out of your head a bit, being high.
Also, I mean drinking too. They serve alcohol at Renfair. Yeah.
And people love to drink at Renfair. Sure. It seems like, yeah, that super boozy affair.
It's certainly candy. Something about the, something about psychedelics and weed, I think, are very conducive to the, to, yeah, time traveling.
To transporting. To another.
I feel like there's a thing too where like everyone's like committed to the bit. Oh, for sure.
Like everyone really wants to be there. Everyone was. I feel like this would be a place where I would be more comfortable dressing in the period garb than like cosplaying a comic con.
Absolutely. It's the kind of thing where the first time I went, I found that out very quickly.
And then every year after, you got to dress up. Otherwise you get ribbed by the the jokers who roam the the boulevards of the Renfair.
They'll rib you. The opposite of the Huzzah for the tipper.
You're not being commended. You're being, you're, you're, you'll be committed for dressing like a future man.
Yeah. They're like, what is this garb that you wear? This is what is this strange printing on your shirts? Good, sir.
I'm confused by stuff like that. Printing press does not work on fabric.
Oh, that there's a lot of times where people like two guys will join jump in on someone and be like, yes, what is this man doing with what is this strange contraption?
He has like you have to bring your phone out or something. That kind of stuff, which I like.
I think it's cool that they get after you. Sure. They're like basically like you can't.
How dare you? How dare you not time travel with me?
That does that sounds humiliating. So it's like completely in your best interest to to just jump in, do it.
Yeah. Well, also, we're talking about the Renaissance Pleasure Fair here, which is a Southern California thing.
Oh, yeah. Well, that's a good question. I know how you wanted to narrow it, if it is the general thing or if you're if we're focusing on on so because you've been a regular of the SoCal one.
So the Renaissance Pleasure Fair, which is very important to say because it is a it is a sexually tinged Renaissance Fair.
And it's that's well known. Everyone knows this. Yeah. Yeah. It's part of the tradition of it.
It's it's what they call it's a bit body. Well, you don't even know what you just stepped in.
Body has been a running word on this. Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
I noted that body comes up in Ren fair discussion. Oh, yeah. A lot.
What what what are your associations with bike and fill you in on why it's come up with us?
I would say for me, it's the sort of thing where it's a way to say something that's sexual in nature, but it's also kind of jokey and it's good nature.
It's good nature. It's not like it's a little bit pervy, but not in the sense where it's obscene or uncomfortable.
On a graphic. Yes. It's like everyone's in this arena where everything you say is like, oh, everything's a double entendre.
So yeah, it feels like it's body in this with playful. It's very playful. Sure.
Here's the best example I have of it is a lot of people who work at the stalls and stuff there are women and they have a significant amount of cleavage available to see.
This seems like a big thing about this is a big thing. There's a lot of pushing up going a lot of pushing up with the corset.
And a lot of times these women who have the extremely ample bosoms will put a little horn in between in their cleavage and they will squeeze their boobs together and honk this horn.
When you tip them like you're buying a turkey leg, it's like honk honk.
Honk honk. That to me is not at all sexual. I find it to be not.
You know what I mean? That is not a rousing at all. That is because you could do that with your your butt.
Right. That's very just like weird anatomy. That's body.
Huh? Yeah. That's on the fringes of here's what the human body BODY can do.
But not like that's not a you're not watching that in a pornographic film. I don't think unless there's got to be something some porno where that's in there.
Sure. But I'm just saying it's not honk honk for sure.
I wish I could do it. I've never been a Peewee Herman ask.
I feel like a little bit. You know what I mean? It's kind of a it's sexual maybe for like a teen or like a child or something.
Yeah. Oh, that's sexy. It's like, no, it's kind of being used in some way.
I watched some shows from the the one I went to growing up, the Pennsylvania Renaissance Fair.
That's probably a great one. It is incredibly elaborate. It's on a wineries like property.
I'm already. So they they also now are partnered with a brewery and a distillery and a hard cider local hard cider company.
And they've built Tudor structures in stages and stuff.
Where is this in Pennsylvania? I didn't know about this. It's like north of Lancaster.
OK. And it's at the Mount Hope Winery.
And there is a show called like The Washing Wenches Show.
And there was literally like this woman. Everyone's on, you know, benches.
And this woman stood on a bench with like her crotch in a man's face and gave him the instruction of like, all right, I need you to we need to check each other for weapons.
So pat your way from the top of my back to my bottom and give it a squeeze.
And I was like, dear God, this is cross the line from body to straight up horny.
Call the local authorities, local authorities and add the only shut down.
I called the sheriff and you know what happened?
He slipped and fell in the mud pit on the way to the Washington Wenches Show, because that's one of the other.
There's a mud pit. There's there's all the things.
There's like a Globe Theatre replica. You got to have that.
It's very essential. You got to have that.
There is the what everyone I only went once we went for a school field trip and they're like, do not miss the human chess game, which I learned just in the last year or two is now called the Tournament of Arms.
Same show. Skip the chess moves.
So everyone just does stage combat.
Oh, that sounds a little more exciting than watching the steps be taken.
Well, one over and two up.
What happens is when your rook takes the other person's pawn, they fight for a second and they don't always like win.
I feel like.
Oh, so it's not by chess moves.
It's literally by combat moves.
Yeah, kind of like everyone is moving like the chess pieces they represent.
But then there is battle.
I guess it's I guess it's stage so that like the piece is taking another piece.
Right. The one wins.
Like metaphorically, this is what's happening in chess.
We don't we just don't think about it.
We just do it as like knock off at most.
But in every chess move, there is like blood being shed.
The game of Star Wars chess game where like the monsters fight each other and one dies.
It's really that's sort of what's happening in chess.
Oh, that's the actual eyes to get violence into a little board game.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, it's nice they provide an opportunity to finally flesh out what chess really we should really like more in each piece as we got to go to this Ren fair.
We want to go now.
This is it's really cool.
And it's like I watched some videos.
They rehearse for like a month and then it runs August, September and October on the weekends and the holidays.
But when I was like 12, like in seventh grade, we definitely went on a school field trip, got in the bus at the middle school, went up there and they were just like, all right, meet back up at five and just unleashed us.
And we just did whatever we want.
So I remember like doing archery.
I remember pricing out swords.
This became a man.
Would you say I became a man?
I became a very fussy man because I was saying to you guys before the show.
It happened. I was like, we have to be back on the bus at five o'clock.
But the grand finale is a five thirty.
We're going to miss.
We never saw the end of the story.
The Queen's procession.
Yeah.
I now they call I believe they call it the final pub toast.
They have fully leaned into the boozyness.
And now it's just on the weekends.
It's not really on the weekdays except like school days where they seem to mostly do like, you know, they they do a Shakespeare workshop and they do like a different educational workshops.
Less boozy, presumably, and less body.
Hopefully, hopefully.
Yeah, no, it's not just like we're doing the day and we're unleashing 12 and 13 year olds to like go wild.
Like it was but it was so exciting in 1997.
It's like, wow, I get to get a turkey leg not at Disney World.
It is. It is an amazing experience.
I went as a kid to the one in Minnesota and where I grew up, Minnesota and Chocopee.
And I was I was blown away by I loved it.
Remember, there was a guy walking around the shirt off who was selling pickles and everything he said out of his mouth was a was a joke about his penis, but also about the pickle.
Yes.
It was great.
It was so body.
It was just off the charts body.
That was my first Ren fair.
I remember that that guy at the pickle salesman really just it sunk its teeth me because I realized, oh, this guy's walk around.
This guy's probably I mean, he's about as close to close to unemployed with a job that you can be an occasional job for a brief.
Yeah.
And a really specific strange job.
Here's let me here's a little mind blower of because I was thinking like I was probably the Minnesota fair.
I should look up what's up with the Minnesota fair and somebody I don't know if this was your pickle boy or pickle man.
Oh, well, we guess he's got a restraining order or something like that.
No, I don't have like I don't have a rap sheet.
No, it's it's it's good news.
It's one of our one of our finest performers got started as a pickle boy.
Jason Mraz.
Really?
At that one.
Minnesota specifically.
So you're a pickle boy.
Wait, probably not.
Hello.
Jason Mraz is like our age is and I don't know how he's a little older than this guy.
Well, all right.
Could have been that this guy was a little older.
I think this guy was definitely you didn't say pickle man.
Not pickle.
He was pickle man.
He was definitely a man, but he wasn't like that old man.
I'm pretty sure it wasn't Jason Mraz.
This guy feels like kind of guy.
Forty five years old.
OK.
Yeah, that timeline doesn't line up.
But, you know, I feel like Jason Mraz has a kind of a direct line to to people's hearts, their heartstrings and maybe this like the sensuality of the pickle boy job that you described.
Maybe it got him thinking, how do I write songs that, you know, tingle people?
He seems like he would be the perfect guy to like motion capture that like rooster in the Robin Hood Disney movie, like with the little like with a little guitar or whatever.
The mandolin.
That seems like a yeah, mandolin.
Like it seems like he's definitely like hat tip to one side, like strumming and making like bawdy jokes while singing.
He's a rake.
I would say that.
What's that word?
He's kind of a rakish, a rakish.
Carouser.
He's a rogue.
Yeah, rogue.
Rogue gets used a lot in this language.
I agree with you, by the way, Mike.
But you know that they're going out to Lin-Manuel first on that.
When Lin-Manuel passes, whenever Disney does this, then we're getting then then they'll go to Mraz.
But Lin-Manuel can't really sing, can he?
Can he?
I think he can't.
He sings like he sings like if you're not singing, it's more like you're trying to sing, but you're not really singing.
You're doing a thing that's like this of a sing.
There's a certain musicality to it that I could do it.
But he doesn't have pipes.
Yeah, maybe not.
Yeah, could he like say that?
Yeah, yeah.
He might divide up his own.
He invented that whole thing because he doesn't have pipes.
He had to figure out how he could.
How can I make it in musical theater without being a real triple threat?
Yes.
But writing parts for singers like there are some very good singers.
Yeah, a lot of his shows.
Sure, sure.
Yeah, I watched a video.
Do you want to talk about actors at this fair?
The Pennsylvania one, at least.
They did like interviews with people who work there.
And it's so funny because someone was like, yeah, I got the job here because I had done a few plays in the area and I knew a little stage combat.
And after three or four months, I'm jumping out of a second story window.
Wow.
Because so everyone like picks up skills.
And it's also like for like an actor, it is like a four month gig.
Like at least at the bigger ones, they do like a month or more of rehearsals just to get ready for it.
Oh, yes.
You don't think about that part.
You think of it as a weekend thing.
But it's like, yeah, it's a way to be employed with odd skills for a while.
Yeah, it's like a scary actor.
Oh, yeah.
It's I would say it's it is on that level of scare actor where it's a little bit.
It's barely employed.
It's sort of that.
You know, I mean, like you're you're almost fully employed.
Yeah.
But the reason you do it is not so much for the job, but because they're letting you do this thing that you want to do.
Like I watch a lot of scare actor auditions.
You ever watch those?
Oh, I know there are videos and documentaries that I haven't gone into.
There's some good ones.
Oh, really?
And it's a certain type of person who is very much the job is like they have to pay you.
But that person, they would do it for free.
You would definitely do it for free.
Just the privilege of being able to play in the arena.
I feel like a lot of Ren Fair people are that way where there's a lot of people who aren't paid to work there.
They just sort of camp there and they they walk around in garb and character interacting with people.
But they're not being paid.
I think it's more they're more just camping there.
I'm not really sure how it works, actually.
I know there's a lot of there's a big behind the scenes at Ren Fair that is I've never been a part of.
Sure, sure.
Did you ever consider trying your hand at working it with that ever occurred to you or scare in your acting?
I definitely have not thought about scare acting because I only learned about that sort of recently.
I think it's something where I don't know.
I don't think I want I don't think I'd be the right person for that.
It'd be a step down at this point.
I guess so.
Yeah.
And I also just don't think I have the I don't have the passion those guys have to do it.
But Ren Fair, I think I don't know.
I don't know.
Maybe I maybe I could do it.
Maybe I would do it.
I don't think it's a commitment.
You also have to buy a lot of stuff.
I don't have like a ton of stuff to wear that would be really sink me into the period enough.
Yeah.
What is there a position there you would want?
Like if there was like one role there that would seems more fun than others.
I mean, probably the pickle guy.
Sounds like it.
Yeah.
Selling those pickles.
Do you remember what a pickle double entendre was?
Wait, we're looking at a pickle guy.
Oh, thanks.
And he's shirtless too.
Wow.
Was your shirtless?
Yes, he was shirtless.
Wow.
Oh, I didn't know that was a dimension of being a pickle guy.
I didn't know that either until just now.
Geez.
I think the pickle thing, it's just everything.
You just talk about your penis, but you say pickle instead of penis.
Yeah.
Ladies, would you like to take a so we're sucking one of my pickles.
They're juicy and long.
Hey, everybody.
I got some fat, juicy pickles.
You can suck on them while you walk around.
No problem.
Touch my pickle.
I dare you.
It won't hurt you.
Geez.
Was this something that actually there was a documented man who would do this in olden
days?
I bet.
Like, was there a?
Yeah.
Ye old Disneyland, Mike.
That's where they got the idea from.
Oh, OK.
That's the big thing about Renfrair too is it's also it's an amalgamation.
There's nothing.
They have like steampunk people there.
There's no wrong way.
There's no hard.
There's hardliners.
But there's also people who are just anything from like I don't even know, probably from
like eleven hundred to sixteen hundred kind of falls in there.
It all counts.
It all blends together because I like looking at this big chart you can look at of all of
them across the country and they all define a specific era that they're set.
And there's a difference between Elizabethan and more like Tudor Robin Hood.
That's Elizabethan, isn't it?
I don't even know.
Is it?
That's what they I've seen the houses and the stages and buildings described as.
They also a lot of them do theme weekends.
Yes.
So there's pirates.
There's unlicensed Harry Potter weekend.
So you're fine on the yard if you still want to do it.
Yeah.
If you want to give us a yard.
Hey, great.
OK, OK.
That was a little theme minute to the pirates.
Pirates are big.
Pirates are really big.
Pirates.
Yeah.
The crossover pirates.
I think what happened when Space
dosage wasuls was time traveler weekend.
And there are just like leaning on a phone on the Doctor Who phone booth.
And so it's like because I do think well, it would be very fun to dress up
and go to these things.
It is funny to wear a Star Trek outfit and go to the I think it is funny.
That's funny.
That's pretty funny.
I thought I think it's funny.
It's eight hours of funny though.
And that long funny.
I mean, there are a lot of improv shows at the sort of like ye olde
Shakespearean like 20 minute improv shows at different little pop up areas.
Ye olde Harold.
I've done a bunch myself actually because usually I have some sort of psychedelic
and then drink a bunch and a lot of times ends up being where you're shouting
just like don't look at this tree.
How dare you look at don't look.
And it's just to people you don't know, which becomes like this weird.
It's like your own personal improv show because you're just so fucked up that
you don't care that you become an entire other.
I really I like the voice first of all, because I was I was curious.
Yeah, what you become when you go there.
And that is that like I feel like you like de-aged yourself with that voice.
Like you're a boy now.
You're a lad.
What are you doing here, sir?
Please give me your sword.
It's like so about that voice.
It's so stupid.
But you know right away what it is.
You're a person.
You're just you're you're bothered by everything.
And you think people aren't where they're supposed to be.
Or you have like a boy with a job who like keep moving.
Move up, move forward.
Keep passing.
Keep walking.
Don't stop here.
Don't touch the deer.
You're an order keeper.
Yeah, kind of a medieval hall monitor.
Keep walking.
I'm I'm 13 years old.
Life expectancy is 26.
So I'm having midlife crisis ease.
Who wants to marry me?
I have nothing.
Looking for a good woman who works hard.
Peaches, peaches.
We all have adult colic.
Tapeworm, tapeworm, a limonade.
Eat this now.
So for no sulfur here.
So you walk around with like mush or ice cubes or something to get rid of people's tapeworms.
That I usually carry like a big huge stick like an old sunflower stalk and have a bunch of rosemary and like bunch of herbs on it and stuff.
And we'll we'll touch people with it like from a distance.
Whoa.
And sometimes that's usually pretty fun.
And that that cures them with something or gives them more power.
It's kind of like it doesn't matter, right?
That's the whole thing.
It's just a grab bag.
If it's kind of ye olde, then it works.
You can have like a but you can walk around with a bunch of rosemary and have like a wool blanket and some mud on your face and you would you'd fit in like a slot boy.
Yeah, you're the slot boy.
Who carrying a bundle of sticks back to your master who is the blacksmith, the smithy.
Sorry, the smithy.
Pardon me.
Who needs them for your collecting.
He's like probably got a burn stuff.
He needs a fire to fuel his blacksmithery.
So you need a bunch of sticks.
All you have to do is just be dirty.
If you're just filthy, that's your costume.
Filthy, no labels.
Instantly and you're instantly time travels.
You could wear the current clothes as long as you you cover up all logos.
If you're wearing a Tasmanian devil shirt, just like modem up real good and then you're not going to get my and just be very almost horrified and confused.
Like what time am I?
Where am I?
When am I?
Well, for the time travelers, for the time travelers weekend for sure.
But and you can buy pretty much any accoutrements.
You can buy herbs.
You buy walking sticks.
This was the only field trip I ever went on where they're like, remember, you cannot buy weapons.
Weapons will not be let back on the bus.
Wooden swords may be discussed, but like they have very elaborate like swords and knives and stuff for sale because that's the other thing.
This employs not just actors for a while, employs like all kinds of crafts.
Blacksmiths, glass blowers, sword makers, candles.
Oh yeah, candles.
Yeah, right.
That's a part of it because I've never done one of these.
What's everybody's full literacy?
I guess just Mike is full literacy.
I can read.
I'm able to read.
Actually, that's one of my special gifts during the Rensma's Fairs.
I'm able to read stuff.
Wow.
Which a lot of people probably people were not educated at that time.
So you're doing them a real like labels.
Labels.
Anyone need a label read?
I knew how to read.
And then I read Martin Luther's proclamation he put on the church door.
And I was just like, never again.
Horrifying.
I will.
I will bang my head on something until I don't remember.
I'm a papist and I don't know what this Protestant nonsense is.
I've gone blind.
I meant to say Ren fair literacy and by which I mean experience and not literacy.
So that having been said, Mike, you ever done it?
No, never done it.
Anytime when I was little and I would go past anything that looked like it, honestly,
it made me uncomfortable.
And I don't know if it was the body Ness or the ladies.
I don't even know if that was being conveyed to me that that's what was happening.
But there was something about it that made me feel odd.
I didn't want to be part of it.
And I guess it's carried over into my adult years, but I'm not against it now.
It's just no one's ever invited me in the last 10 or 15 years to even go.
So it's never come up.
Oh, no.
Well, somebody invited me.
I just said go.
Well, I'm looking.
I was a leader.
Like, yeah, I was looking for like a woe is me like no one invited me.
So I don't want to know.
I don't want to go if no one invites me.
Well, if you go, you got to take acid.
OK, so I'm working on weed.
I'm working on getting weed to work because that freaks me out too much.
And I end up like vibrating at a different frequency.
So acid seems like it's going to be maybe 30 years away from from now.
Unless you're right. Is it possible that somehow acid works in a way that weed doesn't?
I guess I'm asking for myself because I haven't done any drugs in a while.
I think it's all very different on the different person, probably.
But all of it can probably be scary as hell at Renfair if it's done wrong.
I've had bad experiences there.
Mm hmm. Oh, yeah.
Not to take you back to it.
Way too high, like accidentally too high from edibles to the point where you're not going to be able to do anything.
It's difficult to leave the shade of a small tree like sort of stuck.
Oh, shit. Can't move.
One of the last ones.
One of the last times where I where I was like, I think I'm going to stop doing this is I got high at that thing.
I was out with you, Mike. Desert trip.
When we split off, we like parted ways and I met a friend and got too high.
And I just remember that like I was so high that I was like, OK, you got to get your shit together.
And you're going to use cash money correctly and use it to buy a hamburger.
And the person when you do it right, the person is going to be so impressed that you did it.
These are my high thought like you're going to blow her away with your ability to put out money correctly.
And so then I'm doing it so slowly and carefully and weird.
I remember walking up to watch the Neil Young set still full of pride that I used money right.
And then when I came to us like this seems like it's not the fit of getting like five hundred percent dumber for not something I want to do.
That sounds about right. Exactly.
Yeah, this is what I was going through, though, too.
And I was in the pit watching Paul McCartney and I also was high and weird.
Like I was so weird. Yeah.
And I was watching Paul McCartney and I literally all I could see was his old skeleton.
Like I just saw the man's old skeleton dragging himself from the piano to the bass guitar and being like this one's for John.
And like I'm imagining his skeleton talking to me.
And I'm like, I don't know.
I love this song, but I'm a little too much right now.
The opposite of the joy of a Beatle concert that you had.
That's misery.
It's hard to control your dosage with edibles.
But if you go get like you go to a dispenser and say, what is the cheapest pre-roll you have like a four or five dollar pre-roll?
That's pretty reliable.
Yeah. And that's going to rip you up to a good way.
You know, it's going to get you again because they say there's no there used to be like people talk about mids like middle of the road week weed.
And now there's people believe that those have been bred out by decades of like weed is too strong now.
Oh, huh.
So but if you know class of weed has been eliminated.
Yeah. But if you go for the cheaper stuff, it's usually weaker and it's easier to control because there's I mean there's edibles and there's so many gadgets and do that nowadays.
And those can really mess you up.
Accurate.
Can you regulate?
Yeah, I think that's right.
Okay. Okay.
Also, everyone's different.
Yeah. Yes.
Some people find one thing that works.
And also, I think with with Renfair, I think it's good to get just a little more than you want a little more than you're comfortable with.
So you get to that time travel zone where you're feeling that's what I call it is time traveling.
Yeah.
Yes. That's cool.
And the other thing is if you're too high at Renfair, all you have to do is look at your friends you're with and you say if you're getting skeezed out, you got to just say, shall we carry on?
And that's how any situation you just say, shall we carry on?
That's the instant eject button for uncomfortableness.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Well, because from the looks of of like Pickle Boy, for example, right, the uncomfortableness seems like something.
Oh, there's another one.
Oh, no.
I well better or worse than the previous.
But we were looking at the first one we were looking at.
You can watch this on YouTube on the forever.
YouTube.
But the first Pickle Boy was shirtless and kind of like Pete Davidson physique.
This guy's shirted, which is an improvement, but a little bit of like a beret long hair beard creeps.
This guy's older.
He's probably put a shirt on because he's come along in years.
I'm sure he used to be shirtless.
Was once a Pickle Boy, shirtless Pickle Boy.
Now he's shirted Pickle Man.
He's a veteran.
He passes out the start work.
He passed out the W 9s at the start of the season.
Hey, man, I hate to do this, but you got to sign this crap.
It sucks.
It's going to be the last modern thing you got to do after this.
You're in the past.
You don't got to worry about taxes.
They're really good.
They're really fast, though.
And you pick weekly or every other week.
You know, it's cool.
They're all swarthy, though.
They're all swarthy.
Yeah, they're all coxman.
Yeah.
Well, on that point, Jordan, can I ask for a clip?
This is the first clip of two from PM Magazine.
This is the second time this has come up lately.
This early 80s pleasant snooze magazine show that I like.
They profiled the Cabbage Patch Kids.
And then this woman in a really sharp PM Magazine baseball shirt.
She's touring the great...
This is the Houston Ren Fair, I believe.
And this is a guy I think you would want to carry on from.
As quickly as possible.
I'm a rogue.
Come here.
I give away free kisses.
Would you like one?
Yes.
Oh, kissing the reporter.
Rogue.
He's into it.
I know what you are.
You're a renaissance dirty old man.
That's what a rogue is all right.
You got it, lass.
There you go.
Yeah.
A renaissance dirty old man.
Just going in and she had to turn left to break the kiss.
All she had to do was not be directly lined up with it.
So that's a rogue for you.
Another certainly swarthy...
Are beards part of swarthiness and long hair part of swarthiness?
They certainly can be.
I feel like it's all about the movement.
If you got something jangling around, you got some long hair,
you got anything baggy or anything that attracts attention,
that's all swarthy to me.
They're all very Captain Jack Sparrow-esque to me.
They're all half in the bag.
Yeah.
They're definitely half in the bag in the daytime,
roaming around looking for whatever will say yes
or whatever doesn't say no immediately.
That's a question for you.
We've established bodiness, but there's also certainly horniness to it.
What has been your level of comfort with the general horniness?
Or are you, as the impish hall monitor, not privy to the horniness as much?
I don't know.
There's definitely a lot that's on display and stuff.
You see it just in the costumes and the way people act.
People will say ribald comments to you, to strangers.
They'll say stuff about your appearance.
I've had people hit on my girlfriend right in front of me,
and I had to defend her honor.
But it was very fun.
That's kind of fun. Yeah, yeah.
The weirdest thing I think I've seen in terms of that is something called
the Dragon's Lair, which we stumbled upon very late in the day.
It's a glass-blowing area.
You can go back in this tent and you go back to the Dragon's Lair,
which is 18 plus, which is a bunch of dildos and stuff back there.
I remember seeing this stuff.
This is outstanding, going into the Dragon's Lair.
That's what it's called.
They keep all the hand-blown glass dildos and sex toys to have.
That's a surprise.
That's not what you're expecting.
You're like, am I going to see the most impressive animatronic?
Is fire going to be breathed?
Good sir, fair maiden, would you like to come to ye old dildo shack?
You can't call it that. You have to call it the Dragon's Lair.
The old Dragon's Lair.
Are they medieval, are they past-oriented dildos?
Isn't every dildo a past-oriented dildo?
Because I don't think anything has really changed, right?
Ultimately, there's a basic structure to it that you're after
and a task that you need to fulfill.
Is it like one side is a dragon's mouth
and the actual apparatus is coming out of its mouth?
Is there anything crazy like that?
Weirdly enough, I don't have a great memory of this.
I just remember going in there and being like, oh God.
We just stumbled into the Dragon's Lair
and thinking this was not expecting to see that.
I was also probably pretty high at the time.
This was a shall we carry on?
This was fast, shall we carry on?
Would you now like to examine the booklet of skews?
The ISBN numbers for ye pleasure instruments?
That is the best part of it too, is all the commerce,
how quickly it shifts from oh good sir to browse me where's to,
okay, the square isn't reading the,
I'm going to have to type this in manually into the iPad I have here.
When it's done like that, it's pretty great just how quickly commerce takes over character.
Hey, did you notice that the blacksmith has an iPad with a Naruto cover on it?
This was the thing in the,
they were trying to get a Renaissance fair vibe going
in the very early days of Star Wars Galaxy's Edge, the Star Wars landing.
It seemed like the bar they were trying to hit was full time travel
or in another place in this different language that we speak.
I don't know if you did it ever in that time or have since.
I think what they thought would happen that people will come and kind of live in the world,
and I think it did not.
I think it is a place with rides and you buy stuff.
That was certainly where the roads diverged.
Because I bought something on the first day and there was some fancy term for credit card.
I already don't remember what it was, and I did not have fun with it.
I was just like, what are you talking about? Your credit card.
They had a name for it. I remember this.
Yeah. Do you guys remember the name?
Credits is usually what they say in the Star Wars universe.
They say credits for money.
But I would have known that.
They call it like a pass or something like that.
I call it like a, I remember distinctively being like, I like this.
I like this that they're all in.
They won't talk to you at all about anything.
They're hardliners.
I appreciated that.
You brought that term to us too.
Hardliner being just like fully go for it.
Would you call yourself a hardliner or would you not give yourself that full?
No, but I really like, anytime there is someone there,
a lot of times what I will do is a walk to the very end where they have all the,
there's a lot of people camping there.
A lot of people camp there every weekend.
There's people who do reenactments.
There's a whole group of people who reenact Scottish Highland warriors from that area.
And I talked with one guy for probably, I would say more he talked to me,
but for probably about 40 minutes I sat there and it was so interesting.
He was talking about all the Hallbirds, all the different pikes and stuff,
explaining each one of them to me.
I was pretty high and having a bunch of beers,
but it was fascinating that he was also explaining and it ended with him clearly seeing I was very interested,
saying, let me get your phone number and email and we have meetups every weekend.
If you would like to join us, take it down.
And I just, you know, I'm not going to say, oh, no, no, no.
I said, okay, yeah.
And sure enough, I got a call from this guy for a couple of weeks in a row before he realized
I'm probably not going to go out to these Highland events.
Which are where? Which are like out, probably like in Whittier or Pacoima or something like that.
The fair itself is like half hour east of here.
Yeah, it's in Irwindale Recreation Dam area.
But I kind of wanted to go to them. I did. It just didn't work out.
It's not something, it's kind of, I think it's a, you got to be in.
You know what I mean? It's a real, it's like any kind of extremely dorky thing where you're kind of, you can't be half in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's a commitment.
Like I remember going to comic stores growing up and seeing like the Warhammer miniatures.
And I thought they were very cool, like these little soldiers and tanks and all this stuff.
And I was like, I don't know. This seems cool, but I cannot commit to this.
Like I knew I was like, this is another world.
This is the back of the store. And I gravitate to the front of the store.
And they're never shopping to two houses equal of dignity, but not.
Jason, do you remember when we were at the Margaritaville Grand Opening at City Walk and this like some of the heads of the San Diego parrot head chapter were there.
They were very enthusiastic and they met us and they were like so excited by the idea that we could come down and be part of their San Diego chapter of paradise.
Because they said the San Diego parrot heads were much more active than the Los Angeles.
And the Orange County more vibrant. Yeah, it was a much more vibrant community.
They talk shit on the Orange County crew.
Yeah, they said that they were the best ones and that there were like a lot of like political problems with the other chapters of the parrot head organizations.
But they were like, like, yeah, here's our information. Like they were so ready.
This is exactly the same thing. It's totally parallel. Yeah, 100 percent parallel.
Same thing. Yes. And it was like I wanted to do it, but like I'm like, am I really? No, there's no way you're going to go to San Diego and then you're justifying it.
You're explaining it to friends like, well, why do I drive all the way?
Oh, yeah. Well, it's just better. There's less politics. It's just organized.
What you just said doesn't make any sense. How do you explain it to friends?
No, you don't have friends. Those are your friends. Yeah, that's the issue.
That's what that guy was doing. He's like, oh, clearly you don't have any friends.
Do you want to be friends with us? Because we'll welcome you.
Which is kind of beautiful. And like he really thinks he's like that you're a you are a lost soul who he can recruit into his band of married men.
Why would anyone else listen to a speech about Hallberg's for 30 minutes and keep asking follow up questions unless he was a person without friends who needed to have some friends and had weekends?
Weekends? I'm open. It did not occur to him that you might be gacked out of your mind and frozen in the spot.
Loving it. But still, like, I'm here. I'm visiting. I'm not like looking to move into this area.
I'm just I'm here as a tourist. I'm a tourist to your world.
I'm cosplaying in Renaissance gear, but also cosplaying as a person who would do who would listen to you.
Yeah. The interesting thing with all of this set with the body and the boozey.
Yes, I do. I will say Renaissance fairs are very family friendly.
A lot of them do outreach for school groups. So I would say like the vibes are pretty chill.
Like you can kind of pick whatever level you're at.
I don't think they've gotten into the some parks that do haunts have started selling like light up necklaces that you can pay extra for and go like, please don't scare me.
Oh, really? Yeah. So I I'm wondering if there's money to be made to like beef up the budgets on these Renaissance fairs.
I'm like, hey, give me extra personal space. Like, I want to commit to this.
But I a necklace that you wear that lights up where you're like, don't throw a double entendre at me, please.
Please don't. Yeah, I do not want a washing wench to try to make me give them a piggyback ride.
See, that's what I think about the Ren fair is it's so close to not happening at all.
You know, it's so homespun DIY that they just they can barely do what they're doing to do.
That would be it would break their backs to try to accommodate people.
And that's a system. Yeah. A subtle form of accommodation that wasn't like a sort of thing.
Like, I think it would probably just tear them to.
I just why would you why would you not want to have someone?
Why would you come if you didn't want to have someone talk to you?
It's like the whole point of it. It would just take this gnashing in your brain.
I have a back. I want to give people rides on it.
There was a disclaimer on the Pennsylvania one website of like, look, the pathways are all paved.
They're ADA compliant. There are some stages that are in grass fields and we can't do anything about that.
Talking about this, my memory of the marketing for the Pennsylvania one was like very like low budget commercials where it would be a shot of a night on horseback and then the logo and slowly panning over like a slideshow logo that says like sponsored by Burger King.
And like someone just singing like the Pennsylvania Renaissance Fair.
But Jordan, if you can pull up that video I sent you, this is the twenty twenty two commercial for it.
And they upgraded their marketing budget.
Oh, crap.
Let the celebration begin.
Indeed. We went out of a castle to a woman doing a dance.
Oh, one flops.
Turkey lay women surrounding the turkey guy.
Or fair maidens.
Oh, fish are swimming out of graphics.
Visit pa renter dot com.
Whoa, I'm there next year.
I'm going.
It's great. And there's travel packages.
They partnered with local hotels in the areas, which there is many because this is a city that's been in the business for a long time.
I didn't know this was such a big rent fair.
That's cool.
Yeah.
And at some point they swapped out one small stage and built a mermaid tank.
I saw that.
That is truly they're just gone.
They're gone for broke.
Aren't they?
Yes.
That is truly absurd.
The mermaid tank that is like so unnecessary and has nothing to do with the Renaissance at all.
Yeah.
Square.
I guess it's mythological.
It's fantasy.
But I love that's what I like about it is it's sort of just that's the theme at Renaissance fair that no one ever talks about.
It's the original inclusive place.
It's the original all inclusive.
There's no no one's turned away.
You can be the biggest freak you want to be and show up and no one's going to say anything to you whatsoever.
Other than just like hell yeah.
Anything is anything's welcome.
Yeah.
I was looking into the history of it which I didn't know because I didn't know like have these been going since the Renaissance has it been 200 years or has it.
And I didn't know it was in this it came out of the 60s.
It's a 60s Laurel Canyon thing.
Malibu.
Specifically.
Huh.
OK.
That was original was in Malibu in the hills of Malibu.
I think.
Oh and Agoura is where it's at.
Yeah.
It was there for a while.
It was a really bad documentary about it.
That's not that fun to watch.
I have watched and that.
So this Renaissance fair here Renaissance pleasure fair is not the longest running but it is the oldest.
I think.
Yes.
This one.
That's what they credit is like the first real.
There was a littler historical festivals smaller ones.
I think an early one was at the Paramount Ranch.
That's the Agoura one.
Yeah.
Which is the filming location for Dr. Quinn Medicine Woman.
Oh wow.
It all burnt down though I believe sadly.
So sorry to tell you Quinn heads.
You can't go to the apothecary or whatever.
Is that a thing in the Old West?
Yeah.
Is that OK?
All right.
My history literacy.
Early version of pharmacy.
OK.
That would have been.
All right.
But yeah.
But what I.
There's a bunch of hippies.
Yeah.
I did not know any of that lineage to it that it was like it was a hippie oriented thing
and besides the the theming and the time travel of it there was also just the very hippie element
of anybody come and it's communal and you peddle your wares and and and where and it
was like sleep with anybody you want to.
It was very like it's very openly like free love kissing booth kind of thing.
Yeah.
That's how it used to be.
There are articles I was reading I think Bloomberg is one of them that like they they were like
you can draw a straight line from early 60s birth of Renaissance Fair to Woodstock or
any of that that like that did not have the theme to it obviously but the idea of it's
going to be a semi organized field that is communal and everybody take care of each other
that maybe that doesn't happen without the rise of Renaissance Fairs a few years earlier.
That makes sense.
I just didn't know that like and that also a lot of it was done in counter to like a
Red Scare like really.
Yeah I think so that like like the idea of a place where like hippies and lefties can
come work and not be like like the school teacher.
What's the name Phyllis Patterson was the person was the person who started what became
the pleasure fair but that she was like very put off by like the get these pinkos out of
here like that you know and a world where like people couldn't work because of their
ideas and their freewheeling ways.
Yeah.
The whole thing was a rebellion to of the 50s essentially.
Wow.
Yeah.
So it's like you can see the like the thing that I keep thinking of is like there's a
lot of furry cons like there's a thing called Midwest Fur Fest and I go this is just a ren
fair for people with fursonas and big costumes animal costumes basically like it's the exact
same thing.
There's the exact same amount of horniness as far as I can tell I've never been a little
bit more.
Yeah.
Maybe a little bit more horny.
That's fair.
But yeah it's like everybody's like almost recreating the model I feel like.
No.
Yeah.
I also I think then I have notes about how like they encountered rebellion like there
were people who tried to shut down the early ren fairs because they read of that these
places are full of lewd dances and distribution of literature advocating free love and the
use of LSD.
Oh.
We must shut down these these dreaded endeavors.
Only the CIA can use LSD.
No no.
That's a good slogan right there.
Only the CIA can use LSD.
I'm sorry but only the CIA can use LSD.
I have a card it's to treat my Havana syndrome.
Oh.
Which is suspiciously similar to a very bad hangover.
Let me stay in in the free love horniness zone a little more.
Can we pull up the other clip from PM magazine.
This is like we discuss dildos but there's one word that that is adjacent to dildo.
Maybe it's not actually.
Is it a pud?
Well what we're looking at right now is the codpiece.
Let's hear this guy discuss his codpiece.
And the codpiece here is a symbol of one of Henry's idiosyncrasies.
He had a rule that no man could have a larger codpiece in the kings and it was a privilege
to be with the king when he dressed and so he would deliberately get his courtiers to
help him dress with a moderate sized codpiece so they would happily go out and put on theirs.
Let's just stare at this codpiece for a second too.
Kind of like fancy pattern yellow orange a rose on top.
I just.
It's like a little locker like a little purse.
A satchel.
It's a little satchel for his penis.
It's a penis purse.
A penis purse.
I just never given a lot of thought to the codpiece.
I think it's an interesting facet of this that it's like a way to.
Like a comfortable environment to for people to be able to wear a codpiece and it's just
a funny item because you know like there's clothing meant to accentuate women's body
parts but very little for the penis and with the codpiece having dropped off in popularity.
I don't know.
I'm fascinated.
It's interesting if codpieces came back all of a sudden.
Yeah maybe like it's a different name maybe it's like a pickle storage box.
Pickle purse.
My pickle purse.
My pickle.
I think you've got to get rid of that name.
The name is so why is there a name of a fish which feels limp feels gross not the way you
want to present your penis.
I wonder what it is if there's any relations of the fish cod and the codpiece.
I don't know.
Yes why cod.
This is something you'd ask someone at Renfair and they would give you a lengthy explanation
in the Queen's English.
And you'd be invited if you want to join the codpiece society if you want to like fight
the fight to get codpieces back in the national consciousness.
Going to the cod tank.
It should at least be a better fish.
Yeah what's a more virile.
A marlin.
Strong for a barracuda.
Yeah marlin definitely.
Marlin and barracuda are both good.
I don't know.
A trout is not.
Trout would be bad.
Troutpiece.
Walleye.
Is funny but yeah.
What's that one.
Anything like the cheaper stuff at a restaurant.
You don't want a tilapia piece.
No.
Scrod.
Scrodpiece.
You've managed to find one that's worse than codpiece.
Just took a couple extra letters.
In the modern era similar clothing pieces are worn in the leather subculture.
Oh yeah.
And in performance costumes such as for rock musicians and metal musicians.
So like.
Well I think of it with Batman and Rob.
I feel like Batman's the main.
Batman had a cod didn't he.
Yeah you'd call that a codpiece I would say.
He's got a dangler.
There's that yeah there's that Chris O'Donnell toy that hasn't come out yet from Batman Forever
That I Want and his codpiece is possibly the biggest I've ever seen on any person or toy.
Bigger than King Henry here with his rose.
That's why he doesn't work as much anymore.
I'm going to find the picture and I'll just send it in the chat.
That's why he doesn't.
He's relegated to NCIS New Orleans because they're like well it's a party city so it
makes sense for his character to always have this codpiece on.
He has to wear a codpiece it's just like a it's actually a medical device.
What does it do for him?
I already helped medically but is it like are they like is there like a like a gas moving
through it that's just like.
I don't really know.
I'm not really sure.
I've never worked with them on this.
I don't really know.
I mean it'd be a cool thing to explore I think.
They'll give you the run day if you're ever cast in something with Chris they'll give
you the talk.
Hey Johnny can you come into that office real quick.
The UPM might talk to you.
Hey we're happy to have you.
Won't you know a little something about Chris and that you know the rest I won't say because
I don't know what to say.
You don't know the specifics of it but yeah but the main thing is Chris's eyes are up
here all right.
He is not his codpiece.
There's a lot of room for improvisation in this scene.
Whatever you do don't punch him in the dick.
I know you are a naval deserter in this scene.
You are deserting from the Navy and the NCIS are after you but whatever you do don't become
so desperate that you try to punch him in the dick because you will be hurt by the codpiece.
I wasn't going to do that but I guess I definitely will not.
This is standard safety meeting.
It's in the SAG.
It's in the twenty twenty two agreement.
And we've told people not to do it and they say they won't do it and then they still do
it.
So we want to make sure you're not one of those.
OK.
Your word is your bond.
No I didn't come here.
I didn't spend my entire life just to get to this moment where I could do a thing that
I was told not to do.
OK great.
So your handle remain functional and you'll be fine.
I sent it in the chat.
So it's look I don't know that he it's actually based on his own thing.
I think this the toy makers got excited perhaps and decided to really like have fun with it.
You sent us the picture.
I don't know.
Well Jordan the picture is in the zoom.
Jordan if you can wait a second.
Chris O'Donnell COD.
Oh my God.
Oh fuck.
Been hiding in plain sight all these years.
God.
What's up.
I just want to give an update.
Chris O'Donnell is in NCIS Los Angeles.
Scott Bakula is NCIS New Orleans.
I like your notion that a story in the show is about capturing naval deserters.
Well that holds water to me.
It's exciting.
It sounds good.
Like military crimes I believe.
It could be.
I have zero idea what a plot would be on NCIS.
Yeah.
Jack.
I think the original one is like well Mark Harmon is super competent and he's really
handsome.
Like that's his character's game.
And he got punched in the dick.
That's why he finally left the show.
He got punched in the dick too hard.
My dick's getting too old for this shit.
And O'Donnell's like just listen to my voicemails.
Call me back.
That is.
Okay now we're looking at it.
Now we got it.
This is the toy.
Wow that is not right.
The COD piece.
That can't be real.
That's insane.
The movie wasn't like that.
It's like a thrusting outline.
That's what I'm saying.
Like a movie didn't look like that.
That's ridiculous.
It's even got like a sort of webbing that indicates it's under stress.
The fabric is being.
You know what I mean?
Like it wasn't designed to.
Being pushed to its limit.
It feels like plastic to me.
And even the plastic is like we're breaking down here.
Because the Batman one is more like a shell.
Like a protective thing.
This appears to be.
Yeah that's a protective.
That's a protective thing to protect Batman's balls.
Kind of makes sense with the way the legs are sculpted.
You can see veins.
If you squint enough you're seeing a bonobo monkey right now.
Kind of with the red nose right?
Or instead of bonobo whatever that one's called with the red nose.
It's that monkey that has the big ol.
A proboscis monkey.
It looks like that.
Whoa what a pull.
It's like a Snickers bar.
It's got the caramel dick veins on it.
It's not.
Batman's codpiece is playing defense and this is playing offense.
This is like facing forward.
If he lines.
If he jumps.
Like jumps at the penguin.
He could poke his eyes out on the way.
I think Ace and Gary are less sexual than this.
I think so yes.
They didn't push it far enough.
The company that makes this is called Hot Toys.
Oh well.
Well.
Takes on a different meaning now.
You could.
Yeah this would be in the dragon's lair no problem.
Mike you have to let.
Are you getting this?
Is this going to be in your home soon?
It's not out yet.
I haven't pre-ordered it.
If I get it obviously the first people that will know is the podcast the right audience.
That's what I was going to say.
As soon as it is available please bring it to a video version of the show.
And then I don't want to say where it should go in your apartment but you know I love that
Leonardo with the big dick tail.
I just think you put these right next to each other.
Touching you want their dicks to touch.
That's exactly what I want.
And then I want to see photographic proof of it and then also keep your daughter out
of there.
Yeah no she should not be exposed to this film.
Robin's a rogue.
Yeah he's a rogue.
And Mike so you moved recently so you might still have some flex space that you haven't
decided what to do with yet.
It sounds like you need to make it an in-home dragon's lair.
For dildos?
Well for your filth toys.
For my toys that have prominent dicks.
Yeah sweetie and remember honey you're not allowed to go to the dragon's lair until you're
much much older and we have a talk with you about dragon's lairs.
The dragon's lair.
Again it's funny to say this but I think like the level of body in this of a lot of the
shows and the Pennsylvania website does like there are icons where it's like this is a
PG-13 show or like this is a.
Oh yeah.
Plus PG-13 plus like avoid the kids.
Like I think you can take families to the Renaissance Fair.
It's just maybe now and then you have to go like oh hey we're not going that way.
It's a more natural form of sexuality.
It's not like a junior at the computer finding something and all of a sudden he can't unsee.
It's everyone's around you can discuss it.
It's out in the open.
Sure.
It's a more like you know it's a more like old school version of it.
It seems less if it's something that's outside it's in the air it's daytime it's less like
you know what it's not.
Shameful.
Yeah it's not shameful.
La Civie.
It's not this thing where it appears to be dark and vicey it's more fun and maybe maybe
it's titillating but it's kind of it's OK to embrace your sexuality a bit as opposed
to having to hide it and to be.
Yeah I don't know.
I've just all of a sudden got very like philosophical with this whole thing.
There's no like step mother father siblings business going on.
There's no Ted Cruz likes.
Yeah.
Twitter likes business going on here.
You're just saying porno mother daughter porno stuff.
Huh.
That was a confused that was an interesting pile of words.
Were you saying step like you were saying like porno scenarios.
Yeah yeah there's no step there's no step business going on there's no Dean Norris sex
gifts going on.
Dean Norris.
The characters are the characters of the Renaissance Fair are talking about like my step sister.
Which is which.
What did what was Ted Cruz.
What's the truth.
Ted Cruz liked and then what a Dean Norris someone on Ted Cruz's staff liked like a gift
from like a step sibling like Johnny's in porno movie and then Dean Norris just attempting
to Google tweeted the phrase sex gifts.
Oh my God.
Much respect to never deleted it.
That is awesome.
Yeah that is great.
He saw the humor in it.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I think there has to be some sort of something to invent a thing for as you get older that
limits your ability to interact with technology so things like that can't happen.
It's going to happen to everybody if you don't stay.
If you're not super techie and current you're going to misstep when you're trying to use
a thing you don't know that well.
Next thing you know you're tweeting out sex gifts.
Well it's either even not like a child lock or child.
It's a grandpa lock basically.
It needs to be a grandpa lock on things where you just you can't have access unless someone
in your inner circle is with you showing you like OK so if you want to see the stuff that
we know you want to see.
I'm not asking questions.
You have to be really open minded with your parent or grandparents.
Right.
Don't judge them in any way but just like a discussion before you want to see Marina
search is naked.
This is a this is called Firefox focus.
It's a browser.
It's always in private mode and it only opens one website at a time.
Yes.
You're not logged in anything.
It won't leave you logged into anything.
That would be great actually.
That'd be pretty good.
This is a good business idea.
Maybe something to file away.
Hi I'm Marina searches.
Have you been searching for me on the Internet.
Well fear no longer.
You can find me without having other people know you found me without broadcasting to
all of your followers.
I've partnered with Mozilla.
I'm definitely today I'm going to tweet out Marina searches sex gifts.
Please do.
This will solve the mystery if people hear the podcast and like oh so that's why this
is why I came here is I can say Marina searches and everyone knows who I'm talking about immediately.
Yeah this is yeah this is the audience.
Wait let me admit that I don't.
I've liked the sound of it in the reference.
Oh but I actually talked about counselor Deanna Troy from Star Trek.
Oh OK OK.
You knew she was also she was also one of the characters on gargoyles.
Scott Wow.
And animated show.
She was.
I didn't know that I used to love that show.
Hmm.
She's like she's the Mona.
She's gargoyle.
Wow.
Antihero gargoyle.
Is that right.
She's like the main female gargoyle.
Yeah gargoyle sex gifts.
Marina searches gargoyle sex gifts.
Don't start down that rabbit hole or you might never come out.
That's there.
Yeah that is for sure there.
Yeah.
Well I'm looking at these results.
There's guys at Patreons probably who have that like what do you do.
I do gargoyles gargoyles porn you know gargoyles.
This is a more recent picture here I believe.
Oh yeah.
Yeah and not a set.
Yes.
Jordan did not pull up a sex gift of her.
That would not be proper for the forever dog YouTube channel.
Red carpet photo.
I'm a big Marina Surtis fan.
I'm a big fan.
Everyone in Star Trek Next Generation I'm a massive fan of.
I would not disrespect any of them.
Michael Dorn.
Gates McFadden.
None of them deserve.
Gates McFadden does not deserve that.
Jonathan Frakes.
Also on gargoyles the bad like the bad guy on gargoyles.
Oh yeah.
Yes.
I mean I was at a meet there and Gene Roddenberry was just like hey I like this show a lot.
I'm just gonna steal the cast.
Not Gene Roddenberry.
Who's the EP for next gen.
The later one.
Do you know?
Yeah.
Well gargoyles is like 95 and Gene Roddenberry dies in like 90.
Okay so it was not.
It was not.
So gargoyles they met on Trek and they went on to work on gargoyles together.
I get it.
But now you know.
Look up that show and you're essentially getting extra Star Trek Next Gen.
Damn.
Some bounding.
Sexy gargoyles.
What's it called?
Shipping?
Is that what they call it?
Oh yeah I guess so.
Yeah yeah.
If you've ever wanted your favorite Star Trek characters to be gargoyles first of all.
A little Riker Troy shipping.
Not really.
But not really needed because they're together so you don't need to ship.
They've been shipped.
Oh shipping is if they aren't together.
Yeah yeah.
Got it.
That's like Diva and Chitara.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Or like you would ship Data and Troy.
I thought it was like different shows.
Like you take like Tracer from Overwatch and have a scene with.
I think that is allowed.
I think that is.
There's a lot of umbrella.
I think that falls under the same.
Yeah.
Well let me.
Jurisdiction.
Can I.
Then I'd like to ship.
Let's say Ed Asner's character from Gargoyles Hudson.
Okay.
With Mark Harmon's character from NCIS.
Put those together.
Okay yeah.
That's great.
In a sexy New Orleans type setting.
Like I really like they've had a bunch of Sazeracs and now they're going back to his place in the French Quarter.
And it's the place where Hudson is a gargoyle on the building.
Okay.
So like it's you know.
Oh he lives in an old building that has a gargoyle.
Yeah yeah.
Full moon.
I can't get into this.
I can't get into this for free.
That will be on the.
Yeah.
We'll start.
Yeah we'll do all of our fan fiction shipping behind a paywall.
Before we wind it today here let me just do some like quick hits of stuff we have.
Let me see if you have experience with these.
Do you like these big parts of your rent fare experience.
We haven't talked jousting.
You watch joust.
Yeah I thought the joust is the what do you call it like the most obvious thing.
It's the it's the kind of part of the big finale.
Yeah it's crowd pleaser.
It's also kind of the normy part of the rent fare.
Sure.
So you take your kids take the whole family down to joust.
It's always crowded and that's where you go.
It's fun but it's also to me it's the normy part of it.
Like you see it once you've seen it enough.
Sure.
Yeah yeah.
You got that's interesting.
I think it's interesting that there are rides at rent fare but not electric powered rides.
All the rides are like pushed around by somebody.
I saw Adrian Grenier on a swing one time.
That was cool.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
Yeah you get on like a big big rocking horse a giant rocking horse.
That seems like fun.
Yeah.
You get in a big maze.
I don't think we ever talked about big mazes on this show.
Oh that's a good one.
I kind of like a big maze.
These mazes aren't super big though.
The ones at least in my experience they're not huge mazes.
It's not like the big mazes are attraction themselves right.
This is more just like a it's more for kids I think.
OK OK.
I think you set up hay bales and you make a maze as opposed to like a pre-built hedge
maze.
Oh sure.
Yeah yeah.
Hedges.
That's too much.
You like put one of those up permanently and then that stays.
Yeah.
Yeah yeah.
You die in it in the snow.
Yes.
I think terrorized your family.
Hey I feel like we got to talk about maypoles real quick because I just feel like Jason
would like a maypole.
I mean I can't remember if I've ever done a maypole but I like the concept just ribbons
off a pole and you you everyone runs around it and you wrap the ribbon around the pole
and then you do it all over again.
You got to do a maypole.
I've never done it.
I've never been there in time to participate but they do it all the time.
It's a giant line.
You got to get there five in the morning to do the maypole.
That's very family friendly.
A lightning lane for a maypole.
You got to pay extra.
It's the rise of the resistance of the renaissance pleasure fair.
I drinks there.
Well first of all what's going on with mead.
We got we got mead happening.
Is mead any good.
It's kind of sweet.
It's honey wine basically.
It's slow fermented honey wine.
I don't like it.
It's too sweet for me.
Yeah it doesn't sound like it would.
But you know people like it because it's of the time.
It's very it's such.
I think it's the oldest fermented beverage maybe.
It might be.
Sounds right.
It's before beer.
Right.
So what are you drinking then usually?
I'm drinking a lot of usually a lot of just beers.
I'm drinking a lot of let's say I have craft brew now so you get a higher ABV.
If you really want to get blitzed.
Just get real slacked so you're just dragging your foot around there you know what I mean.
Just real.
Yeah.
Real inebriated to the point where you feel totally unencumbered from saying literally anything.
Of the period.
Yes.
You know.
Ye old double IPA.
Yeah.
Ye old double IPA from Goose Island.
But back then Goose Island was just an island that was terrorized by geese.
People you could never go there.
Beware Goose Island.
That's not our kingdom anymore.
That belongs to the geese.
You want to be goose food?
Are you crazy?
Yeah.
Scott I was telling you before we started recording the day I was there the day me and
like 50 seventh graders were just unleashed on our own to like all right just have a buddy.
You can run around all you want just don't do it alone.
I ate a turkey leg and then they gave us like refillable cups at the fair and just all day
for eight hours only drank Coca-Cola.
So this was like the the field trip that I left feeling like I am dying.
Something has gone wrong.
And I so and of course it wasn't it was just a yellow school bus.
And I'm like we're so many hours away from the middle school.
How will I live?
And I looked it up.
I looked at the Google Maps and from the Renaissance fair to my school was an hour and 10 minutes.
So I was in such a state I was just like that that was probably when I learned like OK if you go to
Renaissance fair you go to theme park because these are essentially very so like pop-up theme parks
for like two three four months of a year.
I need to drink a lot of water.
Yeah.
Because a lot of that would have helped this situation.
I mean what I think this would have helped I would have felt better.
Yeah.
The peak would not have been resolved but I would not have felt like shit from that much corn syrup and caffeine.
Would it have been would it be justified to wear a diaper.
Such as I don't think you wore diapers back then.
I definitely did.
Yeah probably.
Yeah I think it's almost you can piss yourself there.
I think it's one of the few places you can piss yourself and it's not a big deal.
Geez.
It's really not.
That's that hippie idea to not be judged for your clothes being soaked in urine.
You could also probably sell it.
You could be like I'm the bad man of the town.
I'm the piss man.
Or just say it's pickle brine.
Give me a hug.
I'm the piss man.
We gotta hug the piss.
We came all this way we can't not hug the piss man.
Oh honey look it's the piss man.
I got some of his piss on me.
He ran out of snake oil and just started selling piss.
Is that Jason Mraz playing the piss man.
I was the piss man for a little bit then I was the pickle man.
I upgraded to the pickle man.
Wait a minute.
Is the remedy piss?
Has this whole time the remedy?
The remedy is the experience.
The serious is the dangerous liaison.
The liaison is you in a toilet.
Yeah we all know the lyrics to the remedy Jason.
Yeah.
I'm surprised you do.
I have one more little thing before we wind it down.
Is it the dunk tank?
Oh wait we haven't talked about that.
I've seen the phrase drench a wench.
Oh my god I have drenched that wench every time I've gone.
I'll do it two or three times.
Wow.
And I'm like deadly accurate too.
Jeez really.
Wait what are you throwing?
These little like kind of like it's like if you go to a batting cage it's like a softball from a batting cage.
But I have I have drenched this wench.
She insults you like crazy.
She will be very very mean.
She will insult your manhood.
She'll insult like if you're with a significant other she'll insult that person all kinds of stuff.
And I have hit I have dunked that wench right in the middle of an insult.
That's something that feels better in the entire world than drenching a wench right when she's saying she's mouthing off and you just dunk her.
Wow.
In the midst of sailing.
Oh you and your little your little cut.
Oh really.
Jeez.
She doesn't even get out the full thing that mouth floods with water and then that.
That's only happened one time I had the perfect timing.
But you must really feel that like because they also if you're if you're high in trend then you're probably like the emotions are stronger too.
So like that rage like you feel it go into your your hand.
This is usually early on it's kind of early in the fair so I'm probably pretty sober at that point.
OK. Oh you hit that one on the early.
Yeah.
Well for accuracy I guess.
Yes.
Yeah. You don't want to be throwing willy nilly.
We would have dunk tanks at like fundraising school fairs and stuff and like teachers or principals would like rotate through doing it.
And I always liked and got along with most of my teachers and the principals and stuff.
But when I saw them at the dunk tack I was like I want to I want to get them.
Oh yeah.
I would have dunked them in the water.
It's a primitive thing.
You just want to drench.
Yeah.
You're allowed you're allowed to like.
Own someone you know just really get it.
Sorry Mr. Salvatore.
That polo is getting drenched.
Did you dunk Mr. Salvatore.
I think so.
I am not the most accurate throw but I was always pretty good at dunk tanks.
Oh it's the best.
It's something we should maybe offer to the listeners possibly is like if you want.
So we've had our you know we had our gripe situation complain at us that way.
But splash the Scott.
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Uh huh.
Oh it's hard to think of them for the other.
This is not splash.
Wait wait.
We'll splash the Sheridan works.
That works.
Yeah.
Um.
So.
You got soaked.
You got drenched.
You got wet.
Mm hmm.
You got splashed.
Michael.
Yeah.
Get what get Mike Brown.
Drown Michael.
Somebody a listener really hates you if that's the.
I guess that's true.
Yeah.
But you know like instead of just complaining at us if we get stuff wrong give if we gave
people an opportunity to like you think you know everything about I love Lucy you motherfuckers.
Those years were all over the map.
Bang.
Drowned.
And then you then you don't know everything about Marina Surtis.
You faker.
You liar.
Oh I do.
No I do.
All right.
I.
One thing I saw on the Pennsylvania website that I really like they listed all the vendors
and it's so like specific.
There's so much cool stuff you can buy.
There's so many craftsmen employed like in selling their wares and stuff.
But the list was like swords.
You know candles homemade longbows.
And then there was just a little icon that just said cheese steaks.
And for all the language there are a lot of comforts of the modern.
There are like there are ATM scattered throughout the fair and in the wine shop.
It was mostly cash though as surprise but they're like OK you can go in and with a credit
card that you know there's all those like if you have cash converted to a debit card
this was the opposite.
If you have a credit card you can buy coins that you can use for goods and services at
the fair or just take one home as a souvenir.
And I thought that was a really clever way to do it.
Yeah.
And they're like oh if change is required we will just give you change in regular legal
tender.
OK.
They don't have every increment of coin.
I can't believe how good the pen of Pennsylvania one is.
I didn't realize that.
It sounds really solid.
Yeah.
Seems like a strong one.
A quick quick thing before we wind down.
Here's somebody you might want to drench.
This is Jordan.
Can you pull up the one that the clip that has the words January 6th.
Oh yeah.
I'm happy to bring those words in.
What's that mean.
I don't know if you know.
Oh it's a topsy turvy day from the hunchback of Notre Dame.
That's true.
That is a bizarre thing that that is true.
All right.
Let's let's see this.
A woman from Pennsylvania accused of stealing House Speaker Nancy Pelosi's laptop during
the January 6th riot will be allowed off of house arrest this weekend to go to the Pennsylvania
Renaissance Fair.
Again Riley Williams of Central PA had asked a judge to let her go to the fair this Saturday.
The judge granted that request today making this her second trip to the fair while on
home confinement.
She was allowed to go last month as well.
Honestly I heard about this and I support this and I love this woman despite everything
that she has done.
I feel like this is like this is the jewel of a human.
You know what I mean.
There's something there's this dichotomy going on there.
Ren Fair and insurrection meet.
Yeah.
And a person.
It's just like this is it's too good.
It's almost like how is that a real story.
It's so good.
Your honor my client is not Mr. Ren Fair in 20 years and the first time she went the mermaid
tank wasn't ready but now it is open.
She's got blogs to make your honor.
You expect her to not partake in the bountiful cheese steaks.
Yeah there are a lot of videos like video full videos of shows videos of like what's
new at the Renaissance Fair.
There is a lot of crossover with like theme park vlogging stuff of like here's what's
new here's what's the best.
Like secrets and she'd probably make the best one of all of them and we don't want to give
her a we don't want to give her a shot.
We know that she's a dynamo.
She's the one who made it in there and got the laptop.
I think she should probably be in the military and she's got what it takes to be a leader
in the military.
Well she's right.
She got into the capital and she got out of she broke out of house arrest with everyone
what legally to go to clear to go to the past.
This is just too good.
It's just like this is so good.
It's like a perfect story.
Basically you're in love.
Did she bring.
Did she bring the laptop to the fair.
Ye old pilfered goods.
She get on the podcast.
Yeah sure.
Yeah.
She could stand her house arrest.
But obviously as with you Johnny in person it's you know it's it's better it's more
organic it's more fun.
So we're going to want to.
Well let's start.
We'll file an appeal and see if we can get I don't remember her name but we'll know it
and cherish it soon enough.
Yeah just add her to the pile of all the different January 6 people we've tried to get on the
podcast.
They're just they're they're too in demand.
Yeah.
We were right out.
They just kept saying I don't need to tell you that.
Am I being detained.
Is it possible that the insurrection was sort of a pop up theme park.
Wow.
Well it was it was a themed experience like you know the boring capital got rethemed for
a day.
It's like it's Viking Day in the capital.
Yeah.
There's a lot of lore.
There's a lot of exhausting canon.
Yeah.
It's a lot of people who live in fantasy worlds.
Yeah that's well that's really what it is.
The people who've the who are the most the biggest hardliners are the people who've gone
a full insurrection mode.
Mike and I'm waiting in an 80 hour line.
We want a chance to buy that laptop.
It's very similar if you think about it.
It's got to there's definitely got to be a crossover.
It's a full time cosplay that you're you forgot is a cosplay.
Mm hmm.
God.
Yeah.
That you never come back from.
Also Nancy Nancy Pelosi's laptop is still using an unsupported version of Internet Explorer
with six different search tat those search bars that would just add themselves to your
browser back in the day.
It makes it harder to buy like child blood on the black market when when you've got all
those pop up.
Yes.
And you have not renewed Norton antivirus 2005 but it is still prompting you to.
Well look I'm sorry we didn't.
If I'd known I would have gotten her today to be here to be at the fourth microphone.
But unfortunately hey it was still great to talk to.
It's great to you minus.
Glad to be here in her stead.
Well yes so happy you could.
Johnny Pemberton you survived podcast the ride.
Thank you so much for the blast.
Thanks for having me.
Have you.
Thank you.
Let's exit through.
Let's exit through the the the Dragon's Lair.
Is there anything you'd like to plug.
You know I guess I just Google me and whatever you whatever comes up you can engage with
it how you will.
You can choose to listen to my podcast or you can also you can just like look at photos.
Just kind of ugly.
Yeah.
I admire you.
Do that.
I do watch you can purchase films I've done in the past.
Maybe purchase them a couple of times or watch them on direct TV.
I don't know something like that.
Okay.
Do all those things you could find information of when films you've been in will write on
direct TV and on what channel.
I pay the three hundred dollar license for a getty image photo.
Yes that would be great.
Actually I don't think I get any of that but.
Here's one I don't know if this is a purchasable one or if this is just this one's for free.
These are all these are all getting right.
I love looking at my face on this.
This feels so great.
A big TV.
Yes wonderful pixelated.
You know interact with these interact with these photos you know doctor them make them
look like they're from the Renaissance.
Go for it.
Give you funny mustaches and turn them into a shirtless pickle man.
Exactly.
I you know what I think that's in the spirit of the Renaissance where you're essentially
saying like gay cut loose.
You explore my body of work at your own pace.
You're not putting regulations on it.
No regulations.
Yeah.
Unlike these people in the capital.
Okay.
As for us none of that shit we're telling you what to do.
Here's specific instructions.
You can watch this episode on the forever dog YouTube channel.
You could find us on the socials that podcast the right merch is available on our tea public
store.
Thanks to Jordan Katz for producing this episode.
You have to do that to say thank you out loud and Jordan Katz as you're listening to this.
You did a great job.
And for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the right the second gate or you
get one more bonus episode on our new tier club three.
That's all at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
All right.
You do that.
You don't fuck around.
You want to be Willie Millie.
That's for looking up Johnny on Mozilla.
Yeah.
Be Willie Millie.
You got a you got a cooler vibe.
You're looser than us.
I can I say it's the weed thing.
Yeah man.
Yeah.
All right.
We did it.
Next episode.
Chill.
OK.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at
forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.