Club Three.
Welcome to Club Three, Emergency Update Edition.
This is something that my two co-hosts are not aware of.
And I'm not, there's Scott Gardner, Jason Sheridan here,
but you know we're on Club Three.
I wanna give a quick update on the Garfield Eats episode.
Oh, no kidding. Okay.
So something that happened a couple of days ago
that I was involved in that I need to tell everybody about.
And I made a little video to show what happened.
We all remember the character, the main guy, of course,
Nathan Masri. Yeah.
Yeah. He is-
Masri? Masri, yes, Masri.
I've got his name wrong.
I really should know it.
Because- Reversed.
Yes. So he is an eccentric character
that sort of got the rights to Garfield,
but didn't make a Garfield restaurant.
You probably know all this if you're a Club Three listener.
Scooby-Doo after the fact.
After the fact, got a Scooby-Doo restaurant going,
we think. We're not sure.
Maybe- Frozen food.
Frozen food. Maybe I know something about this.
So what happened was a couple of days ago,
I'm taking care of the baby.
Lindsay is napping.
And I see someone has gone live on Instagram.
Someone is doing a live something on Instagram,
and it is Nathan.
Oh. And I go, oh my God.
So I click on it.
He is in a bookstore.
He is signing books.
And he is taking questions.
From Instagram users.
Oh. Oh my God.
Now, at first I go, oh shoot, is he going to see my questions?
I noticed that there are seven people watching this.
So- Twitter likes are always extremely low.
Yeah. So I have a little bit of a cut of this,
because I was on with him for about 40 minutes.
Oh my God.
Now- Oh, I love the surprise in that.
Not as many questions as you would think,
but I've cut it into like a five minute video here,
and we're going to play some of the highlights.
And we can skip through this.
It's not all that interesting,
but I want to set the stage here and I'll show you guys.
He is wearing his Garfield orange jacket,
because he had made like a Garfield clothing line, basically.
Well, this tailored suit, that was the main-
Yes.
His main credibility was owning a suit.
Right. He owned a suit.
And then in the side, like in the jacket inside,
it would say like Garfield or something.
Like he said it's some sort of authentic Garfield merchandise,
basically. That's the way he had presented it.
And he's wearing this and he's in like somewhere in Canada,
in like a Barnes and Noble, and he's got his new book,
and he is sitting there signing copies of it for no one.
Yeah.
He's at a table and he's signing copies of it.
And you'll see, I have a few of these moments left in where
he just like, got to sign more books.
I got more books to sign.
And you're like, do you?
What are you talking about?
Oh, does he frame it to where you could not?
Does he have, does somebody keep putting in like mannequin
hands to simulate?
There's a woman who shows up and I'm not sure if she's a plant or not.
It's possible she's a plant.
Never, what should you say?
What should we say?
Never let anyone suppress you.
OK, so Nathan is signing these books and the thing he keeps saying
is never let anyone suppress you.
This is the, this is the like mission statement of his book or something.
And he kind of just keeps repeating it periodically, which is odd.
But I don't know.
Yeah, it's like a kind of a like,
I don't know how it applies to Garfield necessarily, but he's got a lot of.
Never let anyone suppress you.
Anyone suppress you.
Nathan Masri.
So yeah, Nathan Masri.
And he's showing you the books that he's writing this in.
OK, so he's writing this in many books.
Now, I know authors do sign things and leave books behind.
So it's not unprecedented, but he'll say periodically,
like, I love meeting the fans.
Well, it's going to be some more time for the fans to come out.
So here we go.
Never let anyone suppress you.
George, thank you so much, Mr. Masri in town.
Look up your sons and daughters.
Looked up here like you, you're nasty.
Good luck.
So someone named George has now said, hey, lock up your sons and daughters.
Nathan's in town.
He's very tickled by this.
He's the he like I know that people don't like me and I play into it.
We're going to get there.
We're going to get there with what he thinks about other people,
because there's a lot of information he reveals in this to seven.
Or now it's 10 people, I see.
Thank you, George. Long time.
Hi, how are you?
I'm good. Are you Nathan Masri?
You Nathan Masri?
Plan. Plan.
So this seems like a plant for sure.
Yeah.
Because he talks to a different person later, but I cut it out
because it's clearly just somebody walking by.
They got roped into a conversation with him.
Yes, I did.
Oh my God.
How are you, Nathan?
Do you like YouTube videos?
Oh, yeah.
Don't tell. What's your name?
Strange Aeons.
Yeah, Strange Aeons.
Now they're discussing Strange Aeons,
which is one of the main videos about Garfield Eats,
who is one of the YouTubers who made sort of a comedy.
We watched the video.
We watched her. Yeah.
So he was about to reveal something about this.
He's very aware of this YouTuber.
Of course.
Do you think she hates me?
So he has seen the video.
So this is one of the big questions we were asking about,
like how self where is he?
Does he know this stuff is happening?
And the insecurity, which seems so strong.
And now he's about to reveal something about this YouTuber.
I think it's just everyone wants to.
I love her.
Do you know there's a secret that she doesn't even know?
OK, I don't know if you are you a fan of her?
Of hers? OK, well, she ordered so much from Garfield Eats
that I delivered it myself to her.
She has a big house.
She has a big house in Mississauga.
I think it's her parents.
No, never. She wasn't there.
She was in New York. I think.
I don't know.
So Nathan has revealed that he is the one who went to this person's house.
He also like imagine that that I personally do something involving Garfield Eats,
which I have made everyone believe is a company that 70 people were involved in.
Right. Not one, not just one.
Ramshackle.
One suit owner.
So I may have to cut a little bit because I went back too far.
Terminated and then six feet on the.
What's official?
It's the official.
Oh, take a break.
And then they gave me Scooby Doo.
And I did.
There's an Instagram.
I did frozen burgers for hot dogs.
And it was a little terminated.
Terminated. Oh, interesting.
It's just terminated. That's over.
Yeah, I never saw that line about that.
All right. We had that info.
So that's a good update that Scooby Doo Eats is gone.
It's great.
I want nothing to do with licensing anymore.
And that's what brought me to Iggy's, the app Iggy's that's coming out in six months.
OK, so here's the update. I got this.
There's a new app called Iggy's that is coming out in six months
and it does not have any licensing.
Whoa, great.
I need no further information.
I would like to give Nathan as much money as possible.
Yeah. So Iggy.
So this is the new thing that has to be on our radar is Iggy's.
OK, because he's done with this as far as licensing, although he doesn't say
he's done with Garfield.
Also, you would think he might be done with Garfield.
Incorrect.
All your licensing stuff worldwide, whatever you want on this app,
it's like the Amazon official licensing.
No licensing.
So he keeps he says, OK, sorry to step back.
He says Iggy's is not about licensing,
but it's also the place like Amazon for licensing.
I'm not sure.
It's that it isn't that he didn't have to make a license.
It's a marketplace.
I guess it's a more like license and licensees.
So we should see if we can license some of our original podcast
to write characters to Nathan, maybe.
Oh, yeah. Or other people on Iggy's.
Yes, we could get a deal.
There could people could eat shitty lasagna.
That's sector keepers.
Yes. Right. Yeah.
Or even one of the other sector keepers.
Lil Tillman for Tida.
Yeah.
Lil Tillman.
By the way, I just learned he's from a family of gangsters.
He's like, so a little scared now.
All right. Well, that's fair.
Three generations.
This is buying the paywall.
The paywall protects us from the villains of this world.
OK, so here we go.
There's a lot more news to break.
And come on Iggy's and sell their stuff.
If we don't have, if we don't see a contract with them in Walt Disney
So, yeah, it's exciting.
I'm excited.
He also I think I skipped by this.
He tells her that he's doing the Garfield documentary.
The Garfield.
Netflix. Jim is he says Jim is involved.
And then he says and he said, I'll say this again, Paramount knows about it.
Instead of saying they're making it, he will say Paramount knows about it.
It's like I've let them know I'm doing it.
So anyway, it's a priority with all this shuffling of corporate
mergers and streamers and what do we they're
they're trying to prop up Paramount Plus, but also thinking,
how do we keep Nathan happy?
Yeah, this documentary work.
So I started asking questions and I first make an error.
I call he we've talked about on the episode that he has his own version
of Garfield called Nath Feld.
Oh, yeah. And I accidentally called him Nate Field.
But I asked, when is Nate Field cartoon coming?
And he sees my question and he's going to answer it. Whoa.
Nath and Cartoon coming soon, soon, soon.
I'm raising the funds for Nath Field Animation Series, and I'm not going to quit.
You're going to see the first pilot very soon.
Here we signed the first one.
So that's the update on that.
And he goes right back to the signing books.
If you guess, we're definitely know that's been happening.
Know that for sure. It's not Trump like at all.
Yeah. Don't worry about it.
We're doing that. Of course.
No, I was I knew you're going to ask that. And yes, he didn't ding you
know, forgetting the name wrong.
He did not. Yes, he was.
He was nice, even though I did get the name wrong.
And I apologize.
Your heart was in the right place.
I'm just thinking about Nath Field, which he is.
He lost the Garfield license, but should be fine to make a cartoon
about a half Garfield, half Nathan hybrid.
Well, that's fine.
I think I skipped through the part where he tells the woman
that he doesn't want to just be one and done with Garfield.
He wants to actually go out on a good note with Garfield.
So I think this is all part of it. Yeah. He needs redemption. Yes.
So, OK, so I asked some more questions.
You find this work, this is after he's
he's making a kissy face also.
Cool.
Well, anyone suppress your
Nathan do the reading from the book.
OK, OK, I'll do a reading from the book.
This I did not ask for the reading from the book.
This is someone else.
I was also likely a plant.
He never gets to the reading in the book.
He never does it.
I'll do it. I'll do it just in a bit because there was a window
for fans to come in and followers to come in and customers.
There's a window.
So I'm going to do that and then I'm going to do a read.
Oh, you got to use the window.
Yeah, the window came and went.
Never let anyone suppress you.
The piece of advice, Jim Davis.
So now I have asked him, what is the one piece of advice
Jim Davis gave you that you'll never forget?
Oh, cool. OK.
Gave me. He said, Nathan, take it.
It's time to take care of Nathan and let go the cat.
And when I had Garfield, he said, Nathan,
take care of the cat and the cat will take care of you.
So that was nice.
So he said that apparently he had a conversation
I've been recording him in a conversation where Jim Davis said,
you have to let go of the cat.
That might have been, yeah, but that might have been out loud, said more like
you have to let go of the cat. Right.
It might have been angry. Oh, that's so nice.
No, no, it's not.
OK, so then I ask, does Jim Davis like lasagna?
So that was nice.
Does Jim Davis like lasagna? Yes, he does.
Yeah, he does.
And his wife, Jill, lovely, lovely in Muncie, Indianapolis.
And nothing to do with Garfield.
Jim does still draw the comic comics for Nickelodeon under Paramount.
Now it was called Viacom.
The executive, the documentary Garfield by 2023.
And Jim Davis knows all about it.
Again, another thing where he says, and Jim knows about it.
I'm doing a documentary. Jim knows about it.
It's regular stuff, normal stuff to say. Right.
So he does, yeah, roll again, just rolls through like three talking points.
Yes, Jim likes lasagna.
And it's like and he's set up like, all right, if I'm not talking to you,
then I'm talking to a plant over here.
And if not, I'm talking to an off camera person.
And do we have time for? Yeah, I think we OK.
But this fans in the window. Right, right.
So I then ask him,
would Jim Davis let you dress him in your Garfield suit?
And could you give him a makeover?
You're getting bold.
Would Jim Davis let you dress him in your new Garfield suit?
No shade, but Jim Davis use a fashion upgrade.
I would love to do a makeover on Jim.
No shade, but oh, my God.
So, yeah, he would love to. That's the answer.
He said love. Oh, but he liked the question.
So then I ask or then I say,
I think you should run for president and Jim Davis should be VP.
And he's not alarmed.
This is all coming from one. Of course, this is how he does.
Everyone is to me.
You'll see he makes a little he's a little he's wondering why there's a lot of this.
OK, so another batch to sign.
I think you should run for president and should be VP.
Imagine Jim Davis.
And I know that Mary Lynn and my oh, the problem is Jim, not.
Yeah. Imagine Jim Davis.
Uh huh. We can.
Of course, we can readily imagine what Nathan.
What citizen is he?
What country is he a citizen of Canada?
I don't know. It's a good question.
I guess Canada. Maybe.
Uh, there's also a part where I cut out where he was talking about running.
He doesn't want to get into politics because, you know,
he wants to actually do real change like Oprah doesn't want to sit in chairs
like Oprah, like hot Oprah, right in his book. Right.
So, OK, I forget what I asked next.
I asked something, though.
Oh, that Mary Lynn and my always were.
Now I'm just focused on Iggy's, you know.
OK, so I say here I say, what do you think of Heathcliff?
Oh, interesting.
And Iggy's, that's all I'm doing. Iggy's, Iggy's, Iggy's.
Go follow Iggy's app, you guys will follow Iggy's app.
I contacted Heathcliff.
They never they never responded.
You're so hot. Thank you.
You're so I did not say you're so hot.
I don't need proof of that.
You know, that's the whole thing.
So I asked about Heathcliff and he tried to get Heathcliff.
This is that feels so shitty to me.
That's like you view like you just you put like that.
That's, you know, how we if you make an offer to an actor for something,
they're not supposed to know that they were the runner up.
Or you're not supposed to know who else was in consideration.
That sucks. That's I love Jim and his advice. Right.
And then look how he's he would shank him in a second for Heathcliff.
He can make some Heathcliff lasagna.
I'll switch to ham.
I'll throw the lasagna pans in the trash.
So these are these are big breaking stories.
So in a lab, boy.
Yeah, there's only a little bit left, a little bit left here.
And I forget what's next.
This and you guys asked me a lot of awfully a lot about Jim Davis.
Oh, he's now noticed
that my questions have turned exclusively to Jim Davis.
Nathan time, not Jim time.
But I do have time for one more question, because I was at this point,
I was like gearing up for another 30 minutes.
Yeah, because I thought I was all you know, the nonsense.
And I go, OK, we're really going to hit it hard.
And I got time for I think one more question here.
And you're doing this one hand while holding a baby.
Yes, I have the baby on my lap.
I'm one handed trying to calm the baby from crying.
I have this in my ear.
I'm recording the screen.
It's glitching out sometimes.
So I had to restart the video.
So I had to put two couple of videos together and I had to cut out
some like dead space.
You're taking Kate, you're soothing the baby and you're soothing
the club three members. Yes, exactly.
I asked the questions I asked that he did not respond to.
Like, do you think Jim Davis has a dark side?
He did not respond to that.
And I think there was one other one that he didn't.
I can't remember what it was. Oh, he hit me.
He hit me a number of times.
But he had but I learned from them.
Oh, I think there's a good maybe there's a good thing coming up here
unless I skipped it.
Jim Davis is good.
He wants to he wants to rest.
He's much, much, much older.
Yeah, Jeff Davis is old and wants to rest.
That's what he says to me.
He also says and I think I accidentally skipped through it here
and unless it's about to happen right now,
he says something along the lines of Jim Davis should have left Garfield to me.
I should have been the protege, he says. Jesus.
Yeah, he says a very dark thing there.
But did not elaborate, like elaborate, like I want to draw it or I wanted to.
He's trying to black widow. Yes. Yes.
Yes, he left everything to me because we were such close friends.
Right, right.
So I have time for one more here.
He should have given me
I should have been the next
part of J.R. Garfield, sadly.
I should have the next protege of Garfield, sadly.
Did I say in the episode that there was in one of those interviews with him,
one of the food and wine or something, I don't remember, but that he
responding to no questions said, where will I be in five years producing,
producing the next Garfield movie with Viacom perhaps?
He just would know with no prompting.
He thought he was going to turn the that he makes like he that he sells
eight lasagnas a day, maybe on a good day to into he's Garfield's film producer.
Well, he had he had the blessing of Jim Davis, who does like lasagna.
OK, so here we go. Here's the last question.
And I ask, will the Natfield cartoon be all ages for all ages?
Whoa.
Yes. No, no, no, it won't be appropriate for all ages.
And that was it.
I don't like that laugh.
So Natfield is going to be R rated, I think it's going to be a dirty cartoon.
It's going to be a sausage party.
So characters who cuss now, Harley Quinn, Velma, Natfield.
Yeah. So you got it wrong again.
It's Natfield.
Natfield, Natfield.
I can understand the confusion.
It's OK. So it's Nathan.
Natfield.
I got his last name wrong, too.
But then Nathan. Yeah, I was like, OK, wait, maz.
But Nathan is just Nathan.
So there should be Nathan Field.
Oh, I thought it was Nate Field.
Yeah, that's better because Nate is like Nathan.
Nath, but it's Nath Field.
Nath Field, I think. I think so.
Nath like math. That's the update on things.
What do we think R rated Nath Field is all about?
I think we have to reckon with this.
That's a good question.
Does he?
Does Nath Field stick his dick in the lasagna?
You know, I think that's too body for Nathan, but I could be wrong.
I think it's going to be like
I think it's going to be like Nath Field looks in and like there's a cat
changing or something like he's like at a pool and it's the glasses down
because there's a sexy lady cat.
Yeah, that's what I think.
That's my instinct.
But I could be wrong. You know, you're right.
You might have sex with a lasagna.
You know how sometimes Garfield would get in his little box
and put his blanket on?
I do know that just his head would be sticking out.
But sometimes he'd put it all the way over.
So he was all the way over under the blanket.
If it starts rocking when that happens,
like the box starts shaking a little or maybe as company under there.
OK, like a little mouse.
Mousefield, yeah, his name.
This is a good audition friend with benefit.
It's kind of f buddy, you know.
Hey, I think we're all we'll all take a job in the writers room.
I mean, I think a lot of it is so if we have it's a look at the WGA,
I'm I'm in WGA is trying to unionize Nath Field.
Yeah, it's like I don't want to be good news.
Everyone we got an F.
I mean, I'll take animation guild if that's the guild.
That's that's what it's covered under.
But well, yeah, it's going to be I think I think it's going to be covered by the
the the the Nathers Guild.
OK, that sounds seems respectful.
I don't know what that word means, but I'm sure I can trust this.
The Mounties might shut this down
just in their traditional red garb with the big hats and they're like
kicking in doors.
Yeah.
But like the in the Untouchables, where they do a bust at the border
and the mountains go to just them kicking down doors, riding horses.
You know, on the up and up, a
yeah, they enforce union stuff in Canada.
The Mounties. What's all this about?
We've already shut down the Iggy app.
We're shutting you down now.
Followed the paper trail.
Iggy's gets going to be based out of the Cayman Islands.
Yeah. Right. And there's a big paper trail because you're doing animation.
So there's one cell and then another cell slightly different and then another
lift all the papers trailing through the forest from here to South.
We only get the Mounties down here to take care of the disputes
with the unions and the studios.
No, you and fuck with. Yeah.
Fuck with the mountain. No.
Well, let's let's get in there.
We should volunteer our own, you know, because we're going to want to
put our stamp in there.
And as we if the point of the show is combining your our names,
us very famous people, just like Nathan Bezri with the equally iconic,
maybe a little less iconic Garfield characters.
I would love to get in there as Scotty.
I'll be Scotty. That's good. Scotty's good.
I don't leave a lot left by taking Odie, but if you guys seem to know the extended.
Yeah, we just know Arlene.
We know Arlene and normal Arlene and normal.
So you can be normal, German, Jason, like John, like
Stratley and John isn't claimed. Yeah.
What's the U.S. Acres characters?
I don't I don't know.
But I got distracted by Jace, Jace on Sharp.
That's good. Yeah. Mm hmm.
Well, I guess you want to be the duck, the duck.
Yeah. Oh, the egg and the egg. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. I'll be the egg.
Great. Meg. Meg.