Forever.
Dog.
Record, it's Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about rides, except sometimes it's not, and also
it's often just speculation about rides that we haven't been on because we're too scared.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Yes, I am here and I am scared still to this day as I enter my late 30s.
Well, I've been in my late 30s for a little while.
But yes, you know what's funny?
You remind me now, I looked at some of our reviews on whatever Apple podcasts because
I haven't done that in a while.
And there are, they're so nice people, are so nice five, oh, this is wonderful.
We love the good boys, whatever.
But then you get like two stars.
What is this?
This isn't about rides.
These guys just go, it's 10 minutes of tangents.
What are they going to get to the topic?
And I go, oh, I guess we have to allow for that part to get figured out.
Yeah, just there.
They might not even dislike it.
They're just processing what all the listeners deal with at some point.
I'm not even mad at them.
I'm not like they're not mean.
It's not like they wouldn't be on like a Jimmy Kimmel mean social media bit or something.
They're just confused.
And I understand it.
I get it.
It's an adjustment that you have to make.
Look, in this case, look, we are talking about a ride and Jason Sheridan hasn't been on the ride.
But I feel like you might you might go on this ride today.
Yeah, I would say this definitely a ride.
And one I would consider.
Consider at least consider at least once I got over the hurdle, not a fear of being like however high you are in the air, but the fear of the dreaded add on the dreaded charge.
The price that we get you.
Yes.
Jason's biggest fear.
Could you scale it?
But now I can chalk it up to research when I was like 18 or 19.
You couldn't write off your theme park add on or your tourist site, your gorge add on.
Yeah, in theory.
Sometimes this ride appears at gorges.
This is an attraction that is everywhere.
Maybe you don't know the name Skycoaster offhand, but they exist all over the place.
It's in every continent except Antarctica, which Antarctica.
Why are you sleeping on it?
Get a sky coaster going.
It's a big like harness and cable based attraction that is an add on many theme parks everywhere.
And we're going to delve into it with somebody who's done it.
And if you are a fan of today's guest and you're looking at this and thinking this is a long overdue guest, you don't know the half of it.
The birthday boys from the sloppy boys.
Mike Hanford.
Hey, hello.
Hello.
Thank you for having me yet again.
Does the audience know what happened last time?
They don't know.
I have maybe have like alluded to it, but I don't think they know the full.
Yeah, we haven't explained it.
We had a wonderful conversation, a long two hour conversation.
It was great.
People were being informative, funny stories were being told.
Particularly good.
I think I'm not patting myself on the back.
You were great.
Of course.
I mean, like, oh, I hope I have something to say.
I don't know much about rides.
These guys are the experts and we had a great we had a great conversation.
We did all about sky coasters.
It was sky coasters.
And then it fell into the pit.
It became the very first podcast, the ride that was ever completely lost.
The only one aside from we lost a city walk saga, but then we just re recorded it.
This is this one, you know, in a much broader sense, just disappeared.
Mike, I feel like you have to my Carlson.
I think you have to go back into your stress of that because you had to deal with it first and most.
Yeah. So we were using a little zoom recorder and it was a hot day.
We hadn't figured everything out maybe about how we were recording outside.
We were just to do it in person.
And it was last year.
I don't know Los Angeles.
I mean, probably everywhere.
But lately, Los Angeles has gotten so morbidly hot.
Yeah. August and September.
So it was a nice like backyard chat, which I like to do that was over a year ago.
Yeah.
You know, we were all having fun.
It was hot facts.
Summer. Everyone was acting like, you know, just living life to the fullest.
What summer? Hot Vax.
So hot. Oh, that's right.
Yeah. Oh, yes.
When the Vax came and changed everything.
Gum companies were doing ads saying like, go out and kiss strangers after you're vaccinated.
As long as you chew Trident gum.
We have the vaccine in the gum now.
Yeah, we have the vaccine in the gum.
Trust us.
Only us.
Yeah, I do look at my Vax card and it's like, you know, they got the date and it says Trident next to it.
Yeah. Poverty, Procter & Gamble. Yeah.
So we were in the heat and I noticed it like toward the end of recording that I was like, oh, this should be like in direct sun light.
That's not good.
So I didn't cover it, but I think it was too late.
Yeah. Because then I was went to stop it and do everything.
And then it like it was loading forever.
Then it shut down.
It was the dreaded like we were done and then it was like, oh, great.
Thanks. Thanks for having me.
And then like you were like, hold on.
Yeah. In a tone that just meant.
I'm reliving it now and I feel the stress coming back.
It's like the muscle memory of the stress.
I'm sorry.
I feel like you had to, unfortunately.
Well, yeah, I am the one who hits record.
I have to pay attention to it when we're not doing it in the studio.
I know how you feel.
It's not your fault at all, but I know you just because you were the closest to hit the record button.
It's on you. You feel what it's not.
It is. Well, it is.
It's like in Apollo 13 doesn't one of them feel maybe Kevin Bacon feels the guilt the most.
Yeah. What happened to you is that he pressed the buttons.
Yeah. You're Kevin Bacon and I'm Kevin or whatever the real astronauts name was.
Yeah. Well, we don't know that.
We just know Kevin Bacon.
We don't know that's been lost.
There's no way to look that up.
So Jonathan space, probably.
Yeah, yeah, probably.
I think what we learned was that like the Zoom recorders are pretty rugged in terms of hot and cold, but the direct sunlight will just destroy them.
Because as that was happening, my phone was also like a Brit.
My phone did that Apple overheat thing.
And I went, that's weird.
Those screens. Yeah, those.
Yeah. Yeah.
Crazy.
So but anyway, you could have been nicer about it, which is great because look, it's oh, that's that's great.
I'm glad the time was valuable because you're doing it again.
I'm not convinced this is being recorded.
We had an issue with I can't hear anything.
My headphones. If you're watching the video, I'm not wearing these.
I was wearing some of us or not.
There will at least be video recorded.
I think we'll be able to dub it over.
For some reason, the audio isn't working.
Now we have to bring you in and make you dub over because we have videos.
You can just go.
You've done 80 hours.
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
So just watch your mouth for the next 90 minutes.
Remember all your time.
I don't memorize what I say.
Let's all do that.
So you do get the superlative of being on the podcast.
The ride lost episode.
But you might also be our cooler.
You know, the guy that you know, said to like, he's on a run.
Send him next to it.
That is William H.
Macy.
There was also then because then I saw you the next day or so because you
organized a bar hang and it was that I gave you the official verdict.
Are you so are you sure?
I'm sorry.
I tried.
I tried to retrieve it.
I was online.
Yeah, you had like little hack notions.
Yeah, you told you told me and I instantly said two shots of anything you got
behind the bar.
We need to erase this from our memories right now.
That's right.
That's the spirit.
But then that was at eventual podcast, the right topic.
Tam O'Shanter with the guest for that episode, Tim Calpacus, who the next
morning we all got texts from saying I have covid and we may have everyone may
have and you two didn't feel well because you both did shots of creme de
mince.
Yeah.
Mike Woodard from behind the bar.
He said anything.
Anything.
Whatever is closest.
The nearest bottle.
The durian blue chorus out, please.
My favorites.
But then anyway, you immediately said let's do it again.
I said, oh, yeah, maybe we could talk about something different.
And you said, no, we're doing skycoaster.
The only thing I know.
No, because it did.
It was when you asked me to do the show, I was like, oh, what would be a ride?
I know specifically.
And this kind of was the only one I could think of that was like I've been on it.
I because I've been on roller coaster before.
I don't remember the loops and the twists.
I don't remember any of it gets very to we don't talk about a lot of roller
coasters.
Sure.
I get into like, well, and then the G's and the like, it's sort of becomes very
dry and factual.
I got a funny roller coaster story.
I'll tell you as we get into it.
Oh, great.
Since the last recording.
Oh, I was wondering, yeah, if anything had transpired related to our show in
last year.
But skycoast, you're you're committed to skycoasters, although in the
intervening time, I think we all forgot what these were called.
Yeah.
Yes.
You texted and said, are we still doing the giant swing?
And I didn't know either.
Those things could be named that on the, you know, some signage.
It could be called giant swing.
I think that's it might be a more accurate title because skycoaster the listener,
if you haven't seen one of these, you might not be picturing what we're talking
about because coasters, the biggest keyword when you think coasters track, I
would say.
And there's wheel on track.
Right.
And we also do.
Yes.
What the word coaster translates from.
Yeah.
It's from the Latin origin.
Yes.
But it's not it is just it is like a it's adjacent to bungee bungee jump.
Jumping bungee.
Dives swing.
I mean, you see there's bungee swings.
Yeah.
But then it's not bungee because it was invented to be a better bungee.
They were trying to read the bungee.
And something that's more of a free fall.
Yeah.
Well, without the snap back, because that seems like the unappealing part of no one
here has done a bungee dive.
I'm afraid of I'll be honest.
I'm afraid.
Seems like if it's it just seems like a apparatus or an event that will happen
sort of off grid, if that makes sense.
So I just safety protocols are there.
Yeah, it feels like it.
Because like at Disney, for the most part, you know, you they've gone through sort
of you assume safety checks every morning.
In fact, yes, there's too much money to be lost at Disneyland.
But the thing like the ones who you seem like on a bridge.
Yeah. Is that permanent?
I don't know. Right.
Are they just tying it up there?
Like that seems like the MTV sports version when people like do their own like this is
I have my own bungee equipment.
I do this.
And then we opened up as stands or like then it felt like who's checking this stuff.
Who's regulating?
We get five bungee deaths since 2015.
That's not in America.
But deaths are better.
Death is death.
Death is not.
I think we all agree.
Death is bad.
Is that can I read the summary of like what the creators I just think this is so odd what
the creators had in mind.
Yes.
They invented this.
Mm hmm.
They wanted to find a way to let others experience the thrill of jumping out of a plane or the
thrills of bungee jumping but with the safety factor of a merry-go-round.
How do you get to that point?
How do you get to the point where you're like so this and this but then it's as safe as
getting on a little carousel.
I think yeah that seems tough to do but it seems like I think they were kind of after
what we're talking about where if you're worried about like this bungee jump operation seems
like two guys who have a bridge that nobody's told them to leave.
Right.
Could we get it seems like almost what they wanted more was like theme park infrastructure
and safety and also that this could be kind of like rubber stamps in a lot of different
theme parks.
Which it is in like a lot of big ones and six flags and you know the chains.
And it's so easy it's just like an arch or two sticks and put a swing between them.
Yeah pretty much yeah it's like a there's like a there's kind of like a loop or an A
frame.
Yeah.
And there's another big stick that you are pull that's the technical term and it's you
are pulled back by that one and then released.
Is that right.
Yeah.
And I think you pull it yourself.
The one I did.
I yeah I forgot.
So I've talked about this.
I did it in I think sixth or seventh grade.
We did like a school trip the end of the year and we had to borrow money from a cool teacher
who there were like three of us who wanted to do it.
We're like oh well we don't have any money.
And our cool teacher was like I'll pay for you guys if you pay me back tomorrow.
Done.
Money exchange with the teachers.
Wow that is weird.
It felt like this is not your what you need to do for us right now.
But we did it and you go up.
We were in threes.
You could do it probably these days.
They probably have them as much as six or seven.
That seems like a bad idea.
Six or seven people can be up on that thing.
But it's like a bit is like kind of a like a sack almost.
Yeah.
You get in this blanket.
You lay face down.
I think we put these like you know when you go to the dentist and you put it they put that like they do x-rays they put sort of a smock.
A lead vest.
Do you like that as a nap fan or is that like oh it's a little relaxing.
I do find it a little comforting.
I mean weighted blankets are very popular.
I don't think I would like that much weight on me when I slept all night.
But you do like wearing a lead vest.
I kind of like I've never liked going to the dentist.
I really didn't like it when I was young.
So like having a little comfort having a little you know safety blanket.
Well I don't like it because I mean that means they're giving me the x-rays and they're putting a plastic in my mouth and I'm a gagger.
Me too.
And it's got to be just so they keep like moving around.
And you got to make sure breathing your nose and like I'm just like this I'm like it's like clockwork orange for like 10 minutes and I'm like that's the way to do it.
It always goes through my mind too.
It's like we got this laser shooting right in my head and we're just covering my body with the lead.
Yeah they're shooting your brain.
I need a lead helmet.
Oh that'd be cool too if they gave you some big like you know.
Tron helmet.
Yeah yeah or honey I shrunk the kids.
Oh yeah yeah sure.
Or more of a because it's just your mouth so it's just it should be more of like a Roman helmet.
Yeah.
That kind of goes like Magneto's helmet.
Yeah yeah yeah.
With like a little cut out here maybe.
With the little nose ridge I like that on a helmet.
Yeah yeah yeah.
When it would be at a super villain or a soldier.
It's funny to think of a Roman soldier with that little nose piece.
Yeah.
Those things aren't held on their head so tightly that like if you get hit in the nose that whole thing the whole helmet is going to pop off and.
The arrows is getting hit.
Or spin around.
Yeah that's the worst thing.
Oh right and then it's jutting into your back.
Yeah.
Look there's a reason the empire collapsed okay.
They paid too much attention to ornamental nose pieces.
Yeah.
Nose ridges.
Wait where were we?
Oh the blanket the heavy blanket.
Oh yeah so they kind of put you in this smock thing if I remember correctly.
And then the three of you three of us got into this like other harness thing that went in front of us.
They sort of lay you down on your you're looking at your facing down and they pull you up and then one of us had to pull the string.
Pull the rip cord and then we away we go.
And I think they counted it off like from a megaphone.
Here we go one two three.
I the making you do it I hate.
Oh my god.
This is an element that I don't skydiving the jumping off the stratosphere in Vegas.
They make you jump and I don't like a ride that forces me to start it.
Right right right.
Because there I can't do it.
Even like rides I like I bet I wouldn't be able to.
Yes I know what you mean.
Pull a big lever.
If like the times I've jumped off of like a high dive or a high cliff into a lake or something.
It is always that like okay I'm going to go.
Yeah I mean count from down from 10.
After 10 I'm now going to count up to three and I will do it on three.
I promise you all.
Yeah I can't.
I can't do it.
This might be a weird thing to equate it to but now that you and I have both had children doesn't it feel like the ultimate.
Like we have to pull the rip cord and I feel like the way both of us do it was like we still didn't quite do it.
It was kind of like to do what we'll see.
We'll see.
They have kids.
Yeah to decide to do it.
It still felt like not a full pull of the ribcage.
Like I don't know maybe it'll happen.
I don't know.
Let's not think about it.
Well you want it to be.
Maybe it won't.
It probably won't actually won't and then we want to.
Well we.
I mean this is too intimate.
I mean it happens real quick for us.
We were very lucky.
But yes I don't think that's too intimate.
Well to me.
I'm covering up.
This is so personal.
I just don't want to reveal so much about myself.
But but yeah well to some degree it's such a big deal.
I mean I have said before I almost wish like we just like during the pandemic especially I was like I wish we just had the kid already.
Like I wish it had just happened somehow.
So there are big life choices where you're like OK this is going to be intense but we got to do it.
Could somebody else just do it for me.
Yes.
Could somebody else just decide.
This happens all the time.
That's kind of what happens.
You let.
We let God decide.
Whatever you want to define the ultimate decider.
This is the best we can do because we're too afraid to go on this thing and pull a rip cord.
Well metaphorically we've still not pulled rip.
I want to go back and talk about the rip cord.
But after talking about having children it seems silly.
Here's one more thing about the piece of nylon you actually do have to know.
Mike's under a lot of stress at this moment with sleep.
This is what he needs is to think about something else.
Yes.
Sixth grade ijinks.
Week five.
We're in the shit.
Oh you're very.
Yeah.
You look great.
Thank you.
You get to sleep.
You could never tell.
Thank you.
So going back to the rip cord.
Somebody has to pull it and it's one of those things.
You know we were like little seventh eighth graders so we didn't have the big muscle man muscles we have now.
So it's inevitably it's that thing where someone like pulls it a couple of times and you're like is that it is that it.
And then it gets you on one you don't even think is coming because like they pull it three times it doesn't work.
And then they give a one real big pull and then you go down.
So you don't even really get to like savor the moment.
You're kind of like when's it going to happen.
Oh yeah.
Oh gee.
It happened.
It just suddenly.
Yeah.
That feels to me like the the vests because there's a cord that you're pulling on the airplane vests.
If there was an emergency.
Right.
And I've always been so sure I would not get it.
Like it sounds simple.
Yeah.
They probably make it simple but aren't you like positive that you would fuck it up.
You're here.
You're grabbing the seat cushion before you even try.
I think so.
Just to be sure.
I'm getting my phone and my iPad and get that above water.
Putting my hands up.
I haven't listened to the the like safety warnings on a plane in years because you know what's going on.
And if something did happen I'm like fuck I what are we doing.
I haven't been listening to this in a long time.
I've updated on this.
I've forgotten everything.
It's also crisis wise.
I just don't know how I'll perform.
I don't really know.
I've been in like a minor you know minor crises where I'm late to record a podcast.
But.
I thought I did something wrong today because I pulled up and you were both standing outside.
I was like oh what the fuck did I do now.
We were mad.
Am I going to get yelled at.
I've only been awake for an hour and 15 minutes.
I couldn't have done anything yet.
Oh I definitely was like getting ready at nine today.
I was like is it 10 we're doing this or was it nine.
Nine nine's too early to rip core.
It's really get caffeine get the juices flowing before you talk.
Well so then so the rip cord is pulled then you're then you're swinging then you're free falling.
How was the experience you're doing the old Tom Petty plunge as they call it.
You go down you swing and then you swing way out above the whole theme park and every were you also.
Darien Lake Darien right outside of your buffalo.
OK.
And they've one of the funniest lines I've ever heard in my life happened there.
I'll tell you about that in a second.
We flew you fly way out over the park.
You kind of maybe wave to people so people are looking up at you and you go back and forth a few times and then you're done.
And it's not that exciting.
It's not.
It doesn't make a mark on your life really.
Other than.
Hey I can talk about this on a podcast one day.
What's a podcast.
I remember last time that towards the end I was trying to do some like like so what's for the listeners would you recommend the sky coaster expand you.
You did say no.
I think there's a skipper wall.
You get your thrills in other places.
But the also during like they had the Superman ride of steel which was kind of new at the time.
This was a six flags also yes.
Yes.
Then became a six flags but they had the predator was a cool roller coaster wooden roller coaster anyway.
When it became a six flags we went back.
So this was after eighth grade.
There was Superman I see it goes.
I don't know if there's different versions of it but it's one of those ones that like it ends when it ends it's just like the cars come in really fast.
It's like stop right there.
Yeah.
And we were waiting in line.
We were the next right up.
The thing comes back in and this guy was in his seat who didn't really enjoy the ride and was like get me off this ride.
Not now right now.
That is that is lived in my brain rent free as they say for many years.
The difference between now and right now is not enough right now.
But I got it.
He was a big guy.
Just funny to think of like his kids were around him and just like we had fun.
Give me off this thing.
Wow.
That six six flags for some reason you will hear more memorable quotes from strangers I feel like than any other theme park.
Because like when we geo and I went to fright fest it was like there's like 10 quotes of like random like when like when we heard the dad go watch your brother I got to go take a shit.
Which I might not have exactly right.
But that's the gist of it.
Everyone kind of cuts loose at a theme park and you even your language gets a little loose.
But see a six flags everyone's comfortable.
They're not.
Yes.
So uptight and black tie affair.
You know I have to use the lavatory watch your your my son and my daughter of which you both know each other.
Six Flags you know you could have a beer and a little pen and really cut loose.
That's what I wanted to do.
I went to a six flags not right after we recorded the episode last year and they I didn't know Magic Mountain had a sky coaster.
Oh and I took a picture of myself very sad and mournful in front of the sky coaster due to the incident.
But I didn't get I didn't want to wait in that beer pen.
Did you line how much was the sky coaster.
Do you remember.
I don't think I got close enough to see.
OK.
We sloppy boys were just on tour and we went past the on the five past the Magic Mountain.
And I was like oh we should do this for an episode like go there and basically what you guys do.
But I looked up tickets they're like eighty six bucks.
I was like that's crazy off off season like Magic Mountain.
Well I don't know maybe I just don't know prices.
Prices.
You need to get the annual pass is like ninety five dollars.
Yeah.
And it pays for itself in one.
It's like it doesn't make sense to go once.
Yeah.
You have to go five times.
But then I did that and then I was like oh maybe the annual pass will make sense.
I thought that before I went in and then after spending two hours there I was like I would do not want to be back here.
There's also so many I feel like deals are much easier to get for six flags than.
Yeah.
Pepsi.
In the car like scrounged around in the trunk.
I bet you could sneak in.
I bet it's not that hard.
Yeah.
It is just kind of like at least that one's just sort of like against the hills.
I don't think anybody's.
Yeah.
And you can jump fence.
Did I talk in that six weeks episode about the flume ride that I went on one of the only
things I did that were that had like a kind of like a wheel that was powering the ride
that where they just slathered on a bunch of tar and I could have so easily stuck my
hand in that tar and just had my hand.
There's no barricade or a sign telling you not to.
It's just my strongest memory of the day.
Like it was like a cake frosting.
That's why you go to six flags for that for those memories.
Yes.
For the tar for the dad yelling at his kid for.
Yeah.
That and you go by the midway and you see every like booth has a hose and they're just
cleaning the walkways with hoses and it's like why are you just doing this.
There's no one here.
Surely a broom could do the same thing and not waste water in this barren Valencia.
Especially there.
Yeah.
Such a dream.
So well so you was like fine but then not.
Did you feel like you wasted the teachers money.
No because it was fun at the time but just looking back at it like if I saw one now it
would be like oh yeah I got you a thrill.
It's a quick ride.
That's the thing.
It's very quick.
It's like a roller coaster is longer.
Yeah.
So it's like yeah like once you do it it has to last like what under a minute.
Yeah because it's the initial drop and then a few swings.
It's not a lot of like swinging back and forth especially if you're a light little kid.
It's very short.
You just kind of like whee and you flip.
Just sort of go back down like a leaf.
You're on your belly which I don't like.
This is another thing I don't like.
I haven't done the Superman coaster or what's the other one?
Tatsu.
This is a thing I maybe will conquer one day but I am afraid.
This is left on your fear list.
I'm afraid to be on my belly.
It's like you know we're doing for the baby what they call it tummy time.
You put the baby on to get the baby to get its head up and I hate tummy time for me.
For yourself.
Or on the coaster.
Whatever.
You like it I know.
Yeah I'm like very.
You're a pro.
You're a belly boy.
I'm a belly boy.
Well I can't fall asleep on my stomach but as I'm trying to fall asleep I'll do it for
a minute or two and then I'll wake up.
Yeah I like sleeping on my stomach.
Don't get me wrong.
I like sleeping on my stomach but I can't convince myself to fall asleep on my stomach.
I can convince myself to fall asleep on my stomach.
Yeah.
It's not a good thing for my neck maybe but yeah I know it makes me uncomfortable.
The legs dangling makes me uncomfortable.
Belly time on a roller coaster makes me uncomfortable.
Do you share any of this?
Do you understand any of this or these particular or would you just kind of go on whatever?
I've been on Tatsu I think.
Yeah.
That was fun.
It's like when will this thing just open up and we fall into the little forest down there.
If they would give me like a little extra something to hold onto like a little like a
train like that loop on a train that I could hold onto or something like just in case.
Yes.
Even just because I have to put my tension somewhere.
I have to like grind into at least little handles or something.
If it was like or I got like a parachute.
Yeah.
In case it opened up then I can just parachute safely down.
Like something.
I don't think I have a proclivity one way or the other.
I can ride them all but I just haven't ridden a roller coaster a long time.
Actually no.
Remember earlier I said I was going to tell you.
Oh yes.
What's this?
At Coney Island this summer I was there with Jace and I'm sorry Nick Cirelli in New York.
Oh yes.
We did it.
Nick and I did a 10K down there on the boardwalk and then ran a little 10K race and then we're
there for the afternoon.
You're good.
And it's so funny those coasters down there they had a brand new one called the Phoenix
and it's one of these ones where you're sitting but your legs are dangling.
Yeah.
And the thing comes down around your chest and you can hold on to the two grips in front
of you but it's so short.
It was like you go up.
I was like I think there's a loop in this one and it's really just like looks like a loop
but you're just kind of going sideways.
This whole ride was probably 25 seconds.
Yeah.
But the thing that I love the best was we got on and I was wearing Crocs and I didn't
have the back strap done and I was wearing sunglasses and the guy came up who would check
our seats and he's like hey take your sunglasses off.
I said okay.
And he's like and just switch your Crocs into sport mode.
I was like what's that?
He's like put the loop around the ankle or the heel.
I was like oh sport mode right if you want to get into some sporting stuff.
That's a phrase.
That's correct.
And then this other guy the other guy came around he's like it's not that rough.
You'll be fine.
Sport mode not needed.
Is that a popularized?
Yeah really.
What is the sport mode on Crocs?
Sport mode is the heel strap is locked in.
When you actually put the strap around your ankle rather than wear them like a pair of
clogs is this weird official Crocs website.
Yeah I haven't thought of Crocs as being plastic clogs but that's what they are.
That's all they are.
It is funny because like you could I could see where a lot of things like it's easy to
things have flying off of you on some of these coasters.
Yeah.
Like Jason I did hang time and I think I said this already once hang time is it not.
It's someone that goes straight vertical.
Well first which scares the shit out of me and I'm like clinging to the thing in front
of me.
Well when we're doing it I stupidly had my phone on me.
They tell you to leave your phone.
But I remember going oh how does this not happen all the time.
Oh my God there must be underneath that roller coaster that spot there just must be like
every night money and phones while I'm going vertical I move my phone to like my butt
pocket.
Yeah.
And I'm sitting on it at an angle so I'm already terrified of the 90 degree or whatever it
is.
Yeah.
And then you're uncomfortable.
I know that feeling you're like I put it in my pocket and like try to get my pants as
tight as possible there so it like sticks the.
Yeah and I was at least wearing jeans at the time.
Now I'm wearing these what are they called joggers and things fly out of them all the
time.
Sure.
So I get why he would say like those Crocs are going to fly off.
Put them in sport mode.
I understand it.
I do appreciate when you're on a ride and the seat back in front of you has like a netting
that you can like lock in.
Yeah.
Yes.
Velcro netting.
Yeah.
It feels like it shouldn't work like something will shake it loose.
None of us were strong.
I when I was back in Jersey I went on that gill for surriller coaster that I talked about
on the hometown parks episode.
And I gave my mom like my glass and hat to hold and she's like oh you don't want to take
your phone.
I was like no I want to take a picture in the law and I was fine.
I pants are really tight and you did.
My pants are tight.
I was tight.
Yeah.
And then I get out to the line and there's be there.
There's like bins on this cart with wheels on it and they're like empty your pockets
and I see you have to empty your pockets in this bin and then someone is wanting you like
metal detector one there.
I was like there was like eight people loading this ride.
I was like this is the most efficient thing and I was like I just have a phone and he's
like oh just put it in there.
We wheel that on like next to the car.
Yeah.
But he's like no we wheel it and then it's next to the car.
No they wheel it like you go past like a turnstile and he's like yeah we wheel it around to that
and no one gets to those besides the people in the car.
So I was like OK.
That is surprisingly like you guys have your shit together more than some bigger parks.
Is it just so like they're wanting you for you know a set of keys so they don't fly out
and well so they don't fly out.
Yeah for sure.
And they don't hit someone or they don't get lost.
But then it was like a lot of like back and forth and vertical cord screws and yeah I
probably would have lost everything.
I would have been broken man.
He keeps his life savings on him at all times.
Yeah.
When they luge you off they're like did you lose it.
And I'm like yeah.
They're like all right the barrels with straps on them are right there.
Put it on brother.
There should be an arm rest like storage on coasters.
Yeah that's a good idea.
Like in a car.
That would be good.
Just put them in there and close it.
You ever been on a jet ski before?
No.
Too scared.
They have little two or three times I've been on they have a little pot you know compartments
you put your phones and stuff in and then it's supposedly waterproof.
But I'm like I don't know who owns this jet ski.
Is this waterproof?
I don't want water on any of my stuff.
Did you try it?
I did because I'm not going to leave it at the jet ski place.
So you rented a jet ski and then it's just it's like it's exactly like in a car.
Yeah it's like between your legs.
Right in front of you.
Yeah.
Okay.
And I'd recommend especially if you're in the right area.
I was down in where was I Sarasota Florida.
My parents had a vacation place there.
I went down to visit them.
Oh cool.
And boy we the three of us were on two jet skis and at first dad was like okay just one
jet ski.
Like we're getting two jet skis and the three of us are not going to be on a jet ski together.
That's an odd mom dad son.
And I'm not sharing with anyone.
I am getting the lone jet ski.
It's like a jet ski built for three like three different handles.
The family that is excited about that possibility.
Yeah.
Real time together.
All of us in tandem.
Well that kind of goes back to when you asked me if I had a picture of me on the swing.
Oh yeah.
On the skyrocket.
I forgot it was that long ago.
Like of course you know I didn't know.
I forgot it was less fine.
Yeah.
Well when you asked me I was like no no I don't I don't get pictures on roller coasters that
was like Hanford.
Like no way we're spending extra money to get a picture of us on the thing we were just
on.
Sure.
So just the same thing with the jet ski.
It's like oh yeah all three of us in one.
No we can splurge now that we're full of dolls.
Yeah.
I'd say so.
Do you do coaster add?
That seems like also that seems like a thing your parents would teach too.
Once or twice.
Like I have one a real old one on a Scooby Doo roller coaster and then I have one on the
Incredible Hulk with my dad.
Oh well that's.
From like 2003 and that's nice.
Oh okay okay.
And that was the most surplus plastic frame so like as soon as I like tried to take to
my college dorm room like a chip a chip came out of the corner of it.
As soon as I put it in a box it was like oh the cardboard made the plastic chip.
Were you just you were displaying that in your college dorm?
Well yeah it's a mixture yeah picture family and stuff.
It was also cool it had the Hulk.
Cool logos.
I'm not saying the family thing is weird I'm saying like you have a big like Hulk.
Like you know like Hulk display from the Universal.
I mean it was just up on the bookshelf you know.
Out of the way no one's getting hurt here.
Was it the East Tower?
Yes it was sure.
You know you were there.
Oh right oh yeah I forgot.
We were there for a couple years.
We called that room yes okay so you were the one with the Hulk picture because we were
like god that whoever's in that Hulk's room is pulling on some chicks man.
Oh unbelievable.
Do you think the chip in the plastic is gonna hurt his chick chances?
Nah the chip's gonna be fine.
The chicks don't care about the chip.
No he put that massive dictionary his mother gave him like with his graduation gave him
that massive paper dictionary that you would never need again.
You were sent to college with a big dictionary?
Yes yeah a new alarm clock and a big dictionary and it held up the alarm clock.
I had a picture in my room so when I moved into I think junior year in the Emerson suites.
Yeah the air-conditioned one.
Yeah.
With your own bathrooms.
Did you guys overlap in dorm rooms?
No.
Not rooms you'd remember if you were roommates but yeah buildings rather.
My grandmother.
Do we say Ithaca is Ithaca right?
Yeah.
My grandmother was with us with me to like as I moved in I don't know why she couldn't
help but she was there and there was a we took a picture in the dorm room just her and
I and then that picture got developed put in a frame and given to me at like Christmas
so then I had that in the dorm room.
Like Thanksgiving yeah it was like so here's a picture of me and grandma right we were
right here.
Yeah we would talk about that.
And I still have that picture it's a lovely picture.
Yeah it's beautiful.
I love the grandma.
We would talk about that to her we'd be like have you guys been to the puzzle dorm room?
Have you been to the MC Escher dorm room where there's a picture of the dorm room?
That guy sucks.
Picture within the picture.
Who's he trying to impress?
He's smarty pants pictures.
He's impressing nobody standing by the door.
Hey anyone want to see the crazy ride?
Come see the crazy picture.
Picture taken right in this spot.
Alright what else can we say about these things?
Oh well here's the thing.
Okay so the biggest one of these see if you recall any of this from a year ago because
there were a couple of colorful characters who appeared.
Yeah there were a couple of weird I didn't quite remember them myself but.
So the biggest one of these that exists is at Fun Spot which is in Kissimmee.
Sort of near all the parks down there Disney World.
It's 300 feet tall.
So that's the craziest one of these sky coasters you can do.
And when it opened somebody one of the ultimate daredevils that ever was.
Was at the opening inaugurating it.
And there's a picture Jordan if we have it.
This is 82 year old water skier Banana George Blair.
There he is.
Remember this at all.
There's Banana George.
He's an old man who in this photo is water skiing barefoot.
And holding it with his mouth.
And he's holding two bananas.
He's in an all yellow jumpsuit.
And he's holding bananas in both hands.
Wow.
I'm just reading this stuff on it.
It's starting a new movie.
Yeah with Ernest Borgnine and Artie Johnson from Laughing.
Yeah.
He also yes this is a headshot that he signed in 95.
So he's in his 70s maybe here.
He water skied a lot at Cypress Gardens.
And at the time yes he seems to have been promoting a new film.
Captiva Island with Ernest Borgnine and Artie Johnson.
What is that number there 84 over 12?
Is that a fraction?
What is that?
He puts the date.
He just signs it Banana.
Like his name is Banana.
No he's got Fred up there.
And then the date and then 80.
Oh maybe that's his age.
Yeah 80.
But he's 80 and 412.
That's got to be it right?
Reduce this down to 1, 2.
Well he doesn't know math.
He doesn't know fractions of fractions.
He knows water skiing.
He does it because he's in the fourth month of the 12 is for the.
Yeah I get that.
I get why that's easier.
I sort of do it with my toddler but it's weird to do it with an old man.
But it's kind of neat.
It created a little mystery we had to solve.
This guy is pretty interesting in general.
Even regardless of the Ernest Borgnine film.
Which seemed too dreadful even to look at.
Even on this podcast.
Oh I'm so done.
I said Fred.
Fred is the person he's making it out to.
Oh right right.
Got you.
I thought it was Fred Banana.
Oh I kind of missed the Fred too.
He was in the darkness of the trees.
Well he did that I think because it's like I want all the glory here.
Put banana on the white Fred up in the dark part where he can't read it.
This isn't about you.
It's about me.
Banana.
And my 80 and 40 year old's birthday.
Look at him.
He's holding on to that.
Isn't that wild.
Regardless of the age of the man.
I don't think I realize people did this water ski with their mouth.
Yeah.
Only gripping the.
We've talked about various things we're afraid of.
And then we're watching an old man all hanging on by his teeth.
Yeah wow.
That's impressive.
His chompers.
Yeah I've seen an old man pull a car with his teeth but waters?
I've only seen an old man eat with his teeth.
Some of them can't even do that.
But I still got his auger.
Hey good eating.
I just want to remember this.
Put it next to my grandma in the dorm.
All the fresh water and salt water for this guy.
He looks much better than Evil Knievel did in later years.
Did Evil Knievel live harder perhaps?
I think he did.
I don't know everything.
I don't know much about him but that would be my guess from his vibe.
I don't think Banana here was falling from a great height very regularly.
Yeah I guess not.
So but he encountered a tough life for Banana.
The reason that he took up water sports and daredevil kind of stuff.
Because he had back injury for many years.
Oh now you take it back.
Because in the Great Depression a gang of violent hobos threw him from a moving boxcar after an argument over some beans.
No.
Shut up.
This is in a copy and pasted this.
When did that happen?
During the Great Depression.
When he was alive and I don't know what age.
That's just I mean I guess I accept that there were a lot of hobos in the Great Depression.
But that the fight we know that the fight wasn't over just anything.
That it was over beans.
So the ape Simpson and the guy who actually created it, itch and scratchy through this water skiing man.
This pre water skiing man.
These flintzes are lousy.
Hey Banana.
Wow.
This is a.
Yeah yeah yeah and he overcame that and still and got to inaugurate the sky coaster.
And that's how he had his back injury?
Yeah yeah so up through his 40s he was very inactive.
So he got beaten by the bindles?
You could guess that I would assume.
Yeah yeah.
I mean unless the hobos are stronger with kicking than the bindles are going to be.
But I don't know you can get a lot of force with those.
I'm guessing loose boards loose planks were used.
Oh maybe.
That's what I just pictured.
There's probably a lot of those around during the depression.
For boarding up businesses that are closing.
Jason how are you picturing this hobo assault?
I just some low blows some dirty shots you know.
Constant low blows.
Low blows.
So like kicks from behind.
Kick to the knee you know.
And probably like a big kick to the butt to send him out of the box.
No foreign objects.
No honor you know.
No foreign.
Well no maybe some foreign objects you know.
I just wanted to see how you saw it since you were since you lived it.
Since I was going to the boxcar show.
Nice first one up.
Can I amend mine?
Now I'm picturing a big katana blade.
Sort of he pulls it out of the sheet.
It glints in the moonlight.
And one swoop loses his head.
That's exciting.
Yeah that's what I'm picturing now.
Oh and then an oozy.
One other question about it maybe is that it was an argument over some beans and you think like hey those are my beans.
But what if it was an argument over which beans are best?
Oh okay.
Beans weren't there.
Pinto kidney.
I like peas.
Get em.
Is pea a bean?
Peas gotta be a bean right?
What's that?
Pea is a bean.
Maybe technically at the end of the I mean.
Is it a pod?
Maybe not.
I don't think it is.
No I don't think it is.
That's why I got it.
We'll look into it.
They're green.
They're green that's for sure.
This we know.
No fighting needed about that.
We do have a there is a clip here.
If you want to throw your headphones back on.
This is a clip of Banana George Blair appearing on Regis and Kathy Lee.
Oh wow.
It's a little quiet I know.
It's mainly about what we're seeing.
What is he water skis onto the show.
Oh my goodness.
He's in a full yellow suit and then cowboy hat.
And then listen really closely for what he says to Kathy Lee.
Okay.
I knew you were gorgeous.
I didn't know you were dynamite too.
We could stop it there.
I knew you were gorgeous.
I didn't know you were dynamite too.
And he takes you know what's good about that is he doesn't throw it away.
He makes a real meal out of it.
He pauses.
That's what freaks me out.
He really if you aren't looking at this he really locks eyes with her.
Waits for the audience to die down.
Look into my eyes.
I couldn't hear but the whole exchange was intense.
Yes.
My headphones don't work.
Menacing it was menacing.
Yeah.
Hey me and George got sort of a same color scheme going on here.
Oh that's right.
Yeah.
Banana Mike Cantor today.
I can water ski.
I should try it.
I should take off the mantle.
Oh that's right.
Yeah.
I'm kind of doing an homage to Banana George Blair.
And now he's shoeless because he came out of the water skis.
Yeah.
That's true that he does all this with bare feet.
Boy oh boy.
He looks the hat looks like almost like it's well I guess I was going to say it almost looks like a Wisconsin like cheese hat or something.
But yeah it's like a brighter yellow maybe verging on orange.
Mm hmm.
But yeah he's his whole gimmick is banana.
Did you guys ever have in high school or something grade school or middle school like a teacher who had a thing like we had a teacher who liked like pigs.
So she had a bunch of like pig ornaments around like a stuffed animal pig on her desk and like that was her thing.
Did you guys ever come across anyone like that who just like their thing was.
Oh.
I mean there's like beanie baby people obviously.
Yeah.
Somebody who's like I remember being at a church once and the head of the church like liked frogs and there was a little area with like stuffed frogs and stuff.
An altar.
Secondary to Christ on the cross.
What kind of church is this.
I think I had a teacher I'm trying to think like panda bear like maybe my third grade teacher like those panda bears.
Yeah.
There was like an identity like somebody's really trying hard to have an identity.
And it's like you can always get that person a gift if it's like oh yeah pig coaster.
Here you go.
Happy birthday.
Yeah.
I mean there was a teacher in high school who got him.
I didn't get him this somebody else got him a pen that the ladies clothes would fall off.
So his thing was he was like a creep.
There were a couple of those guys in high school.
I like pornographic pens.
They were escorted out some days and I never saw them again.
You know what I started to get off here on a tangent.
The one to do it.
Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
There was a teacher who was like after you all graduate we all go out to Hooters together.
Whoa.
And then like we were like well ha ha ha ha yes.
And then nobody went because we were like this is so weird.
But he went and then one of our friends went and he still denies he went.
We go like you went with him and he's like no I didn't.
We were like you did go.
We know you went.
And then that teacher I've heard may have been arrested for stealing a credit card and calling like a porno line from school.
I think I don't know if this is real.
I've not confirmed this story or not.
But it makes sense because he was also saying inappropriate things about our female friend at the time.
He was made sort of makes sense.
I guess if you think about it it all adds up.
He would be like guys you've got a beautiful woman.
Why don't you put her in your movie here?
And he said it like loudly in front of the class.
It was like he was teaching like film in high school.
Oh no let me teach you how to light a beautiful lady.
Yeah.
And there was one time when it was like you have to cast a movie or something and I think I cast Jessica Alba and he goes I want to congratulate you sir.
He like shakes my head and he goes for putting Dark Angel the Dark Angel in your script.
Whoa.
I got wait I think I have ten more stories now that I think about this guy.
Wow.
Oh keep him coming.
That's insane.
He would say well I think the issue with kids and the sex is that we need more dances.
You need more high school dances because that gets the energy like.
Whoa.
And I was like I don't think that's actually.
First of all sir you don't need to have an opinion about high school sex at all.
Don't put those words anywhere near each other.
The question is when is the half day over tomorrow.
Okay one more one more.
Yeah.
It's the senior brunch.
We're just about to graduate and he comes over to sit at the table and he's talking about the same female friend and he goes all right guys I'm just going to say it.
And now this person's name is hot.
What.
And we were like oh.
And she was there.
She I think she had gotten up.
Okay.
I go I go.
Yeah I go this is her boyfriend right here.
Whoa.
And he goes well I'd like to shake your hand sir.
Why shaking hands.
He gets a lot of congratulations in his handshake.
I am uncomfortable with the handshaking.
Yeah.
It's physical content as much as he's able to do with the high schoolers who he clearly wants to do more with.
There were so many people that should not have been teaching.
Did he seem like a person who was just like so off the wall like had no idea like not to excuse any of this behavior but just like oh I have no idea how to talk to anybody.
This is how I speak.
I know all these.
Or was he like oh I'm going to be a or I'm a creepy guy.
He didn't know he was being creepy.
He thought he was one of the boys.
He thought he was being cool.
Which is by the way the person I'm talking about is also so inappropriate.
I'm talking about this show too the female.
What?
Oh Jesus.
Does she know all of this?
I'm pretty sure she does.
I think we've told this many times.
Does she know she knows she is who this is even though her name was not said.
I'm sure she does.
Apologies.
It would be hard.
You got up from the table at just the right time.
Good job.
The best glass of punch you ever got.
Yeah yeah.
I mean she that she would have been well within her rights to just look him dead in the eye and just say gun.
What?
Gun.
Like no one would convict you for the court of law for making a threat to this man.
Oh sure sure.
That's such a terrifying move you just listed.
I know you just scared the shit out of me.
That's what you thought we were going to do when you pulled up this morning.
Yeah I was.
Gun.
I have like.
I think I hold on.
I think I do really need to make the point.
I do not condone this.
When I was like is he this or this?
I'm not making any excuse.
Well it all depends.
You're right.
I felt like I need to make that.
It can't be too careful.
It's interesting to see where these people are coming from because I literally can I think 70 percent of the teachers I haven't had in high school grossly irresponsible.
Right.
Saying crazy stuff and most of them I would just say were completely out of it.
Like had just been doing the job too long and maybe never should have been doing it.
But yeah everyone's got their own like where they're coming from spot.
Like this guy seems like any job he would have he would be behaving that way.
Yes.
You know what I mean.
And also these teachers are performers and they're fun expressing themselves.
Right.
To and a lot of the believe it or not a lot of people's ideas are bad.
Yeah.
You'd be right.
A lot of people.
Yeah.
We had a teacher who we knew we could manipulate into just putting on a movie and dropping everything you know for the thinnest of reason.
And my friends and I in high school were getting into like let's find kind of the weirdest videos we can find at the at the VHS rental place.
And thus we in school got the teacher to put on a movie called The Sex Machine.
This is and it's crazier even than just like a guy.
And yeah I'm the sex machine.
It is about a literal sex machine.
This is a movie.
This is a an Italian sex comedy from the 70s that we found dubbed.
And it's a movie about an apocalyptic future where we're running out of fuel.
But a brilliant doctor figures out how to harness the electricity the friction of sex.
Oh wow.
And use so that all of our sex fuels like all the world's electricity.
And I remember the teacher that we put it on.
Did it work?
It worked but it went too far.
He grim by the end he's grimacing at the world he created where people.
I think where it ends up it's actually kind of smart.
It ends up at like no one.
People only have sex in a functional way.
No one does it for fun.
Good good good.
This is what Mike wants.
Good yeah.
Well see your dream world in The Sex Machine.
I remember that the teachers the first time that there was there were naked breasts.
Again this is my doing.
I apologize.
I got naked breasts to be shown in this high school classroom in this movie.
And the teacher said is this pornography being shown in my classroom.
And then proceeded to keep the movie going.
I just I just am curious.
I don't want to go.
Which I was look I love I recommend you can find The Sex Machine.
This is genuinely a brilliant film actually.
I love it.
You kids are getting a kick out it.
So am I.
I'm just making sure this is pornography.
And if so great.
This is all mine looks very wholesome now because I had a seventh grade geography teacher who went to the University of Tennessee and clearly really loved it.
Because he had so much orange Tennessee Vols the Tennessee Volunteers is their their football team.
He just had so much on the walls.
He had sweater vests he had sweaters he had windbreakers he had and then his son it was like a year behind me started wearing Tennessee Vols stuff.
And looking back I'm like where did you get all this stuff.
You couldn't order it online.
Like I know there's college supply.
There are college sports stores but I was like it's just impressive because then he pull out a new coffee mug or a new hat and I'd be like how much is there.
Wow.
Well you it's an interesting point about the Internet like not being able to order online because it's like yeah somebody who likes the pigs or the Vols or the frogs like when you see something you're like I got to get this thing is I might not come across it every time.
Traveling or something you got to grab it.
Well we were all taught by a bunch of weirdos.
Straight up lunatics.
Clearly.
I could do an hour on it on all those stories.
This guy yeah.
No hold on to him let's keep talking about him.
We need a code for this professor Hooter.
Oh yeah.
He's also not the funniest one of all.
He's maybe like three or four on the list.
The Hooters thing is so funny too.
The funny thing too is like no we're not going to Hooters with you and also we don't want to hang out with the teachers at all.
No.
Yes.
At least of all at a Hooters but even at a Denny's.
Although a student teacher came over to watch wrestling with us once.
Oh but that's not there's nothing.
He was 22.
Okay.
Look how close.
17 18 we were.
Okay.
In the interest of having actual things about.
Well you mentioned the fun spot Orlando one and I believe that one was originally at the MGM Grand adventures in Las Vegas.
Oh yes.
And it moved when that shut down in the early 2000s.
Uh huh.
Yeah that was at the the MGM Grand theme park that used to be in Las Vegas and I think it's it outlasted the theme park.
Yeah.
They kept it up even when the theme park closed.
I have a commercial for but the sound was pretty bad to begin with so I'll just describe what happens in the commercial.
There is a guy it's like heavy heartbeat.
The guy is rising up and like beginning his sky coaster journey.
I forget what they called it there.
But the doesn't matter any of the name.
So he's like getting ready to go on this thing.
Could be.
Okay.
Yeah maybe.
So anyways the guy looks nervous and the voiceover is saying you've got a house you've got kids you've got a minivan.
But right now the only thing you want is your mommy.
And then he drops and then you watch this guy fly much higher than the MGM Grand which is a very tall hotel.
And if this thing is at most 300 feet there is no way that it is higher than the MGM Grand.
But that that mommy thing that's that's fantastic.
That's great like extreme.
That's a great like 90s.
Yeah.
You like your mommy.
That could be an ad for that or like wild cherry Pepsi.
Yeah.
That attitude too is very 90s commercial like that kind of cadence.
Right.
Like so like nasal to like the way maybe the devil might be.
Or a bug maybe.
Yeah.
Well yes he's the king of that sort of voice.
Yes.
You know.
I watched a video just someone's home movies on YouTube and they were they were riding it in Wildwood.
I think there was one or two on the boardwalk or on a pier in Wildwood New Jersey and the Red Hot Chili Peppers are playing the entire time.
Perfect.
I feel like that's that's what's got to be playing when you get which song one of these.
I think it was like.
All right.
Got it.
I know which one.
I don't want to say it's about California but the course is about California but it's not Californication.
Is it Danny?
Danny California.
Yeah.
I couldn't remember the name.
So that's playing and then the people holding it are are kind of narrating and it's just very nice to hear someone from the tri-state area going like oh I want to get on that for a million dollars.
I'm not getting on that John.
Listeners if you don't know your regional lingo John in around Philadelphia New Jersey.
John means any item anything can John just one thing thing like that John.
Can you hand me that John over there that feed the Fiji John.
What is it.
What are they.
John's.
The situation you just put me in.
I could you really needed to add more.
Oh this system doesn't work at all.
Fiji John.
There's a bunch of items over where you're planning.
How do you live like this.
John.
Yeah.
But when you only said John I didn't know what to do.
Is this something that you say but you got rid of it when you came out to LA.
I never say John.
I don't think I learned it until like like teen pre teen or teen years and then I started clocking that I've never heard of thing John.
Have you ever heard.
No.
And I'm wondering what it's like J.O.N.
J.A.W.N.
John.
Is that I'm wondering what that is coming for like a shorter version of something.
I I don't know the origins.
I should look it up but I mean it's it's to the point where like if you're at the field day off the airport you can buy Eagles or flyers shirts that say like John.
Eastern Pennsylvania used to refer to a thing place person or event that one need not or cannot give a specific name to.
Huh.
Yeah.
I mean I get it like oh pass me that thing over there and like you're pointing.
You just can't think of the word or something.
Yeah.
I guess it could just stand in for anything.
But it only kind of works with that accent though like if I was like oh could you pass me that John.
Yeah.
That wouldn't.
It doesn't sound fun.
Like wrestlers will say like gimmick give me that gimmick right there.
Give me that gimmick.
An item is a gimmick.
Yeah.
Like Steve.
I don't know what we're doing in this podcast.
Uncle Steve Austin gimmick right there.
Huh.
Uh huh.
I don't what are we trying to get around by not naming the item.
Seems pretty easy to just say what you want.
There's so many versions of this like do dad or like.
Right.
Thingamajig.
I guess I get what I just never heard that.
Yeah.
I never heard either.
And I've known this guy for a long time.
Yeah.
He's never said it.
He's never he's never enlightened me about it.
I don't think.
Yeah.
We didn't really say it in my house.
It wasn't until like middle school or high school where someone's like John you know
what John.
I want you to start using it.
OK.
All right.
Oh yeah.
Try to just slip one in in the rest of the episode.
Just try to refer to something as a John in the context that.
Oh sure.
Pennsylvania would.
But but watching that video and then watching you know they of course have it at Six Flags
Great Adventure in North Jersey and your beloved Wisconsin Dells.
It's there.
And the thing that don't know me is like if something goes wrong the last thing you will
see is Six Flags or the Wisconsin Dells or the Jersey Shore and take that as you will
because I think some people would be like thrilled at that like well there's worse worse
things to see when you're going out.
Thrilled to die in the Wisconsin Dells.
I mean there's worse ways to go I guess.
So yeah I guess.
No.
Now you say that but this they are proud of the sky coaster people are proud there has
never been an accident with one of these.
They've really think that they seem a little precarious.
Yeah.
It's incredibly.
We're better than bun.
Yes we looked it up five deaths just since 2015 never with the sky coaster.
That's that's some information that comes courtesy of the inventor of the sky coaster.
Maybe you recall talking about this guy last time.
We have a photo.
Hey.
It's nice to look at.
I would never have expected the person who made a amusement park swing look like that.
To be so professorial.
Yeah.
This guy's got sort of a funny look to it.
He's very scholarly.
It's like a Sears portrait studio.
Yeah.
I mean I like him and I love this.
Coat fits him well.
Nice tie.
Yes.
Yeah they go together color scheme wise.
You know you look at this esteemed person not only the inventor of what we're talking
about sky coasters but also the inventor of.
There he is.
Let's look closer into his eyes.
This is the inventor of indoor skydiving.
Wow.
The company started the company sky venture that eventually became I fly which is the
thing we did at City Walk with Paul Scheer.
You ever done that you ever indoor.
No those look fun though.
They're pretty fun.
Yeah.
Yes.
Is it hard to get.
It's pretty hard to like.
Yeah.
I think we're maybe all proud that we got like two seconds of unassisted.
We are actually.
Yeah.
You were Mike is a tall man was a little hard flailing.
The guys are really good at it.
They're like zooped that.
Yeah.
That's wild.
The people get to do it all day like the experts.
Yeah.
Of it.
The experts are good and then I think we saw like a kid like a 12 or 13 year old kid go
in and like old like an old hand just went in and started flipping around going up high
and it's like oh my god how long has this kid been doing this.
Yeah.
You got to commit to it like you have to take classes.
To get to actual enjoyment.
Yeah.
I think you.
You do have to like you could tell there were people there even when we did it at City Walk
who were like.
Pro.
That was like yeah that was there like maybe more than once weekly.
Yeah.
So where did the sky coat.
How did this guy get into the industry.
He didn't do anything close to ride design.
It just he went skydiving and he liked it and he thought is there a way in his words is
there a way to simulate skydiving without having to jump out of a perfectly good airplane.
Perfect.
Yeah.
He doesn't want to waste airplanes.
I guess.
The wear and tear.
The sky looks so nice why clutter it up with airplanes.
And people.
A bunch of junk up there.
So he drew on a dinner napkin an idea of like this very simple as we've referred to it's
like it's one stick and another stick and he built a little model of it and here's his
quote my girlfriend at the time looked at it and said you've gone crazy you don't know
anything about amusement rides and even if you did nobody would do that.
Oh no.
Nobody would get on that John for a million dollars.
So I got rid of the girlfriend and built the ride which became one of the fastest selling
rides in the world.
Yeah.
If you're with someone who's not going to support you it will just shoot your idea down.
That's true.
Yeah.
I like this guy.
I don't want him.
Maybe he had other like crazy ideas leading on other napkins at other dinners.
He's like this is the hot dog you can ride to work.
No one's going to do that.
That's stupid.
It's a modern bindle that will solve any arguments about beans.
Why did the bindles disappear in the 30s?
That just may have been her stock response.
Like he's drawing.
Yeah no one's going to do that.
You're crazy.
A pile of napkins.
200 high.
You know nothing about theme parks.
All she'd do is write down ride ideas and you don't ask me how I'm doing.
She's like a famous author.
Yeah.
And rice.
So yeah this rogue renegade man went on to invent all this big stuff.
He looks like he will not take no for an answer.
Yeah I think so.
He's no non-sense.
And yet he did, maybe you guys remember this from before, he did find himself in a precarious
situation.
Not all is well in the world of Bill Kitchen.
And apologies for not having the, if the sound is a struggle here, but do we have the clip
which I think I called Kitchen Robbery?
It's a lot, even if you guys didn't hear that, a lot to look at here.
Bill Kitchen in a, under the big news phrase, ninja robbers.
The inventor of sky coasters was involved in a ninja robbery.
Yeah.
Is there any confirmation these were actual ninjas or were they just dressed in black
and head to toe?
That's a question.
Right, right.
Were they, were they?
And can you call yourself a ninja?
Do you have to complete a series, like how do you get designated a ninja?
Are there modern ninjas?
Yeah I feel like being seen and captured on camera, you're automatically out.
Like you are not a ninja.
We got you from a couple angles pal, like you're supposed to be invisible.
Oh wait that's right, yeah we see his eyes in the security camera, that's instant not
ninja right there.
Wait is he wearing, the ninja wearing a hat?
Yes.
That could have been Kitchen's hat though, he could have been like, hey I'm taking this,
boot, put your hat on.
Give me everything in the house.
Like that hat, hey give me that.
My hands are full, put that fedora on my head.
Yeah he's wearing like a fedora.
The ninja, first of all it looks like the ninja's wearing like a black sweatshirt and
like a ski mask.
They look a little more maybe out of shape than I think a ninja would be.
Then you think yes.
Cause I picture ninjas doing like kind of acrobatic type moves around to get to the
shadows.
Yeah yeah, finding the shadows at all.
I think Bill is more in the shadows than the ninjas are.
Did Bill say they were ninjas or is this the news editorializing again?
It might be them trying to like, do a little fun.
Get clicks you know, make it more sensational cause ninja robbery jumps out.
But aren't ninjas, I don't know, don't they fight for what's right?
Well not the foot plan are they ninjas?
Depends on what clan you're aligned with.
I know a lot about ninjas.
I'm wearing a shirt, I have a lot of toys.
If these guys were dressed in like red, the headline would be like,
this kitchen got robbed by Santa Claus' today.
The exact opposite of what they usually do.
Green mocap suit wearers.
Was it Andy Serkis?
They just fill in like the CGI character on the news.
Jar Jar Binks robbed Bill Kitchen today.
Is that even Bill Kitchen? Who knows?
He looks like his arms are bound behind him though.
The hat?
No, that's not ninja behavior.
Sort of like Tommy Bahamas style.
It's an island casual hat on top of a ninja.
Did they chop him at all or did they give him a kick?
That would maybe suggest ninja.
Was a high yaw involved?
Yeah, I don't think.
This is again, this is a news media run amok.
This is something that is not good for the people to consume.
This is getting clicks.
And we fell for it, we love it.
We do love it, yeah, that's true.
They're propagating the myth of ninja robbery.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like Danny from the Ninja Turtles 1 movie.
The kid from Ninja Turtles 1 who gets taken in and the foot clan.
I don't even think it's their Danny level.
I don't think.
Sub Danny.
Danny California.
My ninja name is Danny California.
Anyway, Bill Kitchen is still at it.
He's trying to build a thing called the polar coaster.
Do we have a photo of the polar coaster?
Just imagine it coming out of the wind.
Whoa.
This is something he's trying to make happen.
Actually, let me be clearer here.
On the right is the polar coaster, on the left is the sky spire.
They're similar, they're big towers.
But one I think is a leisurely observation deck.
You know, these exist.
We've all done these where you go up in an elevator and look at the city from a pod kind of thing.
But one, you get a cooler ride on the way up.
So the one's very casual and the other one is a daring high octane coaster.
That's sort of, if we know this guy uses cocktail napkins, the design is very cool.
And the other one is a very cool.
The design of the right feels very cocktail.
It looks like he just scribbled wherever.
And then they go this way and have a loop and like, oh my god.
And then like, poof, and then they go back up again.
How does it get up?
Do you go in the middle there? Is it like a vertical climb?
Or maybe you get up, maybe it goes both ways.
You could get up from the ride.
No. How?
Do you get down from the ride? Do you take an elevator up?
I bet it's an elevator.
Maybe it's a circular...
track that is connected.
It's unclear. Because you'd have to really launch to get, to have the force to get up from the start.
Like if you use the same track.
Oh, and for to keep climbing and keep...
Well maybe the coaster goes down, but look, there's kind of a double helix on the sky spire.
Yeah.
And so maybe one is up and one is down.
The sky spire looks more obviously practical and just like a better ride.
There doesn't look like there's too much going on with the...
I don't know, it's just kind of up and down.
It's very confusing.
I like it.
I will invest.
He'd be happy to hear that because I think he's been trying to get these going for a long time.
He's proposed these for a lot of big...
What he's trying to do is like, you know, you have a mall in your town.
You have a big JCPenney that closed.
Let's build one of these on top of it.
Because that's a big question is what do we do with all these vacant retail spaces?
He's tried to do this in San Diego when it hasn't taken off.
This looks like Vegas or Dubai to me.
Yeah.
I bet it is you load it at the top on the Polar Coaster.
And then the car just probably goes back up without people on it.
That's got to be what it is.
You would think the one you call Polar Coaster you would have the blue on the top.
Not the purple.
Yeah, it could be called the purple coaster.
It's a very confusing pitch. I think that's why he's not getting any of his seed money.
We have some notes, Bill.
I feel so guilty criticizing him now that we're looking at him again.
We'd like to have Bill on.
Bill has to know about us.
He's got a lot of popular theme park podcasts around.
He's got to have his eye on us.
Bill, if you want to explain yourself, make yourself known to us.
Show yourself, as they might say.
And show us that winning smile.
And then we'll talk about ninjas and we'll talk about the Polar Coaster.
I really like that striped yellow John he's wearing.
There it is.
Wow, a handsome John.
Bill Kitchen.
He did get a ride installed recently.
He has another type of ride called the Polar Coaster.
He has another type of ride called the Unicoaster.
And like all of his rides, they're confusingly named.
When I say Unicoaster, you probably can't picture what that might be.
Unicycle car of some kind?
No, that would make sense.
There's already single rail coasters.
I don't think there's any one aspect to it.
Universal coaster.
It's not at Universal Studios either.
There's no crew.
All the way around.
No, it's kind of a centrifuge.
It spins and you're in a pod that also flips around.
You're going around and around, but then you're flipping around.
And this has been built or this is something?
This has been built.
It's called Jimmy Neutron's Atom Smasher.
And you can find that at one of our favorite places.
The American Dream Mall.
Which is out in New York.
Have you heard about this place?
We've talked about it a bunch.
It's a huge mall that's been in slow motion for a while.
It's been in slow motion failure mode for many years.
It's across several rivers in New Jersey.
When we were out there, I went.
And it was an absolute disaster getting there.
It took me two hours to get a lift out of there.
So not a recommend.
I wouldn't say.
But if you ever see a big ugly building.
If you're in the New Jersey area.
If you're by the Meadowlands.
I'll check it out.
There should be a roller coaster into it.
And out of it.
It's hard to get in and out.
I haven't been there.
But a roller coaster that's a mile away.
That takes you in and then a roller coaster takes you out.
But still has some loops and dips and stuff.
Oh yeah.
Scott discovered that the ride chair is an escape room.
An inadvertent escape room.
That I failed.
You're a failure if you take more than an hour.
I think to get out of an escape room.
You have to figure out 30 minutes in.
You have to walk to the Valero.
Boy yes.
The hardest escape room ever.
Well what else?
What have we not addressed about this ride that swings back and forth a couple times.
Will you three, if you come across one,
will you do it now that you've learned so much about it?
I guess the three of us would have to do it together.
Oh that would be fun.
That would be the after fried picture of that.
All of us in a big weighted blanket together.
I'm in baby mode, but a big swaddle.
The three of us getting swaddled in a blanket by a Six Flags employee.
On our bellies. For tummy time.
The weight limit was like 850 or 900 pounds.
So I think we're well under that.
Well under that.
I think we are under that, yes.
I think that's okay.
It doesn't seem like a risk, yeah.
For that photo op, yes.
I don't know how soon it's going to happen.
We're working on some other things to get brave about.
Especially haunt season.
I've been working on these gentlemen to get in the mazes.
So I think that's step one.
Oh well, you know what, talking properties.
It's very rare that these things are themed.
There's over a hundred of these sky coasters.
There's only one that maybe ever
you could consider having
even still not a narrative.
I guess just a theme.
This might have come up oddly with Justin McElroy recently
that Kings Island
where they had to theme things after
properties while they had a paramount license
and then immediately change all of them
when they lost the paramount license.
The one in Kings Island was named after
the movie Drop Zone.
It was called Drop Zone.
Can anyone produce any facts about Drop Zone offhand?
Does anyone know what it is?
Only that we recently talked about it.
And then it was already called
In-N-Out.
I never heard of it at the time.
This is a movie where Wesley Snipes
free falls into the daredevil world
of skydiving to track down
a cadre of techno-terrorists.
Including
Gary Busey as
renegade skydiver Ty Montcreaf.
I mean that's a killer name.
That's a killer character name.
So
I don't think they were
doing the instructions.
So remember to place a polar ripcord
and take it from me Ty Montcreaf.
You might not want to listen to Ty.
He might be leading you astray.
Oh there it is.
Drop Zone.
Leave that up for the next
recording please.
Why are we being advertised
Drop Zone today?
Well anyway
talking about this for a while
made me feel like a real Ty Montcreaf.
You must have felt like Ty
doing it.
Well I don't know.
Any final thoughts about this?
Maybe we do it. Maybe we give it a try.
Will you ever again?
While you were talking about maybe I go with the sloppy boys.
That's a trio.
After talking about it I'm going to do it again.
Nelton arms race.
Do we three ride it first or the three sloppy boys ride it first?
I wonder who
will get to it first.
Who has more opportunities to do this type of thing?
The only thing stopping you guys is that you aren't always
in the same place all the time.
When we are it is at an amusement park.
Well if it is
update us.
Send us photos or videos.
And for now
Mike Hanford at last you survived.
Well we don't know yet.
In theory
you survived.
At the risk of making this too long of an episode.
I don't want to keep it going.
I came on last time the whole initial thing was to
sort of
bridge our friendship again.
Because I was talking.
I don't even remember the story now.
Because we buried the hatchet.
And now I put it out of my mind.
But we I think we were outside of a bar once.
Across from Tam Oshancha.
At the Griffin.
Then Griffin.
And people were talking about Disneyland.
And I said Disneyland is not good.
Disney is not good.
And we were like oh Hanford would be great to have on.
And then you shot the dream down.
I said Disneyland.
But then I said.
Because I see it as and I like this.
I see it as just a get people in.
Make their money off them.
And shoot them out.
Well you should know it has become since you did the show last.
It has become
200% more that.
Boy they are getting crazy with the add ons.
And maybe you get these.
The magic man the wrists.
And you pay for individual rides.
So no disagreement.
I love how it is like the most magical place on earth.
And I like going there.
I really enjoy being there.
It is fun and you see all the characters and the rides are fun.
But you know it is just taking all your money.
So it is at once the most evil thing.
And the most wonderful thing.
You like that you are just watching the dance.
I love it.
I think when I said Disneyland is bad.
That battle.
Fists were up.
The subtlety.
Now I see the whole opinion.
But then that is all you hear.
When you have a couple of drinks in you.
I like to push buttons too.
You are a rabble rabble.
I like to get people.
What did he just say?
This is Eric Bogosian over here.
Doing talk radio.
So I wanted to be controversial in the moment.
And then it came to be where I came on the podcast.
And we did figure out the water under the bridge.
But that is what started this.
To bring up the chili peppers again.
Full circle.
But I do like Disneyland.
I think I made that point on the last.
The Lost Podcast.
So you wanted it on record here.
And on record that you don't approve of that teacher's actions.
Right.
You don't forget.
That is bad. Everything that person did was bad.
No excuse.
I am glad it is all on the record.
And glad we don't have to have a big bendel war.
We don't have to have a bean fight.
We can all just hold hands.
Clash hands.
And go to Big Rock Candy Mountain together.
I'd like that.
What does that mean?
It is an old folk song.
It is in the Old Brother We Are Not Thou.
About hobos luring children to a mountain of candy.
Wait.
So we don't want to go there.
Do we?
People are being lured to children.
It is candy.
But lured is a bad word.
It is like Pleasure Island in Pinocchio.
That is a bad place too.
But there was a ride.
There was a boat ride.
But vapor monsters.
Not smoke monsters.
Vapor monsters in the Zemeckis movie.
To turn them into donkey slaves forever.
Like the Valencia teens.
Like the Valencia teens riding the skycoasters.
I have seen you tweet about the Pinocchio.
I haven't watched Pinocchio yet.
I plan to.
It doesn't seem like it is going to be.
There are dozens and dozens of bizarre facets to it.
So again, mixed ride.
Would I recommend it?
It is a boy made of woods.
Of course there are going to be weird facets to it.
It is a little out there for me.
It is pretty twisted.
But,
Mike, let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
I will plug the Sloppy Boys podcast
and albums.
I will also plug this.
Since the last time we have done a podcast together.
The book, Devil in the White City.
It is an old book.
Have you read it?
Fantastic book.
I am so late.
It was like New York Times top seller like 20 years ago.
I read it since the last time we talked.
It is fantastic.
It is about the Chicago World's Fair coming together in 1892.
Something like that.
It was an early running thread on this.
I think I just read it as we were starting the podcast.
I was just so jacked off.
Early theme park connections.
All the big historical figures who pass through.
The big ride.
The big thing that shows up.
The way they reveal that.
Oh, I have said too much.
A John.
A big John shows up.
There is captains of industry.
There is murder.
It is all happening.
We should.
It is always good to encourage us to read.
Mike and I.
If you want a shorter read, I would like to plug an article.
I found mid episode.
Mel magazine.
Which I like in general.
Which is about sports.
Oh wow.
This is also from Mel.
Jordan has put up.
The difference between peas and beans.
And why it matters.
That is wild.
There is an article.
I have an article about sport mode.
This was written about.
They have a nuclear.
What is it?
A nuclear and mechanical engineer.
Discuss why sport mode matters.
With crocs.
And the benefits.
What could happen to you if you don't properly activate sport mode.
There is a lot of websites out there.
There is infinite content void.
There is an article about everything.
Think of anything.
And then further plugs.
From us.
Thanks to Jordan Katz.
For producing this episode.
And showing that article about peas and beans being different.
Thanks to forever dog.
You can find us on all the socials at podcast the ride.
Merch is available in our T public store.
For 3 bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast the ride the second gate.
At patreon.com.
And I update my documents since a year ago.
Because we have a new tier.
Club 3.
Where you get ad free episodes.
And a bonus episode on top of that.
Every month.
There is an innovation.
We just started this new tier in the last year.
It is an 8 dollar tier.
Your top tier is something else.
Would you like to discuss?
We have a top tier.
It is the pay pig tier.
You can pay 100 dollars a month.
And you get the satisfaction of giving us 100 dollars a month.
And that is all.
That came from.
I think that is a tier on like.
Only fans.
That is a tier 2 thing.
Where you get off on the idea of.
You are paying too much money.
Losing everything.
We put that up there as a joke.
And we have a few.
We have a few pay pigs.
We have encouraged people.
On the podcast.
If you are a pay pig.
Make sure you know that is auto renewed.
And maybe take your.
I do not want to do that forever.
We love every.
We call them Patron's.
We get kind of funny with that.
We are a cocktail podcast.
We love all those people.
It warms my heart that someone.
Likes the podcast.
Pay pigs.
The thing to get obsessed with.
If you are a pay pig.
You get all the stuff.
You do not just get mocked.
For your monthly money loss.
It does sound like it is a sex thing.
It comes from.
I am saying only fans.
It is a kink.
Ruin me.
Take all my money.
Gun me.
Jason really quick on the answer.
Ruin me.
It is more unnerving.
I feel like I have seen it.
You usually just type it.
I do not really just type it.
To a Vomititions.
Captain's of Industry.
Bill Kitchen.
No never.
What if we step into Professor Hooters mind.
That could be a ride at the Universal's Hornet.
Professor Hooters will be.
House of Horrors.
Alright bye everybody.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson.
Jason Sheridan.
Scott Gardner.
And Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts.
Please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com.
And subscribe to our shows.
On Apple Podcasts.
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news.
By following us on Twitter and Instagram.
At ForeverDogTeam.
And liking our page on Facebook.