Forever.
Dog.
Warning! Before you can listen to this podcast, we have to scan you for Pandoran micro parasites.
Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep.
Mmm, you've all got them.
But don't worry, you're in good hands.
We've enlisted the Dr. Stevens from the Avatar Flight of Passage pre-show.
Once he's matched to a microphone, we can start to talk.
And, uh, podcast.
We welcome David Danapour to the final Feliz Navidad, The Way of Winter, on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to the final Feliz Navidad, The Way of Winter, a Yuletide celebration of all things Avatar here on Podcast The Ride.
A podcast series that will soon end, after which, sadly, we will be in Kansas anymore.
I'm Scott Gardner.
That's about the reaction that deserves.
I'm really like, I'm trying to think about what it means.
I mean, I know what it means, but the actual words itself.
The grammar was so next level.
It was so, uh, so wrong that it was a new type of grammar that worked.
I would need to see it on a piece of paper to really decipher it.
Uh, yes, I'm here.
I'm looking at it on paper. It's not helping me.
Well, just text it to me and I'll look.
Mike Carlson, for the last time, I see you.
I see you.
Sharon, I see you.
Sounds more like I see you.
Oh, like I see you.
Medical trouble.
Yeah.
Um, no, no, no.
We are wrapping up our Avatar celebration here.
Um, and by now, The Way of Water has made a billion dollars.
And I would like to think that The Way of Winter has done similarly for us.
And our influencer check from James is coming in.
James Cameron, I'm sure.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Knowing that so many phrases we've contributed to the way.
Wait, wait, wait.
We haven't talked on the show about the new one because we gave them the word mighties in the movie.
You called it the mighty Akron.
That's right.
And then now there is the weekend song.
Yes.
And the week, wait, I already don't remember what it is.
What's the phrase in strength?
You give me strength.
The thing that our character, the sector keeper, our real book, I, we know the sector keeper.
He's a real character.
All right.
He sure is.
Yes.
Um, they're after it.
They're listening to podcast, the rides, catchphrases and incorporating that is crazy.
The weekend is doing a song that's the title of it is a catchphrase from our show.
They're not.
I mean, I don't think we're not crazy enough to think that he's actually stealing it from it.
But the coincidence.
It's getting a little unreal.
Um, I well, and you know what?
But like so much of this little journey and talking about avatar for a little while has been about kind of just like steeping in the culture and finding it together and making the cultural embed much talked about cultural impact together.
And maybe, maybe it's what if it's not coincidences?
What if we are part of it?
What if, what if it's the cultural impact of avatar is going to be helped by the cultural impact of podcasts?
The rock.
Yeah, I think you're right.
And then in a certain like in a future movie, there'll be like a character named Jason eating a hot dog or something.
And it'll continue and continue and continue until the three of us are in one of them.
Maybe I don't know.
I we can we can only hope so.
I mean, were that to happen?
Oh, you know what?
There was a tease I read.
I think like that fifth one might take place on earth or something.
It's going to come back.
I think they have to come fight like nature.
Nature is that the nature?
What's the name of the character?
It's here.
Jesus.
I mean, we are nothing.
Edit that out.
So that sounds good.
It says something about her learning about Earth.
Whoa.
But he but Earth sucks.
And I know in future you just want to go there.
That's a bad idea.
Well, but a recipe for some fun.
I look for I'm up for whatever it is because my love of this franchise has grown only while we've been doing this.
Hope you guys feel similarly.
And if we were somehow to be lucky enough to end up being part of the franchise,
then and only then would we be close to something achieved by our guest today,
who is an actual part of the don't shake your head as if that's not no.
Bill just said you are you are a genuine part of the Avatar mythology.
A character in the way in the characters way beyond all the events of the films even.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We'll talk about it.
And I'm so excited.
He's here to close out the series.
I can't think of a cooler way to do it.
You may have seen him on The Good Place on Westworld or on the dropout.
And you have definitely seen him in the pre show of Avatar Flight of Passage at Disney's Animal Kingdom.
The gentleman who plays Dr. Stevens himself, David Danipour.
Hi.
Hey, thank you guys.
Thank you, Michael, Jason and Scott.
Thank you.
Thanks for it.
We should have the name tags.
No, no, no, I know your names.
I've been listening to the podcast.
Thank you.
Thanks.
So funny.
You guys are so funny.
And I was saying it earlier and I'll say it again since it's recording now.
Oh, OK.
You guys have great voices.
It's like you guys are like radio hosts.
It feels it sounds like you guys are, you know, moving on up.
Oh, thanks.
This is a nice thing to say, because I do.
That's not something I would think that we have is like the slickness.
And that's the thing with radio hosts look down on podcasters for for not being able to like, you know, read a five second promo or talk up a song like you would talk up.
Don't stop believing on the radio and like coming in here.
It's journey with don't stop believing where they throw it away right before this journey.
We don't believe in.
Yes, but that's like that's only like a five second job.
You guys are doing like that's a good guys are doing 90 minutes of like, you know, sure.
Yeah, thank you.
That's nice to hear.
I mean, if anyone wants to give us like traditional DJ jobs, I think we're interested.
Well, it'll be like Wolfman Jack or you guys want avatar jobs and.
OK, we're getting greedy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're complimenting us because you haven't heard those episodes where we just ask, will you hire us to write this or be in this or half the show?
Three words, pal.
Work for scale.
You want to be the new cousin, Bruce's is what I'm saying.
Because I did a tweet, which I should have deleted, but I left it on.
And sometimes I get like, why did I do that?
But I like tweeted at James Cameron and I was like, hey, if you need a scientist, put me in your movie.
And they got like five likes.
And that's great.
I would have liked that if I.
I think it's still up.
Yeah.
OK, let's make all the listeners find the tree as full of her nation.
Yes, Clifford, a Wilbur.
You tweet the tweets on the day everyone will go to our Twitter.
They'll follow you and then they'll retweet it.
And let's get this on this guy's radar.
Yeah.
OK.
Let's do it.
Well, then let's also retweet one of your tweets that let's let's do one for you guys in the movie and then let's all worry about us later.
OK.
Yeah, we don't want to be greedy.
Here's what we'll try to get a number five.
We'll try to get you in three or four.
They're filming for now.
Let us will tweet at the Wolfman Jack estate and will say, let us do be the new Wolfman Jack.
Is state the intellectual property from the voice.
And we're assuming that any like any deceased person has an estate.
And we're also assuming that any listener knows who Wolfman Jack is.
I picked one of those relevant DJs of all time.
Graffiti, right?
American graffiti.
Yeah, American graffiti.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's true.
He lives on in the.
Yeah, yeah.
For the last 20 years, I heard he dislike would they anytime you thought you heard his radio show was just like clips that they had recorded and they were just randomly play them and piece it together.
Like he was barely he was not showing up for shows.
This one's a rocker.
Yeah, it didn't matter.
It's into this one.
I believe that's what the current politics are not ideal.
This is Wolfman Jack and I am a ghost in the machine.
Truly what he was.
We'll do one of those two.
We'll do one of those.
Fair, fair.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But we'll look.
I mean, there's there's compliments come on your way to because we love your performance in this ride so much.
I think we actually have to be first bit of business.
We have to thank you for giving us all the material for the Orlando live show that we did where we essentially recited everything that you had to say on that day.
It was it was I listened to it.
I had a friend whose name is also Scott and he was he told me about that podcast and he's like, oh, you should listen to it because they're talking about you.
We shout you out.
Yeah, no, no.
Yeah, I listen to it.
At one point, I think it was you, Scott.
You're like, before we start the, you know, mild roasting, I just want to say I know David DeAndre for and like, you know, he's great.
And, you know, I love him.
And OK, now let's begin.
I'm glad that registered and I'm glad you I'm glad you know nothing.
We didn't do anything in the aftermath that made you not want to come here.
Oh, no, no.
Yeah, I mean, I messaged you right after that because like, oh my God, that's Scott.
I remember you, you know, coming to the shows with for improv shows sometimes, sometimes some shows.
Sure.
The significant other of the performer will come to a lot of the shows.
And yes.
And you were on a team with Aaron, my wife, who did improv for a little while and super funny.
And and and so I saw you do you guys were on a team together.
So I saw you do improv a bunch of times and I am not I'm certainly not making the supper.
It's like revisionist history.
I think Aaron can attest that there when there whatever the first time I saw the show you were in, I definitely afterwards like, who is that guy?
Like you got that you got that lift.
Oh, thank you.
Because you had this you were just so like natural, but like and like willing to play kind of like odd energies that were not anything like what anybody else on stage was doing.
You were just like on a wavelength that was just like this is like naturally.
This isn't just like thinking of funny stuff.
This is like the guy being really funny.
Oh, yeah.
I really did feel that way.
I just I was just, you know, acting like myself.
But thank you.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
So you would hide in performance.
But thank you.
Yeah, I forget.
What was the question there?
Or is there a question?
Maybe we're just talking about how this all well, this all came together.
Yeah.
This all came together in a nice way.
And then, yeah, you follow me and then we wrote each other and it was like, oh, this is perfect because we had just begun this celebration of Avatar.
Flee is Navi dot.
And I'm thinking about it anyway.
Ever since then, I'm like, it's got to be a way for David to come on.
And this is perfect.
A full examination of of your performance of Dr. Stevens.
Oh, and one more thing just before we dive in, because I've also liked in recent interaction with you that we had to push this because I got COVID and you were giving me tips on this and telling me to explore getting the Pax Lovid, which the then the insurance was like, yeah, you're fine.
You don't need that.
You're so it doesn't sound like you're bad enough.
You don't sound shitty enough on the phone.
So we're not going to give you the so I just get through it in a regular way.
But I was glad I tried.
You actually did make me you helped me make the phone call, which I showed.
There's something else was prescribed.
It was mildly helpful.
Anyway, not cool.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
Insurance.
They're trying.
I hear that's having a lot with Pax Lovid is they're trying to feel like if they have any hoarding it for the higher risk categories.
That might be it.
Yeah, I didn't have a good like stat and lie about.
I didn't play a character who needed it.
You should have lied with all wheezing off and stuff.
Yeah, you also got it in a time when I think a lot of people got it right after Thanksgiving.
That's a good point.
When I got it, I don't think they were just like, no one's taking this.
Right.
Take it.
Yeah, it's funny how it goes in and out of people caring or thinking about it, myself included.
I was like, that old thing that what is this?
I love the 2020s.
There's no covid anymore.
And then there you go.
I got it.
But you are land.
The show is so funny.
I think it made me a little intimidated to come on because you guys were so funny.
And I'm glad there's no audience because I think you guys would be, you know, it would then it's like you got to compete like, oh, wow.
These guys are making all these.
I wish I had if you would come out in that audience, you would have people.
Oh, God, I know what else to get to you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It would be you would have lived.
OK, we'll get to the another avenue of this later, but I'll get you to I'll get you to the comments sections of things.
Oh, I'm so curious.
You're wondering.
You may have seen the dark side of people's opinions.
Oh, God, what a tease.
Well, OK, just just to wrap up what I was saying on the light side of it.
How nice it's been talking to you and I appreciate getting that advice.
And I like that you gave me a little spell of advice and then finished it by saying, but don't take it from me.
I'm not a doctor.
I just play one in Avatar flight of passage.
And I was so delighted to read that email.
That's kind of in this in this odd medical because, you know, you came up another time on the show in a brief window where we thought the pandemic was bad enough that we were willing to do Twitch streams.
We tried a lot of work.
Yes, that's what we found annoying.
A lot of work.
One that we did was we did a competition and NCAA style brackets for that we called the fake doctor final four and Dr.
Stevens was a candidate in the we made sure that you were competing to be for the title of best fake theme park doctor.
I don't I don't know.
I knew that I know that I threw the results of it because the Muppet one and I thought that was boring.
I might have been gunning for Dr. Stevens.
I don't recall. I'd have to look it up.
I don't remember anything about who won.
No, you guys should know before I am not attached to the, you know, Dr. Stevens being like loved or not loved.
Right. Right.
You guys can like go full full honesty.
It's like I want to hear, you know, like, like I want to hear the, you know, the like the honest.
Right. Right.
You could be nice to but also also I'm in the mood for nothing.
I like being roasted, I guess.
Oh, OK. OK. OK.
I didn't I don't think any of us thought we're going to do like an Isaac Chotner like New Yorker take down of you.
Yeah, well, yeah.
We can Dennis Miller over here.
I didn't think we were going to do an Isaac Chotner or a babe.
No, I think well, I when we were down there for that show and we were staying for a few days, I think, Mike, you had been to the Pandora section of the park before.
Yes, I've I've been multiple times.
Yes. And Scott, you and I, that was our first time ever.
Yeah. Yeah.
So to a certain extent, we experienced your character and performance together.
I don't know.
Here's what I'll say.
This is the closest you're going to get to me as far as a roast.
And it's not anything that I don't think it's actually a roast that depending on if the ride breaks down, they make it seem like you don't know what's going on sometimes.
But that's the ride making you seem like you're like a scientist, but you have no clue what's happening in the lab.
And that's the closest it ever gets because some people would be like this.
Say you're a dad and you think that guy is actually helping.
This is a real guy.
Nothing fake here.
One out of 50 dads might think that.
Like, oh, this guy was that was right.
I think that was Joe roadie's idea.
He's a great idea.
He was like after everything was shot.
He was like, OK, now we're going to do one for when we don't know how long people have to wait.
And so he's like, so you're just going to be like, I'm going to come right back and like leave.
Yeah. And then and then and then I would I go off stage or offset and then I come back like 10 seconds later.
But, you know, they edit it.
So it's like it looks like yes, I came back a lot.
They can do it as long as they want.
And he was just giggling.
He was just like, this is going to be so great when it actually happens in the park.
It happened.
I think one of the first times I did ever did the ride and it took forever.
They scanned your character came on screen left screen.
I swear it happened like maybe twice where you left.
So, again, if one out of 50 dads who like thinks maybe you're like a ride operator, but you're sort of like plant, like maybe this is live.
You're like, I don't know. This guy doesn't know what he's doing.
The scientist is really something's broken.
He has he needs to fix this.
They're fitting it on you.
It's like I there's somewhere I'm trying to be and it's this guy's fault.
This dweeb won't let me pass this door.
I'll take it.
Just, you know, he keeps scanning me.
There's the vibration thing keeps going off.
How many times do you need to scan me for germs?
So it keeps it keeps doing everything.
I believe once it scanned me twice at least.
Oh, wow.
But it was like and then when you do it for the first time, you're like a little long.
Like you don't know how long it's supposed to be.
But yeah, it was definitely a long new set.
Yeah. And of course, and I don't know if I'm getting ahead the move, move your arms around a little, which is an iconic line.
And I don't even say that facetiously or anything.
Truly. That's like if you're a nerd for this stuff, you're like, it's a good line.
That's a memorable line.
But that happened a lot in this stretch of like the ride.
Something was wrong with the ride.
They never tell you certainly when we were together, we got a couple move your arms around.
I think when we rode it.
I bet that's what it is in general is people feeling like that you like that they are what they've been watching you for 15 minutes.
And that's probably where you're responsible.
I think even if people are consciously thinking about it in the back of their mind, they're like, this guy's got to hurry it up.
So that's what it is.
Dr. Stevens is the fall guy for the long wait.
They're like, we've got to.
Yeah, we've got to pin that on something.
We've got to be mad at somebody.
There's not usually a specific person to do it.
All of the ride technicians, what are they called?
They're players or cast members.
All the cast members are like, hey, Dr. Stevens, it's his fault.
Take it up with this guy.
Throw a drink at the screen if you need to.
They should have done it like the Mr. Potato Head animatronic where you got to roast people in line and there were generic roasts.
So somebody like it would just be like, hey, look at your hat.
That's pretty silly, right?
We got to scan that for germs.
I wish.
That's funny.
Let's redo it.
Let's redo it and add something like that in.
Sure.
And of course you get royalties for that.
Of course.
The same royalties I get.
Right.
I was going to say.
So we're going to be rolling in money.
If I had to guess, knowing anyone's history with appearing in these kinds of things, that would have been my guess.
Disney's kind of like, Garrett, and here you go.
There's one thing once and goodbye.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, in a way they sort of had to pay me more because they messed up.
Oh.
Yeah.
So like I did the shoot and then I get a call like three weeks later and they're like, oh, we need you to come in to do some ADR.
Like we just want to add some stuff in.
So I go in into this like small ADR booth and I think it was in the where the Imagineer offices are on.
Wow.
Where is that?
Flowers?
Flowers.
Yeah, yeah.
And you know, it was like 10 minutes.
They just needed me to add like one line or two lines of like safety, like some sort of legal stuff.
Right.
Then I go home three, four weeks later.
I get another call like, David, it's not your fault.
We need you to do ADR again.
I was like, OK.
They're like, no, no, you don't understand.
You have to do the whole thing.
Wow.
So I had to dub the entire thing.
And this time we went to like a really sophisticated, fancy ADR studio where there's like a huge theater screen.
Like that's where they do all the like Disney, like the actual Disney movies.
Whoa.
Yeah. So I'm there for like eight to 10 hours.
Jesus.
Like dubbing my own voice.
And they want all the uhs and ums.
So it's like it's I think it sounds a little like not as authentic as it should have sounded like when you sit when you were when you first acted it out because I'm just like trying to, you know, and um, you know, and then also they're like, can you can you make it a little more energetic?
So so it's like the voice probably doesn't match my face in some interesting some like intuitive way, you know, like people watching right just get a little like something's off.
Like that adds it makes like whereas it was kind of like maybe downbeat and naturalistic the first time and then you add to add this thing.
So the combo makes it like just gives it this odd.
Yeah. What is up with this guy?
Yeah. Super. So it's super odd after that.
And but they but I got paid so much more.
Oh wow. Yeah.
Yeah. For all the multiple days.
That's awesome.
Yeah. And and yeah I mean overall I didn't get paid that much more.
Yeah.
I wonder if I'm allowed I don't know if I'm allowed to say how much maybe I can give a it's like it's like closures.
It's like six months, five months of rent.
That's better than I thought.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Actually. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Not a great place but like a decent place.
Yeah.
I you know it kind of makes sense what you're like having to dub yourself you know ADR stuff can be very difficult and stuff but I always saw it like watching it for the first couple of times.
I was like oh this is a fun choice for this character because he's a scientist who probably does not spend all day in front of the camera.
So he's like you know who's not a polished broadcaster as referred to at the beginning.
Yeah, you're a real you're a real guy.
You're not a camera, an on camera presence.
No, he's intelligent and he knows what he's talking about but maybe doesn't do presentations all the time.
I would say it's very charming.
Yeah.
Right, right. Yeah.
No, that that that was what they were going for.
So you got that on the on the nose.
Yeah, they wanted.
They wanted me to be a little fumbling which which was easy because they like gave me all these new lines on the day of.
And then not only that but they wanted me to do it out of order.
And so they're like okay now do this part first and then do that part.
And I'm like oh well that's not the way I had just you know.
Yeah.
Learned it.
And they wouldn't give you a card.
I know that I had I had a monitor sorry teleprompter which was I think an iPad that was like jigged up.
But it was here and the camera was right in front of me and they're like try not to look please look directly into the camera.
So I would do takes where I would look at it and they'd be like no no no no no look directly into the camera.
Yeah.
Wow.
And what you're doing is all I think that's the craziest thing about it is that like you are responsible for introducing so many elements of this world and this like you have to let people know about scanning for micro parasites and the doctor Ogden.
Restarted the Avatar program and that and that we call it a crime but we call them banshees.
It's like it's so many things like those are not easy things to like individually to keep it here let alone to like shuffle around.
Right.
Yeah.
It's not like you know it's not normal vernacular.
Right.
Oh which also wait.
So the one question is not that it would have helped because I've like.
But I guess OK.
My guess is did you know Avatar at all before this.
I watched the movie and I thought the first movie was I thought well it was James depending on.
No let's just be honest here.
I thought it was good but like not super memorable.
So it's weird because when I watched it I was like oh this is a pretty good movie you know.
But for some reason it never stuck around in my mind as some other movies it didn't like stick deep.
Yeah.
I don't know if that's because they're just using the same formulas as some other movies do like once they just don't surprise you and just keep the same formulas they might not.
Sure.
And with you maybe.
Yeah.
But yeah I mean I knew the movie I knew that there was avatars and like you know you control them by getting plugged in somehow.
So I got the basics.
But then it's not like you could have easily.
Oh this is the part where I talk about a week on that or as we call them banshee.
Yeah.
Like that part I didn't remember from the movie.
I don't even know if it's in the movie.
Yeah.
We've only our weird avatar thing is kind of it's bubbled up like I feel like very early in the podcast we started talking about it because of the land and the ride that you're part of.
And then it like I think just by repetition and like just that it kept coming up like that's the only reason we all ended up kind of liking the whole thing is just like we've just like stood in it so much and now I am fond of these like what happened.
We went around this like merry-go-round so many times.
Now I do know it.
I do know the characters and I do like them.
But what a weird thing that like for a movie and a franchise to need like you.
But what you have to do is just weirdly think about it for 13 years and then it'll kick in and you'll start to like let it simmer on the stove for 13 years.
And then it's right.
It's like it's like a fine wine or an aged whiskey.
That's what it is.
That's why I like it so much.
Right.
I one other thing I have to say before we move on from that you having to repeat the whole thing.
We talked about this on the show a while back.
The the ride test track which is at Epcot.
I don't know if you've ever been on it but it's it's a like you it's presented by General Motors and you drive a car really fast.
There is a there used to be this big intro with a bunch of jargon from like a scientist and that was played by John Michael Higgins great comedic actor who I got to work with once.
And of course I'm like oh you want to talk with that ride.
And this whole story was I did the whole thing.
I had to say all this complicated stuff and it was big long takes and it was really hard to do.
And then a couple of weeks went by and they said I need to do ADR.
And I went in and it looks to just a few lines.
No no no the entire thing.
The exact thing that happened to you.
I'm shocked that this you're telling this story when this is the exactly what happened on this other ride years ago.
Oh my gosh.
We need to have like a group like a therapy group for for for for for for those coping with Disney World shoots.
You know what you should do.
There's a band of all like actors on it's called like the band from TV with Greg Grunberg and he plays drums.
You should have a band with all the other guys and girls and everybody in the intro video.
Patrick Warburton.
Gary Sinise.
I think these people are all musicians by the way.
Yes.
John Michael Higgins.
I'm working on my violin so maybe I can work that in.
Or maybe I'll do percussions.
Do you play anything?
I mean no.
I did violin in elementary school and you know I just I just we just had a daughter.
And so I'm like oh I should probably get into some music.
And so I started like I bought like the cheapest violin.
Bad idea because it doesn't sound that great.
And then you know I started like practicing a little bit and doesn't sound good.
So you know you can do lullabies and like Dave Matthews band songs and stuff.
Maybe. Yeah I should I should learn sounds a little.
Yeah.
Twinkle twinkle little stars at my level.
That's nice.
That's good.
That's something.
I guess one question to ask is to go back to the beginning.
How are the the basic stuff like how did you come to be part of this to begin with.
Oh OK.
Yeah.
So I auditioned through Actors Access which is like a casting website.
So it's it was basically not a cattle call where like anyone can go but it was like an
open submission so anyone could submit.
You didn't have to have an agent and it was listed as theme park workshop.
So like I because of this podcast I went back and reread the email and it had asked us to
you know dress comfortably.
Don't wear any lab stuff because we'll provide it for you and be prepared to do improv.
And I remember when I went there it's like they didn't care about the lines.
They just want you to just sort of workshop with them.
Oh yeah.
And so the audition was like a workshop where you just for 10 minutes you just sort of did
all the you know different variations of the of the audition with them.
And then what are you talking about in there because it's not bad with our stuff.
I wouldn't imagine.
Yeah it was it was just like it was basically everything except Avatar.
So like the micro parasites.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Or like yeah you guys you all have them.
I think that was part of the audition.
It's just like you guys all have them but don't worry but you do have them.
And then you know it's just like I just started talking about whatever you know.
Oh they go through photosynthesis which is you know when the when the sun creates when
they're able to produce energy but we're using the sun.
Well you don't need to know that.
You just need to know you're safe.
You know it's just it's just improv.
And then I didn't hear anything for like two months.
And then I get a call from from my agent.
I think it was my agent.
It was probably an email and it just said they want you to audition again for grad student.
This time it was called grad student.
Yeah.
And then I went in and this time they wanted you to get all the words right and just did it.
And then same script essentially.
And and that was it.
And then didn't hear again from them for like a month.
And then they just called and said you know we want you to play this character.
And I didn't know it was for Disney.
I was trying to figure out which theme park it was for.
I was thinking maybe you know Universal or like Knott's Berry Farm.
But I for some reason I didn't think Disney because I couldn't think of any Disney characters.
Right.
That would fit like this sort of scientist guy.
Oh sure.
You know and then it isn't.
Disney movies.
Non Disney at the time.
Yeah.
Oh weird.
Wow.
I love the like successfully getting through the layers of like a mysterious project that
has to be a pretty cool thing as an actor to do.
Yeah.
I mean it's always good when they want you to do something.
But yeah.
And then and then I went to do the shoot.
No no no.
You know there was a lot of prep for it because they wanted to do the wardrobe and I got I
went into the Imagineering Studios.
The one on flowers.
Flowers.
Flowers street.
Yeah.
And it's like that place is like a dream world because everyone there is so passionate you
can tell about their job and they're so meticulous and specific with how they want things done
and but they're also open to like suggestions from each other so it's a very collaborative.
And I also remember there was like a Starbucks there they kept policemen like do you want
something from Starbucks?
There's like a Starbucks inside the facility and everything's free from that Starbucks
for everyone so it's like everything's on your tab on their tab but I don't drink coffee
or anything so I just go no I don't need it and they kept going but it's free it's
like anything you want it's free.
I gotta make something up.
Muffin?
Do they offer a muffin?
No no muffin no I know yeah anything you wanted anything from a Starbucks was there for you
to take for free for everyone not it wasn't just me it was like free for all the workers.
And a workplace where everyone's doing like insane next level stuff and they're all excited
to be there and Starbucks is free.
This is great to hear about.
Would you guys ever want to do stuff an Imagineer type job?
We've only begged on the show many times.
I'd see if I could fit it in.
It's a weird genuinely I'm always like well where do I fit into that because none of us
are engineers the second half of the word we can imagine but the geneering part is where
it gets tougher for me and I have no literal like heart skill when you think about the
level of like a Joe Roddy we'll talk about like who I'm sure like if he like if his whole
career ended at just like he's an incredible matte painter or mural painter like he was
good enough to be that alone so I like I think having the specific skill sets is probably
the toughest thing.
Two friends of ours I think we can say right because it was tweeted about two friends of
ours rode a ride that's coming to Universal.
So like that aspect where it's something that's like the mini we're talking about Van Robe
Show and Evan Susser wrote Dominion's Ride.
We're saying yeah VillainCon.
So Evan and Van you've heard them on the show.
Friends of the show are right amazing.
Pretty crazy.
Yeah.
So like in that like they wrote a lot of I think I don't know if I'm going to get jokes
and stuff and like set up.
They're not crunching numbers or anything.
So like in that aspect I believe yeah this would this would be great.
Now do I also think I could maybe conceptualize a new ride.
Yes I do think that.
But I'm just saying I think from like at least from a standpoint of like oh if not to Barry
Farma at some like simple little thing where we need we could write some fun copy and come
up with a scenario.
Yeah I love anything like that is a dream.
Yeah because you already pitched some good stuff here for the Avatar ride that making
fun of things would have been great.
Dr. Stevens Rose.
Well wait I just thought of what it could be.
It's like hang on we have to scan for something.
An ugly hat.
You have one.
Great.
Perfect.
Oh yeah.
These are good auditions for that job.
Yeah yeah yeah.
So we're trying to illustrate it by Doug.
Well and the specific thing that you got to do which is like I've always been obsessed
like somebody being in the video that plays all day every day somewhere.
Something that happened on this show once was that I found an opening somehow successfully
to film a video where I was an astronaut that played in a Fry's electronics in Anaheim
for two days before it closed.
And this was me trying to do what you got to do.
I was just like if I could get any weird just for two days that's great.
That's a dream come true.
So this thing where like I'm a guy and I'm telling you rules about something and make
sure you press the button.
And it was like fake.
It was like a make a wish thing they made up for me.
But it was still it was like the coolest thing ever.
So what you got to do this thing where like you're playing into infinity forever.
It's it's it's it's so impressive that I'm very impressed.
Well thanks.
Yeah.
So you were so was it like a commercial for Fry's electronic where you were an astronaut
that was like so confusing by this TV or something.
There might be a whole there's Fry's electronics things behind you in here.
I went to a fry.
I really like fries electronics in general because they had all these great themes.
It was a themed electronics store and the one in Anaheim was space themed.
And I went into it one day and there was a video that played where a guy is like we're
about to launch and you need to press the red button to make sure that we have a successful
launch.
They're really mini version of what you did for real.
And I was like why is this playing only here in this one store.
That's so weird.
Maybe this is my chance.
Let's red tape.
I don't have to go through.
I don't have to do the workshops and all this stuff you had to jump through.
I'm not a real actor so I don't have to prove that I'm a real actor.
So somehow we got a hold of Fry's people and they were like yeah the store is closing anyway.
It's fine.
Put it in there.
And they played it for a weekend before it is as all the listeners know about this already.
Wow.
So you made it independently and then gave it to them to play.
We tweeted it.
We tweeted it out.
And then our listeners were like this maybe shows that this is the way we can maybe help
you out and try to get you in an amateur film.
Our listeners were like Fry's you got to see this.
Boy Fry's this video is great.
And then it genuinely did make it to somebody deep in the Fry's.
I don't think I've even said the whole I can't say everything about this but it had to go
all the way up the flagpole.
It actually did and that's it.
All I'm at liberty to say but somebody very powerful had to go.
All right.
Why not.
That's great.
Yeah.
Let's try to get a scientist spec thing together and to get us on Avatar.
Sure.
We do our own workshop.
Yeah.
These guys improvise.
I'll try to fake my way through it.
You'll be fine.
I'll do it.
I'll just repeat all my astronaut stuff.
Maybe if we just put our like make it and we record it on a VHS we slip it to a cast
member on the ride and one day for some reason there's four scientists in their lab.
That would be hilarious.
Scanning for germs.
Yeah.
That would be great.
Come on.
I have to consult with Dr. Robinson and Dr. Miller.
Dr. Miller.
Dr. Jones.
Are you the hot dog Dr. Miller?
Yeah I was.
In the lab?
And now it's a bumbling set of four scientists.
I do like this.
Disney Creative Campus locked down today after mysterious VHS dropped at the mail drop.
Were there secret messages in it?
Was it a bomb?
Was it a threat?
VHS.
It's like we don't know what's in it because we don't have a VCR.
We don't know how to play this.
There's no way to find out where the technology is not here.
One of the three fillases in the valley where we could play this VHS thanks to being the
second largest media company in the world.
So you do get through all the layers of this and you wait first of all it's like it's prep
and it's shooting you're out here on the Engineering Campus.
That's all a dream.
That's crazy.
And then the shoot.
What's the shoot like?
Oh the shoot was great.
They rented out a sound stage in North Hollywood or Sun Valley area.
And they set up the stages.
They had Dr. Ogden's stage.
And the woman that plays her was great.
She was also in a bunch of other stuff.
I think maybe just that's her voice.
I forget what else she's in.
But she was sort of like you know like sort of like being around the block like oh yeah
this is your first Disney shoot.
Wow really?
I don't care.
No no no in a good way.
But it was like oh yeah this is my first.
Wow.
She's showing you the road.
She's like oh I got stories.
Yeah she's like I'm also in I forget some other ride she does the voice for.
We don't know this.
I feel like god it sounds familiar.
I mean I've forgotten stuff but that's interesting.
Maybe it's in Disneyland where she does the voice.
So I can figure it out.
It's possible we did a whole episode on this and I forgot.
Yeah yeah it happens a lot.
They're not the easiest thing to find credits for at attractions.
Yeah yeah that's true.
But that's cool because Dr. Ogden is your mentor and Dr. Stevens now that we know specifically
Dr. Stevens is a grad student so who may be.
That's a question.
Do you have it in your head that maybe you like looked up to Dr. Ogden?
Yeah yeah yeah that was part of it.
She's someone I looked up to and they really wanted me to keep you know saying her name
like I look up to her.
I don't know if it comes through that I keep saying Dr. Ogden.
We noticed.
That's one of the funniest that you're in this room for so long and we are getting all this
information and about worlds and cultures and you're gonna fly but then within that
you need to know that Dr. Ogden is great.
Dr. Ogden wrote a book.
Dr. Ogden restarted the program.
So that's funny it was similar it was funny to do to read all that.
It's coming back to me now they're just like you really look up to Dr. Ogden.
Dr. Ogden.
Okay.
We have talked about before like man they really like Dr. Ogden.
Do you think that Dr. Stevens got ever got to meet Dr. Ogden or was there a distance
was it somebody you like read in grad school or like did you have a relationship or did
she blow you off in the office?
Do you have any sense of further mythology?
Oh you mean like the backstory of Dr. Stevens and Dr. Ogden?
Yeah okay yeah coming from me and how I played it it was yes we had like training back in
the home base wherever that is and then I got shipped to like Antarctica like some sort
of remote station where I'm just sort of explaining things to people and I'm like all alone and
so that's why it's like oh I haven't talked to people in a long time so this is why I'm
sort of you know talking to people like this because I'm just isolated it's just you know
oh people yeah I know how to talk to you yeah so this is what you do.
This is what you were playing the feeling that all of everyone had coming out of the
pandemic like yes I know how to be at a party I can talk how have you been how is your life
like we were all everyone was like Dr. Stevens after all that.
Oh yeah after the pandemic everyone was yeah a lot of strange behaviors.
Yeah the first part the first party genuinely I went to the first half hour I'm like are
you a maniac what are you have you not said sentences in your life every lights are shining
I'm like I'm recoiling I want to go in a cave.
They made a funny SNL sketch about this I don't know if you guys saw the there was like
an SNL sketch video about so yeah it was it was it was funny a lot not all their stuff
is great but this one was sorry I mean I love you but some of this stuff is you know you
do it every week so it's hard yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
if they're batting 250 then that's you only remember the good stuff from the compilation
we like what we grew up with in high school.
Go back that was your favorite that was your favorite cast.
The actress Dr. Ogden was her name is at the top of the page Allison Blanchard and she
was the it's it says luggage scan computer in star tours.
Oh so does that mean that's not the there's the Patrick Warburg robot but then there's
is it like midway through the line.
So yeah there's some voices checking in.
There's the x-ray if yeah with the robot but I can't remember if that how audible those
lines are.
So that might be something she did yeah yeah yeah there before you uh well you get getting
into that I guess that's a that's a huge question probably a lot of people have is like the
awkwardness that was completely a designed that is a that was that was what they wanted
that's a choice it's what you were you were going for.
Um yeah yeah I mean if you if you judge my baseline as this and then see how far away
Dr. Stevens is I mean it's sort of a little bit you know it's like always part of you
how you are so yeah I mean it's it's just like an extension of that I just played on
it a little more plus the dubbing you know made it extra awkward probably yeah or maybe
not I don't know maybe the dubbing didn't make it awkward it's just in my mind it's
just like right that's not that's not my voice like this doesn't match but they're just like
no no it's perfect yeah if it's the yeah the weird thing must be like the rhythm of saying
the ums like having to like remember like you don't know your own vocal patterns that
well to like no no no it was a quarter of a second before the um not a half second yeah
it's I mean it's like doing a karaoke with oh yeah because the words are there and there's
like a little bar that you have to like try to match and it's just sounds right there's
something visual yeah yeah oh yeah these places that they try to give you all the help you
can there's like there's a beep and then there's like this line going through of like where
the where sorry hit the mic where it where the words are like where you should say them
and then the words are underneath and it's just like karaoke basically with your own
interesting I wonder if this is common with all these ride videos for some weird reason
yeah what is the why do they need the timing wise or something like is it like did they
like speed it up a half second or something or a quarter of a second and then like you
know come like come in and do it a little faster like I wonder I wonder what yeah why
that might be common I mean my theory is just that they don't shoot a lot of stuff like
like Imagineers do a lot of stuff but one of the things they don't do is like film production
and they don't hire a sound guy maybe this they don't hire any sound guy yeah they don't
know a good guy they need a good guy where was the guy holding the stick thing oh we
didn't have them yeah so who's making the call this time it's like I'll call the actor
you get it then you get it in 15 years when this happens again oh go back to the imagineering
thing I didn't see anyone there that looked like an engineer that like builds things they
were all like artistic right so I think it's a lot in the name like sure just add the engineer
so so you guys have a lot of potential posts to fill look direct I've directed for television
I would love I've also I've made ride videos for rides that don't exist I've done every
possible yeah every possible addition for this kind of thing and then it's and now I'm hearing
that they can't I've done things with a sound person I know how to get the sound right can
I sound engineer this podcast that's where what am I talking about you do it all the time you've
logged kidding me thousands of hours I guess what I'm auditioning for is to run sound on ride
videos you'd love it though I know you'd like to go higher than that but when you do to be there
to watch every raw take of every video say this the sound person is always the most interesting
person on set hmm they're just always for some reason like I'm like this person's lived the life
like yeah like there's something about people that are obsessed with sound that makes them
more interesting I know that seems vague but it's truly I don't have a specific type of person I'm
talking about it just always there's somebody's hyper focused on sound and I'm always like oh
okay sound this is the sound person is I agree with you and I think there's also just in the
way they like you see them working with equipment or like hooking up your mic or someone else's
mic it's that kind of quiet confidence that like if you if you have a regular mechanic and they
just start doing stuff without looking at it yeah it's interesting I don't know why that is but the
guy who did all the sound for everything at Funny or Die was the used to be the drummer for Yngwie
Malmsteen perfect so he's in like old like you know crazy European hair metal videos in the early
90s wow that's what you're after yes like is what I'm after yeah this guy must have a story oh yeah
that's a good one um but anyway uh but back to the shoot I'm sure what other stuff about well I
was asking about like the the awkwardness in the case you know this I think maybe has to be
brought up a phrase that has not been said yet in this episode and that phrase is you know what
I'm going for uh uh uh fly uh and this this clearly is that I think there's a couple iconic
things that you say in this but that that takes the cake and you've probably I imagine this has
come back to you in a it's on t-pub people have made shirts yeah and shirts and yeah I've got
friends send me links to these shirts yeah is that legal can they do that not technically yeah I don't
know though it's if it's not oh I guess I guess if it's like that's a phrase in the world you can say
uh fly yeah as long as it's not like a picture of an acron on it yeah is there I wonder if I should
sell I maybe I should do and a shirt or something that sounds legal I think so yeah I think you're
fine on that and we know look that for a long time at least until this new movie the avatar font
papyrus and that's just free on every computer so you can use papyrus without a problem hey real
real retweet it yeah yeah of course yeah I mean or maybe and uh podcast the ride shirts
oh man that was exciting to hear we'll split the revenue but yeah yeah it's it's a it's a it's a
it was I guess it was improvised but come on it's just a line it's not really like you know
it was improvised though I don't know that's pretty big it I mean I just sort of rephrased the line
I forget what it was was it just and fly and I added uh or was it maybe that's it maybe that
was it and I probably don't remember super well because you did not expect that to be the thing
that is latched onto hey I just remember whatever the line was before that I started saying and I'll
fly and and uh I think Joe roadie was like keep that keep that you know he's whoa I love that whoa
well because we're full in Chris Farley show mode right now yes I know absolutely
uh
well I didn't know who Joe roadie was I just knew he was like the passionate guy on set with like
yeah like a lot of stuff on his ears and like I was like oh this guy's different and he's really
into everything because there was like three directors there was Joe roadie there was like
some guy from Disney and then there was like another guy from Disney but from different
departments I don't know if one of them's like corporate Disney and one was like theme park
Disney and then it's like Joe roadie is like the creative guy that's like trying to push for the
creative ideas right uh so there's like three voices you know do this do this do this coming
up to me each time yeah is that confusing it's very confusing yeah you have to like figure out
who's the guy in charge it's sort of like commercials you guys have done commercials where
you're like who's the guy in charge yes I just listened to whoever whoever last told me what to
do anyone can tell you anything I'll do it yeah exactly the last person to tell you something
you're like got it the camera you're telling me like go in the front of the camera and say these
and I go like yes yeah yeah in that case sometimes the most unnerving thing is when the director is
very chill and laid back and just like I'll just try it a few ways well we'll record it all whatever
and you're like oh but what is what are the people from hostess have to say there's about
a dozen of them by the way Jason I saw your hulu you your hulu commercial it's so good
yeah it's like actually pretty funny you know and you're like perfect in there you're just like
oh what about plus uh hulu plus yeah that was one where it's like everyone was an improv uh train
performer and actor and everyone was very chill and uh it was really nice time yeah so I don't
know if you're allowed to talk about this we can edit it out right yeah sure okay yeah so so everyone
did you guys all improvise that together like with your pitches of like hulu I they did a lot of alts
like everyone tossed out a bunch so they had a bunch to go and then there was like 15 second
version of the spot 30 second version uh try this ending okay try this ending um there is a bunch of
endings where it is uh said that I am the main guy's nephew uh and everyone got gets mad at me
because they didn't know I was in nepotism higher the the main guy being the guys like give me ideas
the lead the ringleader guy yeah who also we we later learned that like um uh we were talking
about UCB and stuff and he he brought up our friend Zach Reno who's been on this show before
and he's like oh I performed his wedding and I was like I was at that wedding so we were in the same
place before oh wow wow so mild nepotism mild yeah so so yeah a few degrees of separation
that's a hell of a backstory yeah yeah they're not clear to the hulu ad viewers no now you know
yeah you know all the secrets of dr steven's and if uh yeah I don't know if you're allowed to
because you always sign all this stuff but it's like who cares you know but also I don't want to
give you money back um what I want to say about the the uh fly thing well first of all like because
roadie I feel like has helped make it a thing because you retweeted so that there was like a
poll of you can all right here's three sort of like what we did three like pre-ride videos or
doctor people and you can only keep one and and roadie himself said has to be the uh fly guy
and which I love seeing because his typical I guess as you experience you met the man you
worked with the man he his his typical mode seems to be like flowery language big eloquent
paragraphs so seeing him say something as blunt as the uh fly guy I thought was kind of charmingly
off brand yeah and he must have enjoyed getting like the the props from him for that oh yeah yeah
he's he was like the most supportive person on set like he made me feel really confident because he
it was like the opposite of what you're saying where the director doesn't say anything he was
just saying I love he would he would be like dr argh agden is straight is like a straight like not
straight but you know um uh traditional sort of type of character like a sort of traditional
high status character that do you get at the parks and he's like and then this character is
just sort of you know all over the place it's like I love it I love it it's gonna it's gonna
blow their minds because he wanted to blow he wanted people to be like you know this isn't
normal Disney stuff that that's what he was saying and like the whole time I'm like so you're saying
I'm not doing like it's not polished like and you like it you know it's like okay
but he was like he was just you know very encouraging yeah huh yeah he like he kind of
like caught how you were generally doing it and said keep going further in that direction
and you like you sort of like found this mode for it together right right that's pretty cool yeah
he also do you know that he did this big instagram post about dr stevens and why it's
important to the fabric of the ride have you come across this I got tagged I think
yeah yeah I think I remember reading it what it was positive right it was it was very positive
and we've we've talked on the show a lot about Joe roadies posts as I was saying he'd like
some little things some like the you know a frame of a picture a detail up on the roof he will
here is a long long rationale for why this is important yeah that it is the way that it is
and this I don't I can't I don't want to read the entire thing but it's a big breakdown
specifically of uh but then it gets into other stuff about about your performance let me just
let me do some of it uh how I love that the word uh is so pivotal to the characterization and plot
that it must be translated for people who cannot hear meaning that it's in the captions
it's in the closed captions on the ride and that a distorted fish eye lens view of an ill shaven man
who seems unsure of what to say is the preamble to a major theme park experience at animal kingdom
we're always trying to place our design in that right place where you're not quite sure is this
really real is it supposed to be real but it's not real is this a mistake and I'm not supposed
to be seeing it like it ties into his greater animal kingdom feelings about well when is it
contrived and when is it just nature being nature and how do we trick you like he's including your
beard the choice of your facial hair in like in the fabric of why the the ride is successful
yeah I mean that was their choice they you know they told me to come in ill shaven wow yeah wow
ill shaven it was on the on the notes before the before was that literally no no it wasn't that
they said to come in you know with some stubble I think sure maybe was the word
uh regular person says it ill shaven it's very judgmental that was the only the barest roasting
of you on this episode is the the implication that you were not good at shaving yeah yeah but it was
a choice yeah it was yeah because you know you always go on set with like a razor and like
you know whatever because they're always like uh keep it or let's shave it or maybe just a mustache
I've never done a mustache maybe I should do a mustache I've never done a mustache it'd be a
tie you'll probably get something specifically because of the at least one thing we want that
mustache guy yeah Jason's mustache is pretty good oh thanks yeah and yours yours is a full beard
I got a full beard yeah Jason I mean Jason sort of I guess Jason has a goatee-ish
I during during like lockdown era pandemic I would shave just the mustache like I was just well
just as like when you would come up with ways to amuse yourself I was like I'm gonna try having
a mustache for a while and I remember Mike we got on a zoom once and he went well we'll talk about
it
and then we never did it never came up yeah I forgot I forgot I was like oh he's gonna make this the
first I made I may have thought like oh wow look how different it is and then as soon as we started
I go no it's good and that's how you've always had it like I may have just absorbed it I well I
think I shaped all the rest of the beard off except a mustache I just accepted it I mean the
history Jason you've ended up having to be on edge probably in every episode of I have done
something two percent different that surely this will take up 15 minutes you're never gonna believe
how they say this word in southeast Pennsylvania and we're gonna talk about it 10 percent of the
podcast is just saying what word did you say I really is I feel like if I ever met anyone from
that area it would never come up it's just it's always unfamiliar to me it's all new to me it
bleeds into my real life because Jane Jane is started calling out when I say milk
is it more of a milk it's it's more okay yeah it kind of sounds like me lk right she's like
milk milk you repeat and you can't think yeah what's the simpsons up and at them
yeah the goggles do nothing
I was thinking about a simpsons thing in relation to all that that you being
getting this thing that you improvised becoming a he's this guy he's the a flag guy this is similar
to Bart being the I didn't do it guy right is it weird in any context to be like
to have that phrase in your head like the something guy uh you know it's not weird to me
because the only way I hear about is if I have to do an active search online I have to do like
and uh fly in quotations and then and then I can start but like I would not have known about any
of this unless like friends send me links right so it's not like something I think about but when
I do go and read the the stuff uh yeah sometimes it's like there's like you guys are making me feel
good but I've I've gone and read the comments sometimes and there's like a lot of you know
there's some people that uh prefer dr stevens be uh removed and oh no no never yeah and like
sometimes it's you it's usually um you know my weaker stages of time to time we become weak and
sure it's usually late at night and you're just like oh I haven't googled myself in a while yeah
and you just like do a little google and then you're like oh this didn't bother me that much
I can go further and you start you know look looking further and further and then you and then
you start it starts like hurting your feelings a little bit um and to the point where you're like
you start clicking on their profile and like trying to see like whether their comment is of value
you know it's like oh well they only have 13 followers this comment that you count um uh it's
all negative I shouldn't be doing it and but but now I've gotten better at it where it's like I'm
okay it's like it doesn't hurt my feelings anymore as much yeah we'll see then then what happens is
I start digging more and more until I find one that that hits uh like you need to kind of like
get the little zap yeah almost like I just want to I don't know I gotta feel it a tiny bit and then
I'll like oh I remember once I I clicked on some guy and it's the guy that co-wrote the pixel movie
have you remember that movie pixel yeah it's with adam sandler yeah yeah the guy hates the pre-show
what dr stevens yeah he hates him and it's and it's like I'm just like why why is this guy like
why does he care about it so much that he has to like tweet I guess he's like a super disney fan
and like it's it's messing with his vision of the way disney should be but um we gotta find this
comment yeah it's uh oh I know these names there's two writers it's like the younger writer guy
there's there's two writers one of them I've heard of this person okay okay yeah but then
but then I started looking up dirt on him and then I'm like okay so you're gonna dis me let me go see
some sure and then I looked up I was like oh pixel won a razzie a razzie is an award for the worst
movie yeah I was gonna say you didn't have to go very far to get to the phrase co-writer pixels
it's right in there isn't it yeah come on co-writer of pixel yeah so it's like I have to find
something to like to level off the that that's my yeah unhealthy hat therapy of of that so do you
find enough positive or just like for being having fun with it that it feels better than this is this
is the whole thing for you has been more fun than than not you know the positive always comes in
person like I went to um a uh uh give the kids a village is a non-profit oh right yeah in orlando
give kids the world give the kids the world okay yes and so they they had this big convention
where they wanted to you know fly in all of these disney uh persons like the uh I think it was the
voice of aladdin or maybe it's the voice of little mermaid you know all of these different disney uh
people notable performers notable performers thank you you're the professional you know how to
how to extract what what i'm trying to say uh and and uh one of the and uh see I guess I just do it
normally um one of the one of the panels were the theme park um theme park theme park specific
yeah yeah and so I went there with and I don't I don't really go to Disneyland or Disney World so
I don't really know oh yeah yeah yeah but there was like the woman from the haunted
mansion and then there was the fig the fig puppet fig fig fig fig the dragon yeah yeah uh-huh he
was super nice he because so it's like so so I'm going and I'm and I was talking I was like so what
it's okay I didn't finish the story um ah sorry guys no no so so give the kids the world oh yeah
yeah I've created this um convention where all the money goes to their foundation to help the
kids that they help and so you know I went out there and then the people that actually saw the
panel were very uh uh loving and yeah gave a lot of praise so I guess in real life the interactions
I got were all positive but you know how uh the internet and twitter and all that stuff is oh yeah
do you guys ever read bad comments about the podcast the ride or if there were
no we don't get fixated on every bad thing that gets said any mild criticism
well the two things I I have feel like I've had a couple reactions one it's every now and then
you just double check yeah the other person's post and and sometimes you go like oh they're insane
nice don't have to worry about this and then the other is like they hone in on something so
particular so odd and then it's just like I never I'm not insecure about this because it never would
have occurred to me to even be remotely insecure about this so yeah yeah fair enough if you don't
relate to it at all and who care yeah it's tougher if it's something you you care about or something
I mean you know what's a scarring moment in podcast history for me that almost got me off
of doing podcast it almost made me go I don't like doing podcasts before we started doing this
podcast with many many episodes when I was on I was on the show dough boys which is a podcast
about chain restaurants I was a guest on it and I felt comfortable when it started but then when
it began I was like wait I've never really been on a podcast have I oh I'm sure it'll be fine
the next day a comment or somebody tags me on twitter and says say um and like more motherfucker
just in my replies and it truly made me like well I will stay out of that game forever and a
I'm so glad I I didn't but to bring it back to to your performance and uh like you told us this stuff
about being sounding like slick and broadcasters I don't feel that way at all and I like that you
did this like non-polished performance with an uh with an iconic uh in it as somebody who does
say it from time to time but he still wants to try to be funny in front of a microphone it's nice to
have a uh celebrated people to like it a lot yeah for sure I'll uh I'll take that thank you yeah
it's a nice moment for the for the unpolished in general yeah
yeah and on your your character is an unpolished hero I guess oh yeah standing up for all the
unpolished having an impressive job it's it's right it's interesting because again I truly mean
it like when yeah because you felt it like meeting theme park fans who are some of the most rabid
fans of anything but does it feel like you should be like doing the con of convention circuit no
right I don't know I don't I think I the way I think of it is like I'm only
in like recognizable in Orlando like in that area certainly maybe those specific conventions
but like there's Anaheim wonder con stuff like that I don't know I don't know maybe I'll
like people we know around everybody listens to show it would be so psyched yes that's
absolutely absolutely true I think people are going to be very excited to hear you on the show
yeah yeah I hope so I hope uh I hope uh I hope they there's another tweet that I got so I get
tagged on stuff yeah so then I look at it one of them was there's like three pictures of different
Disney uh scientists yeah one of them is putty from yeah yeah yeah and then one of them is uh
this other person that I don't know and then there's me and then it was like Mary F kill
Dr. Stevens was killed so you know um I haven't seen the other people I mean the putty is like
you know he's looked he's pretty good looking I guess uh they're traditionally using their
marrying putty or their uh fucking putty I don't because I don't know his like character's name
I'm thinking there doesn't have a name I don't know yeah maybe but then what isn't if it's
Wallace Langham in the ride dinosaur which is my guess I think it was Dr. Seeker I believe
doctor that's a crazy choice Dr. Seeker is a slime ball that's not somebody that's who you kill you
would be the least popular Dr. Stevens with no ill intention for anybody you're a guy doing your job
I think you're a Mary oh thank you thank you I think you have sex with putty
with Dr. Seeker sleazy in Vegas and that's I guess what people are thinking maybe
putty's more of the like uh you have a I'm just saying putty now I said he's the character but uh
this is a tough choice and when it's a group of three that's what we are I don't want it don't
kill me or f in the pilot or whatever the hell he's a pilot right yeah yeah
so unnamed pilot thing unnamed uh soaring pilot and I'm marrying Dr. Stevens oh um that's that's
very nice I think that's the universally correct choice I'm not I think yeah I totally agree
the um there's one there's another tweet that I don't think is a mean I don't think I'm I'm uh
I'll offend you by saying this but I was curious anybody's Dr. Stevens tweets and here's one from
Just Mateo a couple years ago here's what you think of this I've seen arguments over which
Disney character is a Republican or Democrat but I think we can all agree that Dr. Stevens from
the Flight of Passage pre-show forgot to register to vote oh yeah yeah I think I think Dr. Stevens
is like a uh yeah he's he's not he's not a voter he's got too much stuff on his mind yeah you're
out of the country you know you need an absentee first of all with mail-in ballots I think I think
he's a mail-in he's a mail-in guy he has he's an independent mail-in guy but you maybe like forget
because you're busy like because the way that like you said the way the camera you go oh right I have
to talk on camera maybe you're also like uh I got these lab results to go through oh wait shit oh
the ballot when was that two months ago crap yeah yeah yeah I mean I don't know if you guys uh
go political here but I think Dr. Stevens is um not for you know I'm not gonna do it
I'm so curious I was like where's the line no I'm not gonna okay it's just you can certainly
keep it to yourself Dr. Stevens you don't want to reveal all the all the recesses of Dr. Stevens
sorry yeah um but he let but if Dr. Ogden switched into politics uh and ran for office you know he's
supporting Dr. Ogden that much we know yeah probably I mean Governor Ogden yeah I guess so yeah
I'm trying to think what else to ask here I mean we've covered a lot of ground for sure
I had something I was wondering because I had heard um someone who did music for a part of
universal once and they were like well I should really get down there one of these days like uh
I should see the Spider-Man ride my kids are teenagers would they like it and the I'm listening
this interview I'm like yeah man I think your teenagers would like Spider-Man ride you were
part of yeah yeah uh have you been to Pandora have you read it have you seen yourself oh right oh yes
okay this is a little story which I've never told um okay so when I went to that convention
that was the first time I went uh right to Orlando yeah yeah and um it's not it's not in Disney
World it's just in one of these hotels nearby right it might have been a Disney World hotel
that they rented um and I had never been to the ride and I didn't have a ticket because Disney
never offered right you know which has a little while so so this was a non-profit organization
giving me flying me to Orlando and uh the host of the panel I started talking to him his name was
Mark uh Mark Daniel I believe um and I might be getting his last name wrong uh and he said
I told him I'd never been on the ride he and he was like flabbergasted like what you've never been
on the right we got to go right now and it's like 4 p.m. Orlando time I had flown in on red on a
red eye and woke up at like noon like an hour before the so it's like I I was very uh out of it
and he goes we got to get you to the ride and I'm like okay let's do it and so he had a season pass
but he had to go to like a different park to get checked in and then then he could go to any park
this is recent so it's all like yeah Disney World's insane yeah you can't park off yeah this was like
last year yeah oh and so I go on the I go into uh is it Animal Kingdom it's yeah we go into
Animal Kingdom we walk in and it's like almost closing time and there's no line so we just walk
through the whole thing like the whole there's no line for that's crazy by the passage we walk all
the way through and then you see the big avatar who which is huge I didn't realize how huge it was
yeah in the tank in the tank the avatar in the tank is huge yeah it's like 10 feet tall um uh
and then you know I'm wearing a mask so no one is noticing me it was during COVID during the middle
it's more of a it was like last year so more so masks were sort of required I believe right um
um so I see myself and I'm like oh my gosh that's so funny I've never you know have you seen even a
video off on YouTube I've seen the video on YouTube but it just felt a little surreal seeing
you know yeah seeing it right there and then and I was in the back so nobody could see me so then
I turned around and did a little selfie I like took the mask down took did a little selfie
and took a picture of you know me with the with the uh pre-show in the back and you know he does
he says all his stuff move around a little bit yeah it's sort of I mean it's sort of like uh
it's sort of like you know it's just I think most people to go to the ride maybe are just
not too pushed either love them or hate them they're just sort of like oh this is just part
of the ride sure um so you know we go through the flight of passage pre-show and then I get on the
ride which is like sort of like a bicycle seat and then yeah you strap on and there's a big screen
and the ride starts and it's incredible because it just feels like you're flying
yeah and then there's little sprays coming at you and it's just incredible and then I'd say like a
minute into the ride I start to get nauseous wow like I'm just like whoa I'm feeling sick like
what's going on and then and then uh you know I can hear like Mark next to me he's loving it he's
just like whoa yes he's like repeating lines that they're saying you know because because there's
one avatar that's like you're sort of following that's like guiding you along right yeah um or
ekron one one banshee yeah and I'm just feeling really sick at some point I like close my eyes
and it's like I can't take it anymore because like it's making me like it feels like I'm gonna
throw up and I'm just sweating and sweating and when the ride's over uh Mark looks up at me and
he's just like wasn't that incredible and then I go yes it was and I didn't tell him like I was
sweating so much but it it uh it was so humid it was during the summer or September months so it was
it could have just been the heat but I the ride for me was yes it's I I don't I can't do those
rides I could do a roller coaster just fine the 3d is probably the 3d yeah universal studios has a
lot of those now a lot yeah and I had the same thing happen to me I think the harry potter ride
I had to just close my eyes it was just like this is a really similar really nausea and yeah I even
get a lot I do it but I get a little like tingle of it but people love it I think it's just that
I'm like like older and as a kid maybe I didn't have do those rides I don't know or maybe it's
you're like yeah it was like you didn't get it you're the immunity yeah I didn't get the
early immunity yeah so yeah to answer your question Jason I went on the ride and it made me sick wow
wow the person who explains the ride before it was back it was a major part of the experience
we had a tough time on the ride yeah that's pretty crazy yeah um so uh so you were not fully prepared
to uh fly no no I wasn't yeah you wouldn't do it again no I it was not a fun experience the first
part was the first minute was incredible and then after that it's just like get me out of here it's
just like not ending wow yeah um a question about that video that I guess I'm curious about that
feeling like does it ever just hit you out of nowhere like oh there's that video of me playing
right now there's strangers watching me across the country right now and then there will be again in
10 minutes and then in an hour and then again tomorrow that's interesting you know I've never
thought of it like that I I don't know how I feel about that I think if I really think about it I
would not feel too good because it's like it's like you know I would I because of the dubbing
thing it's like I don't want you know I feel I feel a little like it's not fully representative
right so so yeah I guess I wouldn't feel too good about it but you know uh they can change it if
they want I wouldn't feel bad about that if they if they decided to change it would you not really
yeah I don't think I would feel bad about it huh huh yeah because it was just addressed we haven't
talked about this in the little Feliz Navidad season that James Cameron said when Eiger got
reinstalled uh I you know I told Eiger hey I'd love to I'd redo the ride and we could do like an
underwater thing for the new movie so there wasn't the talk of do we put a different uh
ride film in there not that anything was said about would we change the pre-show
but it certainly could happen because they might have to explain now how you ride a what's do you
know the name of the other the creature no I'm going in cold I don't I want to know the water
one do you know you want to cover your ears no oh okay it's the yaloo the yaloo sorry the mighty
aloo are we going with mighty are we sticking with mighty you're still going to determine that hey
let the king uh see the movie first before I was just giving a name to uh uh in vulture they say
you've met the mighty cron now yes yes that was nice to see yeah yeah tagged us we have this whole
thing mike uh invented he started saying this phrase the when you get on about the ride when
you get on the ride and you get on the mighty acron and you ride on the mighty acron and then
we were starting to go like I think we you might have even thought that was something that David
said in it I knew or the mighty editor it's in the movie but it's not apparently it's it's only he
said it so when mike googled the phrase ultimately all of the results were him if you look up mighty
acron it's just me in this podcast so are they did they incorporate that in the also okay the
fall we've we discussed a little bit but but in the new trailer for the one of the one of the
trailers for the new movie there's a shot where they just what are they asking for a description
of it's talking about like what is it like to feel a was heartbeat right there god and there's a big
long pause and then the character goes mighty and then there's a cut to the water acrons flying and
we were like this feels very weird purposeful mighty's not like a thing that all the navis said
in the first movie or anything so anyway that got to them someone listened to the podcast and then
someone pitched it probably like it probably wasn't written and someone pitched it and then
they're like okay let's let's try mighty it's like can we do it again but say mighty this time
I have a pitch and then boom mighty yeah I'll let you say it and not not take the credit ourselves
where that's a nice theory so you're saying they're going to change the software sort of like the video
that's being shown and I don't think it's an official plan something James Cameron maybe
wants to do in success of the the movie which I wish it's success I think it's gonna get it but
the uh so so if that happens and then suddenly you find out there's a new video you really you're
fine you had your time oh yeah yeah I would be perfectly fine with that yeah wow yeah but
be perfect if they want if they need somebody to tell us talk about what it's like to uh to
get in a link chair and board an an elu uh and maybe learn about maybe a different doctor's
experience training the elu would you be up for the job again um good question I think I would
want someone else to do it but I would want to do like a little cameo you know oh cool maybe just
like one thing so I don't have to do all the all the dubbing again that's fair well what if uh I
mean there's got to be a way to like that you're like you're in the back like your your chair is
turned and then the the new person who's talking needs to like then these you know and these
characters swim as opposed to the ekron who what's that we're um dr stevens could you help me out
yeah you have to roll in back in and just be like all right guys let's get ready to and uh swim yeah
yeah I think it has to be you'll just do that just that's all I would do yeah yeah same money
though as last time yeah yeah roll in the frame and your hair is white and you have an eye patch
and everyone's like what happened to dr what happened to him between rice this is it's been a
tough 40 years for yeah dr stevens uh that this is great well at least this needs to happen this is
where we can start james cameron do do more as much with david as you want to do this I feel like
at least the cameo I'm glad you pitched that um I well I mean we're kind of coming to the end and
this is anything else you want to say about the experience but there's you know there's a little
thing I'll veer into but uh and I don't know any like anything we did we did not get to about this
whole weird no I feel like I told you about how I got sick on the ride one and only time I told
you about the shoot I told you about the audition I told you about the mean tweets
dumb wrong mean tweets yeah I don't know I think yeah that's a lot there's well um there's one more
little thing if I could spring on you and I um I asked about you you brought up violin I asked
about the music abilities and it probably it doesn't really matter here but there's something
that we have been ending these episodes with because it's the Feliz Navidad the way of winter
we've been doing little uh uh Christmas carols at the end of the episodes or as we call them
amati kaya carols that's for the name of the tribe in the movie and we've just been singing
these silly songs at the end of the episodes and I have a song prepared which has a two line
cameo for you speaking of cameos uh would you be up for doing a brief uh part in a song that uh
that I'm gonna perform uh yeah uh do I need do you want to email to me or do I have it I have it
printed out printed out and and you'll know your part is in bold and then gentlemen at the at the
end it's all uh oh sure yeah thanks we're gonna uh at the end there's italics and um the uh so
that's where maybe we can all come in but one last amati kaya carol and I think you'll know the part
and I think you'll know the song but I'll cue you too um but here I do one take there
did you guys did you guys rehearse it oh no no no they they they haven't okay we don't know
what it is yeah okay uh okay so apologies if there's any you're viewing the brunt of it
yes but everybody everybody come in at the end everyone is coming in at the end let's end in
in in full harmony can I turn it over yet oh yeah oh sure no no go ahead okay okay okay
I'll hand you this oh sure yeah and uh this is great thank you so much
David for being for being part of this and uh you know I invented a little bit of new avatar
mythology myself and it's kind of based around a flight of passage and a new a new character
hopefully a new beloved holiday character who's the the star of of this song
rutuk the mighty ekran had a luminescent glow and if you learn to ride him you would be ekran
mock toe all of the other banshees matched with human dna rutuk could not go flying
till a proper link was made then one flight of passage eve dr stevens came to say
hey even though no match was right you can still uh fly tonight so he and dr ogden
shouted through the rookery rutuk the mighty ekran no ekran is more mighty one more slower
no ekran is more mighty
yeah hey I'm gonna do a quick scan it's a scan for stellar pipes guess what you all got them
yeah hope I didn't ruin the song no that was great thank you for indulging a musical of fly
for being the santa in the tale of rutuk and uh and with that thrilled to say david danapour
you survived podcast the ride thank you sir thank you so much such an honor to have him
so how do I get paid or like how do oh well yeah well we're gonna we're gonna go over the footage
and see if we will listen to the audio and see if we need to adr anything and then we'll determine
it off of that oh okay yeah okay I see so okay so got it we'll check we'll see if it's one
line or we'll see we'll see if you have to rerecord this entire yeah well I would love to
redub my part of this podcast every second well feel free if you you want to do another one just
for you uh we're open to that but uh uh as for now uh let's exit through the gift shop is there
anything you would like to plug oh I should have plugged something but no I don't I don't maybe I
should make a t-shirt that says and a shirt and maybe I'll have it up by the time yeah yes
go for it we'll we'll we'll promote it we'll plug it for sure we got it and we'll share the proceeds
we'll share the you take it okay it's all you it's your phrase you said thanks for saying it in the
in the song as well it's really delightful I'm so glad you could do this oh yeah uh so it's so much
fun and listeners you survived podcast the ride the main feed for 2022 that is the end of our
season yeah I think a great way to go out glad David could join us for it uh so last one of the
year here but um if you're worried that like leaving Pandora you will end up with post ptr
depression uh and you will that you will miss us too much over the holidays the episodes will keep
coming on podcast the ride the second gate or you can get one more bonus episode on our vip tier
club three or we of course uh will soon be describing the you're talking about the 1999
macy's thanksgiving day parade uh so if you want to hear any of that and we'll keep you company
through the holidays you could find that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride merch available in our
public store uh with maybe a link to a an official uh and a shirt uh if you uh if you feel like doing
it uh up to you but as uh hey I guess that'll do it for the year that'll do it for this entire
dodd three wolf men jacks signing off and saying
you know howling at the final moon of the year hey hey always remember I see you
this has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott
gairdner brett bowman joe cilio and alex ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever
dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your
podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook