Music
scored
Welcome to a little bonus, Feliz Navidad, the way of winter, a Yuletide celebration of all things
Avatar here on podcast the ride the civico gate. I'm Scott Gardner and it's just me. I'm doing this
without Mike and Jason and frankly without their permission. But I needed to do it because I have
some things to get off my chest. First of all I hope that you've had a wonderful holiday season
and that you've taken some time out to reflect on the reason for the season, JC. That of course
being James Cameron and his new film Avatar the way of water. Let me say something about this movie.
I fucking loved this movie. Holy shit. I think it blows the first Avatar out of the water
appropriately. If you've been on the fence about Avatar this whole time as I used to be,
this is the place to get in. I think it's fantastic and I've been thinking about the movie non-stop
since I saw it and especially one scene in particular that is so instantly iconic and
instantly way up there in the James Cameron great moment, Spantheon. And if you've seen the movie,
I think you know which scene I'm talking about. And that's kind of why I'm here is that I wanted
to process this moment and I figured what better way to do it than with a carol, with one more
carol. But let's be clear this is not an Emoticaya carol. This is a Metcaena carol because they are
the water people. That's who this new film focuses on. And really quick, I have to issue a sincere
spoiler warning. If you have not seen Avatar way of water yet, there are spoilers in this carol.
So if you haven't seen the movie, let this motivate you to see it because I know how much you want to
hear this song. It's going to start in several seconds. So pause it, go buy an expensive movie
ticket and drive to see the movie for four hours, then come back and listen to the song. But here in
real time, I'm going to start the song. Please enjoy the first ever Metcaena carol, a tribute to
my favorite scene in Avatar way of water. Out of all the space whales, you know you're the mastermind.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, Lowoxys that you are kind.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, Quaritch wants to burn up the town.
Sully's on the ropes and only you can take the poachers down.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, time to crush them into the ground.
Now I know that you were banished by your species and the water.
I know that you were banished by your species and the water clan.
But the poachers killed your family and your family is your fortress man.
You are my brother, flatten them as fast as you can.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, wisest of the great Tol'kun.
The stupid poacher thinks he's smart cause he's the one with the harpoon.
Jump on those fuckers, splat them like a water balloon.
Where the evil Aussie hunter only thinks about financial gain.
He's gotta meet his quota and suck all the goo right out of your brain.
Yank that cable, chop his arm off like a samurai blade.
Let's three brothers rock!
Damn, Pyocon, you are a composer of songs.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, revenge is what you gotta get.
When the soldiers see you coming, all their camo pants are gonna get wet.
Jump, jump, Pyocon, time to kill Jemaine Clement.
You survived Feliz Navidad the way of Winter Civico Gate Mini Met Kiana Carol Edition.
Thanks for subscribing. Apologies again for the Navi Babies episode.
New Club 3 drops tomorrow and otherwise we will talk to you in 2023. Happy Holidays.