visto
Welcome to Podcast the Ride presents Feliz Navidad, the way of winter, a Yuletide celebration
of all things Avatar. We're kicking off the party here on the Civico gate. I'm Scott
Gardner and I'm thrilled to do it. Mike Carlson, a mighty hello to you. Hello. I was in, I
went into Walmart yesterday and I saw an Avatar shirt, but in a different size, like not in
my size. And I was desperate to find it and I couldn't find it. What was the shirt? What
was on the shirt? It was a face of a Navi. Oh, okay. Big face of a Navi. That's one of
the things in Avatar. Yeah. And I was like, this is going to be great. I'm going to buy this
shirt and I hunted around and hunted around. No, couldn't find it. But it was like, it was,
it was like many, many feet long, like meant for a 14 foot body. Oh yeah. It was a Navi
size shirt. It was for a Navi to shop. Yeah. So it could work as a night gown, but that's not
what you're after. No, no, I want a shirt. So Jason Sheridan, that sure would not work for you.
Well, for, for sleep in, I'd love it. But I'm not in his avatar, a Navi tall T they would just
call them teas. Tall T Navi, tall T with an apostrophe between tall and T.
Was this a problem in your high schools? Tall T's tall T's. Well, this phrase I've never
heard this phrase until now, but I know, I know low T, but I don't know tall. We all know.
We all suffer from it. No tall T's like very long T shirts. That was the nickname of like
T shirts that you would wear and that would go down to your, like your calf and very quickly
they were like banned and they're like no tall T's in school. And I'm like, I, I looking back,
I'm like, you for sure banned these for a racist. Like I feel like what you were saying
with all dress code issues at schools, it's like a hip hop thing. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. I do. I remember vaguely this, this was like an elementary school. I feel like,
Oh, okay. For me. And I'm not that much older. So I feel like in fifth or sixth grade was maybe
like some kid wore a big shirt one day and they had a big meeting about it. All right. We have
something to create a bunch of hassle over all hands on deck. Every teacher. Yeah. Right.
I feel like kids are always like kids wear baggy shirts in general as they're still growing.
You know, they buy like, well, everything was baggy and then we wore baggy things in the nineties.
That was the style that was style. It's come back around and it's back or come back around.
I wore this giant sweater in seventh and eighth grade that is too big for me now. Way too big for
me now. And it just like I was swimming in it at the time, but I guess that was the style.
Well, it's, I don't know. It was the style for some people and for others, it was your impression of
the style. Interesting theory. You've got that. Maybe I wasn't fashion, fashion forward.
Why are you pointing and laughing at me? It's the style. Is it not the style?
Yeah. You wear an onion on your belt. That's the style at the time.
Yeah. So anyway, I think that this policy was actually, I think who they were actually targeting was big
chipmunks. They didn't want chipmunks coming to school wearing their first initial on their giant red shirt.
Oh yeah. Sure. We all, and then other kids would copy and they would, the chipmunking was what they
called it. And you would wear a big guy, your initial J big J on your one big shirt that you were wearing.
It's a distraction. It's a distraction from learning. Yeah. It's the fear. Cause you're, well, you're,
so you're thinking about everybody you're looking at in the classroom. Are they wearing pants under this or not?
Yeah. Yeah. Well, so what better way to start our, our celebration of avatar than with a bunch of,
a bunch of shirt talk. They're big. It makes sense. I think it makes sense. Uh, look, we're, this is, uh,
so it's like, it's a little mini celebration. It won't be the whole month. I think the main party is
going to start on the, on the main feed very soon. You could probably guess what we're, what we're
covering over there, but I, I'm very excited about this because we, we were like a little cluster,
little cluster of avatar episodes to celebrate the impending release of the way of water after
a long wait. And we weren't sure exactly what to do in terms of smaller avatar episodes. You know,
you could just be by the books and just go, well, what are the other things in the land? And you look
at a list and then you pick those, but we wanted to club three style, throw it to the audience a
little bit, maybe try to crowdsource. What are you the audience passionate about in terms of
avatar ideas, Pandora ideas? And I couldn't be happier with where it landed with today's episode,
the big seed, but this is a truly one that would, this would not have happened naturally exposed
me with me, with my limited experience in Pandora and animal kingdom. I have not come across
the big seed. It might not be accurate to call it the big seed, but that's the first, the first
tweet that we saw suggesting it, uh, called it the big C and this we've landed here at the big seed,
the big seed, not the big seed, the big seed, the big seed. Jason said the phrase, the big seed a
couple months ago. Yeah, that's right. Now, yes. Remind me what the, this was a runner, I think in
the live show about guardians, but how did this play out exactly? Where did, do you guys recall
where the, the, what the notion that there is a there or will be a big seed in the avatar world?
I just took a big swing and I assumed that the seed bearer, I feel like he had a 50, 50 chance,
either he's got a million little seeds or he's got one big seat. I imagine, I picture it like, um,
bigger than a football, uh, maybe about the size of a Thanksgiving turkey. Oh, it's a big,
that's it. That's not that big of a, well, I think it's big enough for him to bear.
It's still, I think, keep in mind, somebody has to bear this seat. That's the title, not of the one
that's about to come out way of water, but, uh, in supposedly two years, the seed bearer, maybe we'll
meet the seed bearer. This could, you know, I know we're the James plays it different than the
marvels. We're not, maybe we're not doing post credit scenes. Yeah, probably not. If the credits
die down and we think that's it, a little shimmery blue into black, but then, uh, we're back on it.
And then somebody steps out of the shadows and their silhouette is carrying some object that's
around the size of a turkey. There's also the possibility that we've already met the seed
bearer that it could be Jake Sully or it could be Niteari, you know? Yeah. We don't really know
what defines the city. Yeah. Are, are many people, are many Navi seed bearers? I I'm not sure,
but you like, okay. In the, I am shocked that in that whole discussion that we had in the live show,
I think I imagined a seed when we're talking about a big seed being an avatar. I think I pictured
more something that you could like, you could ride on, like, you know, you go to a, you go to a park
with the kid and there's like a big dome or like a, maybe like a, a fake turtle or something that
you can sit on and you kind of kick your leg. I think I was, I thought your imagined big seed
was like four feet wide or so. I'm open, you know, I'm open. I haven't, I haven't fully cooked up the
big seed thing. I'm not Jimmy. I'm not Jimmy Cameron. I thought the big seed was like, uh,
an Adam Warlock style cocoon that would sort of give birth to like a person. I don't know why.
I just figured a big like egg. I was thinking of an egg really is what I was thinking.
Whoa. Well, we all pictured something pretty different. Isn't this the wonders of avatar
that it lets our imaginations just run rock, run wild. That's, that is what it's good about it.
I think so in a way that that is what I, because as we decipher, like why has this stayed with us
and why have we ended, at least why I ended up so excited about avatar. One thing I like is that this,
this whole thing, which we'll get into in the, in the future episode, but this whole thing of
no cultural impact, I feel like we have all found the cultural impact together. We've all made it
our own. It's like, it's not, uh, I love it because it's like, it's, it's free rain for,
for us to like plant our seeds and for, we decide what to do with it and what characters to celebrate.
And it feels like we're all like the first people to like, try to do comedy about these characters.
It's not like when you think about like star wars, it feels so like not only picked over for
like making fun of it or having fun with it, but also just like a, a barren landscape until these
movies, like people are having fun with the new shows, but the movies are become just like
when the birds take over the town and you just have to back away. This is theirs now. That's
how I feel about the movie. I don't even want to talk about them anymore. But avatar is like,
it's just this big open, right? Playing fee. Yes. It's extremely ripe and we're waiting,
right? Waiting to bear big seeds. Now I, that all having been said, I have one more question for you
about the idea of the big seed. Do you think that he, the seed bearer, we might've even said some
of this in the show. Do you think that it's like a, um, like a, I might've said Johnny Appleseed
or some sort of like pied piper. Is he like, is the seed bearer not from their village?
And he comes in, look what I got. And he's got, or he's got some, like he's, there's something he
has to do with the, uh, I don't know what he, what is he up to? What is the seed bearer?
Now that we've seen a few trailers for the new movie and we, it seems to imply that they leave
their forest home and go to a neighboring water. They meet the water people. They meet the water
people. So I'm not really sure, uh, what the seed bearer will be doing now. Well, it's, do they
bring the forest back, you know, and is it a literal seed or is it the seed of the life of
the people? Well, yeah, I don't want to completely get off topic, but actually no, it's on topic.
It's perfectly on topic. It's on, that's on that I looked up and apparently wood sprites, I don't
know if you came across this, are seeds. Oh, I see now this, all right, to go back, like something
that will, will come up in the, the, the subsequent episode on the main feed, uh, and you're talking
about the flora and fauna of Pandora. I, I especially, it was very effusive or will be very
effusive about wood sprites, which are those sort of like jellyfish, very slight, like flying jellyfish
type creatures. They are seeds. They're seeds. They are seeds. A wood sprite is a seed of the tree
of souls that lives on Pandora. These seeds, according to the Navi are very pure and sacred
spirits. So they're part of a ritual. Like in the movie Avatar, many wood sprites, they lay on Jake
Sully, uh, and that's sort of, they're trying to, uh, uh, I think bring them closer to, uh, Iwa.
So it's sort of, uh, uh, it's a, it's a religious ritual of some kind. Okay. And they also, it says
they gather in, in places of mythological importance, like the cavern of songs.
And the cavern of songs is where the ride, where Navi river journey takes you. I believe so. Where
the shaman sings. Okay. Yeah. Um, and now there are also different seeds on Pandora and these are
called essence seeds. Oh, and they are way deep into the whole entire seed ecosystem. And the
thing we're going to talk about today is not a seed, but we need to get all this seed stuff out
of the way. It looks like a seed. I will explain. We'll explain why. But I just want to, the audience
needs to know what are seeds and what aren't seeds before we proceed. That's what we are doing here.
Essence seeds are small blue bioluminescent pellets, which are found across the Pandora
landscape in Navi mythology. These seeds are said to contain small amounts of IWA spirit,
more than just good luck charms. The seeds are also believed to bring IWA's blessing to those
who know where to look for them. So those are sort of different than the wood sprites. I believe
those are blue and also very similar. They use it in a religious context. Now hold on. I have a very
important question. Is IWA real in the avatar universe? Yeah. Yeah. I'm very comfortable
Yeah. I think like religion is real on Pandora. Yeah. Yeah. I'm ripping off this observation from
a podcast and I don't know. I feel like Griffin and David have said, I've done fun episodes about
Avatar and Chapo Trap houses. Well, one of these podcasts mentioned said how yet in this where
IWA is real, their God is real and they talk to the God. Okay. And that is like, this is presented
as a badass thing about the movie and the world, which I agree. I don't think that I don't think
it's a hypothetical. IWA absolutely is around. Got it. Their God is in the tree and in the
Pandora is in the planet. Like, yes. Yeah. That is. And the spiritual leader who is, I forgot I had
to look this up. I believe it is also Nate Tire's mother, CCH Pounder. Moab? Moab? Moat? Moat. That's
right. Moab might be biblical. She's a spiritual leader. Could the seed bearer be the next
generation spiritual leader? Yes. Okay. Yeah. That might be right because if there is a more, if like,
if the ideas are passed and if religion is passed down through tangible items, like nature is
religion in this world, that might be a very good guess. Right. Yeah. Because the, like,
political leader of the group was Nate Tire's father and he dies. Yeah. Yes. As I remember.
So it's interesting there's political leaders, but in addition, there's also God that exists.
To me, if God was actually existing, you wouldn't even need the leaders because God would just have
a conversation with everyone all the time. Yeah. And there wouldn't be an intermediary.
I think IWA speaks to everyone. Yeah. And I don't think, I think that's a beautiful thing
about the Navi and life on Pandora. I don't think you got any charlatans. Well, that's what I was
saying. You don't have any Joseph Smith saying, yeah, yeah. Going like, I talked to, I talked to
IWA. Maybe that'll come. That'll come with, what if this, oh no, what if the seed bearer is a con
artist? What if the seed bearer thinks that they have a deeper connection with IWA? And that's like
the start of, couldn't you see that being something James Cameron would want to address is like
religious profiteering comes to the Navi people and they have to like, you know, throw that person
out and what if they're full? I feel like James Cameron's bit of a movie guy. Maybe it's like a
night of the movie guy, like, like classic movie, like a night of a hunter, like sleazy, uh, uh,
revival preacher who is also a killer with the tattoos on his knuckles and stuff. Okay. So maybe
the seed bearer is bad. Maybe the seed bearer. Yeah, wait, why are we assuming? Oh, that'd be an
interesting turn. This phrase has been looming for so long and might loom for longer. Here's another
quest. Let's make another one of these predictions. Do we think it actually is two years before the
seed bearer or do we got more to wait? I'm going to say, uh, I think it comes out as scheduled.
I think it comes out in two years. Yes. I think he's on track because they're both shot. I think
that's shot already. Yeah. Yeah. The sum of four is what he's revealed. Right. But recently, but
that's not fully like green lit. No, I think he just started doing something. Yeah. Yeah. I don't
think we have the full, right. Um, we'll see. Well now I'm scared. Now I will be, I'll be entering
that theater with nervous trepidation of, am I going to be happy when I meet the seed bearer
or not? Or do we already know the seed bearer? Yeah. So much to wonder here. Um, um, so yeah,
the last thing I'll say, unless you guys have more about seeds before we start a topic here.
No, we'll transition over into the topic, which is not a big seed, but I'll explain why we call
it a big seed. I just, okay. Yeah. Well, we'll explain that. I just want to really quickly just
explain, uh, I brought up something, uh, that Bill Maher eats seeds exclusively and I have his full
diet here. I just want to explain what it is in more detail that this is what this man eats. Uh,
so he has sesame seeds, flax seeds, sunflower seeds, pumpkin seeds, barley and rye. He says
they're very good for you. He mashes the seeds with water in a machine that looks like a coffee
grinder. After the mixture sits for a few hours, he adds black cherry concentrate and that's what
he eats for lunch. Black cherry seed concentrate. He mushes up a bunch of seeds and only black
cherry. Yeah. No other flavors in his vernacular. Later in the day, he has a seed shake with a raw
egg and a different type of syrup. Jesus Christ. Well, this seems like the syrup in the concentrate
is undoing some of what the no, no, no, no, this is the rich guy. This is his diet. That's going to
keep him alive to a hundred. It seems like he's always in a bad mood all the time. It's like,
oh, I gotta go eat my seed smoothie. Like if he ever changed the diet and just had a pizza,
it would have taken one pizza long ago in like 2003 and real time would have suddenly become a
variety show with like, uh, uh, like girls in big can, can dresses and like knock, knock. Yeah.
Yeah. His whole career would have changed. Totally different. He had one pizza. No,
but he eats seeds. He is the seed eater, the seed drinker. He's the, Bill Maher is the seed drinker,
not the seed eater because he drinks them and shakes. Just do a mental auto replace. Next time
you see the name Bill Maher or hear the name Bill Maher, I'll give you a hint for where you'll
next hear the name Bill Maher on this show. Your exclusive home of bill Maher. Sorry. I made a
promise to myself not to bring him up again a couple of weeks ago. And then the seed thing
came up and I had no choice. You did it. Well, you made the promise to yourself. I don't think you
said it to us. I didn't know which is smart. No, I didn't break it. Yeah. Yeah. Almost immediately.
So it's good that don't tell your promises to others. That's the lesson here.
That's a weird, that's an interesting, weird thing to say. Moral. Yeah. Yeah. Don't tell your
promises. Put that on a shirt. It's like a wish. That's right. Let me explain. So here's how we,
we got here and then we'll get into what the thing actually is. But we were, we went through
everyone's responses to what should we do for Feliz Navidad the way of winter.
And one that we all sparked to was from Ken door with three Rs on Twitter. The response was
the giant seed that ejects mist when you rub it. There's a lot contained in that. We'd never
heard of that. Has anybody, you guys have been a little more than me. Does this sound familiar at
all? I've seen it. I didn't touch it. I knew as soon as I heard that I went what? And then I went
back and looked and I went, Oh, and then I know exactly what it was. Yeah. So we had this to
unpack and me especially, cause it did not ring a bell with me. I was there pretty briefly. So
we'll start explaining what that is. But, but credit to two other people who tweeted the same
suggestion, but with very different phrasing and both of their tweets unlock new information about
the big seed, which is some of some of which being that it's not a big seed. Anyway, what we're
actually talking about here is called the Flaska Reclinata. And it is part, it is one of the more
prominent, interesting interactive parts of the Pandoran landscape in animal kingdom. Some of which
that was some of the impetus is like, well, if we talk about the big seed, we can also talk about
the beauty of this land. One of the most impressive, because we've talked about the
attractions, but we've not necessarily talked about just like the stuff and the vibe, all of the things
that aren't the attractions, which is like maybe the best stuff about Pandora. No, no knock on the
attractions, which are fantastic, but just, just being there, just looking at it is incredible.
Yes. So yes, this was a good opportunity to talk about that. Now, will we have time? I don't know.
We can't, I just, we can't know for sure. We don't know for sure. It depends on how much we have to say about
the Flaska Reclinata. I, I got a DM about this too. And I feel like, somebody slid in your DMs to talk
about rubbing seeds. Someone I know. He's, but the phrase, and I saw other people mention it this way
too. It's like, Hey, you should talk about that big phallic thing that ejaculates on guests,
that giant phallus that you can like slam. You can pat a lot and then it'll spritz. I mean, yes. Okay.
Now that we're right in vulgar town, it's a giant phallus with an open sore that you rub, you rub the
sore out of here. And maybe this is who DM'd you and maybe not. I mean, just, this is about a lot
of people might care, characterize it. This is Dylan on Twitter. The third attract, you should
talk about the third attraction of Pandora, the big plant that you jerk off and it ejaculates on
the other guests. This wasn't the sole observation. Many people have noted, but Mike, you've brought
an interesting new facet into this, which is that it, the where the, that the stimulation comes from
a big open sore. Yeah. That's the, okay. So it's like, it's like, if you don't know what we're
talking about, it's sort of, it's a tilted giant, I would say almost like a closed mouth of a Venus
fly trap. That's sort of the look of it. And it's kind of tilted like a, a cannon. It's like the
shape of a cannon and leaned up like a cannon and it's massive. It's huge. It's like what, 20 feet
in the air or something. It's a very, very significant size, 20 feet long, 15 feet high.
Yeah, that makes sense. And it's right when you come in to the, to the land, what do, the,
the first like entrance, if you're sort of just making your way around clockwise around animal
like if you're the, I get lost geographically in this part, but you're, I think maybe if you're
nearest to the tree of life and to kind of the hub as much as there is a hub. I believe. Okay.
If you're by Tiffin's, that's the entrance there. Yeah. So it's, it's pretty prominent
and I'll be honest, I didn't think it was phallic until all this. And now I can not, not see it.
Well, we should also mention the nickname, uh, kind of adds to the, the boardiness.
So confused by the nickname. Baja tickler.
It's the bar and this is just tossed off so casual flask and the flask of reclinata also known as the
Baja tickler. It like, huh? Every, I feel like no article or blog post or anything that I saw this
and noted how weird that is the Baja tickler. Why is it that that's not Baja is not a magical
Pandorin place. That's a place in Mexico. That's our world. Why? And the name that could not be
more like, I mean, it's, it's either it's in that like, uh, donkey punch type, like sex move name,
or it sounds sort of like a dildo. Well, yeah, it, to me it sounded like, um,
a movie set in the forties or fifties and like a character is going like, oh, we went to a stag
party last night. They had a bunch of Tijuana Bibles. They had Baja ticklers. Yeah. It was nasty.
I really, uh, did you see the monorail thing that came out that looks like a dildo?
What's up? You can buy it at one of the gift shops. There's a, I forget even what it is,
but it's basically a big green monorail that looks like a dildo. That's a green,
a monorail has never been green, has it? Let me look, I'll send it to you right now, but yes,
that's just, that's in the air right now as well. Um, but this is a strange, I found on the, uh,
Pandora Wiki that like a lot of these, like they have official names, which like is fake
Latin kind of, and then they have more of an English sounding name. Yeah. Which is the format
of that. The cron is what they call it and Banshee is what we call it. Something that I found annoying
the first time around the bend on all this stuff, but now I think it's a little neat that they,
it kind of fleshes out the, you know, you're actually, uh, wandering around and trying to
identify flora and fauna in a, in a, in a natural park type environment. It does, you do go, well,
that is what a real place would do. There's the slang term and there's the, the stuffy term.
Right. There's a, there's a, I was on the, on that same wookie, there's, um, like a giant mushroom
in the land and it's called a fungimonium giganteum, also known as an octoshroom.
I like that. Which is fun. And it seems more, that seems right to me versus the Baja Tickler.
This one, this, I'm confused where Baja Tickler came from. Are we sure this is officially handed
down? Did James Cameron approve the term Baja Tickler? That's the one, that's the page I was on.
So I don't know if that was added by some, uh, rambunctious prankster or yeah, or that's some
sort of official copy. I, I found it on Pandorapedia. Okay. That's okay. And then they had the,
the Navi name and then the taxonomy in quotes, it says that the Navi translation is poison
squirting plant. And then the, the translation of like the human one is reclining flasks.
If you Google Baja Tickler, it comes up on a different, like it comes up on the fandom
site for Avatar. Um, and it is not oddly, it's not leading us to some type of pornography that we
were not previously aware of. This, this, they aren't like trying to like Trojan horse. Uh,
I don't think this isn't like an old, like the anime animators putting in a frame of porn
agro. I don't think so. I mean, maybe it is, but that's just the design of the thing. But
if you keep scrolling down, like it doesn't get to porno quickly, it gets to a little bit of a
barricade. Yeah. There's a motorcycle called a Tijuana tickler. Uh, there's yeah, there's,
I don't see any porno on this first search result page. Well, that's pretty impressive.
So the bar tickler, I mean, I'm impressed that there's, there's theme park mythology and a
dual word I've never found before, but doesn't, you mean, I kind of wonder if like, what if it is,
what if it is like one imagineer kind of pulling a fast one on everybody and this,
the Baja tickler was like his move, a sexual move called the Baja tickler, where there's nothing
inherently dirty about the name, but there's like one person out there or maybe all of the other
people who were pleasured by the Baja tickler, that there's only a select group of people who
all, if they see that or know that they go, I know what this is. I've experienced a Baja tickler.
This is a, some sort of sex move that Joe roadie learned when he was traveling overseas.
It was given to him by someone in a village somewhere and he took it and made it part of
his own repertoire and now wanted to at least have it represented in some way.
It's passed down. It's like a long storied history, three, 3000 years. This has been
the most satisfying sexual maneuver. Very possible. I mean, people sneak things in all the time,
like the, what's the, what's the, the body, the casting couch stuff, like in California
adventure and all that stuff. Although that's barely sneaking stuff in. I'll be like, that's
not, yeah, that's just for people. Just were not sensitive to what that actually means. Yeah. Now
look, the Baja, you know, I don't want to put Baja tickler in that territory because the tickler could
be a wonderful, consensual, deeply pleasurable if it exists. And if it doesn't exist, then it's up
to you, the listener, if you feel free to take something that you do that does not have a term
and this term is maybe waiting to, it's waiting to be grabbed. It's waiting to be grabbed. It's
waiting to be grabbed. Cause if you look, if you search Baja tickler sex, nothing comes up. It's
not nothing comes up that has those three words in it. So yeah, this is wide open. This is a,
make your mark. It's, it seems really weird to, I, I would like to see the official Disney literature
that uses the term Baja tickler because it at least feels like somebody would have flagged it. Like
doesn't that kind of sound like something? Yeah. California is not, you know, terribly far away,
which is just the strip of it is not California. It is called Baja California, but it is a state
in Mexico. And it's also where much of Titanic was filmed, which makes you wonder, is the facility
set up by James Cameron himself to have oceanic proximity to be able to flood big pieces of the
Titanic over and over. And then it stayed open. It was called Fox studios Baja for a while. It was
actually a themed attraction. You could go there and tour set. It was a little mini studio tour.
And then I think the area got too seedy for a while for them to do this. But I think now it's
been on the, the mend and they're shooting stuff there again, but it's not owned by Fox anymore.
And thus not owned by Disney. They didn't buy the Baja studios, but that's the only thing that makes
me wonder if somehow there is a James Cameron connection here. If he is, he, he, he did much of
his most famous work in Baja. Maybe it was, they called the Baja tickler like the stick James
Cameron would hit actors with when they would flub their lines. Maybe that's, there's some sort
of inside joke there or the, the, like, maybe it was an electrified stick that he would like
stick into the water really fast, just to like give everybody a jolt before the next take.
Yeah. Little sleepy Winslet. He's the real way of water for you. Yeah. So it could be any of these
options. My mind has been blown by the recent information that the K Winslet at the very
unpleasant time making Titanic and specifically the, like the James Cameron was a tyrant and crazy
to work for you. She spoke publicly about this and all of the water stuff was so unpleasant to do
cut to she's not only in the way of water in the water. She bested Tom Cruise's record for
underwater shooting. Yes. Seven minutes and 13 seconds or something. She not only like hate
James Cameron plus water, never again. These things came back, did it better than anybody's
ever done it. Say, you know, people change their minds and maybe James may get a good pitch,
get a good pitch to her. Hey, look, she was married to Sam Mendes for a while. Maybe she's like,
Hey, you, you weren't that bad after all my man. Does he have a Baja tickler? I mean, I don't even
know. I don't know. I just think he's a really, he's like an intense director, right? Movie and
theater director may, I actually don't know to be with, with a lot of these folks. Yeah. She's a pro.
I love it. She's great. She's amazing. Yes. Yeah. She's joint, like the cast additions in this new,
as we, yeah, we're in our final days of speculation of what's happening in the new one. And you,
but we know we get her, we know we get Jemaine Clement, we get Vin Diesel. I was so excited
about Vin. That's great. I have no idea what Vin Diesel is doing. Really excited to figure it out.
And we also get, this is a quick, I forget if, did I text this to you guys or apologies if I
already did, but this is so bizarre that here's a little, this thing, this came out in an interview
or something. James Cameron was talking about, because Sigourney Weaver is back, not as Dr.
Grace Augustine, but a new character who is an adopted daughter of Jake and Nateri. She's a
15 year old Navi girl. And okay, so adopted. Okay. That's all right. So not the, not the biological
child of Jake and Nateri. Okay. So then what, where, where did Kiri come from then? Listen to this.
She, she's naturally conceived, she's a naturally conceived Navi raised in the rainforest. It's just
that she's born of Grace's avatar. Cameron explains. It's a natural birth, but the avatar is brain dead,
but she's not. She's normal. What the hell does that mean? Okay. So just to clarify, and if you
aren't super avatar familiar Sigourney Weaver's, wait Sigourney Weaver, human character in the
first movie who died while in a Navi avatar body. Right. So that presents some questions. If you die
in that body, what happens to your body? What happens to that body? So that means the new
character, it's not an accident that it's Sigourney Weaver playing her. They are related, but it's a
natural birth, but the avatar is brain dead, but she's not. Okay. Why is she,
okay. Was the character pregnant at the time of death? Is that what the implication? Dr.
Grace Augustine the av in avatar form? No. Okay. Okay. Here's here quickly. This might not even
be explained in this movie. This might be backstories. Okay. Here's okay. The, the avatar
bodies are Navi and they are created in a lab. So human beings are able to transfer their
consciousness into them. Yes. Yes. Because the Jake's avatar was made with Navi DNA and his
brother's DNA. So it had to match and he's a twin. So that way he could, that's why he could get it,
but not just anybody could go into any of these avatars. Yes. And it's an empty vessel for
a human. Basically it's not like you're taking over the consciousness of a Navi. Right. And the Navi
did like a spiritual ceremony that like glued his consciousness in the avatar at the end of the
first movie. Yes. He's perma. Yeah. He's perma. He's perma avatar. So if I, perma Navi, so if I
understand correctly, what would have to happen for that scenario is that Sigourney Weaver in her,
when she was in the avatar would have had to make love with another, maybe real avatar, maybe,
or a real Navi. This is, I made this mistake like every time I've talked about it. Yeah. Or another
avatar got like a human, it could have been a human in another, because the bodies biologically
are the same as Navi. Yes. So she would have had to get knocked up as a Navi. Which is so crazy
that it's like a, so it's fully functioning. That means, do we know that? Do we know that if you're
in an avatar of a Navi that your sperm works or whatever they call it? That I think has to be
addressed in this new movie because they suddenly have two kids. Yes. So we know they've adopted one,
but he got the, but he's a perma now. So maybe the ceremony made it so that his sperm works,
but it maybe it didn't before until the ceremony. If you were only temporarily going to be a Navi,
it would be highly irresponsible to get a female Navi pregnant. It would be highly,
and then you get out of there, you leave, I guess you could go on Pandora's a human and help,
but sorry, but that's tough. How do you, then you're like, you're raising a baby. It's much,
it's as big as you. I mean, that's, that's funny though. Six feet tall. That's you can't,
and you have, you have to raise it through a foggy mask. That should be, because you can't breathe.
Humans can't breathe on avatar. Hold that note for later. Remember that when we get back onto
topic, that should be a fun, that should be one of the movies like four or five where like a human
has got to raise a bunch of babe, a bunch of Navi baby, a three men and a three men and a Navi baby.
That's right. Three avatars and a Navi. No, I guess it's men. It has to be, and it should be
honestly, Tom Selleck, Steve Gutenberg and Ted dancing. Yes. Yes. That's the way.
And then it doesn't matter. Then it's all mo cap within like they'll seem as vibrant as
when the first three came out. Well, okay. Let's I'll change it. The three very old men and
a little Navi lady. Ted's tall. They're all a little tall, maybe except for Gutenberg. So they're,
they're off to a good start, but still you're changing diapers. It's going to be tough.
Gonna be tough. Um, I anyway, isn't that, that's a, that's one of the things that we're all going
to discover in a few days. What the hell does that mean? So wait to, to finish it out really quick.
So is she got deducted Sigourney Weaver avatar get impregnated. The body was dead,
but the baby was still born. Thus it has Navi DNA and the DNA of Dr. Grace Augustine. That's what
it would have to, I mean, and it also would have had to happen off camera in the first avatar.
I think it will be something where it was like the child was born in a fraction of her consciousness.
She doesn't have the full knowledge. She's not doctor, but this child is kind of hurt.
What are you saying? No, that was, that was dense.
I think like the child is born and there's a fraction of the Grace Augustine consciousness.
In the child or what are you talking about? In the child.
So you think it's not genes passed down. You think some of grace is in Kiri.
Well, that would explain that. I think that's justifies why Sigourney Weaver is doing the voice.
Well, isn't it just because she's the daughter, the related.
Yeah, I think it's just because they're related.
Okay. But I like that. I do like that as we discussed, she's not a doctor.
This young girl is not a doctor. But maybe she goes up to the.
You know what? That's my knee jerk, but we are in the avatar world here. That could very,
Jason's premise could very well be. I think we're getting wild with these movies.
I, yeah. I look, there's like half a dozen instances of stuff like this in the X-Men world
where it's like, Oh, this character has lived a dozen times and they remember every time they lived
or like, okay, this character died and their friend who was like kind of a robot died.
But then the robot came back, but then the human's consciousness was in the road.
And I just like nine or 10 year old me. It was like, okay, got it. Sounds good.
Got, yep. I'm on board.
Schoolwork. I will not do, but this, I will do this homework for the rest of my life.
Long division by hand. No, no. Doug Locke, the merger of Doug Ramsey and Warlock. Yes, please.
X-Men also has a long history of blue characters.
Lot of blue. Yeah.
A lot of blue and some of them are related. Some of them aren't.
Yeah. Who's wait. Oh, Nightcrawler Mystique.
Yeah. You know, if the movies are starting to do multiverse stuff, you got to remember Rebecca Romaine
is the old older version of Jennifer Lawrence. And also Alan Cummings is their son.
Really? Alan Cumming?
Alan Cumming. Is he a singular?
Is it singular? Alan Cumming?
It is kind of, yeah. Okay.
It's singular. Okay. Sorry. Yes, that's true. Jason's correct, but they have,
they screwed a lot of the time.
They, there's, it's all kind of, yeah.
Sorry. Yeah. So it upsets me. You know, it's not like the comics.
So we've established that the name is gross and we've established, maybe let's fully explain that
this, because it's only been described as a sore, but if you're going to take that out of it, what
this is, you know, really this is in the grand tradition of Disney interactive water elements.
Ultimately, it's a thing that squirts water onto the guest and it mists. Does it,
actually does it just mist or does it, is there a water spray?
Mist, I was trying to remember, it looks like a mist from the videos and I'm trying to remember
if I ever stood under it and I don't think I did, but I think it's mostly just a mist.
It's not like a hard, it's not like on the Dudley Do-Right ride or anything.
It's a mist and then there's inevitably some drops.
There's, oh sure, there's going to be drops, yeah.
But it is like to, to activate it, there is like a little hole in the side.
On the shaft, you might say. Yeah.
You might rub the shaft towards the bottom of the shaft, but it's kind of like, it's sort of like a
pink, this is a little help. You go to the pink part, go to the pink part and rub it. Although
I've also seen, it seems like from a lot of videos, tapping is also in the cards.
In fact, I think there might be more mist, the more hands you get on the thing.
So the more surface you can cover of the pink, the more.
Spray. The more pink you can grab, the more it will spray.
Yes. This is, they did, first of all, they did this.
Yes. We're just discussing.
We're just, everything we described is applicable. That is how you would describe this.
This is not a reach.
No. There's a big long thing.
A reach around is something you might do to get extra pink.
But we're just explaining what they did. So don't be mad at us if you don't want the
bodiness on this episode. It's their fault.
So it, you know, it is what I like about this to bring it back to more innocent. I like it.
It feels like a, the like next evolution of, you know, the sprinkler and the honey,
I shrunk the kids area, but it's this, but it's a thing that is not a stretch in the world of avatar
and that adds to the diverse ecological life of a beautiful area. It's a, it's a grand piece of
sculptury, whatever you want to call it. It's very impressive.
Story line wise, it is important to.
Okay. Let me hear, let me transition. Let me read the other suggestion of somebody who said we
should talk about this. Okay. So this was from Marquez. I want a whole episode on the flask
of Reclinada, the plant that allows humans to breathe on Pandora. So, whoa, that too,
most people gave it to us from the gross angle, but now on top of that, this is how we,
this thing is the key to that. We can walk around in this place.
Yes. It's very important.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So it should really, we shouldn't be making fun of it.
No, honestly, it's how, that's it. All right. No more. No, we will not have fun with this.
It absorbs toxins from the atmosphere. Yes. Yeah. Absorbs condenses, purifies atmospheric
toxins. So it like, it's like, it would be poisonous if you got just the raw spit on you,
that might be bad, but just that it like takes in what we can't breathe. It gets a little muddy
here because how can the difference be split? How can we be there as well as the Navi if we breathe
different things? Well, how, oh, that's a good question. How do the Navi, what do they breathe?
Do we know off the top of our heads? Good. Don't know what the air is made of. Yeah.
Because obviously I'm smart. I know we read oxygen and we exhale carbon dioxide and plants
are, this is, this is the length of how much I know about this. Plants do a similar, they take
the carbon dioxide and they put oxygen into the atmosphere, into the world. And that's good for
humans. So that's the extent of my knowledge about this topic. But yeah, what do Navi breathe? What
is the, it is, uh, it's okay. It's a mixture of there's, there is oxygen and carbon dioxide,
but also nitrogen and there is a high amount of xenon and the xenon makes it denser than the
atmosphere on earth. And the xenon is why we can't, we aren't able to, we aren't accustomed to this.
So just xenon. Xenon is the problem. Xenon, maybe some methane. So does the, does the,
Baja tickler take the xenon out of the air? I think it takes stuff out of the air, purifies it
and then expels it as water. Okay. So liquid can be poisoned by the way,
cause they exist on just oxygen, oxygen and not xenon.
So maybe what it does is like get the levels to where it's acceptable for everybody. Right.
There's some xenon, but less. So we're okay. But the xenon that the Navi crave,
it's all is still there. Yeah. So it was a little, a little trace amounts of xenon.
Yeah. And by zine, I want to be clear that xenon with an X, not xenon with a Z,
like the Disney channel original film, xenon girl of the 21st century, which is a movie I watched
and enjoyed in the late nineties, early 2000s. That's one of the top ones. I think with a,
you never seen any of this, Mike, actually haven't. I don't think there's a, a, a future pop star in
it named protozoa. Cause the main reason I like the movie does a song called the galaxy is ours.
Oh, wow. Sounds great. Shout out to all the pro zoa fans out there. It's the same format as like,
where they're kind of like chasing through the move, just like who's the goofy movie power line.
Power line. Yeah. Yes. Xenon has a power line. Wow. And it's protozoa protozoa, a big performance
at the end power lines. Been having a moment these last, this last year or two, I feel like,
and protozoa is I think ripe for protozoa is due. Yeah. That's what I mean. Box lunch,
protozoa merchandise. That's what I'm saying. Um, so yeah, maybe that's what it is. It's just,
it just like evens things out so everybody can breathe. Everybody's happy, which is,
which reflects the world that we find ourselves in plot wise. When we go to Pandora and animal
kingdom where the wars are over, it's really a big spoiler for the entire franchise as if we needed
to look, we know the Navi are going to win. We know that the, the RDA doesn't stand a chance
and the Corritch is going no matter what kind of body he's in, Corritch is going home with his
ass handed to him. Right. Uh, but it's, isn't it nice to know that like, oh, for sure the wars end
everybody's living in peace and enjoying Satuli bowls together. Oh my God. It would be great if
we knew like, oh, all this stuff will work out here. Wouldn't that be great? Yeah. So knowing
just in one of our favorite fictional universes, same way. Yeah. If there was some way to, if we
could all get giant seeds to depurify, to purify our atmosphere and take out all the stuff we
aren't going to want, it's going to hurt us as the years go by. Okay. Get that guy, you know,
that guy, you know, must get him on building some Baja ticklers or growing some Baja ticklers.
He'll look into it. I think if somebody just presents him with a shady looking website that
has nebulous information on it, he'll start taking it seriously. Yeah. And I think maybe he'll,
he'll say something along the lines of like, I'll stop growing these. I'll grow these. Yeah. We
should start growing these 10 years. We'll have a million of them. Yeah.
Yeah. So, Elon, you might want to invest in this. This is a big plant and all, as long as it is
misting and as long as you're rubbing its shaft, it's fine. This will fix global warming. You just
get enough of these around the planet. Oh, I don't know. It doesn't seem, it seems kind of
sus, basic, doesn't it? LOL. Well, it was, let's just lie to him. It was made up by white supremacists.
Oh, sounds good. All right. I'm in. I mean, I'll do it after the phone. After I make a phone.
He's going to make a phone. The crazy. It's ER. Did you not see that? I saw it. Oh my God.
I saw it. A phone, a phone we can do racism on. And one of the, it's one of those things where
it's like, well, Apple and Google, they're going to be quaking in their boots. Someone opens a,
like, like the gun theme rest of the Lauren Bobert gun themed restaurant that served food
poisoning as their main course. And they're like, watch out McDonald's, watch out Olive
Cardin. This is going to be taken the nation by storm. If you can convince Elon that there is it
elsewhere, that there is a woke Baja tickler out there that he could, he could crush the business
of, then he'll get going on his, no problem. Humanity saved. Let's talk about, that is a
that's a, a person, a so-called visionary who we don't like very much, but there is somebody who
we should talk a little about who I think, well, I don't want to say we've underrated this person.
It's just, we don't know much about him. The person's name is Zolt Hormay. Zolt Hormay is
introduced in the Imagineering story. And it wasn't a name that I knew before. I don't know
if you guys remember this, that in one of the last few episodes you meet the guy who is the
fake rock guy. You see him, I believe in action, putting together radiator Springs,
which of course won the fake rock final four. If you look at the whole fake rock final four list,
most of them were touched by Zolt Hormay. Most of them were the doing of this guy who,
first things first, the coolest name ever. Zolt very well could have been the pop star who
xenon girl of the 21st century was trying to go see. Love Zolt Hormay. Just a little, okay. So
basically like all of that, all of that Pandoran atmosphere this guy was responsible for. Here's
this guy's career. He's 23 and he leaves Hungary, comes to America, you know, in search of satisfying
his artistic existence, ends up getting a job for a company in Lansing, Michigan, who is making a
miniature golf course. And he so excels in creating this miniature golf course that he is snatched up
by Disney. The first thing he works on Typhoon Lagoon, the mountain in Typhoon Lagoon is where
he starts. That's wild. And he's in his early twenties still. First thing I gave was a fake
rock final four contender. Then he moves on to Honey I Shrunk the Kids play set. He's part of that.
Then he does all of the rock work at Disney Paris, which we said for its faults, beautiful in terms
of the natural, the environments and the surroundings, which means they're big thunder,
the most beautiful big thunder he works on. Then he does Toontown in Anaheim and Tokyo. Then he
leaves, runs his own company for 12 years or so. Then Radiator Springs is on the horizon. They're
like, there's only one guy who can do this. We got to get Zolt. Zolt comes back and stays where he
does, wait, I might be wrong with the order. Well, some, oh wait, I missed some things. Tree of Life.
Oh wow. Mysterious Island, the volcano in Disney Sea. And then he sticks around and he does the
Cadillac Mountain Range in Cars Land. He does the new rock work at Rivers of America,
which and that transition into Galaxy's Edge. He of course does Galaxy's Edge as well. Then all this
Avatar stuff. Will you take in that body of like how much of our lives are truly built by Zoltor
May and the people who he hires and the care that's like all-star stuff from when we were kids and
then leaves for a little bit, comes back and does the best stuff they've done for the last 15 years.
That is, yeah, he's yeah, like a low-key legend at this point. Yeah. Just because the atmosphere is
so important. Only not a legend because there's not more of him because he jumped out at me from
that imaginary. He's still like cool name, cool accent. Yeah. Then I've found another little bit
of interviews and stuff and he is just like chill, non-pretentious, travel buddies with roadie. Like
they're going all the crazy Asian countries together like exploring, you know, to figure out
animal kingdom influences. This guy rules. Do we know has he been fired?
Is he still there? I hope not or if he or I hope Universal has snatched him up ASAP. Yeah, I wonder.
I think they know this guy. You can't like, do they know? Maybe they don't. Did they know with the
old regime? Yeah, yeah. Or does or if somehow he slips through the cracks. They retired roadie pretty
good pretty quickly. Yeah, that's yeah. When you look back at how many of the major people who left,
Bob Weiss left, all these people kind of coincidentally like, yeah, something about now
feels like the time. A lot of old imagineers I feel like are dancing on the grave at the moment.
Yeah, I think so. Yeah. Oh, that one, Tom Morris, who's great on Twitter. This is all weeks ago,
by the time you're hearing this, but like Tom Morris are like great, cool, thoughtful,
imagineer, built a lot of the best stuff, 80s, 90s. He just flat out said, you know, every other CEO
or head of parks came around and asked everybody what they do and about their history and what they
contributed to the company and their story. And Shape X, the first guy who didn't. So I don't think
a lot of people are going to be too sad about all this. Yeah. Crazy to just, you know, it's bad if
people are because people shit talk. The people who are in Pat, you know, you know, like they're
everybody shit talks to everybody, but sometimes it's quiet. So if you're willing to do it,
I would do it at public. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, I've seen a couple other ones say stuff immediately
too. So yeah, I think it's a consensus, but Zolt, I want to know, is he there or is he not? I hope
so. And if he's not, I hope he's off on some other great event. By the way, as if this guy wasn't
cool enough, a lot of the teams that he assembles for all of these projects, for the best projects
the company does, he makes it a point to seek out and involve native American students to work
with him, shadow him. He like very actively finds native American talent who build a lot of the
stuff that we love so much. Zolt's the best. Where is he? Let's get him on here. Yeah. Yeah.
We can go park by Flower Street and count the 30 people going into the Imagineering building.
Who's left? Who's left? Yeah. And if he has some novelty, if there's a license,
novelty license plate, that's like King of Rocks, Rock Guy, Rock Man, number one rock.
I don't know. I feel like those always cut me off like on the freeway.
Yeah. Rock is probably all taken by douchebag. I don't know how you figured out how to do a crazy
maneuver, crazy maneuver on a road where you're allowed to go 65 miles per hour. But I wasn't
going fast enough. Highway to hell blasting. Yeah. Cool. I don't want to get us off, but
the rumors are, Jason, that you won the Lake Nona move is dead. That's the rumor. Not my intent.
Not your intent, but you're doing 100%. 100% you're doing. That I'm not sure who wins in this.
It'll likely just be an empty. Well, now that everyone's either quit or been fired,
at this point, there's not by default. It's muddy who, what the 15 people who work there are
not forced to move to Lake Nona. It's like there's tons of office space in Burbank. Like there is,
there is a massive like skyscraper buildings for record companies going up along the one freeway.
And it's like, how are you going to fill the, like who's going in here? Yeah. This is so much.
Fill it up with Imagineers. Stuff by the airport and. Isn't there an Eiger like town hall?
We're recording this couple of weeks before it's coming out, but isn't there some sort of Eiger,
like town hall? Are we allowed to ask questions? Are we allowed to ask questions to this?
I don't know. Well, maybe if we buy each by one share, can we dial in and ask questions?
I want to ask questions. Well, if by any, if you, weeks ago you heard an emergency that we got on,
like, wow, Mike's been real lucky. He got in that, he got in that Instagram live with
Mazury and a little less importantly, a town hall with Bob Eiger.
Hey everyone. I just want to say, I'm sorry. I panicked and asked why that cheese cup I had
in California Adventure wasn't great a year and a half ago. Really sorry about that. Hadn't thought
about it since then, but. Why are all the hot dogs the same at the different restaurants in
the Disneyland resort? We have proof. When are you going to make Rise of the Resistance
the same quality as Transformers? These are the questions we have to ask Bob Eiger now that he's
back. And he. People with the video cameras on are like looking confused. Like, who's this guy?
Or does weirdly, so that one bizarrely gets like suddenly like slow clap and then every
shareholder across the nation. He said it. He finds someone, a Spartacus finally said it.
It will Black Tap continued or will Ballast Point continue their
tyrannical price gouging? They're using at downtown Disney.
What are two places that use open table for some reason?
Well, that's a different topic as well. Yes. Well, there's these are important questions that he
needs to know. Well, Scott's beloved Katal restaurant. Will it maintain its essence
during this renovation? Well, that's see, I don't actually care about Katal. I care about the bar.
With the outdoor. Well, it's all sad.
A location they can tear over bar. They could blow up. It's all for like, I just give me that
uber bar. I guess we need their kitchen. So don't blow up their kitchen, right? Don't blow up the
kitchen. What else about the big plants that that that missed? You know, it's well, it's part of
Mike, you looked up some like other Pandora, uh, the flora. Yes. And I, what I didn't know is that
you can go, it's me. I kind of do this next time. I, you can go to avatar.com and on avatar.com
where you find information about how you can explore Pandora with Alpha Centauri expedition.
Of course you can download a PDF. That's a checklist of all of the different creatures and
plants that you can see when you go. It's like, it is like a little national park map. This thing is
great. It's really pushed out. You get good little like, uh, you know, like here's, there's
good little like many versions of everybody. And it tells you how many there are in the land. So
you have like a little game you can play that you can concertedly win. Like, Hey, there's, uh,
there's at least 12 goblin thistles in the Valley of Mawara. Go find all 12 goblin thistles.
And it's just interesting to know they actually did think about all this stuff, like that everything
as everything as a name and they, they repeat, but not so much to it. They don't repeat to the
point where you can tell they repeat. This is the road. Like this is roadie really making sure I
feel like making sure that it fits into the animal kingdom. Like, I don't know, a template or whatever,
like it means making sure like it feels kind of like you're exploring, like you're on the expedition
to see our experts in Everest or you're seeing animals and the it's like that element, like a
PDF and making it feel like it's a scavenger hunt. You're discovering things makes it sort of all
feel similar in the same way. Now it's fictional. Obviously there's also that book. There's an avatar,
like Pandora's survival guide. It's like 260 pages, 262 pages, right? Like backstory and stuff,
like all the cannon that people argue about with star wars or Lord of the rings, like Cameron showed
up with that, you know, and all the people working on avatar, working on the land stuff.
When I was a kid and I realized that somebody had put this, I didn't have this conscious thought,
but when I realized people had put this much thought into mythology, I think the first time
I thought about it was when I got the Star Trek encyclopedia as a kid, which is big. It's not that
day. I still have it. And it was like an encyclopedia with all the things in the universe and like
what the warp speed meant and all that. And I was like, this is the coolest thing I've ever
read. Like this it's like, it's re, oh, it's all real. Huh? Okay. And like that blew my mind.
Like I, and then right around that time is when I was like, oh, there's a Klingon dictionary.
Someone, someone wrote the Klingon language, which I was like, this is amazing. Of course,
did I go and learn another human language that's on planet earth? No, but the idea that there was
his fake history and fake languages that were available to me to learn. Like fake rock. We
prefer fake rocks to real rocks. Really strange for fake languages. Really study why this is
such a similar human history. Very interesting. Just us being born in an era where there'd been
more media than ever before. It's weird where we just always like pointed in that direction.
I guess media centric, the comfort of narrative. Like there is, there is a beginning, middle,
and end of these world, you know, there they exist in uncomplicated worlds compared to real life.
That's probably part of it. I think it's probably also just that the way
you're like history, like your elementary school, third grade teacher, the way they presented
history was pretty dry and you go home and Star Trek was on and data is a robot and they're doing
cool stuff and there's crazy, the Borg and you're like, this is better than the story.
Closeups. You don't get any closeups of history. Yeah. So it's like,
cut it into a little thing for you. Your dumb kid brain is just like,
this is a better story than that story. I know this is vibrant and real. This history shit. What is that?
It is, it is. No one ever says the perspective of the kid. Like, you know, oh, this is a distraction.
Phones are a distraction. Back in the day, Tamagotchis were a distraction. Everything's
a distraction. You be more entertaining teacher. You get some stage presence,
take some classes in the summer. Take some improv. Take a couple improv.
Yeah, take a couple improv classes. Jason and I coach if you want to.
I've gone from begging for acting work to begging for improv coaching work on the show.
To make teachers as exciting as the TV. Yeah. Teachers have to be as exciting as the TV.
That's what we've really uncovered here. Jazz it up teachers.
Yeah. You know, you've been phoned in.
You be as entertaining as Tom Brokaw.
Yeah. Tom Brokaw. The most dynamic thing. Who's more entertaining than Tom Brokaw?
Yeah, really. To Jason. To young Jason.
This little like, I mean, I recommend looking up this guide to the flora and fauna of the
Valley of Moira. Because you get like, I mean, there's a fun bunch of other, you know, you can,
you learn more about the wood sprites. You could, but then, and then like there's other
ones with weird names. You got the vein pod. The vein pod is really.
The vein pod's really something. Let's take a second here on the vein pod.
I almost was wrapping it up and then like, wait. No, no, no. The vein pod.
This is another, this is, they knew what the, it's sexual. Oh, this is sexual.
Well, the phrase vein pod had never occurred to me for any part of the genitals. But have you,
have you previously, have you looked at your own anatomy and ever thought, I don't know,
look at that vein pod down there. I've never thought of it as a vein pod, but the vein itself,
I understand veins are, maybe look, maybe I'm just in that mode because we're talking about this big
phallic object, but the vein pod, I don't know. That's also.
Undeniably a sexual term. I've just never previously like, hey, let me whip out my vein pod.
No, well, I have not thought, let me whip. I've never, that's a phrase that I don't think I've
ever consciously thought regardless of the word vein pod, but yeah, vein pod, vein pod is really
creepy. Yeah. Yeah. In a way that bar tickler is cute bar tickler. Like is, is it seems like a
euphemism, but it is kind of cute. I guess so. I find the Baja nature of it a little like
seat, you know, I'm not saying it's not seedy, but like, now it feels like a spring break kind
of thing. Vein pod is gross. Vein pod seems gross to me a little bit. Well, let me see if any others
top it in terms of goblin thistle is not sexual puff ball tree is. Is it? I don't call you don't
classify that as cute. I'm trying to get puff. Okay. You're right. All tree is very cute. Puff
does so much work. He's made the ruling. It's very puff puff takes away the sting. If it was
as a ball tree, then yes. But puff ball makes it seem fun. Ball cause of ball tree. Yeah.
That one's also weird. I still think ball tree. I I'm thinking of something in like the,
in the Teletubbies world or something. I don't, I'm not, I'm thinking about a penis right now
and I'm thinking, can you call it a ball tree? I don't know that you can. Well, but a ball,
a tree with like balls hanging from it. That's what I'm thinking of. It's like the fruit on the
tree look like testicles. Well, that's a whole other thing. So you're not thinking of that
genitals can be called a ball tree. You're imagining a tree that is with a lot of dangling
testicles. Yeah. And then miles Quaritch comes in and goes, what is this ball tree over here?
You like nicknames it a ball tree. Puff ball tree seems fun. Puff balls, like a little cute little
thing. It's like a Furby or something. I don't want to know the circumstances that led to a bunch of
testicles being dangled from a tree. I'm saying the puff ball tree itself, you know, you know,
all of it looks there. I think we've said before, there's a real crossover between Pandora and the,
the green planet, the ET. I feel like it is like just this like times 10 version of like a
kooky space nature world. So that's some of the delight of, of this place in this land. Spiny whip,
spiny whip clean could be a item that you use, but I don't think it itself is, is like, or, um,
I see a big one on here. You see a big spiny whip. Well, no, I see one that hasn't come up yet. I
mean, a lot of these just look like various, you know, exaggerations of succulents or underwater
plants that look very dirty as well. Well, that's true. Once again, you're the one with the, just
because suck is at the beginning. I have never heard the word succulent and thought, ew, this
word is body from now on this from the English language from now on, you're going to recoil when
you hear someone say it. What are you saying? The one that seems concerning is bladder polyp.
Like that is, that is something like you have to go to the doctor. That's a different situation.
There's nothing sexy about the phrase bladder polyp, but it is extreme. Yes. Why is a plant
called that? That's insane. Yes. That's real. That's a, that's a bad, that's a very bad thing.
Dapo FET just looks like a cactus that's blooming on the top. How do you spell it? Dapo, P-H-E-T.
Dapo FET. Not like Boba FET. Not Django FET. Not Django FET. Okay. Um, there's one more that,
well, no, I'm sorry. This is not a new one, but this is something from this guide and this is maybe
a good final point to make about the flask of reclinata. This is from there. You're not going
to believe when I get to the word and the word is in quotes, like it's calling to us. Um, this,
okay, let me just read some of the dry buildup of their ex. This is the official explanation.
Doesn't say bah, teckler. This is just what Disney and avatar say the flask of reclinata is.
Atmospheric toxins are absorbed by the plant and dissolve into liquid that accumulates inside.
When agitated, this primeval soup will build pressure before ultimately releasing a plume
from the top of the plant. Guys, what we've been talking about this whole time is a souping plant,
a souping seed, if you will. Wow. It soups. It soups the air and any sort of human that's under it
or Navi. You get souped from this plant. Yeah. So the phrase that we used before was I souped my
pants. Yeah. So if you go to the world of Pandora, you can say I souped that plant
by touching the open sore, by touching it's opens by rubbing. It's the open sore on its shaft.
Go soup that plant fresh boy.
Wow. Well, that's that. I think, I think that's the discussion of
of the souping plant. It's a thorough discussion. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We covered a lot of ground.
There's a lot to say in a much filthier episode than I realized it was going to be. One more
bit of business before we wrap it up. This premise will be completely unveiled again on the main feed,
but something that I wanted to do to tie together the topic and the, that, you know, it's December,
it's the holiday season as well as the Avatar season. And I thought we should tie all these
together by singing some carols, not Christmas carols, but a Motikaya carols to pay tribute
to the tribe and in the film. And that's what I've done. I'm going to gear this up. I might
hand you my little speaker. So here's, here's the first one of these to, to celebrate the season
with, you know, it's weird as people are hearing this, that it's just a few days away from the big
Avatar family reunion. All of our friends will be back at the table with us, but we don't like
everybody who gathers for the holiday festivities. There's, there's, there's always some, you know,
some family members who you're not always so happy to see. And that is what brings me to this song
here. I'm going to hand you this speaker. Okay. So now a tribute to the, the ultimate
no goodnik in the Avatar world.
You're a mean one, Miles Quaritch, a stain on the marines. You tell us we're not in Kansas as you
plot a genocide, Miles Quaritch. You're a spoiled sartuli bowl with banshee gun sauce.
You're a rotter, Miles Quaritch. Your mech suit reeks of farts. You calmly sip your coffee while
you bomb the giant tree, Miles Quaritch. I wish instead of coffee, your mug was full of hot
sulfury than a torsion. You're a dingbat, Miles Quaritch. A crooked, curdle, clod. In the sequel,
you're a Navi, but you're still an ass to me, Miles Quaritch. I'd like to take a huge pile of
unobtanium, shove it up your penis and make you pee it out like kidney stones.
Yeah. All right. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. The first beautiful Amati Kaya Carol,
we'll be bringing more of those to the table. We gotta release that on the main. Can we release
just that on the main feed? We could do, you could do a single drop. Yeah. Well, hopefully we end up
with a little EP here. We're still figuring out how many of these there are, how many songs there
are. Anybody bring, this is a potluck. Anybody bring them to the table because we have so many
friends who are, who we haven't seen in 13 long years and we have to celebrate them with song,
even the bad ones. So that's, that's for you, Miles. That's for you listeners. Thanks so much
for this. You survived the first night of Feliz Navidad, The Way of Winter for three bonus
episodes every month. Keep it tuned here to podcast the ride currently the Civico gate.
One more bonus episode on our new tier club three. So stay subscribed and check us back out on the
main feed Friday where the celebration continues. Civico ho ho ho everyone.