Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate where today we are saddened because the recently
re-elected Governor DeSantis and his cruel immigration policies have dealt a cruel blow to a sweet Russian mouse.
I'm Scott Gertner. Mike Carlson is mournful about this as well.
Yes, this is the number one thing, the bad thing that happened in the midterms is what happened to Fival.
Yeah, there was not a red wave.
Was it a red wave? Was it a flood? What was supposed to happen? It was supposed to be a flood, it was supposed to be a tsunami.
The tsunami, they were all saying it was going to be this massive.
Joe Rogan said it was going to be like the elevators in the Shining opening up with the red coming at you.
That's what he said. He knew it. He knew what was going to happen.
So for some reason, he wasn't right. He wasn't right. What?
He wasn't right about something Jason shared and I.
Hi. Yeah. Now it is the norm in most midterm elections that the party that holds the White House loses control of Congress.
And this is like they said the most in like 20 years that it has not happened.
And when it happened 20 years ago, it was after 9 11.
So the Republicans like hell no.
It's like, where's Jason going with this?
Where is he going? The magic numbers.
It was after the World's Fair.
Actually, it happened.
Jason goes to Vegas, every roulette table.
You put down nine.
Where do I go with the other one?
Twelve? No, it doesn't feel right to me.
No, the only red wave is what swept away the red shirt of our beloved rodent pal.
Yeah, I can only assume that's what that's what happened.
And and it's a shame we're losing Fievel.
And that's why we're talking about Fievel's Playland today.
Here's the broader context is that a couple of weeks ago,
Universal Studios Florida announced a bunch of closures of kid oriented attractions that are right next to each other.
I'm going to go through the list.
You can mourn as much as you want or skip them or whatever.
Curious George goes to town.
He will go to town no longer.
Shrek and Donkeys meet and greet.
I mean, already Shrek 40 is gone and now you can't meet or greet them.
I think you'll be able to meet and greet them in a different way in the future.
I don't have any information inside information, but I believe Shrek and Donkey will still be around.
So I'm not so worried. I'm not so worried about that.
This one was just opened recently and they're already closing it.
Yeah, I think they're going to be so like the Blues Brothers are still around.
Universal Hall or Orlando.
Universal tradition is keeping things around and certainly a long time.
So I would imagine Dreamworks destination.
This was in a list that they put out.
And I asked Jason, what the hell is that?
And you knew somehow it's what it is,
a smattering of Dreamworks characters in the old Barney building,
just kind of moving around, dancing around.
Oh, in the... So they kept the indoor setting of that.
They didn't do a whole lot.
Yeah.
Moving around, dancing.
Is it like the Madagascar guy that you see at all?
That's at the American Dream?
Yeah, Madagascar guy, a troll or two.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
Did the farting glitter in there or no?
I don't know that.
What happened to the farting glitter troll?
Do we know?
I still think I think they have it on merchandise, but I don't know how much
per day, farts per day you're getting at the moment on either.
I don't think it's... Yeah, I don't know.
Was this a character in the park?
Is that what you're asking?
That is not there anymore.
That was in the park right now.
Yeah, there was a... Yeah, they had figured out...
Finally, Imagineers, Universal Creative People had figured out how to make a
character fart glitter.
Rolly Crump had tried in 1965.
Trying to haunt him.
Ayahuasca didn't help him.
Yeah, Bob Gurr tried, killed a man.
The glitter ran inside the body of the performer.
Oh, God. Killed him.
Too tightly packed.
Like a bullet.
Yeah.
But finally they figured it out.
What did it do though?
Like, what was the glitter?
What did a glitter burst look like?
Like an explosion of glitter coming out of a walk around character's butt.
And it looked like a gender reveal party.
Like when those glitter guns or whatever things that shoot out colorful.
Like way above his head?
No, it went up horizontally.
Oh, wow.
It got some distance?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was really good.
I mean, it was naked glitter farting troll at Universal Orlando.
This is from the movie.
I believe it's in the movie.
Yeah.
It's not original park IP.
It's a little crass for my taste, but I have to appreciate the artistry.
I'm sending you the other video of it, but I actually just don't know
because I haven't seen a video of that dance party.
There probably wasn't a farting troll because I think it's too...
The effect probably is too...
Sounds dangerous and gorge.
Yeah, potentially.
Woody Woodpecker's Nuthouse Coaster.
Right.
And really what all of this is, is a gutting of one of Universal's main
lands, which is Woody Woodpecker's Kid Zone.
Right. That's what all of this is adding up to.
You know, this is we know that we know that Disneyland lands.
We know Adventureland and Frontierland,
and we know the Universal lands, World Expo, Woody Woodpecker, Kid Zone,
Production Central, and for any of these to disappear is gutting.
I'm gutted. We're all gutted.
And how can we how can this be done to Woody Woodpecker, Universal's Mickey?
We all agree.
And when I say we, I mean, the nation, the world agrees Woody Woodpecker is as beloved as Mickey Mouse.
And what now?
Now he has nowhere to prove it.
We can't see his nuttiness on display in his ultimate Nuthouse Coaster.
That's a good point.
Hopefully, when I add a Woody Woodpecker land to Epic Universe.
Oh, yeah.
I got to look up now and more Woody in the future.
But we have to figure out because we all
realize we don't like Woody Woodpecker on the show, right?
Yeah.
Yeah. He's like one of the least liked of these characters.
We don't ever think about his catchphrase.
It's not even a catchphrase.
It's a noise.
Yeah, I like what he does that noise.
You like that? I like it.
But I also want to see how old he is because you sent me a tweet the other day
wishing Felix the cat a happy one hundred and third birthday.
It's got one hundred and three years.
I like Felix. I've seen barely any Felix the cat.
I feel like I've seen some, but I like him so much more than I like.
Woody Woodpecker.
I like every character better than what he would.
I like an offensive maybe maybe.
But Felix has the magic bag as a kid.
I remember the bags called Mary Poppins bag.
Anything come out of it.
What do you would have better?
I have no fondness for whatsoever.
Felix the cat is a better candidate for like 20 years ago that they should have
been like, we need a guy.
This is our guy.
To have a Nutt House coaster.
Well, to have like Felix the cat's kid zone.
Yeah, I feel like we'd feel more warmly to that.
Maybe.
But I don't know.
I think neither is relevant to children in any way.
That's 100 percent correct.
But I'm just saying that Woody Woodpecker will be all kind of what a couple,
what a month when we're talking about Universal Bucks, maybe.
And you asked.
Oh, that's why it came.
Like the their equivalent of Disney dollars.
Those are close three, right?
Which are very expensive.
The universal books.
I was like, oh, wouldn't it be funny if I found Woody Woodpecker dollars?
And they're like 30 or 40 dollars a bill.
OK, yeah.
But yeah, Woody Woodpecker.
I don't I don't think I even knew Felix
the cat was associated with Universal Studios until this moment.
But you're right. Why not?
I guess if it's arbitrary, why is he not?
Look, we're going to we're going to do an episode about that.
We're going to discuss Woody Woodpecker in full.
Absorb all the Woody Woodpecker culture and see if that makes us understand why
kind of in the 90s, Universal landed on.
Well, I guess this is our guy.
And I guess he's our Mickey.
Yeah, it's a good question.
Yeah, we need to get there.
There's a long exploration, I think, that needs to be done here.
Yeah.
Figure out what's going on.
What is that until we're shutting down
Woody Woodpecker until we can figure out what's going on.
But for now, the biggest well, well, I'll say this.
I mean, today's topic, if I was Playland, is part of Woody Woodpecker's
KidZone and it is going away.
And that's why we're we're talking about it.
But let's talk about what's safe in Woody Woodpecker's KidZone.
I know you're waiting to hear it.
You need a soothing voice to tell you
SpongeBob store pants is safe.
You can still shop at SpongeBob store pants.
The animal actors stage is safe, unlike in Hollywood, which is breaking pretty
recently, I guess a couple of weeks ago as you're hearing this.
But losing that stalwart in Hollywood, they're shutting a lot down.
But the main thing, E.T.
Adventure is in Woody Woodpecker KidZone.
And this has always been the fear that that the wrecking ball finally comes in.
It is not happening.
E.T. is safe.
And the pizza place that's over there by the store.
OK, that is safe.
What's the name of it?
Do we know what that's called?
Let me look it up.
Is it? I don't think it's a fun.
I think it was in a list I was looking at and I didn't write it down because I
assumed it wouldn't come up and now Jason.
No, well, I was going to ask, like, are you excited to, like, take your son one
day to Florida and share the most mid pizza you've ever had at the
or you can cross the park to the New York Street and probably have the same pizza
or you can get it with a big mural of the Fantastic Four looking down on you at
Islands of Adventure. Oh, sure.
Yes. Yeah. Kind of same piece.
And I think I may be your first use of mid on the show,
which I remember that you said mid in a text and I didn't know what you were
talking about. And you respond when I asked you
responded with it's a young person insult.
It is.
I popularized on TikTok,
but it seems to go back to the wrestler MJF.
Did he invent a lot?
I don't know that he invented it, but I think like it caught on after he there
was a lot of clipped. I love to give him credit for it.
I just didn't know if it was his.
I think he's a young person.
His 20, like 20s at this point.
So young. Yeah.
Well, I'll be younger than late 20s.
Can't fathom. Hard to think of any numbers.
You know, I can't fathom it.
Too young to say mid.
Yeah. Well, no pizza will have to come.
Yeah. The mediocre pizza will have to come from elsewhere.
Oh, are you ready for this name?
Yeah. Yeah. Hit us with it.
Kids zone pizza company.
Wow. Kids zone pizza company.
So it's fine. So despite most of kids and disappearing,
their famous pizza company will be safe.
Yes. Great.
They haven't talked about there's no rebrand.
I guess there has to be a rebranding because Woody Woodpecker.
But kids zone to me sounds like Discovery Zone.
It sounds so very like, I guess, sort of generic in a way, too.
So base it probably a lot of things have been called kids zone.
Yeah. So you're probably a shoe store was kids zone at a certain point or whatever.
Kids clothing store.
So, yeah, losing Woody there.
I wonder if it'll be a new kids zone.
I guess this is maybe for the end of the episode, but there's maybe like Dreamworks
they're adding in, I'm not exactly sure.
But I wonder, yeah, if the kids own name will be complete.
And do they keep any of them?
Do they just redo the coaster?
Do they redo? Yeah, I don't know.
That remains to be seen.
So maybe even some of the things we're talking about today will be repurposed.
But it is all giant stuff that you would find if you were a mouse in the Old West
and it might be a little hard to repurpose a lot of that.
This all opened in 1992.
Fievel's Playland did rather not, I think, the rest of kids zone.
Not sure when all that was, but Fievel's Playland, it does feel like very
like grandfathered forever universal stuff goes way back in Hollywood as well.
I don't know.
When you guys heard this, did you feel like, well, that's actually a bit of a
classic universal thing that that's going on, or at least like from your childhoods at all?
Yeah, I have very warm memories, very clear memories of this.
I did find a picture.
I don't think I put it on my iPad today, but I do have a picture of me meeting Fievel
in this area, wearing a bright, wild, like paint splatter, orange Tasmanian Devil shirt.
It's a very 1993 picture, you know,
and I remember doing the slide with one of my parents.
But it is an area that when I've gone to Universal, I've got, wow,
it hasn't changed at all.
It's just like I remember.
It hasn't changed at all.
Because the other thing is I have very warm memories towards
Fievel and Wiley Burp and the whole Maskowitz family.
Of course.
And I am wondering.
We all got it. Wiley Burp.
No need to go further.
Yes.
I'm sure we'll talk about Wiley Burp planning.
But I know that is I looked up where can you stream the two American Tale movies
and you can buy them or rent them anywhere.
But the only place that Just Watch said was streaming is Stars.
Yeah.
So I want to know one ventures to Stars.
Are you crazy?
I don't think Stars is high on the like in terms of like streaming services people
have no no no that's a that's a free trial or nothing.
Nobody keeps something like Amazon.
You could get it through Amazon or like Amazon maybe is a stars like you could
get a stars trial via Amazon and I did watch the first one of these.
Yes.
OK.
And not to be too obvious.
But I as a kid really like the second one because it was very bright and it was
a Western and like I knew about like cowboy movies and stuff.
And so that was a little cleaner.
Whereas the first one is very melancholy.
The saddest movie.
Saddest.
I felt myself getting sad just watching the clip of the male singing somewhere out there.
Yeah.
It's a it's miserable for sure.
And it's very like
grimy and filmy and optical.
And I don't think that helps.
Like we we put it on and kind of only half paid attention to it the other night.
And we're and when it finished, we were like Aaron said it's weird.
I wouldn't there's things I wouldn't say this about from like the tooth or like
what she said. She just said like this feels like 60 years old to me.
Like there's things that are 60 years old.
I don't feel 60 years old.
And this one from 86 feels like ancient.
Yeah.
And it was I think it's from a time when
what was there was another thing I couldn't think of.
But like you you the American dream involved like Ellis Island immigrants,
your grandparents, your great grandparents, like this is a story told in a cartoon
with mice and I kind of got that as a kid.
Like I was like I was like I want these
mice to mice to come to America and have a better life.
Like I fully bought the premise
and now kids.
There's a lot of kids with parents who are insane and would have a stroke.
Keep the mice out. You mean telling them, describing to them what this is about.
Santas voters would see the first American Tale and be furious.
These films 86 was American Tale.
It is a film
produced by Steven Spielberg and therefore, yes,
Frank Marshall, Frank Marshall was one of the producers of this film.
Beautiful kisses.
The last time he came up, you called it cute that he plays guitar.
Yeah, this affection.
I swear you're more affectionate about Frank Marshall than I've seen you be about the baby.
Well, that's true.
Cute, so cute.
I haven't said anything about the baby, about being cute yet.
But Frank Marshall, yes, with his guitar.
So cute.
So I didn't realize the extent to which that I knew that there's that Steven
Spielberg credit and you're like, what does this mean?
Because his name's on a lot of a lot of stuff, but this completely was hand
delivered to Don Bluth, then Disney rival.
I mean, this is one of the things that made him a Disney rival.
He leaves the Disney folds because they were doing a very bad job in the late
70s, early 80s of holding on to promising talent.
They let everybody go out the door.
Yeah, Tim Burton and John Lasseter, chief among them.
Movies aren't good enough to keep them.
You're working on more mediocre movies and like, well, I wouldn't do that.
OK, well, bye. I'm out of here.
Surely this is not history repeating itself.
Would they have like 30 Imagineers on staff?
Yes, yeah.
Yeah. And Universal is announcing a zillion things and nailing it.
Just like if not, whom runs every Universal project?
They have a lot of RBI.
Yes. Yeah.
Just things are happening.
Things to announce and talk about.
Yeah, we might be in one of those in the old in the Imagineering world for sure.
But yeah, look, this is a this is a dark time.
It's a pre Eisner time.
This guy, if Don Bluth leaves, does odds and ends the video games
and the animated sequence of Xanadu, which is delightful,
ultimately makes Secret of Nym is the big movie.
Secret of Nym opens opposite E.T., the extraterrestrial, does horrible,
gets its ass handed to it.
But Steven Spielberg sees it, loves it, really wants to thinks Don Bluth
maybe his in because like Disney does it the way they do it.
That's not going to be my ticket to do an animated movie.
So he goes to Bluth, says we should do something,
leaves, Bluth doesn't hear from him for two years.
He comes back and he thinks, well, that was the end of that.
But then he does come back and just perfectly crystal.
It just exactly says immigrant mouse family, the Mousekowitz is.
And it's called an American tale.
And it's spelled like a mouse's tale, not like a story tale.
I think he was originally called Mousey
Mousekowitz is what I read.
And then then Spielberg came back and fiddled with it and said,
I think it should be Fievel.
And so he said, does anybody know that name?
And he said, that's my grandfather's name.
And that is why he is Fievel.
I did not know any of this stuff.
So before the fabelman's, before we all met and loved the fabelman's,
he invented the Mousekowitz.
Wow.
Yes, this was this was his most personal story.
I don't know. They're all pretty.
He's pretty personal. Sure.
So that's the secret there.
So this is like yet another one.
By the time it comes to the Universal Parks, it's yet another extremely
Spielberg property, just the domination he has over early Universal.
Even put next like it kind of wraps around the side of the adventure.
Build. Yeah, I saw one walk through where they're like,
that is the extended queue and it is like feet mere feet away.
Oh, gotcha.
If they need that, if they're using that.
Yeah. So the sequel, like the production of that had some interesting,
like I saw some little things because Don Bluth leaves.
I think Don Bluth not really involved in the sequel.
Not involved.
First American Tale, big hit, really outperforms Great Mouse Detective,
which Disney puts out the same year.
Another movie I watched a lot as a kid.
Yeah. And American Tale had VHS copies.
Yeah. So we had I didn't have a VHS copy of Secret of Nym.
I'd VHS copies of both of those.
And I probably watched them to death.
Yeah. Yeah.
So by the time you love Fievel, but I loved Fievel.
I love Fievel.
It makes so much sense to me so much.
And yeah, Mike, what was your your five?
I saw I don't think I saw the original American Tale.
Maybe I haven't seen all of it even to this day.
I saw Fievel goes west and I saw it in the Waterfall movie theater.
I talk about all the time.
So I remember as if I saw it like projected onto a waterfall, which is not how I saw it.
But then my memory there combined like we went under the waterfall and I went into
the sea, Fievel and it was a.
The theaters you see things in are very much part of it.
And when you saw the little pre rolls before the movie and the the company's
logo and the film strip man or the Regal roller coaster.
Yes. Did you go on the roller coaster or did you are in recent days?
You got on the Pacific trip through the Pacific.
Oh, yeah.
In the ocean, I see dolphins and I haven't been to Pacific theaters much.
I've seen multiple generations of the Regal roller coaster.
It like upped the CGI.
They all.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Regal roller coaster and film strip man, I think some of my fondest movie going
memories. Did you guys have Sony theaters?
I remember I can't remember when it started, maybe 96, 97, because I saw Star
Trek Generations there.
But I don't remember Sony theaters existing.
That might not have been everywhere.
Yeah, it feels like its own episode movie theater guys, movie theater.
Well, the Regal roller coaster, the Regal roller coaster.
Essentially, I mean, the one I rep is the General Cinema space candy,
which you guys are right back to watch things.
I have to I can't if there's a screen up, I have to watch the space candy,
something that's terrifying to me for whatever reason.
It's like, you know, it's just candy and popcorn and sodas popping up.
And it's like
there's no reason it should be terrifying.
But Aaron and I really bond over.
Yeah, you were scared of space candy, too.
And that's what it's called on YouTube.
Look up space candy.
Oh, yeah, that's probably something, though.
All the movie our friends before the movies begin.
But wait, where did that come out of the Pacific?
I mean, oh, my you asked me about five.
And I said, I said that's sort of my strongest memory of five.
I always liked five.
And I'm sure I did not go.
Of course, when I was a kid, I didn't go to Universal until I was a little older.
So it wasn't something on my radar.
But I was not that into five.
But I liked five.
I enjoyed him.
So
pretty big hit American Tale Land Before Time bigger hit,
which never super reflected in the parks, maybe here and there and some way.
But so they're really cooking with gas.
And then I don't remember why Bluth's not involved in Fylde Goes West.
I don't either.
I know Fylde Goes West kind of happened.
One of the reasons it was happened, it got rolling, is because
Steven Spielberg wanted the all the animators from who framed Roger Rabbit
to continue to have jobs was the framing I saw.
Just put them right into something.
Sure.
Dreamworks, not Illumination, that's the current company.
But Dreamworks
for a very short period of time, they had like
an animation
or Amblin.
It's something about it.
Like Amblimation or something.
It's very cumbersome.
I couldn't remember.
Yeah, I just remembered that it was cumbersome.
So Dreamworks animation that comes much later.
But Amblimation was not around for very long.
Yeah. Yeah.
But they make Fylde Goes West, which I agree I liked more,
more fun, poppy.
I didn't get to rewatch it.
Did you rewatch it? Have you seen it lately?
I haven't seen it lately.
I think the the I don't remember.
Did you watch it?
No. OK.
I was trying to remember.
I think the big songs were in the first one.
There are no cats in America.
I really loved it.
Yeah. Yes.
Yeah, I know. Well, like, what do you remember from any of it?
It's that there are no cats in America and the streets are filled with cheese.
Oh, I remember the showdown.
The high noon showdown at the end of the movie,
which is done with slingshots.
With is it Fyvill and
Cat R.
Wall, Cat R.
Wall voiced by John Cleese.
Well, and Wiley Burp pulls himself out of his stupor.
Voiced by the late Jimmy Stewart, I believe, last final role.
Jimmy Stewart's final film role is as Wiley Burp, which I don't want to say.
Look, I'm not trying to rewrite history.
I obviously didn't know who Jimmy Stewart was as an actor, but I knew every cartoon
had a character who referenced Jimmy Stewart.
Oh, so that character made sense to me.
Yeah.
In Little Did I Know.
Oh, no, it's the actual guy.
It's not the Looney Tunes doing a joke about the actual guy's voice.
Sure. This is the guy.
But you've heard some facts.
Oh, wow.
My feelings about these two and I guess I have I've seen a lot of the first five.
But I'm trying to think.
I always get them mixed up in tone wise with the rescuers movies because I feel
like there was a similar thing where like the first rescuers is a lot like
quieter and obviously there's a big break between the movies.
I forget how many years between those.
But like the first one is like a mood and it's a little more sad.
And the second one's kind of just like
feels to me like more of a straightforward.
Kind of a brighter, more of an adventure.
Yeah, yeah.
I think Bluthman would be part of rescuers.
It was because by the time I think he worked on that and then Secret of Nim is
about mice. So then when Spielberg showed up and said, so it's about mice, he was
like, I don't know, but he can't say no to the mouse guy.
Spielberg. Yeah.
And it's mice in a human world.
It's like the mice stuff mirroring what the like Great Mouse Detective, like the
thing with Ben Franklin, Ben and me.
I loved Ben and me as a kid.
Me too.
Oh, history.
I loved Ben Franklin from the park.
I was probably to me like Ben Franklin, a character from the Disney theme parks.
Yeah.
Well, then when that VHS went in during elementary school, oh, boy.
Second only to when they showed us Turtles and the New Line Cinema logo played.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy.
They can't couch that as educational whatsoever.
Hey, I bet if you showed Ben and me now, it would come back.
But I the faintest.
It was like a little mouse helped Ben Franklin figure out electricity.
He was up in his hat, way predating retatooie.
He like hangs out up there.
Yeah.
Wait, does he know he's that they talk, right?
Or do they not? Is it just accidental?
Good question. I don't know.
Does he leave items out to spark ideas and Ben Franklin?
The mouse is dressed, though, with like a tricorder hat.
He also has a hat.
I don't think he has like a tick up there.
Yeah.
Doesn't have a being whispering ideas to him.
At least they didn't show that.
Is it the voice of Winnie the Pooh?
Is it Sterling Holloway?
Man, I think possibly.
I didn't realize we were going to be talking about all of these questions.
They might. I feel like I can't be pulling these questions from nowhere.
That seems right to me.
Yeah.
I'll look at Benjamin Franklin mouse thing.
What is an official Disney?
Yeah.
It was like a feature at basically.
OK, so you'd see it paired with other things or I don't know what the release
of it was like and certainly in in schools, I would say.
Yes. Sterling Holloway.
Sterling Holloway is the mouse.
So good.
Always. I wonder if it's on Disney Plus.
Probably not, as I'm saying that sentence.
Yeah, I don't know if it was either it was in that initial glut when everything
came out or it's an awkward fell between the cracks because it's not a feature
length thing, I don't know.
But yeah,
I mean, we were we were wondering this like, what does anyone remember?
Because this is the main thing I would say.
Fievel, I don't think any, but they've done nothing with this.
These movies fell out of the consciousness.
I think maybe Fievel, the Fievel popularity had died down by the time
Fievel goes west came out then in the early 90s.
Right.
So talk about now it is kind of I don't think there's been many generations of
kids now who want to go to a playground and run around, but they have no idea what
Fievel is, what America who the Mousekowitz is are and the hardships they endured.
They don't know anything about that.
It versus like the land before time,
which we realized recently there's 17 sequels still being produced by that one
company. So if you're yeah, if your parents are like on the the cheap red box,
yeah, then they might still know who Littlefoot is.
But these, yeah, they did not milk these for endless.
So there's a couple of straights of video
sequels that I have no idea what happens in them.
And there was a TV show Saturday morning show also with the old West veneer.
Yeah, I remember that that I don't think was very good.
I think that might have occurred even then.
I thought might have like taught me that.
Well, Fievel every week. Oh, this isn't OK.
Maybe not every Saturday morning product is great and perfect.
But yeah, these are they're sort of lost to the sands of in a way, this entire
it has a lot in common with ET that ET and Fievel are right next to each other.
And these are both Spielberg characters,
properties, worlds that we have let decay.
Yeah. And there's a good side to that,
which is that there haven't been a mind numbing amount of terrible sequels or
retreads. Right.
But the flip side is we're losing these legends.
We aren't passing them on to the next generation.
Yeah. I wonder, curious George, how much lives like in book form?
I think he's around and like scary are still around.
But like I have mentioned, like, say,
Amelia Bedelia to people and just blank slate.
But then again, I like that was an old reference when you were a kid.
Was it? I mean, they making it even after
the author passed, like people took over.
That wasn't a thing that every kid.
And when we were kids, I knew it, too, because my mom would bring it up.
But I don't think most kids knew Amelia Bedelia.
We had a ton of Amelia Bedelia books sitting around in school and at home.
Like I don't I didn't.
But on the other side, like a lot more people know Eloise.
Jane grew up with like Madeline and Eloise.
I knew Madeline a little because there was a cartoon.
Yeah. But Amelia Bedelia, I just think was an old reference.
Then, yeah, I think, do you do you know?
Yeah, but that might have been that might have been another thing.
Our parents were passing to us.
I think so. Yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, look, there's there's no fire.
We kind of we remember vague details about these movies.
We know that the first one is sad.
We know that there is the song somewhere out there, which I realized something
about this, that here's the thing Disney straight up stole from the Bluth films.
Maybe only this one, but somewhere out there, version in the movie sung by kids
kind of like off key, I was going to say charmingly.
I'm not sure if that's true.
Having rewatched it, I was like, this is what's in my head.
Somewhere out there is the saddest song, like whatever people apply to Hallelujah.
I put on somewhere out there like there's no sadder song ever made because it
reminds me of being three years old and that you mean there's a there might be a
chance that the people I love won't be with me all the time.
Like it reminds me of the most raw emotions that are gutting.
And then I watched it and like Aaron, both of us were both like, this is the song
that's like wrecked us since we were children.
But there's the version of the movie and then they did the hit, the adult
contemporary hit with Linda Ronstadt and James Ingram.
And this is before Disney straight up
stole this, this idea of the movie.
The first time that has ever happened.
I think it's the first like modern hit.
It's the first post MTV hit from a kids animated movie.
Before they started doing it with Beauty and the Beast and Aladdin, both Pibo.
I love Pibo.
I like Pibo.
But that became like the formula was interesting version in the movie.
And then we also get kind of a
syrupy adult contemporary hit out of it.
So I think they completely.
Yeah.
Can you feel the love tonight?
They really like a lot of the songs.
Yeah. I remember my music teacher in elementary school just always playing.
I was like, why aren't you playing as the one from the movie?
What is this other one?
What are you like?
I didn't know there was a soundtrack cut in the album, like the single.
That one's confusing because the one in the movie has like plot points in it.
So like the when you when you hear Elton on the radio, you don't want to hear him
singing like the king, he really is the king or this parts about where Timon and
Pumbaa are like their friend is leaving them.
Beware if Elton was singing from the point of view of Pumbaa.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
He wrote it. He did write it.
But you know, you want to like streamline it so that like it can be like a wedding
song, I guess, and it's but that's somewhere out there.
The the the hit version of it loomed large for me.
And also, I thought Aaron and I think both agreed like we when we're three years
old, we knew that as a hit song and we're like, wow, adults must be really sad.
Adults must listen to sad.
This was this must be as heavy as it is to be an adult, which is something she also
said about the song She's Like the Wind by Patrick Swayze.
You know, Patrick Swayze, yeah, yeah, I think we just heard that was Lindsay was
on Lindsay's playlist yesterday.
It popped up. Oh, well, yeah.
Did you did you get sad when she said the wind came?
I actually didn't.
But now I got to go back and listen to it.
Everyone put it on her little like kids tape player and then just sway around and
kind of like get law and like think like, so this is what it'll be like.
I better be happy now, because when I'm an adult, it'll be as sad as Swayze is.
Well, wasn't wrong in a lot of ways.
Not 100 percent wrong.
We all feel Swayze's burden here and there.
Yeah.
Anyway, all this is I'm just collecting like general
American tale memories.
But here's the strongest one I have is that we're talking about the Florida one
closing, but this was in Hollywood and I think in Hollywood before
Universal Florida was even open, I want to say 89.
And so it was a big part of my early going to Universal experience.
And not just that, not that it's this big,
foamy playground.
And we've talked about those not foam like foam at a foam party, but foam like soft
foam and and been soft slides and stuff.
So I love that element of it.
But what I also remember is
if you haven't been in L.A. and been past Universal Hollywood,
now I feel like people joke about the minion, that there is a big minion you can
see from the freeway with his big single eye and that that is like it's become kind
of an accidental L.A. landmark, maybe not accidental.
It's just our choice whether to like view that as is this our Statue of Liberty?
Does it have to be because we don't have a lot of choices?
It does. Yeah, I accept that.
It's fine. But like before you had the minion
peering out in the freeway, there's basically there's two freeways where you
could see Universal really well, the one I want and the one thirty four.
And just what I remember my whole childhood until 97 when they took this down
was that you could see Fievel's Playland clear as day up on the hill from either
freeway. So if I'm going to if I'm on a field trip,
if I'm going to the Gene Autry Museum or the zoo or if my dad's taken me into
Hollywood to see the Capitol built to teach me about Beach Boys lore,
just in doctorate early, I just like
it was just part of the L.A. skyline to me was Fievel stuff.
And I don't even remember what you could see exactly.
You know, it's probably like a big a big spool or I don't know,
the slide that's like a big banana.
I don't know what you could see from the freeway, but just my whole childhood,
I would go like, wow, there's Fievel up there.
That's like a dumb kid thing that I can see from the car.
And it made me happy every time.
And I'm glad you can see. I think kids get that with the minion.
I imagine how excited a four year old is to see the minion on just a drive
to the store or whatever.
So that's that's they get that now.
But this was like it was a part of my childhood not even going into the park
and going to the playland.
Do you think what
less of an effect on kids like look, see that building?
That's the Terminator 2 building and actually the mural on the side.
They took a frame and they blew it up
to such massive proportions.
It looks like abstract art.
You think a kid is saying?
Possibly less children.
I think less. Yeah.
What do you think Mr.
Cameron would have to say about that?
Yeah, less less child excitement about cyberdine systems.
But I'm glad that's back, I guess, to the minion is what I'm saying.
And I just I don't know, I did just buy all of this hook line and center.
And I like
that I feel like in my memory, I think the Hollywood one was bigger than the
Florida one. I think there was more stuff to do and it was a bigger
auditory or like an amphitheater for the little show they did.
Right. But the Florida one, despite I think having a smaller physical
footprint, loomed larger to me because of extra stuff.
It was more relevant because of the more recent Fievel goes West and the water slide.
That's one of the weirdest things.
If you're listening to this and you've never been over there, you go to
Universal Florida before it closes, which I think is January 15th,
twenty twenty three is the final day.
I think I feel like a lot of people do not know there is a water slide over there.
Raft water.
You do it on a really confusing type of water slide.
It's not swim trunks because you go, well, why would there be a water slide
in a non water park? How does that work?
Well, you just got to try to stay dry on this little raft, which kind of gets
ripping is what I recall, at least having the last done it when I was
10 or something. It was really fun.
It's not too long.
So you're not too excited or too scared.
You don't have time. You're going to get a little terrified.
You're not going to get soaking wet, but you might get a little splash.
I would equate it to like Pirates of the Caribbean wet.
It's there's a similar ride system at
Volcano Bay where you get on a thing.
Yeah, you get and it's not just an inner tube.
It's like a little piece of something.
And you're like, this is an odd way to go down a water slide.
So more like aerodynamic is in a tube.
Then you're spinning. It's kind of fat and it takes its time.
Yes, but a little sleek bobsled.
Maybe you can get it like that.
And it feels a little scary because it's a bigger slide than this.
Then we're talking about here. But yeah, I didn't know that this was here.
I didn't know until looking into it for this.
Yeah, I didn't know it was there.
I didn't know it was there. I've never really done this.
You didn't know about until looking into it for this.
Correct. Yeah, I didn't know that was there because you didn't really go
to this as a child when you were the right age to be in.
Right. And so, yeah, when I was more of an adult, more of an adult, I would.
Oh, there's a big playland like the Honey, I Shrunk the Kids thing.
Oh, that's cool. Take a look around anyway.
Back to the things I'm even though I wanted to go in like the rope,
whatever you call it, the thing that we walk up the ropes.
I don't know.
You always want whatever these like net bridges.
I don't know what the net bridge.
Yeah, I want to do that.
But rope is more accurate, actually.
But yes, rope bridge is probably where you go.
The Grizzly Challenge Trail of California
Adventure is much more welcoming to adults to do it than these other ones.
There's more space.
It's a pretty grand one.
But if you're in kind of a claustrophobic climbing space with mostly children,
that is not a good situation to be in.
No, I didn't notice.
This is wild to me because if I had known this full extent when we were down in
Florida and we like we I remember us all going on ET at the start of the day.
If I had known this, I would have been like, come on, Michael, we're doing the slide.
We're doing the slide.
This is a formative theme park memory for me.
Wow. And it is just a blank space for you.
Well, the play I don't have the I don't have it.
Yeah, I can see where it would have been.
But yeah, we didn't go.
We were so brand loyal when I was younger,
which is still like I talk to some people and there is still some like weird
Jiffy Skip brand loyalty for certain people.
So we're like we go to Disney World and that's it.
I go, yeah, but why?
What is this?
Well, I think we have to start breaking apart.
We can help break it apart because we know what's happening.
Universal Resort Florida is on the rise.
That's correct.
We get better. They're only letting Disney to.
Yeah, I'm starting to think it's the place I've said a thousand times.
But I think that's where I think it's where the base of operation.
That's what they're that's the strategy is to get people staying just there.
And then maybe they do a couple of days at Disney.
That's a long term Disney.
But the base is because the most the most the molten core of stuff to do.
Yeah, long term plan.
Makes sense to me.
My family did that a few times in the early 2000s and it was very fun.
Well, you guys were trendsetters.
Yeah. And it was it was not super built up.
It is crazy to think about, too,
that the last new theme park in Orlando from one of these big companies was
the Islands of Adventure and the next brand new theme park in Orlando is also
from Universal Florida. Wow.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
Nothing not entirely new park from although I'm glad they should.
They should fix the ones they have.
Well, yeah, right.
Yeah. Less complicated to be there.
I don't know. But maybe take some prices down to while you're at it.
No, they're going to keep pushing it as much as they can.
As much as we can take.
That's right.
So the maybe some of the lack of awareness that there's a water slide here and
that it doesn't loom large to anybody really, unless you've been over there,
is that it doesn't really have a name.
I looked at a map and it's just called Fievel's Playland Water Slide.
Yep. How do you not?
How do you miss an opportunity to do like rip roaring?
Yeah, I give it some.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel like it would it would help.
I feel I think on the park map, it even just becomes lowercase.
That's how joyless it is.
Yeah, it was Playland Water Slide Water Slide.
I think it's an afterthought.
Name the thing. Name it for the last two weeks.
Do you think Steven Spielberg knows it's here?
Gosh, maybe not.
He might not have had a lot of eyes on.
He probably was not so hands on with the way to begin with.
And then I bet the Playland not either.
But it's interesting because supposedly
the rumors are that like Spielberg has some protection over.
Like he's at least keeping E.T. in Orlando.
I don't know if this is true at all,
but there's some feeling like he really wants E.T.
and he is a little more protective of E.T. than, say, the Jurassic Park franchise.
We'll maybe let whatever happen to it.
Anything you want to do.
Maybe he doesn't give a shit about the Jurassic Park franchise.
If they try to touch the E.T. adventure,
I think that I believe what will happen is Steven will get very pale and emaciated.
Oh, my God, you're right.
And having to get put into a tube and then only when they start plugging stuff back
in, will Steven spring back to life.
Right.
Sick Steven. No.
That scar.
No one who could take that.
The bulldozers, as soon as he's dead, will come out for E.T.
I'm worried.
I'm just I feel like it's simple.
I think the fact that it made this round means that it has become whatever the
Peter Pan's flight of it or the, you know, the Mad T part.
I don't know what you want to call it, but like it's become the Disneyland 55.
It's becoming that it's Universal 90, which is a long time ago at this point.
And it's like the one thing that's like
where you would say something that you say about Disney stuff way more often,
which is it's a little out of date, but it's so charming.
It's so charming.
And it's part of the part.
And it's been there since the beginning.
Like they have one of those and it's now and that's genuine history.
And they got to keep it.
That's the only thing.
Well, look, we were just talking about this on a text, but like I recently there's
a little more retro merchandise, there's a little more, I feel like embracing of
Universal's history.
And I also think the argument for like the Monsters land,
they're building an epic universe is a little more of like, yes,
this is Universal history type classic property.
So I'm hoping that they realize that about ET.
Yeah, they're so aggressive with everything else with demolishing it,
which we like in some way, really like.
But when it comes for a friend and by friend, I mean Botanicus ET.
I'm OK with I have no ill will towards ET.
But when I say friend, Botanicus is yeah, if they could just keep that there in the
line, whatever ride they replace it with, as long as Botanicus is still there.
They get rid of Botanicus.
We will all turn.
Oh, yeah, that's good. More white and sick.
Yes.
So so you're saying so as long as they just put him somewhere like hurry Hobbs
and Shaw need your help. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're worried they can't push 90.
Check this out.
It's the old rotating statue from the Universal Monsters Cafe.
They had to put us somewhere.
Yeah, whatever. Yeah.
They had the turntable sitting around.
So I'm here now.
He's just how you guys been?
They could just put they could just change that.
Put that into a bathroom or something.
I have them in one of the stalls.
Hi. Whatever occupied.
Come back later.
Sparkles on the door.
I'm making magic in here.
This is right now.
This room is the brown planet, if you know what I mean.
Then he goes back into the toilet.
You know, it's weird. It smells nice here, too.
It's still got the smell.
Did you have you read about the smell?
I know the smell change.
It changed.
You read this? I don't feel great about this.
Supposedly.
And there's a lot of speculation, but the smell is now different.
The classic ET smell is like more of a generic forest smell now.
And I saw speculation that the company who made the original smell went out of
business so they had to find a different smell.
We'll just talk to any of the great candle manufacturers across Etsy and other
stores, but they never got the formula just perfect.
Yeah.
So it's not safe to light.
I bet you light enough candles in that place.
The whole thing blows up.
That's going to know what they built that right out of universal.
It does have a relationship with some of those candle manufacturers now.
They do make official stores.
Oh, really?
I don't know which one.
I don't want to get it wrong because there's a few of them now.
Oh, really?
Yeah. Wow.
I didn't know that at all.
I haven't seen that out here because I've been up to those stores recently.
Like those rotating stores.
Oh, my gosh. We got to look into that.
Yeah. But yeah.
So the smell is different.
So look here, I'm going to play a little clip to get us back into Fievel
World, which is this is from an ad.
This is an ad from Hollywood from 1991.
And this just exemplifies that it was, you know, look, the playground out here was
built for the first movie, but then it's Fievel goes West mania.
And I guess this is the context that then, you know, that propels Fievel into 1992.
Kids are meeting Fievel face to face because now their movie ticket to Fievel goes west.
Give them a coupon good for free.
There's a little that was a little like
standoff old West style where like close up on kids eyes, close up on Fievel's eyes.
But then it's nice.
Then they all run at him and hug him like this.
Fievel going to shoot you?
No, he's not.
I would think that if I saw this.
Yeah. So Fievel in real life is bad.
He's mean, not like in the movies.
And then, you know, and then you see all his friends like,
I don't know, old West can can dancer mouse who no one on this earth could name
and naming like more than three characters from American Tale.
I guess that's not true because I can name Tiger
and I can name Wiley Burp, but I couldn't name Wiley Burp until like three days.
Is it doesn't she become a can can?
Oh, that's right. Yes.
Do you know her name? I do not.
Yeah. The fan.
I know the mask.
I don't know names.
I couldn't have named Katar wall until this till brand of research.
Let's let me remember what else is in this
admission to Universal Studios Hollywood.
They'll see a spectacular new show and
the magical
Bible playland.
So hurry on out, partner.
Isn't that like that's what you think and hope it'll be that it's not just like
I go on a slide that looks like a banana over and over and I have to wait in a line
when I do it and I have to really get my mom's attention, who's already watched me
do it nine times, so she would like to not watch.
She's she doesn't care that I'm going in the banana slide again.
But in this scenario, in this commercial,
Fievel and his whole family and lots of other kids are cheering me on.
I'm the star of Fievel's Playland today.
Did you see that?
There's a picture, a promo image of Fievel going on a slide with the kids behind him.
Yeah, yeah. Yes.
Uh huh. And he's huge.
His face is really big.
Yes. Yeah.
That face is like this is as wide as four children stacked up.
That's what you always imagine at any of these places at Chuck E.
Cheese when they would show the commercial is like you're going to be like
partying with the characters.
Yeah. Yeah.
But it was never disappointment like a Chuck E.
Cheese would be like maybe the teen on on duty there would like mess with your hat
if you were wearing it and you like not like it, it would be annoying if he didn't
have like a shift cleaning the bathroom in 10 minutes.
Right. Yes.
He would maybe come over and like take your hat off and you'd be like
uncomfortable and then he would leave.
What is this? Why is this?
I want my hat.
Yeah.
I mean, but what that looks like magic.
And I felt some amount of this.
I liked all the things.
Do you remember, Jason, do you remember anything
when you like there's a water slide for sure.
But was there anything else that's like, oh, there's that thing.
I would go on this slide or play with that
in that like dense room of ropes or whatever it was.
Well, I remember the actual slide.
They kind of upgraded in Florida.
It's big cattle skeleton.
Cool. Like a skull.
A big skull.
And then the spine.
Yeah.
Right. The spine. You walk up.
You walk up a dead animal's spine and then you take a slide down
the sinister massive skull.
I
you know, I rewatched a lot of walkthroughs and I remember going through the room
with like, I'm pretty sure I remember going through the room.
I may have convinced myself otherwise of the like hanging foam.
Like, like mini punching bag, little punching bag.
I know what you call it.
Yeah.
Do you think when Spielberg, when this opened, he went up to the top of the
bleached cow skull, but he wouldn't go down it and he had to be evacuated off at the top?
He had to walk back down the stairs.
Maybe.
No, they got people to carry him.
OK.
Be careful of this.
That's a really good inside joke, by the way.
You know, this
Jurassic Park ride.
I remembered the big newspaper.
Yes.
Fables Playland open at Universal Studios, it says.
There's a few jokes, a few things in it that stuck out to me.
One, it's dated July 4th, 1980 or 1892.
I'm assuming this opened.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
The other thing.
I wish I could come here every day, says one child.
It's very, it's Jason S.
The there is the sentence.
And don't forget the live stage shows.
Universal did forget those live stage shows reasonably quickly.
I feel like that has not happened in a long time.
Yeah, I don't know when that stopped in Florida.
It was a smaller show in Florida.
It was an opening day thing in Florida.
I didn't realize it moved.
It was in San Francisco, which became
Beetlejuice, which became Fast and Furious.
Yeah.
But it was smaller than the Hollywood one,
which had which was like Waterworld size.
There were big bleachers.
So you'd like I watched a video.
I watched a video from 1993 where the bleachers are the third full.
But the coolest thing, because the characters come down for they arrive
in America, walking past you go down onto the stage and off in the distance,
you can see construction cranes building our future home city walk.
Half built city walk a mess like in the movie.
There's a lot of movies set around like it's the Statue of Liberty,
but it doesn't have its full face yet.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. It's like seeing the Death Star being built.
Yeah.
Just knowing the adventures that will come in that.
The show what the show had that is pretty crazy was this giant tiger tiger.
The Dom DeLuis voiced cat.
If you don't know these movies, they think and assume in song that there are no cats
in America, and this is some of the promise that America holds.
These immigrant mice who come over, who sneak onto a ship and hope for a better
life at Ellis. They also do Ellis Island, where also there's a thing where they have
to get their names changed, even though they are mice.
And this this system need not apply to animals as well.
But
so they think there's no cat.
And then you quickly they do encounter cats and the cats are mostly pretty mean.
But there is one cat who hangs out with the bad cats, but he's not a bad cat.
He's nice. He's Dom DeLuis.
And and he
there's a gigantic version of him in this show that I never knew what it was and how
it was. I think I thought it was a robot because the proportions are kind of like
King Kong. It's a lot like King Kong, where it's just like chest up.
Right.
Like, well, this is a kid friendly version
of King Kong, which I at the time was probably too afraid to see and go on the
tramp tour.
But I didn't know until prepping for this.
That's a puppet.
That is a giant puppet, which is incredibly impressive.
Is it like that stay puff they had in that Ghostbusters show?
I think that has to be a puppet, too, because it wasn't probably built a robot
that would stay there.
But I already don't remember how that was
such several Halloweens ago, and I don't know what it was.
That's true.
I think it has to be some sort of puppet.
I mean, there's no way they I don't think they build like robot, like pure robots
for shows like this.
No, that was a big deal on Broadway when they did the King Kong musical.
I think they built more of a robot one.
That's a reason.
Yeah, it's closed now.
But I think it was a mix of animatronic and robot.
But like Universal also, I think the creature from the Black Lagoon musical,
that fucking Nightmare Show,
that someone was in.
That we know you mean?
No, you know what it was?
I believe the actor Katrina Lenk, who was doing Company on Broadway,
who had COVID when I went to go see it, is in a video.
She is the creature from the Black Lagoon musical when she is younger.
Anyway, there was a big creature in that on stage.
Right. Yeah.
They did spend some money on that production, which made its folly that much funnier.
Yeah. Yeah.
Really inexplicable.
I don't know what that was about.
Anyway, this thing, like I saw a diagram of it and it's crazy.
It has animatronic part like the face has animatronic elements.
But then there's somebody in the main body turning it.
And then there's a person in each giant hand and two of the fingers move so it can
hold stuff, it can hold Fievel. Really insane.
I remember any iteration of this show.
I must have seen it in Hollywood and Florida.
Like really blew me away.
Like everything you want as a kid of like,
but the movie I like is coming to life before.
Like there's nothing of that.
I always liked the stage shows of Beauty and the Beast or whatever.
But to me, getting to see a giant tiger
like blew any of those, any of the Disney ones out of the water.
Yeah. Were you afraid because it was a big thing in a smallish place?
I was probably on edge, but no specific memories of being.
I'm sure I would have been on edge because I was on edge when I thought Shredder
locked us in the room for the Turtles show, the live Turtles music show.
Junk. Yeah.
I was like, the doors are locked.
And then it was like it was intermission.
And I was like, wait a minute. We left the doors.
He told us it was locked.
Go.
Boy, we all outsmarted him.
I think at that point I added another layer.
He must have meant the outside of the theater doors.
He's Shredder is no fool.
There must have been a real plan here.
Anyway, I liked the show.
You get all the you get the hits.
You get No Cats in America.
You get somewhere out there and you get the other songs, which I
do not remember nearly as strong.
Yeah, there's one that's like that's like the West Side Story America,
but it's not that we're here in America.
Finally here in America.
I guess I liked it enough to want to sing it.
So I don't remember if it's in the movie or not.
It's like the Neil Diamond song.
It's kind of like that.
It's like an impetuous.
On the train.
Yeah, it's kind of it's between that and West Side Story.
Solid America song.
Right.
And oh, and then there's a lot of pyro.
There's like it's a shocking amount of like so much goes on at the end.
It ties together both movies.
It's kind of like they arrive in America and then Fievel says he wants to go west
and then they go west.
So you get all of it.
What happened? Why did Fievel?
Oh, here's the I mentioned earlier
poor Don Bluth.
E.T. blows secretive name out of the water.
Then what happened?
Like, all right, this is a hit and maybe we can keep making Fievel movies.
Meanwhile, Katzenberg has showed up on the scene and he's like, not on my watch.
Disney animation gets back into shape.
And by the time Fievel to Fievel goes west is ready.
It opens on the same day opposite another animated film called Beauty and the Beast.
And that might have something to do with why Fievel does not loom as large
in our consciousness as he was.
That's true.
That's the bummer.
I was trying to figure out the time range of like, could you have made a Fievel
where he's grown up and fighting in the trenches of World War One?
Could you have?
I was trying to figure out what years were the first two supposed to take place?
Do mice live that long?
Oh, that's a good point too.
He's sort of a more I was about to say he's more realistic mouse than Mickey,
but that's maybe not true.
Maybe you can make it to World War One.
Yeah, you can make it to World War One.
You can do it. Dunkirk with.
Yeah, one single shot with Fievel.
It's also just the companies that
it's crazy. I think I'm sure I've said this before, like Toy Story is the best
example of something that it's madness to think about me seeing it in 90.
What? Five? Yes.
How little I was and how the characters feel new ish to me still.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like there's no like the the the new Golden Age with Mermaid and Beauty and the Beast.
Like also feels like that.
But I still really think of them as in my childhood, not Toy Story, though.
Yeah.
In some bizarre way where I go, wait a minute, I was 10 when I saw Woody for the first time.
I know. Yeah, yes.
The more than half your life ago.
I go, that's not right.
That isn't right.
They feel so relevant still to this day.
And I guess because obviously the sequels have been good and big hits.
But yeah, I think as opposed to it,
like a Bugs Life is maybe you got to like go back and remember what those characters
you probably can't name all of them.
You have a vague sense of it.
I'm not against.
I like stuff about Bugs Life.
But yeah, sure.
But but it's interesting.
Yeah. With five, like it's interesting how
certain things just like they die off quickly in the public consciousness.
And even though the first one was a hit and we all have something, we all have some
memories of five, but like just wasn't a well-oiled machine.
Even Disney wasn't doing sequels yet.
So like they took a little while to get it out and then Disney crushed them.
And yeah, I don't know.
It was not it wasn't polished yet.
So what clearly, I mean, probably the easier answer is to demolish Fievel's
Playland as they are going to do because it is very small and flimsy.
And it will be a day's work.
But
you know, if they want to, they have this character, if they want to do anything
with it, I just like, don't we want to see Fievel with very realistic hair?
That's like we got it right.
Like, clearly we as a culture are demanding to see every character we vaguely
recall from any point in our lives, but with every follicle of hair,
it's clear as day in a beautiful CGI manner.
You're not talking about in real real live action.
I'm not talking about you're talking about
Fievel made with the modern Warfare 2 engine.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
No. Yeah.
Beautiful hair.
Fievel.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's you know, it's what always held Pinocchio back is that like this draw,
this vague shape of a cat, I don't even know what I guess it's a cat.
But how do I know there aren't thousands and thousands of hairs that are
especially clear if this cat leans up into the camera, which he does in every
single shot, Fievel has not gotten the opportunity to be done to an incredibly
photorealistic degree.
We owe him that.
We do owe him that because I want to like him as much as I like honest John in that
Pinocchio movie. I want him in my face.
You want Fievel looking at you and going, is that even a thing?
Can't Fievel say some modern quips also?
Can't we add that to his repertoire?
Fievel doing the TikTok dance like the scary Megan
robot for the new horror movie.
I think I know that movie.
I'll say that. I don't know the dance you're talking about.
No, she's just doing like with the little kid.
They're like filming like a dance on their phone.
And later she's killing people.
She's doing like a dance again.
So Fievel will do the TikTok dance.
Yeah. I mean, why?
Why not?
I really I don't know.
Is the Fableman's? Is there been a premiere yet?
Can we run up to Spielberg on the red carpet?
Can we hop the barricade and go on Sir, Sir?
Realistic fur. He's realistic fur.
Let me show you on my iPad.
Realistic fur. Fields of Flanders.
Modern retelling for modern times.
I like Jason's notion of let's see the rest of Fievel's life.
Then what happens and like I mean, so does he have to experience history?
Is the part of the stock market crash?
Oh, yeah.
Does he get really into spiritualism and like try to con people out of like,
I can speak to your dead relatives.
Is that timing starting to work?
It works out. You know, what year is that start?
That late 1800s, early 1900s.
When people would start conning people.
So many people died in the Civil War.
There were so many people looking for an answer.
Looking for. Yeah.
So, whoa.
So, so in your your pitch is it's still the Fievel we knew, but he is older.
He found his calling in America as a sham psychic.
He's a piece of shit.
John Edwards style.
Fievel meets Jamie Loftus's ghost church.
Like, you know, there's a word with C.
Is this how Fievel sounds?
A word C, a name with a C I'm getting.
Is there a C in the name?
Maybe he's maybe he becomes like the Houdini of mice.
Maybe he's debunking it.
Debunking.
He becomes a big showman.
Right.
And yeah, when he dies, he leaves a word with his wife.
And if any psychic could tell what the word was.
So we'll show that too.
He'll die.
But we'll watch him give the word to his wife.
And then all the psychics try to figure out what the word is.
And none of them can.
Fievel prestige with Fievel.
OK, it's got to be twins.
No, it's not.
It's got to be twins.
What does Fievel's voice sound like?
Like, geez.
He's like a falsetto.
We default to this.
And I'm so like we just did an episode about babyland about Cabbage Patch Kids.
And my cab I was aware in the moment, like here's my Cabbage Patch Kid voice.
And it was Mickey.
Yeah, I think it's something we all got to work on is better and shit because the
voices fall into a lot of boxes.
There's a lot of it.
There's a lot of McGruff.
Oh, maybe this is a New Year's resolution.
We're getting towards the end of the year.
Oh, yeah.
But we've got to we've got to perfect our voice.
Griffin, Griffin, will you charge us to do like a one day workshop?
What you're asking him to do?
We have to pay Griffin?
Because he's a voice actor.
He's booked a lot.
I love Griffin.
I'm not paying Griffin money to make a slightly different voice.
I just want some tips so I don't always sound like Mickey.
All right. So Griffin, you've heard it.
Jason's open up the wallet.
You can do you're doing a one day seminar.
Does he do impressions?
No, I just mean in the diss and chenis and Masters of the Universe.
You're saying a variety.
You want more variety of OK, I was thinking Scott was more talking about.
We need to get our impressions sort of down more specifically.
Oh, I see. Yeah.
So let's test it right now.
Let's here's the I'm going to find a clip of Fievel and everybody's going to try
to figure out how to do him.
I think I hope he talks in this so there'll be a lot of wasted time.
He better not just look sad and start crying
because I guess we can impersonate Fievel crying.
You are in mouth.
I can do it down the way.
He's just smiling. God damn it.
He's just smiling.
Oh, you're my.
I picked your mouth.
Everyone smile for the microphone.
Eloise voice. Of course, Dom DeLuis is the voice of the Roger Corman produced
movie Munchy or not much.
Sure.
No, not much from the new Ghostbusters.
Munchy, although it's got a different name.
It's confusing because Munchy 2 is I feel like it's confusing when you look at it
because it's almost like American Tale and Fievel goes west where it's like
it doesn't sound like the sequel name.
When did every fucking clip I pull up,
Fievel is just gesturing and he doesn't talk.
Does he talk mouse?
Does he talk at all so we can do an impression of you?
He doesn't talk at all.
I love the talks.
The soundtrack for the movie for
Fievel goes west in the land is very fun.
I like that as a kid.
It's very sweeping.
Yeah, kind of a fun Western Western.
Munchy. OK, sorry.
Munchies is the first one and Munchy is the second one.
OK, so there's a it's it goes.
The opposite like to like, you know, gives the plural like alien aliens.
It's the reverse.
This is I'm getting nowhere with this, but we're not going to look.
We're not going to have a Fievel impression for you today.
I'm sorry. That's too bad.
Yeah. You could just look up Fievel talks and you would think it would be there.
I put in Fievel. You think talks is going to help?
Yeah, it talks to it.
I think that'll be the key word that's missing.
Well, what this has taught me, actually.
Oh, well, first of all, you were right.
And I apologize.
So what it has also taught me is that for wow.
Amazingly, from the YouTube user inspired figment, one little spark.
Wow. What I have learned is that there was a Teddy Ruxpin of Fievel.
So they do. Wow.
They did the Teddy Ruxpin thing.
You put tapes in him and he talks and tells you a story.
So all right.
Good job on that. You're right.
Talking Fievel. Here's a clip.
And if everybody would like to try to do this, here we go.
All right.
My name is Fievel Mousquick.
I see that you're ready to hear a story and I have a good one for you.
All right.
Everybody want to go?
My name is Fievel Mousquick.
And I've got a story for you.
That's great.
OK.
Hi, my name is Fievel Mousquick and I hear you're ready to hear a story.
He's a little nerdier than the regular Fievel.
That's why I got to take one of these voice acting classes.
I can do like three voice.
You got to pay Griffin a couple of hundred.
Just start dropping money in his Venmo.
Don't say why.
But I want you to commit and start to get on the book.
We'll figure it out later.
You know, I just recognize it's a craft.
It's hard. Everyone I know does voice acting.
My name is Fievel.
Did classes and did like test reel and really had to work at it.
So I was like, I don't believe this for one second.
I think it's easy.
Let's all just start.
I it's just a thing.
I am I have great admiration for it, you know, and I feel like if I if I really
want to do it, I know I would have to do a lot of work to figure it out.
I refuse it.
That means you're refusing on this podcast to make your voices better.
You're using the excuse of that.
You have to take a class.
I suppose I don't know where to start.
I should probably just ask Griffin or Justin Michaels.
I don't think you have to do any of this.
I just start just try to do different voices.
That's all I'm saying.
All right. I don't think you have to do a class.
I don't know.
You you have auditioned for voice stuff and you've heard other people do it.
I can just like just do a million of them.
Not all of them know.
Yeah, not all.
Some people just do their voice and it's a little more energetic.
I mean, that's good.
Some people watch this voice master work.
Here comes my Fievel.
Here we go. Here we go.
Here comes I'm Fievel Muskowitz.
Ruff, ruff.
I want to die.
Why is he barking?
Take a bite out of an American tail with me.
Did you say I want to die?
I want to die.
I know what you said.
I might have said it without realizing it.
I want to die.
Wow.
Scott's dark thoughts manifested through a McGruff doing Fievel.
Well, I guess that seems like a good sign as any to end the episode.
You survived podcast.
Even thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
Your donations go towards Jason's voice over classes.
He's going to put in the work.
Sure.
And you're going to hear great new voices in twenty twenty three.
And if you want to dig even deeper,
join us at our new Patreon tier club three where you get one more bonus
episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
So, yeah, I guess.
All right.
With that being said, I mean, let's just all run through a quick couple more
impressions real quick.
Don Deleuze.
Wait, this said to Don Deleuze, this was not his last movie.
He lived for a while.
No, I think Munchies came out after this.
Munchies came out.
Well, I know also the Munchies came out.
He's also a troll in Central Park, another Bluth production,
which is something I do an impression of because there's a part where he
the like the troll is very sad.
I have nowhere to sleep.
I just need someone.
I just need a patch.
And then he puts his magic thumb out and it makes a little tiny bit of grass.
And he says, there's my patch.
I've been saying there's my patch for years.
I'll try to find a clip.
Dom Deleuze, he's dead in 2009.
He lived. Wow, he lived a long time.
He had time to.
I was just making sure it wasn't like a buddy hack it.
Jimmy Stewart, like, oh, in this big anime movie with their final role.
No, no, it gave him a life.
It gave him another 15 years.
Yeah,
we'll do the whole filmography.
But for now, they'll do it. Bye.
Bye.