Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, today we're talking DZ, where kids wanna be.
Here on PTR, where stunted adults are.
I'm Scott Caron here.
Hey, Jason Sheridan's here.
Hi, first one of the new year, first recording of 2023.
But one came out already, nobody cares about the order.
Well, that's all right, you know, no one's say, you know,
I like to hear how the sausage gets made, you know?
Do they, do they really?
I think they do.
I think you'll find that they do.
You're confusing it because you love hearing
how actual sausages get made.
I, literal and figurative, I love it.
Sausage tours are your thing.
Mike Carlson, hi.
Hi, I'm here, yes, and I wanna give everyone
the exact date and time that we're recording this,
just so they know.
521, it's brisk out, we had to close the door
because of the rain, yeah, let's make sure you know.
Google Earth coordinates are as follows.
Wait, hang on, I don't want people to know where I live.
If they're vague, just leave the last few out
and we'll be okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey, it's Discovery Zone today.
This is a delightful one and it came out of a recent day.
What do you wanna hear in the new year?
So thank you, Ryan Lovell, for suggesting this.
What a delightful one and kind of an inevitable one,
but I hadn't thought about it.
And if you don't know Discovery Zone in general,
this was a very 90s place.
The 90s were the time to be this kid indoor playground
entity and the 90s were the only time
to be Discovery Zone, I would say.
I might say a very specific subsection of the 90s
as the earnings and mergers quickly showed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, didn't make it too far out of the 90s.
But I kind of think they're self-inflicted wounds.
I think there's a world where DZ is still fairly popular
in the same way that Chuck E. Cheese is,
Chuck E. Cheese still feels like it's limping along,
but hasn't it felt like that forever?
I mean, it seemed like the pandemic
would have been the time.
Right. Right.
Like anything that was kind of teetering,
hometown buffet fell into the pit.
It didn't make it out of the pit.
And I think probably we might've all early on,
our thoughts went to Chuck E. Cheese.
Is it gonna make it out?
And it did somehow.
I don't think it's- Yeah, so far, yeah.
Fine.
And I actually go there without irony with the kid
and a lot of people do.
Right. Yeah, I don't know.
So I'm DZ, I think that, you know, we'll talk about it,
but there could be a world where Discovery Zone
is still around.
I think so, and especially being that it was a way
to kind of cheaply fill big retail spaces.
Yes. And how do those places get filled today?
Well, through trampoline parks
and big kid run around areas.
It's like, it's just all splint.
It's all a lot of independent Discovery Zones.
Which is good.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
We like that.
But we also really love a huge bloated corporate entity
that is tricked into having to grow too fast
and then disappears entirely.
Yeah.
This one was interesting for me
because I feel like there was like a wealth of information,
like a full three act structure to the story,
the rise and fall.
I have no memory of ever being in the Discovery Zone.
Oh, that's interesting. Really?
Okay, okay. Interesting.
Yeah, you never did it.
Do you remember them being around though?
Faintly, I remember them kind of being in the ether,
but on the East Coast, there was also a glut of like,
yeah, we have kind of a big space.
We're gonna put in some arcade games
and an outdoor play set indoors
and sell the worst pizza you've ever imagined in your life.
And then eventually that would transition
to the scariest go-kart track you've ever been on your life.
Laser tag, the darkest, deadliest laser tag.
Where you're worried about other real weapons.
There's bayonets. Behind some corner.
Bayonets on the end of the guns.
Yeah, like you know everyone in your party,
but you don't, there was that kid on the other team
that looked really like he might pistol whip you
from around the corner.
Oh, those kids, but those kids would hold their hand
over the receiver on their chest.
Do you ever see this?
Do you ever play laser tag?
To stop themselves from, very real.
I have not played a ton of laser tag.
It was cheating basically.
If you put your hand over the target on your chest
playing laser tag, you wouldn't get shot.
So there was like a pro kid in there,
hand over his heart, shooting kids sideways.
It's nothing because he just does this all afternoon
because his parents probably drop him off every day.
Yeah. Neat.
And you think the parents don't want that kid around?
Well, they created him.
They created his poor morals and ethics.
See how he plays laser tag with these little kids?
I was traumatized by him.
Maybe the kid gets it out with,
so maybe the aggression comes out
via his aggressive laser tagging.
He's gotta put it somewhere.
Mike, that's also the nicest version
of the way they could act out as opposed to like,
all right, I'm gonna climb to the top of that fake door
and jump off it.
You're right.
I'm gonna ambush these little twerps.
But this was a traumatizing thing
when you would play laser tag against kids
not in your own friend circle.
You could play against older kids
or be some kid who knew all the ins and outs of it
and you felt like you were helpless to do anything.
Yeah.
I remember I haven't played a ton of it,
but enough to experience this syndrome
and you really feel impotent.
Yes.
Is how you feel.
You feel powerless. It's all feeling.
And limp and like you're not your full self.
Right. It's humiliating.
You feel humiliated.
Yeah, a little.
When somebody's doing five times better than you
and you know, if I did 20 more rounds,
it's not gonna get any better.
And I would feel guilty cheating too with that,
especially back then.
You'd feel guilty like holding or like,
this is classic good boys stuff.
We bring another shirt.
Some structure is in place.
I don't know.
Maybe if I cheated,
it's somehow gonna get back to my social studies teacher.
Yes.
And I'm gonna get a lower grade.
We should have brought another shirt
and put it over the receiver on your chest.
I, as a kid too, I didn't like the dark
and I did not like being startled.
So I just stayed out of laser tag.
Unless it was, there was one place
where there was a giant plastic pipe in the middle
and it was like side versus side, much more manageable.
And then there was also one place where you sat in a chair
and it was half the audience
versus the other half of the audience.
Whoa, hold on a second here.
No.
Jason Sheridan played seated laser tag.
I think this would be up his alley now.
This would be so up my alley.
Now, ironically though, when I was in college,
there was a pretty popular laser tag place in Ithaca
that was really cheap.
So we would play it like sometimes.
And there, at least everyone agreed like,
okay, we're gonna be human beings about this.
Like no one's hitting you with a gun
or like running and zapping you in the eye
or whatever bad boy things are going on.
They need to administer morality tests as well.
Just like with different kind of
goofus and gallant scenarios.
Trick that you don't wanna give a test that's like,
would you ever butt somebody in the forehead with a gun
playing laser tag?
You have to trick that.
You have to do a little,
create some scenario with an old lady
with her pet walking across the street.
Or what would you do?
Right, right.
And then you can tell.
And then if they can't play, then they get,
I don't know, get sent to a real,
some sort of real fight maybe, like a prison yard.
They're delivered straight to a prison.
I guess, yeah.
That's, I don't know.
I'm just spit balling here.
You get two minutes in the yard, go.
They should invent, Jason, they should invent a laser tag
where you get to lie in a twin bed.
Yeah.
And shoot at your opponent.
That's like some sort of a sensory deprivation tank.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
That's some sort of therapy for something.
Yeah.
I think there's clearly a whole laser tag episode
to be done.
Well, of course.
And by the way, there's some laser tag components to that,
which I didn't realize that that was part of the evolution
of Discovery Zone.
But what it started as was this kind of kid
run around climbing gym.
And I think it might be helpful for multiple reasons
to let the place explain itself via an ad
and via a song that you almost definitely know
if you grew up going to this place
or just being aware of this place.
I'm going dizzy at Discovery Zone.
Discover what I can do on my own.
Hey, Alex, you're walking on the moon.
Discovery Zone fun centers are safe, colorful play zones
where kids can get exercise, have parties, and discover fun.
And where parents can relax and have fun too.
Alex, you can do that.
That's our daughter, the mountain climber.
I'm going dizzy at Discovery Zone.
Easy.
Where kids wanna be.
That explains it pretty concisely.
It's nothing that other places hadn't done.
It's extrapolated from components of Chuck E. Cheese
or the McDonald's Playland,
but is fully devoted to climbing and play
and physical activity and mazes and tubes and environments
and slides and interesting kinds of slides
that would not be at your regular park.
And the very important marketing decision,
which they highlight in other commercials too,
you can be on your own.
Oh, there's a big play of like,
imagine what you can do without those parents around.
Or I can be on my own.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that is big.
Yes, and I forget, there's another commercial
that might even have another funny thing
that somebody says in there, but that's a big part of it.
I guess to market to kids like, oh, I'm free here.
Now, was that something I wanted?
No.
No, no.
Yeah, I currently have a child who I have to do
all the climbing with him.
Yeah, right.
In general, I've been picturing my son
who's not quite at the age for this.
And I'm watching the ads and like, boy,
this would be his dream if there were
no other children in it.
And you were with him.
And I was holding his hand the entire time.
Yeah, which also seems like it was allowed
judging by the hours and hours of people climbing
through these things with VHS cameras.
Oh yeah.
And uploading those eventually to YouTube.
But not common, my memory of any of this stuff.
And I think Discovery Zone of the major ones,
and I consider the major ones,
Chuck E. Cheese, Leaps and Bounds,
which we'll talk about in a second here,
and Discovery Zone.
I think I went to this one the least,
but I don't remember adults in that play place with me ever.
Okay.
And not even now, you said this was not your dream,
but you did have Discovery Zone experience
and you did not force your parents to come in with it.
No, I was comfortable with my parents
not being in the tubes with me or in the ball pit,
but I didn't want them, I wanted them close-ish.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, within, yeah.
I mean, when I get like 10, 11, 12,
I didn't need to be there.
Sure, sure.
But when I was younger, yeah, yeah.
There's the kidnapping fear.
Sure, yeah, and believe me.
That just there's somebody hiding in the ball pit
right at the bed, that you just get snagged
and yanked into some secret compartment.
Yeah, that's all I was told every day of my life,
is that you will be kidnapped.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Beware, you're going to, you will be kidnapped.
Anyone who you see, any adult that you see,
and maybe even a younger person you see
who you've never seen before is a candidate to kidnap you.
Yeah.
Especially the people who work here
because that's an awfully good excuse.
Yeah, yeah, you develop this false persona of,
yes, love kids, love working with kids,
love not stealing, I mean, love helping kids.
I don't know what that was.
That was a hiccup.
So yeah, so I don't remember parents in there,
but yes, I think you could probably,
I don't know if they would take you out of there
if you got in there, but some of the Chuck E. Cheese ones,
especially, because Chuck E. Cheese was not as
like play place heavy as Discovery's own was.
Yeah, part of it, but a more minor percentage.
So especially at Chuck E. Cheese, it was like,
you're going to notice an adult man is in there.
I like to do the rounds at Chuck E. Cheese.
I liked a little show, a little ball pit, a little game.
Eventually, when my family got to the point of like,
okay, we can't eat this food anyway.
This food is not good.
This food is twice as much.
We got into a routine of,
we will go to a much better restaurant first and get pizza.
And then easy 30 to 40 minutes in the comic book store
next to the Chuck E. Cheese.
And then into Chuck E. Cheese,
you each get five or $10 in tokens.
We'll sit at the bar and watch the show in between playing.
And then we will,
then you can turn your tickets in for prizes.
And inevitably you will badger us into just buying a prize
that you don't have enough tickets.
You have half the tickets
and then they will assuredly let you pay cash
for the other.
Right, right.
This is, yeah, this is not, did I,
I always wanted like a month, like a little PVC
or like a munch little statue or something.
And I never had enough tickets for an,
my memory is it's like this big.
It's like a thousand tickets.
For a tiny little, for a three inch guy.
Yeah, right.
Somehow that's the ultimate dream.
Something that retail price is $7 probably.
Less probably.
I, well, okay.
So Jason did not actually go to one of these.
You did, do you remember the circumstances,
Mike, of your discovery zone?
Well, this is, yes, I do.
I went maybe a couple times to,
my memory is like three to five times really.
But the one that stands out is that I got in trouble
at this discovery zone.
Oh no.
We went with my friends and his brother,
my sister and I went and it was like the two moms
and then my sister and I, and then two brothers.
And I don't know if I've mentioned them before
because one of the brothers was my age.
One of them was a couple of years younger
and he was the bad brother.
He was the one who was like shooting BB guns
and like lighting a bottle rocket off in the laundry room.
Oh yes.
So we were in the parking lot.
I think we all drove together.
And all of a sudden the two of those boys
started running in the parking lot.
And my sister and I are children.
So we go, oh, I guess we're running.
So we ran after them in the parking lot.
And oh my goodness, if this isn't a story
that my mother will tell you
if you talk to her for 30 minutes.
That kid started running.
She pulled me aside, my sister aside,
yelled at us so thoroughly, you don't run in a parking lot.
You could be hit by a car.
You never do that.
I don't care who, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then that's all I could think about the whole time
while we were at discovery zone that day
is that I had been bad.
A pit in your stomach.
Yes.
Oh my God.
I had been bad at discovery zone.
I think in some ways this experience
taints my feeling about discovery zone in general.
Wow.
And my voice did not shake because I was about to cry.
It was a dryness issue.
Yeah.
What explains the tears?
What explains those tears welling up in your eyes?
That's moisture.
Ah, yes.
Sometimes we're hearing a lot of drip drop right now
that is a rain that spiked a lot
and it's not coming from Mike's eyes.
Yes.
If you use that to fall asleep like I do,
pull the car over, switch to doughboys.
There's no.
It's true, a rain free podcast.
ASMR.
It's OK.
Cut as a breaker.
Try to figure something out.
I think we've done it before.
I don't know if it shows up, but we'll see.
All right.
We'll see.
But anyways, oh my God.
So tainted.
I love also that that's a story today because the kids yell,
the kids ran and I yelled at them.
That seems like something that could happen every day.
Of course it does.
This is how good we were as kids.
Is that this is one of the top five
awesomest behaving stories and we'll
be told as if we like stole from a store.
Buying heroin in the dark.
We found a six year old Mike, her eight year old Mike
and a five year old Katie.
How do you think the running was?
I think it was like 15, not even by 10 cars, maybe less.
Wow.
And I get it.
You're not so guess little kids.
You can't run.
Someone's pulling out.
Of course.
But it's pretty clear why we like these two maniacs
started running.
This one kid, especially, I won't say his last name is Alex.
Be on the lookout for an Alex in your life.
It could be this Alex.
I don't think he's going to listen.
Alex will take you for every penny you're worth
and we know he can run.
So it was clear why we did it.
We weren't doing that normally.
But no, we were punting.
We were yelled at and that felt so devastating to me.
But yeah.
I remember all mine too.
One was that my sister and I, you
see this a lot with kids and elevators.
Elevator etiquette is something that needs to be learned.
You want to get out of the elevator,
so you just start walking out of the elevator
and maybe you bump right into the people who
are waiting for the elevator.
And this happened one time and it
happened with some kind of harumphy old ladies.
And we just ran on.
We kind of bumped into them maybe.
And then before the elevator doors close,
one of the ladies turns to the other and says,
those are the rudest children I've ever seen in my life.
Which is not a thing to say in front of my mom.
She was so mad.
I think if there had not been a sound bite,
it never would have come up again.
That's not something you want to hear about your kids.
We'll see where I get.
By the time my son is older, I think I would give a shit.
I think I'd say, hey, don't do that.
And the quote would not be ringing in my head
like it's a Siskel and Hebert movie quote that damns the film.
Yeah.
They also like, OK, maybe you guys broke the social contract.
You're not supposed to run into people, especially older
people.
They're also supposed to shut the fuck up.
They're not supposed to be like these terribly.
You're not supposed to menace strangers, children or adults.
Give a review.
You don't review every but.
Now, these children were mild.
I didn't love them.
But they also didn't bother me.
Two stars for these kids.
Were they like, were you in Manhattan?
Were they like snooty old rich people from a movie?
That's how it felt.
It felt like Looney Tunes kind of.
It felt like they felt like the kind of old ladies who would
rightfully be bothered by the characters that we're rooting for,
which is how I feel about my sister and I in that scenario.
We were the fun characters.
Yeah.
Briefly running.
That's right.
And yeah, there you did.
You touch their mink stalls or something like what was it
that they got so upset?
Oh, I should have mentioned.
Yes, that I caught on to one of their stalls.
And kept running with it.
And it spun them around and around as if they were on a turntable.
And by the end, they were fully naked and had to cover themselves and go,
oh, I never.
And all of their pearls like rearrange.
Uh huh.
They seem justified then in their response.
I should have.
I guess I didn't tell the whole story.
It's important to be honest.
What did your mom say to you then when the ladies were out of your shot?
I don't remember that.
I think it was just did you hear that?
Did you hear what you said about you?
Clipped like that.
Uh huh.
But is that weird that how bad like other kids, I think, would have just a mountain
of these and we have like five and scarring to this.
Right.
And my mom still thinks they're as bad as they were.
That's what's interesting to me.
Wasn't kids being kids?
No, I have the lowest stakes version of that.
But thankfully, my parents are like, don't just ignore.
Don't do not be bothered by this.
And it was, you know, I my aunts and uncles were all pretty chill.
And so we got in the habit of just calling them by their first name, like Jimmy, Johnny.
You know, we didn't say on her uncle before it if we were directly addressing them.
My aunt Dolly, who was, I think, my grandmother's sister.
So a great aunt.
I said, hi, Dolly.
How are you doing at a party at like a family barbecue?
And she went.
And I said, Aunt Dolly, I am your great aunt.
And everyone's like blood chilled because everyone was also like, what are you?
What are you doing?
Like you are.
You are very old, granted.
And but there's a nice way to say that to an eight year old.
Like and my family was like, don't mind her.
She is very old and powered by hate.
Like this is all I have.
Yeah.
Had you called her Dolly before?
I have no recollection.
I think I avoided talking to her before.
I was trying to be friendly.
Right, right.
You were like, I'm in a dog.
I'm getting older now.
And I crossed this member of the greatest generation.
Wow.
I have earned this title.
Great.
So highest rank of aunt there is.
It is a story we tell, but it's a funny story.
Yeah.
It's like that was really weird.
Right.
So what we've determined is that this place is a place of sour.
Yes, I don't have a good feeling about it.
I don't really either.
Mine is kind of not.
I don't have a story about it in particular other than it was OK.
Full context, it was at the Fallbrook Mall in West Hills, California, which is still
home to a Chuck E. Cheese with a full munch.
Listeners, if you're looking for a full munch, go to the Fallbrook Mall.
Still there.
And I think these things were concurrent.
So a place with the Chuck E. Cheese and a Discovery Zone.
Amazing.
And I think we didn't.
Although maybe they weren't.
I might not have had a Chuck E. Cheese that close to me.
So this was closer.
So it was a big deal.
Basically, my story with it is just the ad that I played at the beginning.
And listener, you could only hear it.
But if you could visualize every type of play equipment in the world,
foam that looks so huggable, like seems like it'd be a delight.
Texturally, the brightest colors.
This place was so aggressive color wise.
It's just primaries, red, yellow, green, kind of don't super go together.
No, it's a real clashy place, but they gave it an aesthetic.
It's kind of like a box of primary color crayon aesthetic.
And of course, the ad is also like we spin the camera around.
And it's selling what should.
I think it's selling what the equivalent for me now of
do you want to spend three and a half hours in beautiful Pandora?
Do you want to be transported?
You can go not that far from where you live and be transported into another universe.
And when it's done, you're going to want to stay there.
You know, which you could keep being in there.
That's what I thought the Discovery Zone was at the time.
And I went and I just kind of like got tired.
There were a lot of elbows flying.
Oh, it was a little annoying.
And my parents clearly did not like it one bit.
So it kind of maybe I brought up one more day.
We haven't been to that Discovery Zone in a while and their vibe was so bad on it.
And again, good boy.
I'll go along with this.
Right.
I didn't like it enough to if they were insistent, I would have gone back.
Sure.
Anytime.
But I had to be the driver and I wasn't the driver.
Right.
I don't know.
Underwhelm me, I guess.
Yeah, I don't want this to be so negative of an episode.
But certainly not.
What was the history of Leaps and Bounds?
I liked better.
Did you have Leaps and Bounds out here?
I know they changed and I was there.
Some fascinating facts about it that I learned today.
I've I had never heard the phrase Leaps and Bounds until researching this episode.
Yeah, I was completely unfamiliar with Leaps and Bounds.
Yes, Leaps and Bounds was the one at least by us was bigger and better.
And I had like a fifth grade, not my party, but a fifth grade birthday.
I'm sure I've talked about, which is maybe my favorite thing I'd ever experienced.
Just playing around and running around that place.
That was really fun.
I don't know what I can't articulate what the difference was.
It felt like it was bigger, more expansive maybe than a DZ.
Was it more about the long tubes?
It seemed pretty tubby.
It's pretty tubby.
And I like the aesthetic more because it's sort of more in that zone of like
the Memphis style Taco Bells with the turquoise and the purple.
Yes, it was.
It's a color scheme I more want to run around today than the strong red of Discovery Zone.
Yeah.
Well, and the connection too.
I mean, it was started by McDonald's.
I'm so excited by this connection that I didn't know.
You didn't know this.
I didn't know.
I didn't know it either.
They were the ones who made the McDonald's Play Place.
Yes.
And they're like they set the standard for like the tube based play place.
Sly tube based entertainment.
That started with Leaps and Bounds of McDonald's in what?
87 is when the Play Place, I think the first Play Place went in.
Was it not till 87?
There was something around there.
So we grew up right in front.
They were all new even.
Yes.
That's interesting.
But then there were like playgrounds, right?
Because those characters exactly.
I've seen ads from the 70s for those.
That's different.
The actual like tube stuff, not the like Officer Big Mac jail, I believe.
I think that stuff is older.
Yeah, the transition to the plasticky bubbly tubes and all.
Yeah.
That was in the way that all the McDonald's now are kind of being stripped of personality,
a lot of dark colors and metal and very modern.
Very sad.
A lot of them were redone to add the Play Place.
Play Places just started showing up in my memory.
And this is also the rise of like Happy Meal toys really starting to cook.
And heap.
They had them for a while.
But the Disney, the Disney agreement.
Characters you know, you feel like you're participating in the movie that you're excited about.
No, for sure.
Well, let's do history a little bit.
It'll lead us to some leaps and bounds.
So founded in 1989 is what I saw.
Three founders.
There was like a kind of a lot of sportsy people.
So I'm Ronald Match, somebody named Dr. David Schoenstadt,
who was the owner of the Kansas City Comets, which is an indoor soccer team.
And it all founded in Kansas, by the way.
And then a guy named Jim Jorgensen.
This is the guy.
Jim Jorgensen, yeah, I think maybe he's a light guy.
I think it's at least guy light.
We'd have to determine a little more.
But I say this because he has a Wikipedia with a list of the many, many businesses he started.
Referred to as a serial entrepreneur on Wikipedia.
I think serial entrepreneur might be a key phrase of any guy.
I agree.
That might be our way to keep finding more guys.
I think that's a good start.
Is there, I couldn't pull it and I couldn't search it.
There's an architectural Jorgensen that comes up a lot too.
With a similar name, like was involved with City Walk.
Who am I thinking of?
Well, City Walk is John Jurdy is the guy.
That's the guy.
Okay.
And it's just the name sounded close.
Jorgensen just probably sounds familiar because you've probably heard it
in a number of like improv scenes or sketches over the years.
I mean, it's a very funny name.
Jorgensen, get in.
Now Jorgensen.
Yeah, I know because Michael Jorgensen plays keyboards in Wilco.
Oh, there are real Jorgensen's out there.
I don't know if it's the same spelling.
I'm doing good work.
But this guy was Billy Jean King's business partner.
There's a lot of ventures of Billy Jean King, who was in fact an investor.
An investor in Discovery Zone.
That is so funny.
This guy reads, if you read all the stuff he created, whatever it was a part of,
it reads like a fake list of stuff you've never heard of.
Yeah.
And it's really great.
Yeah. What do you got?
I mean, there's one I really like, but some of the newer ones, he runs something called,
hold on, let me scroll and get it.
True Artists, which is the largest international organization of certified tattoo artists.
All right.
Fair enough.
We had to put all the tattoo artists in one place.
They all been running around willy-nilly.
We gotta organize it.
They run the annual tattoo awards.
I know nothing else about it and I don't have tattoos, but I demand that we host the tattoo awards.
I believe we should do that.
They scare me.
They thought of getting one.
Yeah.
It's scary and I'll get sick and I'll throw up.
It adds up with everything else we know about.
Western equity, all-American indoor sports, a chain of indoor sports malls.
The company built indoor sports malls in the Midwest.
That's a Kansas business.
There still is one.
Yeah. Some of them are around.
Some of them are not.
Women's sport magazine, Soviet Union national team, an entry in world team tennis in 1977.
My favorite one.
Do you know, did you look at this list?
Yeah, I'm sure I'm staring at things.
Is that the same one?
We're excited about this.
Yeah.
Ronnie's ranch.
This is where I thought, God, maybe it's a guy.
You open Ronnie's ranch.
Ronnie's ranch.
The details of Ronnie's ranch.
Jason, do you know what Ronnie's ranch is?
I read this list really fast and then got upset with the VHS tapes.
You would have said it at the start of the episode if you knew what it was.
It's a restaurant in Los Angeles.
It was co-founded by this guy and Ronnie Burns, son of George Burns and Gracie Allen.
You mean I could go to a restaurant conjured up by Ronnie Burns?
The Ronnie Burns.
He was an actor as well.
I am blindsided because I'm like, there's no way it's Ronnie James Dio.
I wish.
You'd have to go Dio's place.
I use the first name.
Ronnie's ranch.
Could you find a picture of it?
No, no, no further information.
Only on Wikipedia.
Right.
This is the only place I could find it.
Yeah.
So devastating that.
Desperate to find Ronnie's ranch.
Also very frustrating because this place was listed as the last of three different
restaurants that Jorgensen tried over the years, all of which failed.
So where are the other ones?
They were in the list.
I need to know.
Was it other sons?
What other son?
Imogene Coca's son.
Billie Jean King's racket restaurant.
The big racket.
They serve everything on rackets.
Yeah.
Where was it?
Floreto on rackets.
I'll throw this out there.
I feel like finding restaurant stuff is often not preserved unless it has a real
diehard fan that is scan stuff.
Well, especially the old restaurants.
Old restaurants like stuff that's not around anymore, especially stuff that's more recent.
Like, you know, let's say a, a Bennigan's or a ground round.
You see that stuff on eBay.
Sure.
Womp hoppers.
But there's not a lot.
That's recent.
You're right.
It's kind of a, it is a black hole a little bit in terms of, in terms of pre internet
preservation.
Yeah.
Unless you loved the restaurant.
List of like every combination I tried, list of former discovery zone locations.
Cause it did not get up to like 300.
It's almost.
We got so many.
This was a massive chat.
Yeah.
The maybe the kind of exciting stat to say is it went from one store in 1990 to,
yeah, I saw a lot of 300.
I don't know if this is, I saw somewhere it said almost 500, whatever it was massive
within five years.
And then all dead again by 2001.
Yeah.
We're talking United States, Canada and Puerto Rico.
There was a video I watched that was pretty good on the business side.
It's the channel is called company insight.
And they had like, here are all the business bad business decisions, like why this fell
behind, why this expanded way too fast to begin with.
And then here's all the stuff, Chuck E cheese did that kept them in the game and all the
stuff that like a discovery zone absolutely did not do.
Huh?
Interesting.
So I guess they feel so similar and it feels like sort of cheap in its construction.
But I, yeah, I think just like the bit of the management fast.
Yeah.
That's what I was saying earlier.
This guy, I will say, this is one of those guys where like, I do feel like we could write
up a one page on our, we were pitching on last year, a podcast, hard rock cafe idea
where it's a podcast.
It's all the podcasts like a podcast restaurant.
This is a guy who would bite.
Yeah.
I think he would go, yeah, you know what?
You're right.
The only thing you'd maybe have to make, well, you don't want to undersell it.
You just might have to like be aware of the possibility that we're going to have to change
out these menu items a lot as different podcasters get canceled.
But as long as you're like, as long as we can just keep reprinting, just don't like,
you know, set it in stone.
Don't make the menus very expensive.
Yeah.
Cheap lamination because we're gonna have to slide those in and out.
Very good.
Very good point.
But I think this is a guy to send a proposal to.
Our fine.
Yeah.
Jorgensen getting here.
He does not mind having a business startup and flame out in six months.
Yeah.
That's, this is what we want.
The thrill of the chase.
Why else do you get in the Ronnie Burns business?
You're in the Ronnie Burns business.
Ronnie's ranch.
I know.
Ronnie's ranch in Los Angeles.
Where was it?
I don't know.
There's no other info.
That's a great point because there was plenty of Discovery Zones in Las Vegas.
Right.
Was Ronnie's ranch turned into a Discovery Zone?
Yeah.
I don't know.
You know what was a Discovery Zone was is the Burbank Chuck E. Cheese.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And us was a Discovery Zone.
It's, it's hard to tell what.
A lot of them just become like sporting good stores.
Yeah.
Gyms or there's an interesting history to a couple of them, but I'll save that.
So starts as one thing, right?
And it's these, it's these kind of sports oriented people mostly who are observing
that children are in bad shape and a lot of them can't do very basic athletics.
Probably looking at some young Scott, Mike's and Jason's out there.
We got to do, we got to do something about this.
So, you know, sort of a fun kids gym and it starts in Lenexa, Kansas in 1989,
which incidentally is the town that Paul Rudd grew up in.
Oh, wow.
Young Paul Rudd moved there when in age, age 10.
Other interesting fact about Paul Rudd's Kansas years,
he then was in a city called Overland Park where he worked as a ham glazer.
Oh, Jason.
Oh, I like that for a honey baked ham or just a home grown ham place.
I might've been a more indie.
Okay.
You know, you get less of the prestige than working at a honey baked ham.
You get a lot more hands on experience, a lot sooner.
Jason, have you ever glazed a ham?
I mean, I've opened up the oven with a spoon.
Sounds like a no. Moving on.
No, you're not letting me finish.
I've opened up the oven and scooped the juices on top of the ham.
That's how you glaze a ham.
Is that all it is?
I think so.
I mean, if you're making it at home, like we weren't making hams from raw meat and stuff,
but you brought a honey baked ham.
So that's where-
Or a turkey, you just baste it. You just keep doing that.
So glazing is basting?
I think reasonably close to basting.
Don't quote me. I'm sure we have some great cooks in the audience
who can delineate this a little better than I can.
This is a tough area. I got the wrong-
I was trying to, early in pandemic, say what the ingredients were for a Carthay Manhattan,
and I had the one type of bitters and like-
This is different, but it's the same.
Immediately somebody pounced on me like, no, raw, no, no, no, wrong flavor profile.
Well, I will admit I know nothing about this.
But I don't mean to say that about you. You might be right on the money with your glazing.
It might be more DIY home cook, you know, kind of thing.
Let us know if Jason has glazed. From that description,
if you're a listener and you've glazed, if you're more of a pro glazer, let us know.
Was that a glaze? Did Jason glaze?
Hashtag did Jason glaze?
I mean, look, if you're buying a honey baked ham, a lot of the work is already done for you.
You're probably warming that bad boy.
Where maybe you're just taking it-
That's why I expect they glaze it before if it's a honey baked ham.
Yeah, it's crazy. Yeah, it's got the sugar on the end.
That's got the brown sugar crisp on the outside.
That's already set. It's already made.
I'm going to say also that I looked it up. It's the honey- I'm sorry, the Holiday Ham Company
in Overland Park, Kansas, original.
I like that Paul Rudd's story involves studying drama at the British American Drama Academy
in Oxford and then soon after being at the Holiday Ham Company in Overland Park.
The Holiday Ham Company.
Now he's Ant-Man. What a journey.
So in Paul Rudd's backyard, it starts as one thing, but it booms because I think there is
an appetite for stuff like this because concurrent with the rise of Discovery Zone and them adding
locations is the rise of Leaps and Bounds and Leaps and Bounds is a McDonald's company.
That is a McDonald's subsect and I watched a video from the Bankrupt series by Bright
Sun Films, which is great.
Yeah.
And the implication there is that McDonald's is kind of like, well, let's do this Discovery
Zone thing. Who knows if that's correct, but maybe they were trying to like, they at least
had their eye on each other certainly and were competition and Mike, you preferred Leaps and
Bounds, but something about it didn't work out as well and soon enough Leaps and Bounds is dead.
Yeah.
And all the locations become Discovery Zones. This is a great little game of Thrones.
There's a couple more stages of this to come where the companies kind of-
Because McDonald's-
Conquer each other.
Yeah. McDonald's sells basically, right?
They sell. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And they end up with a huge investment in Discovery Zone. So this is a big Discovery Zone win. They
have more capital. They have more locations. They vanquished an opponent right away.
Serious XM radio versus Serious radio or XM was just like, okay, you're doing better.
I was like, well, they merged.
Yeah, they merged because it felt like XM wasn't doing as well.
And similarly like, you know, and Chuck E Cheese is all part of this. And we know that's the story
of Chuck E Cheese versus-
Chobis.
Rockaf- wait, what's the Rockafire rest? Chobis.
Chobis Pizza.
And then yeah, versus Pizza Time Theater.
Right.
Not all of which were Chuck E Cheese Pizza Time Theater.
This entire industry. And then when you get to the end of the Discovery Zone story.
So 45 Leaps and Bounds become Discovery Zone. They got 10- McDonald's has 10% of Discovery Zone
now. Things are going great. Lots of expansion. And then they meet the company that really takes
them to the next level and the company to tie in with if you've got your eyes on the future.
That's right.
Blockbuster.
Unbelievable when this came into play. I couldn't believe-
I didn't know that.
And then the other thing I did know at one point in time, I just blanked it out that Blockbuster
at the time, a division of Viacom.
Yes. Well, and I'm confused by this timeline a little bit because I think maybe the Blockbuster
interaction, I think maybe the Blockbuster investment with Discovery Zone is right before
Viacom. I also forgot how all these companies came together.
That Viacom merges with Blockbuster. Huge deal. And then they set out together to buy Paramount.
I forgot why Paramount is a Viacom.
This is relatively recent. They're all in the mid-90s. So this all converges
and it fills a niche for Blockbuster because they have been wanting to do
this kind of big experiential arcade types of places. They have had their eyes on this anyway.
This is where I stumble into the chain, the briefly existing chain called Blockparty.
Are you guys aware of Blockparty?
I did not know anything about this.
I think this is their, what we would say now is it Dave and Busters?
Yes.
I think there are some videos on this online that I've kind of carefully gone through. I've
watched really quickly, but I don't remember the specifics. It seems like they were trying to do it
a lot. There's a big thing of this area, I guess, a lot of places. I mean, it's all sort of right
before Disney Quest. This is clearly an area people thought was going to open up and it did
not really open up. But there's a really good review. This is its own thing, but the channel
Review Time did a great video about Blockparty. So it's more adult oriented. It's kind of like
Disney Quest. They made two of them. It wasn't hypothetical. There was one in Albuquerque and
there was one in Indianapolis. These bizarre, that they're Blockbuster theme, Blockbuster Blockparty,
but then they're also video game oriented. And like, there's like a here, the restaurant part is
like you're in a giant pinball machine. They seem, oh, and it's a Blockparty. So it's meant to be
like that you're having a big outdoor Blockparty, but with a roof over your heads, but we want to
make it feel like it's outdoors. So we're going to pipe in, in addition to very loud music, loud
street sounds and like sirens going by. Oh, so hell. So like the level of hell.
All the things we try to block out on this podcast when the garage door is open, they're like,
we want it. This is part of Blockparty. Part of it. Indianapolis location open until 2002.
That's wild. That is really crazy. You know about this before this? No, no. Maybe I passed by that
video. And I was aware of the efforts to make a Blockbuster entire theme park. Right. So in
Indiana, I believe, which if there's any infer the struggle with some of these to turn them into
episodes, is there enough information to go off of? Right. But God, if there is, I would, I am
fascinated by why Blockbuster of all places is trying to go into that sector. It might be a
Blockbuster catch all, but not movies. No video stores have just all of the way when they were
mad with power and mad with money. Yeah. Like there was, you know, West Coast video, video update,
you know, there were, there were RC colas to this Coca-Cola, but I really can't think of,
I guess Hollywood video eventually was kind of like a Pepsi. They were big number two. Yeah.
But I don't think they tried to do anything but video store. Right. No, that's the insane thing.
Like you're looking at concept art of a big outdoor Blockbuster theme park where there's a huge
blimp with the Blockbuster logo going by. Who would like that? Blockbuster is like a place you
have to go. I shut up the kids today. Let's rent something. Yeah. Go rent the page master.
Whoa, I'm in Blockbuster land. As inconvenient as it was convenient. Cause you're like, oh God,
it's Friday night. Is it going to be crowded? Is all the good stuff going to be taken?
Yeah. We never went to Blockbuster. Yeah. We always went to the other stores. It's across
the highway from the pizza place. And when I say highway, I mean a two lane road. That's 45 miles
per hour as opposed to 35 miles per hour. That's right. Yeah. No, we never went. We would go to
new wave video. We would go to a family video. Yeah. No way. Yeah. Or far more rented than the
NES cassettes. No annoying. Yeah. Why would you want to go be in Blockbuster land? Anyway,
I so weird. I think the impetus of it and the impetus that why discovery zone quote on, you
know, we're well before the child obesity panic, you know, we're, we're well before that, but I'm
remembering now a lot of emphasis when we were kids about like, well, it can't be couch potatoes,
this television and these new video games like they need to get outside and play.
And you remember this in your home. Yes. I remember my home, the local news, the local
newspaper. Like this was the biggest threat. Yeah. This was the biggest threat. Because Nintendo
was fairly new that we all have that there's this very engaging thing in our house and there's never
been more like solid entertainment just pumped in front of us. And now there's VHA. Yeah. It makes
sense why these things go together. Yeah. Was it correct? I don't know. I don't think so. Yeah. At
least we can get them out of the house. There's something for the whole family. It's communal
and there's food so we don't have to cook, you know. DZ though, I think DZ went wrong because
it doesn't have as much like, I take this, I say this and I'm wrong, but a parents could at least
in talk, Chuck E. Cheese enjoy a robot show. Yes. You could find some amusement in that even if you
aren't weird irony hounds like us. Right. And also beer and wine. And this was not part of
Discovery Zone probably due to the, you know, their health kick because we're about working out and
so we're not going to have beer and wine. And now we are going to have still horrible pizza, still
the worst pizza you could ever imagine. But then also like we have adult items like quiches.
All right, mom, you're set. Eat your quiche. My mom loved quiche. Yeah, that's true. There's
no doubt about that. They all love quiches, but you're going to the doctor if you're eating the
Discovery Zone quiche. If you're not even all the way through one Discovery Zone quiche. You
will negate whatever good thing you did by running around the Discovery Zone by eating a Discovery
Zone quiche. Yeah, I know. If your mom had known there were quiches inside, she would have been
running too. Yeah, that's a very good point. That's true. Very good point. I know grainy VHS footage
lazily uploaded to YouTube like with a million layers of static is not the best way to immerse
yourself like in what it was really like to be there. But watching all this back, I am like
the DZ Diner, which that's what they call the snack bar. The DZ Diner looked rough. And I got to say
equally rough. Some of these arcades were shit. Like some of these arcades were bad.
This is what's weird. It's just like percentages. Like it is all the stuff Chuck E. Cheese had, but
less robots, although not entirely. We'll get to that. But still arcades. It's like everything. But
then kind of less of some of the good stuff. Right. Yes. So they are arcades. But what's
shitty about the arcade? You just all remember. Just very few machines kind of all over the place
in terms of timeline wise that more business focused YouTube channel emphasize like well,
Chuck E. Cheese has had their ups and downs, but they've tried to stay current with the times. They
update the machines a lot. They update the tick. They went from ticketing to like swipe cards and
discovery zone. Just they, they went all in on lots of locations at the top, but they didn't keep
them up to date. Okay. Yeah. There was, it was not as much variety. And then there was not,
this is what I was the insight from the YouTube channel company insights of the video. I watched.
That's the one. Yeah. That's what I'm talking about. Right. Yeah. Yes. It was like Chuck E.
Cheese. And I do remember this. I do think this is true. You go to Chuck E. Cheese and go,
I wonder what new arcade game they're going to have. Like there was a selling point for me as a kid.
It's a possibility of new, which discovery zone is sort of, I think this factured into me,
not really liking it as a kid. You feel like you went and then you did it. Right. So how do we
keep a turnover and keep adding stuff so that it is different now, which might kind of tie into
the next block of history in my mind, which is so yeah, it becomes part of this Viacom blockbuster
entity. And as soon as you enter into that, it's this thing that we've seen a thousand times,
which is, well, now you have to grow and grow and grow and probably everything we're saying is an
issue. Why are people going back to discovery zone? If they've already done it, they've already been
on the foam pyramid or whatever. And the answer starts to become, well, now we've got it's Viacom
and block, or I'm sorry, and Paramount and these properties, we can put the properties into
discovery zone. And this is stuff that I didn't know about. I always, I thought it was only just
generic run around places. I didn't know that there were tie-ins and I was pretty delighted to
discover the tie-ins, which you mainly discover via like halves of commercials, like the first 15
seconds are general discovery zone. And then like now, you know, we got this and this. First one I
saw Fred Flintstone, the rarest bird of a Fred Flintstone tie-in to a physical place for kids.
Right. But I was very exciting to hear Fred Flintstone singing the song. They made custom
animation for it. Hey, bond, we gotta go to DZ where kids wanna be. Yeah. But never do.
And he does that at the end, like the two phrases tie together. So this, you got Fred Flintstone
stuff going on. The one in the list that's like, well, this might have been good. This may, if I
was too old by then, but if I was the right age when this happened, an MIB laser tag zone. Oh man.
So they did expand into laser tag. I don't think all of them had the room for it, but there were
laser tag arenas. And when I say MIB, I of course mean the animated series. So yeah, you're busting
aliens with maybe the characters from the movie. It is. Jay and Kate, Scott. This is my time to
shine. Yeah, okay. It's time to talk about some of the tie-ins to the most forgettable cartoons
of the mid to late nineties. All right, black suits coming. Well, put that aside because we
need to talk about Godzilla laser adventure. Oh yeah. Oh no. I'm where I was very excited
because again, you hear that and you go, Oh, a Godzilla thing. I could see that. Oh wait,
but then it would have to be that's Godzilla 98, the movie. Oh wait, no, it would have to be.
Yeah, no, it was the very forgettable Godzilla animated series movie tie-in, but not,
which again, I watched most of, if it was in the Fox kids block or the WB kids block, I was watching
it. Sometimes I was watching the one channel and taping the other. And your mom wanted you to get
out. I watched all of it, like the men in black animated show. It sounds like that was good.
By the way, it was pretty good. There were some really great animators where he had some cool
cartoonists and it kind of like expanded the universe. Although I consulted with the friend
of the show, Andrew Grissom on this point. He seemed to be pretty into that one. I think he
tolerated Godzilla, the animated series, but I don't know that anyone tolerated the mask,
the animated series. That too. Yeah, that was, uh, that's very annoying. Yeah. That, that, that,
that voice is a rough people trying to be Jim Carrey. I mean, how many things went wrong?
All, I mean, literally all three of the big initial Jim Carrey properties, they tried to turn into
other things that were just profoundly annoying and don't give you what you want, which is this
one man, the funniest man, any of us, 10 year olds could possibly imagine. Right. Cause there was an
animated Ace Ventura. I think so. Oh yeah. Yeah. And dumb and dumber. They did all of them. Pretty
rough. Uh, this compared to like, again, the earlier, earlier nineties when they had to
work a little harder for that, like the animated Beetlejuice, I remember liking. Yo, yeah. Yeah.
I remember liking that just fine. But then when they were trying to pump out the animated
giants where it's like, it kind of doesn't matter. I mean, am I being big hit? Uh, Godzilla, I think
a reasonable hit, not well received though. No, no. I think it was a disappointment. I was sure it
was okay on paper, but they were, that's post independence day. They're expecting like
ginormous hit, which it makes me wonder, like, were they already tied into, they, like it must
have been, the wheels must have been turning already on the animated series because why else
when you have Godzilla as your main character, what makes you have to keep using the character
Dr. Nico Nick Tadopoulos as played by Matthew Broderick, but then Ian Ziering,
Ian Ziering, Ian Ziering in the, uh, in the show or like Vicki Lewis from news radio
is in the movie and then her character is in none of them. None of them do the voices. Right. Dr.
Elsie Chapman, of course in the, and these are not to be confused with the stars of the latter day
Godzilla, but the more recent one, the 2014, which was of course, Lieutenant Ford Brody and then uh,
2019 Dr. Mark Russell and then Kong versus Godzilla, which was Dr. Nathan Lind. Um, so
how do you spell Lind? What's that? How do you spell Lind? Uh, Lind, L-I-N-D. Like Paul. Uh, no,
Paul Lind is L-Y-N-D-E. Oh, right. You're right. You're right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, no, unfortunately,
not. So anyway, yeah. Dr. Ted, Dr. Tadopoulos, Dr. Mark Russell, Dr. Nathan Lind, but it's, it's
these we know, we know these and it's important that we only apply the name standard to Avatar.
This is the only film ever made that we will ever hold to the name standard. Yeah. Um,
anyway, um, these tie ins, I, I, I saw a few of these in that there's like a commercial from 1999
and it's much more intense than the older ones. The song is gone. Uh, you get a little peek of
the Godzilla laser adventure. And, uh, I also saw, I think they called it a video wall. Did you,
it was look like a bunch of TVs and a chain link fence. And if you know, do you, can you picture
what I'm talking about? A few big TVs and a chain link fence. I am very curious if that was a,
I feel like I've seen that I saw that in college for like, um, location art, like gallery video
art. And I'm like, did they do that first or did some corporate dummy make this an aesthetic?
Cause I have very 90s, like nine, like who was the first to do that? Demolition man or something.
Like there's some scene somewhere like a bunch of TVs and a chain link fence. And that was like,
I feel like when DZ started to make that turn, it was like, Oh no, because they can't ever,
they can't fully go that way. It's too primary color little kid. You know? Yeah. I mean, that's,
but that's, everything's going extreme. While cherry Pepsi's can is going wild. It's going nuts.
You know, everything is getting a little bit harsher. Advertising is being as a very,
that edgy can that can was very edgy. I like every wild cherry Pepsi can is a piece of art though.
I will say this. I don't think it's ever been a bad wild cherry. Did you like the cherry Coke can,
the red and white, like the classic font? No, like the nineties one. I think anything in the
nineties that had cherry Coke or Pepsi was pretty great. I, I, I'd have to see all of them again.
A while. Let's see wild cherry Pepsi. I think that's not, yeah, the new one's boring.
It's not offensive to me, but it's yeah, it's all really good. You're just going to keep lost in
your arch. Let me get lost in this. Yeah. WWF New York had that aesthetic of chain link fence TV.
That's after the nineties. How few items can you use to fill a space? Yeah. So yeah, they were
sure they look, they were flailing. They were trying so hard. It's interesting because I,
this was not on my radar at all. These tie. I don't think any, any of us, I guess we were a
little older. I never heard of it. Yeah. What do we wouldn't have in the audience? Although maybe we
should, I think they were aiming for like 11, 12 year olds. I don't remember this at all. Maybe
I now in these properties, like there was a little bit of implication of Nick tunes being an, like,
sure. I'll go somewhere where the Nick tunes are, but Godzilla, the animated series or like the worst
one lost in space rescue challenge. Yeah. I guess it's all the Lacey Shabir,
Matt, William hurt and spade William hurt. Oh, well you think William hurt will be there?
I was very excited to see Gary old boom play. Dr. Smith.
I did like the movie that the tie-ins for that. I remember going like, all right, they're really,
I don't know about this. Not good though. I have no recollection of really what happened in that
movie. I saw it too. I remember, but I remember nothing about it. I got a free like, um, what's
the robot's name? Uh, yeah, I can't think. What is the robot's name? It's just called a Ross in space.
This is a big fail. We don't know the lost. There's somebody who was like, I thought these guys liked
Kitschy bullshit. Cause it looked like the old TV show one. And then he gets like upgraded to a giant
hulking one. And I like that. I like that as well. Um, but yes, I guess men in black,
I didn't really watch that men in black cartoon. It might've been fine, but yes, you're right.
It is like maybe with a better, stronger set of properties, you're getting kids. Maybe if it's
based on like independent state of the movie, which I think every kid collectively who saw it
were obsessed with it. We overthought it. Its name is just robot. Is it? Okay. Yeah. Well, thank
good. I'm glad it's not a specific name because I would be very embarrassed. Robot, uh, robot model
B nine. Everyone just remembers danger. Will Robinson. Yes, I remember that. Yeah. Well,
so I guess what we're finding is that the paramount connection did not open all the doors.
Kids are not like, we gotta go back to discovery zone to see lost in space rescue challenge. Where
was my star trek tie in? Well, they had power Rangers for the first movie. That's true. Yeah.
We're getting a big one. Yeah, that is true. That is on point. And it seemed like there was like
risks things you would get. Um, uh, uh, it did seem like a lot of locations. It was mostly some
cardboard cutouts of the power Rangers. Yeah. That I think you, I think the, the business model was
like, if a regular party for like kids were $5 a head, if you want the power Rangers upgrade,
it's an extra three. So that's the idea there. Um, it doesn't seem like they thought like they
had some really cool things to do with the power. Like if you, the kids all got to dress up, I guess,
like them. And then there was some sort of like organized game. Okay. A little more closer and
you played the music loud. It's not, it doesn't take much. It doesn't take much. But from the
sound of it, I don't think they nailed some sort of transformative experience that kids were
desperate to do. It seemed like they were focused on making money by nickel and diming people.
Cause you can't upcharge for the jungle gym. You know, you can't charge for the tubes. Well,
if you're playing the power Rangers theme, you can, but you can, but like, it's hard to say. So
this side's a few bucks extra, you know? Oh, right, right. There's certain parts of the jungle gym
are more expensive. I was also what Disney's doing. Yeah. We're describing it is. And, uh,
yeah, I there, but there was like, um, like there was a like unattended zip line at some of the,
like a, a 10 foot like thing that you would hold and then drop into mats. Like what was your
favorite part of these contraptions? Like to do pie, just as high as I can be. Yeah. I did like
being high and these things. Yeah. You were a height miser kind of being, but it's this.
Clear. Yeah. Not all being off the ground in a tube. I liked, uh, so that was the end and the
ball pit for sure. But I, yeah, I mean, I'm trying to think like, I think as a kid, the ball pit
seemed like the most fun in reality, not as much fun to do it. Yeah. Once you were in smell,
certainly like kids in there. Yeah. And, but, but navigating it, especially with a bunch of strange
kids, usually it was like, I gotta get out of here and in a different part of this. I know it's like,
you really imagine like I will be, I'll be in there for two hours. That is going to be so glorious.
And instead you sort of want out in three minutes. Yes. So that, so, but, but crawling through the
tubes and stuff. And yes, I agree with getting a very high up in this thing, which is why I think
the leaps and bounds is my favorite because you could get very high in my mind and look down,
see the gains from that height, see him playing the gains, maybe see the characters. Right. Um,
so yeah, I think that either care you, you liked seeing the characters from up high, not close to
them. Well, no, I would, I would be, I would do every angle. Like describe one character that
you liked seeing from up high as opposed to in the cab. No, I mean, if a Chucky is walking around
and you see from the desk, like, Oh, there he is. There he is. You don't mean like seeing a street
fighter. You don't mean see bison on a screen from above. I mean, it's nice if you're trying to clock
like, Oh good, that machine looks as Simpson's games empty now. I see. I gotta get down there.
Yeah. It would take a second to get down there though. And it would be easy to get.
You know, that's part of the thrill. You would try to, I've said this before on the, on the
playground equipment in elementary school, we used to come up with ways to play on it that you
weren't supposed to stand on top of the tubes, like jump off the side of the slide as opposed
to going down the slide. It's a good thing. Your mom yelled at you. She doesn't know anything about
this. She doesn't know anything about this. She's going to listen to this. She will, but she will be
so zoned out listening just to the sound of my voice that she's being discussed. I think so. I
think she's still just going to be listening to how I know we're really protected. We're talking
about you right now. This is Carlson. You don't even know. See, I didn't like, I was a little guy,
so I didn't like being up high. If I could look down and see asphalt discovery zone, I feel there
was some stuff watching this, these videos. I was like, wow, you can really climb up high on that
net. And again, I wasn't a jump off things kid, but I'm like, I would have seen if I could have
landed in that ball pit because my head would have been like, well, they wouldn't have put it here
if I couldn't do this. Right. The, I think another thing is the Chuck E. Cheese. I don't,
I don't believe I spend a lot of time in the play place at Chuck E. Cheese. I was more arcade and
show, but it's because Chuck E. Cheese generally had a smaller one. So I liked if it was a big
play place, I liked it feeling like you could get lost in the tubes a little bit. Yeah. That was
something like fun. If it felt like you were on like a little bit of a journey,
this was more of a maze sort of thing, like discovery zone or leaps and bounds see much
more base. Chuck E. Cheese wants you to do a quick intermission in the tubes and then get back on the
floor, buy some pizza, play some arcade games, get dad to get another picture of court slide.
Getting fired up here. You had, you, yeah, you had your way of doing business there.
Like you seem confident is the way to do it. I agree with what you're saying. The,
the YouTube video we were talking about mentions that some franchisee of, of DZ felt that she had
to buy Domino's pizza and Baskin Robbins ice cream because the quality of the normal stuff
they would normally get from corporate was so poor. Oh my God. So she was losing money.
There's like a six minute video of a guy, like clearly like an in mall entertainment thing. And
he's like, Hey, I'm here checking out the discovery zone here at the South gate mall or whatever. And
he orders one of everything on the menu and the tray they give him looks like, you know,
I love garbage, but I was like, this looks disgusting. This looks bad. I'd like to see that.
Um, so while we're just, we're finding the cracks here, we're discovered the Paramount library does
not, uh, give them all the gifts, the treasure that they want. The food is not so good. The,
the quality they open strong, but the quality does not increase. Um, and of course you're always
fighting that look, I could go to Chuck E cheese and Chuck E cheese has robots. There are no robots
at discovery zone. Well, unless, well, let's pay a little bit of attention to our new friend who I
didn't know about before this, but the discovery zone robot whose name is Z Bob Z Bob. Um, now Z
Bob has, well, maybe we physically described Z Bob for a little bit. If anyone has a photo of him,
I mean, I saw him in the commercial. That's, that's what I realized is like, Oh, subliminally,
they would indicate there is a robot spinning around. Um, though I don't recall if I saw this,
I don't have a strong, I might've seen it not understood that it was a robot. I mean,
I just thought it was a statue. Yeah. Well they, yeah, they, they, I are a video game. That's sort
of just the casing looks like a robot. Yeah. Yeah, totally. That's kind of what I thought.
It's just, it's very bright plastic. It's the color scheme that I described here earlier. It's,
it's big, bold, bright primary colors, big yellow ball face and big blue nose. And then, and, and
red body boxing glove hands like that. Um, and then kind of springy, uh, antenna with little balls up
on top kind of looks like a, like a children's drawing come to light. Like it looks like a kid
tried to draw Ernie or Bert. Yes. It ended up off, but it's kind of cute in its own right.
Right. It looks, it looks like a knockoff of some, it looks, there's a cheap quality to it,
even though it's not poorly made, I don't think. I don't think so. It seems, it seems well made.
Decent quality. Um, now one leg up that these robots have as opposed to Munch and Jasper in
the gang is that you might be able to get right up close to this robot in the ads indicate that
he might roll up and join you at your table. Terrifying, terrifying prospect. I would've
down side for so scared. Touch my buttons. No, I know. No, thank you, sir. Oh yes. So that's part
of it set of four buttons of the only colors at discovery zone. And I think you would press them
and it would make like silly sounds. Right. That sort of thing. Curly from the three stooges made
the sound. It would play one of those. Wow. A robotic curly every kid's dream. That's right.
Um, so I don't know. You know what I have to, I gotta say nobody's tone really spiked when we
started talking about Z-Bob. I don't like it. Nobody likes Z-Bob. Maybe I hadn't come to terms
with it until I started describing him. I don't hate him. Look, I don't look, I don't want to make
for the record. I don't hate Z-Bob. I would even if you were to say, is he cute? I might go, yeah,
he's cute. Not enough to save the enterprise. No, no. Okay. There's a YouTube video just called
Z-Bob eBay video. Yes, I found that. Yeah. Everyone find this. Yeah. And you can hear an approximation
of some of the sounds and like what sort of shtick he would do at you. Right. Um, and it didn't help.
Yeah. It matters. Yeah. I guess I don't, I don't know. It's kind of like it's, it's sort of
my old party entertainment, which seems like where Z-Bob has ended up today. If you're looking for
what happened to these Z-Bops, there are several things that I found. One is that, um, okay,
well all of the information seemed to come from a listing on Worth Point, which we've come across
before with, you know, weird old Arcania and like find old menus or whatever. Right. Uh, Theme Park
relics. Um, recently got a lot of ads for that on Twitter. So things are going great at Worth
Point. What happened to Worth Point? No, no, I'm just saying like if you're getting fed Twitter
ads for in 2022, start at 2023. Oh, I see. Might not have high standards. Uh, well the listeners
are all going to get Worth Point ads because they're listening to this podcast right now.
That's how it works. Um, so listing on Worth Point says some stuff about, you know, kind of
some technical momo jumbo. I didn't understand about the, the, the making of Z-Bop and his,
his innards and what's in him. Like he's got, he's got a computer in his backpack and there's
he's got two amps and, um, and, and it could work if you had somebody who knew what they were doing.
And, um, and actually, um, there's a few of these around. One is used by something called,
called Vaudeville Entertainment, not spelled the way that you know, but VOD, V-I-L-L. And, um,
he's been repurposed and renamed Gizmo, the little boy robot. I went to the website for
Vaudeville Entertainment and found this listing and I saw a picture of a, of a smiling man. His
name is Richard and he works in the Kansas area and he seems like he would come around with a silly
hat and stilts and be maybe your kid birthday party entertainment. Um, then I, the same listing said,
oh, this Z-Bop actually has been on Pawn Stars. There was a Pawn Stars episode where somebody
shows up and Z-Bop just rolls into the store and he's spinning around and showing what he can do.
And it's a good sp- he's pretty like mobile. I got more on board watching him in action on Pawn Stars,
but the Pawn Stars are not impressed. The guy is trying to get 2,500 for it. I believe he paid
15,000. He claims, well, I want to get rid of this because I actually have another one. So I'm fine
with the one Z-Bop and there is no deal. The Pawn Stars compare Z-Bop unfavorably to newer robots
like Asimo. And so, you know, it just seems so old school. We don't think it's a fit for us and to
have in the store. I put something together in watching this Pawn Stars episode that the three
artifacts of Z-Bop, Worth Point, Vaudeville Entertainment and Pawn Stars, all the same person.
Oh, really? The guy who walked into the store is the guy who has the website of I'll come to
your party and bring Z-Bop or rather Gizmo the little boy robot. I'm not sure, like, why does that,
does little robot boy sound better than little boy robot? That's a good question. Little boy.
For some reason, why does that feel creepier to me? Is the little boy robot? I think it's lit. I think
little little robot boy Jason, would you, would you, would you say that phrase in the way?
Little boy robot. Let's not say the other one. Little robot boy.
It rolls off. Yeah, it's cleaner. You have to stutter stop. Yeah. Right. Anyway, so there's one
man, Richard Renner in the Kansas area who is trying to make some dough off of the, I don't know
if he's ever unloaded one of them, but he's, he's certainly trying to turn ownership of Z-Bop into a
business. And I wish him luck. Do you think he's ever had a bad night at the business and he's
kicked Z-Bop? He's like, you're not doing anything for me. We were supposed to be in this together.
This is supposed to be our ticket out of this town. She left and you stayed. He like kicks him
and then you're like,
come on, answer me. Give me a business plan.
That doesn't help me. That's what you always say. He leaves him on the side of the road and then he
comes back for him the next morning. I don't want to say this is a trap, but I feel if you push any
further, like you're gonna like Robert Earl's gonna throw a net over you. Like you're gonna
going to get more information about little boy robot and it'll be under like a big cardboard box
held up by a pole and you will get, you're saying that you think there's a way like that,
like this seems like a way to bait Scott Gardner. This could be a honey pot scenario. Yeah.
Well, luckily my interest in Z-Bop is low enough. Are you saying that if you dig deeper,
you're going to learn that this guy like legally adopted Z-Bop? No, no, I'm saying this is a trap.
There you have the work point is set up to try to that a previous like enemy of the show is
working in conjunction with the gizmo Z-Bop owner. Well, you didn't fool me today. Just like a pond
stars didn't bite. I'm not fighting. I also liked the history that this robot was made by 21st
century robotics in Atlanta, which is a company that previously existed to sell robots to the
Atlanta police that are like robots that the phrase used is child safety ambassador.
Oh my God. And there'd be a robot named NG one or I'm sorry, an ambassador droid named NG one,
who may be a child would feel more comfortable talking to than a scary police officer.
The ambassador droid look like it's, oh, I got to have to, I definitely saw a picture of it,
but I don't have one in front of me. I'll see if I can find NG one really fast.
As I recall kind of like scary and angular and like that one that was in Disney world slash
Rocky four. It seemed a lot up in that neck of the woods. Yeah. Oh, the John,
one that John Daffer out at the nightclub outside of Philadelphia.
Daffer thing with that too. We did that episode so long ago. I, oh my God, I think that ties together.
That's the robot Seiko. Seiko's the monomy Seiko. What are, what are our, our brains made of marbles
today? We're forgetting the name of every robot. He's got to see, you're right. It should have been
at the, it should have been that fast. There's just so many, when you're learning about new
robots all the time, like I got the information about NG one, the child safety ambassador droid,
and it shoved other roads shoved Seiko right out of my head. I have recently listened to that Seiko
song monomy Seiko. Oh, right. Yeah. There's a single Seiko's on a single. I forget the artist
that Seiko is singing with. Um, well, actually I'm sorry, Seiko. I'm sorry. I forgot your song.
Um, and pretty good. It's scary. Can you see it off my computer? He,
this NG one is much scarier than any human is going to be. Oh yeah. Trying to get a kid
comfortable. This is not the way. I mean, I guess if we had a kid who was like an Ultraman enthusiast,
that's true, but that's the only thing I could quick check. You ever seen Ultraman? No.
Um, so I, all right. I mean, this is three strikes, Paramount properties and, uh, the, uh,
new, wait, what was the other problem? Uh, robots, no good food, no good. And yeah,
three strikes this come and all of this combined with expanded too quickly. They owe too much to
the Sumner Redstone Empire, who this is part of why I'm saying maybe this was Blockbuster's dream
and not Viacom's dream. I think they had to, I think Sumner had to deal with this in order to,
all right, what's Blockbuster doing? I guess we'll put up with this and Sumner Redstone had to deal
with this in his autobiography. There's a part of his autobiography where he explains, let me tie it
all together that the, uh, uh, the Blockbuster indoor, the block parties, those were, those failed
and then they were quickly converted into discovery zones. Um, although I think he was wrong about
that because the other one was open until 2002. Sumner, maybe I'm going to say Sumner Redstone
might not have had the vice grip on the Viacom Empire that he might've suggested. Preoccupied with
some other things. Change my diaper. I'm organizing a threesome for me and Robert Evans. Probably.
It's, don't worry. It's Robert Evans, another hot guy. Look at him. We don't have to explain
more. You're going to want to take our shoes off all day. Look, I'm going to Redstone and ultimate
guy. We should really find a reason to talk more Sumner. No, no, we love the tails. Clip my nails
or else I'll drop you at this airport and not pick you up again. Really telling the line from
guide a villain. Oh yes. Yeah. I don't know. Probably. Well, telling the only, he got his
diaper caught on. Oh, he's doing the line. It's like a looney tooties. The diaper with the hole
in it because he was getting an erection through the diaper. These diapers aren't strong enough to
contain erections. I need a better brand. The Acme brand contractions. If you don't know what
we're talking about is Google Sumner and any other words we're talking about. Find a picture of
Sumner Redstone and you'll go, ah, and then you'll realize that that whatever photo you're looking at,
he was still alive for like 20 years past that. He has the thing Bolsonaro has, the four president
Brazil where it's like, are you dying? Like, oh no, this is your normal. Like,
yeah, there might be more Sumner in our future. But anyways, oh, there, boy, I Googled it. There's
great photos. Sumner Redstone. So anyway, I just, I did, I did not know that Sumner Redstone
sometimes had to deal with discovery zone and that is funny is discovery zone is in his book,
three times. What an interesting crossover. That's great. But ultimately it was not to be
in the Viacom empire. I guess the, at the end of the day, discovery zone was an entity that
met disaster after doing business with Viacom, much like my career. I wish I knew the full
discovery zone story or I would have pitched my cartoon somewhere else. Are you in Sumner Redstone's
book? Then there's this dumb cartoon, Nagel paintings. What's that? I want an alcoholic bottle.
One of the poor, I know milk, but with like vodka and wine in it. One of the poor prostitutes,
like watched 15 minutes of it and said she didn't like it and that was the end of your career.
That's probably it. Do you like this? No, that's boring. That's what I thought.
Get the guy who made it onto my plane and then I'll shove him out at 35,000 feet. And if we can't
do that, I'll banish him to be making a podcast for the rest of his life. Playboy mansion. Watch out
for the dog shit and all the hallways and my shit. Oh Sumner. Oh boy. So yeah, look, it went away so
fast. They all started closing in 1990. They were, there were several passes at chapter 11.
And then in 1999, a hundred stores just closed one day, which left all of the managers of these
places who did care about kids and families all having to call dozens of families who have booked
parties and say, I'm sorry. Like, Oh man, we need to find like a manager and be like, how many did
you call and cancel? Cause you booked some of those at least Chuggy cheese. I remember we booked,
my mom booked like my sister's party like weeks, weeks and then you have to really make sure.
Oh yeah. I'm certainly into this area. We, you know, we have not jumped on it fast enough yet.
I don't know how to do this yet. But the, yeah, like here's a quote from one from a manager.
Let's just forget the children crying outside the school bus that arrived with 68 children.
Why the 17 scheduled birthday parties for Saturday? I understand that this is a business
and there's a way to do things, but a business that's supposed to be for the children sure
doesn't seem to care about the children. Wow. School bus 68. All right, we're here. It's time
to go. That's so much more traumatic than what I went through in the parking lot.
Probably all ran. They all like, of course. And then they ran and they just ran into a brick wall.
Summoner Redstone was outside where it closed. You go back on the bus. Step one, close a hundred
stores. Let me see video feeds of all that crying kids. Put the laser zone, put the laser adventure,
put it in the back, collect your tears. I want to save them. It's a whole weekend of tear drinking
for me. Maybe I'll save it. A fine vintage. I'll open it when I'm still alive in 2018. Does anyone
have some plasma to keep me young? Who wants to donate plasma? Early adopter of young blood.
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Let's see. Those are the tears from when I closed discovery zone.
Those are tears when I closed the Paramount theme park. That is me. I'm sure there are lots of kids
who grew up saying like Paramount's King's Dominion, you know, and thought fondly of like,
look, the Nickelodeon characters here are Paramount. This is positive. Flushing it down the drain. We
don't know the brand record. We don't need to eat. We don't need kids liking us. We don't need kids
at all. I'll be alive forever. Let's stop all kids. I'll be around when I'm 300.
Should have added a blood bank in each one to heart. I ran by that Jagged Metal thing.
Oh yeah. Right. That's right. Maybe that kept Sumner alive for a decade. Jason Sheridan's blood
was coursing through Sumner's veins. Well, you'd have to do it as a tie-in. Like I actually,
earlier I had a list up of Paramount Pictures films from the 90s. So if you tied it into like,
it's all right. It's the Harriet the Spy forensics adventure. Harriet needs your help. First,
just give her a couple drops of your blood so she can eliminate you from the suspects list
and help Harriet solve the crime. I am Mark Wahlberg, star of The Italian Job. To pull off
this heist, we need a few things. We need a crew. We need Mini Coopers and we need a pint of your
blood. A pint? That's a lot. You can trust your DZ associates. They're friends of Wahlberg.
Don't be scared of that needle. If you're too scared of that needle, then you're too scared to
help me. This is no Italian job for you. They should have just made Sumner like the Chuck E.
Cheese of DZ. You should have been in all the commercials announcing all this stuff. Then you'd
have a face and kids would want to come back and see him in the show. Come see me. Give me your
blood. Yeah. Oh wow man, I want to give this guy our blood. I'm waiting. He's like the Crypt Keeper.
We mentioned Chuck E. Cheese and they came into play. Oh yeah, that's right. Oh yes, the final
step. Yeah, yeah. They were given control or like they bought a handful. Yeah, they took over a lot
of the spaces. Discovery zones and attempted to like frantically reschedule the birthday parties
or fulfill obligations. Yeah, why not? Wow. Wow. Oh well, good for them. That transition time must
have been interesting because there would be, they're having parties. They have obviously enough
stuff for a kid to do probably in a discovery zone, but then they're probably starting to move
Chuck E. Cheese stuff in there. So they're probably in like, it's like a half Chuck E. Cheese,
half discovery zone. Like there would be hybrid situations during this magical year or two. Geez,
wow. Crazy, crazy flavor combinations like you couldn't imagine. Yeah. So there might have been
Chuck E. goofing around with whatever the hell the robot's name that I've already
forgot because it wasn't good enough to wow. We have forgotten every robot today. Yeah. Z Bob
is the name. God, imagine Chuck E. and Chuck E. and Z Bob. Imagine the possibilities. Just like how
there were Chuck E. Cheese with Billy Bob from the rocket fire explosion photos when there was that
transition as well. You really, boy, think about that. That's another, we didn't realize this was
yet another, an enemy vanquished by big cheese. Yeah. He slid the throat of Z Bob. Well, well,
well. I've done it again. Oh, a little kid's playground, huh? Wanted to get the kids exercising.
That's a way to be different than the old pizza place. And now you come crawling,
but maybe I'll buy your locations. Yeah. How about at one tent at a price?
Hey, thumbnail. I don't need no hole in the front of my diaper.
I don't know how to, where to possibly take it from there. Right. Turn out of that. I think,
I think you survived podcast the ride. The second gate. Well, wait, real quick. Discovery
zone is back. Oh, but it's not discovery zone. Somewhere else is just using that name and
painting everything with bright colors. Basically. And, you know, this kind of came up with the great
Wolf Lodge episode, but there's some language on the website that really rubbed me the wrong way.
Oh no. There's no other way. What's wrong with getting rubbed the wrong way? Yeah.
I need to do it for free for me thumbnail. I don't gotta pay. It's right when it's wrong.
These are located in Union Township, Ohio and Florence, Kentucky. I just gave the lady some
tickets. Both, both at malls. I guess a good use for empty anchor stores, you know. Okay.
Just as a language I'm reading. General admission. Potty trained children, parentheses, not wearing
a diaper or a pull up are $12 and permitted to play in the large play skate. Children still
potty training are get ground level play toddler zone area for $5. The toddler area. If your child
is in a diaper or pull up, we have you covered. Our toddler area is, is only your CEO. That was
in a diaper. What is that? Well, they're writing the checks. So you, they get to go wherever.
The toddler area, it's kind of, it's not a lot to write home about, you know. Oh, that's what they
can do. They have that at home. It looks amateur hour. This is taking making kids stay out of areas.
Every kid can go in our area. The VIP zone where is meant for 96 year old CEOs must prove your
wealth, must prove at least 500 million in net worth and just, just for safety, for cleanup
purposes, no holes in the diaper. Yeah, no, we don't care though. They do mention, you know,
arcade games, straight in your tickets. We have everything from slime to sour candy,
not interested in playing arcades. No problem. Buy prizes straight from the case for your little
ones. Now that's got my attention. That's what I want. That's good advertising. That's good
advertising. You'd have to, it was a secret thing with Chuck, with the Chuckie, you'd have to kind
of make it, you'd have to like wink because they didn't say they didn't advertise it. You could just
buy. Wow. Yeah. Prizes and off menu. Oh, yeah. I just had to know the code. Yeah. But there's
nothing he loves doing more than winking. That's true. Under the table business, wimping, begging,
just a rational solving. I break people down is what I do. You want that pack of Smarties? $50.
$50. That doesn't seem fair, sir. You don't give a shit. You don't want your kid to cry,
do you? I don't care. I love watching kids cry. Same as you, right? Yeah. That's right.
How is my summoner voice different? It's 10% less Jersey. I'm already taking these kids' blood and
staying alive with it. How do you think I got so big? We welcome people of all faiths because it
doesn't matter in here. I'm the king and the god. All right. We're there now. That's it. You
survived by a third of the second gate. If you want to dig even deeper, join us on Club 3 or you
get one more bonus episode every month and our main feed episodes ad free. Yeah, just a little
more money. You can afford it. Yeah, right. It's real. You don't like $3. And what if I said it was
$200? You want to hear them, don't you? You got it here. You want to hear us talk about it.
It's going to splash around, don't you? I just got to say, let us entertain you for $200.