Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains cherub faced garbage cans, goats sitting at a table,
Jason Sheridan's secret identity, and many calls to heed warnings.
Jason Woolner returns to talk Efteling on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast, The Ride, a theme park podcast, which today is your home for horrendous
mispronun...
Sorry.
You did you mispronounce it.
Nice.
Keep it in.
So insecure about the mispronounce.
I was going to say horrendous mispronunciations of Dutch words.
Yeah, but you're also English words.
Seemingly.
Well, shit, Scott Gardner here fucking up from the get go.
Mike Carlson making fun of me all the way.
Well, no, I'm saying this is a mistake that we must embrace it.
This is part of the reality of podcasts and people love to, as Jason said, people love
to hear how the sausage is made.
Yep.
Well, this is Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
I've noted that this has been said a lot lately and I've found that you guys saying how the
sausage gets made just means a mundane fact about how we're recording right now.
Oh, I see.
Just to go into how the sausage gets made, it's 57 degrees right now.
Right.
And like, just interesting sausage making.
Jason's wearing shoes with a white Nike swoosh logo on them.
Very healthy people like hearing how the sausage is made.
What the sausage looks like.
Tiny mistakes the sausage makes.
Scott, I looked that up too, because I'm like, I'm going to mispronounce a lot of this.
Yeah, we're screwed on this one.
But I will say that the park today has a very good English language website and in
the Netherlands, while the official language is Dutch, you often hear, it's very common
to hear French, German, English.
So.
Oh, so we got a lot of different languages we can screw up early.
We butcher the English language a couple times a week.
So this will be exciting.
Hey, you remember when I, what did I call the agave?
What did I call it?
A guave.
A U, yeah.
It's not.
That's maybe my least, my worst one, I think.
Or no, no, you know what it is?
Multiple times calling Jan Wenner Jan Winter from Rolling Stones.
Oh.
That's my most humiliating mispronunciation, I think.
How dare you sail the legacy of a boring man that, like in a few years, the last person
who knows who he is will be dead.
No one will need to know what his name is.
That's fair.
Let's bring in our guest who is here to talk about Efteling, a big one, legendary theme
park in the Netherlands.
And we're here with somebody who's been and he's also one of our favorite folks.
He's of course the director of Borat's subsequent movie film and the director and creative mind
behind Paul T. Goldman, a fantastic series on Peacock, all six episodes of which are
streaming right now.
It's Jason Walliner.
Thanks, Scott.
Thanks, guys.
Very happy to be back.
Yeah, yeah.
Happy to have you back.
And also, and I'm glad that you're willing to come back also, just given some of the
recent weirdness.
I don't think I need to say this.
People have seen the headlines already.
But of course, I am being charged by the Santa Fe district attorney with involuntary defamation
for all the times that I've called you the Alec Baldwin of Podcast The Ride.
Well, you know, I thought, yeah, I didn't think we'd get into that.
I know, maybe we're not supposed to and we can cut this if we're not, if we're not, we'll
run it by a lawyer or something.
But to me, that feels like that's for lawyers to sort out.
The trial will happen.
But you know, you and I here, that problem is not between us.
You know that I first said it meant to be in a complimentary way.
And look, it's you being charged by the Santa Fe detective or sheriff's office.
I mean, it's not me.
To me, when you say Alec Baldwin of Podcast The Ride, I think that means I'm probably
one of the noblest guests you've had on one of the best human beings.
Exactly.
Yes, yes.
A most humble, not a murderer.
You have to think the context of when it was said.
And this is so getting charged.
This is what I'm this is going to be my defense.
You're telling me my own defense.
You're a great father like him.
Great father.
Strong father.
You've got to get a couple more going.
You've got to get a few more in there.
Strong voicemail parenting history.
You call you have young children, but you still you set up a phone line to call them
just to leave them like great wonderful love notes.
The best way to distribute life lessons to your kids is through a voicemail when you
tell them what they are.
Whenever you think of something, just call, leave a memo.
And much like Alec Baldwin, you do a killer Trump impression.
We love to hear it says I don't want to do it.
I don't want to do it.
You usually charge people to do it.
So we don't want to.
Yeah, no, I can't.
But thank you.
Thank you, Scott.
Yeah, no, I'm glad we can start through this anyway.
All right.
Well, to move from one thing that you're you're known on the podcast for to another the mainly
people have been listening for a long time know, you know, what is what is I think a
great episode of the show, which is our failed parks series is the first that you came and
talked to us the two ambitious episode where we had two entire episodes worth about just
one of the failed parks, Hard Rock Park.
Well, it was also and the Sid and Marty Croft land was part of that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Which we just had to gun it through to get into.
I still feel bad about it.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
We gave it the short end of the stick.
It's wonderful.
There's been video of it going around lately, I feel like of that that pinball ride, which
is so nuts.
Yeah, really good quality video.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like shot a nice film.
Yeah.
And I want to start talking.
I mean, I've been talking a lot about my favorite show Club Random a lot lately, but I want
to start stop talking about that and start talking about Sid Croft's Instagram Live,
where he interviews like Adam Carolla.
Oh, wow.
I like there's different shows I want to talk about.
You're telling me there is a there is a weird low budget online only show that landed Adam
Carolla, believe it or not.
That's right.
OK, but I bring I bring all this up to say I just got curious.
Like in the last few years, we have not checked in on the former site of Hard Rock Park, and
I wanted to see if there was any update that I could give you since you're here.
And there's a pretty exciting one.
Oh, wow.
I'm excited to share this.
I looked it up.
There's been activity on the site very recently.
There's been newspapers, squatters, by activity, I mean, piss and shit, every human piss and
shit everywhere.
No, I so you know, it's just been sitting dormant for a long time.
People go wander around there still.
I think it's really is squatting.
But that's all about to change this spot in Myrtle Beach, where Hard Rock Park used to
be.
The newspapers have been buzzing about something called Project Crestfield.
Big mysterious kind of like code name of movie.
So what is Project Crestfield going to be?
And now it has come out in just the last few months.
Project Crestfield is the the mission on the site of Hard Rock Park to turn it into a mass
grave.
Project Crestfield has seen tailor made to be like the defendant in this case.
Project Crestfield.
Sorry.
Prozdgiv attorney Erin Brockovich.
Project Crestfield is supplying Ukraine with tanks right now.
Sorry, Scott.
What is it?
No, no, no.
Very exciting.
The grand reveal.
It's going to be a FedEx distribution facility.
Let's go.
Yeah.
All right.
Taking a work out like out of the existing buildings that are like someone's office going
to be that Knights in White Satin ride.
They have not figured out like, OK, there is good news.
There is a light in your office.
Bad news.
It is a strobe light.
It's just flashing rainbow colors all day.
I don't know if we've said this on the show before, but and I don't I'm not going to say
anyone's name, so it's fine.
Listeners went into the site of the old Hard Rock Park and there was just it's sitting there.
Merchandise is just sitting strewn about on floors of buildings.
Brought us some merchandise, some other urban explorers, untouched, untouched merchandise.
Other urban explorers found a similar like dead drop of merchandise.
But then other people also found I think it's a Brighton Films maybe like was exploring
it and they found like we found the agreements from the Eagles.
Like we found the licensing agreement of like bands.
How fast did they leave this place?
It's like overnight.
He's like, just get the fuck out of here.
We got to go right now.
We are wanted in this state.
That's rock and roll, baby.
Winston, the punk rock dog is just scurrying out trying to get through a door.
Fill the dog costume with whatever shit can fit in it.
Let's get in the car.
We need to move faster than Led Zeppelin the ride.
I've got a bunch of Coca-Cola syrup canisters and I'm going to resell them.
Let's recoup our losses.
They've started demolishing the facilities and as of October there were still big signs
that said Freestyle Music Park everywhere.
Like the second name of it.
But it's so it's starting to go finally.
But this next new chapter is going to begin and imagine the pride of the FedEx workers
knowing the history.
Can I ask the name Project Crestville?
Is this sort of like the Florida project where if people caught wind that it was a FedEx
all these businesses are going to pop up around it because they're so excited and they want
to keep the prices down from buying the land.
Oh yeah.
That's what it is, right?
Instead of just saying FedEx shipping center.
Maybe people are just as excited about like a FedEx as they are about like a Disney.
FedEx is one of the most popular shipping companies in the world.
Yeah they're pretty accessible though.
Top three.
Yeah they're around though.
What's number one?
Is it FedEx or is it the post office?
I don't think it's the post office.
They're not I don't think they're doing very well.
Right?
I don't know.
Jason will figure it out.
Yeah.
I know I think people are just excited that like a that there will be a business in the
Myrtle Beach area that doesn't fail within four months.
That's fair.
Yeah I can see that.
That's why the boom.
Anyway, just excited that you know the next chapter to the story of Hard Rock Park.
Well, that keeps rocking on.
But we're not here to talk about that.
We're here to talk about.
I need to cut you off Scott.
I have another thing I need to bring up because Jason is here.
Because Jason one of the last times I saw him something happened that was very embarrassing
to me that I brought up on the show before.
What was this?
And I would like we haven't really talked about it in a second.
So I know you do know it.
You'll know it as soon as I say it.
But you were there when I freaked out about the Minotaur.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
As soon as you said the word freaked.
That's right.
And we this is not your fault that you were having a physical reaction.
You were afraid of the Minotaur.
Who could fucking blame you?
That's all it was.
There was no other dimension to it.
It was just fully that I wish you could see how silly I did see.
I remember I stayed.
Oh wait, you I stayed and then I walked through.
So if you don't watch us on video, how did you actually know the Minotaur?
We saw you at the end when we did.
Yeah.
And then I saw I don't know that you earned being in that picture.
I said I didn't want to do it.
And everyone said I should.
And I said, no, I don't want to be in the picture.
But I am in the picture.
Photoshop him out.
Somebody Photoshop him out.
There was an escape room event that happens where you would go in and solve little puzzles.
And it was called the Minotaur.
I forget something was the Minotaur was in a subtitle.
Yeah, it's like Escape the Minotaur.
It was a Russian, I think, escape room that they had carted over to L.A.
Yeah.
And you're in a dungeon.
You're solving puzzles.
It's like halfway between an immersive play and an escape room where you're encountering
actors, you're running through things, you're doing tasks.
But then every once in a while, the lights will go out and the Minotaur will come and
try to kill you, try to take one member of your group.
But the thing that would happen every time the Minotaur would come is they would play
this early 2000s drum and bass music.
I remember.
Yeah.
And so it was so funny that it could be scary.
It was like the Minotaur was like a DJ coming to get you.
So it was like if they had scary music, I would have lost it.
But it was so silly, the music they played, that it was just like you're suddenly in a
club.
Yeah, I remember because what happened was as we were getting the explanation, we were
all wearing jumpsuits and we're all wearing masks.
And I have some sort of like clothing claustrophobia in addition to like I remember this now, a
darkness sort of like claustrophobia too.
So I'm sitting there, they turn the lights down a little bit.
I remember my vision kind of like shrinking and I'm like, no, no, no, no.
And so in the middle of this, right before we go in, I have to like raise my hand like
I'm back in third grade or something.
Excuse me.
I'm having like a panic attack or something.
I'm having like a, I think I said a mask, mask based panic attack.
And the person looked at me like, we've never had this happen before.
Like, just like, like, is he joking?
Is it serious?
And was like, oh, oh, and like they're doing like a whole, like a whole like voice and
stuff for the mood and the atmosphere.
Right.
Like, yes, and then we'll go in this and then you'll, you'll confront the minutes.
And I'm like, excuse me.
And they're like, oh, well, you can just sit over, just sit over here.
So in my mind now I'm recovering from whatever this anxiety was and I'm hearing the dumbest
sounding shit.
Feet away.
In my mind, there was some massive dungeon urine.
It's feet away.
I'm hearing yells.
I'm hearing the whole thing play out.
I'm like, this is like as big as a garage.
Yes.
I'm sitting there waiting for you guys.
And then you guys came on.
Everyone was very nice.
No one was mean to me.
No one was even judging you.
No, I know.
It's not your fault.
But I'm just saying this is, we haven't, we haven't re-brought, I mean, we've brought
it up a little bit, but it's something now I have to conquer.
It's become like a mountain.
Let's go back.
So we're going to have to go back.
What are we, is, has this, has this come back?
Is there a chance?
I think this company was doing like a revolving, yeah, they had a couple of escape rooms at
this one place.
So yeah, we, whenever you want, let's go face your fears.
We will go face my fears.
Well, first things first, just listen to a lot of early 2000s drum and bass, psych yourself
up that way.
That's a good idea.
Which shouldn't be a chore.
Was that part of the deal?
If it was carted over from Russia, did they have to like, we have an ironclad deal with
the composer.
Something like that.
Yeah, no one in America would have made this choice.
When the lights were on and then I walked through, I said this before on the show, the
Minotaur's just standing there.
The costume couldn't have looked shittier.
Well, yeah, the lights were on.
Well, of course.
I'm just saying like, there was, it was so much more embarrassing to see what it was.
And again, I wasn't actually scared of the Minotaur.
I was scared of the dark.
Let's be clear.
I wasn't scared of the Minotaur.
It's more reasonable to be scared of a Minotaur.
I know.
I was scared.
I mean, literally, I think I was scared of the dark.
And so, hey, you know what happens?
It happens.
No, no one was making fun of you.
No, I know.
I did not think that, but it is one of the most humiliating things that's happened to
me in the last 10 years of my life.
Well, that's good then.
That means that really humiliating things haven't happened to you.
That's a good point.
It's a very good point.
We've done a bunch of live shows and never in any of them have your pants fallen down,
you tripped, and then the audience all vocalized, hey, look at his tiny dick.
That does not happen.
You've successfully kept your pants on.
That's true.
We're in the dark about how big your dick is.
It could be huge.
They don't know.
Jason, did you know they don't know how big it is?
Oh, no, I saw it that night.
Yeah, because you came on and I didn't have my pants on.
Yeah, yeah.
He said you had to calm down.
Sorry, just cleaning up here, cleaning the shit off of my dick from when I shit my pants.
I was changing my own diaper is what was happening.
Sitting on a booth.
Oh, yeah.
And then that's when the other employee from the other one came out and looked at me like,
oh my God, are you okay?
And I went, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm fine.
No, he probably thought something really bad had happened.
We have no training for this.
It has not happened.
We're told not to worry about it.
It will not happen.
We're getting paid by PayPal and the head of this often forgets.
Anyway, you feel okay?
Yeah, yeah, I feel okay.
I'm going to call my shot Minotaur.
We're going back to the Minotaur.
Okay.
I hope there is a Minotaur to go back to.
Let's do it.
And it'll be good because Jason's coming with us.
No, we are.
Yes.
I mean, sure.
Yeah, no.
Our good friend Eva is big into that stuff and our friend Landon.
We should get a group together.
We're going to get a group and do it.
Maybe I have to do it.
I don't know.
Maybe I'll be scared of the Minotaur just due to the...
Now you have it in your head that during the intro part, that's the time to freak out.
So maybe it'll make it come true.
And if they hide something later that's actually the scary thing, like an Ernest doll or something,
if it's anything like Ernest goes to Splash Mountain, then I'm out.
Okay, we got to get into the mega part that we're here.
We're here to talk about that also is like, I'm sure we've all had the thought of this
is a big one.
We're not going to be able to get to everything about Efteling.
So we should just take the pressure off for it to be a definitive Efteling episode.
Unless, Jason, that feels rude to you though, Jason, to like, if we're telling you this
isn't going to be the...
Would you like us to close it out and never talk about it again?
No, no, please.
Let me contribute just a little part to whatever this becomes.
You're the trailblazer, you're the early adopter.
Yes, the first guest, and I'm sure we've had people on who have been there, but you're
the first to grab it and talk about it.
I'm so honored.
Yeah, no, I think our friend Marissa Strickland has been there.
Oh yeah, sure.
Oh, bro.
Yeah, yeah.
I went there in 2016, back when it had a lot of attractions that I recently found out while
I was doing research for this are very thankfully not in the same state or there anymore.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That seemed to be one of your...
Maybe can we get into that in this episode?
It just seemed like, yes, what you can bring to the table.
Yeah, this was one of your knee jerks about talking about Efteling was some of the somewhat
offensive things.
And then, yeah, we started looking...
I think they're all gone, unless they've like...
I think they're gone, but they were very...
It was a process.
They were unhappy about it.
Yeah, we should get into it.
But also it's not...
I was like, oh yeah, we should talk about Efteling, the racist Dutch Disneyland.
But in researching and remembering it, that's way more than that.
It's great.
It's one of the best theme parks in the world, probably.
It's crazy.
This is a question.
Is it because...
I've never...
I've almost stayed away from looking at it too much in a spoilers way.
And probably we thought, do we not cover this until we've been?
But now, there are children in the picture.
Travel is hard.
I don't know when we're going to go.
I would love to go.
I'd really love to go.
But let's at least start and dive in.
This is a good excuse to link.
I'm saying it's worth leaving your family to go just for a few days.
This was Mike's master plan, I feel like, all along, was to like, now we have a reason.
We can say it's for work.
Leave for anything.
Do any dumb shit.
That's right.
2017...
I said it to him.
You could like, go to...
Because in researching this, I was looking at what's that, Europa...
What's the one in Germany?
Europa Park?
Yeah, like, that looks crazy too.
Yeah.
I might try to go there this year.
Yeah, yeah.
The ones we did a little like, European vacation month and that place, Fantasia Land, has been
in my head ever since.
And then like, the cruddy ones.
Yeah, the cruddy one I'm really excited about.
And Popeye Village.
Oh yeah.
In Malta.
Yeah.
I remember that one from the movie that I didn't tear down.
Yes.
It looks crazy.
And there are Popeyes walking around.
Yeah, they like, danced to pop music.
They danced to early 2003 music.
Just like Popeye.
That's right.
But yeah, I think we'd love to go, but I basically, it had just always been like, this legend
in my...
We've only heard it in this utterly breathless way.
And seeming...
What I thought about it was grand scale, you know, things being done in this ornate way,
full of animatronics, full of original IP.
We got no movie tie-ins.
The closest thing to IP are fairy tales and stuff, but it seems like, basically, I've
always just heard it talked about in the same breath as Tokyo DisneySea in terms of huge
scale.
You can't believe, like there's none of the cheapening out that might happen in the American
parks.
And I just always hoped that it lived up to that legend.
Everything I saw made me think, yes, but Jason, you're the person to ask.
It really fit, like just thinking back, you know, it's not like you're walking past gift
shops and everything.
Like you're really walking through like a forest full of like incredible, like multi-million
dollar dark rides and roller coasters.
So it was, I guess, built in 1952 as it was a park and then they added this like fairy
tale walkthrough, which they still have.
And so you just walk around a forest and then you'll find, you know, a talking tree or like
a guy with a long neck or...
But there's a lot of like weird European fairy tales that I'm sure none of us have ever heard
of like...
And you'll just like find a house and look in and there'll be like a family of like goats
in human clothing sitting around the dinner table, like moving and talking to each other.
Like it's really creepy and weird, like as fairy tales are, but it's not...
It's just like, it's a good place to wander around.
And yeah, the rides are crazy.
I sort of grew up from there and then they made this like haunted mansion kind of thing.
I forgot what year that was, but yeah, no, it just, it seems to have like kind of just
grown organically over a long period of time.
And it doesn't feel...
I mean, I went there, I think off season and I went there on my honeymoon and me and my
wife, we just bounced around Europe and I was like, we got to go to this place.
So we were in Amsterdam.
I think you take like a two hour bus ride down.
We stayed there for I think two nights.
And you stayed at Efteling?
Yeah.
In the Efteling hotel?
There's like an enchanted village of hotels and you're around a lake with a little castle
on an island in the middle of it.
And you just walk around and then we broke into the park at night.
We hopped the fence and just went right back in and just walked around.
It wasn't anything crazy.
Like you couldn't get deep into the ride buildings, but like there was no guards.
No one cared.
Whoa.
What were you near at that point?
What was the, what was the sneaking around part?
I don't know.
We just wanted to see what it was like at night and I guess it closed pretty early.
But I was just looking through all my photos and yeah, I have a picture of Becky, my wife
jumping, jumping over the fence.
And then I think I was afraid to take more pictures.
But like, yeah, it's just a cool, it's a cool, crazy place.
It's yeah, it's a, there's lots of stuff to it.
Yeah, geez.
I, we're, we're, we're to dive in even.
We can start picking up like, well, I mean, anything general, you kind of gave us the
general history.
Mike, what do you think?
I was just gonna say like the, if I'm correct, like where it is geographically feels also
kind of like a special, am I wrong?
About this.
It feels like you have to travel.
It's not near anything.
Yeah.
No, it was hours away from a few hours away from Amsterdam.
I feel like doesn't that add to the mystique of it?
Definitely.
Yeah.
It's in a pine forest, like a real like very wooded pine forest.
It does seem like when the views that you get from anything with a, with a drop or anything
where you go up high, it is not like, it's not like looking into no offense, Mike, Buena
Park.
It's you're maybe getting a stronger, a more beautiful view.
I think, I mean, it just depends on your taste.
If you like trees and vistas, but if you like seeing the big rock and bruise guitar or the
claim jumper that's.
Is there a rock?
Yeah, but you get to see long neck.
You get to see my man long neck and the paper gobblers.
Paper gobblers.
So there's a, all the trash cans are these chubby kids that you walk by and you hear
they like play a recording.
They're like begging you to put paper in their mouth and other trash.
Yeah.
I made an effort to look up the name of this one because, and this like, cause I, and I,
my guess would have been way the hell off.
Wait, can I even do it?
I tried to write it out phonetically.
Hola Bola Heish.
Hola Bola Heish is the name of the, the paper guy.
Heish is how you, is how you say G I J S.
This is why we're screwed pronunciation wise.
I saw one video where they were calling them Holy Boli guys.
That's probably the translation.
Yeah.
Holy Boli guys.
I mean, I like that better.
But yeah, I saw it's in, it seems like it's an entire little garden of little like characters
with cherubic faces and gaping wide mouth holes that all, if you, I mean, and you fed
them I assume you put something in there.
You feed them your garbage and they, you know, thank you.
I saw the copy somewhere, feed them with all the papers you've got or else they'll yell
a lot.
And it's all manner of characters.
This kind of like, you know, cherubic man boys, but then like giant twins who cry because
they don't have paper.
And I, here I have a, let's just listen to the sweet sounds of what I'm going to borrow
the Holy Boli guys.
Let's hear some Holy Boli guys for a second.
I guess paper here.
That sounds like it unlocks the Manchurian candidate.
Like it unlocks some sort of programming.
There might be a listener somewhere who's been activated.
He's going to kill a politician right now.
Here's a couple more, all variety of pleasant sounds.
What the list is this technically ASMR?
Could be depending on your taste.
If you're psychotic, the, the, what you got with the listener is not seeing also are these
like gigantic helm, these perfectly round helm mouths.
So maybe given current company, I should ask, are the Holy Boli guys cute?
I love all the creatures.
Well, but that's not the answer.
That's not the answer to the question.
Yes.
Do you think baby heish is baby heish who we're looking at?
And let me play the clip and then you can determine cute or not.
It's a giant baby with like a, like a mushroom hat.
Yeah, there's a whole like family tree of like, this is, this is the one.
This is the sun.
What is Jason?
I'm waiting on the answer to the question.
I mean, I think they're pretty cute.
All right.
For a trash can for stuff that's like, in the scheme of things.
Baby Aladar is cute.
Baby Grinch to me is cute.
Is this baby cute?
I think they're pretty cute.
You know what?
I'll qualify.
I'll say, I'll say no.
All right.
You say no.
That's a scary baby.
It's important to hear these from you sometimes to know you're being honest.
I like the baby though.
I do like the, I would love to feed any of these babies.
I would love to hear these papyrhirs in person.
Wait, I think this is the most horrifying one.
This kind of like giant, this like 50 year old man looking guy.
You think that's cute?
They just say long to eat paper.
That's all they crave, you know?
That's what's cute about it.
It keeps asking, not once are simple, you see.
Yeah.
I think in the con trying to contextualize, like Jason, as you said, a European-
If you need context for why it's cute, I think it's not cute.
Yeah, I think you guys have to say cute or no.
There's a different standard.
A European fairy tale is often a lot more dark or grim.
So for a European fairy tale, it's cute.
By American standard, I mean, Disney is soft enough.
If that was in America, okay, the hubbub is, if that was in America and there was no like
trash component to it, would you still think it was cute?
I will at least go to intriguing, but I think-
Oh, see, that's it.
It's nice or not cute?
I'm not moving the trash.
Do you think long neck is cute?
Do you like long neck?
I don't like long neck.
I'm a little scared of long neck.
I love long neck.
The cutest thing in Efteling is more disturbing than the most disturbing thing it is.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah, for sure.
Like it's just, there's something inherent about European like caricatures that are just
grotesque always.
Yeah.
Like there's always, they're always like just disgusting inherently.
Like nothing, like they don't have that kind of like any of those like hallmarks of cuteness,
like big eyes or smooth skin.
Yeah, or like symmetrical, everything's bulbous and like heads are like plunging off of necks
and out of clothes.
Baby looks like an 80 year old man and that's as good as they can do.
Which part of the history of it, I don't think I, maybe I don't have the name, but the like,
the initial, oh no, Anton Peake.
From 52 to 74, everything here was designed by Anton Peake, who was an illustrator of
terrifying fairy tales in the Netherlands and probably elsewhere in Europe.
So it has, everything physicalized has the feel of the like too detailed, too many lines,
terrifying fairy tale drawings.
Yeah, and they, everyone, like the guy who took over after him is named Ton Van Deve
Van.
What is that right?
Ton Van Deve Van?
Ton Van Deve Van, yeah.
He from like the 70s to like 2002 was like the guy.
This is not a tour.
And he retired in 2002.
Yeah.
Everything, like basically two guys.
Well, he's kind of overseeing everything.
And I was like, I was saying to you, Jason, before we did this, like it all, this whole
park feels like an alternate dimension Disneyland where like the peaks of the place are really
similar to Disneyland's like started in the fifties was like, you know, little fun things
for little kids, charming.
But then in the seventies, it ramps up and expands and it's roller coasters.
And the original guys are no, are no longer there, but it gets taken over by the new wave
Like Ton Van Deve Van is alternate universe Tony Baxter.
Tony Baxter.
Two of them knew each other.
They were friends.
And Tony Baxter, like always pointed to Efteling, said Efteling's great, helped it win a Thea
Award.
Consulted them before they did Disneyland Paris, I believe.
Really?
I saw that.
Yeah.
Wow.
And then, and then like, and due to this guy.
You consulted them.
What's it like being a theme park in Europe?
Any advice?
You need to make it.
Thanks.
You need to see the horror.
You need to up the grotesqueries.
That's the, that's the, I've said this before, Tony Baxter talking about that.
Like there's all these like European rules that he talks about that I'm still a little
suspicious of them actually being rules.
Like he's like, the French don't understand funny and scary.
They just understand scary or funny.
And I'm like, is that true?
He says it with authority.
So I go, Oh, I believe that.
And then I think about it for a second and I go, Oh, maybe was there like ever a Jerry
Lewis ghost movie?
I don't know.
I feel like he must have run away from a ghost at some point.
But they thought in France they found it scary.
Yeah.
They were right.
It was, it was played.
Yeah.
It was played.
It was a serious ghost movie starring Jerry Lewis.
Even though he's yelling.
Yeeeah!
He was a guy wearing a sheet, but it was no laughs.
No played for no laughs.
But basically like because of this guy, much like Disney in Tony Baxter's run, the 80s
and the 90s are fantastic for like that.
That's something I didn't know about the history is like, are these, is it all attractions
that are grandfathered in from the 60s and that are classic?
And in fact, no, they add something new and incredible, like at least every two years,
if not more.
Like so many of the great stuff here is very recent.
Yeah, like recent dark rides that you would, I feel like would fool you into thinking it
was there for 50 years.
Yeah.
Let me, before I get to newer things though, original classic charming stuff, one of them
will not try to say the Dutch version.
The American version, the English version is the, it's a donkey from the table, the
ass and the stick.
Is that the donkey that shits gold coins?
That's right.
Did you see that?
Did you do this?
Did you get gold?
Yeah.
We got a token.
Kids, kids gather around the donkey.
I think it's actually plastic, but yeah, I know it, it does that.
That's cool.
That's great.
I like it's like, everything's like a little more like it's, it's a little edgier than
American parts of being a little body, little body or down to what would you classify this
as body that like in, in articles that were like, yeah, see, it's a little more European.
One of the things they mentioned is that there's Ariel, this little mermaid.
She just, she's a topless.
Fully topless.
Yeah.
Well, and now European standards, like Jason was saying that isn't maybe body, that's just
normal.
That's fully closed.
Yeah.
By European standards.
Right.
They managed to get more naked than regular people.
Yeah.
And American, yes, I am a little offended by it, but sure.
If it's Europe.
In terms of body, can we get into the carnival festival?
A little early for that.
Some of the compilation videos I watched sort of gloss over carnival.
I can show.
Yeah.
I have a video.
I recorded the whole thing because I was so blown away by it.
So basically they have their own fully a knockoff of it's a small world.
That was one of the two extremely racist, right?
It's like a very racist.
It's a small world where the, you go through parts of Africa and Asia that are just like
jaw-droppingly shocking.
And they did remove this, I think in what, 2017 or something recently.
Still in 2017, they figured it out.
So that's good.
Oh, he got this was a different time.
Pre pandemic.
It's world was different.
I don't want to specifically describe what you saw.
All I can say is that it's like, okay, it's, they aren't even, everything is scarier than
the small world dolls.
It's like everything is huge and bulbous and just big circles and exaggerated features.
And I will leave it to the listener to think about or don't think about it.
But everyone could not think about it.
But I think what was not changes in the France section, there's definitely a sex worker standing
on the corner, trying to pick up a client.
Wow.
There's a, this I like, this is good.
Knott's Berry farm has sex workers.
You wouldn't see that in a small, it's a small world.
I think the Dutch are more open about all parts of society.
90 minutes from Amsterdam.
You know?
Yeah, no, exactly.
Yeah, I know.
Not to jump her out, but do not let Palti Goldman know about this to make sure he never
sets foot in this.
I, it like, the ride besides these things, it's like, it's definitely a lot more, it
seems a lot more like claptrapy and annoying, even then it's a small world, which famously
gets shit for being an annoying song.
But this seems like a lot more grating.
Am I wrong?
Maybe it was different to be there.
I was just in shock going through not expecting the Africa or Asia sections that I was not
bored.
I wrote it again.
I was, I couldn't believe that was 2016.
I could not believe that was real.
So I know, I think they closed it and they removed, they said about a hundred dollars
and redid it.
And I think 20,
Only a hundred dollars were offensive.
This was 2019.
So this was only four years ago.
A little over so.
Two hundred were perfectly passable.
But there were two rides that absolutely should never have existed.
Or one could say needed an update.
And so the other one was way like more offensive.
It was called Monsieur Cannibal.
It was like the tea cup, rip off the tea cups ride except with a just horrifying caricature
of an African person.
Just the craziest thing you've ever seen.
And when they changed Carnival Festival, the small world one, they made a point to be like,
we're not changing the other one.
And they were like, look, some people, I read an article where the quote was like, we understand
some people are offended by this because they did not grow up with this ride.
I was like, well, that's not why.
That's not a good rationale.
It's the most incriminating thing I've ever seen.
If you grew up with this awful thing, you would understand.
Also, they said when they changed this thing, and I mean, like, I mean, I don't know if
you guys have seen this picture.
It's the craziest thing you've ever seen.
And you're all, the ride vehicles are the, the, the, yeah, you're being cooked by a cannibal.
You're spinning around this cannibal character that's, it's like, you know, you won't believe
what it looks like.
But, um, and you had no, you didn't know this was coming out.
No, no, I didn't know going in.
But they said, a spokesperson said, we have to keep moving with the times, emphasizing
that the attraction is over 30 years old.
Over 30?
Ancient.
That's not, this was younger than us.
It's not that old.
It's not old.
Jesus.
It's not just a different time.
It was a different time on top of a different time, on top of a different time.
They, uh, consulted with Disney PR on how to run.
They talked to the Splash Mountain people who ran interference for decades.
And they're like, what do we say?
And it's like, let me tell you, if you didn't grow up with that, a lot of these defenses
also seem like, isn't, isn't a Christmas thing in, in Amsterdam involve blackface?
Yes.
Pete, something Pete, that character.
Oh no, you don't understand that Santa's helpers.
And it's like, what?
Yeah.
I don't understand.
No.
They just keep saying the same.
Let me explain it again.
Black Pete is the name.
Is it really?
Oh, all right.
Yeah.
So you look up black Pete.
I mean, the Dutch have a history of extreme racism.
I would say that's an accurate statement, but yeah, they all go in blackface and wear
like curly haired wigs.
I mean, it's so yeah, that's the culture.
And so I guess you could see why they were like, what, why, why would we change this?
It's fun.
Well, and that when it was finally to this one was a 2021 change.
Yeah.
So eventually finally got rid of a Monsieur Cannonball in a.
Which had a song on it.
Also, like an old French song that played that must help.
Oh yeah.
A French song from the fifties with the same title and message.
Yeah, they were cool with their colonialism for sure.
This yeah, 2021.
Yeah, it's wild.
And then like, here's the thing that in the fallout of this, I read this and I thought,
well, things are kind of the same everywhere, aren't they?
In a way, because you can woke cancel culture is ruining everything.
Right, Scott?
Here comes the rant.
Yes.
Welcome to Clor Random.
It's a randomization of podcast.
Right.
So let's bring in Adam Carolla at this point, Adam.
We've been drinking man.
Greer this whole time.
And you know.
No, this they took this ride out and most people are like, OK, we are finally stepping
up to the times here, except for right wing politician Geert Wilders, who tweets angry
stuff about how they're giving into politically correct, inclusive, lefty nonsense.
And I'm like, well, I guess, wow, across an ocean, it is the same bullshit.
Yeah.
DeSantis and woke Disney.
And we have DeSantis and they have Geert Wilders.
There is one of these everywhere.
You have the fan art for Splash Mountain.
This is rare lives matter, which I saw today.
Good Lord.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
Boy, yeah, it's been a wild little little week.
I mean, they didn't have to do that public execution of rare rabbits in critter country
this week. That was a little much firing squad.
And you know, Disney no smoking, so they wouldn't even give them a cigarette on the way out.
Let's do an empty costume.
Don't make somebody.
What's done is done, though.
And that it's you know what?
They didn't declare him dead on site.
Rare lives matter.
Off the body off site.
That's what they do.
Their lives matter.
Wow.
Human being.
That's the one that really did that.
That's the one that really made me go, oh, like, exhale.
I don't the TikTok screen grab of like the woman holding a baby.
That one's like, oh, I got to tell them the ride they were named after is closed.
And what was that?
What was the name?
What does that mean?
It's going to be hard for that kid when they show up in elementary school
and have to tell everyone their name is Uncle Remus.
Oh, I have the real answer.
It was the name.
Yeah.
Briar.
It's Briar.
Yikes.
What?
Yikes is right.
Beyond the connotation like that, that you would name a child.
That I don't know.
It sounds like dryers.
The ice cream.
So they can get Brian, which is a name that's probably at the hospital.
So wait, sorry, Brian.
No, no, no, no.
Have you not been on Splash Mountain?
Briar.
We keep getting the birth certificate wrong.
You got to fix it.
OK, we've been through this for Jack.
Not saying it's back again.
Don't worry.
There's plenty of thorny vine bushes out there.
There are still plenty of briars.
Sorry, kid.
You're saying it's a thorn is still an acceptable name.
Well, isn't it?
I never mind.
OK.
I just meant a briar patch, like a thorny patch of like.
You're saying so the name is still relevant.
Like there is still tangles.
This is Jason arguing that the name is a good name.
That's what it sounds like to me.
We've all seen the patches.
It's a good name.
Uh-huh.
It's named after a famous patch, a different patch.
But there's rides that are not defensive and haven't needed to be changed.
I think.
Are those the ones or are they like lingering?
I mean, you never know.
I mean, there's so there's this incredible ride, Fata Morgana.
Uh-huh.
That is based on the legend of the 1001 Arabian.
I said they're knockoff of pirates of the Caribbean.
And it's great.
It's got hundreds of animatronics.
It's got songs.
It's you know, it's like it's great.
It's it's like very, you know, it's probably borderline.
Yeah, I guess given the subject.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh, for sure.
It's like you go.
I mean, you go.
I don't know those stories well, but you I mean, you you flowed through on a boat
and everywhere you look is like suffering and begging, toiling, drowning.
What are Arabian nights like?
Pretty tough.
You pass a guy looking into another guy's mouth for some reason,
just steal something, perhaps.
Then you go past a a man in a dark alley screaming at you.
And then then you go.
Then you see a tiger.
And then you go through the only time you see women are you go through a harem
slash opium den.
Do I do I want to go to this place anymore?
It's incredible, though.
I know I saw I look at pictures.
So angry and bummed out.
And then you go under you go underneath this like giant squatting genie,
like basically like grazing his balls with your head like there's.
All right, I'm back in.
But it's a it's a marvel to behold, though.
I mean, it's it's a great dark.
It's just massive and very long.
It's like seven minutes.
And to a place like this with this huge sprawling pirates level
bride that is based on nothing and that it doesn't come from some
gigantic corporation either, because I think the way this is straight,
I think it all there's there's the Efteling Foundation or it's some foundation
that pays for it. I just saw the explanation that like ultimately,
Efteling does not owe a bunch of money to shareholders somewhere.
So all of the money stays in the park, goes back into the park,
keeps everything looking nice, keeps them making new rides.
It's not like feeding into, you know, in the surrounds of executive pockets.
Right. So it all gets it's it's all the money's on screen.
They make these rides or they like contracting Sally Corp and places like that.
There's some of that. There's definitely some of that.
Included, there are rides for sure that are made by like
places that have made stuff that we've all been on.
One of them being there's
was this after you were there, there's a ride called Baron 1898.
Oh, I think that it just opened, I think, when I was there.
That's like a gold rush roller coaster. Is that a different one?
Yeah, it's it's really interesting because I saw a video where it's like,
oh, this is kind of a lesser ride.
And by American standards, it's very elaborate. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, it is so much. It's a pre-show with animatronics and projections,
big crazy story and carrot mythology.
The Baron, you meet the Baron there. Yeah.
And it's so it's so tower of terror.
Harrison Hightower, like this guy's got a shady operation
and he's going to get punished. And so are you.
The story of this in 1898,
the wealthy Baron Gustav Mouma, whom a wed,
whose last name is a variation on the Dutch word for hubris.
Gustav Hubris is led to a cave that is rich in gold deposits.
But and it is haunted by a spirit known as the White Women.
And the spirit of the White Women gives hubris the admonition
that if he disturbs the gold in any way, he will suffer terrible consequences
for the rest of his life.
So he can't disturb.
I like I want the gold, but I can't disturb the gold.
What will I do?
I will force the destitute local population into the gold mine.
So they're the ones disturbing the gold and they're the ones
that the white women will go after.
So it's a it's it's white women fiercely protecting their land.
It's a it's a ride about Karen's. It's Karen's the right.
Well, that that's a lot simpler than the first 80 percent of what you said.
Yeah, if you have to bullet, if you have to do it in synopsis.
But anyway, so you're going to you're in a crooked mine and you and then the
with the right itself is a drop coaster.
This is this one doesn't have a water component. This is a pier.
So it's one it's a coaster where you you hang, you get a view,
you go into a tunnel, it's all mist and fog.
And then and when you get screamed at, like you shall not evade my curse.
Prepare to forfeit your lives.
It's it's it rule.
I mean, that there we're going to be like Hulk tear it.
Yeah, it's extremely. Yeah.
Yeah. Your souls are he says your souls are mine, right?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, this it's got dark ride.
It's got like dark ride stuff at the start of the ride in the queue.
There's a barren animatronic.
There's multiple ghost projections.
And then it becomes a standard kind of roller coaster.
Sure, sure. But they have the theming and everything makes it feel like
like more than that.
And this one built by Bollinger and Mabillard,
who rides they've built Incredible Hulk,
Batman, the ride Riddler's Revenge, Apollo's Chariot,
the Fabio Goose Coaster and a little ride called Led Zeppelin the Ride.
The Fabio Goose.
Wait, is that different from Apollo's Chariot or is that?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not one in the same though.
I'm really that roller coaster, Fab Kai's Goose Coaster after the incident.
They really, really should should still should have.
I mean, because I as of now, it's like, you know,
trivia that barely anybody knows that that's not like a black up or something.
They should have something where someone by the end has like
when exploded goose against their forehead or whatever he did, like
and like you get to be the Fabio, like you go on the ride
and guess who's going to be the Fabio.
Every chair has like a blood path like the rebels.
The rebel spy on Star Wars.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But you get to go home with something.
You get a bunch of big blast of blood and feathers in the face.
It's like double dare.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everything gets you wet.
But what else gets you bloody?
Yeah, they have to they have to embrace their history.
Yeah, at least sell a hat.
At least sell a hat.
A bloody goose.
Yeah, yeah.
With like blood.
And then it's like one of those long hair hats. Yeah.
So you got. Yeah, yeah.
With the hair like, uh huh. Uh huh.
Do I survive Fabio's goose coaster?
You've got long Fabio hair.
My nose fared better than Fabio's did.
Is he like a right wing guy or am I confusing him with Kevin Sorbo?
Or they both right wing guys?
Right. Like so very much more vocally a right wing guy.
But I think he might be a right wing guy.
I mean, he's a businessman.
He's on Fox. He's smart.
Smart man. He's a right wing man.
Wants to protect his money.
Anybody who keeps their money and protects it.
Yeah. The reason they're on that side.
So that one's cool.
Baron 1898 rules.
What else struck you?
What are big ones for you going on?
You read about that one?
Spookslot closed last year.
I just found out on the drive over here.
I shouldn't have been looking at my phone driving, but I was.
And I found out Spookslot closed a few months ago.
Yeah, that was the first big attraction, I think, after the
when they were branching out from the the fairy tale forest.
Yes. Oh, this was yeah.
Like 1970s like we're we're kind of it's it feels like they're big thunder
or something like we can do relevant higher tech things.
Yeah. And it I was shocked when I saw this and I couldn't.
I was like, oh, my God, it's like a giant haunted mansion like walkthrough.
It's not even a walkthrough.
It is a walkthrough, but it's it's almost like mainlining
the haunted mansion where instead of going through an environment,
you see a little like pre show, but then you go into a room
and then it just like throws the whole thing at you at once.
So you just stand there and you're looking at a giant courtyard at night
and everything is like happening in front of you.
We don't move.
So it's like a weird animatronic, spooky play
where there's like great, you know, coffins wiggling.
And then there's a guy hanging in one corner and you look over somewhere else.
And there's like a witch burning and then there's some monks.
And but it's like all happening at the same time in front of you.
It was it was cool.
And so they already when they were closing it,
they uploaded multiple videos of like
ride throughs of this attraction, including like a 360,
which looks like a CG version of it.
And then they've also uploaded teasers of like this is what the replacement
dance macabre is, and it appears to be a very similar attraction.
But you sit in a giant, squirreling, moving theater
that will point you at different walls, like different scenes and stuff.
That sounds good.
Well, that sounds good.
Dance macabre, I think, is the classical music piece
that played in the original ride.
You see also a witch burning like this, like there's like suffering in this.
Oh, my God.
Well, there's a whole story that when I was there, because I don't speak Dutch,
I didn't understand any of it.
But I watched a YouTube video today that explains some of it.
And it's like that they're in a haunted castle that was cursed
because the owner, yeah, like kind of gave up a witch and she got burned.
So she put a curse on the castle.
And so you're watching the ramifications of that.
So you're watching the caretaker hang himself.
You watch the witch burn.
You watch someone's funeral.
But it's like it's really everything is like, from what I remember,
kind of happening at once.
So it's just like sensory overload on like spooky stuff.
It sounds I cannot.
I actually didn't get to watching a ride through this.
I can't. This sounds so insane.
And like, you know, you like,
oh, it's so crazy that there's a hanging body in the haunted mansion.
Would you see the hanging occur?
Do you see the moment of of death?
I don't think you see him drop.
I don't know the bell. He's ringing the bell.
He's ringing the bell.
You see him write the letter and then he hands a letter to the audience.
And then you see him go up on the chair.
Well, it's Europe. It's nice to say goodbye to Europe.
Yeah. Different over there.
Well, that is also, yeah, that's so crazy that there's still in
in our day and age hanging that you witness at the haunted mansion in Disneyland.
Yeah. Yeah.
But it's the it's the aftermath.
It happened a while back. Right. Right.
And he's like happy about it, too.
Like he seems like it's fun.
And that's him, right?
That's the ghost host's body.
Yeah. He died by suicide.
Yes. He said, why do they say why?
Do they?
Because he's trying to.
He realizes there's no way out of the haunted mansion.
The room that we're in, the like the elevator, there's no windows and no doors.
And he can't get so he has to he kills him.
Like we would all do it if we were stuck in that.
How did he get to the roof in that room?
How do you get to the ceiling?
Hang the news and where do you get the news from?
What do you he came there with a noose just in case?
I think he's in the attic.
Like we're seeing a little brief, like we're seeing into the attic of the haunted
mansion, right?
Like he's not in the room directly that we're in.
I think we're seeing through the.
Sorry, I need to go back to whatever year you guys covered this scene.
Twenty seventeen.
Yeah, I don't think we were we were very detailed and we always are about the haunted
mansion. We did not discuss where he got the noose from.
And I guess that's true.
Do you know the book Boundless Realm?
You know this book? You got to get this book.
It's incredible.
It's a it's a former cast member wrote
just the most in-depth book on the haunted mansion at Disney World,
but analyzing every inch of it as though it were basically like an art piece or whatever.
But it's I've been just working my way through it very slowly over the last few months,
but it's a wonderful book.
Boundless Realm for any haunted mansion.
It sounds cool, but it sounds like it doesn't have a definitive answer for your questions.
I got to go back and look. No, I think he does.
Oh, he does. OK.
Maybe not how he got the noose.
Everything could possibly be fashioned from parts of his clothes that he stripped off.
It is a rope.
I believe you can see that it's a rope.
OK, like a necktie.
I like to have a rope on them a lot more often.
That's a good point.
Like a clue or something.
Yeah.
Sparrow's he came in with.
All right, we got it.
This is you, however, derailing the no, no, no.
Well, my concern also is that the the book sounds great,
but that you've just thrown us something to make us go even slower through the haunted mansion.
You should be going.
This is terrifying.
I was going to say you were going through it way too fast.
Most of the room agrees with you.
We'll take a vote.
Do we admit this book into evidence or not?
Well, we'll discuss it.
What is other stuff here?
Oh, the flying Dutchman.
The fine Dutchman seems incredible.
Yeah.
Which one is that?
This is a water coaster.
OK, yeah.
This is in 2007.
It would have been there at least.
OK, this is a evil sailor who recruits his crew from orphanages.
Despite that there is a heavy storm blowing into port, he sets sail for the Dutch East Indies,
even though it's Easter.
And I found another description that like, OK, here we go.
Captain Willem van der Decken sailed the seven seas looking for riches and fortune
with his crew of orphans.
He was so greedy he even set sail on Easter Sunday, which was forbidden.
So this is a scary ride.
That's a morality play about not working on Easter.
And now the ship is cursed and it's doomed to sail the seas forever.
And you are on the ship, so you're fucked.
You're one of the orphans, basically.
And then here's some of this crazy, there's more crazy mummy dialogue.
When all despair for his lack of fear for God, he proclaims,
I will sail storm or not, Easter or not, this motherfucker prohibited or not.
I will sail even into eternity.
And then before the big drop, there's a scary voice that says,
you shall also sail until the end of time.
So we've got multiple scary mummy type attractions with big four,
with crazy writing, with like a dialogue that cuts into your heart.
It's great.
Damning you to be a sailor forever.
An orphan sailor always working on Easter.
Your Groundhog Day is Easter in 1678.
Jason wouldn't like that.
That's a Sunday.
That's a day of rest.
Yeah, it's a day of rest.
It's one of the many days that Jason rests.
Yeah, no, I said Sunday, Monday.
Tuesday through Thursday.
And then Thursday, you take a break because it's a busy Wednesday.
Yeah.
That looks fucking great though.
I like a good, I feel like I've never actually been on one,
one of the, like the hybrid where it's a coaster, but then there's a splashdown.
The line was way too crazy at the SeaWorld one that I really wanted to do.
Is that an Atlantis ride?
Is it the splashdown?
Is it like, is Hulk technically a splashdown or no?
No, this one splashes in the water.
Like it starts out.
You go in the water.
And then it becomes a standard coaster.
And then the coaster splashes in the water.
So this one is an open during Winter Efteling.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Cause they became year round at some point, but not the more water-based rides.
Also, this ride is in a big Viking ship kind of thing.
And I love the Maelstrom so much.
Yeah.
Maelstrom, one of the greats.
So we still haven't made it to, it's like, this is an entire,
this is a whole park that's like the Maelstrom.
Yeah.
That's the level on which I would really love it.
You would want to get yelled at by Norwegians and go inside big ships, big old ships.
It's a wonderful place with hustling, bustling city centers and the tourism.
Why did you come here?
Get out of here.
Do not witness our tourism.
A theme park where you're like damned on each ride.
Yeah.
Every ride dams you.
Or you see things that make you feel like you've been damned.
I was going to say, yeah.
One of the few exceptions I would say is a ride that I think is very intriguing.
The English is Dream Flight.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
I watched that.
It's a dark ride.
Droomvlucht.
And you're suspended, like the track is above you.
And Peter Pan, yeah.
Yeah.
And so you go through all the, there's a big diorama to start and then there's like a big
fantasy forest and then you are in space, which from the video I'm like, this is one
of the best portrayals of space in a ride I have ever seen.
It's great.
And you're looking at these planets that are like half planet, but they look almost like
they have castles growing out of them.
And then you float to somewhere else, like another forest.
And then there's like this big giant spiral room where you're going around a scene and
you're kind of descending, if I remember correctly, similar to the Calico Mine ride
actually at Knott's where you're looking at just a giant space from a lot of different
angles.
Yeah, it's amazing.
Cool idea that not a lot does.
And the fact like building a space that is truly three-dimensional and lets you see
everything that's not just like, well, that's a flat, you can't go back.
Yeah, you're not just going past scenes.
Yeah.
We've been talking about this lately with the people mover and with Discovery Zone
that we like seeing things from different angles.
That's good.
I mean, that is not to get all highfalutin, but that is something that the dark ride
as an art form can achieve in a way unlike any other form.
Like when you approach the prisoners trying to get the key from the dog and pirates,
and you see it in the distance and you creep towards it and then you're seeing it kind
of over their shoulder at the dog.
And then a few moments later, you're seeing it from the dog's perspective because you're
floating by and like, yeah, the angles.
Yeah, the angles are good.
Yeah, it's like bridging different.
You get major key frames and then everything in between.
It's the great unexplored art form of the 20th century, I think.
God, wow.
That really does like...
That elevates me.
You know, it makes me feel good about that.
We talk about these things.
We've done this for six years.
Yeah, it's good.
It was art that we're talking about.
No, there's so much potential.
God, I thought about this way too much and not in a while, but there is so much potential
with Dark Rides as an experience that beyond what we know of in theme parks, I think there's
a lot there.
But even the way that it tells a story where you're kind of just drifting through and it's
not often so much about tension and storytelling as much as moment to moment experience is so
much more like real life than any movie or anything.
Especially on that Fata Morgana ride we were talking about where you're just kind of like
going through these scenes in the ancient Middle Eastern times and you're just getting
a feeling and you're just kind of observing.
You're floating through.
And it's like some of the recent rides, the rides where they point you at something or
they're attempting to do something that feels more cinematic, but it's not as usually as
interesting or a good experience as like Pirates where you're just hanging out with a bunch of
And you're deciding what to look at.
Yeah.
And yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you were the camera.
You were choosing what to look at in this room.
That's what makes it different than like a 3D movie.
So when they do rides that are like really hardcore pointing, except for Transformers,
which is perfect, everything else though, when they're trying to do that, it feels like
you're pointed at the most perfect things that anyone's ever done.
That one they nailed, but everything else it's like they're trying to like imitate
sort of a thematic experience, but yeah, it's generally better.
In terms of that real life thing, the way like, especially Pirates and I imagine
Fatima or Ghana too, like the conversations weaving in and out that you like leave one
sound loop and enter another and enter another and like the lack of music can be a nice thing too,
in terms of just creating reality and not like imposing, no, this feels like
foreboding and dangerous.
Like you kind of get to decide the feeling of certain scenes like this.
The thing I saw a couple of people mention about Fatima or Ghana that you don't see in a lot of,
at least American rides, it's a boat ride, but it's not straight, there's doors,
there's doors, thematic doors that you go through, that open up at the start of every scene.
And like that kind of changes, like Pirates, you're floating the whole time.
There's no real obstruction.
There's no separation.
Yeah.
So you get more of like separate.
So it's like little scenes playing out, but you still have to choose what you pay attention to.
Like it's more, they honed in on the like ethereal, like, well, let's just pack this with detail.
Let's pack this forest with Dreamflight and you can see all these little guys and little creatures.
Wasn't that the cool thing about a lot of these rides then is like,
when you think about what Efteling doesn't have the pressure to do, like that they don't have the
pressure to serve a CEO and put money into his pockets.
And similarly, they don't need to promote a movie.
It's not one piece of a big promotional puzzle.
So there's no like, okay, we got a race to get every character in there that everybody.
I'm glad they didn't put these characters in movies.
I'll say that.
Yeah, but I would not see any movie with any of these characters.
Do you think Disney will ever again do a ride like that?
That's not just about tying in and promoting a movie or a Marvel property or a Star Wars property.
I've said, I think the only way it happens is if they sneak it in with like a totally new park,
like one ride out of like a new park with like six rides.
And it's probably not in America.
Yeah.
But even then, even like Tokyo Disney Sea, which is not super IP centric, they did just,
there is this big new expansion coming, but it's fully IP.
It's all IP.
Basically.
Yeah.
So you're not getting a new, which IP Island sounds like a wonderful place to be.
It's really not where all our favorite IP is all together.
I mean, there is like, they could do, you know, there's enough in Guardians of the Galaxy,
there's enough in like Cosmic Marvel or like the magic stuff in Marvel where there could
just be like a million things going around you.
You're saying there could be an IP ride that was at least good.
Oh, well, not per se good, but I'm saying something a little more like a theory in
spacey where like the Guardians of the Galaxy are not yelling at you to complete a task.
It feels like every Marvel attraction so far has been here are many instructions and here is
lots of backstory.
You are being yelled at with specifics as many as you can possibly take.
I would love what you're describing.
Sounds fantastic.
I would love to imagine that and hope they would do that.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
Something we talked about last month.
Have you done Avatar the boat ride?
Not yet.
No, I haven't been to Orlando in like 20 something years.
Oh, that's going to be a huge one.
Yeah.
If you do it with family.
I know I have two kids, they're four and two.
And like I was going to go after I finished working on Palti Goldman.
I was like, I want to go take the family there for a week.
But also I take them to Universal like a few times a year and the older one is just in a
mode right now of being scared of everything.
And the younger one doesn't know what's happening.
The other one is like mostly open to stuff.
We did the studio tour and the younger one, the two year old.
But to that it's just like either so boring.
It's just like buildings from movies that they never heard of.
Or it's like King Kong fighting dinosaurs is like way too scary.
But like my older one is afraid of the like one minute thunderstorm in the tiki room.
So it doesn't want to go into that.
So it's just like, oh, and he used to be obsessed with pirates.
And then he hit a certain age where he doesn't like the drops basically.
And so it's like, yeah, I think I gotta wait till they're old.
So I don't want to go to because I really want to take him to whatever's left of Epcot.
And see the stuff down there.
But it's like, oh, that won't be fun if like he's upset or not wanting to do anything.
You might need to do the adult trip.
Maybe I just need to go by myself.
I definitely will be going there solo sooner than I'll be going with my son.
For all the reasons you're describing.
He spent a lot of time in theme parks.
He will again soon.
To go across the country, you need a guarantee that's going to be great.
And work and not like a horror show for them at every turn.
Yeah, I mean, they barely got through the secret life of pets because of the
there's some just this vibe of being in a scary city.
Yes.
Yeah, I did that with my son.
And he like, well, it was the first of him reckoning with a bar lowering onto you.
And imagine you're two years old and that happens.
And also like they, you know, like it has to click to the that's as far as it can go on a
little two year old.
Yeah, that's as far as it can go beyond just nobody being in there.
So it's like Presta, but like he thinks he's being like what I thought on every ride when
I was still like eight was that he's being fed into a machine.
It's like an incinerator that's going to burn him up.
So lock him in tight, like watching him after reckon with a bar lower.
Oh my God, it was so awful.
And then know what?
I'm sure you've had this of like, all right, it's this ride has started bad and now we
have to get through this for depending on that slow ride stops like, oh God, six straight
minutes of hell.
All right, I'm going to wait till my daughter's like 10 to do my stuff.
Well, it's either although although you agree that like maybe you do you do everything
between one and two and then maybe it's not true.
One and two.
Yeah, actually, they don't know what they don't know what's going on.
They're not scared.
We went all around Tokyo DisneySea when he was six months old and there was no problem.
Six months.
That's crazy.
Okay, and now and since you've been there and not a lot of guests have been there,
comparing the two if you like in terms of like are either of them in greatest theme park
in the world conversation or one more than the other?
Did you like one more than the other?
Tokyo DisneySea is like such a more unified environment where, you know, it really feels
like you're on another planet and it just feels so perfectly done except that Italy
part that just does feel like the Americana or something.
That's true.
We can all go to fake Italy's and everyone.
We have so many fake Italy's.
That's true.
Adopted to have any magic to it.
You grew up in New Jersey too.
Plenty Italy there.
But yeah, that's like a crazier achievement, I think, because it's like this giant intentional
thing.
This is like, though I hadn't thought of it until I was looking stuff up for it for this,
but it's like it really is because it grew so organically.
It wasn't like a plan.
It wasn't even meant to be a theme park.
It was like the sports center basically that started a garden and then we'll do these little
fairy tale exhibits.
Yeah, that it was never like, let's build a theme park, but it became this.
Yeah, but it does have this crazy quality where it almost a lot of it feels like you're
just kind of wandering through a forest and then happening upon these like insane, very
expensive.
It's not janky at all.
They really like the animatronics are good.
The music is good.
Like it's legit.
Like they spend tens of millions of dollars on these rides.
A full orchestra doing the score for things.
And wait, that's a question also.
Like, do you really wander?
Are there like big stretches of this?
Just this just feels like a garden or nature or I just remember that like especially in
the part near that like fairy tale forest, you can wander around there for a long time
and just find stuff.
And then the rest of it, I think, is like paved, but also like a pretty themed, pretty,
pretty well done.
But there isn't any kind of like Main Street or hub or anything that's intentionally designed
to like bring you into the experience.
You just kind of are there and you're just kind of like finding stuff.
There's also this one ride with I think it's a roller coaster inside with this giant like
bird outside.
You see a picture of that this giant rock.
Bird Rock.
Bird Rock Park.
I think it's also about how Arabian Nights are difficult to endure.
You'll find a lot of peril.
More peril.
It's a Sinbad coaster, I believe.
Okay, yeah.
That seems like a common thing there.
Sinbad or Sinbad?
I'm not sure.
It's a good question.
I'm going to say Sinbad just in case.
Sinbad, I think is, yeah.
Then there's one from just that open, I think, right after we were there, year or two after
we were there.
That's a trackless one that has three paths.
Did you guys read about that?
Symbolica.
Yes, it looks incredible.
So this is like they worked their little mascot guy into this ride and he's a little jester.
Is he Jokey?
Jokey.
I think so, yeah, Jokey.
No, no, no, wait, no.
Pardos.
That was the old one.
Wait, Jokey is different than Pardos?
I think so.
Everything I saw said that the Jester's name is Pardos.
I didn't see Jokey.
That's Pardos.
I don't want to be missing a space Jester.
But who is Jokey?
I saw Jokey too.
Is he a different ride?
He might be the old mascot.
One of them, okay, one of them is in the Small World knockoff.
Pardos, I think, is the new one.
That's right, Scott.
Okay, but Jokey.
Jokey's in the carnival.
Oh, I've seen Jokey.
He has neat, simple, like the big circular faces.
He lives in a hot air balloon and he likes to eat pizza in the shape of a heart.
Is that right?
That's what it says on the website.
Pardos is a magician and Jester who was born on the planet Symbolica, which sounds adjacent to a mystica.
I was going to say he sounds like Chris Angel, so.
This ride is really wild in terms of the Trackless Dark Ride.
I mean, there's a bunch of scenes that you all do together and then you like pick your path.
And those paths each have two exclusive scenes on each path.
And you have an interactive console on the front of the ride vehicle so you can like play in Oregon.
Wow.
Or make like different shapes appear.
Yeah.
Some kind of spell in front of you.
This is, I mean, I'm sure as with all of these things, I would rather see them in person
than watch videos, but there's some of these, you're like the video,
maybe the video is not conveying the whole thing, but the video is conveying a lot.
Like this you can tell very clearly from this video.
This is one of the best rides built anywhere.
Did you see it?
There's a scene where you're in like an aquarium and there's this giant,
I think it was real.
I don't think it was video.
Whale that comes down is floating and blinking.
Yeah, the whale is insane.
It's incredible looking.
And then the glass starts to crack similar to the Jurassic World thing here, I think,
where it starts to crack, but then real water starts coming in.
Wow.
It's cool.
Look cool.
But let me ask you this.
Does it have three giant fans blowing trash at you?
Or is that in a Mystica exclusive?
What's the correct?
Maybe a Mystica, he said it's closing to tour Europe.
That was their ridiculous excuse lie for why it was closing.
That's not happening.
But that will run in Europe for like Starlight Express.
It'll just never close.
There'll be no way they can get those giant fans over to Europe.
They're like as big as a room.
Maybe through magic we can.
Their trash regulations are also much more strict there.
At Efteling, the creatures suck the paper away from you.
At a Mystica, the paper's blasted at you.
This is a very specific Yekhov smirnoff.
Yeah, I know that.
I'm like, yeah, I'm sure you're a...
No, this thing, I mean, what I wrote down about Symbolica is this is like a new
journey into imagination.
This is like a deeply sincere
cinematic like stirring with original characters and not just Pardos, the Jester from space,
but also King Pardulfus.
It's all about going to visit King Pardulfus, but before you can get to him,
you have to get to his taskmaster guard, OJ Punctual.
Of course.
Is this also a European thing that they're still willing to name characters OJ?
Yeah, what year did this open?
2017.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, why not?
The name's out there.
It's catch...
I like OJ Punctual.
OJ Punctual.
I like OJ.
You like OJ?
He's funny.
He's like an influencer now.
I do his Twitter videos.
I mean, I turn him when I want to know what to think about the slap.
Yeah, he's always shaking his head and stuff.
Yeah.
Foolishness.
No, this thing's...
Oh, wait, and here's...
I forgot another one.
Jason, you're asking about who made these rides.
ETF Ride Systems built this one.
I think they've made a lot of the more innovative trackless rides,
but also a little ride called Knights and White Sets.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I thought that was Sally Corp.
They did.
I mean, I think they did the effects and the decor, but the...
The track you're talking about.
A lot of people are trying to take credit for that ride.
Yes.
Everyone's racing to.
Everybody is.
There's liars.
I wish I could have gone on that ride.
That's an ethereal ride without a straight A to C narrative, like A to B narrative.
It's more of an experience.
Yeah.
You're not saying...
We haven't been saying the full name either.
Knights and White Sets.
The trip.
I know.
Not the ride.
Yeah.
Because at the height of lockdown, I was just buying things on eBay.
One of the things I bought was the psychedelic coffee bug for Knights and White Sets and the trip.
It's an inconvenient shape.
It's got a lot of squirrels on it.
What do you mean inconvenient shape?
It's just odd.
It's trippy.
It's a trippy design.
It's square on the top, then it goes to a circular bottom, and it's heavy.
Have you posted a photo of this?
I think I did.
See that mug.
Let's look at the mug.
We've been calling shots a lot.
That's been the catchphrase of the year.
What I'd really like to do, Jason, I'd love for you to be there.
Well, I've been dreaming for years of Hard Rock Park 3 with John Binkowski and you as well.
I don't know how to...
He's got to have listened to that episode, right?
I don't know.
That's a question.
If he's aware of it, I guess if you're...
There's not that much media about...
I feel like we were very respectful to him.
We kind of were doing it assuming he would listen to it.
Some people are close enough to...
What's he up to these days?
Does anyone know?
Would you...
He works...
He has a themed entertainment company, Unor Orlando.
What do they do?
They helped on that porn identity.
Oh, really?
She stole his business.
Wow.
Yeah.
Which we need to see.
Everybody is very happy of it.
Where is that?
That's at Universal Florida.
Oh, damn.
You replaced T2, T3.
You really got to go.
Solo.
No bachelor.
I might have to do it.
I haven't...
Yeah.
That's 20 years.
That's a whole lot of stuff.
A whole lot of construction walls.
Closed, yeah.
You got to see everything that's closed.
You missed a lot of stuff.
All the Epcot projects that have been canceled.
I can't go to Florida right now.
I got Royce Rocco on my tail.
Oh, wow.
I got to lay low.
Oh, he'll send his boys after you.
Are you sure he wouldn't just take you around?
Orlando?
That's a ride.
Yeah.
Going on Royce Rocco's Daytona.
Be careful.
Might be a bomb aboard.
You talk about people listening to things who are only like a stone's throw away.
We were...
And we'll talk a little more at the end about your show.
But for anybody who's watched Paul to go...
You said at the beginning you think it's very possible that Paul is listening to this.
I just know that.
Yeah.
I think Paul's listening to a lot of interviews I'm doing.
You know, yeah.
I think he's getting a lot of ads him and checking stuff out and seeing the response to the show.
So yeah, he may listen to this.
And also he was saying to me the other day that his first wife who's in the show,
Galina was pitching him ideas on like new things to do.
And one of them that he was excited about was could you do a Paul T. Goldman theme park?
And I said, well, actually I'm going on a theme park podcast that some good friends of mine do.
But then we started talking about something else before I got any of the
details of what that would be.
Pass them along, please.
Send screenshots of the text messages.
I can see if he wants to record something and send it to you.
You can get an exclusive...
Oh my God, a Paul T. Goldman appearance with him?
You know what?
Let me see.
I'll text him.
Geez.
You should send it first to John Binkowski and see if he's interested in starting and funding it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Let's tie it all together.
Yeah, he could do like the...
He could be the Walliner of that project.
That's right.
Yeah.
Are you saying Walliner doesn't want to be the Walliner of another...
No, he just wants someone from that world.
I knew how to make a TV show.
You need some...
If you're going to do a theme park where you do whatever rides he wants to do, then you need someone.
Yeah.
And that's...
Well, if Paul is listening also, we are describing one of the only people out there who has built an
entire theme park from scratch.
This is who you need to work with.
And now it's just a matter of pitches.
I mean, his whole life is a roller coaster.
So, I mean, is it...
That's what Binkowski should do next is an autobiography in the form of a theme park.
Oh, right.
Is his life story?
Yeah.
So it involves...
So there's a ride that is Hard Rock Park the Ride.
Yes, that would be...
The ride would be his experience of the rise and fall of Hard Rock Park,
but that would be the ride.
Jeez.
And that's only one part of it.
Like the rise up through...
Yeah.
Like you see all the ideas forming and the brainstorming and the possibilities.
You make a shady deal with a Native American tribe to license the Hard Rock brand.
That's right, yes.
And then you go off the cliff and you just go...
And then agreement deals with the Eagles flapping by you.
Flapping.
Yeah, licensing deals.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
The bare metal family waving to you from heaven.
And you go underwater, you go...
You can make the ratio correct.
Like the lift hill is as long as the prep period.
And then the drop is as fast as four months.
And then when it's over, you just stay there.
Like the park is still there.
You just stay there forever.
We need to get his thoughts on like...
Because I don't know if you guys have been following this,
but Hard Rock is taking over the Mirage Casino Hotel.
Oh my...
Oh yeah, that's pretty handy.
Are they gonna rebrand that, a Hard Rock?
They're gonna rebrand it.
It is gonna close for a while.
Did they close the Hard Rock in Vegas?
Is that gone?
That's the Virgin Hotel in Casino now.
So Mirage is becoming a Hard Rock.
Mirage is becoming a Hard Rock.
Are they gonna get rid of their big freedom royals enchanted garden?
That is slowly being retired.
I think they're rehoming all the animals and stuff.
My brief Googling says volcanoes, fine.
For now, for like the next year.
And then they're gonna close everything
because they are gonna build a guitar-shaped hotel tower.
It's gonna be like the one they're building in...
Is it Florida or are they building it somewhere else on the East Coast?
There's a big guitar hotel being built.
I think they have one.
This looks so stupid.
Look at a picture of this.
Yeah, yeah, that's what...
This guitar tower.
They built one of those already.
Cool.
That looks so cool.
Somebody's going in for a free room.
It's just so...
The whole idea of Hard Rock is...
Is really relevant.
Is really relevant, yeah.
God, Jesus.
Wait, I was judging off of the headline.
It says it'll live on into 2023.
But then the quote is,
we will not be continuing to operate the volcano once we commence construction.
Well, what does it have to do with rock?
It's like the Stephen Tyler...
Flames bursting.
That would be at a Hard Rock concert.
Would it not?
Jimmy Buffett has a song called Volcano,
but it's not his idea.
Jimmy Buffett sent Hard Rock.
And he's already got a place across the street.
So what the fuck are you talking about?
Yeah, you don't want to double up on that.
A volcano is a big part of Dianetics,
and there's a lot of rock star Scientologists out there.
Yeah, Chick Korea.
It all ties together.
That's for the Chick Korea wing.
There's online...
Hulk Hogan has been seen with a couple of people from Scientology recently.
Yes, that's good.
He needs it.
These worlds have been waiting to meet forever.
What did we miss?
Oh, I know something.
Mike, to quote you a little while ago,
you said you did not want to see any characters from Efteling in a film.
However, there is a TV show called The Magical World of Pardos.
And I thought it was animated because it's a character you mostly see animated.
No, this was like a cheapo.
Although, effects, I don't even want to say cheapo.
It doesn't look like a movie.
It doesn't look like Harry Potter.
But a decent-sized syndicated sci-fi type show,
The Magical World of Pardos.
Better than Bible Man Budget.
Definitely better than Bible Man Budget.
Although, I put on a minute of it last night, and Aaron said,
oh, this looks like Space Cases.
Oh, yeah.
Remember Space Cases?
I do, yeah.
I had Latter-day Snick Show.
Oh, yeah.
So if you want something with Space Cases quality.
That vibe.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm impressed by that, that Efteling made a show.
Yeah.
They're making people fall in love with Pardos and OJ Punctual.
There's a TV broadcast that actually kind of tied in with,
it was right around the time of when they were opening Spookslot on a castle attraction,
which was Kate Bush did a performance,
an Efteling TV special, like exclusive performance.
Because her song, Wuthering Heights, was very big in Europe.
Yeah.
I watched this whole special.
It's so great.
It might have broken the dam for me on liking Kate Bush.
I'm like, I mean, I've liked everything I've heard,
but I've never gone deep.
But I liked every song in this thing so much.
Oh, yeah.
This song, I think, is called Them Heavy People.
It's all from her first album, which I've now listened to and really like.
I'm like, oh, this might be what I need.
But her doing Wuthering Heights in Spookslot, and then,
and then, Them Heavy People, she does arm and arm with these three troll creatures,
with animatronics, and she's swaying back and forth with them.
It's so charming.
It's such a great performance piece for-
It's better than Meghan Trainor in front of the Disney World Castle.
Like a holiday special is what you're saying?
To me, but it's in the eye of the whole-
There's a quantity with Meghan Trainor because she's been part of those specials every year.
Every year, it seems like.
For the last 12 years, I think.
Can I bring up something real quick that's completely unrelated, but I have to mention it?
Okay, Jason is wearing, I think, socks that are Spider-Man socks.
These are Spider-Man socks, but they're wool, so it's pretty warm.
To me, it looks like you're wearing a full Spider-Man outfit under your clothes.
I cannot keep- I can't get the thought out of my head, so I had to say it.
It looks like Jason is Spider-Man on the side,
and I couldn't help but bring it up because it's been driving me nuts for like-
This is actually a classic Dutch pastime.
It's called Spider-Man-ing.
You wear a regular outfit, but you have a full Spider-Man outfit underneath.
I would not be shocked if you were just wearing long Spider-Man underwear under that.
I know it's not what's happening.
Actually, you know what? Prove it to me that those are socks.
These are very snug socks with very snug joggers on.
They go pretty high.
They go- Oh, he's got a full- I can't see it!
I think he's wearing it.
No, that didn't prove it!
That didn't prove it!
That didn't ruin it.
That was so high, and he's not going to show me.
You're pointing at him like the Spider-Man's in the meme.
You're a friendly neighborhood Spider-Man, you know?
Mason is wearing a full Spider-Man outfit under these seats right now.
As soon as he leaves, he's going to pull that mask up and either go stop some crime or commit a crime.
That's how he's getting the CVS candy for free!
That's it!
We solved it!
He's faking coupons.
Yeah!
I run in, I send someone in to get it, and then when they run out, I don't stop them.
Oh, just like Uncle Ben.
Yeah, just like Uncle Ben.
Wow, that's a scheme.
And then I forget the lesson and eat the candy he got me.
What have we not gotten to?
Oh, did you- you stayed there, did you do the hotel?
We stayed around a lake.
There's a hotel in there and there's a bunch of, quote, holiday villages?
So the holiday village- I was looking at that today.
That's called Village Boss Ridgek, which really looked like a family-friendly Midsommar kind of situation.
It really had those buildings and that vibe.
We stayed, like, stay overnight.
Yeah, I don't know what it was called, but it was like a little-
there were just little buildings around a lake and it's- yeah, I mean, it's really cool and you can
just walk around and there's an island with a little castle and this- yeah, I got pictures of
that and then you see that and it's on the way.
Oh yeah, that's great.
I'll send us any pictures also.
The main hotel is these crazy themed rooms.
Yeah, we were in a themed room.
Cinderella suite that's got a little- some boiling stew somewhere.
We weren't in an elaborate one.
We just had like- it was like a little old-timey and it- but it had a painting of this
owl on the wall that was very cool.
Whoa, that's good.
That's really intense.
The Owl Who Hunts Sinners, another classic children's tale.
Well, you talk themed suites.
You know what the Efteling Hotel has is the Pardo Suite.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Yes, it sparkles with magic.
Read a story together from one of the books in Pardo's bookcase or watch the story of
Pardo's in Symbolica on TV.
Watch Pardo make love to your wife.
Hear his jingle jingle as he goes down on earth.
Welcome to Europe.
Wait, I have a little bit of- one that I missed, I think of a kind of watershed ride for this place
is the Python and it's kind of a- it's controversial in Efteling history.
It's just- it's a steel looping coaster.
It seems like just a good steel coaster that is not fairy tale and forest and mythology
and it was really the first ride that broke from that and so there were people who didn't
like it and I think it broke all kinds of noise ordinances so the ride was protested
and I read this- I'm not really sure how they got over it.
I think maybe they just did it.
Just stopped listening to the townsfolk.
But anyway, it's just notable for being a very solid roller coaster.
Really got people in the door.
Took them into the 70s but there's a lot of silly stuff how they promoted this ride and
some of this by the way comes from Expedition Theme Park.
They made a bunch of great videos about it so to credit them.
But that's where I learned about a couple of weird things.
One is that for a commercial I think they attached a Porsche to the coaster
and there's a video you can watch of them installing it and then this won't be
interesting sound-wise.
This is just for you guys to see.
There's a full Porsche on the front as the front car of a roller coaster.
All right.
Okay.
Why do that?
I don't know.
I don't know what it conveyed or was it for a Porsche commercial?
I'm not sure but the ride vehicle is red and so is the Porsche.
It's really silly looking.
I guess it's nice to give a car the chance to ride a roller coaster.
It was going to die.
Our confusion they would call a lack of understanding on America's part.
You know they just go for it.
They commit to the bit at Eftel.
Like they don't ask the question.
They committed to an aesthetic and not using cheap materials.
Imagine what Epcot would look like if the day one thesis of Epcot and execution of opening
Epcot just never tapered off.
Never stopped.
Another thing that is said by Expression Theme, there were a bunch of musical acts
that performed at the opening including local favorites the Dolly Dots.
Let me just play a bit of the Dolly Dots.
I think I found my new favorite band.
They're like ABBA but just the girls and then two more sets of girls.
They're not even quite at like Spice Girls level of dancing.
They're not professional but they're on roller skates for this one performance.
This is I'm just gonna play a little of the song Money Lover which is a screed against
money lovers and I really like this song.
All of the Dolly Dots are yelling at a rich man in an open top car.
You're sure this is not an anti-semitic track?
He's not sure.
Well it's sung in English but with a thick accent which might be masking some very offensive lyrics.
Let's hear what the lyrics of Money Lover are.
Well I love the lyrics which if you don't understand it when I play it.
These lyrics are bite the dust hot shot.
There's a roulette.
And then it comes to roulette.
Well you see this awful rich guy in his showy car and then you see him doing some evil gambling
by the end after they all dance and yell at him by the end he's a pennyless.
He walks in like impoverished him and he's drinking in an alley.
So the Dolly Dots ruin this man.
They destroyed him.
But I really like the go-gos or something.
It's a little bit yeah they start a little more ABBA seemingly and then they kind of turn
that way.
I really like bite the dust hot shot that feels like a cousin of what's the Mickey phrase?
Soak your head fresh boy.
Yeah yeah yeah feels like a cousin of that.
And then there's one more thing and I think this was kind of the like the Python must
have been the splash mountain of Efteling where they're trying all kinds of crazy stuff
to promote it.
Actually Efteling has many splash mountains as we've learned.
But in terms of promotional efforts and this I have to play a second of that one promotional
thing that they did is they did an elaborate escape sequence from the roller coaster like
a car was coming at a magician who was tied to the tracks and the way before Lance Burton
did it outside of Vegas way before that it was first done by a Belgian magician I think
named Joe Alcatraz.
And I'm just gonna this is just gonna be the sounds of Joe Alcatraz
moaning and writhing as he tries to escape the roller coaster.
And then at the last second when you think all hope is lost Joe Alcatraz is saved by a camera cut.
It just suddenly like this is the most cop outy thing.
I mean granted if you're if you watch it the coaster does come at him but like why do the cut?
I don't know I'm not sure.
Wait where was the cut?
Like you were looking at one there's one angle for most of his riding.
Oh and then it yeah it's I mean that's yeah.
But I guess it is well look he's on the track and then and he's still screaming
and then the car comes it's better than the Lance Burton one.
I was gonna say is this what Lance Burton got the idea?
Yeah yeah Joe Alcatraz got to it first and I would like to learn everything I can about Joe Alcatraz.
He's got a pretty like nifty van with his name on it.
Wow.
Really like the name.
So these python promotional efforts love it.
You know that's all like if you can't go to a park what you at least want are a lot of
bizarre YouTube videos stemming from the park and there's no shortage.
There's some I should have actually taken a clip of this there's some great we were just talking
also on the uh people mover episode about that 70s horn vibe that's missing from Disneyland.
Like that Herb Albert.
We didn't say porn oh wait oh you said horn.
Horn.
Okay oh sorry I thought I mean you because you could describe that music as being.
Like Herb Albert the famous pornographer.
Well there's that very sexy woman on the cover of one of his albums.
And the whipped cream.
Yes indeed.
Very body dance happened to Mr. Albert's music.
The body brass of Herb Albert I believe is the name of the record.
Well there you go.
So yeah but there's a lot of commercials that have that vibe too for Efteling.
Oh sure yeah yeah.
Huh like a little swinging retro.
You know that that thing.
Yeah yeah.
Good commercials good materials I don't know what have what have we not
gotten to we've been very productive for being.
I think we covered the main one.
I mean there's other they have um they have a madhouse style ride where it's like you're
sitting in a room and it seems like the whole place goes upside down.
It's fun.
These are kind of there there used to be one at Six Flags Great Adventure I remember doing.
Uh that was like Houdini based uh that's just neat.
Oh yeah I did that yeah.
It stuck around for a while and um so they have that at one point in time they had a
bobsled roller coaster that's like imagine a giant bobsled track but with like roller
coaster cars and then yeah you're not on a tread they just release the they just release the car
and then that that was replaced by another upgrade by like dueling power coasters which
I I'd always seen this phrase I I never really processed it but a power coaster is a roller
coaster that is powered the whole time it's not like dropped from a hill to like oh I see
none of it is gravity you're saying yeah so it can it can do like unique starts like uh uh
so I I again just committing to like oh we're going to do something interesting if we're
removing something we're replacing it with something worthwhile and there's a museum too
within the park there's a small museum where you can see like old artifacts or like a track from
you know old rides and wow yeah the museum's great I went there it's great it's worth going
Efteling's great it's a great place it sounds yeah you got you cleaned up their act they did the
right thing they were kicking and screaming into the present day and now we're good uh I did I did
look up like how to get here to see if it's like because I always heard like oh you get on a bus
in the middle of Amsterdam and it doesn't run that often yeah uh yeah it was very uh inconvenient
yeah I I so I I looked it up and it it does mention like there are many public transportation
ways to get here but then there's driving directions from different points and the first
thing I saw was just the phrase maintaining the direction of door direct slash breetta and I was
like oh man this is this is a little intimidating they're already using the phrase I've I understand
but I've never seen before maintain the direction is this door direct a monster or something
it seems like a thing but it was the website is fun to per use because like there's just little
phrases here and there where it's like not quite a direct translation yeah yeah yeah yeah it's not
terrible english but it's a little like uh it just reads a little crazy yeah in there like the go
like the um Jason what was this specific one of the in the fairy tale forest there's like 30
different scenes and stories represented and the one is you peek into the cottage with like
oh it's incredible there's a wolf dressed goats sitting around the table yeah it's these dressed
goats there's a wolf at the door um he has a full suit suit and tie yeah he is a suit and tie and
then there's these um he's you know moving they're all moving and then yeah they're sitting on the
table and it just looks like just this crazy like movie I mean it looks like um Lars von Trier's
christ where the animals come in at the end um where it's just like they're just having this
weird meal or another playing a game and but it's haunting it's like really disturbing yeah yeah
this is wonderful yeah yeah it's really yeah it's awful yeah as long as they're like goats uh
willingly as long as they're well I guess you're what I'm saying is I don't like I am so disturbed
by the donkeys having become donkeys oh and Pinocchio the hands of magic so as long as
they're okay with being goats that helps me here's another thing I love and I can give you this clip
is these these boats um there's a boat ride on a lake but they just go on a track and they just
run them when they're empty so it's just like so scary there's just like this line of empty boats
with no one driving them they just like float through all day and night this ride had no
survivors they were like they're coming back from hell well they were all taken they were all okay
the uh resurrection happened oh yeah that's better yeah left behind happened um uh yeah there's some
mid-sommar stuff uh I don't know that that's the right country to be referencing but you know what
I'm saying just like weird euro like yeah just euro euro weirdness yeah yeah it seems like the
thing about it and that it's like it's still allowed to be weird there isn't some cedar fair
type company it's like yeah I mean you might get more people if you take away the weirdness
sure it's um yeah it's weird and rough around the edges and I'd really like to go just Seth Meyers
was interviewing Jordan Peele they were talking about going when they were in Boom Chicago this
is like a week ago oh I saw that yeah they went yeah during Boom Chicago's uh uh Amsterdam oh
yeah it's where a lot of theater a lot of people do go there for like a year and do improv we never
you didn't audition for that I didn't audition for that because the way everyone described it in the
way it's been talked about it's like we go um to Amsterdam and you do improv for a year and the
audiences do not like you but it's cool that just hang out in Amsterdam for a year you don't get
paid very much and the audiences are not wild about a lot of the shows but it's a great tourist
so I went there when I was 18 I think I went to a Boom Chicago show in Amsterdam yeah you hated it
I like I was 18 I liked it I think Will Forte was a um did a dissent there actually well their
alumni role is it's insane yeah of people who did that yeah well the problem is the locals were all
in the audience like who are these performers none of them are goat faces
um uh Jason anything else about uh you want to throw in for me that covers all my Efteling
memories yeah no it's just a good it's a good place go geez yeah great uh I'm very excited to
we will uh I'm so glad you could you could take us through it mentally Jason Wallander you survived
podcast the ride uh so so happy you could do this and let's thank you I will get this something
you do not typically choose to do which is exit through the gift shop you don't have to hear
either however uh Paul T Goldman is so amazing we've all watched it yeah we all love it very much
and uh and the listeners should uh should check it out thanks afterling of shows
uh no I have a new I have a new show newish came out a few weeks ago uh it's on the streaming
service peacock it's called Paul T Goldman um look for the thumbnail check it out keep your eyes
opening click it watch it it's six parts um and it's it's the one with the guy it's the one with
the guy who doesn't look like the typical stars of shows it doesn't but that was from a photo
shoe where like it wasn't a great we didn't get a great photo that really captures him he kind of
looks unspectacular uninteresting in that photo he's a pretty interesting guy um and the show is
about his story that he tells about marrying uh a woman who turned out had a secret double life
and his attempts to take down uh her international crime ring which may or may not exist and uh and
that's kind of the simplest way of uh talking about the show and it's much more complicated than
that as you guys know oh yeah some great actors some great actors show up in it great actors uh
yeah like paul t gold paul t goldman melinda mcgraw earl brown just great actors you've seen
in all sorts of things but but acting with this real guy who uh wrote this script and lived his
life and then there's a bunch of other kind of documentary elements to it it's a very hard show
to describe but it's an easy show to watch that is absolutely i know like like it sounds like it's
it might sound like math when you hear it but it's all these formats blending but it is so exciting
and it goes down so smooth and it keeps like the there's such variety to it because it's
cycling through the formats but it's all weaving one story so wonderfully together i hope thank you
thank you uh we had really great editors and uh yeah i worked on it for about 10 years and it's
out and uh that's my plug it's a it's a really good one and i i don't want to say i don't want
to that implies that other people's plugs have not but but look uh it's top notch it's so i i
demand that the audience uh check out paul t goldman on on pico i would say this this crowd the
listener base of podcast the ride definitely a type of person who's after experiences i would
say this is more of an experience than other tv shows by the time you get to the end uh you've
gone through something like every possible permutation of of like what it's like in this
guy's mind inside and out of it and and things are turned on him in a way you don't expect and
yeah there isn't an easy uh path through this but i i hope it's uh enjoyable in some way if you sign
up sign up for peacock today you can watch all of uh paul t goldman you can watch the real rumble
tomorrow and you can cancel after the free trial you know cancel on sunday you know he's not
jason i'm supposed to be saying that cancel after the free trial so that's just jason jarridan
jason walliner had no involvement with that warner brothers discovery god okay i was laszloff
everything else is canceled as soon as i says love stan
hey we gotta cut the fat okay you know we've all heard my many rants about the national
deficit reality show on hbl max that's just as love deciding what stuff to cancel oh yeah
hbo max and like each episode he like he's like weighing different things and like people are
pleading for their shows to stay on begging and yeah it's just got that like tic toc reality
competition music he's like he's like sitting on a throne he's like it's called like the show is
called please mr zazlal and then and then what he cancels at the end of that episode
disappears from ratio backs the next day and you're watching you're watching please mr zazlal you
go quickly watch whatever he canceled no because you don't know until the end as soon as it ends
it's gone and then but the season finale is one of the shows on the chopping block is please mr
zazlal and he has to decide whether or not he commits a show suicide so you never see the end
of the last episode because it just disappears before you can watch it yeah if he chew if that's
the one that goes it just goes back to the menu no credits nothing and it's and there's no evidence
that the show ever existed wow wow wow that's good i should pitch that to hbl max yeah we'll cut this
we'll cut it and you'll have a great sense of humor about the current status all the people i knew
there uh have been like oh so i don't uh yeah yeah i'm burning i'm burning no bridges
that's a ghost town show made by anyone i like there is not the wait eagleheart's still up i
don't know how i mean it's because they don't maybe they're if they're pulling things off hbl
max based on not wanting to pay residuals eagleheart they still send me bills they're like this is how
much you owe us seriously because i got like i got like some uh you know profit statement or whatever
and it was at the last line was in the red i always still owe them money what do you want
i don't know how could that find out of your pocket i don't know i don't know
so somehow eagleheart is still on the adult swim nook of uh of hbl max check it out right next to
the rick and morty thumbnail definitely that's that's gonna stay up for a while if you don't
feel like clicking on that particular thumbnail for whatever reason click a few notches away
there's a lot of good thumbnails non rick and morty um that are available to click and nobody
in your show nobody's had to have been uh recast you don't have to go redub anybody in eagleheart
not yet not yet shockingly but anybody's he's got ample opportunity to need to be redubbed
this is how much i uh this is how strongly i feel about the paul t goldman plug i will forgo our
plugs whoa we will not do it because that confuses the issue you have what uh jason is grimacing jason
so upset with you now for not shooting our patreon he's gonna go into spidey mode oh he's taking the
suit off we better wrap it up quickly watch paul t goldman he's gonna shoot the web scott's mouth
assignments goodbye forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced by
mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more
original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on
apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news
by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook