Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcasts that Ride the Second Gate.
I'm Jason Sheridan joined as always Scott Gairdner.
Hi, here and ready.
Mike Carlson.
Hello, I'm here.
I almost said toot toot I'm here.
Toot toot I'm here.
Yeah, but no.
It's not a train.
It's not a train, that's why I didn't do it.
It's a futuristic iteration of a train.
I said don't do that, it's not a train.
And then I thought, then I analyzed what my instinct was
and it was incorrect.
It was wrong, it was bad.
I mean, I'm glad you were honest.
I think, hey, you know what?
I think it was cute.
I think it was very cute.
It was.
If I said it?
Yeah.
Or if I, okay.
Well, let's try to take it again.
Say it every time.
Jason, introduce me.
Oh, Mike Carlson, also here.
Toot toot, I'm here.
Toot toot is here, like he always says.
I think it's a catchphrase now.
Yeah.
Okay, toot toot I'm here.
Put it on a shirt.
I think I'm too embarrassed of that.
I'm embarrassed to be next to it.
So what's this podcast you're doing?
Oh, it's good, it's, you know, it's the same person.
Yeah, the guy is, Mike goes, does a catchphrase.
He always says toot toot.
Oh, is he the toot toot I'm here guy?
Yeah, no, it's him.
Oh, I hate that guy.
Oh yeah, awful.
Yeah, okay, yes.
You wanna talk to other people at this party?
Okay, that's fine.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Well, I understand.
Folks, we're here.
It's the second part of our discussion of the People Mover.
Honing in on the Florida,
and the Florida redo that Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
It was the People Mover there for a while.
For a while, the Wedway People Mover.
Yes, which had a great sign, by the way.
I also had this sign.
Yes, okay, okay, yeah, yeah.
Was it sponsored by something specific initially?
Yes, it was sponsored by the Edison Electric Institute.
But the sign specifically says,
presented by America's investor-owned electric companies.
That clunky sentence was in a theme park for people to see?
It is as long as the phrase Wedway People Mover.
It takes up so much of the sign.
It's also so generic.
Investor-owned?
So that implies it's not an electric company
operated by the government.
It is by investor-owned.
What the hell does that mean
to a five-year-old with cotton candy?
Nothing. Nothing.
Nothing, jargon.
Doesn't mean much to me now.
I feel like I have a 30-something of,
feels like he has cotton candy for brains.
Well, you're not alone there.
You're just getting fuzzier.
So this is the 70s.
It's not an opening day Magic Kingdom attraction.
It opened in 75,
but Tomorrowland was designed
with the intent of a people mover.
So there was, you could see a second story concourse.
Oh, okay.
You could see overhangs. They were ready for it.
Also, when they built Epcot,
there was plans for a people mover
that would go around Spatial Earth
and go through the second levels of Communicor.
That got scrapped.
That people mover never got built.
Huh.
What a minute, wow.
In a different park elsewhere in, wow,
Epcot people mover.
Yeah, that would have been,
it would have been cool if they had just like maintained,
because they was almost a version of the people mover
built in Galaxy's Edge.
Yes.
Which is going to be themed to what?
The Banthas?
Banthas, yeah.
So it would have been fun if that sort of
was just a trademark of Disney parks
where it would be sort of different types of vehicles
that would move you around.
That Bantha ride would be so popular.
You know the way that everybody feels like there's,
I like Galaxy's Edge.
No, I like it, but there's something a little,
I think it would be the thing.
I think everybody, we'd be seeing celebrities Instagramming
on the Banthas, families laughing.
It's like something for children, little children to do
that's not our answer to this.
And yeah, with the lack of like little shows and stuff
because the place is so big
and it feels a little empty sometimes,
depending on what time of the day.
You always got a big Bantha flying,
or not flying, but roaming around up above you.
Messed up, they messed up.
And I'm also, you know what?
We got Nintendo coming soon
and we're gonna talk a lot about it,
but Hollywood is not getting Japan's Yoshi ride.
And I've watched a ride through of the Yoshi ride
thinking I won't get there for a while.
What a cute, pleasant ride.
There's a little game,
you have to do an Easter egg hunt on it.
Oh, and I'm so frustrated having a two-year-old
and that there's not gonna be a little Yoshi ride
for him to do.
What a stupid, why did they cut this bad?
Yeah, I know.
That's a very small, though Japan land is small.
And the one here is smaller.
This is not a big physical footprint land in general.
I saw someone have a negative review of the Yoshi ride
in Japan, but they may not have a child.
I mean, I'll say that it was, I did,
that's more of what I'm thinking.
I did a watch through and even was like,
seems a little slow and nothing and rinky dink.
But then also I'm like, but imagine being on it.
I think if you were on it, you would have.
I think the big thing is getting to be on a Yoshi is awesome.
Getting to see a different color Yoshi, awesome.
Then getting to see the above the land view, awesome.
And then I think maybe the negative part was like,
it was inside they felt it was not as themed.
It was not as cool when you would go into the tunnels.
When you go into little tunnels, there's not, yeah.
It should have been better.
That's the review of it.
So I think you are missing out on that vantage point.
That's the big thing.
And the Yoshi's getting a kid going,
oh, I get to get pink Yoshi or whatever.
This vantage point thing came up
in the discovery zone episode recently.
Yes.
That was something that you said, Jason,
about you like being in the tubes
because you could see characters from a weird view
and games from, and let me plan the rest of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's funny that ties right into what we're talking about.
Now, something that this is true
of both versions of the people mover.
Why is it so satisfying to be up in a window of a store?
Like it's Star Traders in Disneyland.
I don't know what it goes through in Disney World exactly.
Star Traders.
It's Star Traders again, okay, great.
Like why it's so, and like waving to the people in the store
and like, oh, I wonder what they're buying.
What do they do?
Wow, I can see the cashiers.
I can see their computer.
And then you're in the store and like,
wow, there's people going by.
Wonder if they're enjoying the ride.
It just like creates this arbitrary division
between people.
It has the riders and the people watching the riders.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess it turns the shoppers into like animatronics
in a certain way.
Yeah.
You're watching that show.
Yeah, so without knowing it, your entertainment
while you're looking for what mug to buy.
Yeah, exactly.
It's just neat.
And the Florida version has so much of what was neat
about the original one too.
But do you wanna, Jason, do you wanna put up any like
arguments for what makes this one better or more?
I don't know that it is a competition, but.
Well, I'll say, you know,
the one I like is specifically
the Tomorrowland Transit Authority that runs,
the narration that runs from 1994
and then they took it out in 2009.
Okay.
And more specifically, I really like the one
with that Tomorrowland loop, which I found
by going year to year in footage.
Wow.
The music loop that I like seems like it kicks in around 2003.
Do you have a name?
Can you quantify or how did it,
how did the listeners find it?
Okay, you can find it on YouTube.
If you look up the term,
I, because it kind of plays throughout the land too.
It plays.
Does it have like a, like the,
like Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow as part of it?
Part of it, it has, if you had wings as part of it,
now is the best time of your life.
So it incorporates all of these songs
from Tomorrowland past and present.
That's cool.
If you look on YouTube,
it's called Tomorrowland area music loop.
It has 1.7 million views.
Wow.
So, and this was an early lockdown.
I mean, before, even before that,
I would put it on if I was working or stuff,
but especially during early lockdown,
I was going back and forth between Pandora,
like music and just repeating footage,
Pandora music, Avatar Pandora.
Yeah, they're not the stage, not the radio.
Yeah, that and this Tomorrowland music loop
just to keep myself sane.
Wow.
So, but I, when I was watching through
people mover footage, which according to my YouTube history,
I have watched 23 videos of various people mover
through the years.
Like in the last week or so?
In the last three days.
Oh my God.
This is including California and Florida
and the multiple narrators in Florida.
Cause Jack Wagner was the original narrator.
Then it was-
Who's fake Mickey, who's, wait, he's specifically the,
he's, I use the den and also the,
okay, you asked for it.
Yeah.
So it's weird that he's such a like,
swirly, nice sound, like the voice of Disneyland.
The voice of Disneyland, yeah.
And so that's how they first rolled out this people mover.
And then it was Orac One, the commuter computer
from 85 to 91 or 94.
Yes.
And then in 94, Peter Rennaday becomes the narrator
and kind of was doing like a Jack Wagner voice.
Yeah. It's that sort of, it's similar in tone to that,
your attention please, the Disneyland,
it's in that neck of the wood, kind of like trumpet it up.
Yes. But that, but the one thing I can't figure out,
cause the like now departing rocket tower Plaza
that I have as my phone ring for years.
I think I played this on the show.
This came up before once.
Yeah, this came up before.
We tried to activate it organically, but it didn't work.
And so I think it, I know how to get there.
Can I call you?
Yeah.
Why weren't we talking about,
what was the last Peter Rennaday conversation?
Cause this came up, I remember you bringing up.
He's just in so much here, this is the clip.
The Iranian transit authority,
the Trinidad and Manstap now departing
rapid tower Plaza station for a round trip
super Skyway tour.
So that, that is like my favorite thing.
Like when, since I was a kid, I loved that.
And then when I went back in like 2012,
I was like, who the fuck is this voice?
It is like a funky teen.
It is like a hip young person and I hate it.
Yeah.
And no vibe, there's no real anything to it.
There's no vibes.
They did keep the music loop.
So that was at least there.
And then I was very happy to see in the summer of 2022,
there was a, it is new again.
It's a little more of a hodgepodge.
It's kind of everything.
It's all the narration,
it's little pieces of all the narrations
and cute music cues and references to older attractions.
This is kind of when in talking about the,
the split and figuring out how do we divide these episodes.
I think some of the, this is a big difference.
Florida, I think has always had more personality
in the narrators.
I love the narrators in the Disneyland version,
but they're just sort of kind of like,
just generic talky people, which it was originally.
But then that you have this computer voice
and kind of a character with Orac one
is a very different thing about the persona of the,
and they've kept it up.
That you may, you maybe are getting characters on here,
which fleshes it out as a themed experience a little more.
You, to be just to clear it out,
you like all of them except for the teen.
I, I.
I know you have your preference, I'm saying,
but you, the only one you have disdain for is the teen.
I just didn't, yeah, I feel like they removed personality
and they also put in the version.
Like Poochie they put on, like Poochie's voice.
Yeah, essentially.
Well, they put in a lot more character,
like Mike Wazowski or Stitch or like Buzz Lightyear.
And it's a little.
None of them are the voices, clearly.
So it's not like you're really getting your friends.
Right, yeah.
And I also, I, if we ever talk to them,
I do want to ask Peter Reneday, is that you?
Because there's a narrator and there's an announcer
and I can't figure out if they're the same person.
This was a real leap that you have,
you want to get Peter Reneday on the show?
Are you calling your show?
Oh, I would not, no, I just mean if we're.
We ever have them on, it's very casual.
If we ever have them on, I, yeah, I'm sure we'd love to.
Peter, we gotta know.
Is this you, like, as I, I was trying to figure out,
it's so hard to find credits
for some of these attractions of like,
who was this voice, who was that voice?
But so he's, and we've done this list before, I'm sure,
but sir, that specific, your ringtone.
Lincoln's a big one.
I don't know when Lincoln, now I don't remember.
He's been Lincoln at certain times.
Right, which, in and out with that original,
it's either that original guy, Royal Dano,
or it's this guy.
And he's Lincoln, Peter Reneday is Lincoln recently in Seoul.
There's a brief Lincoln appearance
when there's the different mentors
who might, trying to sync up with 22, the lost soul.
So still doing like a go-to Lincoln in a lot of things.
And we might've talked about Reneday before also
because it's another, it's a different fake Mickey.
Reneday is Mickey at the beginning of Splash Dance,
the Splash Dance album that was fun to talk about
a while ago.
All the fake Mickeys are in play in this thing.
My favorite fake that he does is fake James Mason
in the 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea ride.
Right, right, okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a good one, that's a tricky one to do.
Fake Nemo, he's, James Mason plays Captain E,
it's not just James Mason, a little sloshed going like,
are we going to the Roosevelt?
On a talk show, no.
Yeah.
Peter Reneday has the credit, Bailiff in Cat from Outer Space
and the, an earlier voice that you mentioned, Orack One,
that was the voice that was done by an actor
named Ronnie Shell, who was the cat from outer space.
Wow.
Another property represented throughout
People Mover history.
Anyone wanna call that shot?
I don't know if I do, Cat from Outer Space episode.
I don't know anything about the cat from Outer Space.
That sounds like your shot you would call.
Reneday is Splinter as well.
Oh right, yes.
And Splinter in Coming Out of Our Shells
that before it switches to the Bryan Adams vocals.
For his song, Skippin' Stones.
Yeah, Skippin' Stones.
Sandin' in water.
Might be the worst sung song in history.
It's insane, I mean, maybe the singer,
the singer isn't trying to straddle the difference
between Bryan Adams and elderly rat.
Maybe he's a better singer, usually.
Skippin' Stones.
Yeah.
Passing Stones, kidney stones.
That's what it sounds like.
But so Peter Reneday, yeah, so he's the narration.
I feel like the 94 Tomorrowland, when that was redone,
that was a very aggressive push in the regular magazines,
we got Disney Adventures, Disney Magazine, The Glossy.
I got Disney Magazine, they really hyped up.
That got me so psyched to go to that new Tomorrowland.
I was so excited for all of it.
And I loved it.
And I still think it looks pretty good.
Like they've added some more mod stuff back in,
the entry, they changed the entryway.
They scaled back on some of the more retro future
Buck Rogers, kind of like Finns and all.
And I can't complain too much,
because they replaced it with a lot of blue lights
and neon blue, which I think always looks good and futurey.
They should just default to that, absolutely.
I will say, this, when they redid Tomorrowland in 94,
big aesthetic swing that was very bold
and could have not worked.
Could have not, yeah.
I thought it was so very, you know,
their attempts to answer the question,
how do we keep Tomorrowland just permanent
and not change it all the time, is doing this weird,
it's the future, but it's also the 1930s.
And it's a future that seems to involve a lot of big boxy
30s type robots who are very friendly.
And all of Tomorrowland becomes this actual,
I mean, not actual, but like a simulated community
that has public transit, which is what we're talking about,
and a convention center and a science center
and little like, you know, here's a newspaper stand
and there's characters.
And it sort of is a consistent little world
and through line that was very, in a very pre-Galaxy's Edge,
very well done and consistent in the original way.
Yeah, and I think, yeah, very civic minded,
which is kind of ironic when we're talking
about the people mover, because, you know, in the 70s,
they tried to sell the people mover to cities
and airports and balls as like a way of getting around,
as like a public transit option.
And there is a marketing brochure you can find online,
like a 10 page, like, this is what it looks like.
This is the Houston airport people mover.
And some of the language in it is like,
and you know, isn't this nice for society?
Isn't this nice for the civic population?
Like they are trying to pitch it as like, you know,
we tested it in theme parks and now it's working every day
in an airport, why not put it in your city?
Is the MCO Orlando airport,
is that a people mover or a monorail?
What is it technically?
If you use people mover to mean automated transit system,
I think it's closer to people mover.
I don't know if there's conductors
at the end of those trains.
I think that is, if the, if, well, yeah,
if is it like the way we've determined,
we're using the word people mover,
or is it the Disney definition of people mover,
which is no motor.
Right.
And the track is doing all the work.
And that I couldn't tell you.
I bet it's not then that.
Cause it's not, that seems like it has.
A skateboard is a people mover.
No, because the ground isn't.
But it's moving a person.
Yeah, oh yes, in one sense.
Yeah, in one sense.
I think we, maybe how do we do any definition.
People mover lower case is when it's just something
that's moving people.
But people mover upper case means Disney's definition
where the track is doing all the work.
Yes.
Oh, and we didn't, I don't think we said the phrase
linear induction motor somehow in the first episode we did.
Well, here's a big difference.
Yeah, the Florida one.
California is powered by, was powered by Goodyear tires
every once in a while, pretty constantly.
I think it's like over 500 points
along this mile long track.
You hit Goodyear tires that are forever spinning
and that gives you the momentum to keep going.
In Florida, different thing.
Powerful electromagnets in the track
that attract and repel and can be customized.
So like, all right, speed up in this section
or slow down in this section.
They're kind of, you know, there's fail-safes too,
both for safety, but also like, okay, this motor's out.
So the other ones pick up the weight.
Okay, oh, so you can, certain particular ones
can go offline and that's okay.
And so this is a system that the Houston airport one uses.
By the way, I watched the full loop
of the Houston airport people mover
and it is maybe the most boring video footage
I've ever consumed in my life.
This is, to fully explain this, Disney is making,
like we have this idea for a public transit system
that it's only deployed as a theme park ride
and they wanna sell it to actual places
and it works in exactly one forum, we think.
And it is that Imagineering built this tram
in the Houston airport, which is the George Bush
Intercontinental Airport.
And yes, you can watch video of it.
And it is, I think you might be able to declare it
Disney's most depressing ride.
Because it's just going through not just terminals,
but it's like basement and claustrophobic, low ceilings.
I think if a very determined person could walk
pretty well faster than this thing.
And it's enclosed, it's not open air.
Undecorated, like the stripes on the side of it
are the most decorations associated with it.
Stripes, yeah.
That's not much.
I always, and it was actually disappointing
because I knew that bit of trivia.
And I always pictured the fun friendly Disney people mover
being oddly in the airport and everybody having a good time
like on all those posters.
But no, it's in the dingiest, saddest.
There's no decoration in these hallways.
No.
There's not even a like, watch out for bombs.
There's not even that.
Just bare walls, low ceilings.
It also, I mean, good, it connects to parking
and a hotel like convenient.
I saw a thing that said like, well, for the airport,
it's before security.
So you have to go, if you're connecting flights,
if you're gonna use this monorail,
you might have to go through security again.
God, that seems like a waste.
Yeah, a little bit.
Well, I think, I believe that this,
what was kind of cool and cutting edge in 1981,
if you can imagine, is struggling a bit in 2023.
And I think it's in need of replacing.
And it's not even the main people mover
that services this airport.
Yeah.
Are we calling, we aren't calling the shot
of the Houston airport, are we?
Hmm, are we?
I mean, if one of us has a crazy layover
and something to do, you know, a day.
If I decide to go visit Monday, then.
The asterisk of it is like,
oh, this is the only one that Disney ever sold to outside,
outside of theme parks.
Except, there's an identical copy of it at the US Capitol
that goes between buildings.
What happened is Disney spun off this division of WED
and sold it to a Canadian company called Bombardier.
And they were the ones who got the contract
to make the one at the US Capitol
that connects a bunch of the Congress buildings.
This is insane.
There is a, there's a sort of,
depending on how you want to define it,
kind of Disney people mover under the Capitol.
Which I have written.
So you can go on it as not a government employee?
Yeah, when I went on like the, you know, high school.
Was that on the date January 6th when you were there?
I know, wasn't running that day.
I don't know, something else was going on that day.
When I did, like in the year, early 2001,
when they would just let high schoolers
loose on the US Capitol to just wander the buildings
after you met your congressman.
And they're just like, all right,
you have six hours until we meet back up at the buses
to go back to the Holiday Inn.
There's a ride, you want to do the ride?
And my friends and I found a ride
and we're like trying to find
the most famous persons off it.
So we would just go from building to building on this ride.
And this was, sorry, this was early 2001?
What happened, what changed?
I don't know, I think just everyone,
like after Shrek, everyone was having such a good time
that year and people were doing other stuff.
Just the Shrek world.
Yeah, pre-Shrek world.
Pre-Shrek world, post-Shrek, excuse me.
I think we all remember where we were when Shrek came out.
I think, yeah, should we have a quick moment
of silence for Shrek?
I am a believer, so I think so.
Well, we'll do it off mic.
That's so weird and you can watch,
there's a little bit of that included
at the end of the very long Martins vids
that shows you a lot of these iterations.
I laughed when I said, like,
this video contains seven iterations
of people move a ride throughs and then you get to the end
and you get a little ride through of this one,
which has, this one's got great decorations,
not like Houston, it has the seal
of the United States Senate.
It's so weird seeing the Senate logo on a ride
and Mike, you brought up a certain date,
not another date that was avoided just now,
but on January 6th, did any of those senators flee using,
this is an underground way to get out of the building
with a bunch of crazies trying to,
with a bunch of patriots, I'm sorry, trying to get in.
Yeah, thank you.
It's a very good question and you'd have to imagine
someone, some of them wrote it
at a certain point during the day.
I bet, I bet.
Yeah.
Who was the guy who ran away very,
who like tweeted in support of everybody,
but then there's the footage of him.
Holly?
Josh Holly?
Josh Holly, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If there was then footage of Holly
under a blanket.
Or like doing the same kind of floppy run onto the ride,
slipping and falling, hitting his head on the windshield,
like Ernest pressing his face up against the glass,
banging into every pole.
There has to be.
And I don't know, they didn't talk about it.
Some people I think hold up in their office.
Some people went to different like safe areas,
but yeah, somebody had to hop on that thing.
Yeah, yeah, you think so.
And thank God that it wasn't breached.
Thank God that the shaman wasn't like,
we've captured the Senate mover.
Right?
It would be funny to see the shaman crying this.
He'd take his hat off and scratch his head
like while this is going,
and he's like pulling up the station real quick,
gets himself back together.
It's going 130, baby.
If he was at least like next to the ride
while it pulled up, it would be like he was the shaman
of song essentially on Navi River Journey.
So it would be the closest thing to a Disney ride.
There's a shaman at the end of it.
But he sings, kill my parents, kill my parents.
Yeah, it's sort of a different.
It's still just as pleasant a tune,
but the message is different.
The footage you're going to see today may shock you.
You're going to see footage of a people mover attraction
absconded with by bandits in goat horns.
And by the end of this 21 day procedure,
nothing will change for anyone or anything.
Yeah.
I will lose my job is what will happen.
Anyway, I won't say anything else.
What, what?
No, no, no.
Okay, okay.
I'm getting punchy.
Speaking of tunes, Mike just said tunes.
I did, yeah.
I, so I started watching a lot of these versions
of the people mover and there was on retro WDW's channel,
one from 1994.
And I was like, oh great,
let's see what it looks like opening year.
And this is, if you'll recall Alien encounter
opens December of 94, then real quickly closes
and reopens in June of 95.
So the land was done before that big ride
and the narration is in there.
The narration that I recognize,
the music is not what I recognize
because it is like Looney Tunes old music
when they go to a factory, like the dun dun dun,
da da da da da.
Like it's really kitschy, cartoony music
playing in the background with the regular narration.
And then a year or two later,
I don't know how long it took.
It seemed like it was just placeholder music.
And then eventually at some point,
it's kind of like more twinkly spacey music.
Okay, okay.
That seems like it runs from like the mid 90s
up to like 2003 when I started to find videos
with that Tomorrowland music loop.
Well, so much of the vibe of this thing
was like, was bustling city and then like gears,
a lot of gears involved in this new,
like it was a very, it's like the,
it's the city that the robots live in and robots.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Robots.
I know robots.
I don't know what the city is called.
Perhaps robot city.
It might be called robot city.
I just saw on that Twitter account that posts
defunct foods, they posted the robots tie-in cereal.
There was a robot cereal?
Six months or a year.
Yeah, it's just frosted strawberry Cheerios or whatever.
Gears probably.
It was a robot city.
Yeah.
Oh, great.
And the main character.
Rodney Copperbutton.
Your eyes went right to it too.
We all know.
And the evil Ratchet is trying to cheat older robots
into buying expensive upgrades.
This is like, it's Chapec.
Yeah, wow.
Chapec's entire plan was laid out by the character Ratchet.
Wow.
And then there's a guy named Mr. Gunk.
That's a thing I've been saying to my son lately.
Yeah.
And make him laugh.
Gunk.
Well, I gotta show him Mr. Gunk.
Who plays Mr. Gunk?
Hold on, let me find it.
I just saw the name.
Dan Hedaya.
Oh, I love Dan Hedaya.
We love Dan Hedaya.
Dick.
It's Dick.
Wow.
And the guy who doesn't get along with the Addams family.
Yeah.
Maybe I would like, wait a minute.
Look who played.
Are you looking at the same thing I'm looking at?
Are you saying who plays fire hydrant in robots?
No.
Fire hydrant is played by Jay Leno.
Well, we gotta call the shot.
Call the shot.
Robots.
Stephen Tobolowski's in it.
All the American Idol judges are in it.
Oh, wow.
Can someone, is robots, is it Disney film?
No, it's Fox.
Meet the Robinsons is a Disney film.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Whoa, my God.
And look who's at the premiere, Osomo.
Here's Osomo with Greg Kinnear.
Here's Osomo with Amanda Bynes.
Wow.
This is great.
Oh, boy.
Oh, I can't wait for the robots episode.
Who does the music?
We're gonna learn all about Cappy and Big Weld.
Also, in a different town called Rivet Town.
Rivet Town is not Robot City.
Awesome, I'll kind of,
an early ding against the Disneyland Tomorrowland
where I was like, they don't have people moving,
but they got fucking Osomo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it didn't seem to be working 100% either
from like 20 feet away.
It's a scene like it.
Right, right.
Was jerking around.
There's also, by the way, there's a separate,
people know my thing, Tiny Fuppets,
which is a Brazilian ripoff of Muppet Babies.
One of the things that that's based on
is a real cheap Brazilian movie
that got made called Tiny Robots.
Which, and that has a whole other,
and I gotta find the name of that city.
I'll figure that out.
But don't let me interrupt.
I'll work quietly.
Back to the people mover.
So the people mover in 94 gets renamed
to the Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
I've established on the main feed episode,
never in my life have I referred to it vocally as that.
But in Canon, in K-Fape,
I know this is the Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
And they play it up.
They play up that this is a line.
There are other lines.
There's red, you know, I think this is the blue line.
There's a red line and the green line.
One would take you all for a,
one would take you to the exurbs, the suburbs, you know?
Is that a, they made up like a future word
for suburbs called exurbs?
No, I think exurbs is a term already.
Oh, it is?
Oh, I never heard exurbs.
Oh, I was hoping that was like Disney mythology.
That would be crazy.
They do, what is the term they use?
You know what would be great is if they did like,
the people mover would go on all the lands
and it could somehow change what you were in,
at least just from your vantage point
of what like kind of vehicle you were in.
Oh, sure.
Like you could start in Tomorrowland
and end up in Galaxy's Edge
and all of a sudden it feels like,
oh, now we're on a Banta.
I don't know how they would quite do that,
but that would be cool too to make it extend out.
Scott, your thinking was correct.
They did come up with a term.
The green line provides local transportation
to the hoverburbs.
What?
Wow. The hoverburbs?
I love the hoverburbs.
The red line takes you off planet.
That's so dumb.
Oh man, that's Back to the Future 2 dumb.
I love it.
Floating, I assume.
It must be a floating city, a hovering city.
It might only be like two feet off the ground.
Right, right.
You don't have to be up high to hover.
No. Oh man, that rules.
And here, just really quick to close this loop.
Tiny Robots is set in New Iron City
and it follows the adventures of Trank,
who's an old fashioned kind of robot.
So he doesn't get along with the high tech robots
that he finds in New Iron City.
Imagine what could happen with the worst animation ever
done by any underpaid people.
Didn't we go to Iron City for Alita Battle,
was that the name of it?
Alita Battle Angel.
Was that part of the Alita Battle Angel?
Isn't that the name of the city?
I can't remember the city.
I think so, right?
I know we were trying to get to Zalem.
You're trying to get to Zalem, but where we were.
I think it wasn't at Iron City, am I wrong?
I didn't realize that Alita Battle Angel
was at one point a pivot point for James Cameron
and he was deciding, do I make this or do I make Avatar?
And what a different world it would be
if he'd instead gone with, would it have worked?
Maybe we'd all, and Alita Battle Angel
crushes box office records.
I mean, it didn't, with not him directing,
but if he'd done it, we might be up to Alita Five by now.
Sure, passport to Iron City.
Yeah, that was the name of Iron City.
Yeah, where's Iron City?
But not New Iron City.
They stole it from this movie
that stole everything from robots.
Yeah, so, oh, and I always forget,
James Cameron produced Dark Angel on Fox.
Yeah.
Which I don't know if that had anything to do
with the Battle Angel.
I don't think so, but he liked angels.
He liked angels.
And this is, remember I talked about
my creepy high school teacher a couple months ago.
I was trying to forget.
I know, but I.
Oh, what a dark.
We were supposed to cast the movie
and I think I said that I cast Jessica Alba
and he in front of the class made a big show.
He goes, I gotta congratulate this guy.
He walked around the desks.
He shook my hand and he goes,
he cast TV's Dark Angel, Jessica Alba in a movie.
And like, he made a big show of it,
like a real horny show.
Oh no.
That's very odd.
Yeah, you don't, he like, no one else casts
like an actress that like was good looking
in the class other than me.
Like there's no way.
I don't know what, he must've been like
a big Dark Angel fan and really wanted us to know about it.
If anybody in this class wants to stay after
and is willing to be cool about it,
I do have Jessica Alba on the cover of FHM.
If you wanna hang and just look at pics.
That was the vibe of him,
but he also looked like John Lithgow.
Oh no.
Oh, you never didn't give that visual.
And I didn't give that visual,
but he very much felt like this weird kind of like
hyper nerd man who looked very much like Lithgow.
Jeez.
So there's an extra dynamic to that story now.
Oh, yikes, yikes.
Let's speed away from here.
Yeah.
Maybe seven miles per hour.
Let's get to the hover burbs.
The hover burbs.
Yeah, the hover burbs.
No pervert teachers in the hover burbs.
Not the pervert burbs.
The ups are regulated.
So let's see, what did they redo
when they redid the people mover?
Well, the main thing, this Tomorrowland Transit Authority
thing is what, this is what I'm like,
that Tomorrowland, it's gone.
We need a thrill ride.
Nobody wants this boring, gentle ride.
Strip it out now, there's just nothing.
Now we have no ride.
As opposed to here with this name,
which is a very stiff name,
but it ties everything together.
And you go, and like now it is, all right,
so this is the little train that takes you
from place to place.
And the narration explains,
here where Alien Counter is, is the convention center.
And like this is considered,
this rocket port or whatever.
Like if you go, if you went to New Tomorrowland
and you got on this first,
this explains the story to you.
Yeah, I mean, that's great.
And I think I really like that it does.
One, they call it the TTA,
the Tomorrowland Transit Authority.
A piece on Laughing Place points out
that it addresses each location
in the reality of like, so yeah,
they say the Interplanetary Convention Center.
And this company, Excess Tech,
is testing out their teleportation technology.
They don't give away
like the horrifying Alien Encounter elements.
Wow, as opposed to the Disneyland one,
which would just be like,
George Lucas brings Star Tours, which is fine,
but like doing the full K-Fabe is pretty cool.
Yeah, and they, I mean, as it goes on,
as like Dream Flight flips to Buzz Lightyear,
there is a little more.
You get the fake Buzz Lightyear.
It's like Buzz Lightyear blasting off
or like join Buzz Lightyear in whatever.
That one's a little more straightforward.
It's a little more straightforward.
They do, you can still see into Buzz Lightyear
just as you could see into Dream Flight
and If You Had Wings.
But a thing I really like on that music loop
that is still on there,
it starts playing the If You Had Wings instrumental
as you are passing over that.
And it continues for a bit of the ride.
And then it plays, now is the best time of your life
over Progress City.
So in the spots where these things were,
that's pretty cool.
Wow. Yeah.
And the Progress City element,
when they changed it to the Peter Rinade narration,
it's a lot more like here's Walt's vision of the future.
They specifically contextualize it
in the world of Walt Disney.
They don't just say like the world of tomorrow,
like a city of the future.
It's interesting because it's like,
maybe everyone can give their opinion on this.
It's like we've talked about Sea,
the Society of Explorers and Adventures,
which like touches a lot of the different parks
around the world.
And it's kind of subtle depending on,
some places subtle, some places it's not.
There's characters in the secret organization
and certain characters have been added
and retroactively added to rides.
But then there's this Tomorrowland Transit Authority,
basically like tied everything up in a narrative
in one area and it can find it to an area.
Is it better this way or is it better
where Sea is sort of loose?
Is there an, you know what I'm saying?
Cause like Sea can actually sort of overtake everything
if you really want it to in kind of an annoying way.
Where like, you know, everything's connected
to the point where you're like a little tired.
Versus this though, which I think is cool.
Like I think Sea is cool too,
but I think this one almost like,
it being a little bit confined to Tomorrowland,
I don't know, I like it.
We fleshed out this, well, it's more manageable.
It's certainly more manageable.
Just flesh out mythology of this place.
I think you just stumbled into a good idea
for fixing Tomorrowland though,
which is doing that premise that they're trying to employ
for the Marvel campuses, which is a narrative
where all the Tomorrowlands are a little different.
Oh yeah.
But there are certain components and like,
well they all have space mountains.
So maybe those all function as this, you know,
they're a hub of, right.
You know, like travel for whatever.
Like if you add consistency to the rules of Tomorrowland,
instead of that they're all kind of a hodgepodge.
Yeah.
You could like sort of slightly fix
or clarify things across the board
and especially Disneyland, that could be cool.
Well like, at least in the current narration,
and I think this has always been around at different levels,
but they referred to Space Mountain as Starport 75,
which is the year it opened.
So like that you could easily apply
to all the space mountains, you know.
Yeah.
You just put the year they opened, like.
If we're saying that like that's a space day,
that's some kind of launch point
in the way that Star Tours is as well.
Like probably a lot of the rides you would consider that.
Those places that take you to different places.
Yeah, that'd be cool.
Yeah.
I'm wondering if every land should have its own sea.
I'd rather have more seas than just one sea, yes.
And sea leaves out, sea is entirely Adventureland,
Frontierland, past stuff.
Why not?
Yeah, I would love that.
But then also waterpark stuff.
And waterpark stuff.
And cruise.
Disney private island stuff.
Cruise, yeah, the cruise ship has some sea stuff.
Uh-huh.
So yeah, maybe the answer is more seas.
Yeah.
That's the sea of the past.
What is the sea of the future?
Right.
Yeah, cause I think, I mean,
it's not the worst version of it,
but like as they added more characters,
as they added Puzzle, Light, Ear, and Monsters,
they can get Stitch.
It did weaken the narrative they were trying to do.
Like it kind of like.
I, they melded it into the narration
and have updated narrations and stuff over the years.
And I think those rides, Stitch being the exception,
I don't, I'm sure there are fans of it.
I don't, I didn't mind it terribly,
but like I think those Buzz Lightyear and Monsters, Inc.
being pretty decent rides,
like being decent rides that people enjoy,
lets it get away with it, you know?
Yeah, sure, sure.
It doesn't totally break the narrative.
It doesn't totally break the world.
It kind of makes sense being there.
Yeah.
You know?
It's all heard the aesthetic to me a little bit
because there was this fully committed,
I really liked the like 30s future that they had going.
And you know what I don't like is like,
it's kind of a rinky dink rocket with the green aliens on it.
Or like, I don't like, I may have said this before,
I don't like any exterior of any Buzz Lightyear rides.
I like the ride, but I think the signs are junk.
And there's much better iterations of Toy Story aesthetic
done in the parks.
I just don't like these ones that they've,
they just feel cheap to me.
They feel like Disney store or something.
That was, and it's that 90s vibe too, which doesn't,
I mean, not the bad, like cheap 90s vibe
versus the good tomorrow in 90s vibe.
I guess I should just make that distinction.
Sure.
I almost wish, and this is really,
it makes sense that they're just like,
this is a Buzz Lightyear ride,
because we're in the 1% of people who care about that.
But if you want to stay consistent with what you're saying
about like alien encounter,
I would like them to couch and hide the fact
that Buzz Lightyear's in the ride.
It should be a different thing.
That should be like, oh, you know, this is,
cause I'm trying to think there's no narrative reason
other than you're just getting on a ride
to go destroy Zerg, I guess.
But it should be-
Oh, sign up to join forces to stop this menace.
Whatever the space rangers sign up,
space ranger, whatever.
And it's a sort of a generic thing.
Space ranger out, well, it's like the mall,
when you, the mall has the army sign up station
and the Marines sign up station.
Yeah.
It's one of those.
Yes.
The space rangers are renting out a defunct office space
to Marlin.
Specifically the mall in Burbank has the army station
next to the Marine station.
And you're like, I've never seen,
I've never seen them next to each other.
Like, should there be a store in one of these?
Do they get along?
Yeah.
And the emoji, I just remember once
there was a giant emoji movie poster, like in between them.
And if like somebody's in one of the offices
and they go, oh, this guy isn't cut out to be in the Marine,
let's send him over to the other office.
Does that ever happen?
I wonder.
We've got somewhere better,
more suited to your specific skills.
Or they send them downstairs to the Navy office.
Like what happens?
I don't know.
This is by the other emoji movie.
Oh yeah.
Standy, yeah.
I bet it's still there too.
Yeah.
All the, yeah.
It's the Burbank mall.
It's not.
Yeah, yeah.
There's probably a lot of just stray emoji movie artwork
that the pandemic, everybody forgot about in the pandemic.
So yeah.
So like a Monsters Inc. laugh floor.
Just make it look like the laugh factory sign.
Yeah.
It's the Tomorrowland laugh factory.
Right.
And then you go in and you see them,
but that'll keep the aesthetic and everything on point.
Oh, they just happen to be here,
these characters in the Tomorrowland world.
Do you want the digital billboards saying,
we support our comics.
We support free speech.
I would like them to say that.
And then I would like it to say like,
Dane Cook under that.
But then Zane Cook was there.
I was just gonna say space Dane Cook.
Yeah.
And like if they can tie together the,
any acknowledgement that like,
isn't that where the Mike L. Blipchards incident happened?
Yes, right.
When that robot went haywire.
It started insulting those other robots.
Yes.
Yeah.
Those robot slurs you don't use.
That's right.
Yeah.
So if they could do that, that'll be for the parents.
That's the wink to the parents.
Yeah.
But it would, yes, it would keep the,
IP bleed from bothering the 1%, which are us.
They can do it easily.
Although if they fix it,
then we don't have things to talk about on this podcast.
That's true.
They shouldn't fix anything.
Well, untouched, I feel like is the two,
like there were two big scenes
that I think came along with the TTA version,
which is the robot shipping department
next to star traders.
What happens in that?
It's so hard to get like still stopped footage.
They're all like shipping stuff off world.
Okay.
Like it's right after the progress city scene,
which I learned that is the,
you're in the attic space of cosmic rays.
It all bleeds together.
Really?
Yeah.
That's what I saw.
That was even when they built that,
they were like, all right,
we're gonna put some sort of diorama upstairs.
We don't know what yet.
So you're up above.
Sunny eclipse.
At that moment.
Yeah.
Somewhere thereabouts.
Wouldn't that be great if the space angels were up there?
Like waiting to come down.
That'd be a good way to tie it.
Yeah.
Encouraging you to get a bite, see the show.
Sure.
Yeah.
Get a mediocre chicken sandwich,
but they have a toppings bar so you can load up.
There is a poster for pan galactic pizza,
which kind of ties into the pan galactic pizza bar,
which I love so much in Japan.
There's also the digital,
the robot like hair salon,
the person getting the crazy hair.
It's another civic moment.
It's very strange.
And for a thing,
it's odd to only have two little sci-fi scenes.
Yeah.
That's it.
You feel like at least one more would make it seem like,
oh, so that's a recurring bit of this ride.
Cause as it stands, it's like,
are there little scenes or not?
Yeah.
What is this?
That comes, like I'm wondering if that was a fix,
like where you would see into,
if you would wings or Delta dream flight.
Cause every time they updated those rides,
they're like, oh, the people mover,
we gotta make an eyeline for the people mover view.
And I think it was really clean for,
if you had wings,
you could see into the different like footage scenes.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
It's, yeah, I'm trying to remember.
Cause so much of this stuff,
I think even blends together.
We've talked about sort of how we were kids in Epcot.
Epcot, all the dark rides are sort of a piece.
And in my memory, world of motion could be
part of my spaceship earth memory.
It's hard to sometimes,
but I think some of the people mover stuff
is also mixed in with that too.
Well, that's why-
For so many trips to Disney world.
I was shocked to find all this old 90s footage
where the narration is the same,
but the music keeps changing.
Right.
And that was like-
That makes it feel like you're either gonna try to turn you,
like make you go insane.
Well, I was the one who insisted
on trying to find the music for Josh.
Look, the whole podcast that we're doing this to ourselves.
Yeah, sure.
We're driving ourselves insane.
But I'm saying like, it's so interesting.
Cause yeah, you're like,
it's just like kind of a little off of what your memory is.
Yeah.
And then you're like watching something you're like,
I remember this music.
I was eventually right in the 2000.
I'm looking back, I was right in the 2000s,
but I just filled in the blanks of like,
okay, I like this half and I like this half.
Like we could completely wreck people's memory
if we find a lot of footage from rides
that are no longer there.
And then subtly edit together scenes
that didn't belong on the same ride.
Yeah.
And music that wasn't on the thing.
Like if you could do it in a subtle way,
you can completely reshape people's memories
of what these rides were.
Make them really upset.
Yeah, make people upset.
And it could be a long con of some kind.
I don't know how we got money out of it,
but at least we get some laughs.
I don't know.
Well, there's all that, you know,
those like Mandela effect type, like Berenstein bears.
Yeah.
And those things that people,
there are some people who just find all that stuff
kind of interesting.
And then there's others who are like,
and see, that's what proves that Hillary is drinking.
But like somehow there's a path from,
I remember things not so,
I remember a movie called Shazam to,
now see, this proves that there's adrenochrome.
And I'm not sure how those things connect, but they do.
That's true.
People are really off the.
It's just seeing like there's stuff out there, man.
If you look for the little things,
it proves the bigger picture.
Yeah, no, that's a whole nother episode.
But yes, there is a direct line from like,
misremembering a theme song to a cartoon
to lizard people walk among us.
Yeah.
That's what it opens up Pandora's box.
Like, yeah, that's possible.
Right.
Isn't it possible that Tom Hanks has just a big bottle
of infant blood every night?
Yes.
It's because I forgot the second line
to the tailspin theme song.
I've been misremembering it this whole time.
I always thought it was win it if you spin it,
but then I looked it up and it was spin it in a minute.
Right.
So therefore.
Therefore.
You wanna go storm the Capitol?
Don't mind if I do.
I'm hijacking the Senate mover.
Well, the little versions of that is like when,
if you prove someone wrong,
you see people being proved wrong on the internet
and they go like, well,
the fact that I would believe it was real
that says something about our modern era.
And you're just like, shut the fuck up.
That's how changing the world.
That's like on the playground just deciding.
And I have the infinity weapon that defeats everything.
Yes, exactly.
Anyway, my memory of Tomorrowland and the TTA is perfect.
Eventually they did add PeopleMover back.
Isn't it now today called the PeopleMover again?
It is now called the Tomorrowland Transit Authority
PeopleMover.
But isn't there,
I think in the last couple months,
it may have gone back even further.
Oh really?
To just PeopleMover?
I think maybe.
Let's see.
I barely.
On the Disney World website should have the official.
Oh, that'd be the source.
Yeah.
Right.
So, cause they have the official name of Ride listed.
And it is still Tomorrowland Transit Authority
PeopleMover on the website.
Okay.
So I guess that's the official.
So.
I thought I'd seen that maybe they just reduced it
all the way.
But you're right.
They were not using,
we'll see the way,
well the way I remember it proves that maybe
there's some possibility.
No, but it was just Tomorrowland Transit Authority
and then they intruded,
like why not put this nice term PeopleMover
that people have fun as for back into it.
And those can all live together.
I think maybe that was added back in around the time
of that thing I hate,
like the narration I hate.
Okay.
Of the more funky.
I think this 2022 might've brought back that chime,
that little like three thing.
That's part of your ringtone.
That's part of my ringtone.
That takes you back.
Very satisfying chime.
It is very satisfying chime.
But yeah.
And it's funny to think about like young me going like,
I like this middle-aged man doing a version of an old man
doing public service announcements for the city.
Like I don't,
I know what rides are in there.
Like tell me the backstory.
Tell me the reality of the cityscape you've created.
Weird children.
Weird, weird wild stuff.
Strange fixations, weird children.
Little quick hits about what's different in Florida
besides the electromagnetic thing.
It's also all flat.
That's the only, with the difference in the tracks,
it did that this Tomorrowland one didn't have the power
to take you uphill.
So you couldn't do the like climbing and descending
over the Autopia track like you could in Disneyland.
What's the other?
The cover.
They made the whole thing covered.
No roofs.
On the cars.
It's just all got a big roof.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a little bit of the voiceover
that we have not mentioned,
which is when a very specific person is paged.
Of course.
This is what I wanted to mention.
Oh, okay.
There you go.
There is a little, probably those little chimes
and then you hear paging Mr. Morrow.
Paging Mr. Tom Morrow.
Yes.
Which is a name that's been part of a lot
of Tomorrowland things.
Yes.
If you got the pun, I don't know if you got Tom Morrow,
what the pun is there.
I'll say I always knew they said this.
I think I got it.
And then of course, this is why my favorite YouTuber
has taken the name Paging Mr. Morrow
is because of this reference.
Yeah.
So now I have a lot more fondness for this section
of the People Mover because of how much content
of the gentleman, real name Nate, but his name,
which we can't find this, maybe this question to ask.
The internet says his name is Nate Morrow.
I don't know if.
Name is Morrow.
I do not know his last name.
I don't know if that's real, I think,
but he goes by the moniker Mr. Morrow on YouTube.
If we have him on, we can ask.
But by him, I mean Peter Rennaday.
When we have Peter Rennaday on,
we can ask if he knows what's Morrow's real name.
We can only have Peter Rennaday
if he's in character Splinter the whole time.
That's my, that's what I want.
Yes, today Splinter, you may know him as a Master Sensei rep.
He's going to teach us ninjutsu today.
But yeah, so now I have a lot of,
I'm gonna like cheer next time I go on this section.
Cause I also like watching, cause Mr. Morrow
is in Disney World almost every day and he's making videos.
He makes a big deal when he goes on the People Mover
and he like kind of makes a thing.
He does a little point.
Jason watches this.
Okay, the point that you do when.
Green Day comes on.
Mr. Morrow is my favorite TV show.
I want to say that as well.
I think you can find the name in the Disneyland People Mover.
One of the narrations there.
They say real quick.
Yeah.
Mr. Johnson is mentioned.
Well, they say Mr. Johnson in the one narration,
I think is giving the traffic and weather report
and another, I think they say paging Mr. Morrow,
call Mr. Johnson.
You are having trouble keeping these straight in your head.
After 23 versions?
Sure.
Yeah.
After watching the arc from like Super 8 to VHS to digital,
like yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, you know, we've been like very detail oriented
in this episode.
I'm going to bring up really quickly two big parts
of the human experience that tie into the People Mover.
Go ahead.
One is death.
I don't want to meditate on this for long,
but it's worth mentioning this somehow,
this pleasant ride that we have enjoyed talking about
so much for two episodes is one of the deadliest rides
and it's not Disney's fault, I don't think.
Just early, like people just start,
like in two cases, teenagers just were trying to pass
from car to car.
Jumping from car to car.
Yeah, yeah.
Including one was a month after it opened in 1967.
This nice, one month in, it had a death on its hands.
Crazy.
One was Grad night.
How grim is that?
There is a Grad night death and somebody,
I'll tease this, somebody who's been on the show,
somebody we know, their mom was at that Grad night
where it happened.
Jesus.
I won't tell, let them bum us out with a sad story later
if they want to.
These deaths were all at the Disneyland version, correct?
Yes, well, there was recently an older man
who died on the Disney World one,
but I don't think it had anything to do with the ride.
I think it was just pre-existing conditions.
Yeah.
Or so Disney would have you believe.
I think some of the Disneyland versions
led to lots of different safety,
like led to the kind of more caged ride vehicles
and then led to the Florida,
like I think the Florida programming,
I think they can like stop on a dime a lot more.
They can just kill them.
They can just not people, what is the wrong word?
They can kill the vehicles.
They can stop the vehicles.
That's the better word.
Right.
Disney cannot.
Yeah, you can't say.
Walt's space laser was not created
and is so exacting that it can bounce through a people
mover tunnel and take out people who don't look right
to the Disney company.
When Walt's God was still alive,
God used to be able to just pick the person out of the car,
but that was before.
Well, that's why they made it go through Space Mountain.
You just, you don't see the claw coming for you.
It just plugs you.
When you come out the other side,
there's one less senior party.
Wait, that's something we haven't talked about in both
versions. You can go into Space Mountain.
I know.
And there's nothing better who doesn't want to go on Space
Mountain.
I'm sure I've said before the,
the first time I went in the part of the first time I went
on the people mover and it said,
you're going into Space Mountain.
I started screaming at my mom with,
they said we're going in it's skin.
She said, no, no, no, we're just going into the building.
We're not.
No, they said it's going to be it.
I'm going to like, in my mind,
this was a trap that Disney made to force children to go on
scary rides. They weren't ready to go on without harnesses,
without even being in the proper vehicle to do so.
Like at that moment,
I thought this is an evil company that's like going to put me
into a big machine and grind me up.
That's so interesting. How old were you about when there?
Well, I hope this was when I was three.
I actually mean to ask it as if it was eight.
I do not know.
That was not with my intention for asking the question.
Cause it's interesting the type of scared kids we were.
Cause I was sort of the like clench my seat,
close my eyes as tight as possible.
But I don't think I was like yelling like that.
You just internalized.
I internalized and it is so what I do to this day.
I think I do too. Cause I like, you know,
I like complain a lot.
That's probably what I, that's me.
That's my version of screaming.
It's interesting cause we still have our same versions of
dealing with whatever dealing with stress, yelling to anyone who listens.
And I just sit there clenching and you're just grabbing the chair.
Jason, what were you, you never got scared on these?
You were so, you were just kicked back. You put your feet up.
Oh, not on these. No, I loved going into space.
Mountain. I let you saw the lift hill.
I'm saying what kind of nothing, what kind of a scared kid,
if you were in a, like you were five years old and you were scared.
I would invent impossible scenarios.
How would you express it? I guess what I'm saying,
would you be loud and say, or would you kind of just be quiet?
Internalize until it got to a point where it was too much and I burst into tears.
And that's about right. What you do now, I think.
Does that ring true to this day?
I, I try to minimalize.
I try to use healthy coping mechanisms nowadays.
Well, that's much like the people mover put mechanisms in place so that people don't die.
Yeah. But you've given yourself safety mechanisms.
Yes. The space mountain stuff in Florida, I, you know, they,
the music cues are often very good. You see the lift hill. You,
if you're lucky, you see the work lights on it's main place to see it with the lights on.
Oh yeah. If there's a problem on the ride and you can ride through it and see the whole track,
the space mountain track, which looks so ugly and bad.
Horrifying. Oh, awful. Yeah.
Two different rides. So like if one breaks down, the other can keep going.
Like they're not dependent on each other.
When they do major construction, they close both.
The other thing is in very early versions of this ride, you could look down into the
then sponsor RCA into the home of future living, a very cumbersome name,
because I guess the house of the future was already taken.
Future living. Yeah.
Huh? I, that the view that you get going, going between the two lift hill,
that's a big superior part of the, uh, going between the two space mountain lift hills.
So maybe you're getting space mountain rockets on either side of you.
There's the upside down people working with space tools. Oh man.
Above you. That's a great dramatic viewpoint. Very cool part of the people mover down there.
Also, when I was a kid and it was sponsored by FedEx, I love the exiting scene where the
astronauts are making FedEx delivery. Like they have FedEx boxes. It added to the city,
like the functioning futuristic society element. I think I think I just liked it because it's like,
yeah, well we saw the shipping department and now it's FedEx. So I guess they beam,
they beam the packages, right? Yeah. And earlier when I said big elements of human
existence, one was death. The other is sex. Um, that one story, uh, this was from Erin,
not her and not us. Sorry to lay you down. Uh, she, she talked to somebody once who said,
oh yeah, I love Disney. I, you know what I used to do? Uh, my, my girlfriend at the time and I,
uh, would go on the people mover and we wrote it a bunch of times and we found where all the cameras
were and then found the longest stretch inside, but there are no cameras. And we, in that, in that
zone, we did some sex full death. I don't know. I don't think she, she maybe was ready to not hear
further details about this person. Turn into a Howard Stern in the 1990s.
What are you going down on her? You know what's going on? You flip around. What was it? Yeah.
She didn't decide to quiz was great. Big tomorrow plan. What, uh, what do you think
were you above star traders? What's a trot superspeed tunnel? Where was it? Uh,
where at one or the current narrator or they, who's named to our FI it's kind of a throwback
to where Mike hop on that Sibian real quick. The sex device of the future, you know,
the other detail I like from the story. She, she said like, this was back when they were, uh,
when, when this guy was in his punk days and he had his punk girlfriend. So these two punks,
these hard rock punk or mohawks. That's what I was, I, again, no further ado, but imagine what you,
I guess like who knows now in today's big brother security state, I don't think punks are able to
have sex on this ride. No, but back in, uh, you know, back in Sid and Nancy days, you could go
ahead and get on with your giant mohawks and go to town. Yeah. Not with these current wait times.
I think last year we waited, or like two years ago, we waited like 30, 35 minutes to get on.
I don't know if it's from the breaking down, but like the railroad and the people mover
have just had insane weights. Well, they may have been, they may have been taking the time to chase
out some, uh, penetration, power wash those pleasing blue ride vehicles.
Jason, that makes Jason sick to his stomach. Do not, if you do that wherever you want,
you do that in the Capitol building for all I care. I have allegiance to one thing. Absolutely.
Go do it. And you know, did anyone have sex in the, was that ever part of it? I don't think so,
but I don't think those lame-os, they should have, they were just stealing laptops and smearing shits.
Two of them, two of those ugly weirdos should have had some sex in there. Here should be a new
part of Disneyland forward to curb this problem. If it's still a problem, bring back holiday hill,
a new version of the hill that was there before the matter horn where people used to neck with
each other, the nasty trash hill, bring the hill back so people can neck. There's no necking spots
in the parks anymore. So that was the old day. So let's bring it back with this and forward.
When we bulldoze Harbor Boulevard business, small businesses, one of those places that will,
one of the attractions that will rise is a new holiday hill. The neck nook, the neck nook,
calling all neckers, all neckers. Let me say this. I think this is funny is that when they're
telling you, you can't use one of the people mover vehicles. Have you seen this? There's a real lo-fi
thing they do, at least in this video. I don't know if it's currently happening is they just
throw up a red cone in the vehicle, like a traffic cone. That's great. Just one single
cone sitting there. Wasn't there a fun way they could say it's like an off, it's off to,
oh, it's repair what? Like a sign with a robot. Whoops, fixing this one. At least a cone with a
big gear in it. At least a cone with a big gear in it. So regular cone, but they just throw up
one cone in there. There's still cones in the future. Yeah, not a future. It's not a future cone.
Look, we've seen our paths. We've seen the bad rotting track world that we have to deal with
in Los Angeles. And then we've seen the bustling metropolis full of hover burbs and
de-atomizing FedEx stations. And I don't know, I'm just so glad they kept it. I'm really going to
make a point every time I go, I gotta go to the Tomorrowland Transit Authority or the Tomorrowland
Transit 30 people mover or whatever you want to call it. And I'm also always sad to get off
when you go back to that station, like, no, you're kidding. This could be a half hour and I'd be
happy. So I guess I feel similar now as we return to the station and thus ends our people mover
export. Cause they never made another. Why didn't this go to Tokyo? Why didn't go to Paris? It's a
great ride. It only went to a shitty basement in Houston. Yeah, I don't know. It's a good question,
but they definitely, not Shanghai doesn't have a version of it, right? There's nothing even close
to it. I don't think so. And it's funny because like that marketing material I was talking about
when they were trying to sell it to people, it did say like the Ford Magic Skyway, Disneyland,
Disney World, the Houston airport. So like they kept saying like we use it in the theme parks
and that you, you know, takes 40,000 people a day. So how much does your, you know, airport or
shopping mall or city use? You know? And so like, yeah, I don't know why they didn't put it anywhere
else. Probably because of maintenance cost. Yeah, I guess. I mean, I'm trying to like, it's, it's
always pretty popular. It obviously loads fast in Florida, but there's been times when I've seen like
a good line. Like there's often a good line waiting to get on it. The line is pretty gnarly
now where it's just like temporary stanchions next to the Astro Orbiter line. And then the like poor
cast member with a sign on the stick. Yeah. That must suck being the sign on the stick guy who has
to move depending on how long the line goes. Yeah. I guess I don't really know the answer why that
hasn't been built, but it, I'm sure it's probably for the same reason at the Bantha thing. Like it
feels like that's the expendable cost when you're building stuff is like, well, this is superfluous
and it's not going to be as attractive of a ride to people. But I think it's a mistake. And I also
think there's a version of it where you plus up little show scenes and you make it a little bit
more of an elevated, elevated experience. Yeah. Little sparkly, make those hallways cool. It is
crazy that they don't just put flashing lights in the hallways and you are just moving through
industrial tunnels. Make it like the space mountain holiday overlay. Yeah. Blast music in there.
It takes, it takes as much as like, it's what it takes to make a party bus cool. Yes. All you need
to do. Yes. And I will call my shot future episode this year, party bus. Party bus is like a little
party buses in general. That sounds good. Well, if it means we have to rent one and drive it around.
It does mean that. So where are we going tonight? Boys? Nowhere. Just take us in a loop. We will
review the experience on our podcast. Well, that is a thing that you go like, well, the people movers
aren't technically a mode of transit because they start and end at the same place except for the one
in Houston and the Capitol. Okay. Right. But I don't know. The company, look, Bob Iger's got a lot on
this plate, but I think looking, taking a hard look at people movers. I think it's a little,
it's quietly just a thing that makes the theme parks what they are. Yeah. It gives you like,
I got on a ride even on the most crowded day on the most hot day and the most rainy day. Yeah.
I went on one ride and it was like, it gives you one. It's pleasant. Nobody's unhappy coming off
that thing. And there's enough technology to make little show stuff, scenes and stuff, probably not
in a crazy expensive way, make you feel like you had a little extra experience. It's not just a
little mode of transportation and waste some time. And Bob, you like the NBA. Bob Iger loves the NBA.
That's true. His wife's name remind me. Willow. Yeah. What's the name? I don't remember. Bay.
Willow Bay. Yeah. Yeah. That's the thing people talk about with sports, right? With
uh, professional sports and athlete intangibles. He hasn't even know where you're going.
Well, I think like stuff like the people mover are the intangibles where they're hard to quantify
for like the money men, you know, right. But they noticeably add things to the park. So it's easy
to cut because it's just like, well, then we save, you know, right. No, $1000. Right. No IP. It's not
a thrill ride. It's sort of just like, well, it's kind of like the train, isn't it? Like we have the
train and there's a, yeah, it's in the middle of all this real estate who cares, but everybody who
is interested, I don't think there's anybody who doesn't like the people mover. Yeah. I don't think
so. I think it's sort of a universally agreed upon. Yeah. It's great. Cause you can, so I hope so
pregnant people, babies, like anyone can go on the people. Horny people. Yes. Horny punks, horny
crap. You know, as long as they can dodge cameras, they can make it their own. Right. Yeah. It's great.
I, I really liked the thing and I'm glad we talked about it for a while. You survived podcast.
There I had a second round, a second loop. We did the little go one more time. One more time.
Old boy. Let's take a vote. The audience want to stop being referred to as Clifford's and be called
horny punks from now on. No, it's okay. Even further removed from theme parks. Let's not do that.
Then a couple of people. Yes. Yes, I would. Yes. You finally, you see who I am. You may know.
I'm so wrong. This is what Mickey hugs me. Hey, thanks for listening and believe in the promise of tomorrow.