Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
a podcast that is always recorded
with the three of us holding hands.
I'm Scott Gardner, I'll give a little squeeze
next to me to Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, we rotate who's in the middle
getting the most sweaty hand action.
Well then sometimes it's triangles
so that we're all accounted for.
Yes.
But right now Mike's way down on the end from me.
I can barely see him actually.
Oh hey Mike, here I'll lean out.
I'll squeeze Jason's hand hard
and it'll make him squeeze your hand hard
so you'll get like my vibrations, you'll get my energy.
I'm still getting Mike's hand hard.
Yeah here, oh.
I appreciate that.
Oh I broke Jason's hand.
Oh, ah.
I think he broke mine.
I made of porcelain.
Jason is like, what Sam Jackson in Unbreakable?
Yes, that would be Sam, Mr. Glass.
Mr. Glass, yeah, there you go.
Oh he is unbreakable, that's what unbreakable is.
Well no, Bruce Willis is unbreakable.
Oh.
Sam Jackson is very, very breakable.
Oh I see.
Yeah, so.
Bruce Willis is unbreakable unless water comes into play.
Yes.
I just saw unbreakable like in the last couple years
for the first time.
Really?
Yeah.
Clearly I haven't.
Yeah, I know, I haven't seen the Glass,
is Glass the sequel, what's the sequel?
Glass is the sequel that brings together.
The McEvoy thing.
Them and what is the McEvoy thing?
I don't remember.
Yeah.
It was a secret, oh it's in the same universe.
It's as if like one of the Yellowstone characters
showed up on the end of Tulsa King.
That's what it was like for this, the Knight universe.
Have you now determined that Tulsa,
it doesn't seem like Tulsa King's in.
Well, I don't think it is.
But you're saying that if suddenly there was an episode
where Jack Yellowstone showed up,
which is what I assume Kevin Costner's character's name is,
it's not about the place, it's about the Yellowstone family.
Exactly, so because there's a prequel with Harrison Ford
that is in Yellowstone universe, I know that for a fact,
but it's not clear, they haven't said yes,
haven't said no, that Tulsa King exists in the same world.
Okay, now is there a dial of destiny anywhere in this?
A dial, I'm trying to think.
Let's just don't have a gold phone.
We don't want to date when this is recorded too much,
but we're all biting our tongues
from talking about cocaine bears and dials of destinies
and any other lackluster trailers
that have come out in the last 10 days.
No, it's not because when people are hearing this,
I believe if I'm not mistaken,
when people are hearing this is as the first podcast,
the ride of 2023, I think.
I think so. Unless we change it
and I take all this out.
Unless Bob J. Bick comes back
and then we have to bump this.
And do another, oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
that created a landslide for us, a little,
yeah, all the episodes slid, but so far,
currently this is slotted to at least be very early
in 2023 and I can't think of a better way
to kick off the year than by talking about
a heartwarming Disney art installation
featuring two entertainment icons.
And I'm referring of course to America's favorite
leading man and America's favorite sweetheart,
the posters at California Adventure.
And we will also talk about the partner statue,
which is the statue of Walt and Mickey holding hands
that's in Disneyland and many of the parks.
But I think this talk about the backside,
we've had so much stuff on our desk with Chay Pack
and Eiger and mostly Frank Marshall,
mainly it's been Frank Marshall material.
It's piling up all the Frank Marshall work.
But this, we haven't, I was like,
I need to take a second and digest this.
Do you know why I'm bringing this up?
I do, yes. I do.
The reveal. The solution.
Yeah, the problem has been solved.
It was figured out, this happened on Twitter
and people may have seen it on Twitter,
but if you didn't, let's explain this whole thing.
So a couple months ago, we did an episode
about these two posters outside of these bathrooms
at California Adventure that are oddly generic.
America's favorite leading man
is Hollywood's biggest star.
Similar statement about America's favorite sweetheart.
And it's a generic like 30s actor
and a generic 30s actress.
What is this?
We got nowhere closer, I would say,
in the episode to figuring it out.
And it's left us frustrated.
I know it's been keeping me up at night.
I assume that's what's keeping you up at night, Mike.
And not other things in your life.
Baby sleep in 14 hours while I'm awake.
Trying to crack the code, trying to figure it out.
You got absurdly lucky with the baby and yet.
Baby sleeps 14 hours right out of the womb.
No problems.
Unbroken.
But you can't, you're tossing and turning.
And this was clearly happening
to some listeners of the show as well
because it was clearly bugging a Twitter user,
traveling salesman at Open Mother's Mail.
And he clearly thinking about it.
And so the question is posed to two Imagineers
who are active on Twitter.
Lively Land, Kevin Lively, I believe,
and Tom Morris, one of my favorite Imagineers.
I love Tom Morris.
Yeah, the guy is, worked on,
designed the Disney Paris Castle.
I mean, a true great.
And now he is having to put some thought
into what the hell are these posters.
The replies both were very funny.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if I have all of them,
but I know one was like,
let's get it.
So the prompt was to the two of them,
I know both of you had nothing to do with these posters,
but what the hell is any of this weirdness
supposed to convey or communicate exactly?
So yeah, I don't have everyone's response.
Oh, I might not have their responses at all,
but both of them just like baffled.
Both of them like, I have no idea what that is.
Yes, yeah, and some notes.
We got a window into like Tom Morris' process,
like what he would say about it
if these posters came across his desk.
And then, so still confusion, nobody helped,
but then Twitter user Haston,
Haston, Haston, at Haston,
says this wasn't exactly an opening day thing.
There's a clue, first of all,
I think we said, we assume this has been there
since opening day, but apparently not.
These posters were put up in 2005,
but they were different.
They were part of, basically,
I don't know in what order to say this.
There, I'll just jump to the interesting part.
They're toilet paper ads.
Oh yeah.
It was a 10-year promotional deal with Quilted Northern.
Yes, and the bigger,
as we like to know our full partnerships and clunky names,
this was a partnership with Georgia Pacific,
the corporation that makes many fine paper products
and bath products, and this deal struck in 2005
made it so that for the next 10 years,
the Disney parks would be using brawny paper towels
and sponsoring the Lights, Motors, Action, Extreme Stunt Show
and that Dixie tableware would be
at Mickey's Backyard Barbecue Pavilion
and Chip and Dale's Campfire Singalong at Fort Wilderness.
I was, I needed to, I didn't realize how many proper names
I'd be saying all in one run.
Okay, but also none of that matters.
General napkins, cups, plates, and bowls
will all be coming from the fine people at Georgia Pacific
and especially the excellent toilet paper
produced by Quilted Northern.
So these posters were a little different
and as soon as I saw the original ones,
it was like something, like a Manchurian candidate prompt
was unlocked in my head where it's like, I have seen that.
Yeah.
That looks familiar now.
I understand.
It's all coming back now.
I had it on my laptop.
I was explaining all this to Aaron
and demonstrating how like, it probably just like,
they passed by me peripherally, blurry in my head,
just like, foop, like that's as much as,
I like, I maybe saw it in the corner of my eye
10 years ago or 15 years ago
and then I did it again seven years ago
until the fateful day that we talked about it for an hour
and made no particular progress.
But yes, I know what you mean.
It does feel familiar.
So now let's all look at what it actually was
in the beginning.
It's the same boring guy, the same 30s actor guy
who looks like he'd be in like a jet fighter movies.
That's right.
World War I ace.
And now the poster says,
America's favorite leading man is,
not Hollywood's biggest star.
He is strong yet gentle.
And then below that more text, which was cut,
quilted Northern bath tissue.
It's Hollywood's leading role.
So that's a clever thing.
That is something. That's an advertisement.
Yes. Yes.
It serves a function, which the others did not.
It was like absolutely impenetrable.
Why would they go out of their way to make the statement
that America's favorite leading man
is Hollywood's biggest star?
That means nothing.
Yeah, no, I know what it means.
As much as this is solving a problem,
I honestly have a couple more questions
that I don't think we still.
Absolutely.
Well, here, let me read the other one
and then for sure there are more questions.
Oh, and also both are still,
it's still a fictional magazine called Movie News.
And then you go to the other one,
America's Favorite Sweetheart.
And in both cases, they look mostly the same,
but a little different.
They're a little bigger.
Yeah.
Like facial features, inexplicably like 5% different.
So that's an unsettling thing about it right there.
Because they had to re-photoshop the whole thing.
It's not like they just placed something over the words.
No, certainly not.
No, a new image was printed.
But it does feel like they copied the same file
and just rearranged the elements.
And Movie News stayed the same.
America's Favorite Sweetheart is stayed the same.
Then it becomes clean and fresh.
Quilted Northern America's or Hollywood's leading role.
So these two, in theory, massive fictional movie stars,
their qualities just so happen to be like the toilet paper
you use on your bottom.
Yeah, so.
This woman is like something you rub your butt with.
Yes. Yes.
They're explaining that nice sentiment.
That Clark Gable man is strong.
And what's it strong in?
He is something yet, strong yet gentle.
Strong and gentle.
She is clean and fresh.
Clean and fresh.
Okay, good, you want that if you're wiping urine
on your urethra, you know, and your asshole.
Wait, you want to do what?
Your wife is wiping urine after,
if you are a lady using the bathroom.
You want the, yeah.
Are you wiping your urethra when you go to the bathroom?
Women, when they use the bathroom,
will use it both ways.
I was trying to say this in the most clinical way possible.
You mean peeing and pooping?
Yes.
As opposed to us, typically.
You mean in one position, we have two positions.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
If we, and if even if we,
even if we sit and go to the bathroom,
we don't wipe our urethra.
Right. Yeah.
But we wipe the, well the end of it, right?
The end of it?
The urethra's?
I don't know.
You don't think around in there?
What?
In your pee?
No, what are we discovering right now?
This is taking a turn.
No, no.
This is TMI alert.
No, I'm just saying like,
you're saying cause it's more exposed,
so you're getting in there.
That's what you're saying.
The urethra.
The women wipe everything down there with toilet paper.
Yeah, they're wiping no matter what they're doing down there.
I see. Okay.
I think I see what you're saying now.
I'm wiping my penis.
Sorry listener.
Okay.
Do you differ here?
I'm a little confused.
I'm confused again.
I got confused somewhere
and I don't know where I got confused.
I don't want to rehash this cause I'm-
Welcome to 2023 everyone.
I feel so confused right now.
I know what the, I know the basics of it.
Do you wipe your penis with toilet paper?
Sometimes.
Really?
Well, yeah, sometimes.
Well, if it's a little messy,
like if it's a little-
I'm saying yes, the shake.
Okay, now we're on the same page again.
If we're shaking,
or if it's a little drippy on the thing,
I'm just trying to be considerate.
If you're in a urinal,
of course there's no toilet paper there.
You gotta shake.
You're not gonna go grab,
you're not gonna go into a booth.
You gotta shake.
Toilet paper.
Rarely, yes, are you using that,
but once in a while, I suppose,
you go, well, I gotta, maybe there's something.
I don't, I don't.
I truly don't.
Am I in the extreme minority here?
This is maybe in the 1% time,
but I think there's maybe been a time or two.
Okay.
So I see, okay, I understand what we're talking about now.
Yeah, okay, okay.
Well, that adds to confusion if sometimes, all right.
Yeah, I think you rethrew us all for a loop.
I think you rethrew it really confused me.
Okay.
It's not your fault.
I am not mad.
Now I know all of your peeing habits,
which is nice to know that you all keep it clean and fresh,
being that we're all holding each other's hands
while recording this episode.
Yes.
Look, whether pissing or shitting,
Quilted Northern is there.
It's there for you.
It's a Hollywood classic.
From now on, and I don't want to.
If you have to spit your gum out,
so that's another use case.
See now, okay, now I'm realizing now,
if you're listening to me, the whole chunk we just did,
you're thinking that maybe I have like little squares
of toilet paper that I carry with me everywhere I go,
and I use that.
I don't think there's a go.
I don't know that anyone, yeah, was thinking that.
Maybe some, or maybe the 1%, 1% of people thought that.
Okay, well.
I'm no freak.
I'm no pee freak.
Okay, I'm not a pee freak.
And Mike does not.
I just want to lay it out there.
I want to be clear about my friend.
He does not take squares of toilet paper,
clean pee off with them,
but then keep the pee squares
and use them for anything else later.
No, I don't do it.
I'm not that guy.
I don't think I'm that guy.
Yes, okay.
I think the thing is,
whether you're pissing and shitting,
and however you identify biologically or.
Everything's great.
Whatever you want to do, they're great.
Quilted Northern is there for you.
And the toilet paper is not going to rip when you're wiping.
It's not going to rip.
It's strong enough to get all the pieces.
Like America's favorite leading man would be.
We talked about what that character requires,
and it requires some dashing and machismo, you think,
but also soft.
It actually kind of breaks down a lot of what we got into
in that episode of what are the,
like kind of the duality that a leading man needs to have.
But sort of the bigger question,
the answers we got, I feel like,
raised more questions than answers.
Because then it led to, okay,
so this is generation two of these posters.
And yeah, they copied the file.
They removed some layers in a Photoshop file
and shrunk some proportions.
And they're like,
we got to take the branding out,
but we got to have these folks back.
They got to go back in the case.
It can't be a blank wall.
People are going to, at this point,
expect to see posters after they leave the bathroom.
So upset, yeah.
And they couldn't just be posters for the rides
or something, or like Disney movies.
Yeah, for like, yeah, Disney movies from the 30s,
the era you're generally trying to convey.
They absolutely not.
It's got to be these two.
Has to be these two.
People, it's like, there's stuff you can't get rid of.
You can't get rid of a pirate.
You can't get rid of a haunted mansion.
You can't get rid of the toilet paper posters.
At this point, people are in love
with the toilet paper people.
Yes.
They got to be there.
And we need to like give someone a new task to do.
They have to go open up an old Photoshop file,
make something that's technically new, but mostly not.
We need to reprint that and then put it in the parks
in one of the most biggest attended theme parks
in the world.
These have to be seen by people.
And no jokes, no fun jokes about it.
Because it's not a reference anymore to the toilet.
Like it's not.
You wouldn't read that.
We're no longer playing with the joke
of comparing an iconic actor to an iconic toilet paper.
Right.
Now we're just comparing an actor to a different way
you would explain what an actor.
Right.
Now it's just, there used to be kind of like a little,
an A to B and now it's like A to B kind of.
Right.
No, it's not B.
It's A to A-ish.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Like what didn't, like, did anyone try it?
Like America's favorite leading man,
he makes all the ladies flush with color.
Like there's gotta be a toilet joke.
To make it still bathroom.
It's still bathroom.
Cause they're both there when you come out of the bathroom.
Cleans up at the box office.
Cleans up, perfect.
Yeah.
Jason, you got one?
His new movie.
He wipes the competition, wipes away the competition.
That's a good idea.
His new movie, they dumped it on home video.
Like anything.
Home video would be a blessing nowadays.
Sure.
Yeah, you're lucky if it comes out at all.
He wipes his urethra when he's done
to make sure he's extra clean.
So your preference would have been that it stays bathroom
affiliated.
Well, I just don't know, it's nothing.
So why wouldn't someone take a stab at
making it related to the area?
Just put like a Snow White poster
and a Steambot Willie or Mickey's trailer.
Like a cartoon poster and a movie poster, you know?
Yeah, you could do that.
And then you could take those posters
and make them toilet themed.
You're still, you got caught on,
isn't there the possibility though
that you kind of forget why it's there
and that you're looking at a thing
and like, why is it about toilets?
Even if you just went to the bathroom,
because you've left the bathroom.
That's the confusing thing about these.
They aren't in the bathroom.
If it's in the bathroom, for sure make it bathroom related,
but it's not.
So you maybe, you're done.
You're not thinking about the bathroom anymore.
You have to crane your neck to look at them
if you're going in, if you're seeing them when you go in.
When you're coming out, you're looking right at them.
And maybe by that point,
you're ready to be done with bathroom business.
I don't want to think about the bathroom anymore.
Just spent a while in there
cleaning up my urethra with squares.
As if I had like, as if I cut myself shaving.
I am dab dab dab.
Cleaning my urine with little squares.
But here, here's what I would argue
is that since that whole area is a little bit blocked off,
obviously that the famous wall is on the other side.
So- Frank Lloyd Wright wall.
Frank Lloyd Wright wall, who cares?
Toilet wall.
Toilet wall is on the other side, is what we like.
So toilet wall is there and it's all blocked off.
So that's, in my mind, that's sort of the New Orleans square
of the pirate's ride, is that little hallway.
That's the, this is the bathroom area.
So this whole area should be themed
within the bathroom universe.
It needs to be supporting the big attraction,
which is the bathroom.
Right, these two most need to support the big attraction,
which is the toilet.
I'm glad we're examining this
on the Partners statue episode.
This might be its own episode, right?
A topic reading about, I was like,
well, there's a lot more here than I thought there would be.
So we still have to do a long episode.
Okay, well, let's look, we, there's maybe not
much more to say, but- There are multiple generations
with the phrase partners involved
that I'm sure we'll get into in terms of lithographs
and statues. We gotta get to all the partners then.
But for now,
what's the conclusion?
I mean, we are, it is, it's like it closed one chapter,
but the answer's more confusing than this.
Which is kind of what, that was where the listeners
were left, which was like, well, somebody said,
I know nothing about these toilet paper ads.
Were they in Hollywood Pictures' backlot?
Long time Imagineer, Tom Morris, apparently.
And then later, then there's, then Kevin Lively jumps in
and says, he grew a mustache.
Tom Morris says, and ditched the lipstick.
And that's accurate.
In the original one, he, the actor does not have
a little thin mustache.
He has bright red lips, but no mustache.
So in addition to taking the toilet paper branding out,
they also kind of changed the physical appearance
of the guy, maybe darkened the hair.
What is this?
What was this assignment?
Make sure you put on a mustache.
And wait, okay, actually Quilted Northern technically
owns the guy if he's got big swollen lips.
Oh, maybe that is what it is.
But if you take the lips down a notch
and give him a mustache, then he's ours.
Then Disney owns it.
It's Quilted Northern IP.
I guess the question is, how far back
do Disney Imagineering Outlook email archives go?
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And if you, well, maybe we gotta,
because there's one person who knows.
One person did this assignment.
Yeah.
They can answer what the assignment was
and how long it took them
and how long they were asked for it to,
like, because probably it was like,
you got 45 minutes, go.
Yeah, yeah, I mean, probably.
What would be the other, yeah.
Because you would, anybody in Imagineer,
you think it's a dream factory.
We're here to be creative.
You would think they would be like,
we'd love to spend a day trying to figure out
some fun new ways to present these characters.
You would think. We would.
Look how much time we've willingly devoted.
We've done a lot.
We've devoted barely paid to talking about them.
Right.
If we could kind of like take this franchise on
as our own, the care that we would put into it.
This is the stuff they could farm out in Imagineering.
Yeah.
Poster work, punch up, taking the branding off
of certain advertisements and making them now
not specific to the company that started there.
Let's start on the poster.
Make somebody do it who doesn't understand the history here
or you can have us do it.
We'll be nerding out as if we're getting to work on
the dial of destiny.
Right.
We'd be on that set, who cares?
What's this hat?
I'm gonna put my coffee on it.
We have no care for that mythology.
But these guys and this mustache and this toilet paper,
we're steeped in this.
The Toilet E ticket needs support
and needs theming around it.
And we're also the only people who understand that.
Yeah.
If anyone is left who listens and works
for the Walt Disney Company or subsidiaries,
I'm telling you, you could go in the D23 offices
and they're like, we need some Easter egg merch.
We need some real deep pulls.
We've given you, we've unearthed Leonardo Columbus.
We've unworthed the toilet duo.
That's right.
We are like, we are voluntary scrapers
of the bottom of their barrel.
That's right.
That's what we do.
We scrape it.
We're in there and no one asked us to get in there.
But we're finding IP and this is what we want
is to find every, they all, everybody wants
to find every scrap of IP.
We're doing it left and right.
Yeah.
And we deserve a little thanks.
The recent architects of the recent time, you know?
This isn't even, this is,
their big promotion this year
is that the 100th anniversary of the company.
God knows what's in there, those files.
Going back to 20s and 30s, the 1920s and 30s.
Yeah.
And we, so we get into the archives and we're like,
skip, skip, skip, skip, skip, where's oh five?
Great.
Wow.
The original, the toilet paper branded actor and actress.
In the first draft of Bolt, he took a big shit
and they eventually used that big shit in Pinocchio.
It's the same shit?
It's the same shit.
They save like, you know, Robert,
we already have a huge library of digital shit assets.
We have, we're gonna have to render it.
We're gonna have to run the Unreal Engine on it a few times.
It's very rudimentary.
It was much more simple in Bolt's era,
but if you want the shape and consistency of that shit,
we're happy to give that to you.
We have the license for a freeware program
that hasn't been supported since 2007.
So as long as this one computer can do it,
it can get us to a point,
then then we can import it into modern premiere.
And if you wanna do a scene, just the spitballing,
if you wanna do a scene where they go up
Monstro's urethra,
maybe that's something we could do this time.
We could love.
And then they block the hole
to make sure nobody else can get in there
with a huge toilet paper square.
And you, and there needs to be two toothbrushes
in the morning, one for his teeth
and one for his urethra to clean it.
Well, that's what I, yeah, I don't use toilet paper
because I brush my urethra every morning.
Don't you guys?
Yeah, no, I brush my urethra too.
I of course do that as well.
Swirls, don't just up and down.
You count one, two, three on each side,
on each side, each corner.
I use one of those children's toothbrushes
that plays a song.
So it tells you how long.
Oh yeah, that's smart.
Happy birthday.
I hear happy birthday every morning.
You feel like it's your birthday
having a sparkling clean urethra.
Give ourselves a catheter every morning.
Well, the partner statue.
The partner statue.
The statue of Walt and Mickey standing next to you.
This is how you thought this one would go, right?
Yeah, hey, you know, when you go into Disneyland especially
or the Magic Kingdom or other places we'll get into it,
the right in the hub, in the centerpiece of it all
is a beautiful statue of Walt and Mickey holding hands
and Walt looking upon his creation.
And we've talked now, nobody's thinking about urethras now.
We've talked our way into a classic, classy element
of the parks that's been there in Disneyland since 1993.
Yeah, how about it?
And then that's the evidence
and that's all we have to say about it.
We're all dying to get,
well what do we have to say about the partner statue?
It's one of those things where I knew it was newer
but I really was like, oh yeah, it's like new.
That's weird, right?
Yeah, I for sure remember Disneyland before it and after.
That's like right when I was,
that's like middle of childhood
and me being like a Walt nerd,
me being a kid who did a voluntary Walt speech
at an assembly for no reason,
I was like, wow, this is great.
They are finally giving Walt the tribute.
Wow, so you remember being there when it happened
and you were like, finally.
Wow, interesting.
I thought it was great.
I thought Walt was cool.
Sure.
It was great to honor the legacy
and to give us an exact height referential
of how tall they think Mickey is as opposed to Walt.
Yes.
It ends up being confusing because if you're a child,
perhaps you have met Mickey Mouse mere feet away
earlier in the street that you're walking up
and Mickey was as tall as your mom.
Now you're all the way down the street
and here is somebody taller than your dad
and Mickey is down at his knees.
Right, it is a very good point.
And it is something, you think there was ever
a consideration that they would have Walt
like arm in arm with a full-sized
Mickey mascot performer sized thing.
I bet, I bet they talked about it.
Yeah. Yeah.
I guess it's like, where did they leave this with Walt?
I guess, are there things where,
yeah, wait, there is.
You know what there is?
There's that photo that's like a silhouette
where it was taken in Walt's home.
I want to say in less please, where there's,
he is like, he's either shaking hands with Mickey
or Mickey's like in the hallway.
You know that picture I'm talking about?
Vaguely.
It's like used on a lot of book covers.
Sure, exactly.
And it's like the suit Mickey, it's a, it's big Mickey.
No, no, it's a, it is a shadow Mickey who is smaller.
So I think the mythology, I think the mythology
when Walt was alive was Mickey's a little guy
or Mickey's a little guy in that thing
where Michael Eisner meets Mickey
and they have the watches of each other.
Oh, right. Yes.
Yeah. I mean, that makes sense.
Like he was like, the original Mickey was tiny.
It was a cartoon.
I understand why they would do it, but the only reason,
yes, is what you're saying is like,
Mickey then doesn't scale correctly in Disneyland
and he doesn't look like the other versions of Mickey.
The reference point that I saw that they used
was the one time an animated Mickey
shook a real person's hand, which is the moment in Fantasia.
Yes.
Oh yeah, they use it as a, as a like a, yeah.
As a template for how it would look
and the scale of which I think they would play
off each other.
Yeah. They also, it was apparently Walt's wishes
to not make a statue of him anywhere.
When he was alive, he's like, do not make a statue of me.
And eventually they had to ask for permission
to do the statue.
They waited decades for Walt's ghost
to really go elsewhere before angering him essentially.
Cause he'd been dead for so many years before this,
they started putting these around.
Yeah. Make sure he's fully dissipated
or at least if the ghost is still around
that he's, there's a number of places he wants to be.
Cause they've, they've opened Disney World by now
and maybe Tokyo, Disney, let's say,
and, and, and, and, and Euro and Paris.
So Walt does, Walt's ghost is like split.
His attention is split.
So they can get away from him for a minute
and make a statue of him.
Okay. Cause he would have started like haunting
the different, the builders.
Yes.
Of the statue at home and stuff.
You went against my wishes.
Cutting brake lines on cars and stuff.
It would have been a real disaster.
He could have gotten inside the statue
and then did like it shakes off.
He could still do that.
Yeah. That's still possible.
That would be the day.
Statue comes to life.
Oh man.
People gathered around it, taking pictures
and all of a sudden crack, crack, crunch.
And then he takes the Mickey that is not alive
cause Mickey's not dead.
So Mickey can't haunt the statue.
Right.
So that's just a big hunk of bronze.
Oh man.
So he just takes that and like whips it into a crowd.
Everybody goes running, streaming.
Oh my God.
You know what the first thing he does is he goes
to galaxy's edge and gets rid of that alcohol
in the cantina.
What?
I assume he sounds deeper because he's.
Yeah. Yeah.
He sounds like a monster.
He sounds like a holo.
Oh don't fly patients.
No.
And then he's strong.
He's made of bronze.
He cracks all those big jugs.
Right.
Like socks that space frog right in the face.
Well he gets rid of it by drinking it all.
Only for me.
So now you have a super drunk.
Paul bronze ghost.
So do I.
I need to sleep in the firehouse.
You left a light on right.
The light gives me power.
I guess my, the thing that I didn't know about this
and a lot of this is coming from a piece on all ears.net
from Disney historian, Jim Corcus.
Did you guys read this?
I did.
I think so.
Okay. So Michael Eisner takes over
and he starts doing a lot of short run events
to try to juice attendance.
A lot of which involves putting big stuff in the hub.
In front of the castle.
Yes.
Cause it's a pretty big open area saying worse.
You know, if you're doing something temporary
it grabs your attention.
So there was a Ferris wheel, I believe
when they did a state fair.
Yeah. We had a episode about that.
What else?
There was like maybe like circus stuff.
Circus.
Yeah.
Episode bank that episode.
So yeah, big splashy things.
But then it became that,
was it that there are factions who can't agree on,
do we, I don't want stuff in front of the castle.
That diminishes it.
Or is that, oh, does there also just kind of a rise of
we want to make sure people remember Walt Disney.
But even that is like a business decision.
Even that's them going.
Yeah, it's a character we own.
Yeah. Yeah.
And we need to get him out there.
That costs us no money.
Right.
Specifically he pointed to Marty Sklar and John Hench
going like, well, we don't want all this stuff in the hub.
But also we think it's been, it's been two years
or two decades plus since Walt's death.
Two decades.
And we think we've, the people have forgotten his impact.
And it is mentioned, this guy, Corcus mentions how they like,
you know, for example,
many might enjoy eating a Hershey chocolate bar,
but had no idea there was a man named Milton Hershey
to thank for their enjoyment.
All of us just glutton's chowing down Hershey bars.
And we don't say thank you to anyone.
We should all say thank you, Milton.
Thank you, Milton.
Jason says thank you, Milton.
I assure you in Hershey, Pennsylvania and Hershey Park,
they do not let you forget about Milton Hershey.
There is no worry about that.
But is he, is there any, I don't,
I can't imagine there's a statue of him.
But on one of these rides or exhibits,
is there ever a thing like,
there's Milton, is he ever like dressed up
or like made into a cartoon or given goofy eyes,
like on that bread tour, or like,
here's the family that made the bread.
Chocolate, blah.
I think in various versions of the Chocolate World ride.
Which is some-
There's some Milton Hershey
and there's definitely some exhibit space.
Do you get to like, did he have an apartment in Hershey Park
that you get to go in that's secret
and has a little lamp that he used to light?
This little chocolate light.
I don't know, I mean-
The brown light stays on.
And then hits him in hand in hand
with a chocolate bar and the statue.
Hershey Park was really,
they really lean into the like origins of the park of like,
then this was for the factory workers to enjoy leisure.
So that meant there was a lot of outdoor greenery space
and a couple of attractions that grew over the years.
You know?
See, we built you this, now shut up.
Now shut the fuck up.
Keep working.
You can see-
Thank you, Milton.
Don't hit me again, thank you, Milton.
You can see a non-union actor play him
in like the Food That Built America
or like those various history channel shows
that I really obsessed with.
I do love, so I think it was like
the first few months of lockdown.
I just watched hours of these shows
and they just make all of these guys.
The Campbell Soup Guy, Colonel Sander.
They all just look like lunatics.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
They all are like, I am taking this Hershey's bar
with almonds and I'm gonna ruin you with it.
Like the Kellogg's brothers, I think.
It's all like the founder type stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
Can we get away with an episode about Colonel Sanders?
Is that in our purview?
Yeah, I think so.
Cause I like, yeah, any special about him
is the insane as shit-
He's a mad man.
You've ever heard.
Yeah, because that TV show,
it followed the phrase like,
well, Colonel Sanders shot him, but he didn't kill him.
Uh.
What I'm, here, I don't know if I wanna give it away,
but what I remember is that there's some story
where he's in like an old car that crashes
and his brain spills out.
Well, I've never heard this.
And then he just collects it and puts it back in.
No.
And like mats it with mud.
There we go.
What?
All good.
He's definitely a guy.
Yeah, oh for sure.
Yes.
And like, I think sexually crazy a little too.
And like, or if not sexually,
that sounds like, I just know he like immediately
like cheated on his wife at the first,
like they hired-
When he got famous?
The company was only him and his wife.
And as soon as they hired a third employee,
they fry cook, he was cheating with the fry cook.
Like I met another woman.
I am cheating instantly.
Wow.
I didn't know.
I don't know a lot, I guess about Colonel Sanders.
There we go.
I mean, what?
I think it's in there.
Just the sheer amount that he was sanded down
to like a squeaky clean Mickey Mouse S mascot,
both in America and in Japan and other parts of Asia.
Oh, where they were.
KFC very popular.
And I believe it's either Christmas or Thanksgiving.
There was like one year,
there was an aggressive push on that holiday
of like have KFC for Christmas.
And then it just stuck around.
It's a tradition now.
Well, it's in Colonel Sanders put it on the list.
2023, we need a lot of ideas on the list.
Very productive at the end of 2022.
We're collecting a lot.
So I think maybe, all right, so they wanna do sit.
They wanna like honor Walt, make sure people remember Walt
and put something in the hub that is permanent.
So there's no more gaudy Ferris wheels.
Yeah, cause if they had waited too long,
the X games would have been there.
Oh, for sure.
Like I was like the only reason
it's just shy of the X games squeezing in there.
The premiere of Mission to Mars
projected in front of the castle.
So maybe at this point is a good point
to bring in the sculptor, Blaine Gibson.
Like one of the greats in Disney history
and Imagineering history, like the sculptor for sure,
who started as an assistant animator
but was taking sculpting classes at night
at Pasadena City College.
So hired to do one thing very well
in this classic Imagineer way.
And then they turn out to be like the ultimate genius
in another category that wasn't even
what they were hired to do.
I've always liked this guy whenever I,
like as a kid, when the statue went up
or just looking into, so who does all this stuff
and who molds the presidents and Lincoln?
You see this name and God, he's great.
Everything he touches is great.
When it was debuted, did you know that,
oh, this is Blaine Gibson?
Or did you know shortly?
Think I was dorky enough to possibly be.
I mean, I was pretty young then.
That's like pretty dorky.
At least within the, yeah, yeah.
But that's one of those names that's accessible.
You get a book and there's a photo of a guy, you know,
putting the last touches on the pirate
and often that's gonna be the name that you.
Oh yeah.
Or not on the, well, you know, on the busts
because he made the busts that then the animatronics are.
He is batting a thousand in terms of theme park stuff.
Tiki Room, Pirates of the Caribbean, Haunted Mansion,
sculpted all the Hall of Presidents except Obama,
which he came out of retirement to consult on.
He also came out of retirement to do this statue.
He did, oh yeah, he retired in 83.
So everything after that, which was a lot,
they would specially contract him
and he would do it all in Sedona, Arizona,
where he retired to.
And in some cases, I think this sculpture,
he had an assistant who like did all of the hard work
because he's an old man by this point,
but he like did the initial design and supervised it.
The Presidents thing is crazy.
Like, cause imagine when Hall of Presidents opens
and there's how many presidents by then,
at least like 35, I don't remember what,
I don't know what the number Nixon is.
That's what it went up to.
But that's so many.
It's a lot.
And people who we have photos of,
a pirate of the Caribbean,
you can make look like whatever goofball you want,
but these are all people we have photographs of.
And Lincoln did not, you can't shake a stick at that.
That's a big one.
Yeah, it's huge.
It's great.
So he, yeah, he's like,
cause he died a couple of years ago at 95, I believe.
So what, 30 years ago, he was six in his sixties.
He was very old and still making every president,
every time he's a new president,
which the pressure on that to like,
if you don't, people don't really know
what James K. Polk looks like,
you can get away with it,
but like you need to do Reagan or Reagan's everywhere.
We know what, or even less, especially later,
like, you know, like Clinton's the hugest celebrity
with before he's even in office.
Right, right.
And they gotta make him.
Would he have made the Trump robot look better?
This is a very good question.
It is, if you think about that timeline,
he didn't do Obama,
but he had a couple like thoughts on Obama.
Trump is the first one with absolutely no input
from Blaine Gibson.
And a lot of people like the fan fiction or real fiction,
a real life, like a speculation that like,
oh, they're getting back at Trump
with this weird looking robot.
But what if it's just because Blaine Gibson was not there.
He would have unlocked the most handsome.
Beautiful of Donald John Trump.
That would have made us all go, actually,
he's really maybe the ultimate example of man.
That's right.
So there wouldn't have been booing during that show.
I love the other rumor that it was just,
they had already started on the Hillary statue
and then they just fucked it up a little
and put it on Trump's face.
Stretch him.
Just stretch, just, he's a wide boy.
He's a wide man.
Yeah, I don't know.
It is interesting.
How could it, it might've changed public perception.
I still, you know,
yeah, it would've, it would've told the whole thing.
He'd still be president now.
He, Trump himself would have seen the robot
and been inspired to turn over a new leaf.
To be a better man.
That's right.
I need to be hit.
This is how the world sees me.
I need to be this.
I think it's funny how no one talks about Biden robot.
Joseph. I don't really know
what it looks like.
I don't. Yeah.
I mean, I saw it once when they debuted it.
Joseph Robinette Biden looks pretty good.
It looks pretty, pretty close to him.
And they got it in there fast.
Yes. The Trump went to forever.
So I always took that as like, yeah, this kind of sucks.
We're going to drag our heels on this asshole.
If he, if Biden is still the president somehow in 2028,
I don't know if that robot is going to look.
The math adds up.
I think they maybe don't have to get whoever today's Blaine
is to come in and do what all the, or like,
what if it did, maybe a Disney sculptor is the person
making Biden look as good as he looks now.
Oh, good point.
Good question.
Maybe he is part bust.
There's a lot.
There are a lot of imagineers working
on the Biden actual man.
People who joke is they don't need animatronics anymore,
but we do need an animatronic to be the president.
Right.
There's a lot of actuators,
a lot of Disney magic happening in the white house.
When a part fuses on the shaman of song, they throw it out.
And then somebody grabs it from a dumpster
and puts it into bite.
It just needs a new battery.
We're all good.
And then he goes, yeah, back to normal.
Feeling great. Seamless.
So this guy, oh, and also like, think about this one.
Great movie ride.
I don't know if they're all him on great movie ride,
but he did some of them.
These are current icon or like classic icon.
I mean, just so many of the Disney historical,
real person now presented in this artificial form
was Blaine Gibson, clearly a master.
Amazing.
So if you're gonna entrust somebody
to make the icon of the company, this is the guy to do it.
Jason, as you said, they did give this a go in 62.
Blaine Gibson makes a bust of him at the command of.
This story is very funny.
At the urging of Dick Irvine, a Imagineer guy at the time.
He makes Walt Disney.
He makes a Walt Disney bust.
They give it to Walt.
When he, Blaine claims, I don't think it was that good.
I was tired, working late at night.
The foundry work was no good.
So he puts the blame on himself.
I'm not sure that that's,
I think Walt would have said this to anything
because his quote becomes, when it's given to him,
he does not say thank you.
He says, what am I going to do with this?
Statues are for dead people.
He's not wrong.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's also like in terms of 20th century myth making,
I feel like powerful people and it's like, oh yeah.
And they would, they could kind of be really rude sometimes.
And that was just sort of not mine.
Back then, not anymore.
Now they're, now powerful people.
Not anymore.
Now they're just liars.
Now they just love to lie.
They didn't lie before, but they were mean.
And now, they're not mean, but they lie.
It's like a lateral move.
Evolution of that.
That's what happens.
Billionaire.
Pretty simple.
So now, Blaine Gibson is insecure.
He thinks this has been a fool's errand.
This makes the story much more dramatic.
Right.
Because the statue goes up in 93 and you think,
well, of course they want to tribute Walt,
but you don't realize that there's been a 30 year,
it's been built up in Blaine's head.
He's thinking, he's remembering this moment.
The man himself said, I don't like this.
Why did you do this?
Yes.
And then he, and then he kept it.
He put it in his garage.
The original clay bust is in his garage.
And he could, he said, I couldn't bring myself
to put a hammer to it.
Even though he might've been tempted,
it might've been a good way to get your aggression out
on the boss who was so mean when you presented it.
Yeah, why would he say that unless every night
that hammer was like talking to him on the tool bench
while he came in every night.
The hammer was there, excuse me.
No, no, I can't.
He's like fighting his own arm.
It's really sturdy, low humidity in Sedona
in Southern California.
So you're going to have to smash it with me.
Take his nose off slowly with the two prongs
on the other side of the hammer that I don't know
the name of what they're called.
Chip, Chip and Dale.
This is the hammer's quote where he doesn't know
what the back of him is called.
This is a hammer that doesn't know the names
of the pieces of a hammer.
Whatever, what's my part called?
I think it's a urethra.
Take my urethra.
Yeah, take it to your boss's head.
Oh wait, no, I thought that was the handle.
Grab my urethra.
He made a sketch of himself sculpting the bust
and with Walt next to him saying,
that dummy thinks it looks like me.
They're haunted, this man.
Yeah, yeah.
This is like, he thought it was his biggest failure
in a history of major successes, robots we all see every day
but then he finally, well first good news, Walt dies.
Yeah.
So he doesn't have Blaine to kick around anymore.
Then years later, Cal Arts, which Walt contributed to
wants a medal and they want on the medal
to be a headshot of Walt.
So he's called upon to put this together
and I don't know if this happened or not actually
but Walt's widow, Lillian, still alive,
tells Blaine, I don't ever want a bust or a portrait
or a statue of Walt to be done.
So he gets his ass handed to him again.
By the wife.
We're trying to honor.
He's like, obviously like, I want to honor this man.
And then we're like, don't you fucking do it.
This is my purpose on this earth to use my hands.
Blaine, I'll kill you if you make a statue of my husband.
And he's like, oh my God.
I don't want him back in 3D in my life.
He's gone, I'm happy.
He could, if you make a statue, there's a good chance
he haunts the statue and he comes back to life.
If he haunts a medal.
He can haunt a medal.
Immediately that thing starts swinging around
on the recipient's neck and then maybe like tries to burrow,
bite into his chest.
Don't you know that souls can enter sort of facsimiles
of themselves once they're dead, if they're created.
They're after light pipelines, they're wormholes.
That's how it works.
Well, that's why the statue has the sinister looking
smoke tree ranch insignia on the tie and the Irish,
I don't know how to say this, cladagh ring.
Oh, he's got two, he's got the two rings.
I didn't look it up before either.
He's got the two wedding rings.
Yeah, it's the symbol where it's-
Maybe a hard C, like cladagh.
It's two hands and a heart and a crown.
And it's a traditional like design,
a traditional ring design that I believe he went to Ireland
and brought them back for him and Lillian.
Cladagh is what I just heard.
I still will not remember that and say,
well, we don't have to keep saying it.
It's his Irish wedding ring.
That's the point.
Right.
It is a design that I'm like, as soon as I saw it,
similar to the toilet posters, I was like,
oh yeah, I know lots of people who have one of those.
Wait, as it's similar in that you know-
As soon as I saw it, I was like, oh yeah,
I know what that is.
I didn't know the name of it.
There was familiarity.
I'm very familiar with it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
So anyways, look, the company has made it clear
they don't want, or not the company, I guess.
The family.
The family, Walt doesn't want it.
Lillian doesn't want it.
Then Lillian's gone.
Now they can do whatever they want.
The idea that this happens, that like,
I know the man really did not want a statue of himself,
but it's in our best interest to deify him,
so we need this statue.
In a succession-esque play,
between veteran Imagineers as a stopgap
from like Michael Eisner putting
like a Goodyear blimp in the hub.
Yeah.
Yeah, he just puts up, yeah, carnival games.
Or yeah, like has people,
the craft fair is set up in Main Street.
The Wiener, Wiener-mobile that's parked
in front of the castle.
He's gonna put up like just one hotel room,
one hotel suite, just one adorned, like a bungalow.
But they start, okay,
they start coming around on this stuff.
There is a lithograph,
is this what you're talking about, Jason?
Yeah, I gotta talk.
The lithograph was made to commemorate the two,
is it the 200th million Disneyland guest?
100th million Disneyland guest in 1981.
And there's also Partners in Excellence is a pin
given to, they say 2% of cast members
for like exemplary service.
But yeah, so the lithograph was made
and only sold to cast members.
And I have the picture here,
and I don't wanna push you guys to an opinion,
but there's a sinister energy coming off this picture.
And I don't know what it is.
If it's just the sheer amount of brown,
if it's just the design.
Hold on, let me take a look at this.
This piece. His sassy arm.
So what you're showing us, this is a drawing
that is like the Partners statue,
but it's in color and Waltz is in a very tan suit
and he's got an arm out
and he's holding kind of a drawn Mickey's hand.
I like it. I like it.
I like the statue.
I don't know that I think it's sinister.
You like it.
I think he's got, Waltz kind of got like a,
I'm a little teapot arm going with the like,
that's his, like he's making the handle, not the spout.
Well, how do you, what's your sinister,
what is the, it's something about the suit?
I don't know.
I think it's just the color scheme.
It feels like it's not colorful enough
for something this whimsical.
Do you feel like maybe it's like faded?
Like you're kind of finding it creepy
because it's, it feels old to you
and like it's like a relic of the past.
I think the paper it's on and the suit are like,
have faded to too similar.
It feels like the suit is your thing.
You don't like a tan suit.
No, well, I was furious when Obama came out
in that tan suit.
We all know that.
Destroyed the presidency.
Do you have a tan suit, Jason?
I did in high school.
Really?
And it was one of the most uncomfortable fabrics
I've ever touched.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Oh, you think it's psycho-psychological?
Bad memories about tan suits.
I think it's the way, I don't know.
It might be the way they're clasping.
Like Mickey feels too little.
What do you, do you think there's something?
I think there's.
I don't know.
I find it fine.
Yeah, I don't know that I can attribute any.
Sinister is a strong word for sure.
It's probably too strong of a word.
I just think it's, it's odd.
Yeah, it's just off.
It's strange.
The lack of the background maybe.
If you're, so you're saying that if you worked
for the Disney company in 1981,
and you've been there for years,
and that the perk that you get is the opportunity
to buy this picture with your money.
You don't think that's gonna make you feel good.
I don't know if I'm spending my, what's the exchange?
Probably like $20.
20 whole 1981 dollars.
I'm not made of lithographs.
Look, I gotta buy, look,
I gotta buy a lot of cigarettes, okay?
Get through this job.
Yeah, even.
I'm not gonna fit in at work, unless I.
I gotta buy cigarettes and Tab and Quaaludes.
Okay.
Would Walt, was there just like,
I mean, I know the answer to this,
but like wouldn't it have been nice in the old days
at one of these companies,
because you hear like, oh, working at Google,
they have a cereal bar, Pixar as well.
Like, oh, go to a cafeteria.
They have so much different food.
You go to these different places.
Like if Walt just had a big basket of free cigarettes
at the Disney company,
where you could go in and just take
whatever brand you wanted.
Different like.
That is like a, I feel like set decorators
do that a lot in movies and TV,
where there is like just a box on a coffee table
or a desk that you open it up
and there's just cigarettes inside.
And then a decorative lighter next to it.
So, I would think maybe.
I like the way you said TV.
I also know that.
There's a story about cigarettes,
and then it's also, and you see it on the TV.
Oh, the TV, the television.
I also noted, oh, that's a good way to say TV.
That ended up being the headline of the story to me.
We ignored everything else you said.
Cigarette bowls on the TV.
Well.
No, they're like, I think there was a very
related, you know, TV, I think, sparks a,
the era where cigarettes were around more often.
That's right.
Yeah.
That's what, Wal would have wanted that
instead of the statue.
He would have wanted a giant bowl of cigarettes
in the center of Disneyland.
Go in and reach.
Obviously you'd pay for it.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Somebody gotta give somebody a dollar, five dollars.
It would have been an A ticket.
That like, when it was still the ticket system.
Like, A, horse-drawn carriages, omnibus.
Cigarette.
Now it would have been an E, E cigarette ticket.
E cigarette.
Now you've got an E cigarette ticket.
That's where the Chapec arrow would have hit it.
He would have started.
Well, they were exploring gambling.
Yeah, that's right.
Were they?
To save ESPN.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I mean, it's whatever.
ESPN's been the biggest drag on the comedy for a long time.
And so like, if you can, if the incentive
while you're watching ESPN is to also gamble on an app.
Well, Fox was doing that a lot during the World Series.
Oh, okay.
That's DraftKings.
What is it?
It's rare.
There's a lot of different places, yeah.
So, it wasn't there yet where they were gonna
put slot machines in like, the Beauty and the Beast
restaurant, but I wasn't weighing.
It might have been the end.
Yeah.
They did spend a lot of lobbying money
stopping casinos from springing up in Florida.
Yes, but that's just because they didn't make the casinos.
Yeah, because they weren't making money.
But, Jim and Len mentioned that big cruise ship they bought,
like the partially built cruise ship,
the centerpiece of that cruise ship
was gonna be a casino.
So now it's like, ah, what to do, what to do.
Wait, they were really,
oh, that would have been the beginning?
Or wait, was it already a casino?
Like when they bought it?
Well, yeah, they bought it and they're like,
hey, you know, I don't know the sequence of events,
but like that cruise ship was designed
to have a casino in it.
That's the major centerpiece of it.
So now what does Disney do?
That could have been the point where it started.
This is the Disney cruise where you gamble.
The precedent.
And then it's, well, then we'll get it on the other cruises.
And now it's in the parks.
And now it's in the, you get like the ultimate VIP
risk suite in the top of the castle.
As long as you just keep, it's free,
as long as you keep playing.
And now there's a video poker on the thing
in front of you on pirates, on the chair in front of you,
the video poker machine.
For dad, if he's bored, he'll have like fun.
Well, they're watching all those people,
like the game that you put up to your forehead,
the cell phone game, they're looking like,
how do we monetize that?
How do we make it?
Well, they tried and they came up with some
of the most boring games I've ever played.
One of the most mind numbing app games.
What an era it's been.
But that is, if you look up most cruise lines
under amenities, it does say casino.
And that is like an oddity with the Disney cruise ships
where it's like, oh, there's no casinos on these cruise ships.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I wonder if they'll, yeah, that'll be,
they'll be curious, well, what Iger does with the ship
and then what does he, yeah, does gambling happen?
I think it does.
Yeah, yeah, why not?
I guess it does.
Everything's getting crazier and sleazier.
It all depends on the avatar box office,
which by now we will know.
Right.
As listeners will know.
Right, but we don't know, we're still in the dark on that.
We're still in the dark.
Yeah, yeah, I don't wanna, I will seem a fool
if I make any predictions.
Let's make some predictions.
I know.
Well, I'm just hoping at this point,
I have seen an avatar slot machine in Atlantic City
cause I feel like the Dune slot machines
were so fast coming out.
Well, some of them are video, so you can do it fat.
Like you don't have to, it's not like you have to install
a physical Navi.
Some of them are sort of just video screens,
so you can, they can just like download it, I think,
like one night and put it up.
Well, there are, there have been avatar slot machines,
for sure, it's just a matter of.
Widespreadness.
And do they update with way of water?
Are we gonna be, people are gonna be on the slot machines
and going, but where's Spider?
Will we love Spider?
That's what I'd like to, do you think you'll love Spider?
Or Spider might be bad, I don't know.
I will love Spider.
Are you gonna love, even if he's bad?
Well, I love the Joker, but the Joker's bad.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
He's a character, not necessarily one of the,
I think I love Spider.
Yeah. We'll see.
We'll see.
Okay, so where does that leave us?
Oh, they've, we're wearing down,
and now everyone who requested it is dead,
so now we can make this statue.
And in fact, before the partner statue is built,
there is a physical bust of Walt done in public.
Anybody know where it is?
Do you know offhand?
I do know where it is, and I've been there and seen it.
Yes, okay, then we're thinking the same thing.
That is the Academy Museum, the Academy headquarters,
the TV Academy headquarters in North Hollywood,
not very far from here.
I went there at lunchtime.
No, you did.
There's me and the man.
Wow.
And unlike the partner's statue, which is in a planter,
and it's elevated, this one you can walk right up to.
And in fact, you can go nose to nose with Walt
as I am doing in a photo, which you will see.
I'll put this on Twitter.
And have you ever been to this, Mike?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I know where it is, and I don't,
but I've never, I either didn't notice Walt was there
or I didn't, whatever.
I have been there though.
If you're around, oh, go ahead.
It's behind the Jimmy, it's behind the Jimmy Johns
and sort of around the corner
from the ice cream sandwich place.
Oh yes, yeah, I've been to the ice cream sandwich place.
I've been to the ice cream sandwich place.
This is Chipotle, Lemley Theater.
But if you're walking around there,
God knows if you're at the Jimmy Johns
because that's far from the only attraction.
You can see there's a Chuck Lorre that you can glare at.
I think I've said before on the show,
somehow this has come up before,
that everybody's got kind of like,
it's just plaques saying their name
and maybe who designed the plaque.
Or if like, oh, this is a television executive.
Chuck Lorre puts one of those fucking vanity cards,
you know how all his shows end with some big screed?
So there is just this massive paragraph that he wrote,
the last words of which are playing with my titanium penis.
So that is in this courtyard,
thankfully far away from Waltz.
He doesn't have to hear this filth.
But the main thing, here's why,
especially, I mean, both of you guys gotta get over there,
is you can get some nice quality time with Bill Frawley.
Here I am resting my head on Bill Frawley's shoulder.
Man, this is crazy that I walked over there,
but I guess I didn't,
I don't know why I didn't see Bill Frawley.
This is free entertainment.
Right.
If like, they used to live much closer to that
and it's really nice if you just like,
I wanna take a walk somewhere,
or this is Starbucks, just grab Starbucks,
and then you can walk around.
Dave's Hot Chicken's over there.
What's that?
Dave's Hot Chicken.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah. Right over there.
Oh yeah, well if you're going there,
then go, well just go eat it under,
you know, there's like steps and on this,
most of them are just on like little platforms,
but like Lucy and Desi are doing a little dance
on the steps, so you can like lay,
you can like be under their hands
and eat your lunch under them.
You can eat my lunch under Lucy and Desi.
Or like one person just put their Chipotle cup
on Bob Newhart.
So if you wanna litter next to the TV greats,
go to the Emmy headquarters on Lancashim and Magnolia.
That's a pretty good gag.
Like that's pretty on point.
For Bob Newhart.
Yeah, disrespecting.
If you like, he would have a good joke about that.
This sculpture garden, whatever you wanna call it,
was duplicated too for MGM studios.
Yes, that's right, yes.
And it's all the, yeah, it's like the same,
whatever company or entity that did it
and a lot of the same bus.
So there's a Walt there too, right?
And at both locations, there was a Bill Cosby
who has been removed and hopefully destroyed.
So that when he becomes a ghost, he cannot happen.
Ghost dad.
Then, oh no, ghost dad for real.
I hate that.
The Cosby one for some reason is the memory I have
of seeing a bust at Lancashim.
Wow, yeah.
I remember seeing, there might be a picture of child me
with bust Bill Cosby in MGM.
In Florida, yeah.
Because at the time when he, that's another here,
back to dorky me, I know, I think there's a photo of me
on a beach vacation at 10 years old
and I'm reading Bill Cosby's fatherhood.
What?
Yeah, like reading it on the beach.
Yes, yeah.
Wow.
Because I like the humor section.
I like sign language, Jerry Seinfeld's book.
Wow.
So you were reading all the comedians' books.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
I don't remember if I read,
what's the Tim Allen book called?
He had like a real best seller
because when he was dominating media.
Is there a naked man in the title?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Don't Stand Too Close to a Naked Man?
Is that the name of Tim Allen's book?
Don't Stand Close to, yeah.
That sounds familiar, but I can't remember.
Let me see, Don't Stand Too Close to a Naked Man.
Very good, wow.
Yeah.
Did you do the Dave Barry books too?
I think I may have,
because if you're looking at the humor section as a kid,
it's dominated by Dave Barry.
And I think I tried one and was like,
nope, not even me.
Not even I can handle this.
Back to Tim Allen.
Reading all the comedians' books as a kid,
that feels running parallel to the kids at like 11 or 12
who are like blitzing through Stephen King books.
And I never understood that.
I wasn't there yet.
I read a few Stephen King books in adulthood,
but at 12, I was like,
I wouldn't have known what to make of The Shining.
Oh God, no, yeah.
I made an annoyingly big deal out of like,
I liked Jurassic Park the movie so much
that I also read the book.
And I am pretending because that book is largely code.
Like big stretches of it are like,
here's this genetic.
And I read it.
Enough to like know that, oh,
the scene with the compies in Lost World,
that's from the original book.
And the lawyer is actually not a coward.
He's strong in the book.
Is that so?
I don't know.
And all I remember really is that
and that there were pterodactyls in the book,
but not the movie.
And I was so, I was like, yes.
I started the book a few years ago.
It didn't get very far.
My dad's read a lot of Michael Crichton.
And he, like when we were older,
and we were like, well, what's the book?
He's like, it's a lot more brutal.
It's a lot meaner.
And Hammond's an asshole.
Yeah, there's a lot of assholes.
Hammond's not a kindly old man or anything.
He's like a dick.
But that's like one of the five books I've read.
Mostly with 10 years old,
I was reading like Garfield mega collection.
Yeah, I was blitzing through goosebumps, you know?
Yeah.
I like Calvin Hobbes for me.
Anyway, point is, and that bust is by Blaine Gibson.
So same designer.
So if you wanna go see one,
if you wanna go get right up close to it,
if you wanna touch it, lick it.
Do whatever you want.
And that was made in 1991.
So look, we're coming around.
We can have the waltz that are physicalized
that we want so badly.
But what are we gonna do with it?
What's Walt gonna be doing?
Right.
And so they tried a couple of ideas.
I mean, it's not that interesting to list them.
The one that I like is that they were really
at some point pushing that it's Walt holding Mickey's hand,
but then Mickey has an ice cream cone.
And they decided that was far too juvenile.
What is it?
Silly, too silly.
Yeah, what does that mean?
They thought people think Mickey's a child
and not an adult?
That's what I did see a couple sources saying that like,
it's not that it's childish,
it's that it would make the character appear too childlike.
So you want- Like it's his son.
It's his adult son, it's not his child son.
But the statues, it's called partners,
you wanna make them seem equal.
Yeah.
So if it was one, first of all, Mickey already is shorter,
so just optic wise, you think,
oh, this is the child of this man.
So I guess the ice cream really makes it seem like a child.
Well, you might be stopped from thinking
it's the child of this man because he's a mouse.
He's a big mouse.
Well, but if you're far away
and you're like kind of squinting
and you're like, oh, it's a dad and his son, I guess.
Oh, there's the ice cream cone, that's his son.
Why is there a father and son up high?
Why are they dark brown from head to toe?
Anyway, I'm gonna turn left and not think about it anymore.
It's the most people experience.
Yeah, so I guess I could see that to some degree,
but also I feel like the ice cream cone would have been fun.
Yeah.
Especially if it was like one of the big, the 10 scoops.
Did they indicate, I saw the same thing.
One scoop.
Do you think that's what-
That's what I'm reading,
but maybe there was a crazy concept.
Tyra didn't say scoop wise what it was.
You're near, you know what?
Yeah, clearly better now.
One scoop, I don't know if I care about.
Scoops that go all the way up to the top of Walt's head.
Yes.
Match his height and kind of have a little curve.
Like maybe they're about to fall out.
It's like 30 scoops.
That's a good statue.
That's a good statue, yes.
Subliminal too.
People see it and they're like,
I wanna get a big ice cream cone.
I wanna get a big scoop of bronze ice cream.
I wanna find-
What color is closest to bronze?
I want a few scoops of that Edie slash Dreyer's ice cream.
That's smart.
Well, that's the plus up clearly.
Yeah.
A giant drain of ice creams.
Some more trivia about this statue.
So it exists at Disneyland Disney World,
the Disney lot in Burbank, Tokyo Disney,
and then that Bayard Park at Disneyland Paris
that we always complain about.
It's the castle parks.
It's their own lights, the place where Walt worked
and then it's the worst park they ever built.
And that went because it's the same position
in the castle parks in front of the castle.
And then in the studios park,
it's just kind of like tower terrors there,
some purple buildings over there.
It's as if they're trying to go,
well, you wanna say this place is cheap and not class.
Look who's here.
Look who's watching over it.
The cheapest man in America that are David.
Different labor.
Yeah.
Labor-wise cheap, yes.
In different, slightly different material in each park,
slightly different coloring to sort of blend in
with the surroundings a little better.
Do you have the names of the different materials?
I don't.
I don't have that.
I think they were just considering the aging
and the finishings of like,
well, the Southern California skylines
are different than the Orlando skyline
instead of the Paris.
One of them's not made out of candy or something.
Not yet.
That would be a good food.
Ice cream.
Yeah, a treat to, yeah, yeah.
There's also a version of it in the Epic Mickey video game.
Yes, I guess.
Where Mickey is replaced with Oswald the lucky rabbit.
And that's the most melancholy.
It's the sign that it's an alternate universe
is that it's Oswald.
There's a version of that that's good.
And that's, I was just talking about this
on the Kingdom Hearts where like,
some of the art even was like darker and more dystopian,
which generally I don't like,
but I liked it at the time when I saw it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But then there was some art for the second one,
and I don't think they actually used it
where the partner statue is three.
Oh.
It's Walt in the middle,
like we were talking about at the top of the episode,
Walt and then Mickey and Oswald.
Oswald on his left, Mickey on his right.
Wow.
Because they work together in the second game.
Exactly.
So I don't know if that actually made it in the game.
It's a striking image.
It's a very striking image.
Yeah, it's very.
It's a, you know, it makes it,
it makes so much sense in that game
that like that's their clock tower.
Like that's the sign that things are changing, I guess.
That you know you're in a different world
because something's up with this area.
It's in the, in Wasteland.
The Wasteland. That's a part of the game.
So. Wow.
Which was really that game,
we just by sheer coincidence
put out the Kingdom Hearts episode,
10 years to the day that Epic Mickey was coming out.
Wow. I believe.
Somebody said 12.
I saw, I sent a tweet that said 10,
but then I saw somebody say 12.
So I thought. Okay.
Well, what a nice tribute to something
that isn't what we.
What we talked about.
Oh, a video game that was unpleasant in different ways.
Was it?
But better, a better game.
It was better, but it was also like no one talked.
It was just text.
We all go, my we isn't working.
So I have to figure out how to get it working
so I can revisit Epic Mickey.
Yeah.
Well, maybe something to talk about is what is happening?
What the scene that it depicts.
We've talked about that they're holding hands,
but it's kind of, I mean, it's, it's sort of, okay.
Mickey is looking up adoringly fondly at his, his mentor.
And.
His partner.
It is his partner.
Yes.
And while Walt's, and this was a choice that they had to make
is what is Walt's doing and what they landed on
is big friendly smile and kind of gesturing to the horizon.
And I mean, I know the intent of, of Blaine Gibson,
what he was trying to say,
but do you guys put any meaning into this?
Like when you see that statue,
what do you think Walt's thinking about?
What is he?
What's, what's his frame of mind?
What do you put onto this, this work?
Well, I was reading that a lot of people, yeah,
have their own feeling of what it means,
what this gesture means.
And I think if I, my, if my first reaction is sort of Walt,
basically like in a Willy Wonka type way telling Mickey,
all of this is yours.
This is all yours.
I will die soon.
Right.
Keeping my cancer quiet.
And he's saying, this is going to be yours.
And since we're partners, equal partners in Disney,
it's all up to you now.
Cause I'm going to die.
So it's a grim monument.
Yeah. It's depressing.
To you.
Yes.
I think he's, cause he's pointing kind of like past,
there's no California adventure at that point.
So he's just kind of pointing out into Anaheim.
So I think he's going like, well,
down there are the strawberry fields
and I don't own those right now,
but why don't I own those?
He's upset.
Those will be mine.
I'm going.
I'm working on it.
I'm going to, I'm going to go after the farmers there.
Or he's going to raise those orchards to the ground.
Or he's saying like,
and there'll be something called the uva bar
and it'll be over here.
And they'll kind of the way that in the,
the direction I'm pointing.
The prices will be expensive by most measures,
but okay by park measures.
And it will be okay to drink there,
but the gate there is what separates
and it is a sin to drink on this side of the game.
But on that side of the drink,
that side of the gate,
drink as much as you want and come into this other side
of the gate as drunk as you want.
But the, it's all about, it's all about gates, Mickey.
That's right.
Well, it'd be interesting to see where exactly
his index finger is pointing at.
Oh, good point.
It's just like that used to be the wrong shot.
That used to be the tobaccoist.
And that's where everyone, you can't buy gum.
Well, you can buy Chesterfield.
So that's an interesting question.
So in the reality, he is,
the statue isn't like we train gets transported back to.
You're in your version of it.
He is kind of alive looking at what Disneyland is now.
Cause what I was saying was like,
oh, in the future, he's telling Mickey about uva bar
and the future he's saying this will be yours.
So your version of it is he's sort of like
kind of alive right now.
And he's commenting on what's happening in Disneyland.
He's being an annoying trivia guy.
He's bothering his friend telling you what used to be.
He's one of us.
So I was put here in 1983, Blaine Gibson retired in 73.
I got put here in 83.
So in the future, I can see the beginning of time
and I can see the end of time.
And from, from whence we became just nothing
to nothing again.
He's like, he's just at the center of time and space.
He is.
An eternal being.
He's an eternal being.
And then in Florida, he's like pointing,
cause you in Florida, you can get a picture
where that statue and the Roy statue
are in the frame at the same time.
Right.
And the Roy statue, which Blaine Gibson also made
is about where Roy was in the dedication opening day.
Okay.
And then that one, he's on a bench
and he is kind of holding Minnie's hand.
Yeah, that one's a bit so, it's odd, right?
It is odd.
Yeah.
It's flirtatious.
A lot of clarifiers.
When I read about that, where it's like,
okay, he's supporting Minnie's hand
and he's comfy on the bench.
So she's bothering him.
He's not bothering her.
She approached him.
You understand?
There should be, there should be,
there should be statues for every executive
that ever worked, like a high level.
So like, Eisen should have got one.
Of course he'd card Walker,
all with different Disney characters
in just random places all over the parks.
Oh, well, we like the kind of,
there's the Easter eggs in Tokyo
and what Griffin liked, the ghosts in Paris.
Yeah, bronze executives.
Well, here's the question.
Here's the big question that we face,
mere months after the thing happened.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And they've, I'm talking about Shapek.
I know what you're talking about.
And Shapek, I don't think we've talked about this,
but they took a sign away on Castaway Key.
It's a ship destination, is that correct?
Or where is that?
I believe so.
Is that in Disney World?
What is that?
That's a cruise ship destination.
That's one of the islands they own part of.
There used to be a sign.
It's not Mushikey.
No, no, no.
It's Castaway Key.
He might go there now with it.
He's got more time.
But there was a sign that said,
Bob Shapek, master ship builder, I believe.
Master ship builder.
Yeah.
And they took it away.
They took it down immediately.
Did they do this for Paul Pressler
when they showed him the door?
I don't know if there was anything of Paul Pressler.
Oh, okay.
I just was made aware that this existed
like a couple of weeks ago before even he got fired.
So like, no idea.
It was like two weeks before they're like,
oh, take a look at this.
Like some people were making jokes about
what kind of a ship builder Shapek would be
because he was still CEO at the time.
And then he got fired.
And like a day or two later, the sign is gone.
Wow.
So like, yeah, somebody, that was a priority at that time.
No one was like a year later.
Oh yeah, by the way, remember we have that,
maybe we take that down or do something else with it.
No way.
Gone.
That got overnighted to those antique malls
in the Orlando area.
Mr. Morrow's probably in a video like,
oh, look at this.
You just turn a corner and it's like.
Look at this Bob Shapek sign.
Well, there's every prop from the Shrek lobby for sale.
Wow.
Well, so it puts them in an awkward position
if we're gonna attribute all these executives.
You know, look, we don't like the guy,
but he was there for a long time.
And in the CEO chair, it's that awkward.
It's what they have to like, does Conan get a little booth
at the race through New York thing.
And I think you have to.
So at least that's the choice I make.
So where does, and here,
I'll just say what I think of where Shapek goes.
Because how do you summarize his legacy?
And you know, you put Walt with Mickey,
you put Roy with Minnie,
they're in these like nice sentimental moments
with the characters.
So I think you get Shapek and you put him,
like you maybe miss him at first.
He's like hunched down, wrapping or like peering
around the side of one of the ATM machines.
And kind of just like licking his lips.
Nom nom nom nom nom.
And who's he with?
I think that's the character he's with.
Oh, is he ATM?
But if you, that's what I thought.
But now that you've said that,
maybe it's a little Scrooge McDuck.
Scrooge McDuck, like they're both like,
they're both just like waiting for anybody
to spill some of the, accidentally drop some of those bills.
That's good, but isn't Scrooge like hyper competent?
How good of a, yeah, who's better at their,
well, I mean, Scrooge having the big tank of money implies
that there's a surplus.
Not that a businessman has to be hyper competent.
But also, but who knows,
I don't know how much his expeditions cost.
I've been looking, I've been watching some
of the James Cameron deep dive stuff
with Avatar mania happening in my brain only maybe.
But he goes on these deep sea diving expeditions.
But they caught, you start to catch
like the cost on these things.
So Scrooge McDuck, it might be the same way.
Maybe he's opening credits when he's like underwater
with the thing on and like the,
he's trying to go for like the dollar bill.
The sharks are in it, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he might find a treasure
or he might find a dollar bill like that.
But if every one of those expeditions costs him
10 million dollars out of pocket,
the Scrooge enterprise might like,
it might be days away from plummeting always.
What's the main character from Treasure Planet's name?
I don't know that.
Someone's definitely screaming this.
My, okay, this is my thing.
Relax, there's no need to scream.
Shepek is my.
There's Milo's from Atlantis.
Yes.
Milo I believe is the leader of Atlantis.
Well, Treasure Planet is Jim Hawkins, like the book.
Jim Hawkins and it's.
So that's, that's.
That's a solid epitome.
People are screaming.
And that's why it's Jim's song by John Resnick
of the Goo Goo Dolls is the song from Treasure Planet.
Jim's song.
I believe it's the song is Jim's song, I think.
I think I recently had another anniversary.
People are posting. Jim did?
No, the Treasure Planet.
I think that's like, this came out X number of years ago.
I'm sure it did.
Every movie. It's 2023 now.
That's the old.
Every movie has an anniversary.
But it was interesting, right?
It was one of those like,
oh, I should look that up on Disney Plus
cause these screengrads look pretty cool.
I would watch it.
Yeah. I know the song.
So I gotta see the movie.
I see Dr. Doppler and turned.
Okay, so Dr. Doppler and Shepek are their partner's statue.
And I want them.
Wait, why is Dr. Doppler with Shepek?
I don't.
I just like.
You remember the chain of events.
Is he greedy?
I don't know if he's greedy.
No, I don't know anything about Dr. Doppler.
I just like the idea that he's.
He's an alien dog is what he is.
Perfect. Dr. Delbert Doppler.
He's voiced by David Ide Pierce.
I still think he should be with Shepek
and the bronze partner statue.
And the dog is peeing.
Can the dog pee on him or something?
Like can we get going with blue here?
Can we work blue?
Well, look, Dr. Doppler is more human than dog.
He is a proper gentleman in kind of a long coat.
So I don't think he's just gonna pee on a fire hydrant
like a regular dog.
But that said, I think,
what I'm saying is I think he's the kind of man dog
that would go use a proper bathroom and clean up,
dop himself with a little urethra cleaner.
But I think he'll make an exception for Shepek.
And yes, Dr. Doppler can be peeing on Shepek's head.
This is just my suggestion.
It doesn't have to be yours can be Scrooge.
Mine is Dr. Doppler.
And he's gonna pee like an adult.
He's like McGruff almost.
He's like a McGruff.
So like standing up, like he unzipped his pants.
There are things.
He's just gently peeing on to Bob Shepek.
Or they're at the urine.
Like it's the statues in the bathroom
and they're both at urinals.
They have to make separate urinals that guests can't use.
Who was, for a statue, I'd like to see,
what was the son-in-law's name?
In what?
The son of?
Walt's son-in-law.
Ron Miller.
Ron Miller, the one who everyone was an asshole too.
So I-
Why were people an asshole then?
I think people were just like,
you are in so far over your head football boy.
Like he, like-
Yeah, he did a bad job for sure.
I mean, he came in already,
he was in a tough spot being Walt's son-in-law.
And because people immediately,
I think looked at him as a successor.
And I don't think he ever had a desire for that role.
He leads straight into the Eisner era.
So you want to see a Ron Miller?
I want to see a Ron Miller in there.
In what?
Maybe like Card Walker slapping him in the head.
But who was he with character wise?
Is it Dr. Doppler?
Or is it a different character?
What character is he with?
Is he with the dirtier, scratchier,
first generation rescuers?
Yes.
More fucked up Bianca and Bernard?
He's an executive producer on rescuers.
Okay, that makes sense.
So he's being, maybe they're biting him.
He's getting rabies from the rescuers.
Yeah.
And Card Walker's like,
what are you doing son?
What are you doing boy?
Smacking him on the back of the head.
There's a few more that I'm sure,
there's some more things to actually talk about
that are real.
But you brought up the escape from New York.
I also, as a thought exercise,
maybe at the very end,
thinking about a partner statues
for other figureheads of things,
like a Lorne Michaels.
Oh yeah.
What would be a Lorne Michaels partner statue
in 30 Rock?
There's a little,
there's not a full bust of him
at that North Hollywood place,
but there's a, it's kind of 3D.
He's kind of like peering out of like a-
The Haunted Mansion?
Just like a, I don't know what you even call it,
but there's-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It feels like an-
Michael's eyes are following you.
Right.
Like you're a first season featured player.
Right, and your job is in jeopardy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And a Don Pardo as well.
Oh wow, okay.
Go walk around this place, it's fun.
I got it.
But anyways, well is there real stuff left?
I don't know.
I don't know, there's nothing like,
look there's nothing that interesting.
Yeah, I don't think so.
You can buy replicas of the partner statue
pretty much at any price point.
Okay, so price point,
this is what I was looking up,
is that there are so many versions
of the partner statue you can buy.
Yes, Disney and Etsy.
Like you can-
Yes, everywhere.
Any level, any material.
Yes, yes, everywhere.
EBay, versions, like there's so many,
like Tokyo and then it's different materials
and some are high end, some are not.
Even just looking at Shop Disney right now
or whatever the hell it's called.
It's Shop Disney, right?
Yes.
There's four, you can buy,
you can't buy a version of it now
because there are ornaments and there are statues.
You can buy a puzzle of the partner statue.
You can buy a throw blanket.
You can buy a sketchbook with the partners on the front
and you can buy a watch with the partners on the face of it.
So that's just currently on Shop Disney.
Blanket is weird.
The blanket is weird.
I go to bed with the partners on me.
This one was, I don't know,
this was just like the Google shopping preview.
I don't know it's still in stock
but it was showing on Shop Disney.
The laser cube, like engraved laser image of it.
Yeah, there are, and there are some,
we should post these.
There are some like facsimiles of this
that are funny in the sense, like this looks like shit.
Like, uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
I'll show you.
Okay.
Let's see.
They both look a little sickly.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, it looks like somebody pinched Walt's neck.
Yeah.
So there are like, I feel like this is one
of the biggest successes in their last couple decades,
just in the sense of marketing.
Because I think it is what I said
where I think most people would go,
oh, that's been here since it opened
or this has been since Walt died.
Yes, really feels that way.
Yeah, yeah.
Like it feels seamlessly integrated into the park.
It's probably one of the top 10 most iconic things you see.
Like if you were somebody who went for the first time,
I feel like that would be in their top five or 10 things
if you showed them pictures.
Oh yeah, I remember that, I remember that, I remember that.
Sure, yeah.
So like, and then the merch,
I feel like the merch is an example of its success
or its popularity basically.
This feels like a Saving Mr. Banks, second unit crew,
someone going, hey, make sure to get a shot of that thing
for the montage at the end.
It's a, I think they did what they set out to do.
I think like let's mythologize our founder
and see, and like, and I don't think I realized
the extent to which it was, it was merchandise along with that.
Yes, it really, there's a lot of Tokyo versions of it,
like a Tokyo Disney, like little statues
and things I found on eBay.
There is a $406 version on the website Mercari,
but then there's also a $60 version on Poshmark.
So, you know, set your price and then shop.
Yeah, it's hard to tell which ones are which
because it feels like some of them look exactly the same
and one's $400 and one's $25.
So I don't know, maybe somebody is like an expert
on the partner statue toys or stat, they could like really,
if you go to Antique Roadshow,
somebody has a jeweler's loop and they can examine these
and tell you what's exactly, what's valuable.
The other thing is that in 2020,
they cleaned the Disneyland statue in November, 2020.
I forget.
Oh, that's a great, like what else do we do
while it's closed?
We can finally clean the, it's interesting.
They made the bronze shinier.
And there's a whole explanation on Disney Parks blog,
Wednesday, November 18th,
to commemorate Mickey Mouse's birthday,
we were excited to reveal a special surprise
at the Disneyland Resort.
Following a refurbishment, the iconic partner statue
in front of Sleeping Beauty Castle in Disneyland
has been restored to its original grandeur.
From 20 years ago.
20 years ago.
For Mickey's birthday, we cleaned him.
So he was cleaned.
Wait, they cleaned Mickey,
but they never got around to that new entry
in signage and planter for Tomorrowland, I feel like.
What was that?
Wasn't there supposed to be something like,
and this is coming to Tomorrowland.
Yeah, there was some picture, I feel like,
that maybe they did, maybe they didn't,
but I can't remember what it was
because that's another traffic stopper
but it's mostly because of the ride.
Yeah.
But yeah, no, there's an explanation
if you wanna know about oxidization of bronze.
Well, you're the one looking at the information.
How much do you wanna say it?
Honestly, not that much.
I mean, it's not, I don't know.
Oh, I wanna read this.
After cleaning, various chemicals were applied
and heated with a blowtorch
to create a reaction infused with the bronze.
So they had to reapply things and then blowtorch it.
Blowtorch Walt and Mickey.
Well, that's great.
I wouldn't have that.
I would buy all the merchandise stuff.
Is there video of a guy with a blowtorch?
Just blasting Walt.
Blasting Walt's crotch
to get the shinier bronze on his pants.
Maybe there probably is
because they have to make those little featurettes like,
oh, we're cleaning the park and this is what we do.
So there has to be some documentation of it, I would think,
but maybe it's in the Disney vault and we won't see it.
It doesn't have the oxidization
that some statues that you can feel
like a lot of college campuses have.
Oh, and then there's a statue of the Nittany Lion
on Penn State's campus.
Everyone rubs it for good luck.
So there's a portion of it that's really shiny
because it's worn away over the years
because everyone's touching it.
So it's not like Walt's butt is like everyone hits it
on the way down Main Street.
I don't think there's a tradition
of people grabbing Walt's ass, no.
Oh, the only one you can touch other than the bust
is the one at the lot in Burbank.
Oh, that one is just on the ground.
That was just on the ground.
So you could rub its belly for good luck,
Mickey or Walt's belly for good luck.
You gotta be on the lot.
There's no tours of the lot really.
Yeah, you gotta get invited.
I've only been a few times.
I didn't touch his butt.
And I didn't touch his butt either.
Have you ever been on the lot?
A few times, yeah.
Okay, did you touch it?
I don't think I touched his butt.
Is it by the Legends Garden?
Is it by the Disney Legend Facts?
Yeah, it's in front of the Dwarfs building.
Oh, and I just saw a photo that they put
a Santa hat on Walt and give him a scarf too.
Oh, are you there now?
It's December as we're recording this.
That's fun.
Yeah, yeah.
I think they put Santa hats on the Dwarfs too.
Oh really?
I saw one on Dopey and it looked weird
because Dopey's in a weird spot
and it kind of looked a little horrific.
He's already got the,
because they all have hats that are kind of Santa hats.
Double hats?
Oh yeah, the Dwarfs already have Santa hats.
Well Dopey does, right?
Do they all have hats like that?
Yeah, they got those, yeah.
I believe every Dwarf has a hat.
But is it the same hat?
Because many are bald underneath, I'm not sure.
Let me see, okay, they all have, yes,
they all have the same type of hat.
Yeah.
Yeah, all kind of Santa hats,
they just don't have the ball at the end.
So they save some money, Disney just add the ball.
Just add the ball.
I just save you some fabric costs.
If we're coming to the end,
Mike, I've been stewing on it since you mentioned it,
attributing other non-Disney executives.
Not too far from here, a magical place
with a Walt statue and a Walt bust
within easy driving distance.
We're also near a place, a very important place,
which is the now former NBC Studios,
which is where the Johnny Carson Tonight Show took place
and also, more importantly,
the Jay Leno Tonight Show.
And there is nothing acknowledging,
there's a nice park acknowledging Johnny Carson,
but there is nothing acknowledging Mr. Leno
and his time and how meaningful he is
to the Burbank community.
Or the executives who made so many of the great decisions
that created TV magic in that time.
So I have an idea of a partner statue for the former NBC.
I don't know who's gonna foot the bill
because they don't own it anymore.
It's me, y'all have to do it.
So I will pay for a statue that is
all time great executive Jeff Zucker.
And there are two squares, kind of like hopscotch squares
on the ground and one says 10 and one says 1130.
And he's like kind of ushered,
he's holding Jay's hand and ushering him over,
wait, I guess it would have to be, wait, wait, no,
maybe it's just like, or it's just like a box,
it's like a little Olympic riser that says Tonight Show Host.
And he's helping Jay up the stairs
to let him back up to his post.
And then there's also a bronze Conan
who he's shoving to the ground.
He's putting his foot on his head.
He's forcibly kicking him off of the riser.
So we need three figures here
and it's gonna have to be active and violent.
But I think we gotta acknowledge the spot
where that wonderful decision.
How much do you think you can get,
how much could you get that sculpted for?
10 grand, 20, 50?
I don't know much about it.
I'll talk to the people who put that Batman sculpture.
That's a cool, that's my favorite statue ever.
It's really good, it's pretty awesome.
That's a good, for no reason suddenly
there's a statue of Batman,
inexplicably tenor Batman.
I saw it at a movie theater in Burbank, California
by the yard house.
Yeah, it gets in your way
if you're trying to walk up to the yard house.
There's like an eight foot, just Jim Lee artist
drawn Batman statue that is so cool.
And people, I saw this myself.
I saw pictures going around
and then I happened to be down there.
People left flowers at that statue
when Kevin Conroy passed away.
Oh yeah, I did see that.
Long time voice of Batman.
It's become a spot to do your work.
It's a memorial, yeah.
It's a spot to do your Batman related grieving.
Yes. Yeah.
Like Batman would do at his parents grave,
which depicted in every movie you've ever seen.
So if you're sad about something that happens
in the Batman universe,
go throw a pearl necklace on the ground.
Yeah, and finish your yard at the yard house
and then go do whatever that is.
Yeah, whatever memorializing.
My statue, I, you know,
Warner Brothers a few years ago
moved the DC Comics offices to the Burbank,
Warner Brothers properties.
And they were assholes about it.
They didn't handle it well.
But, you know, I think in the vein of the Batman statue,
I want a bronze statue of Batman co-creator Bob Kane,
who was also a notorious asshole.
So I would like a statue featuring another insane man
comic book artist Jim Steranko,
who's now a right wing crank on Twitter.
But he has a story of slapping Bob Kane across the face
at a comic convention after Bob Kane did a little like,
how you doing kid?
Yeah, he gave him like one of these,
like a condescending thing to Jim Steranko
at a Comic-Con in like 1970 something or eight.
And Jim Steranko stewed on it for a day.
And then when he saw Bob Kane again, he bitch slapped him.
Wow.
And so if there's a way for them both
to be slapping each other.
Yeah.
I think you can capture all that at once.
Everyone hated Bob Kane.
Yeah.
And he stole a lot of the,
like he was a guy who took sole credit
for a lot of things when this guy Bill Finger.
Bill Finger kind of shafted, yeah.
Yeah, the Bob Kane bitch slap.
Mike, is there an executive that you would like to honor?
Yeah, I mean, I guess I kept getting stuck on Lorne,
just being like, but who would it be
with Lorne and the partner?
I mean, would it be Chivvy?
Would it be Billy or Danny?
I don't think it can't be them.
It has to be something.
I think it's the bees.
And you make the Mickey decision
that the bees are small.
Oh, interesting.
He's holding hands with a bunch of small bees.
Like real, like right to scale normal bees?
I'm not sure.
Or there's a handful of bees.
It's Lorne with a handful of bees.
Oh and it's, who were the bees on the show?
Was it a cut of cut of cut of cut of cut of cut of cut of cut of?
It was.
Yeah.
Could you just have all of them in little bee costumes?
Okay, how about this?
They're small enough you could put every cast member ever
in his hands sculpted as tiny little bees.
Because really what is that show other than like a beehive
that he's curated to help nourish the bees.
Okay.
And they made him honey
but then they were able to fly and start their own lives.
This is perfect.
So now here's what we're gonna plus it up even more.
Take that scene from the Winnie the Pooh ride
where he's like stuck in the big hive
and he's covered in honey.
And Lorne is popping out of that same thing
and he's got honey all over his face.
And he's holding-
Lorne dripping with honey.
Lorne Michaels is dripping with honey.
Well, wait, if he's dripping with honey
then there should be some bee,
all the non-cast member who like Steve Martin
should be a bee on his face and Buck Henry and-
George Carlin.
All the first year hosts.
People just hang, yeah, weird old Desi Arnaz.
Desi Arnaz.
And then, yeah, so he's-
Gerald Ford's speech writer, Ron Nesson, I think.
I think that's right.
Sybil Shepherd.
More names to learn.
Whoever was hanging out, Candice Bergen, Sybil Shepherd,
they're just kind of smoking cigarettes on his shoulder.
Yeah, so yeah, they're all tiny bees.
And then you could do as many as you want.
It's gonna be a little bit tough to, you know,
sculpt that tiny at that tiny scale.
But the technology allows it, I bet.
And I think it's very clear.
I think people will know exactly
what, people will follow the logic.
Oh, got it, because he's nurturing like a beekeeper.
Yeah.
Lorne is winning the poo in a-
Lorne is a poo.
And it's bees because of the bees sketch
from 50 years ago, yes.
And then in his shirt pocket,
there's a little Paul McCartney, a little John Lennon
going like, should we go down there?
There's talking.
They're talking.
Jason, you're adding a little too much to this.
Oh, excuse me.
It's gonna be a little expensive.
That was what it put in.
I'm thinking more of cost.
I don't mean to overstep my boundaries.
I didn't say this was blue sky, did I?
Maybe I did actually say it.
I may have said blue sky.
All right, so the Beatles are out.
Yeah, you're cut.
But everyone who's ever been on the show,
including hosts, as bees.
Yeah, Scott's idea, good.
Jason's bad.
Yeah, yeah, yes, not.
My logic, great.
Steve Forbes up there.
We gotta get Giuliani and Trump.
Yeah.
It's a call.
We did it.
I think we did it.
We had great ideas for statues
that should be installed all over the globe.
More statues.
More statues with slightly different quotes
on the plaque every time.
Yes, those are not exactly something he said.
Just like real life.
He forgot to mention that they're slightly different.
Yeah, they're all different, a little.
And one of them, just the Disneyland one even,
it strings together two things he said.
Yeah, it's a mush up, yeah.
Yeah, we just didn't have time.
We had to talk about urethras and cast bees.
Sorry, it's cut.
But you survived podcast the ride.
Thank you for subscribing to The Second Gate.
And if you wanna dig even deeper,
join us on our new Patreon tier, Club 3,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
that you the audience choose, and our regular episodes.
Ad-free, great place to start.
And keep your urethras clean.