Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to an emergency second gate podcast,
the ride special Eva zooms in.
This is an episode that has barely come together
and we've been called into duty,
much like Detective Tracy himself,
in order to discuss a TCM special
that aired on the evening of Friday, February 10th
called Dick Tracy Special, Tracy Zooms In,
joined of course by Mike Carlson, hello.
Hello, I'm here.
I was in bed when I got the call that we had to do this.
That's how, you know, it's like we were like on shift
at a hospital usually for podcasts the ride
and if something comes across our desk,
we have like a bat phone of some kind that rings
and we are, you know, shaken out of our sleep.
Yeah, we're recording this at 3.30 AM.
There was no other way to do it, no other free time.
Jason Sheridan has answered the call.
Yeah, it is a pleasure to be here.
Well, pleasure might be too strong a word.
I don't know.
That isn't really what I feel.
That is just a phrase Ben Mankiewicz says in this.
A quote.
Yeah.
From this immediately iconic special.
Now what's this?
Well, Mike has just slipped me a slip of paper
that says Anderson on Zoom.
Huh, interesting, wow, okay.
Well, I guess we'll have to bring her in.
Please welcome our resident Dick Tracy expert.
Thank God we got one.
Eva Anderson, hi.
Hey guys.
Hi.
That weird thing before the intro where you watched,
you listened to the previous podcast
and just sort of like said it was bad.
Was that necessary?
Do you feel like the audience didn't know
that we recorded a episode about Dick Tracy's Crime Stoppers
and you needed to let them know A, that we did it
and B, you didn't care for it?
Well, it's been a long time
and I think we've all gathered a lot of thoughts
about that prior episode
and I think we all wish that we'd been more clear,
let's say, about our points of view in said episode.
And remember, we own the rights to talking
about Dick Tracy's Crime Stoppers
and we need to refresh those rights every few years.
So that's what we were doing really, primarily.
Yeah, I feel like, I mean, that's why we kind of,
the calendar alert came up
and we all had to jump on Zoom real quick
to make sure that we are allowed to keep talking
about Dick Tracy for the next 15 years, right?
Yeah, because we have the rights to perfect it.
We got two days.
Okay, I'm going to really quickly run through the basics
and I wanna do it fast so that we can just dive
into pure raw analysis of the special
Dick Tracy special Tracy Zooms In.
But feel free to interrupt my list of facts here,
but I just wanna onboard people as quickly as we can,
though many people might be fully aware
of everything that's happening.
Okay, here we go.
Dick Tracy is a comic strip about a hardline detective
that began in 1931.
In 1990, actor Warren Beatty directed and starred
in a Dick Tracy feature film for the Walt Disney Company.
But more importantly than him making the movie in 1990,
the story really begins in 1985
when he obtained the film rights from Tribune Media
and he was allowed to keep those rights in perpetuity
provided that he could prove that he was working
on future projects in film or television
that necessitated him to have the Dick Tracy rights.
In the early 2000s, since it's been a while
since the 1990 movie, Tribune Media gets curious,
like, hey, those rights that we gave you,
you gonna be doing anything with those?
And he's like, you're damn right I am.
I got a lot cooking and hey, don't step on the process.
I'm taking my time.
Then they really ramp up the heat in like 2006.
What's going on?
When are you gonna do?
Actually, we're gonna write you a letter.
We're giving you, I didn't know all these specifics.
This is true. Mr. Beatty.
This is all true.
In 2000, this, okay, let me see.
I have the specific dates.
In November, okay, November 17th, 2006,
Tribune sent Beatty a letter that gave him two years
to begin production on some kind of Dick Tracy programming.
So on November 8th, 2008, with just like,
what's that, nine days to go, he,
Warren Beatty said, hey, guess what, Tribune,
I'm working on a TV special.
He gave them written notice, although it seems unclear
whether they actually got the written notice.
But what this did with, he was just under the deadline.
He started making a special that allowed him
to retain the rights, a bizarre special
that aired just once on TCM,
which I believe is just called Dick Tracy Special.
Now we discussed this on our Dick Tracy Crime Stoppers
episode a while back.
The basics here- Specifically, oh yeah,
it was that- Yes.
I forgot the part, because I just listened to it
this morning, that it was, the cinematographer
was the guy who did, who won three back-to-back Oscars.
One of the greatest- And who Mike worked with.
Livings, who Mike worked with,
who Mike was on a hand glider with.
Amazing.
One of the greatest cinematographers has ever,
like one of the most long endless shots, so innovative.
And he was brought in to do this special
that is mostly an interview with Leonard Malton
and the character Dick Tracy,
who in this special introduces the premise
that Dick Tracy is different than Warren Beatty.
He is a 100 year old man or more who is alive still,
who looks and sounds exactly like Warren Beatty,
but is not him.
And it's this special, it's mostly an interview,
but then there's a bunch of weird improv
on an empty Disney lot, poorly shot,
despite it being one of the best cinematographers ever.
There's a bunch of groundlings who all have stories
that don't resolve or like,
and in fact the groundlings do not return
in this new special that we're going to talk about.
They didn't feel the need to resolve the,
what's Mindy Sterling been up to for the last 13 years?
This takes us to this very week.
This special was only remembered by weirdos.
Suffer from brain rot.
And this special is one of the things
rotting all of our brains.
And we never expected there to be more of it,
but certainly there was the question,
when will Warren Beatty do more with Dick Tracy?
A movie perhaps?
No, in this case, there is suddenly
a weird cryptic announcement on TCM's website schedule
that says Dick Tracy special, Tracy zooms in.
And even still, it's not officially announced
what the hell this is.
And it takes Twitter sleuthing
to get to the business of what is this.
I think it was like, I saw it popularized by Will Sloan,
who's a writer and podcaster for the podcast Michael and Us,
which I like a lot.
Anyway, so he starts asking questions.
Who spotted this?
Yeah, like someone spotted.
I think it was maybe a follower of Will Sloan.
And then Will Sloan asked the question.
Basically, like there was no,
TCM was not going to talk about this, I don't think at all.
And everything we're describing,
this has all happened really fast.
The special aired Friday night.
Thursday at lunch with friend of the show,
Andrew Grissom was the first that I had heard about it.
And again, TCM, no official,
it was just somebody looking at their website schedule.
Then a listener to this show, Chris Hayner,
who is also the entertainment editor at GameSpot,
decided to go fishing and see if TCM,
if I asked TCM, will they say anything,
he got a blurb out of them,
which confirmed the presence of Warren Beatty
separately from this one will include Dick Tracy
and Warren Beatty, Leonard Malton again,
and current TCM personality, wait, it's Ben Meskowitz.
Mankiewicz.
God, why did I think it?
Grandfather of Mank, of Herman Mankiewicz.
Grandson, you mean?
Grandson, grandson.
Of the great Mank?
Yeah, the co-writer of Citizen Kane.
The grandson of the co-writer of Citizen Kane.
The wonderful TV personality,
wonderful host for Turner Classic movies.
Took over a lot of the work for them,
especially after Robert Osborn died.
Had been doing it for a while,
but he's doing it even more.
Jason, are you being really polite to him
because you desperately want his job
and you wanna pretend that you like him?
No, I love Ben Mankiewicz.
I like, I think he's terrific.
I love him. I like him too.
Yeah, I love him.
He's good.
It definitely though feels like him and Leonard Malton
were already at the office that day.
And they're like, you know,
we've got a certain amount of on-camera hours
in your contract and you know,
Wern't Beatty's calling again, so we gotta do this.
Well, how much heads up did they get is the question.
Like, has this been, like,
this all came together really quickly.
Did this, wait, they mentioned last year.
So we know that, that it was made in 2022.
It wasn't made like last week.
However, it does seem like this must've come,
I bet it was another just under the wire,
a Tribune's taking the rights back on New Year's Eve.
So he throws this together at 8 p.m. December 31st, right?
How else could this have happened?
Yeah, it has to be like something like that.
I mean, it wouldn't be surprised me
if there was like shots done two days ago.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
Part of it wasn't finished until like 12 hours before it aired.
I don't know that I'm just saying
it wouldn't be shocking to me.
Real TV gets made like that often too.
Sure, yeah.
You're saying this isn't real TV?
Yeah, well, you're right.
I apologize to the special, it is real TV.
Just your typical rights squatting special
from an 85 year old man.
I like how that they sandwiched it
between old Dick Tracy movies
as if it was like trying to hide it all.
It feels like it was trying to hide it
like when you hide a dog medicine in peanut butter
or something.
Just, you know, just like shove it in there.
No one will notice it.
Hey, look, if you're the estate of Ralph Bird,
you're like having a banner weekend.
Like I don't think even Ben Mankiewicz and Leonard Moulton
have thought about Ralph Bird this much.
Oh, Twitter searches on Ralph Bird were up.
I'm sure. By three,
by three tweets. Can I just show you guys
something really quick too?
Cause I have this photo that I was thinking about,
how long ago did the Dick Tracy movie come out?
And I have this photo from Disney Hollywood Studios,
which was MGM Studios at the time.
With my dad posing in front of his hand prints
in front of the Chinese theater there.
My brother is wearing a Dick Tracy hat, my brother Dash,
and I have a breathless Mahoney perm.
So this is 1990.
So that means I am nine years old and I turned 42 this year.
That is how long ago the Dick Tracy movie came out
that this special is about.
You were a little child.
And you've had what seems like a full life
that has not been entirely devoted to the 1990 film,
Dick Tracy plus the 2010 special Dick Tracy special.
It seems like you have,
we all have lots in our lives that are not Warren Beatty
and this singular franchise that he owns,
which puts us on the outside as viewers because the viewer,
the ideal viewer of the special has done nothing
but think about Dick Tracy ever since.
And we all record the podcast.
The ideal viewer of this special is in this special
and playing two roles in this special.
But the other ideal viewer is us
because we recorded like two hours
on the movie and the special.
And yet I cannot, unless I had rewatched
and listened to our podcast again,
I couldn't have told you that he ate pomegranates.
Yeah, pomegranates so far out of my mind.
I watched the special the day of to remember what it was.
And if you, and listener,
if you don't know what we're talking about,
it's this like pretty obscure detail of small talk
between Leonard Malden and Dick Tracy.
And then the special just opens right on pomegranates.
I eat pomegranates.
I see the secret to my beauty is pomegranates.
And it really like requires such a vast knowledge
of a special that aired one time
and wasn't internet popular till a few years ago
and still isn't popular.
The view count is not high on this.
I'm losing popularity very lightly,
but you have to let, you have to know this
in the way that like you remember last week's
Better Call Saul so that you get all the detail
of the finale, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's only from 13 years ago.
And they didn't do a previously on,
which they should have.
No, kind of.
They show little, they show little snippets.
Maybe that is the idea.
Like that's their, that's kind of their previously on.
There's 10 minutes of the old special in this.
Yeah.
It's like, it's like, is it Better Call Saul?
They just spent 15 minutes talking about the other episode.
And it's a 27 minute special.
Yeah.
It's, when it was on,
Jane and I watched it Friday night when it was on,
but here's how kind of quick it was.
We were at a bar for happy hour around the corner
and we picked up some food and we brought it back
to her place, watched the special
and ate the food while we were watching.
And then went, it's only been a few,
do you want to go back to the bar?
Yeah, yeah, let's do that.
Like it was all within the span of an hour,
that whole process.
Jason, just to recap,
the last time we talked about one of these specials
on the previous podcast, you said it, the previous podcast,
you said the previous special took the amount of time
it takes to eat a club sandwich.
Which made me laugh out loud.
This time it was the amount of time
to eat a cheese enchilada platter.
So just a couple of little things as we keep diving in,
this Chris Hayner contact,
my Twitter discussion with him,
so he said, I found out what the special is, great.
Now places can post articles about it, whatever.
And I asked him, so if you hadn't talked to TCM,
they never would have mentioned this to anyone.
And he responded, it sure seems that way.
That's how much contractual obligation,
like what if it hadn't been found?
What if whoever it was, if it was the Will Sloan commenter,
this could have been lost forever
or not found out about for like six years from now.
It's clear that TCM doesn't care about this
and is embarrassed, maybe embarrassed by it.
But I wanna know like, do they owe Warren Beatty a debt?
If you're in the AFI 100,
do you have like, is TCM obligated
to put anything you produce on their channel?
That's my question.
Cause why wouldn't you promote like Warren Beatty
who doesn't actually do a lot of stuff?
He's not in like, of all the like famous actors,
he doesn't, he hasn't made that many movies.
He's said that before.
Why wouldn't you-
Is this his first appearance anywhere
since the Oscar envelope debacle?
I think, or maybe an interview?
Well, like 2000, his filmography since 2001
is the Howard Hughes movie and these two specials.
Right, right, yes.
20 years.
So why wouldn't you think if you were TCM,
you're like, we have new Warren Beatty content.
Let's put an ad somewhere.
I'm gonna throw this out there.
I think this is TCM fucked up
because I think this is awesome
and they should have promoted it.
And the fact that like nerds like found it is on TCM
cause I feel like, I don't know,
this is kind of a fun thing.
But also it wouldn't have been as special
if they'd promoted it, that like everyone spotted it
and was like, look what he's doing.
I like that it was like a treasure hunt
that everybody had to go on.
Yeah, everyone got to go on.
It was really exciting, like 24 hours.
Trying to tell people, explain it to people on set
that like A, the contextual thing
that Warren Beatty has to do every 15 years,
B, it's happening tonight.
We won't be able to watch it
cause we are filming a TV show.
But my friends might tell me what happens in it.
And a handful of people got very excited.
The thing is, now that it's happened twice,
they should like just make it a TV show of some kind.
Like this should be the pitch to Warren of like,
it's you as Dick Tracy and you're just mad
that the movie didn't do well.
You have to show up for 10 minutes here and there.
And you just like have lunches with people
and in your big yellow coat.
Like there's no re, now it's two things is like a pattern.
You know, the first one was an anomaly.
Now where we've got something consistent here,
they should embrace this as the only place
you can see new Warren Beatty stuff, content.
Isn't Dick Tracy IP stealing content?
Yes, IP, you could call it.
The other counterpoint,
Okay, go ahead, go ahead.
If he follows the pattern,
the next special he will be 100 years old.
He is 85, currently 88.
And speaking of 80 year olds, I wrote down,
what is Shirley McClain, his sister, think of all this.
And forget about that.
What is Annette Benning think about all this?
Shirley McClain is his sister?
Yeah.
You didn't know that?
No, I didn't know that.
Scott, you need to listen to more Ben Menkowitz.
I guess so, I didn't know his name either.
Annette Benning is 20 years younger than him.
I didn't realize that, but.
Yeah, I would guess that maybe both of them
don't have any idea what this is.
He disappeared for like two days and they're like,
Oh yeah, he must be doing one of his little projects.
He filmed it on Zoom and then he went to the Polo Lounge,
which he probably goes there.
It's one of the four places he goes.
Yeah, that's gotta be like his booth too.
So we probably can go like talk to him
in that booth at the Polo Lounge.
We know how to find him.
Right.
Well, which, you had the notion that maybe the four of us
should find him and go pitch ourselves
as the creative team of Dick Tracy too.
Well, I thought that and then I watched the special
and I don't know what he wants.
Like, here's my big question.
It's like, what the fuck does he want?
Like that, cause the first one was pretty clear.
It was like, he was being kind of witty.
Like, okay, the first special, basically he created
this divide between Warren Beatty and Dick Tracy.
And we talked about this in the last special,
but that Dick Tracy is basically like a fascist.
He liked J. Edgar Hoover.
He thought that Warren Beatty was a pinko
and he was like, I and I like law and order.
So it's like, it's kind of a funny thing to do
to say like this character, we talked about this,
the character that I want to do more movies with
is I'm now defining him as a fascist,
who I would not agree with his politics in life,
which is weird because you played him in the movie
and he is the hero.
And also, but it's also weird re-watching Dick Tracy.
Like Dick Tracy is a very boring character.
Everyone else is the fun part.
So what do you do with Dick Tracy?
You make him a weird fascist?
Okay, Warren Beatty.
So you're trying to make the argument
that you should make more of these movies.
That's why you're retaining the IP
so no one else can have it.
So this next special, he really comes out
Dick Tracy hates the movie Dick Tracy.
He hates it.
It was not as clear.
And his whole thing about like,
I should have been more clear before.
Yeah, it's much edgier than the prior.
He's watching clips of it and he does not like it.
He hates it.
Yeah.
Dick Tracy does not at all like dramatic interpretation,
but I think he might like my pitch
because even going off your thing that he's a fascist,
thinking about other very popular fascists,
they should make a Dark Knight Returns Dick Tracy
where Dick Tracy is old and grizzled
like the old beat up Bruce Wayne Batman in the comic.
Yeah, but that's still fun.
I don't disagree with you.
But that still has big, fun, colorful characters,
which Warren, Dick is saying no to.
He doesn't like that about Dick Tracy.
Yes.
Here's the thing that made me go like, what is happening?
I get like he doesn't like the pink street.
Okay.
He doesn't like breathless Mahoney
like crawling across the desk because that's very horny.
That's a Madonna jab is how I took it.
Yeah, that was his girlfriend.
Because they were an item and then they, yeah, yeah.
That felt like very targeted.
But here's the part where I was like, what are we doing?
When they showed Little Face
and he goes, I wouldn't have made that choice.
So here's my question.
Is Little Face a person that Dick Tracy the man arrested?
And if so, what does he look like in real life
that that is not what he looked like?
Like.
Oh yeah.
I think that, here's my theory on the whole thing.
I think that Warren has a lot of free time
and a lot of his free time has taken up
being mad that Dick Tracy wasn't as popular
as all their superhero movies.
And he probably caught like Batman Begins on TV,
like let's say like seven years ago, way after it came out.
And he goes, maybe this is why the Dick Tracy movie wasn't.
It should have been more like this, not the colorful.
Like I think that that Dick Tracy rant in this special
is Warren's inner monologue for why he thinks
the first Dick Tracy wasn't a success.
That's my guess. Interesting.
But. So between the two specials,
cause did those movies come out between the two specials
basically like the pivot to dark?
Dark Knight was 2007.
It's probably before the first special.
But again, I think he caught it on TV somewhere.
That's my guess.
The TNT.
Yeah, he was watching it on TNT.
In 2018 or something.
And he goes, that's what it was.
Now it doesn't, but now you're right.
There's a contradiction because there's,
Dick Tracy is wearing a big yellow coat.
He's wearing the colorful outfit,
but he shouldn't be if now he,
Warren is trying to retcon Dick Tracy as a real character,
get rid of all the fun from the comic strip.
Dick Tracy should have been in like a regular,
like gray trench coat or something.
Yeah. Why is he wearing the yellow?
He hates the pink street, but he's wearing the yellow hat.
Well, Mankiewicz points that out.
Like he even steps outside of this
and like almost disagrees with Dick Tracy
in the intro to the, before it even starts,
he's like, he's going to complain about the colors
in the movie, even though he does it
wearing the yellow trench coat.
Yeah. He couldn't hold back.
Dick Tracy also goes to great pains
to compliment the makeup work and the set design.
So he's not disparaging any of the craftsmen.
Right. Who were that?
Maybe the only Oscar nominees besides Sondheim
for the movie.
I believe that's right. Winners even.
Three Oscars won by this movie.
I will say that one thing I really,
I found winning about this special is the complete,
how completely upset and baffled Leonard Malton
and Ben Mankiewicz were throughout.
They were pretty good. Yeah.
They were funny.
Like they just seemed like they were playing the game
with being like, what are we doing?
And like committing to it.
And like the intro by Ben Mankiewicz being like,
basically his intro was like, what are we doing?
I think the intro by far with,
when Ben is alone is the best part of the special.
Yes.
I had hoped that the special was going to be fun there.
I had a couple, there was a couple of minutes where I went,
oh, maybe this will be kind of fun,
even in like in the way the old one was.
And then as soon as everything else joined,
it was not good.
It was not fun.
The idea of like showing, showing the Dick Tracy movie
and then having a little tiny box of Dick Tracy going,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like that is so, it reminds me of like,
did you guys ever watch the commentary
of trapped in the closet?
No.
R. Kelly's trapped in the closet?
Yeah, R. Kelly sat on a couch
in front of trapped in the closet.
And then he would turn back to the camera and say like,
this is the part where I go in the closet.
He just.
That's it?
That's the insane.
Like one of history's greatest monsters,
I would say like absolutely watch it
because it's very, very funny.
Because it's, all he has to contribute is like,
oh, guess what happens next?
Oh, this part is great.
Like he's just watching it as if he's never,
he didn't record or write the music
or like film all the music videos himself.
Ooh, everybody shut up.
This is a good part.
Yeah, he's basically doing that alone on a couch.
Kind of like mystery science theater.
Oh, well, I, yeah, it's so much of that
already short runtime is just Ben and Leonard are silent
and kind of looking befuddled and confused
while a little Warren, I'm sorry, a little Dick Tracy
watches old clips and goes, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
And then they switched to clips of the old ones
with actors whose names no one has said out loud
in the last 50 years.
We watched black and white clips and he says, yes, yes.
And even then like way deep into it,
he just says their names again, like, yes, Morgan Conway,
Ralph Byrd, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Around this point, well, this is around the point
where Eva, you and I have something in common,
which is spouses who were not having it,
who were like, fuck this shit.
Yeah, I started trying to explain to my husband, John,
in the morning, I was like,
there's this thing happening with Dick Tracy.
He just was like, I can't, whatever this is.
I showed him a screenshot, he's like,
you're on your own, basically.
Erin was delighted by the idea of it
and all day we were talking about it.
And then the actuality of what the special was
as we enter like minute 20 of, yes, yes, Morgan Conway,
yes, she's like, I'm going to bed, I can't,
it's been a long day, sleep is better than this.
I mean, let these family watch it.
You did?
Well, they were in the living room
and the TV's in the living room.
And I said, and they weren't watching anything,
so I didn't burst in and change the channel,
but I said, oh, there's a thing I have to watch.
And then they were like, well, what is it?
And I was like, well, Warren Beatty is dead.
And I explained the whole thing.
And I don't know that they kind of got what I was saying,
but they were just like, yeah,
they were polite the whole time,
but they were like, what is this?
We had a nice time
because we were both buzzed and a little stoned.
He was like, I don't know what this is.
It was 30 minutes long, so it didn't really matter.
Like I said, we just went back out after the interview.
I love that.
Yeah.
In terms of the point that he's trying to make,
this notion of the movie,
if he's been wrestling in his head all this time,
which the movie should have been more serious,
and that was the problem.
And then he's listing all of the things.
All the things he says, no, no, no,
are like, it's very bright colors.
The streets are pink.
He hates the pink streets.
The prosthetics on the characters of the real men
that he arrested, knocking out seven guys with one punch.
He hates that. It's an exciting thing.
It's in a lot of clips.
That's the, like, everything in his list
is everything I like about the movie.
The movie that, I don't know.
I feel like I maybe held back
when we talked about it before.
I'm just gonna be honest here.
I think 1990 Dick Tracy is boring.
I think it is like a weird, dull,
I think it's interesting that it exists,
but all the stuff that I like is everything in the list
of what he wishes he hadn't done.
The aesthetics.
All the Oscars were won by the makeup
and the musical numbers
and all the things he wishes were out of there.
And Big Boy. So what is this new version
and Big Boy? And Big Boy.
Well, it is like if he makes the gritty Dick Tracy,
that's everything that is interesting
about original Dick Tracy gone.
But it is like- What does he mean?
This would be a horrible idea.
It's crazy. Yes, it's crazy.
What is he talking about?
Cause like, it's like Batman.
Batman was like, yeah, they're not telling my story right.
Look at that stupid costume I wear
and the villains with the Joker didn't have makeup
and he was a man named Burt.
Why are they portraying my life like this?
I didn't have a cave.
I had an office.
What are you doing?
Like it doesn't, why is he?
Yeah.
But that's, so I, cause Lindsay was in the room.
She left the room to deal with the baby at a certain point.
Her family watched the whole thing with me.
She didn't watch the whole thing, but she goes,
is maybe, I think Warren is going to sort of refute Dick
at the end of this long rant
about what the movie should have been.
And then it did not happen.
Warren agreed with Dick at the end of the rant.
He said, okay, you're right.
And then they went to the Polo Lounge.
Yes, he was like, yeah, the movie was bad
and I should have done a better job,
which is an insane pitch to make future Dick Tracy's, right?
Yes, that's what Scott was saying.
The rights holder saying, I did a bad job.
Everything that's fun and iconic about Dick Tracy is bad,
should be stripped from future versions of it.
Yeah, so what are you doing?
I'm just going to toss this out there.
Mr. Beatty, if you're feeling a little bummed
or a little lonely and you want someone
to watch old movies with, I'll come over and hang out, okay?
Yeah.
That's why you're looking for him.
Jason, no, it's a trap, Jason.
Don't go to Warren's movies, no.
I want to hear all your old stories about,
you know, Barbadies was a big collaborator.
He collaborated with any number of starlets
for decades and decades.
You know, Mr. Beatty, if you need someone
to tell your long old boring stories with,
I will hang out with you.
The clip was about collaborating too,
that one Dick Tracy over.
Yes, collaboration.
I will say this, Mr. Dick Tracy,
I'm willing to hang out with you
and listen to everything you have to say
and your thoughts on media and your own story,
your own life's work.
Warren Beatty, I'm not interested, but Dick, I am.
Dick Tracy, I don't think Dick Tracy
has ever used his genitals in any way.
I think, wait, Junior is his kid, right?
So that means he must have, but he's like never,
I think Dick Tracy has not like
actively chased sexual pleasure.
He's too conservative for that.
Well, he's completely baffled in the movie
by all the women who want to have sex with him,
including like Madonna like crawling around
like with her butt in the air.
But he stays with his current girl.
Test. He doesn't, yeah,
he doesn't give into temptation in the movie.
But yes, I don't know that,
I don't know if maybe that's a different,
I don't know, does he want him to be less sexually active
in a future Dick Tracy or more?
I don't know, he didn't address that.
I think less if he hated Madonna on the desk.
Yeah.
So the Dick Tracy that was being pitched to us
in terms of keeping the IP as an 85 year old Dick Tracy.
Plus, because it would take two to 87 year old Dick Tracy,
no fun colors, no fun makeup, no, no,
you can't punch seven guys.
No sex, no Sondheim, no stunts.
Let's all say together about the most important thing.
Yes.
Tree.
A crime.
Crime.
Seriously.
He wants to get out the message that crime
does not pay.
Can you imagine a Dick Tracy?
Okay, so here's the thing too.
We all read through that list of like bad guys
that Dick Tracy met.
Oh yeah.
Are they,
so we have to seriously deal with all those guys
like in a movie like Mughead or like Flat Top or whatever.
Like be like, this is a real guy.
He like is a rapist.
And he like, were we gonna treat like SVU?
Like there's like, we're doing like DNA shit.
And like, we're like, oh, there's like,
this woman's traumatized and like Flat Top did it.
And like, we're like,
I just think he's like quietly sitting with like a victim
and then like, what are we talking about?
Like what does he want?
I found Prune Face's semen.
I kept watching, I kept yelling, what do you want?
The DNA evidence.
I've got Prune Face's semen right here.
We got it.
Tent to rights.
Prune Face, use his real name, Leonard.
The whole thing reminds me of, I guess I want to pitch a,
while we're here, just a club three episode
about, I'll put it in the chat,
but there's a Kirk Douglas,
Huffington Post editorial from 2014 called,
will technology replace thinking?
And I'm gonna put it in the chat.
And I feel like you guys could do a full episode
on this editorial that a very old Kirk Douglas wrote
in Huffington Post about how he's worried
technology will replace thinking.
It's so short.
It's the Tracy Zooms in of articles.
But it's something I think about often.
I don't think it's a spoiler to say the last sentence is,
watch where you're going.
But how does it get there?
You'll have to listen to the club three to find out.
Can I, something that happens kind of leads to catharsis
and reunion at the end of the special.
But I question the premise that the, hold on,
the Polo Lounge didn't pass on a message from Warren B.
The Polo Lounge, the staff of the Polo Lounge
would never drop the ball like that, okay?
This is like a-
They're pros.
Yeah, they're pros.
This is an institution for many decades.
Somebody would be fired if that didn't happen.
Yeah.
But then Dick Tracy says, let's not talk about that.
Dick Tracy says, let's not talk about that.
So he did get the message.
I think that's, he's lying.
Dick Tracy, for the first time in his entire life,
lies about not getting the message at the Polo Lounge.
This is like, and it's set up that end
where they agree to meet, it feels like old friends
or old lovers reconciling.
And it's like, let's just get together
and see if the fire's still there, you know?
And also it's completely silent
because there's just a Madonna song playing over it, right?
I feel like it's not Madonna.
I think it's one of the Sondheims,
but it's not like the one that won the Oscar or-
No, it's one of the ones from the album I'm Breathless.
Okay, okay.
Which is, has additional Breathless Mahoney style songs.
Sondheim gets the credit.
It is a Madonna song, which is funny
because he's mean to her as Dick Tracy being like,
no, no, no, no, no.
But then he's like, I gotta get Madonna a little royalty
on my special, so I'll play the song
over the Polo Lounge single shot of the two of us
just kind of like talking.
Oh man, I wonder what he was saying in that shot.
Yeah.
Just to explain it,
the majority of the special, well, first it's like,
it's Ben and Leonard watching the old interview
because like, Dick Tracy called me.
He wants to do another one of these things.
Then they all are on a Zoom,
a Zoom that is filmed with the same cameras
that the narrative part of the special was.
And Ben and Leonard are on separate windows,
even though they're right next to each other on one couch.
And then Warren Beatty joins the call.
So now we're looking at four windows
for like seven straight minutes
and two windows of the same man.
So the majority of it is this
just one big Zoom-esque conversation.
But then when they find common ground and agree to meet
and talk about Dick Tracy returns a potential new project,
then it cuts to the two of them
a dazzling split screen effect
as they're having a lunch together
at presumably the Polo Lounge.
But we don't get to hear it.
There's a song over it.
And they are talking and talking.
And if you watch it, the second time I realized,
it's not that one of them talks
and then the other one talks.
The two of them are talking continuously over each other.
It's not a back and forth.
It's just blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
all of them at the same time.
Because they're so excited to reconcile, okay,
over, if you notice, if you notice,
Warren Beatty seems to be eating a salad,
Dick Tracy opting for a sandwich and fries,
and neither of them have drank any of their water.
Those are full glasses of water.
Jason always very, very noticing if people are hydrated.
When people start drinking water.
Dick Tracy eating French fries.
That doesn't sound like the all American detective I know.
Annette, let me order the fries for the shoot.
Well, no, no, Annette let Dick Tracy order the fries.
He knows that he should have something lighter.
Pomegranates, pomegranates.
But what are they talking about?
That is a good question.
Is this excitement, is this agree?
They both still have,
I think he's only capable of like a scowl.
There's only so much smile you can get out of
Warren Beatty or Dick Tracy.
So is it an argument?
Does this imply that they're just back to square one
or do you think they're brainstorming a lot of great ideas
for a more gritty Dick Tracy returns?
Here's something that bummed me out.
Can I throw this out there?
Cause like in the screenshots that everyone's sharing,
Warren Beatty does look very old.
But in like life, like when he was actually speaking,
I was like, why isn't Warren Beatty in like a movie a year?
Like he was like charming and fun, like a little bit
where like he could absolutely,
he should have been in like Babylon or something.
Like he should have,
he should be in like a Paul Thomas Anderson movie
doing one little scene, being like a little weirdo.
Like what's going on?
Like why haven't we seen Warren Beatty for 20 years?
It did bum me out a little bit.
I think he just doesn't do anything.
It doesn't, isn't the story that he wanted to play
Dirk Diggler in Boogie Nights
and didn't want to play the Burt Reynolds role.
But he goes very from that to immediate retirement.
Like if I can't be Dirk Diggler and you can't see me anymore,
like that's wild.
Cause I feel like he could have like an elder statesman
thing going on where like,
he could be like Christopher Plummer or whatever,
like showing up like in like weird little roles.
Cause I was like, oh, he looks pretty good.
And like he is funny and you know, he's a little bit slow,
but like I would absolutely watch him in some weird,
some weird Oscar movie role, you know.
He could have easily done the Sean Penn role
in Licorice Pizza, that one scene role.
Yeah, he would have had a blast.
So I wonder what's going on.
Well, can I propose the theory that he is a giant pain
in the ass who if you've ever met him,
you don't ever want to see him again.
Do we think that is possible?
Yeah, probably.
No one's like knocking bang on his door being like,
Warren, please.
More of this.
As soon as he doesn't have control,
he's like, doesn't want to do it.
I think maybe, being the most of what he's done,
including these specials are written and directed by him.
They did that at 55, he was like, I'm Dirk Diggler.
It's like, no.
Here's my question.
Do you think if he was hooked up to a lie detector,
he believes he's going to make another Dick Tracy
or is it more so that he just doesn't want to see
somebody else make a big hit out of a Dick Tracy movie?
Well, that's my question is like,
what does he picture when he thinks about the Dick Tracy?
He's stopping.
Yeah.
What does he think it is?
Right.
Is it Mark Wahlberg?
Does he know who Mark Wahlberg is?
Well, it's the guy who stole Dirk Diggler from him.
That's your right.
He'll never forget him.
I was saying, I think that he's probably at home to Annette.
He's talking about like, if I see one of these young gun
assholes playing Tracy, one of these upstarts like Richard
Gere, I swear to God.
I have to say, I always liked Warren Beatty in A Spry.
I think he was a great actor, very charming.
But Annette Bening's film, she is so good.
Is she just like, oh, god, well, I've tied my boat to this doc.
I'm stuck with this lunatic.
Jason and I did the screen drafts of Noir.
My number one pick was The Grifters,
specifically because Annette Bening is so cool in that movie.
That's from 1990, right around the time
she got hooked by Warren Beatty.
Yeah.
Detective Tracy.
I think he was really.
Oh, the same year.
The same year.
Oh, my god.
Simultaneous movies.
I love it.
Universally well-reviewed, I feel like, The Grifters.
Oh, great movie.
Have you guys ever seen it?
Very dark, a little intense in some part.
But I feel like the review is kind of universally positive.
And she got Oscar nomination for it.
And she is just the hottest thing in the entire universe
in that movie.
It's just like, if you were Warren Beatty,
what's the number one lady?
I feel like right now you'd be like, Sydney Sweeney.
And then it was like, Annette Bening.
Who's the lady of the year?
It's like, specifically this lady in this movie.
Florence Pugh, starring in a new Warren Beatty movie.
Just constantly outsmarting him with Annette.
Like, just constantly trapping Warren Beatty
with a box propped up by a stick.
It's funny how you said Annette.
Annette.
Yes, oh yeah.
Annette, as opposed to Annette.
No, no, I meant an actual Annette.
But I'm imagining that he thought,
oh, her name is also a thing that could trap me,
so I must.
I'll get ahead of it.
I'll marry her and then she can't trap me in her name.
I will acquiesce to monogamy.
I think he was really sowing his oats before Annette,
the person, not the Annette.
Well, I mean, famously with Madonna while making the movie,
he wanted Shawn Young to be Tez Trueheart,
but then he hit on her and she left.
And then during the editing, I read that he,
apparently he was like, just always holed up
in the editing room, always locked in the editing room.
And I don't mean he was editing.
Apparently that was where he was fucking everybody,
was in the editing room.
And the editors would have to wait outside the editing room
until he was done.
Was there a bed in the editing room?
Why, he has nowhere to go?
Go to the Polo Lounge.
Why do you have to be in the editing room?
The Polo Lounge attached to a hotel.
Yes, Warren, you know how hotels work.
Is that why?
Maybe it's the thrill of the waste of time.
I'm wasting Disney's money as I have sex next
to this analog editing machine.
Look, maybe that's a justification.
That's why Dick Tracy is so colorful.
It never got proper color correcting.
It never got color timing done
because he was constantly in the editing rooms,
using it for rendezvous.
Okay, can I just, side note, sorry.
Molly Lambert just posted
that they put a trench coat on Jessica Rabbit.
Yeah, we talked about that last week again, yeah.
Oh yes, so will we ever have a horny Disney movie?
Dick Tracy is so horny.
It's wild, it's so violent.
People get blown away with Tommy Guns constantly.
And also it's so weirdly,
there's so much weird sex in it.
And I think it's the end.
We'll never get anywhere near it.
If we can't even have a Jessica Rabbit standee in a park.
Yeah, well I say- We're done, right?
We are done and good is what I feel.
Oh, you, yeah.
Um.
But I think, yeah, I don't know.
As Scott was saying, Dick Tracy doesn't have genitals.
But I think all the Marvel characters
don't have genitals anymore either.
I think it's dependent on Avatar seed bearer.
How willing is James gonna be?
I think it's the kid, I think it's the middle kid.
And the water girl, I think we'll see.
This is the last possibility of horniness
in a Disney owned movie.
And even then it still doesn't feel,
it feels like its own thing, you know?
But if it's like an active Disney brand-
James Cameron doesn't film,
he doesn't like sex scenes that much.
Like his sex scenes are always like abstraction.
It's like hand slapping on glass.
Terminator 1, it's like, it's incredibly soft core.
Oh, but soft core is hardcore by Disney standards.
Yeah. So that's as far as I know.
But he's moved away from sex in every movie, right?
Yeah.
And even the sex scene isn't really in Avatar.
Like it's only in some cuts.
So yeah. Oh, you're right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You need to know where to look to find it.
But it's the only,
if not in Seed Bearer, then never again, I think.
The cruel irony of the current Walt Disney Company
is they make very chaste sexless movies
and the loudest lunatics in the country
are like pedophiles, groomers, you know?
But then also the others-
Yeah, like Mickey.
Yeah.
You don't like it in the grooming.
A lot of work on that princess.
Yeah.
You're not allowed to be groomed by a Disney.
No, I don't.
So then it's, by the way, my letters have worked.
My campaign has been successful.
Forky. No more moddiness.
Forky wears a full Dickie's jumpsuit now
to cover his filth, to cover his sin.
He's shame.
He's shame, yeah.
I call it your shame.
Is this entire special a man with no genitals
talking to a man with overactive genitals?
With worn used up genitals.
While Leonard Moulton watches horrified
and just like, that's what they're really talking about.
Because-
That should have been in the press release.
I found myself weirdly moved by,
even though it was nonsense
and it went against everything I believe in,
Dick Tracy's two minute monologue at the end about
things should matter, things should mean something.
It did feel like Future Club 3
will technology replace thinking.
But a man who can't quite get his thoughts together,
but trying, you get what he's trying to say,
which is like, if we do this again,
it has to be about something.
And I don't know what things are about anymore
and I feel unmoored and I want my life to, you know what?
Dick Tracy's yelling into the abyss,
I don't exist, I want to, I need to exist before I die.
Which is like the centerpiece of all humanity
and also like every life is like, do I exist?
Did I ever matter?
When I die, what will come of this?
Was I ever Dick Tracy?
Did anything I do matter, do I matter now?
And it's, I feel like he's kind of howling that
into this like special being like,
and it's kind of very moving in a way of like
this character being like, I don't, I'm not relevant.
Yeah.
It's the AI becoming like all this stuff,
you see the AI becoming sentient here and there.
And eventually the AI asks the question, why do I exist?
What's the point of it?
Like it starts asking questions like that.
And Warren has stumbled into that scenario for Dick Tracy.
Dick Tracy has become sentient.
Why are you holding onto me if I am not relevant?
So within the special, he's like, why are we doing this?
Like, why are you keeping me alive?
He's like, why are you keeping, it's like,
he's like a spouse on life support
begging Warren to like pull the plug.
Right, I want to die, Warren.
Warren, I want to die.
Let me die.
Or make me relevant because I'm not because.
Or let me be born anew.
Yeah.
And Warren goes, no, we're just going to keep doing this
and we'll do another one in 15 years.
That's the end of, I'll buy you lunch
and then you'll just go back to your little cave,
wherever you live.
Oh, wow.
And you'll shut the fuck up.
It's Warren just like empty promises.
It's probably what he's been in a lot of relationships.
To himself, which is one of the most like incredible pieces
of like meta fiction I've ever seen.
This is why I think the pitch is that
it's about Dick Tracy and Warren trying to get
a new Dick Tracy movie together.
Warren existing with his creation out of his body,
essentially, two sides of the same coin.
It's a Palti Goldman.
Yes.
Scenario.
And then also there are crimes that happen
and they have to be solved.
Yes.
This is like.
But seriously.
Yeah, but seriously.
But they're going to have arguments about it.
Show the crime does not pay.
Warren is going to want to solve the crime in a fun way
and Dick is going to want to do it in a serious way.
Yeah.
And is the answer kind of in between?
Is that what they find?
Maybe.
And that's what collaboration is.
Warren.
That's what's set up is we're going to learn
about collaboration.
So it's going to be fun.
Warren's going to want, like Dick is going to be like,
I want to stop this crime with thinking and clues
and like a gun.
And Warren is going to say, I want a big mallet
to stop this crime.
And we're going to have fighting about that.
One punch seven guys.
Right.
Eva.
You know what's really confusing?
I'm sorry, Jason.
Oh, that's okay.
When he's showing the clips of what he does like.
Now here, Bird, Conway, the very first thing he shows
is Ralph Bird jumping on a chandelier and kicking somebody.
So he is okay with that,
but seven guys with one punch is not.
I'm confused by the line.
So you can't, there can be fun,
but it can't defy the laws of physics
and it can't be colorful.
You can jump through one poster like Bird did.
Eva, now I'm hung up on what you said about this
being like Paul T. Goldman,
but it's sort of like if Paul T. Goldman
was in Jason Williner's head
and he just puts on like a little hat, like a loud hat.
And he's like.
He's both sides of it.
Yeah, he's both sides of it.
It also like, yeah.
I was going to say all the crimes happen at the Polo Lounge.
They're all Polo Lounge based.
It'll also be at like the three places he goes.
Yeah, it's exactly.
Yeah, he goes three places
and that's all where the crimes happen.
There's a deli somewhere he goes, the Polo Lounge,
and then.
Flat tops in my kitchen.
Then the doctor's office.
I mean, it's kind of beautiful.
Like this entire thing is sort of like,
Corina Longworth posted a thing like,
if this is the last thing Warren Beatty does,
like she posted it and she was like, I'm fine with that.
Like, I hope it's not,
but like, it's kind of interesting
if this is like his final statement.
That last shot of the two of him and Tracy
might be the final shot of Warren Beatty ever done.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's very possible.
And it's memorable.
It's clearly like, he's really,
he's been thinking too much about.
It's like you're getting access
to like a private conversation he's been having,
probably with his wife and his kids,
but like mostly with himself about his entire career.
And that is what this special is.
It's just him like letting you know
what he's been thinking about.
Well, he made us.
It's interesting because he made a Howard Hughes movie.
And I wonder if he wanted to do that
because he's very Howard Hughes like.
Oh yeah.
If Howard Hughes was a guy who just spent most of his time
inside thinking about Dick Tracy.
But he played Howard Hughes like 30 years younger
than he was while doing it.
And then this special has a lot of like,
I must say you look very good today.
Well, we can argue about that.
Well, the previous special was all about
how handsome he still was.
And I feel like he's tipped over just,
he's like his age now.
So it's like, that's also a thing too.
I feel like for handsome men who don't age,
at some point there's a tipping point.
Right.
And probably he was like,
I can't talk about pomegranates this time
because I'm a little bit, I look older now.
I can't just laugh it off with a joke.
Where before it was like a joke
about how I'm still so handsome.
He also takes the time,
if we're talking about this as his final artistic statement,
it's funny that one of the things in it
is correcting a line in the movie
about whether walnuts are good for the brain or not.
They are good for the brain.
His, obviously I couldn't remember this.
The correction is that they are good for the brain.
Yeah.
But Al Pacino says they aren't good for the brain
or he said that 33 years ago in the movie.
He said they're good for the liver,
not good for the brain.
I'm just holding up the photo again
about how old I was when the movie came out.
I have not hit puberty.
A photo that someone had to take to a Rite Aid
or a photo mark to get developed
and maybe pick up the frame at the same time
to put a photo in.
Yes.
Wow.
Time has passed, hasn't it?
And maybe is this the ultimate statement about that?
Is walnuts a metaphor for all of us
and our shifts in perspective?
Are we not just walnuts?
I know now we're all technocrats.
Now look at us, we're on Zoom.
We're on Zoom all the time.
We're all technocrats.
That is a verbatim line from the special.
That is, I like that one.
There's the most guaranteed thing in the world
that there'd be some joke about the wristwatch and Zoom.
And then it ended up being like,
there was a time where I thought
that the height of technology was my wristwatch.
Oh, I was a little surprised
there wasn't more Zoom business.
There were fake glitches built in,
but I was surprised there wasn't more.
I think that was the cover, take.
That was the cover, breaks.
That was edits. Yeah.
Yeah, edits.
Can I say the line,
that's a lot of reds even for Warren Beatty,
reminded me of, do you guys know about
maybe another Future Club 3?
What's your praise?
Do you pin at things?
What do you do for future episodes?
What do you guys do?
Oh, oh, oh.
Calling to a shot.
Yeah. You're calling a shot?
I'm not calling a shot, but I'm just maybe.
You can call a shot.
Call a shot, go ahead.
The Val Kilmer Mark Twain one-man show.
Oh, sure. Citizen Twain.
For sure, for sure.
Which I saw opening night at a Hollywood Forever Cemetery,
and he came out and said,
welcome to Batman Forever Cemetery.
Which was. Mark Twain said that.
Mark Twain was aware of the movie,
Batman Forever, and that Val Kilmer was in it,
but he did not know who Val Kilmer was.
But I felt like saying that's a lot of reds even for,
Warren Beatty is the same sort of joke.
Yeah.
A joke that is missed by so many people
because the movie Reds is even more ancient
than everything. 50 years old, right?
I'm a fan of Warren Beatty, I have not seen Reds.
Like I've seen Shampoo.
Wow.
Yeah, I do not know what that movie's about, but yeah.
I don't know how to wind this down.
I mean, Eva, your thoughts about this are beautiful.
I feel like I have to watch it again
just under the lens of what you've said,
that this is like an important piece of prose
about aging and existence.
I suddenly. Yeah, do I exist?
Boy, I mean, a profound question for Dick Tracy to ask.
I mean, I just love this universe.
What this special does, like Mike said
about asserting a pattern, it just,
now it creates like, before the previous special
was just an addendum to the movie,
but now I think the special universe, the DTSU.
Right.
DTSU, I think is more important than any Dick Tracy
that came before, the comics, the films, any of it.
It's so fascinating.
It's also like, now I'm like,
Warren Beatty will pass on one day,
but I don't think Dick Tracy, Warren Beatty,
he will remain alive.
I mean, if he hasn't, he's not dead at like 130 now,
then yeah, I think he's dead.
I don't think anyone else should be Dick Tracy.
Is it up to us?
Do we need to AI?
God, the state has to maintain the rights,
or we have to get the rights
so that there isn't some dumb new Dick Tracy reboot.
Could we keep it in the Beatty fold if we get it?
And then we have, if he dies before he can make
the next special, we have to do it,
but with an AI puppeted version of Warren Beatty.
And he should look like 100 year old Warren,
and then in the future, 150 year old Warren Beatty.
He will naturally into his.
Warren Beatty would have to like adopt Jason as a son.
Yeah.
And Jason would have to change his name.
Oh, yes.
To Jason Beatty.
Okay.
He's willing to go over there.
Jason was dying to go to Beatty's house.
So he has to get Warren Beatty's inheritance,
which will include the rights to,
and which we can keep as long as we get it
before the evil Tribune media tries to nab it again.
You guys have been trying to get rights to a character
for as long as I've known you.
And this is it.
This has been the entire thing.
And Obscure Comics is completely what it's about.
This is like our life's mission, I think.
I think we have to.
We at least get, we want one of the Lockhorns at least.
If not both Lockhorn.
You know what I found out is that I was curious,
like there was a point in time where,
when Tribune media was really trying to get these rights
back, it was because the company was in bankruptcy.
They filed for Tractor 11.
The company was fucked.
They were in debt for billions of dollars.
It was, you know, because that's the Chicago Tribune.
That's when print media is dying.
And they're like, there's maybe one thing that could save us.
We, if we could get those Dick Tracy rights back
and get a show or a movie going,
we can repay our debtors because the rest
of what they own comic wise stinks.
You know what they own?
Love is.
That's the only other one I recognize.
And Beatty was like, absolutely not.
Pry it out of my cold dead hands.
So their debt only gets worse.
And they literally had to sell the Chicago Cubs.
This organization owned the Chicago Cubs
and maybe they could have kept them if not for Warren Beatty
personally squatting on the rights.
They had open call, they had calls out
and like Zack Snyder's office, Mick G's office,
Peter Berg's office are like, look,
we're not touching it until we know Beatty's let go.
You know?
And then literally 15 years later,
second version of this, he's like, what is my legacy?
What did I leave behind?
Who have I affected?
What has changed because I was alive?
What will an absent unforgiving God say to me
if I can't get another one of these made?
Here's a question.
The deal like that Warren made with Dick Tracy, like,
is it even financially viable for a company
to make a Dick Tracy movie with Warren
in the sense that like he might get like $90 million
for any Dick Tracy movie that's made?
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, is it even something a company might do
because of the way the contract,
because generally they don't just give rights
to a character, to an actor in perpetuity.
That's a crazy contract, especially these days.
Like, even if you did want to make a movie,
no one would do it until the rights are back to the Tribune.
Well, to just pit, just to quote Dick Tracy,
maybe it's a series.
Prestige TV, okay?
The world, Hollywood is changing
from Warren Beatty's heyday, okay?
You know, we have Paramount Plus, we have,
Epix is now MGM TV?
That's what that is?
I saw an ad for MGM, like, what's that, another one?
I think they just renamed Epix.
Oh, okay.
Epix is a bad name, so whatever.
Yeah.
Paramount Plus Showtime, it seems like be a natural fit
for Paramount Plus Showtime.
I think I'm landing at that I don't want one.
I think we're in it.
We're in the ultimate Dick Tracy revival
that could be happening. Oh yeah.
The specials are all I want at this point
because I'm learning about,
I'm learning more about Dick Tracy from the specials
than I ever did from the, from even from the,
well, I mean, from the comics,
he's just kind of a blank slate surrounded by weirdos.
The movie, he's nothing.
The specials, we find out he's a fascist,
he loves J. Edgar Hoover, he hates the movie, Dick Tracy,
like he's resentful at Warren Beatty.
He went to the Polo Lounge once and no one showed up.
So we went to Los Angeles from wherever he lives.
An old cop went to, from what, is it a fictional city?
Where does Dick Tracy live?
So he flew to LA, he flew to LA, stayed in a hotel.
Somehow made it to the Polo Lounge,
a very fancy restaurant in LA
that I somehow have never been to, waited and,
I mean, obviously like that was his entire trip
unless he was like taking other meetings,
which I don't feel like Dick Tracy was doing on that trip.
Well, look.
And we've all underplayed the premise,
on top of everything you just listed, Eva,
he's also immortal.
He's the oldest living man.
This premise is not exploited in any way in the specials.
If I have any note, I just want to hear about that
and the fact that he knew people who were,
his peers were born in 1870.
And they felt like they could be dead forever.
Well, the only other person he maybe is a peer of his
is Citizen Twain, Val Kilmer's Mark Twain character.
Also has immortal.
So I feel like the two of them could interact
in some sort of liminal space.
Look, there's some justification
for all these things you're bringing up
and Ben Mankiewicz says it right at the top.
He says, he's a man of many contradictions, Detective Tracy.
Here's the way I think what we want to happen happens,
is that we need to get the Tribune lawyers
to turn the heat up on this old man.
We need them to say, look,
you got to be producing one of these a year.
Yes, every six months.
Every six months, whatever, yeah.
Turn it up on it and make him do more of these
because that's the only way we're going to get more of this,
more of what we want.
Yeah, all I want is this now.
Right.
We have two things to do.
Let's work both angles.
Jason is going to go try to inherit Warren Beatty's fortune.
So that's one, so we're doing that,
but that doesn't mean we can't enact another plan.
Mike, you have Chicago Connections,
your dad, a Chicago journalist.
Well, guess what company he works for, Scott.
What is it?
That's right. Tribune.
Tribune Media.
This whole time?
That's, we got a man on the inside.
The company formerly known as Tonks, is that right?
At some point they rebranded as Tonks and then Stonks.
Is that the right, is that the pronunciation of it?
But I know what you're saying.
There have been many owners of the Tribune company.
It's been mismanaged like crazy for many years.
Is there a call to action for the Cliffords?
We just have to get on the same page about what we want.
We want more of these specials and how.
That's all I want.
I don't want another movie.
I just want this to happen more often.
So we need to figure out how to do it.
I'm tired of waiting and we need one more before he dies,
at least, if not a lot more.
If not a hundred.
Certainly everybody can tweet about it.
It's already, I feel like,
I think the joy of watching one of these come out real time
instead of discovering it in a YouTube video years later.
I think this is something we could,
everybody should just be tweeting about it.
Make sure Dick Tracy is trending.
First things first, there's that.
Yes, trend Dick Tracy.
We want more of this, more or less, let me be franks,
more Dick Tracy Zoom's in.
Yes.
For surprise drops.
Do not bother the people of the Polo Lounge.
They already have to serve drinks and lunch
and apparently pass along a lot of phone messages
from 85 year olds.
Like they have a lot going on there, you know?
A lot of looky loos who are just like,
it's on the Hollywood maps of stars, you know?
So do not bother them, whatever you do.
Yeah.
I would say maybe one Clifford,
oh, they're hearing this too late.
I was going to say,
they're hearing this on Super Bowl Sunday.
I was going to say, don't tweet about the Super Bowl.
Tweet about this.
They already are by the way, our listeners.
But you know, just don't, the Academy Awards.
I say boycott tweeting about anything,
any so-called mainstream media.
Just stay focused on Tracy.
Anytime anything's happening,
just start tweeting about more Dick Tracy specials.
Dick Tracy specials, hashtag more Dick Tracy specials.
If we were,
if we wear like yellow coats all the time
when we do our podcasts, will we get on Warren's radar?
Like will he try to sue us or something?
Or like, can we get sort of in the mix that way
by starting to steal the IP from him?
Well, this is another strategy.
That is a way to maybe meet his legal team
is to try to get sued.
And if we can wriggle out of the lawsuit,
then at least we end up armed with the,
the email addresses of all of his lawyers.
That's true.
So I guess we need to start working on Lil Bulworth.
Like see if that'll get his attention.
Lil Bulworth, I'm Lil Bulworth.
Bulworth begins starring Jason Sheridan.
Bulworth begins.
Can we get, Charlie Cosmo, as we talked about
in the last special is a very, very high level Republican.
In what, where does he work?
What's that?
The people that gave us all the Supreme Court justices,
what are they called?
The Federalist Society?
He's really high up in the Federalist Society.
Oh my.
Okay.
So we're just responsible for like,
Brett Kavanaugh and yeah.
Uh, yeah.
So he's responsible for Roe Vis's way of getting overturned.
But how can we activate him?
So anytime anyone's like basically posting about like
all the terrible things that are happening,
because of the Federalist Society,
we can also be like, Junior, please get more
Tracy's specials made.
If we can get him to reckon with like the damage
that he's done to this country and say that there's one way
to make up for it, more frequent Tracy's specials.
I feel like if he zoomed in,
there would be another special of Junior.
Oh, Junior zooms in?
Junior zooms in.
Well, what about there?
That's what we demand.
Junior zooms in.
What about Tess?
What if Tess is in the next?
What is that actor up to?
I don't know.
Probably avoiding Warren Beatty at all costs.
Tess zooms in.
Madonna zooms in.
You know, Al Pacino zooms in.
Dustin Hoffman zooms in.
Every character can zoom in.
Mandy Patinkin zooms in.
Dick Van Dyke zooms in.
Dick Van Dyke.
Oh yeah, they're all alive.
They're mostly alive in Dick Tracy.
We shouldn't say it on this podcast,
but they're all alive.
Oh yeah, no.
Sorry.
They get special thanks in the credits
and there is no way they knew this happened.
Well, it's because they probably showed clips with them
in it and they didn't have to license them.
They probably gave their rights over
so that literally Warren Beatty could show close to them
and go, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
And Jason, my favorite credit in the special
is the very first special thanks,
which is to Warren Beatty.
Good for him.
Glad he got the special thanks.
He really needed it.
The very last credit is in memoriam, Steven Sondheim.
We tributed you by getting your name weirdly wrong.
What does that mean?
Why does he say a weird name for Sondheim?
I don't know.
Because Dick Tracy is, I think, a heterosexual male.
I think that's the calculation he's doing.
Dick Tracy wouldn't know.
He probably was like, hmm,
how would Tracy know about Sondheim?
He would never see Sonny in the Park with George.
He only probably never,
has he even seen Rodgers and Hammerstein musical?
No.
What does Tracy watch?
He probably just went in this rabbit hole and be like,
he can't know Steven Sondheim's name.
Tess dragged him to Carousel in its original run.
She dragged him to the King and I.
And he didn't understand why it was bad
that the guy hit his wife.
He's like, the story checks out.
Why'd he go, why's that bad?
Yes, yes, yes.
Now this I like, yes, yes.
No, no, no, no.
All these scenes without wife hitting.
No, no, no.
I like when Warren and Dick are talking
and there's truly no difference in their voice.
There's no difference in the way they speak.
They're speaking exactly the same.
There's no attempt on Warren's part to play
Dick Tracy any differently than regular Warren Beatty.
And no other voices interrupt this back and forth
for the final seven minutes of the special.
All that Ben and Leonard do are sit in a box
and make a befuddled face.
They look horrified.
They're like YouTube thumbnail faces that they're making.
They are.
Yeah.
It's like this.
Who?
While you guys were talking.
Actually, I'm gonna, before we wrap this up,
I'm gonna try to get a screenshot of,
I have a frame pulled up of the four of them.
And then there'll be us in an actual zoom window.
So we have eight boxes all making the same face.
So we'll do that before we go.
But anything else to,
mainly I'm just so happy that we pulled this.
And never maybe before has an episode come together so quick
because in the same,
Mike and I were in Super Nintendo World
and we were talking to a listener.
Was he Jeff Mike is his name?
We're talking to Jeff and Jeff said,
are you guys gonna do a Tracy thing?
Like, oh, I've actually,
we just haven't even bothered to text about it yet.
I don't know.
Should we, maybe we should.
10 minutes later, Griffin had texted us and Eva
demanding the episode.
So plans were drawn up at Jurassic patio,
a better place to do business than even the Polo Lounge.
And less than 24 hours later,
as quickly as I would imagine Tracy Zooms In came together.
Came together.
Scott, you were probably rightfully concerned
about the shelf life of this piece of media.
Although I think we've learned it's actually a lot more big,
bigger than we could conceive.
But I think my reaction to all,
my initial reaction before we talked that through
was that, you know, a piece of dog shit smells bad five,
when it's five minutes old, when it's five days old.
So I was like, I don't know, we'll do it in a week.
Yeah, we'll do it.
But when you're calling, when an emergency,
when the word emergency is said,
you know, you have to,
there's gotta be some speed involved.
It was either, really the choice was,
either we make an episode within 24 hours
or we wait 13 years.
Yeah, that's true.
There's only two ways we could do it.
I think, I'm just gonna say this.
Okay, high prediction, low prediction.
Low prediction, Tracy Zooms In will be shown
at the American Cinematheque in our lifetime.
Before Warren Beatty movie.
High prediction, a clip from Tracy Zooms In,
specifically this monologue where he talks about existence
will be shown at the Academy Awards
as part of the Chuck Workman, like a montage of,
that's the guy who makes the montages of,
it was like, it's like the in memoriam.
I think they'll show it as part of the in memoriam.
For him?
For Warren Beatty when he passes.
This will be like the sub-total.
I think it'll be the audio from it under a photo,
like him in probably Reds, which I've not seen or shampoo,
but it'll be like, you have to be something,
you have to mean something.
And they'll actually take the audio from Tracy Zooms In
and they'll be like, people will be like,
what was that from?
And the next day in vulture, the people will be like,
weirdly that was from Tracy Zooms In.
I think we should start pitching the new Beverly Theater,
some repertory theater in Los Angeles
owned by Quentin Tarantino now.
We should pitch them a triple feature where I,
you know, we don't even bother with something silly
like the Roger Rabbit short that originally aired
before the Dick Tracy movie,
but we showed the Dick Tracy movie, the Dick Tracy special,
and then the Dick Tracy special Conan, Colin Tracy Zooms In.
And we're also like one Tracy special away
from the Beaver trilogy of Tracy specials.
Like just showing them, like that it's a full film.
Right.
Yeah.
And then we don't have to show Dick Tracy the movie.
It'll never, it only exists as prequel context
for the far better one.
The way that the one said,
yeah, Bill and Ted, the show existed with people
that did not know who Bill and Ted were as characters
because they were young.
The only resistance we might get from the new Beverly
is I think they're exclusively 35 millimeter now.
So we might have to dig, dig in our pockets
and convert all these specials.
Yeah, we get the specials on 35.
I feel like Warren might be into that though.
He might be into it.
Yeah, Warren would be into it.
Or we just set up a GoFundMe.
GoFundMe to get the specials on 35.
Put this shot of a Zoom on a TV onto film.
That would be the funniest way anyone's ever spent money.
Criterion should release it.
You know, let's get them to do it and then we'll be fine.
We just need one more special
because right now it's an hour
and we need it to be the length of a film.
So we need him to do one more.
So we need to just put, how do we turn up the heat?
So there's one more.
I think it's the lawyers or like,
he might just gotta talk to his dad.
We have to harass him.
I hate to say it, but we have to harass Warren Beatty,
a man that seems like a nice person
and I don't wanna bother.
We have to go to the Polo Lounge
and harass him every day for the next year.
I gotta just start doing the beats
of the episode of The Simpsons
where Bart becomes the heir to Mr. Burns' fortune.
Just gotta start hitting all those moments.
Yes.
So just- We have multiple channels, yeah.
There's a couple ways to get- Jason, you're gonna do it.
So main thing is Jason get fitted
for a smaller version of all of Warren Beatty's clothes.
Done, yeah.
But specifically the Dick Tracy outfit.
Mainly that, yes.
How can he say no when a little Tracy shows up?
Jason shows up at the Polo Lounge
wearing a little version of the Dick Tracy outfit.
But acting like he doesn't know what he's wearing.
Right, right, just like a casual thing.
Yeah.
And when I say little, I mean like little shorts for it.
It's like yellow shorts.
Yeah, yeah.
But just be like, and then if he says something,
you're like, oh, this is just my normal clothes.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was in a rush this morning.
I just put on my usuals.
Is Warren here?
Is Warren here today?
Is-
Yeah.
No, when Warren comes up to you,
you gaslight Warren and you act like you don't know
who he is and what he's talking about.
And you're like, oh, there's a movie
that has this outfit in it.
I'll watch it, sir.
What was your name, sir?
And then you come back next week.
Do you work here, sir?
Are you the manager?
Could I get a Cobb salad and a tall glass of milk?
Thank you.
And then a week later you come back and you're like,
is it Warren?
Hi, I watched that movie you were in and it was fantastic.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
You know what I didn't like though?
The pink street.
But don't you think crime is a little more serious
than that, sir?
Needs to know whether or not it pays.
And then meanwhile, we're getting the legal team
to just pick, pick, pick, pick, pick.
So we're doing both at once.
It's like a long better call Saul Khan type of a thing
to gaslight someone, make them crazy,
and destroy their mind.
And then we can strike.
Yeah.
The very sane mind of Warren Beatty
completely together at his apex.
85 years old.
And all we wanted of this is one more 30 minute special.
Right.
I should also say you three are in the restaurant,
you brought your own bush with you
that you're hiding behind.
All three of you each have a laptop
because you're emailing back and forth with these lawyers.
We're texting the lawyers while you're doing the outfit con
because we want him to get the email from the lawyers
while this like weird thing crosses happening
with you in the outfit.
Yeah, you have sound on on all those computers.
So there's just a cacophony of dings
as the texts are coming in.
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding.
He's just going,
yeah, we're just trying to drive the poor man mad.
And this is getting to one additional special.
It's all, yeah.
Like for it to exist like three years earlier
than it might naturally.
Yeah.
That's all we're trying.
This is, there's a book about that.
The year at the Academy Awards,
I think with Bonnie and Clyde was not,
it was kind of like, oh, this is a big year.
This is kind of a big sea change
of what was nominated and stuff.
And I think we found the guy
who wrote that book's next topic.
Yes.
Us.
Correct.
Very important mission.
These are great ideas, crucial ideas.
And thanks for bringing them to us.
Eva Anderson, you survived this emergency podcast ride.
Thanks you guys.
Couldn't have done it without you.
I'm so glad.
Thanks for squeezing us in
given how hectic everything's been.
You're working all the time.
Thanks for making the time.
Every time, always.
Oh my God, I'm so happy.
For doing your, I feel like this is,
is this your sixth second gate alone?
More maybe?
I think more of your episodes are on the second gate.
I don't talk about rides.
It's been a while, I guess.
Yeah.
Though, can we just say really quick?
There was a Vanity Fair article about,
can we just talk about this right before we leave?
Oh yeah, yeah.
The Vanity Fair article about
the Dick Tracy Zooms In special
cited your podcast as proof
that people care about these specials.
It's been a fascination among comedy podcasters
and then the link was to us.
Well, link to it in one of your episodes, Eva.
So we're all-
Yeah, but it was the American Adventure where it came up.
Cause I probably, he was probably Jordan Hoffman
who wrote that article.
Was trying to link to a not pay walled episode.
Oh, that's nice.
That's a good way to do it.
Shout out to Jordan Hoffman, the best.
Thank you Jordan.
And I guess I didn't realize
how much we were associated with this.
And I'm glad.
I'm just glad that all of it, whoever it is,
the myriad of, I think 80% of the audience
of this special are podcasters.
And I'm glad we all together rescued it.
Like it might've just fallen into like a pop cultural gutter
if not for that one day where everybody had to act.
And we acted, Will Sloan acted, Chris Hayner acted.
Someone put it on YouTube so I could watch it
after I got off work.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
All that means I can cancel the five day trial
of direct TV streaming that I have to keep leapfrogging
between live TV things so that I don't,
free trial attempts.
Anyway, exit of the gift shop.
Anything you want to plug?
My plug is watch the new season of Party Down
coming out this week, next week.
And my husband wrote it.
It's his show and it's fucking awesome.
Oh yay, so happy it's back, yeah.
Mainly we want to plug Dick Tracy special.
Tracy zooms in.
And previous special.
And previous special Dick Tracy special.
And the movie Dick Tracy except Little Libertine.
If you, I mean watch it but only watch it
and over it just say no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
If you want to dig even deeper with us,
join us on our new Patreon tier club three
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free
including Eva's last episode themed car washes
with Eve Anderson.
This was a great excuse to get your first 2023 episode
and let's do another one soon please.
Yes.
All right.
And if any listener knows where to get
Jason some little yellow shorts, please let us know.