Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
The following podcast may trigger
severe dork-outs.
Thanks to the guest's incredible
voices and equally incredible
vintage shirts. Be on the lookout
for rapping rabbits, sun-bleached
rides, and a heavy
dose of Toronto nostalgia.
It's the Looney Tunes at Six Flags
with Looney Tunes voice
Eric Bowser on Podcast
The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
hosted by three very good boys
who are deeply uncomfortable with the
phrase, Puddy Tat.
I'm a racking frack environment
by the name of Scott Gardner
joined by my co-host, what a
maroon. It's Mike Carlson.
That's true, that is what I am.
But I'm still reeling from what you said earlier.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When I said earlier, I mean 15 seconds ago.
That was earlier than right now, yes.
We'll try to avoid
disgusting, lewd phrases such as
that. And host
number three, Aini the Stinker.
It's Jason Sheridan.
I've been sitting over here with beta breath
to see what I was given tonight.
I mean, that's, you've
said the phrase before even,
not even in the context of
the Looney Tunes. Oh, yeah.
You are the stinker of the show.
Today we are talking about
all things
Looney Tunes, including their
Six Flags association, Bugs Bunny
World at Magic Mountain.
And we're doing it because we're joined by
an excellent guest who
he voices some
of the more obscure characters
in the Looney Tunes canon.
Just some of the, you know, the more S.O.J., the deeper cuts
such as Bugs Bunny,
Daffy Duck, Porky
Pig, Elmer Fudd, Marvin
the Martian, Foghorn Leghorn, too many
to name. It's the Emmy winning
Eric Bowser. Hello.
Oh, forget about him. Do me, do me.
Daffy, it's me. Do me next.
What about, am I a loser?
And am I, what am I to you, Scott?
Lists are arbitrary.
I didn't mean to put you in any particular
order. We could do it again and you could be number one, Daffy.
Oh, I see, I see. Not good enough
for an insult from you. I get it.
Not on your radar, I see.
I didn't want to insult you.
I thought you seem a little touchy.
I don't know. I'll just go.
Come on, Daffy. Come on now.
Relax. Everyone's friends
here. I was
going to start off with like
you can do as much or as little
voices as you'd like to do.
You can steer the ship. I am just
a whore when it comes to
these characters. No, I
am just thankful to be here. Thank you, guys.
Thank you for doing it.
Again, these characters for me are
who I grew up watching
and from anyone that's
read an interview or seen another
interview, you know, you'll know
that this was the Bible for me Saturday
mornings. It was reruns.
And I guess it was the 80s,
more particularly the 90s,
where these characters had somewhat
of a like a renaissance, I guess,
because they were originally made in the
40s, 50s. And
you know, decades later
here they are in the 90s being
you know, slathered over
air fresheners, mud flaps,
you know, for 18
wheeler trucks. Coca-Cola
cans promoting Six Flags.
Is that the right brand? I think it was
Coke, right? Yeah.
And that ties in my appearance here
today is my obsession with the Looney
Toons, not just as cartoon characters, but
as backdrops to
the Six Flags Magic Mountains
theme park. Right on. You voice these
characters who are like
the corporate
faces of
you know, various parks
and not just to jump around
a little bit because we're sort of
Looney Tunes focused. I don't want to shut off
another character because
you're the voice of
the face of Six Flags,
but also a character we've talked about
a lot over the years who
is by default Universal's
Mickey and that is Woody
Woodpecker. That's right.
And it doesn't get you into
Super Nintendo World any faster
than any other. No.
You gotta watch the Virtual Q when you get
there. Hi, I'm
the voice of Woody Woodpecker. Yeah, yeah, sure pal.
Just, uh, you have a platinum
pass or not? I do and
you can go. I was there last night. The red
pass, that's what I have, the red feathers
of Woody. But here's the thing I've learned, you can
only, the only way to
skip to the front of the line
for Bowser's Castle Mario
Kart, the ride, is to have a
VIP pass, which is
$400 per pass.
But that includes a free lunch,
a tour, a guided tour.
Oh, that's what gets you the like, you're on
the back line, you're going in the sets and everything.
You're not just on the big tram. But if you're just
there, like that, that is the
only way, unless you get there right before the park
opens and you're lined up to go into
Mario land or whatever it is.
Right, right. Yeah, that's the only,
that's the hack. You have to pay $400.
Money is always the
hack. Let me tell
you something about money and theme parks.
It's what
makes those things run.
Not electricity, but
just paper money.
You've been a
universal fan, a theme parks fan
it seems like forever. Part of me asking
you if you wanted to do this was
your Instagram, which is a treasure trove
of memories of yours.
It's constantly you seemingly
proving your voice
nerd credentials,
I feel like.
You were completely the kid
who loves this stuff and now you get to do
it and how cool is that?
Again, going back to
the night, I ran
into our colleague, Kyle
Mooney at Six Flags Magic Mountain,
who we both worked with on Smash
Saturday morning. Saturday morning All Star Hits,
which you were so great on. Some of our favorite voices
in the whole thing. Thank you.
We were there because of the premiere
of, to celebrate
the premiere of Space Jam
A New Legacy, which I was lucky enough to do
one or five
voices, I don't know how many voices I did on it, but
even if I was like the out of focus
tree in the background, I would have
been happy. There were a lot of out of
focus characters in the movie. Maybe no movie
ever had more out of focus characters.
HBO Max, the movie.
With LeBron, maybe.
But yeah, we were there to celebrate that
movie and
it was kind of funny because on the red carpet,
if you were just kind of like walking in,
there was a mascot of
Daffy, but specifically
for me Sylvester. And I remember
when I first
visited Los Angeles and
first went to Six Flags,
there's photos of me and I
actually compare, I put them together
now, where it's me from like
1994 and
Sylvester in Six Flags
in 1994. And then
what, that was like two years ago
or 2020, like in the
thick of the pandemic. It was actually
a big thing that we were even able to go
to Six Flags to do this because
it was that one week in LA
where there wasn't COVID, if you
remember. They're like, hey, it's gone. Let's
go out and lick fire hydrants
and stuff. And then
Cut the Six Flags padlock. Yeah, and
then literally after that movie premiered,
lockdown again. But
I remember being on that
red carpet wanting to take that photo knowing
that that photo existed in
1994 at that exact same
theme park. Wow, wow. So I
had put them to, I put them like
side by side so you could see
how little I've grown
since then. I'm still like
a tiny person.
But a tiny nerd.
To that end,
do we have that picture, Jason?
I think you loaded up a photo. I loaded up
a photo.
Eric, I got this on your... Blackmail photo, right?
This is the... Yeah, yeah. We will show this
to all of our viewers. This is available
on ForeverDog on the YouTube
also. Well, Eric, you might be ahead of
me because I see you brought a shirt.
But I emailed... Oh, this
might be the exact shirt that we
may or may not see any minute.
If not now, we could see it later,
I'm sure. If we did...
This is, I think, a picture of you
in... You were in eighth
grade. Do I have that right?
If the braces are correct
and the laser background
is correct, that was the... Yeah, the laser background
really gives away a range of
dates. That was the era.
Not to date yourself, but never post
a photo of you with lasers in the background.
Because it looks like
I was like a jewel thief.
Like I was in a heist.
You were in the middle. I was in mid-heist.
Oh, there it is. Look at this. Just that
weird Widow's Peak that I have
there. Oh, there it is. Oh, God!
The further down you go, the
worse it gets. Keep going. We've seen the braces.
Scroll down. This is like it's loading
on Windows in 1985. Yeah, I
feel like I'm trying to download
pornography in the 90s.
We're just trying to get to a kid's shirt
though. We're not trying to do something weird.
We're not trying to do anything weird. We're just trying to see
an eighth graders full shirt.
If you want to scroll down a few more
pixels, maybe
we'll get to the juice of the photo.
Or is this all... There it is!
Good God!
Listeners, this is a very
early
90s kind of like purple
pastel pattern
that's extremely busy in very
90s fashion. And the pattern
is primarily made up of
Bugs Bunny. It's like a Wild Berry Pop
Tart of a shirt.
It's such a good... It's like the most
attractive color scheme to me because we're all
growing up... We all grew up the same.
This is it. That was essentially
what was fashionable back in the 90s.
And this was to
me. Like, I saw this
hanging in the, you know,
the gift shops of Six Flags
in the children's area because that's the only
place in Six Flags where the Looney Tunes
exist. And I was like,
oh my God, I'm
going to get married and buried in this shirt.
I was in the eighth grade and I knew
that already. And I actually
brought it with me.
This is it. So this is the
shirt
that predicted my future.
This is the exact
same shirt. And for whatever reason,
this is the funny, disgusting part about it,
there's a giant hole in the back
where my ass might be.
Like I blew out a fart and
ruined the garment.
And if this isn't
going to make the podcast
even weirder, I'm going to try it
on to see if it...
I'm so glad we have the video
component. Before I pass it around so you
can all get a sniff.
Because that's what I was hoping that you would do.
Like how you're holding it now.
It feels like a holy
garment of some kind.
Whoever wears it is bestowed with voice powers.
I commend you for holding
onto it because that would go for hundreds on
Deepop. This is actually the
original plot of Big. But they're
like, it's too weird that he wants to be the voice of
Bugs Bunny when he's older. What if he just wants
to be Big? And
forget about the Looney Tunes element.
This is what I had pitched. New Line Cinema.
What is this?
This is Looney Tunes exclusively
for Six Flags is what the
label says. Can't find that on...
Well, not the internet at the time. You can't find that in
the Warner Bros. Studio store. And it says
Looney Tunes characters, names, and
all related indica.
Indica. Isn't that...
Sounds like a wheat strain.
Indica and Sativa are
trademarks of Warner Bros. 1991.
Uh, yeah,
so... Oh, crazy hearing Bugs
say the strains.
Is he allowed? Is that okay?
I said, you got any foghorn, Kuch?
That's what I want to know, son.
Okay, here.
I'm gonna try the sun.
This is history.
Am I wrong? Does anyone else get nervous
when Bugs starts talking? And like in a way where
one of the most famous people on Earth
is talking to you? Or am I the only one?
Oh, yeah. Oh, a thousand percent.
It's a little strange. No, it's not.
It's great. I'm like, oh my gosh, Bugs
is in the room. Yeah. There's something
otherworldly about it. Right. It takes me to
a different place. And this
is a pretty successful transfer on Eric's
part so far. This looks great.
I built a time machine.
I'm sure one of these buttons
is gonna pop. I'm gonna leave
the gut part of the shirt.
This is future-proofing from clothing
manufacturers in the 90s by making
all things very baggy.
Yeah. Okay, big reveal.
You're gonna want this again in 30 years.
Oh my god. It's...
It's great. It still fits, guys.
If I could recreate the
pose, the pose.
Can we key out the red of the curtain and give you
some lasers? We'll work on the post on this.
Yeah. Wow. So either
I was a really big eighth grader
or I'm a very small man. It's
either which... I'll just stop it
now because all the dates I had lined
up this Friday on Tinder are gone.
Well, I wanted to commend you because
that is something that I
would buy
when I was that young out of Six Flags.
I would not have had the gumption
to wear it both to school and
on picture day. So people thought
and they still say it, like, why
are you wearing a pajama top to picture day?
They're like, what is your... you're an idiot.
And I'm like, you'll
all see. Wait till we all
live this through this thing called COVID-19
and then
and only then after I will be the voice
of Bugs Bunny in the year
2020, I think.
It's a good thing you have that shirt and not like
a tougher-to-get
voice. I don't know who else
in Warner Brothers.
I mean, you were in the Looney Tunes,
but like, you know, unless
if you went to Universal and bought the same
pattern but Frankensteins,
then you're just
dependent on are they doing anything with the
property? Is the dark universe up and running?
Then my dream would be to be the guy
in the Frankenstein outfit.
And again, it would be a very
unimpressive photo of Frankenstein
at 5'5". Even with
those big phone book shoes, no one would
be threatened. The least intimidating
Frankenstein. I want
a picture with Marilyn. Marilyn Monroe.
That's a picture. Is that
the sound of short Frankenstein?
He's like literally
half the
angst of big Frankenstein.
Sounds right to me.
But yeah, going back to
Six Flags,
again, and being a kid
on vacation where your parents
give you, here's like a little bit of vacation.
Here's your budget. Now don't
go crazy. Don't, you know, buy
food. Buy the things you need to survive
while you're away for a couple weeks.
And of course, I was under the care of my aunt and uncle.
But I blew it all on Looney
Tunes stuff. I bought an
all brown Wile E. Coyote
shirt where it was the color
of his fur and only his
muzzle, eyes, and ears.
It was so 90s. Like, it was like
god, they were so good. Actually, you know what I should
have done, and I'm
an idiot, maybe on part two
of this, I bought every
Warner Brothers catalog off
eBay. I don't think you can search
for it because I'm, again,
obsessed. I'm obsessed.
You can't find a
90s Warner Brothers catalog on
eBay right now. It's because they're all at my house.
I bought. Really? Wow. And they
were released by season. So I,
you know, there goes my son's college fund.
At least the first few weeks
of his university career gone
because I just had to have
that Rover Dangerfield cover
of Rodney Dangerfield and his dog
self. Wow. Yeah. I'll
scan that and send it for your
fans. Please send whatever for the socials.
He understands. These are
priceless items. Where did this
catalog, because there was the studio store
which I was really fond of in the malls,
but the catalog was a whole other
So it was like the size
of like, you know, it was
very thin. It was
seasonal. So it was only like, you know, spring,
summer, winter. Of course, they had Christmas
and holiday stuff.
But like it was just for the studio
store. And there are pictures
of like celebrities that were
hot back then. So I
actually have, because it's Warner Brothers
100th this year,
I have been scanning pages of that
in, of the catalog and like erasing
all like the writing.
So I, if you check on my, on my
Instagram, there's a picture of
Mark Lynn Baker,
Bronson Pinchot, and the girl that played
Mary Ann on Perfect Strangers.
And they're all wearing Daffy Duck or
Looney Tunes stuff. And they're all like
like, hey! Like cause they're
popular. They're so, who else?
Gene Shallot was
featured heavily.
Now you've got our attention.
It's like him and Tweedy and Sylvester
eating cake. And like, cause I think
at that point they were celebrating their 50th.
And then there's one of Jonathan,
there's lots of Jonathan Winters.
Like just like in different attire.
Like Warner Brothers ball caps
and stuff. But they would get, and
of course Fris Freeling, Chuck Jones,
these are beloved directors of the
Warner Brothers, you know, history
and legend. They're still alive.
Mel Blanc also was featured in the catalog
like posing with bugs, like a cartoon
drawing of bugs. Oh wow.
There's so much good stuff in there. Oh, there's
an entire catalog just about Gremlins
too. So if you're a huge
fan of that movie, I'm like
truly, and there's stuff in there
that you'll just, you'll never be able to get. And my
goal is to try to recreate
like, cause I work with intellectual
property like the licensing
of Warners. I'm trying to milk
this for as much as possible.
You have a brand also
Yeah, Retro Kid
in Toronto, Ontario,
Canada. And we deal a lot with
Canadian nostalgia like Degrassi.
Stuff that made it here, hoping
you know, some Americans will latch on to it.
But otherwise it's just a collection of
really obscure Canadian children's programming
where you're just like, what the hell
were they doing in Canada? Like
why does this exist? It's so weird.
When I was reading about
your work, I definitely had some long detours
learning about Mr. Dress Up.
Yes. And
also looking at your store's expansive
website. Yeah, thank you.
And oddly enough, like, Mr. Dress Up
was like our Mr. Rogers.
And actually they were friends at one
point in their history.
But he was basically like our
you know, our childhood
for whatever reason, there was
always a guy who lived by himself
that would talk to you and
would have friends who were, who happened to just be
puppets, that also kind of live at
this weird house that is in his house.
It's like a place where they could be creative
and then like leave. Like, Kiwi's Playhouse
was kind of like that. Oh, that's true.
We go visit a place.
We leave our creativity here
at the single man's house. This is where
we go smoke weed is basically
there was another guy in Canada
like another show called Fred
Penner's Place. Oh, we had that.
They put that on Nickelodeon too. Okay, yeah.
So you would follow this guy through a tree trunk
into this secret part of the
forest and he would sing to you
and then he'd be like, oh, we need
to go now.
Like, yeah, it's too bad.
Don't tell your parents. Yeah.
Don't tell them you went in the tree trunk.
Yeah. So much stranger danger
but then also every show was go
visit a, like
this weird guy's house.
Yeah, it was come over, hang out
for 22 minutes, we'll make stuff and
I'll put some clothes on and pretend
to be someone else. Everything's
gonna be fine. Everything's gonna be fine.
Yeah. Yeah, kids, do that on PBS.
Do not do it two blocks away.
Absolutely. Do not
look stranger in the eye. Do not go to Mr.
Smith's. Stay the hell away.
Stay out of Mr. Smith's tree trunk. Maybe
there's a new thing we just created.
It's like a host that
operates inside an abandoned amusement park
and he's like, come ride, come ride
rides with me. Sure. I have the
keys still. Yeah. Hey, climb
the fence. I got a hole
in the fence just for you.
Go flip some switches. Let's see if any of this
electricity turns on. You don't need
seat belts. Put your mouth under this fountain
soda machine.
It never goes bad.
Never. Oh no, a rat flew
out. Oh well.
The puppet friends are like, yeah, raccoons
and rats and
maybe a homeless guy could be
the sidekick. I don't know. This sounds good.
The security guard. The security guard.
He'd be the nemesis of the city.
The security guard who's seen some shit.
He doesn't use that word, but we know he has.
This is good.
We need to like, abandoned amusement parks
have gotten a bad rap from the Scoop Scoop franchise
and it's time to learn they can be
joyous places. Sure, yeah. We can't let
good time, the second act of good time
be our. Oh yeah, right. Yeah, yeah.
You're not necessarily going to get drugged and
left for dead. No. Yeah, yeah.
Things might turn out great. There's no
a lesson doesn't need to be learned every episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just pure fun. You know?
I think
something else to ask you about too, in terms of that
Instagram stuff. I also love seeing you at the
I forgot this place existed. The building's
still there, but this might have been on your like
LA sojourns also
that you were, you took
pictures at what was then the Hanna-Barbera
headquarters,
which is now like, I think people
live there. It's an apartment complex.
Condos and a gym. Wow.
We have the LA fitness there. It's all
like a complex just below the
Universal City Hill. Yeah. And I totally
actually until I saw your Instagram I forgot
that'd be part of the kind of the tour that
my dad would take me on is like, not
just Universal, but they make all the
they make the Flintstones and stuff here too. What
a magical. Did you guys ever get to see that building
while it was still around? Not in its state, no.
I just thought it was an interesting
building architecturally for a long time.
And then a few years ago I saw like
a photo of the guard stand
with like someone in a yogi walk around
costume in it. Yeah.
There are still hints and remnants
of Hanna-Barbera in that complex,
in that area. Like paintings of
like dinosaur footprints on the ground.
I think there might be some murals on the wall that
they are still going to keep up in memory of Hanna-Barbera.
But I remember
being a kid
growing up in Toronto watching
Two Stupid Dogs, Powerpuff Girls,
Dexter's Lab,
Johnny Bravo. At the end of every
episode in those 90s Hanna-Barbera
before they became Cartoon Network
there would be a voice going,
send all your fan mail to
26555 Coinga Boulevard.
And I was like Coinga Boulevard.
That's a weird name.
I remember, I felt so bad
for my uncle who is no longer with us, but
he never had kids and every time
I visited I was always like,
take me here now!
I need to see this place
now! To Coinga!
The most magical place in the city.
You're probably in your mid
40s, almost 50, and this
stupid kid comes from Canada
and he's like demanding you
take me to these places.
And sure enough he did. He was also
the uncle too by the way that would
send me clips and clippings
of LA Times
newspaper, the entertainment section
like Little Mermaid breaks box office
you know, Dolly.
He was the one that encouraged me to be in animation.
So that's what
he gets. He gets a kid that's
obsessed. So he in fact did drive
me to Hanna-Barbera. It was the weekend so it was
closed. I did take pictures
outside of this building
and yeah now it's a gym.
It's kind of sad but
at the same time
I've managed
to
work and make friends with people
that were inside of that building.
People that could tell me
stories about hearing
people like
Mel Blanc or Don
Messick who was the original voice of Scooby.
The walls were paper
thin. Like if someone was getting in trouble you could
hear someone arguing like
four offices away
and just weird stuff.
And you know I'm talking about
Frank Welker who's still a
living legend still with us. He
is literally half of IMDB if you look
him up. He was like all the gremlins
you know.
Megatron. Yeah he's done so many
voices and everything but
now he is Scooby-Doo and
is still Freddie Jones from
that. He still does it.
We got him on Smash.
It was unbelievable. You did?
Yeah yeah. Just through like it didn't even get to see
him. It was like I don't think we even had the zoom
window. It was like a scratchy bad
connection. Which then you're like are
we going to be able to understand this and then that voice
comes booming through like I think
we'll be fine. That's so great. I'm glad
that he was it just makes it that
much more authentic that you got Frank in
there. That was the thought was like
yeah we're doing this full 80s
90s tribute what better way to make it
authentic than getting like you know
like the people from then
like because those vocal qualities you recognize
instantly. But yourself included
because we thought of you right away because you
are the new version of that
you know. Thanks Doc. I bet
you say that to all your guests who voice
bugs bunny.
This is so sad. I'm doing the voice
that I'm wearing this shirt.
No it's not. It's
we're blown away. This is like
I like this will be the nerdiest episode
on our. I want to say like
I want to say thank you bugs so much
for all you've done. Like I think
that's the core of I think all of us. You're
welcome. You're doing just fine.
You got your own show. There's lights
in the stage and a couch.
Thank you bugs. Amazing. That's all
I ever wanted. The most encouraging note
we've got in years.
Can I ask a question. Do you do the Wiley
like intelligent Wiley?
Yes Wiley
coyote. Super genius.
Yeah.
I've only ever done it like maybe
like once or twice.
Maybe for a
like an app video
game on your phone. Oh wow. It was literally
like here's five things that he said.
Just say them.
But yeah Mel Blanks like normal
normal voice print is very
difficult to kind of
get because he had a very
rich you know
smoked at 9 a.m.
butted out at 9 p.m.
probably unfiltered.
We did have to ask you to put out your unfiltered
Chester Fields when we started
recording. When you saw me I was like
sucking on a rain drizzled cigarette
outside. Is it time to go in?
Oh man he's
got to build my voice up.
If I don't smoke these
I just sound like a woman. Yeah I sound
like my mom.
You powered through a couple of packs that we
started. Yeah.
In terms of that Mel Blank stuff
you must just know beyond that
you do so many of his voices
you must just like understand
the general ecosystem
of him
pretty well. That you know his regular
what's closest to his regular voice and what's
furthest. I kind of call it
the house of Mel Blank. And it's
like some characters
live in the attic so if I'm doing
Tweety it's almost
almost the same voice as
Bugs but Bugs is like maybe
like a step down here.
So Tweety I'll do a self
pitch. Like it's up here and you kind
of have to talk like a baby.
So all the L's and W's
and all that stuff. Like you can't say
Granny. He always says
Dwanney. With a D.
Dwanney that putty cat's
trying to chase me. And then they'll
pitch that up. And then
Bugs I kind of ask them
or maybe suggest maybe not
to pitch that up at all.
Because there's again something
so weird almost like Jack Mercer
doing Popeye. Where it's like
you know you who olive oil I bring
you some flowers. And you who olive
oil I bring you some flowers. It's like
it's this high pitch and kind of
low voice mixed together.
And I always think that's kind of like Bugs.
It's almost like this
kind of higher pitched nasally
Brooklyn Bronx accent
thing that he does.
But you can still hear that grit to
his voice. Now Sylvester
and Daffy are the same voice.
By the way I'll never use this mic again.
This is like I'm probably going to have to buy this mic.
So Sylvester's like
here right. He's that big sloppy
cat that's trying to eat that
bird. I'm going to eat that
yellow canary if it's the last
thing I do.
That would have got to me so much more than I thought it would.
I'm excited about all of these but
I didn't think that was going to hit me so hard.
But Sylvester
is the same voice that he did for
Daffy. But they would take this
and speed it up.
They'd pitch it up. And when
I do Daffy I'm doing what we remember.
Daffy is how he sounds.
Which to me is Richard
Dreyfus with a lisp. That's all it is.
Mayor Vaughn
what we're dealing with here is
a perfect eating machine.
All he
wants to do is eat people and
make little baby sharks.
Yeah like that's what I whenever I hear Daffy
I think about like Richard Dreyfus. Geez.
I never would have made that connection. That's insane.
And then Pepe Lepieux
I say he is in the basement for
other reasons as well. He is a
pervert and we keep
him zel. Stays down there chirp. But
he is in the same rate I say
as Vaughn Leghorn. So if you
take that same bassy type
boys and do French
and then do Southern. It's
in the same. Pay attention
Scott. I'm talking here.
Anyways
that's kind of like the
Ferris wheel of
characters I guess. Do you
visualize that too? Are you
sort of like spatially
to go to those places? Yeah.
And also when we record I'm not doing
the back and forth between characters.
I'm kind of like
when we do Bugs Bunny Builders I'll do Tweety
first then I'll do Daffy and then I'll
to separate Tweety from
Bugs I'll do Daffy in the middle.
Oh wow. So I'm like
reading the script like three times
essentially. When you were a kid
were you like doing it analytically or
did you just do it pretty well and then as you got older
you got the extra.
I think it's the same answer for every kid
growing up. It just sounds like a kid doing it
right? It sounds like worried parents
going what's wrong with him?
I think he hit his head sometime during
recess yesterday.
Yeah for me it was Who Framed Roger Rabbit.
That was the movie that I
thought was real. I thought like
oh man if I go to Hollywood Bugs Bunny
will be walking down the street.
On Kohanga he's always there.
He loves it. That's a lot
more charming than like say Mike
and I going like I am scared of the dip.
I can never meet this judge.
That's true. We were worried about the judge.
It was real hard.
Christopher Lloyd was the...I'm still terrified
of Christopher Lloyd because I'm afraid
his eyes will turn into daggers. Cartoon
daggers.
But yeah I mean
I think as a kid you run around the
house thinking you...
I nailed it. I nailed this voice and it just
sounds like a kid doing it. But it wasn't
until high school when they were like
okay we get it.
You can do voices.
Stop.
Please stop.
And then they'd be like well why don't we
let them just get it all out
and do the morning announcements.
They let me go on the PA system.
I could have said anything. I could have done
awful things. But I took
that as a way
of creative outlet and the
teachers were so nice.
Yeah Cardinal
Newman High School is where I went.
It's at this place in Scarborough
where I grew up which is where they filmed
The Love Guru. Mike Meyers
hits The Love Guru.
Very recently talked about on this show.
Really?
Well that
whole scene at the end where they're dancing
they're doing the whole Bollywood number. It was
done in Scarborough.
If you just look up my high school
was right there where they were
dancing. Now I'm really impressed.
Now I'm telling you. I live
like one block over
from Mike Meyers way which is
actually just a... because they named a street
after him. I'm from Scarborough.
Jim Carrey was from Scarborough.
Worked and lived in Scarborough.
John Candy went to high school
at Neil McNeil's. It's like an all boys high school.
Yeah there's
something weird about Scarborough.
People
with the ability to morph into weird
characters I guess.
Is there like a
mundanity to it that
makes a spark of like I
have to go crazy. Probably.
I was going to say
what keeps us humble are those
disgusting winters. I heard
last week in Toronto there was a day
where it was like
they got like 70 degree
weather or whatever and then literally
the following day was just like
four feet of snow.
Not so
fast there guys. You still got a few more
months of this shit. You ever have to fight
back the Canadian in the void? Do you ever
like find some Canadian in
Daffy El Cervester? As soon as I
go back even for five minutes it's like Rick
Moranis and then you come back and you're like oh
hey like it's Louis Tully from
Who Does Your Tax? It's like I'll come
back here and it'll just be
like ugh. It's
embarrassing but it's also like
you know I always say I recharge
my Canadian comedy batteries when
I go back. That's why
you should.
Well so okay.
To dovetail it back into theme park
stuff a little bit. Oh oh here's a thing
before we talk a little bit of Six Flags
because this was a question I had
just when we were DMing.
I wondered
you must have done voices in attractions
somewhere.
I couldn't tell you where but well I found one
but you tell me.
Okay so it is crazy that
now we live in this age
and era of you know
hey celebrities get busy. They
get too busy or
you know they've been known to
ask for lots of money and
as they should they've
created such amazing characters.
Believe it or not
I'm the voice match for Antonio
Banderas for Puss in Boots
for DreamWorks. Oh
wow wow. So all
you have to do is close your eyes
and listen to this voice.
And that is what I do for Puss in Boots.
Yeah it's like I'm able
to do like the sporadic
burst of energy that he has and
then all of that low
stuff. Yeah.
Trust me. Yeah so
they made
a ride, a roller coaster
actually in Universal Studios
Singapore. Oh right.
And surprise
I got us all tickets. We're going
next week. Hey!
No I didn't. Sorry guys I'm a liar.
I'm also aside from
the voice match of Antonio Banderas.
A pathological liar to
people that I just meet.
I have to tell one big lie.
When you came in and you said
I'm not a liar. I just
took that. It turns out that was the first
lie. That was the first lie.
And there's an on air lie which I just did
and then when the credits roll I'll be like
guys I'm also
the president of the United States.
Not true. Not true.
Also a lie. Reel me in again.
But if you are in Singapore
please let me know how that
because there are moments in the ride where it's like
you're waiting and it's me going
the restrooms are over here.
Yeah it's like yeah.
There's arbitrary things they made me say.
But I can't wait
to one day
go to Singapore.
Aside from Singapore I was
in London for a wedding.
To visit for a wedding.
And I was able to see something
that I did that was a walk
through attraction like
by the eye. That giant
Ferris wheel. And that whole area is
basically like Times Square
or like you know Hollywood
Boulevard. It's basically like the attraction
site of London
England. And Dreamworks
has a theater there where you do a
walk through Shrek
thing. And my voice is there
as Puss in Boots. There's a thing
where he's on a screen
and for I don't know how they did this
I'm still like puzzled from
this day. He coughs out a hairball
and the hairball comes out of the screen
and like falls into the crowd
somewhere. Wow. Wow. And I'm like
how did they do that?
I'm like I want to know.
I was like I have a question how the hell did you guys
do that? It's kind of amazing how they did that.
I know how you did half of it
from doing it.
I'm thinking of a voice and doing the coughing.
But I was like how the hell did that come out of the
screen? I want to know.
That's like catching the bouquet
at a wedding or something. You get that hairball.
Antonio Banderas
Flem. Yeah.
The other one I saw was that
you can assert if this
is correct or not but I saw that you
did the voice of Marvin
the Martian. Yes.
Isn't that lovely? I did.
Actually of all the characters
I've done for Looney Tunes the longest
over
12 years I think.
Oh wow. 12 Earth
years creature.
Isn't that lovely?
For which was that another attraction?
I have it that you do that voice
in Warner Brothers Movie World
Dubai. Yes Dubai.
In Dubai. Of all the places.
So in Dubai somewhere in the
middle of Dubai
exists this giant
Vegas like indoor
theme park
that is Warner Brothers
and DC Comics
themed. And it's all fully
licensed and like there's a
Flintstones ride, there's a Looney
Tunes ride. Apparently
a Marvin the Martian
ride. Isn't that lovely?
And stage shows where I've done
like
they did something for Space Jam
and they did like something for the holidays last
year where I will
have to do you know
Christmas? What's that all about?
Woohoo! I'm greedy!
I hope I learn my lesson
in 45 minutes of dancing.
Talking about this with you.
And it's like someone in
like poor soul in this costume like
moving around to my voice.
A ghost who resembles Fogger and Leggmorton
appears to Daffy to teach
him a lesson. Nah say
spirit!
No more spirit! I've seen enough!
I get it!
I'm an asshole!
Sounds like a good show.
It's going to be a good one.
The four of us are going to
do this right after this
and we're on this stage. I can
get us free tickets to it because we've been
got in a PR email saying we
can get free tickets but we have to fly out. Oh my God
are you kidding me? No I'm not. All we have to do is
finance the flight. All we have to do is fly
and put ourselves up and then probably pay for
food but the tickets
are free. And watch out for various like traps
that you might end up in.
Don't worry about that. That's nothing.
That sort of thing doesn't happen at a Marriott Courtyard
Dubai. Three white guys
and one Filipino Canadian. What could go wrong?
That sounds like
what could we get for that?
That sounds like a bunch of bad people scratching
their chin going yeah yeah
millions maybe. Perhaps
trillions. As long as we get
to go on the Flintstones ride. Yeah
yeah. You can hear me going
wow wow wow wow. I do Dino's voice.
You're in that. Yeah I do that.
Wow. Dino. So I heard
and this is true I guess
when I first
booked it I was going wow wow wow wow
I was barking out and
a very famed voice director
Andrea Romano who worked with Mel Blank
while he was still alive. She said are you doing
what Mel did? And I was like what's that?
And she's like he inhaled when he barked.
Like wow wow
to get that like higher pitch.
So there's another
trick. Another trick. That's cool. I spell it
on your podcast. Straight from the source.
You have to inhale for Dino
apparently. Is there a
wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow.
Is there a Mel voice you can't do?
Oh man. Have you gone through his whole IMD
being gone? I'm just going to have to check them all off
the list.
Yeah that's a tough one. I mean
I don't expect you to have actually gone through
but like is there one yet glaring one?
You know I know there's
one. There's got to be one that I can't do.
Seems like you can do all the big ones though.
Yeah the one the important ones
thank god. But I mean again it took
a while. Like even with Bugs
I had auditioned only
twice for Bugs in ten years.
They only ever asked
people to audition for him in
the better part of a decade since I've been working
with Warner Brothers. And that just
goes to show how often they like you know want
to. I call it the shaking of the
ant farm. You know it's like this
crew of people build this thing and then like
another crew comes in and goes shh shh shh
it's all gone. And they're like we're going to do it
our way. But like
in ten years it's only been twice. And
the first time I didn't get it
that's when I got Marvin and then the
second time I was
lucky. So
you did get it. You got the foot in the door
then and now you're oh my god.
It was a little nutty. It was a little nutty.
But yeah.
But even further I also want to talk a little bit
about bringing it back to theme parks.
Growing up in Toronto
we have Canada's wonderland.
Oh I was wondering. I've never
gotten it. I've always been curious. It's insane.
And again I think for
most East Coast and
Midwest parks they
had license to use the Hanna Barbera
characters in the 90s. And I'm
thinking about Kings
something. Was there you guys know?
Well Kings Dominion and Kings Island
both had them. Yes.
We did an episode once. I think like
35 theme parks have had
the Flintstones over the years.
And then weird shady RV
parks in Arizona.
It's just all over the way. Whoever wants it you can
grab the Flintstones. All the meth
you could. The biggest meth capitals.
Yabba Dabba Doo!
All the meth you can Yabba Dabba Doo.
All the meth you can
Yabba Dabba Doo. I'm telling you man.
Hey Fred.
Grinding my teeth too much.
Oh good.
But yeah. You know breathe in when he
nails me.
That was like
the best time of my life growing up as a
kid in Toronto. Going to
what they called their kid section
was Hanna Barbera land.
So you would have
Bedrock mini golf. You would
have like this you know the carousel
that had all the Hanna Barbera characters.
I'm
pretty sure there was like again that
drive in that they had in
Flintstones where you could get like a Bronto Burger.
I think there was a
jet. There was a Scooby Doo's
Goster Coaster which was awesome.
And it was like it felt
like you were in the car. It felt like this ride
was going to fall apart at any minute.
Which is half of the fear of being
on this coaster. Like
we're going to sue Scoob. Like I'm
going to break my neck.
Like whiplash.
Like is my nose bleeding.
I can't feel my legs.
But yeah it was unbelievable
that this place existed. And the one
thing that scared me the most about it was not
the rides or anything about it. There was a
person in a costume
that was Jabberjaw.
The giant shark. As a child
I was terrified of this character.
Something scary about
a giant cartoon shark that sounds like Curly
from the Three Stooges. Like
that I don't know about you but scares
the shit out of me.
You had me a giant. That's plenty from any
other details. Shark that's just
icing on the cake. A cartoon shark.
Maybe because my parents let me watch Jaws
and that's where my love for Richard
Dreyfuss comes from. Oh sure yeah.
I like
general production value at that park.
Are things a little rickety? What is the like
overall? So I mean they've
I've been there recently. Canada's Wonderland
and they're good. They're
they've held up. They still have some of the classic
rides but have gotten rid of a lot.
They had this really great ride
there called The Bat and it was
kind of like it's almost like similar
to The Mummy where you do it one
you do the ride one way and then you do it backwards
and go like the complete opposite
way. But if you were standing
like right in front of it it looks like a bat.
It looks like physically it looked like a bat.
They called it the bat. I remember
Sky Rider was
a stand up roller coaster.
You'd be standing up completely
and it would do like a full loop
which was insane.
I like those. That's Riddler style. I like Riddler's Revenge.
Oh yeah I remember that when that first came
out. I think I was here because that was
when Jim Carrey was the Riddler right? That was
like the big the big thing.
Those were the days.
The Great Canadian Mind Buster
that was like I believe
like a giant wooden roller coaster and I
remember this one. This is a great one. Top Gun
the ride. So the
ride based off of even
before Top Gun Maverick came out this
was like this is the real
sequel to Top Gun if I may say.
You gotta go on the sequel.
Oh yeah. But like it was the
first roller coaster where your legs were like hanging
like this. And I remember people
were freaking out because if you're
a tall gentleman they actually
did a thing a test where
they put like a tall mannequin
on the ride and I think like at
some point in the ride like the leg
had like gone off
and it's like oh my god we have
to make adjustments. Oh god.
We didn't compensate for tall people.
There are no tall
characters in Top Gun.
Well Tom is short.
Is that the secret?
Goose was a little tall but we all know what happened to
him.
Tom doesn't let an actor
be taller than him in the movie.
Not at all.
Kaput.
On the end of like
a questionable
production value of four
attractions. You can imagine that phrase
is taking me to Six Flags. Yes.
Let's dive a little into
Let's go back. The Six Flags
because you mentioned you do
frequent this place with your son
the Bug Bunny World. Yes.
Like the kids area at Magic Mountain.
You're fond of this place. It's as if the place
was not touched from the 90s.
The characters and
everything that is part of
everything. Sun
died, sun damaged. Like
nothing is different
in that place. And if there is it might
just be the entrance signs or the exit
signs. But essentially
everything is untouched.
Pepe Le Pew is still there even though he's somewhat of
a character again that they like to
sweep under the carpet.
You don't sweep anything under the carpet when you don't have
the budget for new signs.
You're like, what do you mean
we've got to take that apart?
That would require a wrench
and a screwdriver. We do not
have that sir. Yeah.
Six Flags Corporation does not. You could
take your politically incorrect characters
and shove them because we're not doing anything.
I'm part of the
local union 905.
Yeah.
To that, this is not
Magic Mountain. But I was looking up other
Looney Tunes rides.
This is Six Flags Great America.
Yes. There's some attraction. I don't know
what type of attraction but it's called Pepe
Le Pew's Peak.
I just don't like
to hear the word peak after. I don't want to think
about any peak that Pepe Le Pew's.
Oh, it's his widow's peak. It's just like he gives
him a haircut. That's the case. Fine.
It's a little barber shop for all the kids who want
to get their hair done like Pepe Le Pew.
That is the style. If you walk into any super cuts
you can ask really
Pepe Le Pew's Peak. Well they try. I mean
look they tried roller coaster cuts and it just
did instead. Oh yeah that's right. Six Flags
did at a briefly in malls
had a
kid's haircut brand where
kids don't like getting their hair cut. You know what we do?
We put footage of roller
coasters in front of them. Oh my god. That'll be fine.
This business
will not fall apart in a matter
of a year and a half. Six Flags
roller coaster cuts.
We did an episode on our Patreon.
That's insane. Yeah, yeah.
Did not work.
Did it not? Did it spawn?
I need a t-shirt of that.
Oh yeah that should be in your client's shirt.
They had kids parties and stuff there too
so I'm sure there were things like that
out there. Yeah, haircut. Kids haircut
party. You know you would have
a party at the haircut. We all did it.
We all had it. Guys, guys.
It was the 90's.
Everyone in the fourth grade attention. I got
a party this Friday. Don't cut your hair.
Just come
to my party. Kids would show up
to school on Monday and not
half the class has their haircut and everyone
else would feel like shit. Yeah, yeah.
You imagine being the only kid with
the hair over the ears going, hey where'd
you guys go that you all got haircuts?
I wasn't invited to this
haircut party.
Or lawnmower accident.
You were all, yeah, all separate lawnmower
accidents. Not talking about this anymore.
Please really fly.
The
thing is, in terms of like
what I did, now, for sure
it is like a has not changed
in forever kind of
land but I do
I haven't taken my son there
but I'm tempted to just because
like for all the stuff that Universal
and Disney have, they don't really have
just the little dopey land with all the kids
rides. With all the kids stuff. Is it nice
from that perspective?
It is because you know like
again, well my son is turning
old. Last night
we were at Super Nintendo
World. We have platinum
passes. We go like anytime
between three and six, if there's nothing
to do with your
super hyper kid, you take him to
Universal, you run around
you grab a Simpsons
donut and you go home.
Oh Homer, those
Simpsons donuts are full of cholesterol.
But Marge, it
has my face on it.
You do though, you've been doing those too.
They've just been listing the old names in the
credits and it's been you for years.
Dan Castellaneta is not a real person.
Oh wow. That's an amalgamation.
That's true, that's not a lie.
He's another Simpsons character. Matt
Greening created those people.
Yeah I have much respect to
again, Krustyland.
That's another subject you could
talk about forever. But
yeah, having a kid, it's limited.
You can't bring your kid onto every ride.
Except for the fact that I
brought him
and it took me three times to measure
that he was tall enough
to ride the mummy.
He's turning seven so he's a six year old
and I brought him on the mummy and I'm like
this could be good or really bad.
He could probably burst out into tears,
throw up all over everyone,
freak out,
die possibly.
But we did it anyway.
I took him once
and he wanted to go on it again.
And I'm like
daddy is cheap, he did not buy
the ultra platinum which allows you to go
over and over again. It's the one and done
and we have to go home now.
And he was so pissed. He was like
fuck you dad, you fucking ass son of a
he didn't say that. But he felt it.
He didn't say it, but I felt it.
But the Harry Potter roller coaster
at Universal, you can take your
six year old on that. And I think
that the Harry Potter ride,
the half motion simulation,
half roller coaster thing,
which is terrifying by the way.
Because it has those
giant ghosts in there
and the big spiders.
They still get to me every time. I know exactly where they are.
It's terrifying.
The giant tree that looks like a
two headed penis.
There is phallic arms for
that tree. Yeah.
I'm like come on guys, I don't need that.
Just being punched by
giant bendy penises.
The weird nightmare you have.
Harry, look out for the
giant penis tree.
Look out. Don't use your magic
indoors.
It's Hans. It's Hans from
Dino.
Now I have a gun.
Ho ho ho.
Just shift the accent
barely and then you got it.
And you got it.
I'm just
trying to think of details or if you've
done some of this stuff
at...oh well that was one question I
had was that I was like
wait a minute, has Eric ever done
a voice in any of these shows?
And then when you said
no I don't think this place has changed in many
decades. I'm like yeah,
you were probably not recording new VO
for any stage
shows at the Carrot Club Theater.
Yeah, at that time
I was just a kid. But even now
they don't really have any of those in
the theme park and it makes me sad
that they don't excuse me.
Or that they don't have any like old
ongoing announcements in the park
where you could hear the character voices.
Yeah, yeah. Absolutely.
There is actually a little area in that
in the Bugs Bunny
world, Bugs Bunny and Friends world or whatever
it is, where it is
like I guess the equivalent
of...it's like the equivalent
of American Gladiators for children
where it's like you have these
air powered like, these like
guns that fire like foam balls
and like a ball pit
and it's like this whole obstacle course.
One of those indoor foam...
Yeah, but again it has slides,
it's like a jungle gym, and it's a lot
of fun for kids. And I always
I'm always like two bottles of Purell
at any given moment. I'm like oh
God, he's gonna get something
and I'm gonna get something.
But there's no voices in it.
There's no characters like
on a cheesy speaker
going, be very, very
careful not to fall over
there. Ha ha ha ha. You know, like
there's none of that. Go to the Johnny
Rockets.
Any character of your choice,
a COVID protocols
being scarily said
by a Looney Tune over the loudspeaker.
It would be porky, right? Because like you could never
get through it and you'd be like what, what, what do we do?
What you have to do
in case
that you
run into... Oh boy, you know that
thing that I said earlier?
It's like just say it!
Just tell us what to do!
Porky, can you just say the word
coronavirus? That's all we need.
Coronavirus.
We can chop the beginning, right?
We'll just use the end.
We got what we need.
Let me... Now where you do see
characters is in
commercials and I just, I wanted
to like play a couple
clips for you guys and get your thoughts on them, Eric.
Jordan, if you can
play the clip,
let's see, I think it's just called Magic Mountain
Bugsworld. You can
sense like an evolution in
these ads because the vibe of
Six Flags changes over
the years and where it started
was like this very heartfelt
they're clearly going for Disney
money, which is not really
the vibe of Six Flags anymore.
Or ever.
Let's look at this, Jordan.
Grab a smile, take a ride
Bugs Bunny World's just inside
It's metal. It is metal?
Yeah. Bugs sounds a little old
in that clip. Take a long
join the show. I say you're old enough
to go. Magic
Mountain was made just for you
Hold my hand, hang on tight
Let yourself run free
Six Flags Magic Mountain
Magic Mountain
It's what the world should be
You know
That really sounded like Bugs's
grandfather in that clip though
That was probably towards the end
of his career in late 80s
end of his life. 89 was when
he passed away. Was his last, am I
wrong about this, was his last role Heathcliff?
Do you know that? Yeah, I think it was
I think it was. He was Heathcliff?
It was like, not Garfield
Right
It was the other orange cat. Garfield but not
Incredibly
heartfelt, right?
And then we start getting into the evolution of it
Jordan, the next clip is called
Great America Bugs
Birthday
If we have this. And I'm curious
This is something I'm curious if you've ever had to do
as any of the characters
which is rap. Can we play this clip?
Oh, yes
Hey, it's my birthday party at Great America
Don't be late
Hey, my name is Bugs and I'm here to say
We're gonna celebrate my birthday
At Great America
We'll have a ball
So many rides, we'll ride them all
Make a splash, take a stand
And that new coast is really grand
Great America
That's the gist of it. That's insane
You can tell it's a Jeff Bergman
So he was the first guy to do
To do voice
To voice Bugs Bunny after Mel Blanc passed away
was Jeff Bergman in his prime
He was probably like
Late 20s, early 30s
And Out the Gate, one of the best
voice matches
I think in history. One of my heroes
And I've gotten to work with him
Even in the capacity where I'm voicing Bugs
And he's voicing Elmer
Just a great guy
A super nice guy, super talented guy
And he actually voiced Bugs in Space Jam
A New Legacy
I had just got cast as Bugs for Looney Tunes
Cartoons, but in Space Jam
A New Legacy, speaking of rap
I was
Daffy
I say Foghorn Leghorn
Elmer Fudd
Marvin the Martian
And Porky
For that I had to do a rap
Which was
When people hear the name Daffy all they're thinking is duck
When they hear Algy
Which is Algy Rhythm
All they're thinking is yuck
I got LeBron and Bugs, so who should I fear
The best tune squad in over 25 years
You wanna be king of the web?
Well that's neat, here you go
You can start by massaging my web feet
Wow
And then Porky had to rap
And it was insane because
They asked me to do it
And it was funny because it was a gag
That they actually
Were trying to throw it out
But the director
Malcolm, he really wanted it in
And they asked me to do this rap
Because it just wasn't working
They had other people performing this rap and it wasn't working
And I ask
There's something wrong with how this is
Being from Toronto, we all think we're Drake over there
So I was like
Hey man, this isn't lining up
Something's off a little
And I'm like is the rap longer
Was it written to be longer
And they were like actually yes it was
And they're like, give me the full rap
And then once you guys have that
You'll be able to
Line it up or edit it down to
However short you want it
But as of now, I can't make this work
If this isn't lining up
I'm sorry, cause you know my rap demands
Are so out of
Reach
They gave me the full rap, we did it
And it got back into the
Film and it was like the whole joke
Was that
Porky was able to rap without
Stuttering, that's the only thing is that he
Oh the only thing he can do
Yeah, was rap without stuttering
That was the whole joke and I'm trying to remember that rap
And it was
Seems like this is part of the job
Ever since the 90s, if you're doing these
Voices, you're rapping, you have to rap
You have to, as soon as they invented that shirt with Taz
And the
I believe like I may have gifted him some modern stuff
But I think he just goes straight for the vintage
Like he loves the vintage stuff
So, if you're looking to get Kyle a holiday present this year
Make sure it is not modern
Make sure it is from
Like it has to say 1994 on it or something
And make sure Eric has not already
Purchased it on eBay
If Eric hasn't demolished the Phoenix
You're in a feeling of war
It's probably a good two
Is one more, in terms of like
Modern influences
Creeping into
The characters
You know, there were a few I was
Thinking about playing, but I think the one I want to see
I'm going to give it away what it is, which is
Hips don't lie
This is, I don't think it's Magic Mountain
I think it's another six, it might be Georgia
Possibly
Can we see Hips Don't Lie
Jordan
The Shakira song
Oh no
Oh yeah
Make a rabbit want to speak Spanish
Shake it Lola
Oh baby when you talk like that
You make a bunny go mad
So be wise
If you want to let people go
Turn your stupid eyes
Anywhere I'm tonight
You know I'm hip don't lie
This rap no feel this rise
All the taxes, attention
When you're eating tough, feel the conga
Let me see you move like you do in the carrot patch
Oh baby
Wait what? Wait
Let me see you move like you do in the carrot patch
Oh my god
Oh okay, cause the rabbits
Let me see if you'd remember if you did that one
Yeah
Let me see the way you move like we do in
I'm trying to fit some lyrics here
Uncomfortably, that don't rhyme
I believe that was Joe Laski
He was a stand up comic as well as a stand up comedian
He was in a
Sitcom called Out of This World
He was the wacky
Next door neighbor that were
That could be me right now
That's your sitcom part
But he was also the voice of Plucky Duck
In Tiny Tunes
Oh yeah, sure, man, did you grow up with that too?
I think we're probably all big
Tiny Tunes
And eventually he voiced Daffy
And Bugs
Talking about
Don't lie
That's the weird thing too
Is that I could do other people's Bugs
Wait, how does this work?
Impressions of other people doing
Right, right
So talking about hip hop, Billy West
The voice of Bugs for Space Jam
With Michael Jordan
On that soundtrack, there is a track on there
Called Buggin
Oh yes, I know Buggin
I do, I swear
And it is written by
Sean Carter
On the album
AKA Jay-Z
He did not want to be credited as Jay-Z
Using his god given name on that one
Yeah
Who does Bugs Bunny Bunny?
I'll give you some time to get more carrots
Every time I rhyme
Can a mouse write this?
I swear to you I know Buggin
We used to listen to Buggin playing N64
Really? Of course
Wow
Blasting Buggin, eating Cheetos for dinner
That was the life
Wow, I haven't thought about Buggin in years
If you call me right now, it's my ringtone
No, it's not
Wait, so what's
Billy West vs
Joe Alaska, or like any of them in terms of
How can you
Spot the differences?
For whatever reason, when Billy did that voice
When he sang on Buggin
It just sounded to me the most like
Anyone has ever gotten close to it
It's just within that song though
For whatever reason
I don't know what they did to it
What they treated his voice
But there was something so good about his performance
In that song
I feel like Bergman was the most accurate
And came close to
All the characters
Across the board
Like his Daffy is insanely good
His Yosemite is like
Amazing
In his prime, out the gate
Right when he started
And then Joe Alaska kind of had his own
Version of these characters
But again, what ties them all together for me
And then there was Greg Burson
Who did Bugs Bunny in the
Super Bowl commercials
Before Space Jam
So there was a 1992
Hey Jordan and hey Jordan
It was the one that was like
It was like a bunch of jocks
Antagonizing Bugs
And then the two years later they did
A super popular, you know they got my money
I bought the shoes and the shirt
They made another Super Bowl commercial
In 1994
Where it was Bugs
And Jordan versus Marvin the Martian
Because Marvin of course
Steals all the
Oh all the Air Jordans on Earth
He steals them all
And then two years after that is when Space Jam came out
Which I think was too late
I feel like it was two years too late
Had it come out like literally
The year after
I don't know, Joe Pitca was the one who
Directed those commercials
And I thought did an
Amazing job
You know, bringing those characters
Into the, you know, it wasn't
Hips don't lie
The way you move at the carat edge
The choreographers of that show
Are the new Joe Pitca
I'm telling you
Unfortunately that will be burned into my memory forever
Thank you for that
Can I ask a quick general voice actor
Question? Cause I know you
Go very hard, we like all these guys
Thorol, Ravenscroft and stuff
Do you have like your, who are your guys?
Yes, yes
Definitely, I was gonna say
Like if it's not Mel Blanc then for me
It's Don Messick again
He was like the voice of Papa Smurf
Scooby Doo
I believe he did Scrappy Doo as well
Puppi Power
Hey Uncle Scoob
Like it was just such a weird
Range of other, like he was always
The kid that if Mel Blanc
Was like, you know, the main character
He was the person that Mel Blanc was talking to
But he had such a nice rich
Voice as well. He also voiced Hampton
In Tiny Toons
Oh gee Plucky
I don't think we could do that
We gotta talk to Buster and Babs first
Yeah, he was Hampton
And I
I actually voiced a character
That he originated
Doctor Quest on Johnny Quest
He was the scientist with
The goatee and the bowl cut
And the, Johnny, Haji
We have to stay close to race
He's there to protect us
He was this guy, yes
A really white scientist
That's all he was
You're so great at those kind of like
Stiff, smarmy
Which seemed like a world of difference
From the Looney Tunes characters
But I guess Marvin kind of gets you
Into that area
Yeah, that weird like ethereal kind of like
Classic sounding character
And again, like bringing it back to Smash
Right, like we did a lot of that
Yes, you did the narration of the
There was this Casino Knights thing
Was one of my favorite things in the show
Casino Knights, but Tigor
Tigor was my favorite
Because it was basically just the send up of Lion-O
Yeah, yeah
That's another booming kind of voice
Where you know those guys were drinking
And doing cocaine
All sorts of things
You shouldn't be doing while on the job
He's like an animal
Adventure kind of character
Okay, how about this
I'm afraid you're going to throw a glass at me
That will have to be the voice
But I'm also addicted to horse tranks
Yes, that's my thing
If you're a half man
You know, half tiger
You're going to be doing some heavy stuff
You would be
If you never
I love the show
You did great, Kyle did great
The last episode of the show has so much great
This Casino Knights thing that you narrated
I love
You do the voice of Tigor
But a live action Tigor
In a scene that's meant to play as dramatic
On the beach
And Kyle's skip is doing the worst acting
The best worst acting you've ever seen
I just don't know how
I wish I were on set for
If there was anything I was ever on set for
I wish if I had seen that with my own eyes
Seeing a guy
In a tiger mascot costume
Acting all
It was like golden hour
Perfectly Dave McCurry
Overlooking the beach
Yeah, yeah
They built this incredible
It was like our turtles dream
Of what they would have done
In live action movies
Immaculate suit
Built essentially only for
Him to say really stilted dialogue
And not do
Even though this suit was capable of it
It's built just to do this
Hokey scene on the beach
It was perfect
And again, it's one of those things
Where you're like, man
If that ever had
Another season or another celebration
Of that show
It would have been like a live theme park
Version of all those
All those characters in the rides
You know we would have gone into some theme park territory
Hips don't lie with those characters
Yes, we could have
It's an alternate universe
An alternate universe Shakira
Alternate body parts that also
Don't lie
A lot of things don't lie
I know you've got to go, Eric
One more clip just as a fun little thing on the way out
And see if you can name
The voices on this one
This is Daffy centric
I think Daffy carries this one pretty well
I just listened to his birthday song
This is from Australia
This is a live show
That they put all of in like a
Souvenir video that you could buy
And I was pretty delighted by this
A souvenir video you could buy
Of Daffy's birthday
Of like everything you could do at the theme park
Which talking about Warner Brothers stuff
This was this crazy
Returns dark ride
Simulator ride that they filmed on
The set, like the sets were still up
And then they ran a camera through it
So it really does feel like
Being in a burden, it's like the closest to a burden ride
Imagine the ride was
You're having a close
Conversation with Danny DeVito as the penguin
And all that purple mouth juice
Is splashing in your face
He's on the verge of an orgasm and he's spewing black blood
That's basically
That's the ride, the Batman returns experience
Like what is it? And you put your face through this hole
And it's Danny DeVito on the other side going
Waaah, waah, waah, waah
I'm getting mad here
I'm gonna fuck the cat
It's Oswald, Oswald Cobblepot
And then I'm doing the same
I'm doing my Sumner Redstone voice
I don't have a lot of vocal range
But I think those are two that are good to pair together
If you have a whole demo reel
Of just Sumner Redstone
I believe you got the parts
I'm the only Sumner Redstone in the biz
I figured out he's from Boston
Actually the real voice, I need to get a little Boston in there
So that's my personal homework
Hold on, it's Hollywood calling
You got the part
By even thinking about it at all
I'm the only Sumner out there
The animated Sumner Redstone show that's coming soon
Little Sumner Adventure
Little Sumner Rising
Sumner Babies
Not all this is a legitimate baby
Hey, it's my birthday party
Confusingly, Jordan, I'm sorry
I have another birthday song that's a rap
Another one?
Do you have another birthday file?
I could not have made this more confusing
It's a birthday song that you might
You might know by a certain popular group
Each character has their own birthday song
Of course
I say it's me, Vogon, and I'm here to say
Wait, still not this one, oh no
It's always a character and they're here to say
That is how
That is how a bunch of lame writers
Thought rap was
My name is Tweety and I'm here to say
For so many years
They were a little out of it
They were up to their eyes in horse tranks
If I didn't send it
Do you also
Here's an alternate one, do you have a clip called
This is where bugs lives
Okay, great, let's do that one
This also charting the Six Flags
Bugs advertising evolution
This you can tell is kind of late 90s
Early 2000s, they gotta get a little hip
They gotta
I don't want to say what it reminds me of
It's an odd song to me
The second house party movie with Kid and Play
Exactly, those are the vibes I was getting
Six Flags is the only one
With his ride on the ride
This is where bugs lives
Let's eat them now
Ride the rides with mom or dad
Be great in time you ever had
This is where bugs lives
Everyone
Me and you
Find so much to ride and do
This is where bugs lives
That's still there, Bugs' house
If you go in there now
It's like the most
It's like being on the set of Seven
It's like
Yeah, this is definitely a crime scene
And it's Bugs' house
And there's like one
Sofa, like one seat
One fridge, and then there's like a hole
Where like actual sunlight comes through
And I feel like you're in like
I'm just waiting for like
I'm waiting for Morgan for you to be like
Don't open the box, whatever you do
Do not open the box
Fill the room with air freshener so they wouldn't be on to the bad smell
Yeah, yeah
Smells like dead rabbit in here
I'll tell you, hips don't lie
Yeah, I'm telling you man
Go there now, go there tomorrow
You'll probably see me there
You'll see, yeah, see Bugs' weird little room
We'll have to do an episode on Just the Room
Why don't we do an episode where we go and film it?
Yeah, yeah
That's the next possible
If there was a sequel to this episode
We might have to do that
I mean of course with our phones and not tell anyone
That we're doing that there, but
I think nobody would
The full camera crew
They're not looking out to have an idea
Like a 50 person shoot, I think
You could get away with
Recording an entire podcast in that
Little Bugs Bunny room
I think so, maybe that's the next
That's the only way we can top this is doing it
In his house, if there's room
For four people in there
That I'm not sure about
If one of the employees kind of tries to figure out what's going on
We just go, hey, get out of here
And they go, alright
Hey, weren't you just vaping in here kid?
Slip them a 50
Or a vape cartridge
And then they'll be on their way
Live from Pepe LePieu's peak
It is the podcast
We can't record there, no
Eric, this has been an absolute blast
I'm thrilled to say
Eric Bazza, you survived Podcast the Ride
I would go again
In the words of my son
Can we do this again?
Oh, that's great
F you dad, I can't believe you're not letting me ride the mummy twice
Sorry, Ultra Platinum Podcast
The Ride, yes only
Sorry, being the voice of a
Woody Woodpecker doesn't matter son
Yeah, the insult to injury
Is that your son had to be mad for the first
15, 20 minute escalator ride back to the upper
It was hell
But guys, thank you so much for having me on
I had a great time reminiscing
And talking about freaking theme parks
And rides
And again, how they predict the future
Sometimes
Like Tom Hanks and Big
This is a magical garment
Thank you for bringing it
I hope some of the magic
I don't know, unfurls on to us somehow
Yeah
Or I lose it in this episode
And tomorrow they tell me I'm fired
Hey, remember that fame and fortune
Contract that you signed the other day
It's gone
It got rained on
Let's exit through the gift shop, is there anything you'd like to plug?
Just my appearance on this show
That's it
Watch this show right now
God damn it
And if you just finished listening, send it to your friends
Oh, wow
That's a really good plug
That's not a plug that we do
That's thoughtful and we should incorporate
He could have plugged Bugs's house
He could have done anything, but this is very nice
That's what Canadians do
That's right
The politeness and the sweetness that I appreciate
The only real way to end it is
That's all folks
I was gonna ask
Oh, jeez
Alright, thanks everybody, bye
Forever
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner
Brett Boehme, Joe Sileo
and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest
ForeverDog news by following us
On Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
And liking our page on Facebook