Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast features versatile metals, a Dutch boy, decorative test tubes,
and plenty of toilet talk.
Plus a look back when Tomorrowland was weird on today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, presented by Raytheon, quality guided missiles and Kent
cigarettes, the cigarettes of the atomic age.
We're the hosts of tomorrow, Scott Gardner, as well as Mike Carlson.
Yes.
Hello, I'm Mike Carlson.
I just want to say that some of the missiles that Raytheon make are friendly missiles.
So I just want to make sure everyone knows that before we begin.
They protect the skies.
That's right.
They're good.
They prevent less trustworthy missiles.
Good, nice missiles.
Jason Sheridan.
National lead paint, national lead paint.
All our friends are here today.
It's a great lineup of shady companies, like really one of the best that we have assembled
because it's what Walt Disney assembled when Tomorrowland was weird.
The perfectly tied into the title.
Yeah.
So we're talking about the early days of Tomorrowland, from 55 to 60 roughly, although it doesn't
all line up like that, but early Tomorrowland bullshit.
Are you guys excited about it?
I am very excited.
This seems like a tailor made for us kind of topic.
I mean, I knew bits and pieces, but looking at it all together and thinking about the
narrative, I guess I never really knew the narrative of like Tomorrowland almost didn't
happen at all for opening.
Yeah.
And that's kind of the, I found this all interesting from the perspective of, we said in the people
mover episode that we'd talk about Tomorrowland a bunch this year, and this is maybe the first
we've returned to it.
And I think it's interesting because Tomorrowland at Disneyland especially is in a rough place.
We've complained about it many a time and we're going to kind of tackle this problem
this year as much as we can.
But I was like, I wonder if like to, could we diagnose the problem a little easier if
we started at the beginning, if we go back to the roots and see are the roots rotting,
what's going on under the surface?
And I think it's not, it doesn't start good with Tomorrowland.
No, it doesn't.
You're treating the underlying.
You don't want to just treat one of the symptoms.
You want to treat the patient.
You want to treat the underlying condition that's there.
So that's what we're talking about here when we just start this massive Tomorrowland redo
that we're going to fix.
We're going to make happen somehow.
Yeah.
Over the course of the year.
Yes.
We will slowly solve the problem.
When you look at it through the lens of like going all the way back to the beginning, it
really does seem like the land is like a prize fighter in a big bout with a one arm tied
behind its back.
It's just like everywhere else, you know, everywhere was struggling.
Opening day was a disaster.
You always hear that.
But I guess I, it never really dawned on me of just how not just weird, but like messed
up Tomorrowland was.
It was an afterthought in a lot of ways.
Seemingly.
Yes.
Yeah.
So it's a scramble building Disneyland, as we know.
The whole thing was done within a year.
Correct?
We've sort of because it was various ways.
It was not a long time building.
Right.
Because it was going to be delayed and then all of a sudden it wasn't.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, I'm at Disneyland in general.
Like the whole.
Oh, yes.
The whole thing takes a year.
And it seems like the initial energy really goes into like the huge carving of the earth.
You know, we got to make these rivers and then the rivers I think drained and was not
a river and they had to figure out how to make the river actually a river.
And then there, you know, the big stuff they're thinking about the Mark Twain, we're going
to build, we're going to take a lot of care to make a perfect old river boat and the jungle
cruise that, you know, that the foliage has to be perfect.
And then it seems like Tomorrowland just got kicked down the curb over and over again and
not dealt with.
Where it was.
It wasn't going to make opening day.
And then Walt hit a point where he couldn't stop thinking about it.
He's like, I've talked about it on the TV show too much.
Yes.
He's been on television standing next to upstanding Nazi scientists.
Yeah.
So this was another refresher of how many damn Nazis were hanging around the Disneyland.
And if he doesn't get this place open, then it's it's not fair to the audience and it's
not fair to the Nazis.
It's not.
You can't make promises right in front of the Nazis that you don't keep.
No.
It's a weird thing.
Like everybody like it's because if you don't know this, that the Disneyland TV show thematically
represented the big lands.
Here's the Adventureland Weeks and specials.
There's Frontierland.
Here's Fantasyland.
And Tomorrowland was all these like man in space.
These forward thinking specials that were legitimately educational and like helped the
drive to, you know, to the space race and educated the public about that.
But for some reason, it's Nazi scientists.
Some reason it's not.
Yeah.
The source.
It was almost I guess the public was just like it was almost like a game of like risk
or some.
Well, we captured this and now they work for us.
And you're like, wait a minute.
Hold on a minute.
Operation Paperclip.
Get them.
Get them out of Europe.
Yeah.
It was almost just like not even thinking of the implications of what had happened versus
just like, well, now now we've captured a playing piece in a way like they flipped good
as soon as we met them.
As soon as we shook their hands, it transformed them into good.
Exactly.
So everything's fine now.
Don't worry.
Put them right on television.
Yeah.
They're TV ready.
So that's well, look at boy.
It's even before the park is that is the Tomorrowland rot.
That's what we're finding.
Tomorrowland has these specials with bad people in them.
That's true.
And then things get cooking.
And as you said, Jason, I didn't realize this, that it's September 54.
Tomorrowland is essentially killed entirely.
Not that we'll never build it.
But this guy, C.V. Wood, this early developer says to Walt, we can't do it.
It's just we don't have the money and we don't have the time.
We're just going to have to call this future expansion.
So this was going to be it's Galaxy's Edge and Rise of the Resistance opening later.
Or Avengers campus with maybe never a ride over there.
Right.
Like it is.
It's funny.
These things that remind you like, oh, it's kind of all the same like the same syndromes
have happened ever since 55 or 54.
Yeah.
Everything everything repeats in different ways and different.
The Haunted Mansion took 10 years or whatever.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
But so yeah, it then months pass.
It drives him crazy.
He's like, we got to do something.
We're going to do something.
And they scramble.
By the way, a lot of this I'm pulling from something called Disney History Institute
dot com, which is a cool website.
Great website.
Yeah.
Read the the actual stuff.
But so they start getting into it.
They start they start dreaming.
But they only got six months or so to go.
And it's tougher to do Tomorrowland in general than it is to everything we always come back
to of like, how do we represent tomorrow?
And is it a future that never was?
Or is it a retro future?
Like they were again, they were having this problem back then because we know how to make
the old west.
We know what that looks like.
And we know who in California can build old west stuff.
Yeah.
But tomorrow and what is it?
What is it going to be?
They have this problem from the very beginning.
Yeah, they're going to build a UFO.
Like what are they going to build?
Like they have to.
It's an imagination.
They have to they have to come up with a concept and build original things that don't exist
in the world.
Was there even that much like sci fi fascination at this point?
Like was UFO big?
I don't know when like I don't know the timeline of like War of the Worlds and such.
But well, there were B movies before this.
So I don't know that it was such a mainstream thing.
I think like your dweebs and geeks of the time certainly liked this type of entertainment.
I don't know that perverts like you had that year like a science fiction comic book is
like you go read that in the darkest room you can find.
Yeah.
Not in public.
Right.
Yeah.
I mean, Walt would rather have Nazis on TV than a dweeb that likes.
We need all those Operation Paperclip guys.
That is the thing that I keep coming across recently where it's like, oh, yeah, the rise
in like canned food really picked up after World War II because there was so much surplus
and there were so many companies who learned how to make preserved goods for the war effort.
And then after World War II, the space race, so many innovations came from, I was trying
not to say in a venture, so many innovations came from like stuff developed for the space
race.
Oh, that's interesting.
The war stuff fed right into the space race.
Plan nine is 1959 plan nine from outer space, which is not, of course, the I don't know
that it like popularized.
No, it didn't.
Yeah, yeah.
But there's like, yeah, there's plenty of like weird serial stuff from the 40s.
Sure, sure.
Oh, yeah.
Forties and Buck Rogers and stuff.
But yeah, it doesn't seem like that was ever in the cards.
That kind of future was not because I think he was I think what was always interested
in the science fact of it all and everything that fed into Epcot eventually like what really
will be the future soon.
So they start digging.
Well, what can we do with the little time we have?
And Walt started dreaming up a big fountain that's made up of molecules.
I sort of in the realm of what that DNA in front of wonders of life.
Right.
And this looked the designs of this look cool and poppy.
And then they're like, no, not going to happen.
Not enough time.
There were even I mean, the grand plans of it were like that there's like, I think maybe
a stationary but still like a representation of a monorail essentially in the hub that
there's like a track and like a mock up of a monorail just to give the idea of like futuristic
vehicles that's out.
There was talk of a restaurant kind of at the at the front of it where you pick your
food on a conveyor belt.
But then the conveyor belt also cooks the food.
Yeah.
And you watch all of that happen until they realized, well, that is literally a future
idea and I don't know if we can do that.
They couldn't even picture the Burger King flame broiled whopper phenomenon yet.
Yeah.
Or the Quiznos.
Oh, yeah.
The little Quiznos belt.
What was that called?
Oh, yeah.
Did they patent that?
That Quiznos little belt?
Is Quiznos still around?
I think there is a lot less, but I think there's still some.
OK.
It does feel like they were on every street corner.
There were Quiznos across the street from each other at one time.
They were on Subway's ass for a while.
And now Subway won, I feel like.
Yeah.
Yeah, they really won.
2008, 2009 doing PA jobs definitely would stop at a Quiznos every now and then.
Is Togo's still around?
There is still Togo's.
A little bit.
OK.
But they never had the market share.
And how did Subway manage to do it despite having the worst possible spokesperson?
Well, Walt did Nazi's on and Subway had Jared and they both did fine.
The brand was...
It really tells you the staying power of Subway, that they were not hurt, I don't think, in
any way.
Not for a second.
The worst spokesperson.
People were probably finding out in line.
They're like, oh, yeah, the spokesman was a pedophile.
Huh?
All right.
Well.
Well, I'm not going to go touch anybody when I leave this with my sandwich.
I'm going to get...
Tuna.
Footlong tuna.
I'm eating it and then I'm going back to work.
Tuna's not really tuna.
Footlong tuna and what?
I don't care about the fact that the tuna's not tuna.
It's delicious.
That's part of the...
I love the tuna.
I'm not going to let one bad apple spoil the bunch of fake tuna that is spoiled and will
make me sick.
Right.
It is.
I mean, looking at long past Disneyland history is really fascinating because I think I've
talked before about excavating recent history.
Finding the tie in DC comics where Superman's shaking Jared Fogel's hand and going, like,
thank you for your help today.
Or just the eBay...
That one happened?
Oh, yeah.
That's real.
Yeah.
Oh, no.
Or just the stuff on eBay where you can find the Lehman Brothers company swag.
Just stuff that has gone under and it's like, oh, they made so much garbage.
The garbage is still out there.
It's still very expensive.
Wow.
I'm glad DC then wasn't like, we need to commemorate...
We got our Six Flags deal.
We should commemorate the Jared moment in the parks in every Six Flags.
Oh, yeah.
Subway, in every Star Wars statue.
The highest quality.
Yeah.
Well, with Six Flags, though, there may still be time.
All right.
We just finished.
It may be in process for the last 15 years and they're just like, you know what?
We made it.
Maybe we just put the statue out.
Can we put a wig on?
He could probably look, you know, Jared looked like anybody.
Yeah, we spent money.
Why would we waste it?
So it's possible.
So plans are out.
What do we do?
Eventually it lands at just build two big buildings.
Just make two big buildings.
Get going on those because we need the time to get those installed.
What will be in the buildings?
I don't know.
Just make the buildings and we will figure it out.
So they call it a mansion.
Oh, yeah, true.
Build the front of it or whatever.
I don't know what it's going to be, but build it.
Yeah.
Exterior is up for a long time before they even know predates what even goes in there.
And the layout of Tomorrowland remains the same, essentially, that you walk into this
thoroughfare and here's the what now on your left is Buzz Lightyear and what now on your
right is Star Tours.
That basic layout is the same.
But then what are we do?
And I don't know who exactly is tasked with this, but here's where we get into.
Let's assemble the squadron of the shadiest companies in America to toss together some
barely entertaining commercials.
Ads for themselves.
Yeah.
That aren't even as like because now we're a little more accustomed to there's fun little
package delivery scenes at the end of Space Mountain sponsored by FedEx.
These are truly just, hey, it's us.
And awkwardly, because none of them really want to say, here's the this of tomorrow.
It's them saying it's this, which will be really good tomorrow, but it's also very good
right now.
Would you like to buy some right now?
Unlike most companies, we did tomorrow today.
That's just that's just our quality standard.
Yeah, head down the street, head down the street to your local establishment.
Get out of this, go to the crane bathroom showroom.
Actually, it's more fun than here.
Disneyland.
It's so funny because Walt, you know, when you read about him, he was such a control
freak and a guy wanted this quality to be so high.
I like the idea that all this stuff existed here, but it sucks.
It's like bad.
It's all bad.
It does.
It's surprising that he allowed this to open all of this stuff, which we'll talk about
today.
It's funny.
It's desperation.
I know you're right.
And like for the level of the quality control he's able to have over the films is then this
new medium just become an entire land is just it's all together.
World's fair, but worse.
It's awful.
Yeah.
It's so funny.
I love it.
But and the rest of the park is, you know, it's not like the one the park today, the
gray, you can see the grass and see deep into the hills or Vanaheim, people get away or
climb a fence.
That's fine.
I understand that that was just sort of like that's a work in progress.
But tomorrow it was awful.
It was bad.
It definitely mirrors Main Street in terms of lots of sponsors and vendors.
But like for them, for the most part, Main Street had like things people could use like
coffee or liverwurst or like whatever nasty undergarments Jason needs.
I was trying to remember the nasty menu.
Yes.
What is now the plaza?
Could you get a tube of liverwurst on Main Street?
You could get a display tube from the pharmacy.
OK.
And then you put it in there.
Capsules before churros.
You just like took a you walked around with a hot tube, one hot tube, please.
This is too futuristic, actually.
Yeah.
You know.
Yeah, you're right.
This is all it's hard to imagine what function this here now.
I don't know if I know the source of this quote, but I liked it.
This might be from a book by Randy Bright, the Disneyland Store.
I'm not sure what it is.
But all right, with time and money running short before the opening of Tomorrowland,
Walt had been forced to accept several corporate county fair type exhibit.
That's even below.
Yeah.
We're calling it World's Fair.
That is more accurate.
Right.
No insult to county fairs, which can be excellent, but are often intended to run for a couple
months.
And these some of these ran for years and years.
Some of these attractions did little more than promote the companies themselves and
even less to promote the future.
That is very true.
Yeah.
Mostly seemingly unentertaining things.
And now the onus is on us to make the discussion of the non entertaining things entertaining.
Well, I think we can do our challenge on the mics.
All right.
I dare you take the challenge.
Take the podcast, the ride challenge.
It's not like the subway challenge.
It's a better.
No, no, no, no.
No blood on the hands of this challenge.
Can I want to talk first before we dive into the companies, let's talk about one of the
biggest things you would see, which is really nothing.
The Court of Honor, the Court of Honor, the listeners know offhand what the Court of Honor
is and do you does that phrase conjure anything to you?
Imagine what that might possibly be.
And now, Jason, what is it?
OK, I saw this somewhere.
I just saw the phrase and I thought I'd have to look this up.
And then I there was a defunct land that that tied a lot of this together for me because
I saw a lot of individual blogs and it it helped fill in a lot of blanks.
The Court of Honor was forty eight state flags on tall poles and then a taller pole with
the American flag.
That's the best.
And that is a super state.
That is that is seemingly the most attempt to like tie this all together.
Bunch of flags.
It was a bunch of flags.
Yeah, flags.
Uh huh.
So they did that.
Walton get his molecules, but he got his bunch of flags and which I think for a while, I
think it moved a couple of times.
But what now is that if you're depressed when you see what used to be the people mover loading
station and and the rocket jets and is now that sculpture that doesn't move right, at
least that all is better than a bunch of flags.
A bunch of.
Yeah.
Is it?
Did anybody check each flag?
Were there any fake flags that he felt would be there tomorrow or like he?
Waltz thought certain countries would invade each other and he invented new flags.
Like did he do any of that or was it just flags from countries in the moment?
So like you're thinking like Pole, Nebraska, when Poland invades Nebraska.
Yes, new pole, Nebraska, when Poland invaded Nebraska, because Walt had like some idea
of like different countries and what would happen.
China, when China takes over Florida.
Yeah, he had all the states.
He also had the Russian flag and the Soviet Union flag because it's like, well, we could
lose this Cold War.
So just be safe.
We want those on hand to roll up really quick.
Walt loves America, but he will easily love Russia if it comes to that.
It was a color change flag.
It was an innovative flag.
It could change color on it with just like, I don't know, a little button or something.
Just push it gently.
Now we're new allegiance.
I was just looking for some future way this ties into progress or the future by having
all the all the flags.
No, and it wasn't like new New York, the floating New York in the full shape of New York.
Right.
But it's up in the clouds.
I know just regular ground New York.
Right.
Boring is what I say to that.
Yeah.
Similarly boring.
What became the big entrance item, which was the clock of the world, big ish clock that
shows you what time it is across the world.
Now, this, I think, is at least novel.
Like this, I kind of get it kind of looks cool.
Like seems interesting.
You know, the clock of the world to me reminds me of a large version of the mind control
device that Edward Nigma does and uses in Batman forever.
It's got a similar.
It's got like a blender.
It looks like a blender.
It's got a thing on it and he puts it on.
It's disguised as like a virtual reality kind of like Elon Musk's implant that just gets
in your brain and delivers content.
But yeah, it looks like this Edward Nigma Elon Musk connection.
People think it's cool, but isn't he just the new Edward Nigma?
Either undertones of that in my Batman forever two script.
You're holding in the.
But here's the twist.
Unlike Edward Nigma, Elon Musk is not funny.
You couldn't tell a riddle to save his life.
That's true.
His riddles are all stolen from people online and he doesn't cite sources.
So consider riddling me this if you want.
Yeah, yeah, no.
In Batman forever two, Edward Nigma will still be able to riddle well.
Great, great.
He will not be riddling like Elon Musk.
Yeah, that would be tortured.
Yeah, Edward Nigma hosts Gotham Night Live.
Now, look, I don't want to take it by take ideas from people, but maybe I have to steal
that particular idea.
This is a creative space.
You know, just give me a special thanks.
OK, I will.
Did would Bruce Wayne have hosted or did he not want the attention?
Does that like if you stare at Bruce Wayne on television, do you start to figure out
maybe he's Batman?
I think there would be like Bruce would not want to do it, but there would be some he
would be dating someone or there would be some sort of Gotham charity thing.
And Alfred and whoever like Vicky Vail, they're encouraging him to do it for a specific reason.
OK, I don't think he would want to do it, but he would reluctantly do it.
And obviously, you know, the Mad Hatter would attack during the live show.
Yeah, he cuts out so good.
Yeah.
So he's coming on stage, putting a suit back on at the very end.
He's kind of the oddball one of the C's like when Steve Forbes.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Is that the richest or no, Elon's the richest host or Bloomberg?
Maybe he hosted, but he was on it.
The coolest host. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And then like maybe one week instead of a musical guest, they just ladies and gentlemen,
the flying Grayson's.
Well, sure.
They're like circus guests.
That's flying great.
They do a lot of artsy stuff on Saturday Night Live now with the musical guests.
So, oh, that's true.
They are always these little arranged tableaus.
Yeah. Jason, is any of Batman's villains good singers?
Mike, I'm drawing a blank here.
Good singers.
I'm sure there's some like Sonic based DC villains.
Someone's yelling at the podcast right now that I'm missing somebody.
Screaming. Oh, screaming.
Mimi's in Marvel. Yeah.
Catwoman would be Eartha Kitt Catwoman.
Sure. If she had the same singing ability.
Yeah. So maybe Catwoman, maybe Catwoman, Selena Kyle musical guest.
Here's here's one thing to bring up.
And when I think about that clock of the world,
I think about the opening day telecast where Walt delivers
a Tomorrowland specific opening in front of it,
where he misses his cue and it's awkward for a good long time.
And then he does the speech and then a bunch of doves all fly out or pigeons.
I don't know. Who knows?
I'm sorry. He didn't know.
We don't know. Yeah.
Yeah. Just a bunch of flapping happens.
But then there's there's this fact about Tomorrowland that is also,
I think, key to the rot in a way, the maybe somewhat
famous fact that it is meant to be to portray the far off future of 1986,
which whoever's narrating says, 1986.
So that's way ahead, he says. Yeah. Sort of.
Well, but there's one year in the same special.
There's narration that says, yes, this is Tomorrowland.
And it's not a stylized dream of the future, but a scientifically planned
projection of future techniques by leading space experts in science.
Techniques.
OK, I guess.
So it feels like a lot of people's loose definitions made it in
early on of what this thing is supposed to be.
I don't think. Yeah.
I don't think everybody maybe got the memo about 1986,
because a lot of it sure looks like a 1950s industrial college.
It looks like it looks like a mid sized like part of a college campus.
Yeah. Where you go to like, you know, where you bring your slide rule.
Right. Protractors.
It's weird. It's weird, too.
And I guess it's not weird because because every other land is meant,
I think, to be a very stylized version of adventure, adventure land.
And it's like you're on some wild expedition and frontier land,
the old west cowboys.
And everything is very much like centered around an exciting narrative
that would have been on a TV show, the version of it that would have been
in a movie or a TV show, Fantasyland Princess, all that stuff.
And for some reason, why Walt wanted this thing to be dry
is confusing to me.
Does that mean he wanted he wanted it to feel like the people who are
working on the early forms of space travel, which we are not that interested
in yet as a country, right?
Neil Armstrong, we don't know about him yet.
There's no space rock stars.
It's just clinical scientists.
Yeah. And the most famous ones right now are Nazis.
Right. Yeah.
What is it? Almost like dealing with this as a land is a is a flawed concept.
Because you would think that if it was future, it would be a stylized future.
It would be like Star Trek or something where there's technology.
You're seeing technology that doesn't exist.
It's just fun imagining what would be in the future, which stuff comes true,
like Star Trek, people, people using iPads on Star Trek, people like
all different things, kind of like, oh, that's kind of somebody
imagined what that would be like in 30 years.
But he's like not interested in that in a weird way.
He loves American commerce.
He loves American companies, likely sees himself as like, well, I'm a head
of industry, I'm on par with the heads of Boeing and Trans Pan Am and
and likely probably felt because science fiction was the era, you know,
that was the realm of pulp, like shitty little pulps.
And that's why radio, yeah, it's frivolous.
So and even though that's eventually what the Imagineers, you know, as
like, because it makes sense.
It makes sense for that to be because everything else is that way.
It's the pulp version of everything else.
Yeah. I mean, it eventually became the
it eventually they would do the future that never was in the same way
they would do the Hollywood that never was and will always be at MGM Studios.
Is it not the case that if you think about it is not like the
the most successful iterations of Tomorrowland and best Tomorrowland
attractions are always, for the most part, sci fi and alien oriented.
When you think about the highlights that, you know, like the alien
encounter was great.
Captain EO is great because it's this like adventure
and there's weird creatures, star tours, obviously. Yeah.
It's almost like that becomes like it that has to be
a important facet of tomorrow.
It's not a science museum.
It's not that's not the vibe. Yeah.
If everything else was the vibe and you were really learning
about American history or learning about animals, that's fine.
But you're on a boat where you see like cartoonish hippos
shooting water and the guy fires a gun like it's not.
That's the vibe of Disneyland.
It's not that like you're going to go and see something.
And it's very, very educational.
But but this is like the Wild West of what a third early version is.
And he does like World's Fairs.
So there's probably a part of him thinking maybe it could be like,
because we're all everybody's finding this together.
Yes. So maybe there could be an educational aspect.
Yeah. And all this stuff is why there stops being that.
World's Fairs had plenty of industry sponsors or new inventions
and new things from other countries and that kind of thing.
And so he thought highly of that clearly as opposed to like traveling carnivals,
which he if it was on fire, he wouldn't piss on it to put it out.
He probably lived a lot on fire on the way to Disneyland.
I guess Kent cigarette.
I'm just I guess maybe when I was looking at all this stuff,
I was just upset that like he didn't have like he didn't invent
like three different alien races that were like floating around
and people in bad costumes and there were like dumb looking spaceships
that the current the imagineers of that time made up.
Like that would have been so cool and dumb.
If there was that, yeah, if there was really silly Walt Future.
But no, it's all it is dry.
It is definitely dry.
But now let's try to get into the dry and have some fun with the.
Yeah, I think we can.
And here's I'm going to go in order of when things opened.
Yeah, because this seems sort of tidy.
And the one I want to dive into is if you have this one isn't even the most dry,
which probably makes it a good place to start.
And that is I'm so excited to say the phrase again,
the Kaiser Hall of Aluminum Fame.
Yeah, this was an opening day attraction.
This was on July 17th, 55.
And I didn't misspeak.
It is the Kaiser Hall of Aluminum Fame.
Yeah, it is not the Aluminum Hall of Fame.
This came up before on a second gate, one of the ones Jason missed due to Covid
where we talked about it because there was a Kaiser spaceman
whose suit was made of aluminum.
And he he walked around to let people know that there was a hall of aluminum fame.
And that episode then becomes about jetpack related kidnapping.
Check it out on the second gate if you haven't heard it.
But so that's why this came up before.
And this odd phrase, why does it bother me so much?
It's just it's just the wrong.
Yeah. And like aluminum Hall of Fame.
Yeah. But what is aluminum fame as a concept in and of itself?
What's aluminum fame?
No, I don't know. I don't.
Yeah, no, it's bad.
And it's I guess I see why maybe it wasn't just a phrase
that was so thrown around like Hall of Fame.
Maybe not. I don't know.
But if you do the same thing with like it's the basketball Hall of Fame,
it's the Hall of Basketball Fame.
It just doesn't it's it's not where an adjective wrong, but it's not it's not.
It's not as upsetting because basketball is more exciting than aluminum.
Well, that's true. Yeah.
So there's no no one is famous because of aluminum.
Well, prove me wrong. Is anyone famous from like
did anybody like cover themselves in aluminum and run out in the street
or something was? Yeah.
Who's the most famous person because of aluminum?
Like aluminum was there as aluminum fame guy Woodstock, like aluminum man
was at Woodstock and we all loved him and he was like kind of a symbol of peace.
Like, I don't know.
There was a weird little pig guy in this, right?
There was a little pig man.
Well, he might have the most aluminum fame, I guess, is that now here
to that point of that, it's this this this is not the driest
that early tomorrow and gets there is a character is new IP.
His name is Cap.
He's capped the Kaiser aluminum pig, the aluminum pig.
This, of course, refers to the fact that aluminum has a pig state
and that refers to I stopped paying attention.
I don't know why it's a pig state, but there is a there is a pig.
You have a photo of the pig is there.
Are you you got something on your phone? I have no I have the hard to find.
Yeah. A lot of this stuff is hard to find.
A lot of it is even not definitely not like fetishized
in the way that a lot of old Disney stuff is.
No, not like like, for example, something we will not be talking about
in this episode is the Monsanto House of the Future, right?
Which people do like because of that kooky design.
Yeah, there is fondness for that.
But that'll be interesting.
Too interesting.
This is the realm of dry today.
Yeah, too wet. Yeah.
This is a little pamphlet I was looking at.
Oh, I saw some of that. Yeah. Yes.
Here. Wait. All right.
Let me if you if you there's anything interesting on there.
There's not, but I will read it says
Kaiser aluminum pig is your host as you visit the panorama of properties
of aluminum, put him through his paces for aluminum fun.
They're doing it again.
Aluminum fame, aluminum fun. Yeah.
There's no such thing as this aluminum fun.
You know, like I know that what's out there.
I found a lot, I think, because they released
audio files in some compilation at some point.
The wish the other character, the wishful knight, the wishful knight.
Is he wishing that his
his armor was made out of aluminum?
Scott, you hit the nail on the head. Yeah.
All right.
It's a night going like, oh, I wish I had aluminum in King Arthur's time. You don't.
Yeah, no. Aluminum sort is going to go right. Yeah.
Well, I guess it depends on thick.
The aluminum aluminum siding now.
I think aluminum a little more flexible, but as as I think in the defunct land,
Kevin talks about like, oh, yeah, they also put aluminum.
They use it in the building, some of the stuff in the park.
And they discovered that it expands and contracts,
depending on whether it's hot or cold.
So that rocket ship deep in tomorrowland would make horrible noises.
This ghoulish groaning would happen.
And like the aluminum is alive.
Neat.
Which means it could also kill you.
And it can kill you and it can feel it certainly feels pain a lot during the day.
They also used aluminum in the bumpers for the original Autopia cars,
because this change was made so late in the game.
They did not have time to test the aluminum bumpers.
So when they get them out on the Autopia track, which already is chaos
because there's no track and kids are ramming into each other.
When they ram into each other, the bumpers are crushed because they are aluminum bumpers.
So mere feet away from this glory of aluminum exhibit is a practical application
of why aluminum sucks.
Ironically, through progress, we would get to a point where modern cars now,
the front of them, if you hit something or something crashes, it is it crumble.
It like crunches up really easily as opposed to back then.
The cars were like very solid.
You know? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that's I don't know what are what are what are cars made of now?
There's a lot of plastic.
Plastic, it's plastic. It's not aluminum.
I'm not I'm not going to say one word.
I will seem like such a well, I'm going to edit this out so I don't look like a fool.
So yeah, this is this pamphlet has got like it's basically was a walkthrough
attraction and it says your trip through the Kaiser Aluminum show
and then all these different I have to go that way.
Well, that's like the Simpsons box factory where you follow a little line
through a bunch of boring stuff.
Yeah, like I'm just there's 14 different stations that it mentions here.
That's well, that's a lot.
There's not 14 scenes and a lot of rides that we like.
Yeah, so maybe the all of aluminum fame is good.
Four was you would run into the huge aluminum time sphere
with ancient night, which is who Jason was just talking about today's firefighter
and spaceman of the future telling of advantages of aluminum.
So there you go.
I hate so it's better to be a hypothetical spaceman than an old knight.
That's what they're saying.
Now, is it possible that a kid in this day and age went through this?
Because there were things aluminum fairly new at the time.
Were there kids who were kind of interested in this?
Or is it as boring to them as it is to us now?
Well, the night segment, the narration at least has the timber,
like the audio, it sounds like a theme park voice, you know?
But would kids go to school the next day?
They're like, oh, my, oh, my goodness, I went to Disneyland.
I got to tell you about the top five things I did.
Did any kids say the Hall of Aluminum fame or whatever?
Like, you know, they talked about seeing a
like eerie cloth dumbo with big holes carved out his face.
I saw I saw a horrific Pinocchio.
And then I got on the little cars and I ran right into an employee
and broke his leg.
I saw Bob Cummings high on monkey balls.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like I just it's so interesting because I yeah, I don't you don't hear about this
ever. And at this point with Disneyland, people have
poured over everything.
Everything is a piece of history.
That's the whole thing with all of these.
I vaguely seen these.
This is us. We know this stuff.
You have to Google search specifically for some of these.
Yeah, it's like you can't even just vaguely search for them.
Yes. Yeah, they've been lost.
And some of them, there's like one photo per right item.
Or if that some things I think are not documented there anyway,
14 different stations in this, they're not all well documented.
Yeah. Which is pretty wild.
There is a I don't know if this counts as one of the stations,
but there was a guest book made of aluminum.
Well, most guests, but not this, not the old
book binders that you're used to tear through every page
with the slightest pressure of a pen.
And then you the pig, by the way,
you could you like put pushed and pulled
buttons that turn cap the Kaiser aluminum pig
flat as a pancake, light as a feather, round as a post, strong as an ox.
What does that mean that you couldn't push a button and make him strong?
That's that there's no way whatever this exhibit was.
This could not have that.
That's like this is like eight things that this aluminum pig can do.
No way. No, there's no way that like he became like thick
and he could withstand like some sort like he couldn't
like take a sword stab all of a sudden when you made him strong.
And then when you made him weaker, yeah, you would puncture the aluminum.
There's just no like a jowse aluminum blood.
You could you could joust with the pig when he was strong
and he would like the joust stick would break.
Yeah. How would they have illustrated that by having like a big brawny
fifties boxer ram him with his head?
Yeah. Right. Johnson guy.
Right. Right. I don't.
Yeah, it seems it seems hard to believe.
And there are there's no video documentation of this.
No, no, we don't know what it was.
Now, some of that is because it was tougher to preserve these things.
But you can still you know, because we don't know what a lot of these rides.
I I couldn't really tell you what those early fantasy land rides looked like.
Oh, that's generally sure. Sure.
But at least as soon as cameras like home movie cameras
into the picture, things are starting to get. Yeah.
I don't think anyone bothered.
Nobody used any rolls of film when film was precious.
True. They're not using it on the aluminum fame. Right.
You know, 35 millimeter people taking still photos.
So we end up with some of these exhibits and buildings.
You end up with very evocative like black and white photos.
You know, oh, they really look like old films. Yes.
Yeah, because it looked like Touch of Evil or something.
Yeah. Yeah. Because old film preserves pretty well.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So if a picture was taken, it's a good picture.
But I think I think every one of these attractions has any two photos.
Any picture you took is one perfect shot.
That's right. One of these old walkthroughs.
I mean, that's the that's the gist of it.
I would say that at the end, you could get a card
and you fill in your name, let's say Jason Sheridan has been illuminated,
spelled with aluminum and yeah,
the illuminated by the brightest star in the world of metals.
There was a bright star. Did we say that? There's a big star.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So you've been illuminated by the brightest star at the Kaiser aluminum
exhibit, not what it's called at Disneyland and and is aware
of all the benefits pertaining thereto.
So this is like you can.
This is you signing a legal document.
This is you signing a contract, but a fun one.
But but still legalese.
I mean, it's we got to be formal about this.
Please sign this document indicating that you had fun.
You were a booster of aluminum from now on.
Yeah, this is was there any other land that just had a walkthrough for them?
An ad is an ad.
It's just a walkthrough.
It's an ad. And that's it.
I don't think they at least they kind of dress up.
Right. Club Cool has the soda stations.
Is it a big? Yeah, that's true.
You're right. But they do something that could be perceived as an attraction.
Yeah, there is.
I guess there are original characters here.
Cap. Well, that's why this is this is one of the best, I will say.
Oh, that's fair.
You're right. I'm sorry to say.
Maybe if there were more photos, we wouldn't be so down on it.
Maybe if there were some photos of the night and the pig,
if it could convince us that Cap was cool or but I don't.
But that doesn't that that's an editorial voice right there
that nobody bothered to film cap.
Right, because Cap could be like, again, there could have been a park
star of cap, no mention of cap.
It could be, oh, we need cap figurines.
We need cap on the merchandise.
So we're we're bringing cap back.
Cap meet and greet. Right.
And I know what you guys are thinking.
Josh tomorrow on stage.
And there's been a lot of rumors floating around and I'm here to illuminate them.
The character you've all been asking for.
For someone who you have a lot of affection for.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
You're in a fun bra.
He's back.
I have repented and I regret my beliefs at the time.
Let's take a selfie.
He's repenting.
Yeah. Well, that's that's that.
From there, I wanted to start with that one because there's a little bit more
energy than the other opening day one, which is the Monsanto Hall of Chemistry.
Yeah. Oh, by the way.
Wait, one thing I missed just to go backwards slightly.
The Hall of Aluminum fame.
Kaiser themselves were so unhappy.
Oh, yeah. With this, they wanted to break the contract three years early.
And Walt still there still was not anything really figured out for this space.
He's like, no, we can't.
One of these things disappears down the road and it's replaced
with just photo standees and the attraction is called Fun Photos with an F.
That is as good as that.
So Walt needed these things or else he's going to have to resort to fun photos.
Right. So he pleaded with Kaiser to stay.
They they did their full term of five years.
This has gone in 1960.
The Hall of Chemistry made it a while along.
This is an 11 year attraction.
There's a way which gets you into if you're at 66 now, the Matterhorn is risen.
Like there's a small world is there like, oh, my God.
Like, like what we know is Disneyland is there.
And then the Hall of Chemistry is still there. Still there.
And that's why when I was there, good.
That's why there's I think a few more photos because it lasted longer.
Yeah, yeah, true. Made it into the color days a little more.
Did anyone find anything that they liked or thought was interesting
about the Hall of Chemistry?
I like the chemitron.
Sure. That seems like something.
But past that, the chemitron was the chemitron was this big like
it was like eight test to eight giant test tubes
on kind of a statue type thing that represented like the eight.
What is it? The eight most often found like chemical properties
in nature or something.
What was the wording of it?
You know, it's like I have a common substances, substances
which can be made and combined into almost 500 different Monsanto
chemicals and plastics.
Here's the things that will kill your world tomorrow.
Yeah. So it looks I don't I guess it looks OK.
I mean, it's a kind of a cool thing. I might have been as a kid.
As a kid, I'll say this. I liked test tubes.
Yeah. You have test tubes because you'd see like Ludwig von Drake
with a test tube or you'd see some cartoon making a potion.
Sure. I did think test tubes were cool.
So as a kid, I could see going in there and big test to take one.
It's like three feet. Let's be clear about that.
This is there. They aren't like 20 feet. Well, sure.
That's a lot of liquid to fill.
That's yeah. You're going to use up a lot of coal, precious coal.
Right. You can't put that much coal in there.
There's a lot of coal talk here.
That's I this I'm stealing this copy from whatever website.
So this might have been yesterland, but I like this dry.
You'll never again think of coal as just a boring sedimentary rock
that's combustible after you see this display.
This will change your view on coal forever.
It was yes. Salt, sulfur, oil, coal, air, phosphate, rock, limestone and water.
OK, water. So rock rock.
Mom, I saw rock in a slightly bigger than usual test tube.
You know, a representation of rock.
Yeah, that's true. I actually know it was.
I think it was actually I saw some like drawings of it.
And it looks like it was just like, oh, this one's like blue.
Like it's water. And it's just like some like abstract kind of idea.
Like what water is like not not aluminum foil, but like plastic wrap.
Yeah, this is all like I've talked about in the show before about
going to the JFK Health World as a kid,
which is a little like science kind of museum near where I grew up.
And that this stuff compared to what that was is like
that was JFK Health World, like Disneyland compared to this.
Sure. In the sense that they really had not figured out
an effective, fun way to try to teach kids something.
I feel like. Yeah.
I wonder when museums started getting more and more
started getting kidified.
It has to have been post the rise of the Disney.
Probably, I would think.
I would think so. Yeah.
I think we went into like we went into there was a play area
at this JFK Health World, and I believe you went into like a giant man's ear,
which I thought was weird, but cool.
That's cool. Well, that's like double.
Yeah. We had the Franklin Institute in Philadelphia, which is still a big
museum, you know, named after Benjamin Franklin.
We also had the Please Touch Museum.
What? It's called the Please Touch Museum.
And it was a kids museum.
You could pretend to drive like half a city bus.
They had like a set the bus, the city.
And kids could pretend you could drive and drive the bus.
And there was a grocery store section.
You pretend to shop at the grocery store.
Oh, so it's like a Sesame Streetified Museum.
It opened in the late 70s. The museum.
So so what was the learning aspect of it?
Was it to pretend you were an adult or?
Yeah, kind of. Did you ever do it?
I remember going to the Please Touch Museum, which as a kid,
I thought was called the Police Touch Museum.
And I was like, I guess police made a museum.
And that was not the case.
But like the Franklin Institute, a little more for little older
kids and families and stuff.
And you walk through a room size version of the heart.
You'd walk through different ventricles and such.
Yeah, there you go.
Famously, a lot of kids left with souvenir T-shirts and said,
please touch really big, which created a lot of disasters out in the world.
Bad. Bad.
So if you wanted to go learn about sulfur,
you could kind of go here and do that. Kind of.
You could sort of get a vague suggestion of what it might be.
This like this one's so boring to me.
It's like I believe something was here for and yet such a hit
that Monsanto ended up with four attractions all told through that.
Not concurrently, because this closes to make room for adventure
through inner space. Right.
Like this is on the Star Tours, the half of it.
But then they got House of the Future and they also got
Monsanto's fashions and fabrics through the ages,
which showed you how chemicals will help us make the clothes of tomorrow.
Even the very historical Disney parks blogs are like,
we're not touching the fashion fabric for the ages.
Yeah, I found a nice website I liked that had some posts about some of this
called Inventing Disneyland, and they point out that, by the way, this was
Monsanto had a better reputation.
This is before Agent Orange, before the genetically modified food,
before incidents that led to the creation of the Environmental Protection Agency.
They caused it, really.
I think they may have caused it.
What was the DDT, though?
This was around the same time.
Well, they must have been developing some of these things, at least.
But maybe we didn't know.
Is that Silent Spring? Is that the book about?
Hold on. There's this. Hold on.
Just because you brought it up, I want to bring up some stuff
that they were working on that never made it to market.
OK. I don't know. Oh, God.
I don't know if you saw this. Hold on. No.
Well, give me one second here.
So, yeah, so there's some there's some really just awful things
that this company ended up doing.
They were absorbed by Bayer a couple of years ago.
Sure. Wait, while you pull that up, here's just here's
I'll juxtapose it with their copy that like, you know,
your food, clothing, health and transportation all depend on chemistry
and the future holds some exciting, wonderful things in store for you,
such as?
Uh, they're there.
Hold on. Here it is.
Uh, the phrase is Terminator seeds.
Hmm.
The seeds of tomorrow.
Genetic use restriction technology, colloquial known as Terminator
technology, produces plants with sterile seeds.
This trait would prevent the spread of those seeds into the wild.
It would also prevent farmers from planting seeds they harvest,
requiring them to purchase seed for every planting,
allowing the company to enforce its licensing terms via technology.
I have heard about that.
Yeah, licensing crops. Did this not happen?
I think it did happen.
Well, this version of their technology did not go to commercial use,
but maybe another company has done this.
There was a thing where, like, they like farmers had to fight back
against having to buy seeds.
Oh, there's a lot of seed stuff lately, and maybe it is similar to this.
You're right.
But this, they said this specific Terminator seeds was never commercialized.
Okay.
But maybe there is a different, somebody else made Terminator seeds,
which could not reproduce.
Isn't that what Jurassic World Dominion is about?
Yeah, but Terminator seeds, killer seeds.
Uh, yeah.
There's a funny article, I found an article in Real Clear Science
that's really snide about Monsanto.
Oh, Monsanto is the devil incarnate, a ruthless corporation
hell-bent upon forcing their unnatural food down our open gullets.
The soy and corn they sow are more likely to transmogrify us
and to imps and sustain us.
And then they were like, oh, yeah, they may have caused 400,000 deaths
in Vietnam from its use of chemical warfare agent,
but they're basically saying like, they're just like the company de jour to say,
like, is bad, like Walmart or McDonald's,
because they've done some good stuff too.
Oh.
I'm like, this is, what is this article I'm reading?
They're all over the map.
Really all over the map.
So they want to be up front with Monsanto,
but they still want to sell some Monsanto ads, you know?
In case they sponsor it.
They are, they are aspirin, you know, they buy, they buy some banner ads, you know?
So yes, this is before some of their awful human rights violations.
This is the stuff we're talking about.
And they didn't finish the Terminator seeds.
And if any other company took that plan and ran with it and that company,
you know, like the Yen Sid Seed Corporation,
some secret firm of Disney that we don't know about.
Yeah.
But before, yes, they were slightly less evil at this time.
So Walt gave them four attractions and they are the most boring things I found out about.
So around this time, I'm getting like, OK, we sit around and do this episode,
but Hall of Chemistry is boring and like I'm feeling boxed in.
And then like I almost missed this one and I'm so glad that I found it.
Did you guys come across the attraction, the Dairy Bar?
Oh, yeah.
Now let's be clear.
The Dairy Bar is not the milk stand.
The milk stand is current Disneyland.
OK.
That's where you buy the Star Wars milk.
The Dairy Bar was different.
OK.
That's not a Dairy Bar.
That's because that milk probably is not dairy.
No, it's all non-dairy, I believe.
OK. Yeah.
Yeah.
So but this, of course, was dairy because it was the American Dairy Association Dairy Bar.
And we think that today's attraction titles are convoluted.
That one does not exactly roll off the tongue.
Yeah.
So this was a late edition.
Now we're into 56.
This is January 56.
It only made it to September 58.
This was one part of it was a big barn.
And it said, today's food builds tomorrow's man.
Hey, that's not incorrect.
That is true.
It's a strange phrase, but it was technically something you could say to your kid you brought with you.
You're tomorrow's man, so eat today's food.
That's what like when, you know, Lindsay was having some morning sickness and when she was pregnant and she had to eat a lot of McDonald's fries, because that's what it would agree with her.
And now I say the baby was built by McDonald's.
Wow.
Well, that website would have some mixed words to say about that.
Right.
But then where I get excited about this milk attraction is that they there's a whole other.
The barn is just, you know, kind of rustic.
And that's where you, you know, it's an opportunity to try tomorrow or today's today's food.
I can try today's food today, milk here and also at probably every other location at early Disneyland.
Thick whole milk.
Me drinking whole milk.
Walt Disney, you've made my dreams come true.
Have both of you had full glasses of milk at Disney ever?
Probably, right?
Maybe as a child.
Because you were milk up until like 20s, right?
Until my now wife, yes.
Right.
Jason, you too, right?
I'm sure. Yeah, when I was younger, I probably opted for chocolate milk.
Did you have a big glass of like two percent?
I bet I did when I was in my like, it feels so like it feels I know that it hasn't happened,
but doesn't it feel like something that would have happened?
And we forgot the story that four and a half years ago, we were there to do something.
We were there to do the canoes or something.
And then we watched Jason have a full glass of whole milk.
And then four hours later, he's saying, oh, my stomach.
And we're like, probably the milk, right?
And he's like, no, no, wasn't the milk.
Does that feel very familiar to you?
I don't know.
I was trying to do oat milk for a while and that was giving me.
I think that's still bad for your stomach.
Yeah, that's still not great.
Yeah.
But I. Any of them.
Soy.
I used to go to the old country buffet and I think I would have a glass of milk with the meal.
My grandparents would take me out.
Just from the name, I don't know what else is going on at the old country.
The old country buffet was like a hometown buffet, but better.
We were not hometown buffet people.
We were old country buffet people.
And we would go every Wednesday because my grandmother got a discount.
Nice for being five to 10 for being old.
Yes.
We go to venture on Wednesdays because she got a discount for being old.
Then she wasn't an employee of no country.
Did not work. No, no.
But I would get I would load up, get a big salad.
Then I would load up my plate with macaroni and whatever the carving station had.
And I think often I would get a big glass of milk.
There would be a milk machine basically, just like there was a soft drink machine.
Oh, so you could kind of you could customize and if I well, I wouldn't.
I would send with whole.
Yeah, I think it was just two percent, but I could be wrong.
Well, like it's like the bib juice, the beverage in a bag.
Yeah, like you know, it's milk in a bag.
Because we would have to like they have them in the dining halls of college.
Milk in a bag.
They had the machines that you would like pull on milk, you know,
fountain milk or whatever you drinking, found milk in college.
Well, for cereal, I'd have to take the cereal bowl over to the milk machine.
OK, but we're having half they had half and half in those machines, too.
If you want to put in your coffee, did you ever drink a big glass of milk in college?
Maybe if I was eating a big plate of cookies, chug, chug, chug, because you're still doing Jason's
Jason's treat based fraternity.
He's got a keg of milk.
All right. You need to chug that old glass and then he'd a hundred chocolate chips.
Doing a keg stand of milk.
Jason upside down with the tube in his mouth or whatever.
However you do that, whatever you people that had fun in college, however that works.
Milk stands.
You're still doing milk and cookies, though.
Usually just the cookies.
Oh, so you've stopped doing the milk and cookies?
Yeah, not so much because usually just I like just half and half in my coffee.
OK, so you're doing coffee cup of cream.
You're not buying enough milk every week to justify getting a jug.
Not a whole glass.
When was the last time you had a big glass of milk with your cookies?
That's a good question.
Less than a year.
Oh, I think less than a year.
Probably when I was home for Christmas.
Probably a glass of eggnog at one point, a glass of milk at another.
OK, Scott, let's have a big glass of milk.
Years.
I'd say probably 15 years.
I bet it's 15 years or more with me.
Unless I did cookies at some point, but I don't think I did.
Interesting.
Listener?
Chug milk at the next live show?
When was the last time you had a big glass of milk?
Are you happier for it?
Are you happier than us?
Sure, Mike and I have our children, but you maybe you've had a big glass of milk.
Yeah, you're really living it up.
That's what makes you warm and say.
We should play milk pong.
Milk pong?
Milk pong.
Milk in little red solo cups set up on the table.
And that way we don't have to get drunk.
We just get to have fun.
That irritating part of beer pong.
You just get potassium.
Yeah, it's fun to lose.
Then you get strong.
You become tomorrow's man faster.
I'd be good.
A flippy cup with milk?
Yes.
I start.
You made it flippy cup.
You additionally made it two different games.
Oh, there's flip cup.
Wait, flippy cup.
What do you call it?
Flippy cup?
Yeah, I've never heard of it.
Is it just flip cup?
I don't believe so.
Are you thinking flappy bird?
I'm always thinking of flappy bird.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm misremembering the name of it, but I played both of those games in college once
in a while.
Hey, dudes, we got to play some flippy cup.
Who's down for some flippy cup?
Flippy cup and flip cup is not so drastically different.
It's not so far.
No, but it's cuter.
It's cuter, so I added an extra fun Y on it, but perhaps I'm remembering it wrong.
You're right, because it's cuter.
Well, I'm not saying I'm right, but I'm better.
I'm not necessarily right, but I am better.
Let's think of it that way.
All right, OK.
We're moving to the milk port.
We're going to the milk port.
And then under that, it says loading dock for tomorrow's milkman.
And this is where we're finally having some fun in kooky old Tomorrowland, because there's
some kids gathering around.
And then I'm looking at it like, what's in there?
Is that little figures?
Is this little maybe animatronics?
I don't know if they were animatronics, but they were at least diorama figures.
And in one case, in one picture, there is a milkman of the future, and he is piloting
a little, presumably milk covered helicopter, a futuristic helicopter, to deliver.
Oh, wait, and I forgot the sign says different LA subsidies.
So like Pasadena, Westminster, Laguna, Compton, he's going everywhere in Los Angeles.
Today's milkman is stuck with wheels and stuck on the road and burning gasoline, but tomorrow's
milkman takes to the skies.
This is the closest thing to what I wanted, what I said at the top.
This is the closest thing that is like, OK, some nonsense future thing that you could
see happening.
Obviously, we wouldn't.
The traditional milkman, much to Jason's chagrin, has gone away.
But through this 50 centric future, we imagine we're like, assuredly, the future still has
milkmen.
We still have milk delivered to our door.
We have sleek, futuristic, sexy milkmen using what we've learned in the war.
Right.
A lot of the Nazis are working on new milk delivery technology.
They're nice now.
Now they're milk deliverers.
Who could have a problem with that?
So we drop, yes, we still look, they're bombs and they're bomb shaped, but we drop them
softer and they just land on your soft grass.
And then a little hatch opens up and that's where your milk is.
Who could hate that?
We have thousands of decommissioned missiles that we need to use for something.
We built them.
They don't cost us anything.
Why not fill them up with milk?
Milk bombs.
Well, this is the American Dairy Association.
I mean, the dairy industry gets insane subsidies still in America.
Well, then it would all make sense.
Tie together.
Can I ask for fan art of Jason in the famous Slim Pickens riding on the bomb picture?
Riding on a milk bottle?
From Dr. Strangelove.
But it's a milk bomb.
And it's spraying milk out all over and people are waiting and catching it with their glasses.
Now let's be specific about the type of milk because this gets a little weird because if
it's soy milk, does that make it a soy bomb?
Does this now tie to Bob Dylan's famous crusher of Bob Dylan's Grammy's performance?
Oh, yeah.
If they want to draw two photos, that's fine.
Two pictures.
Jason as soy bomb.
But that would have to be a separate photo.
Jason interrupting a Bob Dylan performance 25 years ago.
Two equally good concepts, but different concepts.
Jason as soy bomb.
A lot of soy subsidies, I think, in this kind of lot of soy exports.
I think there was something like every now and then they catch a Republican congressperson
who's like, oh, your family, quote unquote, family farm gets like insane subsidies while
you rail against government assistance.
Oh, gotcha.
That's probably what soy bomb was so mad about.
And Bob Dylan stands up here and doesn't even sing about it.
Yeah.
I got to ride around with my shirt off or else no one will know.
He barely reacted to that.
And he's always in his later years always reacting so so wildly.
And yeah, that seems alive.
The gym halberts of time.
The other thing.
And if you think the helicopter, the milk helicopter is fun, then we go to truly the
milkman of the future who is flying around on a jet pack and he is hovering over three
plastic, clear cubicles, each containing a cow.
So he in through some sort of these are not the filthy farm stalls of today.
This is the sleek, clean farm of the future where the milkman has gone like he's got
probably I imagine two sets of like packs on his back, one tube.
He hooks up to the udders, gets milk straight out of them, loads up.
Then he lights the other ones.
You have to make sure to write light the right ones.
Those are rockets.
He flies straight to Compton and gives them their milk.
Wow.
This is such funny nonsense.
I love it.
This is probably the stupidest thing at early Disneyland.
Yeah.
What was stupider than this?
And again, if you put it in the context of Walt May of thought this was actually coming,
it's so much funnier too because he's like looking at this and he goes, yes, this is
how milk will be delivered in the future.
Walt is imagining a future where like what's coming down that he's probably working on
101 Dalmatians and he's like walk with me and he's walking from the animation building
to his office and talking to the director and like, well, I don't know, it's a lot of
spots to draw.
Well, you could use Xerox machines maybe.
Well, Mike, we have to make sure we hit our and then he just puts a cup out where a milkman
of the future flies by on a jet pack, deposits milk straight into his cup.
Walt, like Bob Dylan, doesn't react whatsoever and he just keeps and that's it.
So make sure it's got to be ready for Christmas.
Takes a sip.
Ah, delicious.
Doesn't get in the way of his.
He doesn't have to go to the milk machine like Jason at college.
That's right.
He doesn't have to go to the bag.
Yeah.
So it's a yeah, he thought this was the future.
I do wonder if it comes from like it was a practical concern.
He's like, you know, that milkman's never around when you need him.
We need to figure that out.
We need to figure out what we're going to do to like I'm going to make a futuristic
utopian city that I'll be the king of.
And also we will have flying movement.
We need to, you know, and the like the people mover will go in between the buildings,
but the monorail just goes into the hub.
But the milkman flies through the sky and deposits milk from his jet pack wherever he wants.
I guess he thought this was there's a chance he thought this was like a bit of whimsy here,
but nothing else suggests whimsy other than maybe I hated it.
That's not what tomorrow lands for possibly hated.
Tomorrowland's not for fun.
Well, you could try milk like that's whimsy, right?
You could go to the milk at the exit of the cafe.
I don't know what to call it.
It's dairy.
We still had some dairy bars where I grew up like ice cream place that had been there
forever and called themselves creamery or dairy bar.
You know, I don't think I've ever been to a dairy bar like a branded that.
Oh, OK.
So like we had Oberweiss dairy in the Midwest.
And if you wanted, you could pay money and you would get like a milkman essentially that would come out
and give you like a bottle.
They'd also sell like a fancy glass bottle of milk in the grocery stores around us.
I don't know if it's probably still there.
Yeah, they're still fancy glass milk.
That's like three times as much as the Kroger milk.
Right. Right.
But you're not drinking the plastic, the microplastics that we all grew up drinking.
This isn't you reminded me of something.
This isn't quite about milk, but it's a little related because it's about ice cream and like a local ice cream factory in Houston, Texas.
And I'm going to ask the listeners because I've had a lot of success with throwing out some vague mystery to listeners.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody knows. So if you are from Houston or spent any time in Houston, I want to say that the word blue is in the name of the company.
And it was there was like a tour that you could take, which is always my dream of any of these.
Like, like to have some factory tour and then with some like specific content that's only available to watch here.
And I swear I was in Houston in probably 2000.
And I went on the tour where there was a video where the founder of the Blue Ice Cream Company came back to life or like his ghost appeared so that he could see what his plant has turned into today.
Does does this make any sense to anyone?
I've thought about it the word forever because like who like we know who Walt Disney is or we know who Henry Ford is.
But like the swing to have an actor come play the founder of this Houston ice cream factory, I love.
Oh, God, if anybody knows somehow Houstonites, I give you an assignment.
I might be able to help you out. OK, does the is a bluebell ice cream. Yeah, it's got to be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Does that logo look familiar? I've heard of it. Yeah.
News a few years ago for like, oh, was it a Listeria outbreak or like something like that?
Well, the founder would not like that. Yeah, no. Yeah. Did he come back to life and was he horrified?
What have you done? It happened right around you. What does this ice cream had like a big they had to scrap a ton of yes, because production, they had to close all the ice cream stores.
I remember. And yeah, I feel like Bluebell had a similar incident. Yeah. Oh, God.
But that has nothing to do with the founder coming back. No, I'm saying I think Bluebell might be known for being based.
So Bluebell is almost like a Houston and Listeria.
So it's like the Chipotle of ice cream at this point where it's known more for stomach problems than it is for the taste of their food.
That's enough time has passed. I forgot about the Listeria.
Well, Brenham, Texas, is that ring a bell? That's one of their factories.
You can tour. It's got to be the right pronunciation.
Well, please let me know if you ever took this tour.
Somehow I've access to this video. That's just a little personal wish there.
I'll try to look myself to. So I haven't looked in YouTube era.
But anyway, delightful. Great. Love this.
And I'm going to move to something that it does not seem like this exhibit was very fun.
But I think there's fun things to talk about with it.
And that is March 1956 opens the Dutch Boy Color Gallery.
So what this seems to be is like lights that have colors and you can like make color matches.
I don't know. It sounds so bad.
But what is notable about this is that this is sponsored by Dutch Boy.
This is a brand that is still around today.
But they have shifted their brand for today's purposes because at the time they were primarily known for producing lead paint.
Yeah. Yes. Yes. We now know causes all kinds of environmental damage.
I'm not sure Santa issues ask. So yeah, from 56 to 63 Disneyland had a big ad for lead paint.
Yeah, of course. Of course they did. And all the paint was lead they were using.
Oh, that's probably true. Well, I imagine they used it everywhere in the park.
That was part of that. You got to lose use our aluminum. Yeah.
We use our lead paint. We might still we might all be getting sick from Disneyland lead paint.
Oh, it's got to be baked in there somewhere in this somewhere in Disneyland.
They're still lead paint 100 percent. There is.
I mean, we hear about like little things all the time where it's like, oh, they didn't clean this thing for 40 years.
And now now there's an issue. Oh, yeah. Right. Yeah.
They don't let these stories leak. Some stories. Yeah.
There's stories we hear. But yeah, no.
So there's got to be like one whole building that's full of lead paint.
They forgot to get rid of it. And we've just been going in there and like eating for decades.
Look, hey, mommy, look, I'm going to lick the wall. Yeah, that's well, that's right.
Disneyland's like Willy Wonka's Factory. You can lick every wall.
We've licked all the walls at Disneyland. And that's what the final four is going to be about.
Right. Best tasting wall is it. Look, is there a higher percentage chance you're going to get Legionnaires disease?
Yes. But still, there's got to be lead paint somewhere.
Another fine Philadelphia invention. Legionnaires. Oh, no, that is discovery.
Jason takes pride in Legionnaires disease.
At this point, let me talk for a second about Dutch boy.
I can't tell if I've found my new favorite character or least favorite character.
Dutch boy is still around. But if you haven't seen Dutch boy, Dutch boy is he's got like a big he's got overalls.
He's got a big floppy Fievel kind of hat and he has very severe blonde bangs.
He has his hair. Basically, he's got a Z.
Oh, yeah, he does. Uh huh. And it's so it's very like euro like well, Dutch, I get that's what it is.
And it's like cut right at the cheeks, just the sharpest you would slice your fingers on his hair.
His hair reminds me of and it's not the same color and he's not bald.
But it reminds me of a guy I was recently talking about. Cookie from the Bozo show.
And this is Cookie. Oh, yeah. He has very like straight hair.
He's bald on the top. So he looks kind of like Hulk Hogan. But ends.
The hair does not fade. Yeah. Over. It looks. Yeah, it looks like almost fake.
And yeah, so Dutch boy looks like that.
And he is I know what you're saying. It's like, do I love Dutch boy or am I a little afraid?
Dutch boy often is rendered in this in that kind of like fifties eerie style of painting that's like old Santa Claus ads.
But I'm not scared by those. But yeah, Norman Rockwell is a good one.
Yeah. But I guess I mean, Dutch boy might kind of feed into my discomfort with like Mary Martin and Sandy Duncan.
There's kind of like a frozen chipper smile. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm happy. And it's like, I'm happy. Like, I'm just insisting that I'm happy. Look at the smile I'm making.
Yeah. Yeah. How could this be insincere? Jason, what do you think about Dutch boy?
I mean, yeah, he's he's kind of cute. When when you were growing up and around this time in the 1950s, were you even friends with Dutch boy?
Yeah, I don't. You know, there's a lot of Pennsylvania Dutch, you know, drawings of people or drawings of the Amish, you know.
And I feel like they look like the little Dutch boy. Yeah. I mean, that probably was friends with a Dutch boy.
Yeah. The Dutch boy definitely looks like he's adjacent to Little Rascals or our gang. Yeah. Yeah.
If they had a European friend, right, moved in, joined the RIP Robert Blake, by the way.
All said, the Oscars didn't say it, but they didn't say it. Yeah. But where I'm looking at Dutch boy currently is from, you know, in addition to sponsoring this lead paint exhibit,
they also had a coloring book, the Dutch Boy Disneyland coloring book. So here is Dutch boy painting the castle. Oh, yeah, that's great.
Bright pink. And then there's moments in this. Look, I don't usually enjoy that. OK. The meaning of this word has changed.
And there is a different meaning in the in the past. But when you don't expect to see this page where it says ice cream from a gay pushcart, it's just it jumps out at you.
Sure. It's very strange. And and then you got hold on a second, even if we're using gay as happy. Why is it being a pushcart being described as happy?
Yeah, the cart, maybe the man is. And then also, why is the man covered up by this umbrella in this weird it's like covering half of his head?
It's very poor composition. Well, certainly is a poor composition. Yeah.
They didn't take a lot of care in this coloring book. Yeah. Yeah. It's a strange adjective for a push, much like aluminum fame.
And then you go. So he like kind of looks at a couple of things at Disneyland, but then keeps moving to the real the real Disneyland.
Here is Dutch Boy's special show. And he's at his own color gallery.
And then it illustrates what the kind of thing you can do in the color gallery. Dutch Boy dials his color charts and then he's got like wheel. He's so happy to be turning wheels that say sandalwood and bottle green.
I hate your I hate your color chart, Dutch Boy.
And then I can answer the why the car was a gay ice cream cart. The gay 90s is an American nostalgic term and a periodization of the history of the United States referring to the decade of the 1890s.
And that's Main Street. And that's kind of what they're. So it's an era specific era.
There used to be there's an old there's a bunch of old black and white photos of Burbank and there's a photo and you can see the blue room like a longtime bar in Burbank.
The blue room neon sign is exactly the same. But the bar two doors or three doors down was called the gay 90s.
OK. But that's gone. That bar is long gone. Yeah. The bar's changed names a lot of times.
Well, the adults Dutch Boy would have been drinking there. Yeah. Yeah.
Still today. Grown grizzled Dutch Dutch man Dutch man.
Things were so much happier when I was Dutch grandpa. Things seemed so simple then.
Anyway, this just got me down this rabbit hole. Then I'm doing Google Images Google Images searching of other Dutch boy media.
And that is where I start finding Dutch boy books from the 1920s. Yeah, there's so much Dutch boy content.
If you look, you find some. Yeah, you go for go ahead.
Well, here's the one one that I found is called the Dutch Boys lead party. Yeah.
It is he hears Dutch boy and he's got his open.
Dutch boys like kind of a Johnny Appleseed, you know, but instead of spreading apple seeds, he spreads lead paint everywhere with a huge smile,
severe hair, giant smile and a bucket full of lead paint. And he is facing a battalion of products with with lead in them like a big light bulb and a plate and a shoe.
They're massive. And they're done. This is again. We're now we're in the 20s. So this is that eerie kind of Efteling. Yeah.
Lewis Carroll kind of like it's these are very unsettling creatures in general. And then here's all right.
OK, so he's talking to this light bulb.
And again, this work they use. This is like a motif of of Dutch boy. The first one at the party was gay electric light.
He said, I'm very brilliant. I always shine at night, no little which gives a light much brighter because it's made with lead.
And then so he's meeting all these things, telling him the benefits of lead forming this lead party.
And then, oh, God, a pair of rubbers, it says, which are shoes, a pair of rubber gloves and took the Dutch boys arm.
We're tough and strong and lively because in us there's lead. This sounds this sounds like somebody made a fake one.
Yeah, maybe. Like some. That's what I was going through some of these and I go, are these fake?
Because they mentioned lead so much, it feels like some sort of perverse parody.
Like you could own this could only come from an era where we know that lead paint is bad.
But I guess why else would they say leads like it's not just that we've changed what we make pain out of.
I'm so proud of the lead. Yeah, that's why only wants friends with lead in them.
And if you don't if you don't have lead in you, he's going to put some lead in you. Right.
I was in something different back then. Totally fine at the time and happiness for a young boy to say he wants to put lead in you.
Yeah, that made them making you smile, making smiles come into your body.
That's why I was terrified in elementary school because I knew they taught us that the pencils have graphite in them nowadays.
But like the clicky pick pencils, everyone always called lead pencil.
Yes. And I'm like, oh, I'm going to touch that lead and I'm going to die.
Like I'm sure it wasn't actual like, you know, full strength, full power lead or whatever.
Yeah, I don't know the you were talking to the mechanical pencils. Yeah, mechanical.
That was work. I think it ended up being like graphite or yeah, probably.
Yeah, I don't think it was led. But the short hand, everyone just said, oh, yeah, we said it too.
Yeah. But yeah, once we learned that was bad.
He also he calls this specifically Dutch Boy Pure White Lead. Yeah.
Unsettling phrasology throughout all of this stuff is like on eBay.
You can get these ads and it's yeah, they look fake.
A product like this one is just as at the end is as a product of national lead, national lead.
That was a parent Dutch Boy does it best and the best is less expensive in the long run.
And he's got this like crazy smile on his face.
Oh, I don't like that Dutch Boy. Yeah.
That Dutch Boy slowly getting lead poisoning through the.
Yeah, here are the facts. This is how I looked two years ago.
What do you mean? It's good for my skin.
I get only more pure white by the year.
I drink a big glass of lead each morning.
Stir the lead into my milk. I can paint my house with it and then I can clean up my intestines with it too.
I wait for the lead man to fly by.
Pour some lead on me. Pure white, of course, my favorite kind.
The lead man is having an affair with my mother.
And I welcome it. And I like it. I hate my dad. My dad don't believe in the lead.
My dad doesn't care for lead at all. What a fool.
My dad uses oil paints. He's a coward.
The lead man brings my mother some lead every day.
I wish my dad would drink some of the oil paints and end it all.
He doesn't deserve to live because he don't know about lead.
I'm the Dutch Boy. This is, Mike, because you mentioned microplastics, this is reminding me of a meme I saw recently.
That's the Spider-Men pointing at each other.
And it's three of them and it says, My grandfather, lead. My father, asbestos. Me, microplastics.
And it's just like, oh, every generation has been poisoned with.
That's right. Different things.
All things found in Disneyland.
Oh, yeah.
The other one that I found, I'm sorry, I'm not going to go into all of them, but there's a lot of Dutch Boy books.
Another one is called The Land of Sad Houses.
And it's a bunch of there are a bunch of houses that all have human legs that are clad in slacks, slack legs.
And then, like, you know, loafers and Dutch boys going through the land of sad houses and fixing them by caking them in lead.
And again, every page. Hurrah!
The old house cried, tis new. Dutch Boy White Lead has made me new.
Here he has here there's a set of stairs and the stairs are all set.
These are ghosts. These are ghosts trapped in stairs and the like whatever the staircase knob, whatever you call that.
The banister?
Oh, banister. Thank you.
The whole thing is banister.
Yeah. All like moaning like hellions.
Like they're trapped. Spirits are trapped in these stairs.
Save me in lead, please.
It's the only way to cleanse my spirit. Only lead can get me out of hell.
Hell would be more prep.
Hell would be better than this stair limbo.
Dutch Boy, go find a gun and fire it into each of our stair faces.
Put us out of our misery.
Oh, they say we look so old, we're nearly dead.
I'll make you new, the Dutch Boy said.
And then he paints them and Dutch Boy Lead, they look just right.
And then there's so much scarier when they're smiling. It's worse. He makes everything worse.
Yeah, he's bad.
In the land of sad houses.
I hear you met a bungalow who's crying big thick tears.
I'll make you new with my white lead.
You just need my white lead.
Put me full of your white lead, Dutch Boy.
Oh, man, I guess I don't.
I do like the Dutch Boy, but I don't like him too.
I have one more.
The most maybe the most sadistic thing that I found is that there's one where he goes through like Mother Goose and famous stories.
Oh, yeah, I think I saw that one.
Yeah, yeah.
In this one.
So he like he sees Little Red Riding Hood and she's running.
And what are you running from? Oh, there's a wolf after me.
Oh, I'll spoil his game, says Dutch Boy.
And then he gets his his bucket that is clearly labeled Dutch Boy white lead and he traps the wolf's head in it.
The old wolf growled and growled and pawed and pawed, but couldn't get it off.
So he suffocates a wolf joke on my leg.
Choke on my lead and die.
You want to eat Little Red Riding Hood?
Eat this. The wolf stopped moving his body so there, but he was gone.
Hey, Little Red Riding Hood, want to go kick his corpse?
Let's dump. Let's dump lead on the part that didn't have lead.
We're eating wolf for dinner with my favorite sauce.
Lead. White lead.
A white lead sauce on the side.
There's no better glaze than white lead.
We sauteed a wolf in white lead for eight hours.
It brings out the flavor.
This what now? There's a couple types of food that I would like in the cafeteria.
I like, of course, my favorite chili and I would like wolf sauteed in white lead paint.
Talk to the Dutch Boy people. Get them moving on that.
OK, Denison's Chili Dutch Boy Wolf Lead Paint. Got it.
I'd like to call a second gate shot for Dutch Boy at this point.
I think there's enough momentum to find more Dutch Boy content.
And if you want to hear more Dutch Boy, you're going to have to pay us.
That's what I feel. Seems like he earned it.
I was boy, love Dutch Boy.
Do you do we want to?
Do we do Bathroom of Tomorrow? Yeah.
You mean as opposed to not as opposed to peeling it off for later?
I don't I don't have a ton about it.
Do we think it fits in here?
Bathroom of Tomorrow joins in April 1956.
I throw that, by the way, what a way to introduce it so casually.
What do we think about Bathroom of Tomorrow?
They had something called the Bathroom of Tomorrow, which has been suggested on on Club 3.
So let's let's talk about it here a little bit.
I have never sent an email or a text faster of like that one.
Bathroom, Bathroom of Tomorrow.
We're going to the bathroom. I want it.
Well, not when did not win, but that's OK.
It didn't win. But with that said, what's what are some of your favorite facts about the bathroom?
Well, the opening ceremony. Well, yeah.
Please, let's talk about that. Yeah, I got it right here.
Walt was involved in this opening ceremony himself, along with Crane Company.
Crane Crane and Frank F.
And then the designer, I think, of the exhibit last is last name is Dreyfus,
who was a major designer of the of the 40s and 50s on like revolutionized design
in a lot of ways that weren't ultimately that funny or interesting to talk about.
But a major 20th century design and Walt Disney and Walt Disney did not open every ride.
No, not by a long shot.
But he's there for the Crane Bathroom of Tomorrow for the ceremonial valve turning ceremony.
They didn't cut a ribbon. They turned on a toilet valve, essentially.
They got turned on the water for the toilet and the shower.
Mr. Elliott, Mr. Elliott, turn that valve.
So there's three men all turning not real valves. I don't think.
I believe they're ceremonial valves. They're ceremonial.
They weren't actually like valves that would turn on and off water.
I don't know, because they're in the spot where ultimately there were five valves outside the exhibit,
which I think these did work. I think the children could turn.
This is this is like a water feature. Children turn the valves.
Oh, so that is those are the valves they were turning.
I mean, I'm not sure, but they're in the spot where OK, it could have been ceremony of valves.
But they but ultimately real valves were installed.
This is where we need Jim Hill and Lantesta to step in and figure out did Walt and company turn the real water valves.
Were they actually affecting water pressure?
And that's what you just said is the title of the episode.
Yes, that is right. Yeah. Come on, family.
Toilet. Jim and Lenny talk about we talk about toilets a lot on this show.
And Jim and Lenny talk more about toilets.
That's what we can bring to the table when the collaboration happens.
Or if the collaboration has happened, I don't know.
We'll see. We'll see.
The funny fun post about this on the Walt Disney Family Museum Web site.
A place I've been to, I think, was really neat.
And I think it's surprisingly more frank about Walt and his company and his contributions and stuff.
More more than the Walt Disney Company is.
But they they mentioned that guests could enjoy, quote, a dramatic story of valves.
And a lot of it was like these are actually, you know, we're talking about this guy, big designer, kind of thoughtfully designed like museum placards and panels, a lot of water drops.
Well, when they say dramatic story of valves, what they mean is it's a story that's laid out into big teardrops.
And what's more dramatic than a big teardrop?
No. So this timeline that is labeled the story of flow control.
Yes, that's a great graphic or whatever you call it.
To be clear, the water that is flowing is blue, not yellow.
This is not about a human being's flow control, something that, you know, we'll all have our struggles with as the years go by.
Well, you see hints of it already. You're a man. You're 30. Yeah.
Amen, brother. Not perfect down there anymore. Yeah, we're not. Yeah, I'm doing all right.
I got to say, I'm going to take this opportunity to brag. I'm my flow control.
I think that's great. I think that I'm not having a big problem, but, you know, there's a little thing you go.
It's not airtight anymore. You start reading about cranberry extract capsules.
That is when you guys are because you guys are drinking ice and even pop rocks every day. They're all calcifying at the end.
But the beginning of your flow, you think my flow is being affected by the amount of ice I'm drinking.
Yeah. Hardened ice is all preventing that. It's all flow blockage. My flow is fine.
I'm just saying you go to the doctor and you go as a little, you know, sometimes it's not airtight.
Now, sometimes a little comes out afterward and they go, yeah, that's fine. That's what happens.
You know, my flow is fine and it's not because of the sugar intake.
That's what I'm saying. And I'm mad about it. I'm mad about the inference. If any backseat doctors are listening.
Yeah. No, I don't claim to be a doctor. That was just one guess. All right. Fine. Maybe you're right.
Maybe it'll come out. We didn't know about lead paint. Maybe we don't know about ice and what they're doing to a man's flow.
When you drink ice for decades and your cocktails are essentially ice as well.
I don't drink. I don't drink milk for dinner anymore, but I do drink an icy for each dinner. I have an ice per meal.
Oh, you got one of those machines that I have a machine suggested on the Instagram ads of like, oh, check out that.
You can get a little icy machine. That's right. I bring that Snoopy Snow Cone maker with me everywhere I go in case I need to do something like I don't have access to an icy.
I can bring the whole doghouse. You know, I'm talking about.
You mean you could like if you're going camping or something. Yes. So if you need ice, ice stat on the road.
Yeah, I bring the Snoopy Snow Cone maker, which doesn't work very well, but you know, it works.
Shit. A bear got into the icy machine.
I never should have gone camping with the icy machine. We had that Snoopy Snow Cone maker and I was so excited when we got it.
And then I we made the snow cones and I was like, this does not taste as good as an icy.
You said that Snoopy Snow Cone. You guys don't know what I'm talking about. No, I kind of feel like maybe this is.
Did you get this when you were 10 or when you were like 28 when I was 10? OK, here.
This is it's a pretty look. I thought it was a fairly iconic item, but it's it's it's like Snoopy's.
It's like a doghouse and you would put the ice in it and then it would like you would crush it up.
There's like a little like a thing on Snoopy's head or this is the new. There's actually a newer version of it, too.
And I think it's basically the same as it was when I was little.
So, yeah, you would grind it up manually, essentially, and make like shaved ice and then add coloring to it.
But it sucked, probably. Well, versus an icy, which was much more integrated as far as the flavor and the ice.
Sure. Because the snow cone was fun. It was fun to get it and see it.
It looked cool. But a lot of the flavor that would run down to the bottom of that little like paper sleeve
or whatever you would call it and you wouldn't get you'd almost just be getting mouths full of ice with no flavor.
Not even distribution. Not exactly. I see. So any dream that I see have made possible.
Yes, the technology finally caught up with snow cones and icy people figured it out.
This is the futurism that Walt well. Yeah. Even distribution. We can all dream of a better world.
That's right. And God bless the scientists at Monsanto. God bless the Nazi scientists who created ice.
That's what I have to say. The Snoopy Snow Cone Machine from Nazi scientists.
Yeah, the icy polar bear actually evacuated in Operation Paper.
We captured him. He's on our side note. What else in this thing?
Oh, well, everything was a certain color, which was like a yellow like a beautiful gold, beautiful urine gold.
Gold like it looks in some photos. It does look like Trump's apartment in New York.
Yeah. And some in some ways I are some places I felt like it was described less as gold and more like just like a weird yellow.
Right. Yellow. Right. Yellow. Which a lot not most bathroom. It has not become the standard bathroom.
No, it looks it looks awful. Yeah. And the photos that exist.
But I think the I think Crane's deal was getting a little experimental because I found the end of one of these articles, the discussion of or this.
This is an ad from this era from 1957, I think.
And here's a Crane bathroom ad and the the toilet is bright turquoise.
It is the it's exactly the color of cherry from Playhouse and the same.
It's like cherry, but without cherries, top half cherry got sliced.
Yeah. The bottom of cherry and then but then also next to it, the toilet paper is the same color.
Oh, yeah. Bright turquoise toilet paper.
And then under that very red shag carpeting, the color of turning red. Yeah.
It's an insane bathroom.
Colored toilets go in and out of fashion.
And I think Kohler, I had I had gotten some ads for like the limited run like Hunter Green toilets like it recently.
Oh, so they like throwback designs. All of this comes back around and throwback designs.
Color toilet paper. I do remember like blue or pink toilet paper occasionally growing up.
Really? Just just what was it? I don't know.
I don't know. Just buying not like a grandma's house thing.
Grandma's house sort of thing.
But did you have carpet? Did anybody have carpeting in their bathroom? Yes.
You did all of them. Wow. Oh, really? Yeah. That's interesting.
And then kind of quickly removed when like something would flood or overflow.
And it's like, well, let's get this out of here because this is a pain in the ass.
And it's catching anything that falls. That's yes.
And if you're a man, you're 30s and sometimes stuff flies. You know, it's getting some flow in that shag.
Right. And the full of maybe not a perfect flow and the aim isn't as precise.
Yeah, you're going to get some some pee in that carpeting.
That's it is a crazy thing to do. So glad you don't have you aren't soaking red shag in your your late droplets.
It's not it's not a big problem.
But look, a lot of other men in their 30s don't want to talk about Jason.
I mean, could this be from like food?
Could this be from that bottle of Captain Crunch Blue Mabel's?
Sorry, Jason's thinking now from the Pandora flakes that after finishing polishing off two boxes,
I realized, you know, I think I got a headache every time.
That's what I'm saying.
I don't. It's always right in front of you.
What's causing the extreme health?
Is there a blue dye just destroying Mike and Mike's urethra?
I don't. Scott's perfect urethra is just because he didn't have as much blue dye.
You said it. Not me.
You know, you can't make up your own poll quote for the movie poster, but perfect.
Perfect. A perfect urethra, says Mike Carlson of Podcast The Right.
I'm going to look into your urethral rejuvenation and I'm going to figure out a way to reverse
our urethra aging that has been caused by the different dyes in the foods we normally regularly eat.
After after careful research, you discovered that the most common cause is the sands of time.
No way to remove that. I don't want to hear that.
I'm seeing the phrase reconstruction, but not re not rejuvenation.
That seems to be mainly vaginal vaginal thing.
I was curious if your urethral rejuvenation is a thing.
No one can tighten up my urethra is what you're saying.
So that was not covered in the bathroom of tomorrow.
There was not. No, the dramatic display did not discuss your urethral rejuvenation.
It's a lot about quote, tomorrow's bathroom incorporates the type of heating and cooling,
which will make you forget the weather.
Uh huh.
So I just I just spend the entire summer in my cold bathroom.
Yeah, I don't even know what's going on outside.
That's like, yeah, like a heated bathroom.
They have heated toilet seats at this point.
Like that's something that people still have. Heater in the fan.
You can make the fan blow hot air.
I feel like most bathrooms have some sort of a heater thing still.
Yeah. If you want to turn that on, it's usually like dusty.
If you're in an old house or apartment, you go in there and clean that thing.
But yeah, uh, I've a heated toilet seat.
I don't I don't think that's I don't need that.
What did you not do that in Japan?
Well, I don't know that I realized it was heated.
I know the day situation, of course. Oh, you were into the heated thing.
Yeah. Oh, really? Oh, it feels great.
Yeah, I guess it was a little chilly. I was in I was in Tokyo.
I remember a really solid you sat on a heated toilet seat in Tokyo,
didn't Tokyo, didn't I?
I guess I managed to not talk about that in my trip report.
My God, I feel like a really good one that might have been built into the big volcano.
Really? Mount Prometheus, I believe, has heated toilets.
You attribute because it's about like the ingenuity of H.G. Wells and Jules Verne.
And even they couldn't dream of the comforts of a heated toilet.
I took a shit in Mount Prometheus.
Wow, how did we not talk about this on the episode?
How did we not? Was that not something I wanted to?
Well, I didn't want to, you know, how just in case anyone wasn't comfortable with their urethral.
I'm so tired and punchy right now.
I'm trying to think of where did I shit in Tokyo?
I had to have done it somewhere because we were in the park for we were there for again, three and a half days.
But this I liked this episode until the last until until the last 45 minutes.
I was the first hour I was like, oh, this is one of more like scholarly episodes.
Bathroom of the Future and Dutch Boy really derailed that here.
This is cleaner because it's about laundry.
The exhibit is from the Disney Family Museum site again.
The exhibit was also home to a laundry of the future, which according to Crane,
quote, only hints at possible attractive settings for the home laundry with Crane material.
So your laundry will be much more attractive in the future.
OK, dryers will tear up your clothes, exposing nipples and butts the next time you wear the clothes that scintillating.
There are like Wi-Fi washer and dryer.
Now we're like, you can start the cycle on your phone and it's completely superfluous.
Don't need to do it. Oh, yeah.
Like what would you can't load it with? It's really weird.
Buttons are fine. Yeah.
So there are like weird like future washer and dryers that exist now, but it doesn't make any sense.
It's also where all the Quibi shows ended up. You watch them on certain. Right.
I forget that. I forget the brand. Producers are dryers. Yeah.
So they got a second life. That's what Katzenberg said. You can use them after you can repurpose them.
That's true. Yeah. Just head to your dryer.
Roku, one of the companies affected a lot of Quibi stuff landed on Roku.
That's right. Their payroll affected by the Silicon Valley Bank.
They seem to have lost a lot of money. Yeah.
I know. I think what does this mean for future recovered Quibis?
I think it's been resolved. I think the government has stepped in.
One collapsing company has heard another really collapsed company.
The government should have bailed out Quibi. That's what I think.
Who isn't sure? Wait, that all happened within Trump, right?
Yeah. That's a quibi. Yeah. That's well Katzenberg such a lib, you know, like he was never going to buy.
Biden would have come on. We need our we need our horizontal work.
We got to be able to. It's turnstile. Come on.
But both way. Come on. Judge Judge Teigen. Come on.
She's got a golden arm.
She's got that golden arm. Hard to live.
She's upset about the golden arm. We can't have her losing her job to create jobs.
It's whether you have a golden arm or regular arm. She can't do her stand up gigs.
She can't do her stand up. The clubs are closed.
This is all during the State of the Union.
I'm going to give a golden arm. Everybody in this country.
Boo. Boo.
Marjorie Taylor Green shouted in protest.
I quibi protest of Biden's golden arm program initiative.
Remember, the Supreme Court strikes down golden arm initiative as unconstitutional.
Remember when that was a news story for like weeks that some guy yelled, you lie at Obama.
I just said a scream fest at the state of the union.
Now everyone's screaming the whole time. British Parliament now.
Yeah, it's just my chaos. They get stuff. That's true. They get that was fun to watch in high school.
And they were like, oh, you they would show us, you know, recording like you had to watch a British parliament on C-SPAN.
That's fun. That's real. Yeah, that's good.
So their costumes too much better. Yeah, they should.
But I want I want I would shut up about Marjorie Taylor Green if she would wear like a Dutch boy wig.
Oh, my gosh. Everybody probably will be your hair at some point.
Sure. She has the cap deal with it. I asked for the Dutch boy deal.
So what you could also you could look at a bidet in this exhibit, by the way, a gold bladed bidet.
Yeah. Yeah. So that was go to Disneyland. Look behind a pane of glass there because you couldn't use the bathroom of tomorrow.
Right. Which is a big, big mistake.
Only in Mount Prometheus years later, you use an innovative bathroom.
Well, they say they always nothing gets lost in imagineering. They always go back and use everything eventually.
I think Crane fixture is eventually used in the Disneyland Hotel right across the parking lot.
But is there a bidet on property in American soil at Disney Park?
I don't know. Let's again. Jim and Len.
Can you get a spray of water after you go to the bathroom anywhere in any hotel? Maybe a suite?
Maybe like one of the high end suites or those like the on the water Polynesian rooms or something.
That's your thing. The more. Yeah. Yeah. DVC. DVC gets the days.
Grand Floridian suites. Can you get a little spray?
And you go maybe they that's my question. What's by Golden Oaks?
Is that a Four Seasons? Oh, but that doesn't count.
I feel like I'm looking for Disney Imagineer. OK.
But days or approved at least approved.
Not they created it. Tony, you want to know that Disney's touch was put into this bidet.
Now, if Joe Rody could write 10 paragraphs on the majesty of a bidet, I would like to see that.
But I don't believe there was one in Animal Kingdom.
And I don't think there's maybe there is an animal kingdom lodge.
I'm not sure of the animals all get that was part of the deal with like we're not going to the conditions are going to be great for these animals.
They're going to have plenty of room to roam and they will each have a personalized bidet with their name on it.
And it's not every elephant, every monkey.
It's not just a human spraying a hose at their asshole.
Not that it's actually a sophisticated thing.
The you know, it's funny to imagine coming out of these exhibits and like, OK, kids, we can do a ride.
OK, we do want we can go on one of the boats in the brownest water you've ever seen.
Yeah, I didn't see that one. Yeah, yeah.
Terrible. And then it's surrounded by just brown dirt, too.
Yeah. This is where the lagoon, this where the submarine voyage would go.
And that's Autopia in the background. Yeah.
This is the tomorrow.
There's not a time history about this. That's the Tomorrowland boats.
They were called. Then they malfunctioned.
They were not very workable. And then they took them back, gave them fins, called them the Phantom boats, brought them back out.
They exploded all the time. And then so they it started requiring like a chauffeur.
You had to have a guy, an employee on the boat with you, which did not prevent explosions. It just made it so you could get back easy, not be stranded on the little pile of dirt within the dirty water.
Yeah, I think there might have been some crashing stories as well.
It's like the boathouse where you got to get that guy in the captain's outfit to drive you in Orlando.
Yeah. Well, that's a fancy vehicle, just like that.
And this has the distinction of being the first to Disneyland ride ever closed.
This didn't make it past 56. I don't believe.
So one more blight on Tomorrowland. Yeah.
All of this stuff gone. You know, some some stragglers, some made it to sixty three, sixty six.
The main thing that starts wiping this stuff out and gets us to the Tomorrowland that we know.
Fifty nine is finally the first of the many big.
All right. Here's a bunch of new stuff for Tomorrowland, which was pretty significant because it's monorail, it's submarines and it's Matterhorn, which is sort of sort of shares a border with frontier for a fantasy land.
So 59 kind of wipes out this Tomorrowland. Anything that we miss about it? Is there anything we'd like to come back?
You know, you went to your 80s night and you're totally mini. If they did totally 56.
Well, superbly 56. Would you be happy to see anything from this era?
All the characters, the future dairyman, the aluminum pig, the aluminum night.
Yeah. All that stuff. They could just throw it all in a room for a photo op.
I would be thrilled to see that the big old bidet.
Yeah. After they de-gal this, after they de-gal it of the lead pain and asbestos.
I think statues, I mean, a walk around Dutch boy. Yeah, we could see that. I mean, they didn't have that back in the day, but just as a tribute.
We take a selfie. Yeah, of course.
And I don't know if this is too much to ask. Could you could you fill me with lead to fill me with your white lead?
I can never say that.
All right. Close your eyes.
Here comes my white lead. Jesus Christ. All right. I'm closing it out.
You survived podcast the ride. I would love. I mean, this is the niche-iest of niche, but I'd love to see all my friends from from Tomorrowland 56 when Tomorrowland was weird.
Yeah. Fun to talk about, but it doesn't tell you it was a land that was always playing catch up. Yeah.
That was still it's it's staggered. The other lands had the magic and the tent pole attractions already here.
We didn't have, you know, it's a big, big dirty lake that still we're not happy with.
And that's still what we're eyeing is the expansion zone that might be the key to fixing Tomorrowland. Yeah.
We're going to keep diving in. I'm not sure where to head after this, but a ton of Tomorrowland stuff to talk about.
But I'm glad we went back to the literally dirty beginnings.
Yeah. I mean, the stuff that makes pack mules seem thrilling. Yeah.
Pack mules and stagecoach rides like, yeah, that's this is the most popular thing at the at the movie house on the on the black and white TV.
I forgive the mules for stopping and stranding me and getting me muddy because Disney didn't build them.
They should know God did that. They should have covered. They should have bought a bunch of different mules, covered them in aluminum foil and called them like future mules
and have the same exact ride only with just like big flats like aluminum flats that would like look shiny.
That's great. And then like put some, you know, don't restrict their breathing for doors, your breathing, but maybe put some weird tube on their mouth so that they're like,
he is filtered in like a Darth Vader kind of. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. No, that would have that would have gone a long way to dressing this area up. Yeah.
And in hindsight, if we double the mules would have fixed the whole thing.
If we had a time machine, go back in time, we would not kill Hitler because we wouldn't have gotten these great scientists.
That's right. We need ultimately you need it for this for Disney's scientists.
And then secondly, we would have given Walter a new future mule idea because that's really where it all went wrong is not doing that.
Just go whisper that in his sleep, sneak into his homey hills mansion like Marty and back to the future.
Future mule. Yeah. Dressed like that. Yeah. It's the same year. Yeah, it's perfect.
I am Darth Vader. I have an idea for you to save your land.
News out of Anaheim today. Walt Disney land continues its growing pains as the future mules have all passed after a mere day and a half of operation.
Some sort of strange breathing tube was strapped to their mouth.
Southern California heat wave continues unabated.
Let me speak for everyone in the state when I say we forgive you, Walt, for this horrible tragedy.
Hey, for three bonus episodes, check out I guess the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride. Hey, and with the most obscure tomorrow and think you want more tomorrow and just something we haven't gotten to or you want more Dutch boy.
Let us know. They are. They want more. That's the place for episodes of the future.
We we don't want we want to hear about not the house of the future, not the cool looking one. We want to hear about the one that ran on Microsoft XP from the 2000s from the early 2010s.
Yeah, that's a whole episode. It seems like something we do. Yep.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.