Hey, Scott here.
Michael's here.
Great.
And Jason.
Hey, we are really excited to let you know
that we are doing our first live show in a while
in Los Angeles.
If you're in the Los Angeles area
or want to come to the Los Angeles area
on Saturday, May 6th,
we will be back at Dynasty Typewriter at 730.
And we're very excited.
We got a lot of big stuff planned.
Very big.
Mike, cut the part where we say that
we haven't planned anything yet, but we will.
We have plenty of time to plan something,
but don't use me saying this.
All right, I will cut it out.
Yeah, this is just a reminder for us to talk about
how we have to actually plan it.
Okay, so big stuff planned, huge stuff.
This will be like a circus times the Super Bowl.
Oh my God.
And it's all happening at Dynasty Typewriter.
If you want to be there,
there's tickets available at dynastytypewriter.com.
Excited, guys?
I'm very excited to do it.
And if you are not in Los Angeles,
there are tickets for the live stream at the same link.
We'll post the link in the description of this episode,
both for the in-person audience
and for the live stream at home audience.
That's correct.
Thank you for remembering.
Experience this anywhere,
from the chairs in the theater
to your favorite chair at home.
Any chair you want.
Any chair.
Standing, working out, Peloton.
Real, this is, we're not restrictive like most live shows.
No.
We think outside the box.
You can even lie down on the floor of your garage
and watch it on a phone.
Lie flat on your back on the floor of your garage.
That's right.
Don't look at it or just look at it on mute.
Really, you can customize any options.
Anything you're experiencing this.
Multidas, do something else as you consume it.
Anything you want.
The choice is yours.
Be there.
Forever.
Dog.
Ride vehicles.
The way we get around on our favorite rides.
There are unlimited options when it comes
to these fantastical modes of transit.
But which one is best?
Which vehicle can win a highly competitive
bracketed tournament scenario?
Listen as the track take on the trackless.
Coasters take on kitty cars.
And logs take on dogs.
It's Final Four Five.
Vehicle Vengeance on podcast, The Rides.
Welcome to podcast the ride final four five vehicle vengeance a high octane but even more highly nerdy battle to determine the best vehicle in theme park history here to see through this history is me scott gairdner also mike carlson hi mike carlson here i'm soaked with adrenaline and testosterone i'm just uh it's certainly like with the testosterone is out of your
body and on on your skin now so yes the adrenaline is outside my body uh the reason i say this because i used to work on a clip show called sports crash and whoever was writing clips they would call like a racer like a car racer an adrenaline soaked throttle jockey
so i always think about being soaked in adrenaline from that so i'm stealing it honestly but but it is true i am soaked in it sorry call what type of vehicle like a guy racing a car
person not the vehicle not the vehicle yeah so i was wondering if that the drive was applicable for any of the vehicles we're gonna go through today possible or do they make you feel like an adrenaline soaked throttle jockey throttle jockey
make sure i have that phrase down adrenaline soaked throttle jockey while i introduce adrenaline soaked throttle jockey jason sharridan yeah uh sorry drew barry moore's character and donnie darko's seller door is no longer the most beautiful phrase in the english language it's
adrenaline soaked throttle jockey that was knocked back by that jason took us on a lot of door that's something that's said in that movie i it said i think it's a reference to a writer a poet who claimed that you know it's not an original donnie darko is um
i think it's meant to be it's meant to be a paradox uh like the uh like the zen riddles you know
the zen the zen like uh i'm forgetting the name of them now there's a thing you're meant to meditate on and consider i see this is a piece of pop culture i did not know or have forgotten oh okay so that's the only reason i look dumbfounded i was a real annoying 18 year old
i had all the good posters that's the entire that that describes the audience of donnie darko entirely yeah that's every member of the audience donnie darko fight club pulp fiction all the good college posters but there's so i would argue there's
non-annoying audience members of these other films oh yeah donnie darko entirely annoying i i mean partially uh i think uh replicated and and bought as much as it did because donnie darko usually cost uh nine or ten dollars and was available at every best buy
so you'd like to because it was a budget film yeah i loved budget dvds it's artsy and cheap so like la confidential was always 15
donnie darko you remember the specific this is fascinating this is a fascinating discussion but we really have so much to get there's a
keep digging into like your memories of how much dvds cost we should just try to like if you can remember a price as like kind of a chaser after every round if you can remember that's good yeah
of a dvd that you just try to throw it in there i love it if they're if they're not in your head whatever but um okay so uh it's it's the fifth final four if you can believe it uh the final fours which is are of course where we take 16 topics
and find and there is a final four in there somewhere eventually so the title is accurate right got it uh well i think we will see no comments this year saying the boys don't even understand that how the brackets work yeah it's so cute hearing how the boys don't even know actually how brackets work
guess what everyone we've heard your thoughts and comments and we've made it even stupider
uh yeah that's true we are look we're changing it up this year because i think the first four final fours were kind of of a piece and part of that piece is that the word fake was in the title that was always part of it stemming from fake rocks and the things kept being fake but today the word fake is out this is all too real this is a very serious topic we're determining an actual thing um a thing that needed to be determined i think we're going to be able to do that
i don't know i i'm not sure i think it'll be interesting no no still not and it's still an arbitrary split up of elements yeah of rides but that's one thing i think to make clear about this that we are we are talking ride vehicles specifically not rides right so as you know classics are thrown out and and butt heads we have to remember we're not
we're not talking about the quality of the ride we will we will be very cruel to rides that are very excellent but that's not we're talking about just what you're sitting in yes so so when we're talking about what we're sitting in let me ask you this do you do you consider how the vehicle moves on the track is the sensation is that part of our process today novelty you're saying no i'm saying more of like is the ride smooth or are we just judging sitting in and the aesthetics
of the vehicle this is tough we haven't talked about this that's what i think something you got to be careful of is are we describing the track right are we talking because this isn't a competition of tracks i agree the vehicle does on the track so i think we need to restrict to just if we had the ride vehicle in this garage and we were sitting in it and looking at it yeah so you're are you saying this is tough are you saying that what it does movement wise
irrelevant but but are there not vehicles that where it what it does is inside the the vehicle yeah it's kind of a piece i think i think these could be considered intangibles like oh i can't quite describe it but it well we better figure out how to say the right answer
podcast we're gonna have to think of some words it sounds like i've been outvoted as far as my feelings well i don't i don't think so i think you've just maybe not made that a criteria for jason and i i think you're allowed to make any if you want to not involve movement in any of your choices i'm gonna try to not involve movement that's great okay that's good well look and i don't you know and we'll we'll dig in we don't have to talk about criteria forever but a movement it certainly isn't like it's not number one
on my list i feel like a phrase iconic is is in my head the word right phrase you might say iconic is in my head which and part of that being would i want a toy of this sure is there a toy of the vehicle should there be a toy of the vehicle not crucial but it's it's it's gonna help at least my votes yeah the phrase is toy attic is the ride vehicle toy attic and you're which you're harkening to jill schumacher in his discussion of batman forever i harkening
most are batman and robin which had to be extremely toy i most things i try to tie back to jill schumacher and batman forever or batman and robin uh so yes yes now okay maybe i'll think about the movement in this way if the movement was just if if the ride was just in a parking lot and there was nothing around it there was no pre-show there was no yeah lights there was no arrow smith what would be what would be the experience i feel like that's going to be impossible for you to to remove the arrow smith
fully from because again we want to talk so that's an arrow smith soaked throttle machine yes the stretch limo not to give away too many of the things we're talking about what people don't know about the rock and roller coaster in orlando is that they uh you know like popcorn smell they pipe in they actually pipe in steven tyler's adrenaline into the room at the pre-show to get you revved up because he has very specific adrenaline that's great that's something you want piped in yeah you could mist a mist of
steven tyler's adrenaline this is not the first time you've discussed his bodily fluids being on you yeah there was one where you said you said that you wanted to go to the deuces wild show oh yeah and for him to like breathe it on you or spit on you or sneeze on you or that you would get covid i wanted to get covid from steven tyler in the in the general admission pit of arrow smith's deuces are wild los vegas residency this is again you know to to like imagine two
vehicles uh racing next to each other and i feel like we started at the same starting line with arrow smith and started moving at the same pace and the first thing we talked about it which was like oh i like the song jaded you like the song jaded oh do you also want to get his spittle all over you you're way past me i stall way back towards the starting line you're just trying to get some of that rich guy adrenochrome you know you're just trying to get some spray that's a whole other story yeah it's a whole other part and i'm distracted i'm at the hershey's store about half
a block away from that venue you're soaked in adrenaline for a different reason yeah because you're around so much chocolate you'd rather have chocolate than old man's spittle an old creepy man's spittle i this is going to be the hottest the hot take that starts us off i would rather have chocolate than old man fluid yeah all right to each his own um jason any criteria for you is any is anything like a singular aspect of the decision
you'll be making uh well i think you know i i scott i i mentioned novelty and i think the the toy attic as might put it that your version of like would i want this as a toy like is this aesthetically pleasing to look both look at and sit in yeah i think is good i think the uh uh is it pleasant to sit in might come into play what are the safety restraints not judging by like oh that's a very old version and this is the very new version
oh yeah and are the safety restraints uncomfortable or are they like part of the pleasantness yeah is it like a warm hug from mommy is it like a warm hug from mommy does it make you feel safe or does it make you feel because i've ridden some roller coasters was like this actually makes me feel worse
uh-huh i think if i think is so rickety yeah this is all i got yeah yeah yeah um i hadn't i hadn't thought about restraints being part of it but that is is part of it and do we have to
have like lock points if it's just a just a strap or if it doesn't really need a i guess we'll see yeah against it in something where you know some of these vehicles it's like part of the the the body of it is where you sit but if if it's if the seats are kind of different than if they're like added furniture to the ride vehicle is that that's part of it i think i guess it is yeah i think it has to be part of it i guess anything in the vehicle
decor yeah yeah um yeah i mean i guess you know if you're judging a car you would count the air freshener yeah of course or lack thereof right yeah
so all right these are all things we'll be taking into consideration and here's another
way that we're going to depart from previous final fours um well a couple things in the past we've kind of worked up
appropriate thematic pairings you know like these two are sort of similar in these ways these two fake theme parks are both from films released in 1994 they should go up against each other in this case not only have we not done that it's randomized and we don't know what's going to be against what in this first round so we've done no preparation in that regard we have no arguments in our head because we don't know what we have to argue yeah we're hearing
about this for the first time yeah i am calling this first round the chaos round yeah and it is much closer to actual march madness where 16 seed will knock out like duke or purdue or something it is very similar to the basketball tournament yeah i'm dead serious it's serious as a heart attack it's done in one day in several hours instead of many weeks that's right there's a lot in common but here's the other big thing
you might be wondering how did we narrow this down to 16 this is such a wide area there's so many great iconic theme park vehicles and we did not narrow it down to 16 for the first time ever we are starting with 32
possibly the most unwise aspect of this year's competition and you're and you're also maybe wondering at this point so this is a four hour episode not true i hope we'll see because we will certainly see but we have kind of put our own rules in place here i'll just say what i am calling this first round which is the hurry through 32
so it uh this implies speed it has to be a speed round not to say that we can't discuss the choices that we're making but i think it's got to be limited to emotional reactions to a couple of words yeah we could try to dissuade each other if we're really passionate about a point right we can certainly attempt maybe we could even at the end go back and say is there one that we need to to litigate yeah but i think mostly we just got to fly off a gut here this is yes
this is going to be the quick we're going to start with a burst of speed a burst of uh adrenaline here is it possible that we do this and i'd almost everyone we're like oh
so we all start standing up like we have to pee and we're like oh yeah i'm drinking coffee and it's a little brisk outside today i gotta take a walk i can't do the first round yeah yeah it's possible it was very possible
then we get back on and we say hey we're back it's been two weeks and we threw all that out we had to do a lot more thinking about it now it's 64 we've added more we've it was unfair the one that didn't get in yeah uh we're gonna try we'll see yeah you might hear some drastic edits but hopefully we just plow through this thing right and get in get through the hurry through 32 are we ready for the hurry through 32
let's do it and just remember this is the law when this gets decided this is legally binding yeah you have to think it as a listener to this show you gotta do it the longer you've been listening to the show the more you have to agree with all our opinions
yeah and you have to start saying this opinion at parties or at theme park outings it's yours and if we left one of your favorite vehicles out it means it's bad your choice was bad yeah means we don't like it we don't like the ride
well so you know yeah you'll you'll just hear them all random i and we'll hear for the first time what's competing against what even i tried to not really look at i didn't look at the list
but i guess we'll dig into the list and i think we have so we'll we'll we'll go around because we it still has to be like we gotta there's gonna have to be breaking of ties
um so we'll change up who starts every time so let's start with jason okay as we get into the first one what is it okay
oh this is funny um all right wow oh man it's randomized and yet holy shit how do these two end up next to each other okay remember we gotta go fast yeah okay radiator springs racers versus the mader's junkyard
jamberry tractor them wow how does this happen how are we in a radiator springs duel i don't know even this is too much talk okay uh but we have to react to that that's very strange okay uh uh jason radiator springs versus drunker jamboree tractor
oh great tough ones tough ones the uh radiator springs racers have those cute little no this is too much no no no stop it i'm going with mader wow mike a mader
i think the intersprings racers are out uh what am i saying the vehicle's cute as shit i really like that ride um i mader yeah mader's in all right that's more fun all right people upset already okay uh too much talking let's do let's let's go to mike and the next one oh shit oh dumbo the flying elephant versus the super stretched limo from rock and roller coaster oh god oh god oh my god
oh no oh shit oh it's no it's dumbo i gotta say dumbo i'm sorry i'm sorry steven dumbo dumbo it's clean sweet oh okay man uh hate that wow oh boy yeah no further discussion of the you want me to read the next one um yes sure yes yeah give it to me okay uh hagrids motorbikes and side cars uh versus elevator car from tower of terror hagrids
yeah hagrids elevator wow well all right all right finally is that the first disagreement okay yeah um all right i will send it to jason and i will say the disneyland canoes with the davy crocket canoe what are they called even now davy car uh canoes versus alice in wonderland caterpillar oh wow
oh i'm gonna give it to alice might be next uh uh uh caterpillar yeah me too caterpillar sorry canoes okay um i will send the next one to mike which is the et adventure bikes versus big thunder mountain mine train oh wow oh wow uh uh
you can kind of see oh no no no sorry you're right you're right too much too much too much
oh i want to uh yeah et
that's difficult yeah
i can give a rest but we don't need to we don't need to belabor here
big thunder oh yeah i almost said it too tiebreaker jason that's the closest i've been yeah i'm gonna give it to big thunder wow
wow wow wow we can discuss any of these later after the speed rant uh okay you want to give me the next one mike yeah it's spider-man scoop vehicle and elizabeth venture uh first order fleet transport from rise of the resistance uh um
hmm first order fleet transport mean or jason uh jason scoop scoop scoop wow okay uh bound to happen i think okay so uh next one goes to jason
hmm heimlich choo choo train versus slinky dog oh my god wow who do you like better the pixar punch out these are good yeah these are good matchups that's a good pair
i think i'm gonna give it to him like really heimlich is fun uh but that's already too much to talk to you
uh slinky dog oh i love that slinky dog i love sitting in that thing i'm gonna allow this discussion because i feel like i need to look at a photo of of heimlich choo choo train yeah
heimlich slinky dog all right okay fair enough i mean i i look i liked looking at it i was really happy he was in the 32 but yeah um okay let's send the next one to mike
okay people mover car versus soren hang gliders can we uh point of clarification is this the florida people mover or the california people mover
uh which one would you like it to be oh hmm that could really weigh it uh i'll say florida okay uh
is your pick mike uh people mover people mover yeah all right i'll give it to people mover too okay
okay um i keep this is going so fast i'm gonna is it you're giving me the next one
uh yeah or i'll do it yeah haunted mansion doom buggy versus space mountain rocket wow oh my god
uh wow oh this is the most difficult one thus far for sure do shit doom buggy ah doom buggy uh
jason uh yeah i'll give it to doom buggy too i was gonna say space rocket anyway okay
uh doom buggy it is doom buggy advances okay the next one to jason which is matterhorn bobsled
versus mr toad motor car interesting interesting uh i'm gonna give it to mr toad
mike mr toad mr toad we were all like we weigh it but then well there's been a couple but yeah uh
next up next is yours indiana jones jeep versus mad tea party teacup oh my god
this sucks i don't like yeah that's yeah both could have made it oh oh oh oh oh oh uh
teacup teacup teacup yep teacup yeah i gotta give it to teacup wow they're cute i wouldn't
have believed that before this that's never a thought i've had and it makes me a little upset
we're going fast here yeah yeah yeah um okay wait it's me yeah yeah okay um wait we're here
read it mike jungle cruise boat versus back to the future eight passenger delorians oh man wow
i mean there's no way i cannot say back to the future yeah jason what do you think
i'm gonna give it to jungle cruise really yeah
shh shh shh shh back to the future wow fair enough jungle cruise out that's crazy brutal
competition this is all yeah this is i feel sick to my stomach we're gonna look at the wreckage of
this when it's all corpses on the ground uh i want to read this next one yeah yeah you make the choice
poo honey pots uh in japan oh no this is disneyland and casey jr oh man i'm throwing it to casey jr
um i shit i'm gonna poo i'm doing poo
but it's not an easy choice casey jr wow okay but the poo has honey leaking out i love the
thing i wanted to point that out i wanted to point it out and you did okay thank you next one goes to
you know jason i think you should read this one yeah please sure i think it's your fault
yeah it is uh fast and furious supercharged party bus versus the seven dwarfs mine train mine
cart okay uh i think i know what i'm wanting to answer mike why don't you start i think i'll go
with the seven dwarfs mine cart as much as i think it'd be fun to keep the supercharged party bus in
seven dwarfs mine yeah i'll give it to the mine card okay okay okay all right
tron light cycle versus skyway bucket this is me yeah i don't know whatever order i think so um
Hmm.
Ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch-ch.
Tick tock.
Tick tock, tick tock.
Tron, sleek vehicle, Skyway bucket, classic.
Classic.
Tron light cycle.
Okay, Jason, what do you think?
Giving it to the Skyway bucket.
Oh wow, this is awful.
I hate this.
Sorry, Mike.
Okay, let's, oh god.
I want light cycle.
Wow.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
Ah.
I was part of the decision and it still hurts.
Yeah, it hurts.
Okay, so last one goes to Jason.
Peter Pan pirate ship versus splash mountain log.
Ha!
Oh, also, boy, we've had a few
that could have been in the final.
Really?
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll say pirate ship.
Yeah, pirate ship.
All right, it's in.
What am I saying?
As a protest vote, I will say.
Yeah, splash mountain log.
It's been noted.
Okay.
All right, I feel awful.
I feel sick.
I feel like I'm gonna throw up.
Without thinking too much about what faces what,
what was the hardest in what we just,
and as you look at this list, what tears you up?
I'm, again, I was part of it.
I'm upset about Tron light.
I'm upset about Skyway not getting in there,
but let me say my rationale,
which is we have Classic.
You'd look at it at the auction gallery.
You'd buy it if you had a million dollars.
I think those are in there already.
If that was the first round,
maybe I would have said Skyway,
but of course you wanna argue Classic,
and in a lot of cases, we went Classic,
but that Tron, and I haven't been on Tron, by the way,
but you could tell that is an awesome vehicle.
Yeah, and I think people have compared it
to the Pony Express at Knotts, which we've done a lot.
Which we cut out of the Pony Express at Knotts.
We tried to have things that were not Disney and Universal.
This is very Disney heavy, obviously,
but Knotts, Pony Express did not make the cut.
The thing that really upsets me
is that the Space Mountain Rocket is not in here,
because that's one of those,
you look in the stock report when you're little,
and you see that iconic photo of everybody on Space Mountain,
and it looks so cool, and that's burned in my brain
as being one of the coolest looking ride vehicles.
So I don't like that Space Mountain has been taken out.
But that's against Doom Buggy?
Look, I signed up for these rules,
so I'm comfortable with it, it just makes me upset.
There's a few of these that were more curated.
I think you'd see a couple of these go all the way to the end.
Sure, but the rules are the rules.
And the winner is really all that's important.
So the winner should win in any situation.
Yes, ultimately, that's the thing.
Yeah, any pair up, they would always take it.
Jason, is anything bothering you
as you look over the battlefield?
Well, you know, that first Cars Land-based ride,
that was really tough.
That's a little insane what we did there.
Yeah.
But I feel good about it.
Okay.
I feel actually fine about that.
To be very clear, just because this ride is not everywhere,
Radiator Springs Racers is the big one,
which is also the same as Test Track, essentially.
So we've eliminated that vehicle,
which is also Journey to the Center of the Earth,
not the shape of the vehicle,
in favor of Mater's Junkyard Jamboree,
which is where there's the stationary tractor in the front,
and then your part swings back and forth,
which is also alien flying saucers in Florida.
And there's a Baymax one, I think, maybe in Tokyo.
Yes, yes.
I mean, I even said, just to do the check at the beginning,
I said, should this come out?
And I was worried you guys were gonna say yes.
And you all said, no, I really like that ride,
and that ride mechanism.
Yes.
That is like a, it's a sleeper.
You can take people who are not at Disneyland all the time.
If you're in that moment of like, I wanna go on a ride,
but I don't wanna wait for 45 minutes for something,
and you know about that one, and that's only 20,
and everybody's laughing and smiling and giggling,
that is a very fun ride.
That is a delight, that ride.
And the Florida one, real sleeper, too.
If you go on it at night
with all the different colored lights
and techno instrumental versions of Toy Story Land songs,
blasting at you, it is a delightful surprise.
I should do it, and I'd really like to do the Baymax one.
You should go to that new family-style barbecue restaurant
of Lock Away in Toy Story Land,
and then immediately get on the flying saucer ride.
Eat a big pile of meat, and then get spun around.
Anything, are you Mike Reeling from Super Stretch Limbo?
I am, but if I'm being honest,
it's like you have to take the Steven Tyler
out of the ride, the vehicle.
And out of society and being talked about anymore.
That's a different story.
Should he be banished?
Yes, but that's...
But if he...
Your decision, ultimately.
If there was like a big Steven Tyler head
on the front of the vehicle,
I think I would be more upset.
Or if there was a little Steven,
on ET, where ET's in the basket on the ride,
if Steven Tyler was in a basket on the front of the limo,
and he would turn his head around
and look at you while you were on the ride,
then I would be more upset
that the Rock and Roller Coaster limo has been eliminated.
Hey, you, you're the most rockin' guy on this whole train.
You in the 12th row.
All right, back to the ride.
If it was a Rise of the Resistance-style,
elaborate pre-show and pre-show with Aerosmith,
and like, yeah, Steven Tyler was like the droid or something.
Yeah, then I would be more disappointed.
Where there's a horrifying visage,
like there's a horrifying mini version
that he could turn his head 360 degrees
like Linda Blair in The Exorcist.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
And spray vomit at you.
Yeah, so they're like, check out Steven Tyler's hat,
and then this little animatronic of Steven Tyler
turns his head 360 degrees with his hat on.
He goes, that's rock.
Sometimes my scars get caught in the engine.
You're on your own.
Does anything, or do you think that anything that we cut
would have stood a chance?
Or do we get the right 32?
I mean, ET Adventure Bikes could have stood a chance.
I don't know if that's making it to the very, very end,
but that felt like it would have made it longer.
You know what I thought about there is that,
I like being on the bikes,
but ultimately aren't you on just kind of
like a perfunctory platform?
A platform, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, you're just like on a black panel.
That's what, the bikes themselves, great, of course.
And again, we're trying to separate a vehicle
from mechanism, but ultimately everything's tied together.
I mean, nothing is making me too upset here.
Oh, one thing needs to be talked about
before we move forward.
One back and forth that we're looking at,
the rise of the resistance, the trackless vehicle
lost to Spider-Man Scoop from the Spider-Man,
Amazing Adventures of Spider-Man in Islands of Adventure.
Of course, I knew you guys were gonna go that way with that.
I'm not mad about that one.
Even, where is the resistance?
I don't know if that was gonna go all the way.
It's a cool vehicle.
Like if there's a droid in it, that was the argument.
But when we were, this was maybe the only prickly thing
when we were narrowing it down to the 32,
is that the longer list included both Scoop,
the Spider-Man vehicle, and Evac, the Transformers vehicle.
Yes, that's true.
We were kind of like, well, should we,
I kind of felt like initially they should have both been in,
even though they were kind of the same ride.
I'm actually now feeling a little bit regretful
that I didn't push for Evac more over Scoop.
Because I kind of feel stupid, I'll be honest with you guys,
because Evac's a character.
Evac has more to do on the ride,
and I feel like the biggest mistake I made
is not pushing for Evac,
because he has more to do than Scoop does.
But that's a guy.
What he's doing is voiceover,
that's little arms on a screen.
I know.
No, no, that's coming out of your vehicle.
That's true, but the knowledge that you're inside Evac,
still to me makes,
I think I should have pushed for Evac over Scoop.
I made a mistake.
Jason would have walked out.
Jason would have quit the show.
Jason wants to...
I would have slapped your laptop out of it.
Jason would want to Scoop bed.
He would want to make his bed out of Scoop.
You know what?
Usually I'm a little creeped out by ideas
where Jason has to be in a little thing.
I think that's a nice idea for Jason.
I think Jason should try to get a Scoop.
Like a race car bed,
but it's Scoop, the ride vehicle from the Spider-Man ride.
It would lend itself to bed.
Yeah, yeah.
Open air.
But you're a little...
You got a little cocoon.
What do you think you could fit?
Could you fit a California king inside Scoop?
Is there any other podcast?
In the actual size of it?
Yeah, in the actual full vehicle,
how big of a mattress could you fit?
If you took the seats out.
That's a very inconvenient mattress size.
It's comically big.
California king?
Yeah.
Oh, well we've had a California king.
It's not so bad.
Do you have one?
Yeah.
Is that bigger than king?
Well it's different.
It's a shorter...
It's bigger in some ways,
but it's not...
I forget if it's length...
Head to toe it's shorter, I believe, than king,
but it's wider.
Okay, okay.
So, but they're both big.
King and California king.
Not sure.
I think you get the biggest possible mattress size
in that...
Might have to be custom, but...
Yeah, yeah.
If somebody can make Jason a custom bed frame that's Scoop.
Sure.
Sorry, we're not asking for art.
We're asking for a bed frame.
Somebody has to build Jason.
Carpenter has to make Jason a...
It's like Nick Offerman's shop over in California
can make Jason.
I know they do woodworking, but if they can make...
Custom woodworking or 3D printing massive plastic panels.
So like, you know, sometimes we do these live shows
and people are nice and give us little gifts.
So sometime we're doing a show
and then a massive truck pulls up.
Beep, beep, beep.
Four workers get out.
It's just start pulling out slabs.
Like, oh, that must be the...
Guess Jason got the bed.
Jason got a bed.
And they're delivering it to the theater, not to his house.
I'm not sure how we're gonna move it from the street.
He's gotta take it home somehow.
The main thing to say though is that
when we were going through the list,
we were trying to find what...
And I said, I think the vehicles
that are essentially the same should not really be on the...
So Dinosaur time vehicle is out and Indiana Jones Jeep is in.
And I said, maybe not both Scoop and Evac.
And the looks that I got from both of you guys,
it honestly felt like you would...
I would have bought that you guys would have left here
and then gone to the front yard and said,
so we gotta get Scott off the show, right?
This is where it's course.
Yeah, I think.
What's going on with him?
It's come to a head.
I've been waiting to say something and I don't want to,
but did you hear him in there?
Did you hear him?
Look, we had a discussion about replacing you.
That's true, after you said that.
We did talk about it.
There was a couple names, but we decided,
not before this final four.
Can we get...
At least we're gonna wait until after.
There's a lot of...
With the advances in AI recently,
can we get an AI that sounds like Optimus Prime,
who would only agree with us, tell us he's proud?
I completely approve of both of your diets,
Mike and Jason.
I will never roast you about any of these things.
I booted up ChatGPT and it immediately started telling me,
maybe you should go do something reckless, live a little.
Oh look, I'll be honest.
We sent a contract to Paging Mr. Morrow,
but we couldn't meet our demand.
He couldn't agree on terms, so you're still in for now.
Look, I gotta tell you, he'd be tough to have
in this exact episode,
because he'd say, I can't choose.
I love them all.
And he'd be right.
And he'd be right, yes.
We're wrong to do any of this.
Look, ultimately, we're gonna get to the end of all of this,
and there will be an arbitrary winner,
but of course they're all winners.
Even the ones that didn't make it.
All right, I think that we should take a little break.
I'm gonna put these into a genuine bracket format,
so we will re-document, and we will pick things up
at the 16, wait, I'll just say the name now,
which is the Please Remain Seated 16.
We'll pick it up there.
Welcome back to Final Four Five, Vehicle Vengeance.
We return now for the Please Remain Seated 16.
We ourselves are on the move due to a neighbor's yard work,
not wanting to ask him to stop.
We're too scared of the neighbor to ask.
Yes, yeah, well, you know, less teep.
If he is an adrenaline-soaked throttle jockey,
I don't want him throttling me.
Well, turning the weed whacker on you.
Yeah, that's true, he does have a weapon.
It's a murder weapon.
Yeah, could be carving up a body as we speak,
like the last podcaster who asked him to stop.
Oh my gosh.
So if the sound is different, that's what's happening,
and if the sound changes again, that's again what happens.
Yep, we'll be back outside, who knows?
If one of us is dead by the end, we got weed whacked.
But we are now into it.
We have a bracket in front of us,
and we can still discuss a little bit,
don't wanna go forever, but we can rationalize these,
and I think we're gonna need each other's help
figuring this out,
because there's big ones going up against each other.
So let's start it off with
Mater's Junkyard Jamboree Tractor,
who again vanquished the bigger radiator springs card,
unanimously versus Dumbo the Flying Elephant,
and I think Mike is gonna have to start this one,
if I remember the order correctly.
Yeah, I mean, I'll start it.
Yes, so this, okay, so I think
the Mater's Junkyard Jamboree winning was correct.
I think that vehicle is cuter,
and I also like the coziness of it,
so I do think that was correct.
I have no regrets about those.
It's very nice molded foam.
Yeah.
They're just very pleasant,
and you're excited when you're sitting in them.
Yeah.
Dumbo is iconic.
You mentioned iconic earlier,
and it's maybe the most iconic ride vehicle ever.
Could be.
That thing that I said about Skyway
that I feel like we've covered the type of vehicle
you'd wanna buy at the auction,
like you just saw one in the wild,
you'd gasp, Dumbo one of those big time.
But here's the thing, I don't love sitting in it.
It's not the most comfortable thing to sit in.
And yeah, I like being in it,
but I don't like the sitting.
The comfortability of Dumbo is not high.
You would say the tractors are more comfortable
than that wagon? Yes, I would say that.
Okay.
And there's something unique about being pulled on that too.
I like being pulled along in a way.
It is what's happening.
You're being pulled essentially.
You're on obviously a track as well.
But I like the unique, you're being towed.
Back and forth.
Which is fun and unique.
Being towed is unique.
But Dumbo, I don't know if it's,
it's hard to beat the iconic Dumbo.
Yeah, that iconic is the biggest thing it has going for it.
Certainly.
And it looks good.
Also, just side issue,
we moved into my office, which has toys on it.
And now I'm like, what about Skyliner?
We didn't do it.
We forgot Skyliner.
Skyliner is a good vehicle.
I mean, I don't wanna like,
but hey, if we all forgot it,
how was that gonna take it all the way?
Well, that and Monorail, I think of more as modes of transit.
Getting from place A to place B.
We took out Universal Tram too.
And you know what never entered the picture is the train.
So I mean, based on our own internal criteria,
we didn't have a lot of disagreement on it.
I guess we gotta feel okay about it.
Well, next year, final four will be modes of transit.
Okay.
Well, there we go.
Now Jason's excited.
Jason's checked out till next year.
An Enterprise rental car versus your legs.
Well, our legs are free.
We do have them.
Yeah.
This is wear and tear over the years, but,
okay, to solve this one, I don't know.
You wanna lock one in?
Dumbo.
Wow, okay.
Yeah, I gotta say Dumbo too.
Yeah, clean sweep, I'm also gonna give it to Dumbo.
Okay, okay.
Probably bonus points for, again,
we gotta decide how much we weight range of movement,
but Dumbo spins around, but also changes elevation.
That's true.
Does two things.
Right, it goes around and goes up and down.
Yeah. Two things.
And some of these just go forward.
Yeah. Boring.
So, something to consider as we move into the next round,
which I think I have to start it off,
and this is Hagrid's motorbikes and side cars
versus the Alice in Wonderland caterpillars.
Alice in Wonderland caterpillars is another one
I was worried somebody would want to take off,
but I guess I don't know.
I don't know your guys' particular fondness
for those vehicles.
I really like them.
Yeah.
It's like a, I like that they're longer.
I feel like the Fantasyland rides,
the long ones are kind of trumped,
or they trump the smaller one.
Like, you know what didn't make it is the snow white cars
or Jupiter, wood carvers' carts,
which is the Pinocchio vehicle.
Yes, that's true.
We never discussed a wood carver's cart,
which is what you climb aboard in Pinocchio's
during Journey.
Right.
But look, it's called March Madness,
not March Sensible Discussion, you know?
Right.
This is mad.
What we're doing is mad.
Yeah.
We're getting mad.
That's the thing I like to say.
And then you, I,
it was brought up for discussion cutting Hagrid's motorbikes
and side cars, but we got, when we did that ride
and we got to try both,
the fact that it is a different experience on both sides
and they feel markedly different,
and that, it's a really well done vehicle.
Like that could be a,
every one of those vehicles could be a prop and a film.
Yeah.
Those are camera ready.
Right.
I might have to stare at one.
I'm gonna pull up a picture.
Do you guys have any points on this?
I'll lock one in.
Oh, you're locking in?
Yeah.
I'm gonna go with the Caterpillar.
Because if we're just looking at vehicles,
it's like a whimsical colorful,
like creation versus dirty, brutish motorcycles.
Oh, you really got dirty in my head.
I kind of can't unsee that.
That made me feel good better about the motorcycle though.
It's a more of a descriptor.
It for wizards who can do anything.
There's a lot of filth in their world.
There's a lot of.
Oh, is that right?
Is that what Tagline, one of the Harry Potter movies?
Yeah.
There's a lot of filth in our world.
Interesting.
Scott, do you wanna lock something in
or do you want me to lock in?
Geez.
That's tough.
Because I'm ready to lock in.
Well, if you're, then mine doesn't matter.
So yeah, if you're.
Not necessarily.
Oh, oh, you're right.
Oh, wait, wait.
All right, what are you going with?
I'm going with a dirty British motorcycle.
That's so funny.
Dirty pushed you one way.
And I think it pushed me the other way.
I love the Caterpillar, but the uniqueness of sitting,
got two different types of sittings.
Two different kinds of sitting.
Totally unique, both fun in their own way.
The look of it is, as you're saying, a movie prop.
It's perfect.
This Caterpillar is really fun.
Sitting in it is fun, but I would say
there's nothing else that feels like Hagrid.
I mean, I guess there's similar things,
I guess like Pony Express or something,
I assume what Tron feels like, but I don't know.
I think this, the Hagrid's recreates a ride vehicle
from a movie in a perfect way and doesn't,
I don't know why I don't say cheap out,
but I can imagine a version of it like 10 or 20 years before
where they're just sort of suggesting that ride vehicle
and you're sitting in little chairs.
I think they nailed it.
It wouldn't have looked as, and you know what, look,
we pulled out ET and I think ultimately,
well, it's so cool to sit on a bike and that that flies.
They didn't go all the way.
And they don't really look like the movie.
It's also confusing ET a little bit.
It's a bunch of bikes all next to each other.
How, you don't get to see ET pop up
and you know that it's there, but he's not turning around
and looking at you like Steven Tyler.
Ooh.
You know what, that way we got,
getting to do it both sidecar and, yeah, yeah,
I think you talked me into it with that.
I think I'm going with the, and there's gonna be other,
look, cute is represented.
Cute is represented already with Dumbo.
That was gonna be a battle of the cute
and I think Dumbo takes the battle of the cute.
And we love cute here on this podcast,
but there should be some realism and some dirt
and this represented in this tournament as well
and that's what this is.
Vehicles get dirty.
Dirty.
Monster trucks, dirt bikes.
It's right there in the name.
Right.
And I would say sometimes you get one of those caterpillars
and it's dirty and not in a fun way.
It looks just kind of like the paint
hasn't been freshened up in a while.
Hmm.
It doesn't always look like a fresh caterpillar.
Not an artifice kind of dirt.
Right.
Okay, I feel hesitantly comfortable with this.
I think the recurring thing with all of these
is it's less us yelling at each other,
arguing with each other and more just it's hemming and hawing.
These are the real winners of all of these are hems and haws.
Yeah.
It comes down to two and it's an even tie.
Well, I think there might be-
We can get some yelling in there.
I think there's about to be some yelling, honestly.
Uh-oh.
As far as the next matchup.
Okay, watch those levels, Mike.
Because I think Jason leads the discussion
or makes the first choice if you want
on Big Thunder Mountain Mind Train versus Spider-Man Scoop.
I'm going to start off the discussion.
I wonder where.
I'm going to punt my voting.
Well, one of you already or if not both of you have already done it.
So Big Thunder Mountain, if we're just looking at vehicles,
ooh, this is tough because we can't not mention range of movement.
Big Thunder Mountain, kind of interesting.
It's a train, changes elevations, moves around a lot.
Scoop also, you know, kind of swivels you a lot,
hooks into an elevator at some point,
but it's also just a big mold of plastic.
So if we're just stepping back and looking at the vehicles
and inspecting the vehicles.
Oh, wow.
I think it might have to be Big Thunder Mountain.
Shots.
Wow.
You know, the chaos round has just inspired me.
It's infected me like a rich man's adrenochrome sweat.
OK, and I feel I'm off the leash.
I'm like the secret lies of pets.
I'm unleashed.
Imagine though being you're leaving all your teenage dreams behind.
But my childhood dreams, young childhood,
Big Thunder Mountain was just scary enough.
You should write your own.
This isn't just an idea I had.
This is a side note.
If we could write a parody of Katy Perry's teenage dreams song,
which I think is one of my favorite Katy Perry songs,
not the favorite,
well, write it about you and Islands of Adventure.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, because I well, I say to you when we were walking to our cars
the other night, I was like my YouTube subscriptions and algorithms
are now just like old theme park clips,
weird, weird German guy opening packs of trading cards and
dead malls, dead and dying malls.
Right.
So all stuff I liked as a childhood,
preferably the malls were not dead at the time.
That's the female X-Men is a storm.
Yes. Yeah. OK.
The opening lines of this song are I think storms pretty without any makeup
on being part of entry.
I'm grabbing some sin of bond.
Perfect. Great.
We're off to the races.
Well, where does that take you, Mike?
In the new and then another part of the song.
I mean, I meant that I mean, feel free, but also.
Oh, and also we forgot to check for any DVD prices in Jason's brain.
Oh, yeah. He's teenage dreams.
But no, I mean, of course, of course, of course.
Yeah. Big Thunder Mountain versus Scoop.
I think it's got to be Big Thunder.
Yeah, I love Scoop and Big Thunder is such, you know,
I don't have to explain, honestly.
No, I don't either. I'm going Big Thunder Man.
Look, I didn't know if we hadn't talked about this stuff forever.
I didn't know Scoop. I didn't know this Scoop.
We all say Scoop is and then it's Scoop and Scoop and Scoop and Scoop
and even Scoop, you know, it's tough, but I'm going to have to go Scoop.
I didn't know the name of Scoop.
And you're right. Ultimately, it's molded plastic.
It's great. Yeah, it's great.
And mechanism wise, one of the squinching.
This is going to happen a lot with these vehicles.
If it's like if it's a vehicle, like if it was the Spider Mobile,
which I believe was the name of his dumb car.
Yeah, that was his car in the 70s or something.
They all had cars.
It's obviously the Batmobile, we all know, but Superman definitely had a.
Yeah. And like Joker has a car like the Joker mobile.
Like here and there, all the characters eventually have mobiles.
Helicopter with his name on it.
Oh, yeah.
This is for he didn't have that in the movie.
No, he didn't.
So, yeah, if it's just yeah.
OK, I feel good. Big Thunder.
You know, what else didn't make it to the 32 is the
the web slingers, big red box.
Oh, right. Web slingers, miniature circuit city boxes.
Within the building that is also a big circuit city box.
There is. Yeah, there's an element of that ride that makes you feel like
you're on a conveyor, like you're in like a factory kind of being,
I don't know, processed in some way.
This is the way the whole thing moves.
It feels like almost like on Radiator Springs when you're getting like
your wheels checked or you're getting a new coat of paint.
Oh, yeah. There's just something about it where it's like
you go to the station, you go to the station.
I Jason, do you want to throw the next category to to Mike?
Sure, Mike, this next category, you got Slinky Dog Dash,
the Slinky Dog Dash vehicle versus the PeopleMover car.
Who is right?
Who will always be right?
This is interesting because PeopleMover,
I think we all have a lot of affection for it.
It's a little blue box, essentially, but throwing out boxes.
But it's I would say is of all the boxes, it's the most comfortable.
Box, maybe. Yeah.
It's like being in a little private booth.
Yeah, like a better Vegas luxury box or a.
Yeah. If they could sell like cabanas, like a Vegas pool, that would be like
you could set it on the PeopleMover track and ride it around like there would be
VIP PeopleMover boxes.
Yeah. With like a little more shade and like a bottle of Grey Goose.
Oh, God, they should.
This is a really good like I'm not usually for the like charge up ideas,
but shape back stuff.
But oh, I would love the bottle service on the bottle service on the PeopleMover
would be a huge hit.
And you get multiple laps. You get like, you know, you can spend a couple hours.
Yeah, you can do it all day.
Yeah. If you want.
This is such a good every eight or every tenth car is like the bottle service
car on the PeopleMover because it is a comfortable seat compared to,
you know, other theme park rides, because that's what it's designed to chill.
You're designed.
You're supposed to chill out on it.
If you were the group had bottle service on the PeopleMover
and you can hang out there for hours, would you split it up with people if you want?
Yeah. Would you?
I feel like three thousand dollars would be fine.
You'd never forget that day.
So sick you are.
But I agree with you.
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
If I had the money, sure.
So, OK, I've given Disney a great idea here.
But Slinky Dog is maybe
and I'm trying to think of before I make this point, so I don't seem like a moron.
Is there a better representation of sitting inside a character
than Slinky Dog?
I don't think on this list.
Not on this list.
Caterpillar just went out. Right.
So that sort of feels like the dream from my kid brain.
It's like, oh, my God, I'm sitting inside or on top of a character from the movie.
And he looks just like the character in the movie.
I love the care. Slinky's awesome character.
I guess it's what are you prioritizing sitting on or in a character's body
versus comfort?
Well, right. Florida PeopleMover, like you say, it's very comfortable.
It's very relaxing.
I was talking to my dad about this the other day.
He's like, look, I always liked Florida Tomorrowland
because it was very like all of those rides early on.
We're super relaxed.
Florida Tomorrowland?
Yeah, Florida Tomorrowland.
No, not Space Mountain.
But like if you had wings.
Oh, yes. PeopleMover and the Carousel of Progress.
Yeah, that's a good point.
But but as we said at the start of this,
we got to take the ride away.
Yeah. And it just has to be the vehicle.
Yeah. So even though those seats are comfortable,
we're not getting the comforting experience of being on the PeopleMover.
So you're left with a nice seat, fine seat, interesting little box.
And I think even though it's less comfortable
sitting inside of Slinky, one of the best characters in Pixar history
wins out. Wow. Wow.
And a great representation, better than the Caterpillar, I would say.
It is. Yeah.
Big two. It's a really satisfying character to see big.
And when it pulls into the station and you watch that smile,
yeah, you see people on it.
I remember watching videos of it getting delivered, of it pulling up
to Hollywood studios.
I also think I think this is a strange idea, the idea that it's
uncomfortable in there.
It's not like being in a, you know, you like sitting across from your friends
or like being seated backwards in the PeopleMover.
I'm also I'm trying to like not throw out the Disneyland one with a little roof.
Sure. No, probably aesthetically the better design.
Maybe kind of over the years as they added more and more safety bars
looked uglier and uglier. Right.
Sure. Sure.
But as I said, I was remembering like some smaller regional parks I was at, like
I was thinking about the sky bucket and I looked up pictures and they did have a full
floor, but I definitely remember riding some sky bucket like rides
where there was just like a square hole in the middle.
And they're like, don't worry, you won't fall through.
And thinking back, I'm like, why was there just a hole on this thing
with no seatbelt? Like, why?
So a plus of a lot of these is no hole.
No hole. Yeah.
You're not falling out of most of these vehicles.
I think, you know, I think your argument really won me over.
I think I'm slinky. Yeah.
Yeah. Jason, what would you have said?
Well, I actually was going to, you know, in the in the interest of making it
interesting, I was going to say PeopleMover because my concern is that
we end up with a just a lot of cute ride vehicles and that novelty outweighs
comfort for the whole bracket.
It wasn't cute. Yeah, we got a lot.
I went with it so far.
Now it's even, I'd say, between cute and dirty.
Yeah. I guess if we're discovering a dirty component, most maybe most right.
Yeah. Let's fall into those categories.
But I would like to see one little box go all the way.
I would. Well, I don't happen in here, pal.
OK, fair enough.
Look, I'm not. I'm not.
Dreams in a little box.
Yeah. And shove them.
Um, this next one,
Mike, you want to do the honor?
I think I'm. Yeah, it's Haunted Mansion, Doombuggy versus Mr.
Toad Motorcar. Wow.
This is interesting.
Yeah. And let's I mean, now the dirty and cute are the sort of things
where we've really separated vehicles by.
These are both.
Well, Mr. Toads is more cute, I guess.
It's a cute little again, but it is also a dirty British motorcar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So is it boxed out by Hagrid's in some way?
I don't know. That's not its fault.
That's not it. Got in first Haunted Mansion, Doombuggy.
I would argue.
Doesn't look very good.
Isn't visually that interesting to me.
It's famous because of the ride.
And by the way, it's kind of representing Omni-Mover shells in general.
Is there an argument that the Little Mermaid ones are kind of more fun?
Big show. I think there are.
If we're just separating the art from the artist,
the separating the ride from the ride.
Well, this is what's your what's your what's more important?
I guess is it novelty or is it minimalism?
Because I think it could be made that the Doombuggy's are cute.
They're cute little curved guys.
They kind of hug you.
I feel very safe in a doombuggy.
Well, that's as there's horrors, a house of horrors that you're going through.
You know, that's your argument to make. That's fine.
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
For to visual protection, if you want to have brief awkward teenage makeouts.
Yes. And look, I will say this.
The biggest thing the Doombuggy is, is that it's, I think, the coziest vehicle in any theme park.
Yeah, I took my first time back at Disneyland.
I took a brief nap in it.
It is cozy as shit.
Boy, and it does. It makes you feel good.
It's covering you. You're in the dark already.
You could be alone. You could be packed in there with three people, with two people.
It's it's unique in that way.
And it's coziness.
But aesthetically, I don't think it's cute.
I'm sorry. I'm not going to go with you on cute.
I think I think cool and that it's like a big coffin that you're riding in.
And I like that the bar lowers.
You've got to give it that. That's one bit of functionality.
I don't even know what I'd say. Cool.
If it was separated from the ride.
I think people are going to hate this opinion.
But you know what? Bring it on.
I think this is I think is mine to to lock in.
I'm going, Mr.
Tell. I can't believe it.
I like because you think I would take Doombuggy all the way.
It's fame. The name is fame.
But, you know, let me get a non intellectual point.
It's got a little wheel and you spin it around.
You can do that. Your kid can do that.
Yeah, it's fun to pretend you have some control of it.
It gives you like interactivity.
They all have different names.
I did. It's Mr. Toad. It's Mr. Toad for me.
You want to vote next?
I yeah, I think coziness hasn't come up yet.
And I think it's important.
I think both the I think both you're right.
Both the stands for coziness, the curve combined with the lowering lap bar,
which is kind of like a safety feature that's pretty difficult to mess up.
You know, what do you mean?
So you're cozy behind and then it's I find the lap bar lower.
I find that comforting.
I feel like I'm tucked into this ride.
So Jason has chosen the ride that tucks you in.
Now, that's he's not wrong.
That is that is a very unique thing, but it's it's pure black.
Well, you want to get tucked into again.
But it's a it's a psychological factor.
Not it's not like a blanket.
And I don't think that's that's not the purpose of the ride.
Yeah, it's to make you feel like you're tucked in.
But it's part of they've incorporated into the narrative
that that's what the ghost host is doing.
It honestly never occurred to me until this moment
that you are essentially tucked into a coffin.
But that is interesting to think about.
It is interesting to think about, isn't it?
And I'd love to think about it for more than the next minute.
But sadly, we have to keep rolling here.
It's tough because I you do make a good argument
that the tucking in and what I was saying, the coziness of it is unique.
It is the closest ride you can get to feeling like you could go to sleep easily.
That it's backwards, backwards.
Like that's a perfect time to go to bed is when you're going down into the cemetery.
Can I throw in that?
I mean, I already locked in my vote, but just to confuse things,
the ability of the OmniMover car to direct your attention,
to stare at this, to lock your focus in on this
at the half box ghost or the scared guy at the bottom of the hill.
That's that's something it is.
You know, Wallenauer was talking about.
It's like the POV direction of ride vehicles.
Yeah. Yeah.
Innovation of that. Yeah.
That said, if you look at them from 10, 20 feet away,
Mr. Toads is obviously more colorful, more whimsical.
Yes. Yes. So I think here I'll go.
I think, though, if you take the ride out of the doom buggy.
The coziness becomes claustrophobia.
That without the fun is of the music and all of that,
you're sort of trapped in a not cute looking vehicle.
And yeah, I can move you around, but you're not going to feel that same warmth
because you're not on the Haunted Mansion.
You're just in an odd piece of metal.
Yeah, I think I know where you're going, Mr. Toad.
Yeah, Jason, another to say dirty British car.
You said it. I think you're ready.
Oh, OK. Got it.
OK, so, geez, I am I am surprised that I wouldn't have thought that before we started today.
Yeah, I thought Dumbuggy could have been the winner.
But when you talk through it, when you realize things,
that one started with me, right?
So Jason, you can make the first choice if you wish on Mad Tea Party
versus the Back to the Future Eight Passenger.
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy, this is a tough one.
I'll say this year, that randomizer, that chaos around us led to some very interesting.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ones that shouldn't have happened until the final the final four.
Right. But that's the fun.
That's the fun of this.
Two Alice's Alice based attractions.
Yes. To the sit down.
Oh, yes. 16.
Oh, yeah. Cars didn't get that.
Mm hmm. Alice is better than cars.
Yeah. Jason, what are your initial thoughts?
Oh, my initial thoughts.
I mean, the teacups are very pleasing to look at.
Very, very pleasing to look at.
I would agree completely with that.
Wonderful. That Mary Blair color palette.
And in a way, I sorry to interrupt you, but maybe the second most iconic Disneyland
ride vehicles. You say Dumbo first and Dumbo first teacup second.
Yeah.
Hmm. And it's lasted and been replicated, you know, for a reason.
Yes. Back to the future.
Kind of an early.
An 80s technological 80s, early 90s technological innovation.
I mean, it's the DeLorean, the DeLorean.
Yeah. And Doc figured out how to get eight people in there.
Yeah. That's the innovation and remote control it.
Right. It's the old DeLorean's
could barely fit two people and a dog.
This is tricky because the DeLorean does look like the DeLorean from the movie.
So it's wish fulfillment in that.
So you are it's got the panels.
Everything's right. It's flux capacitor.
Doors open. Yeah.
The doors swing open.
Yes, they swing open.
So you get a view.
You're watching a different video that's separate from the ride.
You get your own thing up and it's, you know, if you're up
steering, that's cool versus being in the back.
Huh? This is tricky because I thought I maybe knew exactly what I wanted out of this.
But now I don't know.
Now I'm not sure because the teacup is so simple in its design.
You know, it's like it's it's it feels pure to me.
It feels like this is the embodiment of what you want on a ride.
It's been around, but it also looks fun.
It's got fun colors.
All the vehicles are different colors.
And that would be fun in any context, in a dirty parking lot, in a swamp,
just spinning around in a cup.
You don't need anything around the ride.
It can still spin in the swamp.
It could spin in the swamp.
And you know what? Now that I'm talking myself through this, I think I've decided
the teacups as a ride doesn't need Disneyland.
You can have fun and that teacup anywhere you want on in on the moon, on Neptune,
in the center of the earth, Jupiter, Jupiter, none.
Alpha Centauri.
I think I see what you're saying.
The joy of the ride is built into the vehicle itself.
Yes. Back to the future.
DeLorean is kind of dependent on a rotting IMAX screen.
And it's fun because you get to see like, oh, that's I mean, it kind of
if you look at the front part of the it doesn't quite look like the front of the
DeLorean, it's a little bit it's not quite perfect like Hagrid's or Mr.
Toad, but it's its own.
You're right. It's its own thing.
But if we're talking movement visually, yeah, it's teacup.
It's got to be teacups. Jason.
Scott, do you have one?
Teacup, teacup. It's teacups.
Keep boxing. Yeah, we keep just deciding.
But what are you saying officially?
What would you have said?
Oh, I think I think I would have thrown it to back to the future because.
Well, make your plea. Huh?
Make your plea.
Well, I think one thing is that like, you know, it's crazy to say
an attraction kind of disrespect it through its history.
Back to the future. Like gone. Sure.
Is it gone everywhere? Yeah, it is.
Yeah. OK.
And and like probably one of the most common universal,
like, why did they get rid of that?
Well, that's true.
But the upkeep on it, atrocious. Sure.
But vehicle wise, vehicle purely, purely vehicle wise.
What's your argument for it?
I think it's very pleasing to see the control the panel.
It's pleasing to hear the sounds and like,
yeah, all the blinking lights and stuff.
It is a particularly fun like think about that versus a radiator springs racer,
which has no video. It's a car. Right.
It moves. It moves better than right.
Jostles you around. But I think think about that pair up.
I think DeLorean wins handily.
That's true. Yeah.
A radiator springs racers, oddly, we're not going to go all the way no matter who.
Yeah. Yeah. OK.
I can't believe that. Right.
But nobody nobody's mind has changed. No.
I mean, I'm back to the future.
No, I feel not. I feel great.
OK, Jason, would you like to throw that?
Oh, wait, did I? You took that? Yeah.
Send the next one to Mike. Go ahead.
No, you really excuse me.
Send it to me. Casey Jr.
Versus the seventh worst mine train mine cart. OK.
Casey Jr., one of your favorite rides. Very cute.
Very cute. Very cute.
We can all agree it's a very cute ride.
There's we're considering all the cars on Casey Jr.
Because there's multiple again, like Hagrid's, there's you can have a lot of different types
of experiences. You can sit different directions on it.
You can sit in little cages.
You can sit in regular seats.
So we're going to we're going to put all of that in this, right?
We're going to think about all of that.
You just you just made the argument already for me.
There's no question for me. It's Casey Jr.
In this this one, not to make it less dramatic.
What is possibly the argument on the other side?
Yeah, a bunch of barrels.
Yeah, I like bunch of it's better than just some boxy roller coaster.
But compared to against Casey Jr., you've never been on the ride.
I haven't been on the ride.
They do rock. I will say these this rocking mechanism is so much fun.
I don't know. You're right. You're right.
This is important. And I will say because we don't have the original,
like Snow White Scary Adventure ride vehicles.
And I would say as a kid, it was a pretty close.
I would say I would have given the edge to Peter Pan and the pirate ship.
But as a kid, seeing those little wood carved vehicles
on the Snow White ride was very exciting to me. Yeah.
And I those probably those were the two vehicles
I would have said were the best when I was a little kid.
So these are now it's a roller coaster version of those hand
carved looking wood things and a very unique, smooth rocking.
And I love these ride vehicles.
OK, I will say this.
And I think this ride is maybe the ride itself, which we're not trying to.
But the ride itself is too short.
But I think it's a really, really smooth, fun sensation.
And I would say.
That even though Casey Jr.
is cute, I and again, it's a personal thing because of how much I like the
the like the wooden ride vehicles, maybe from my youth.
I think I give it the seven, seven dollars a mine cart.
OK, honestly, well, I think Jason's the tiebreaker.
Yeah, we know what he's going to say.
I'm giving it to Casey Jr.
All right. Yeah. Just pure vehicle alone.
Again, stand back and look at it from a distance.
It's like, oh, that's a delightful, colorful train with multiple options.
And maybe I'm look, maybe I'm saying I don't like it as much because I'm a tall guy.
And when they throw me in one of those cages, it's uncomfortable.
Yeah, I'm too tall for the lion cage.
Yeah. On Casey Jr.
I mean, it's a ride for little kids also.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I'm a little baby.
We've had a very I've had a nice time with with a baby on it.
Sure. I'm with my own.
I didn't take one. OK, good.
But all right. All right.
It's an odd one. But I hear you, Mike.
And sure. Well, you want to send the next one my way?
Yeah. Tron Lightcycle versus Peter Pan Pirate Ship.
Oof. Look, I'm probably not the guy to start.
Start with a lot of pan.
You got to take your pan bias out of here.
I know I do. And thank God I do.
Do do do. It's I like Ike.
It this is the epitome of I have to look at the vehicle
and not think about the ways that I've been creeped out
by the poster of every single Peter Pan.
That comes every year and a half or the a reimagining.
Yeah, not a reboot. Yeah, you're right.
Well, because they're all the same.
Yeah. Mythology.
My feelings about Hook cannot be placed into the hook
has nothing to do with this ship.
You know what? How I feel is almost like a begrudging.
Yeah, I guess I have to.
There is there like Peter Pan Pirate Ship iconic.
We threw out ET so we don't have it right.
We don't have any rides that fly where that is.
Yeah, that's up above you. Right.
You got to take that into account.
And honestly, for my taste, there's already too much new stuff,
newer stuff in here.
I think I'm putting my foot too many new rides.
What do you like? You mean Hagrid and Slinky?
Yeah, I think there's two bullshit.
Two rides from the two thousands to rides.
I now look, none of us have been on Tron, so we don't know.
Maybe we don't.
Maybe I have to stare at it.
It is certainly we know it's good.
There's that's got to be good.
I think we didn't put on the cosmic rewind vehicles.
Are those cool? They're OK.
Kind of like Nova Corps.
I think they're probably cool.
And again, I think like like seven dwarves,
I think they're very smooth and they're they they are cool.
So there's probably an argument to be made for them somewhere.
But visually, it's OK.
You know, guys, Selka was down there is down there, like as we record.
And he posted a thing about like my glasses.
Like really, we're about to fly off on this thing.
And that's what I I told him, like touring glans should track this.
I am interested in like which ride makes your glasses.
What I make your glasses fly off, because I definitely enjoy
like attractions with show scenes more when I can see them.
But I would like to keep my glasses also.
Oh, yeah, because we I yeah, because that's like Hulk.
You couldn't wear your glasses on.
Oh, no, absolutely not.
Yeah. And that queue was very dark like Hagrid.
I'm going to have to stumble through that or Velocico.
I'm going to have to stumble through that.
You do the strap.
Could you do the glasses strap like you're playing basketball?
We're goggles. Yeah.
Giles Grant or just yeah.
Oh, finally, Grant Glock goggles for Jason during a theme.
Oh, man. That would rule.
Zootin up and then he limbers up.
We need to get you course grant style goggles for theme parks.
Finally, just stop being a baby and try contacts at 37.
Oh, is that why you would never try it?
Well, I have terrible astigmatism in one eye.
So they tried to fit them for me once.
And I was like, Doctor, get that out. Get it out.
It's painful. Oh, really? Yeah.
Interesting. So I do LASIK.
I wouldn't do LASIK. Scared. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Of the laser. They shoot a laser laser is scared of like
there's been follies.
People have they've messed up laser, you know.
Yeah. If you want to keep discussing astigmatism, that's fine.
I'm looking at the vehicles.
They light up, guys.
Don't forget their light cycles.
I know we already got Hagrid's on here, but they light up.
It looks so cool at night.
It looks so cool indoors.
I am still a sucker for that.
It's it's like a motorcycle and you ride it like a motorcycle
that you're not sitting.
It doesn't have the comfort, but you're you're at attention.
You're it's and I guess I have to take my feelings about the movie out,
which are not good, which I think both of the movies are boring.
So it doesn't matter.
I since I think it's so much more likely that one of or both of you will go
with Peter Pan, I'm going with light cycle.
I got it. I got to say lights.
It lights up.
Jason, I'd like you to go next.
We have the light up.
I mean, I'm a sucker for neon.
I'm a sucker for colored lights.
I feel like a lot of parks could like really level up
just by putting in some good landscaping and colored lighting.
And it would seem like a six flags could immediately seem
like a much more premium experience with like a little landscape architecture
and some more colored lights.
That said, the other competitor is a cute little pirate ship.
And even though it slammed my ass multiple times
on that aging track, it's a rough ride.
Oh, this is a rough ride.
Let's keep that in mind.
Flying. Yeah.
I feel like flying should have some representation.
I like that you got leg room on that ride.
I like a little bucket.
You're not boxed in like being in a woodcarver's cart.
And I like that molded plastic sail.
I could say plenty of nice things.
Yeah, the sail.
So I'm going to I'm going to make Mike break the tie.
I'm going to say Peter Pan pirate ship.
That's right. Wow.
Peter Pan pirate ship.
Oh, again, I said this when I was a kid.
That was it was that or the Snow White, where I was like,
these are the coolest vehicles to be in.
You're flying.
Man, because that was like the first that was the first ride.
I felt comfortable opening my eyes on, as I've said,
because the characters were too far away.
Snow White, I love the ride vehicle,
but I closed my eyes the whole time on the ride.
You wanted Horace Grant goggles, but painted black, painted black.
Yes. So I couldn't see anything.
But when you compare Tron Light Cycle to the DeLorean,
it looks perfect.
I think kind of it's a better movie represented like Hagrid's.
Yes, it's recent, but look what we're able to do with right.
Your technology, right.
And again, it gives you the it gives you that motorcycle.
I assume what riding motorcycles like.
Yeah, you're tipped over like riding a motorcycle.
Someone might say if they get on a motorcycle. Right.
And I'll never be on a motorcycle.
I have not been.
But it's really this is hard because this is an emotional.
There's an emotional argument in my heart for pirate Peter Pamp hardship.
And I'm trying to I'm trying to remove the ride from my heart.
When I'm if it was.
Yeah, I imagine the photo op outside the that's a good way.
We haven't talked about that for any of these, like not just like the testing,
the seat functional. Can you fit in it? Yeah.
But the just photo op outside the ride, which which is
which do you like that photo of more?
Yeah, yes!
It's like I like it's a cute Peter Pan is cute, but I feel like the ships could be a little cuter
Honestly as I'm looking now they could be cuter the ships could be cuter
I'm sorry to add a new new another new thing when I when we say new ten years old
Onto this but a lot of classics. I'm amazed at what we're not seeing in here that there's no people mover
There's no pirate ship and and but it's it's still a diverse list. It's not entirely
The big new shiny object. There's classics. It's a really good. I think it's good
I think this is this might have been what we were dealing with no matter randomizer or not. That's what I'm saying
Yeah, all right. Let's take another quick break. See if the gardeners are see if the see if my neighbors stopped and
What we'll pick it up somewhere with the eight
all right, we are back for the watch your step while exiting eight and
Begins with Dumbo the flying elephant versus Hagrid's motorbikes and side cars Jason
I think make could make the first choice if you wish
Jason what do you think? I mean just both two loaded
Properties you got the crows on the one end you got the one of the worst
Billionaires we don't have to do this brain
What's talking about the cars the ride vehicle from the rival art from the artists again, I think you know
It comes down to like a
simulation of a real-life thing
versus like a whimsical dream a
flying elephant versus once again a dirty British motor that flies
Huh? Again, we shouldn't be talking about actually what it does in a conceptual way, but it does fly
The motorbikes flies the brides on a track
Well, there's a moved along a track. It was not really boring to battle on this ride. There's a big mechanical arm
Yeah, but could you imagine I mean I can imagine motorcycle riding a track
I don't know if I can imagine an elephant flying that's that seems impossible. Well, you can't imagine it
I mean the greatest imaginer who also man imagine some terrible things, but they also imagined
Who wrote Dumbo?
Great from the mind of some art author who Disney stole from
Well, I don't I feel like you know this I feel like yeah, you don't like Hagrid there's been a lot of yeah
Vehicles again. One of these is a dirty motorcycle and sidecar and one of these is a cute different color outfit elephant
You stand back and look at these from a distance, right?
But sitting inside them and then moving is also a sure a different story, too
And yeah that motorcycles a little uncomfortable to sit inside
Hmm in the sidecar or on them on the sidecar is more comfortable. That's cozier the sidecar the sidecar is cozy
So I think that's even something we haven't talked about is there actually is a cozy option on Hagrid's
There's the sort of more action pose that you can do if you're actually like on the handlebars
But then you are a little cozy in that sidecar. You're a little cozy
So I think we haven't talked enough about the sidecar aspect of Hagrid's which is a big strike in its favor
It's a bit it is
innovative
And also I was more right than I knew just side track the rights for Dumbo were bought by Disney from the two
Authors behind the book for about a thousand dollars
So pretty best
Do we support the current monster or the monster from the past who bought from a nice woman and ripped her up?
None of these things it's about vehicles. It's irrelevant. You know, it's irrelevant. Um, I
Hmm
You have any any leanings Mike well
Dumbo is a little uncomfortable for me as well sitting inside of it and especially when the ride vehicle
I mean if it's just a vehicle itself, but if it's moving in the way that it moves
I kind of slide around it and I kind of feel like I'm gonna tip over and fall out of it
I don't know if that's due to my height or what or my just sort of fear of heights. I'm not sure
Hagrid's I feel great on it the whole time. I
Feel better than in real life my normal day. You feel better than just being in your bed. Yeah. Yes. Yes
Compared all the vehicles to our beds
Well, that's it we should do it hold another episode about that
But yeah, so I don't know the
visually
That Dumbo is hard to beat I
Can I
You know
I'm at a loss for words. It's one it's you would want to own it over the motorbike. Mm-hmm. So
Yeah, somebody might see the bike and think you have an old dirty British bike, right?
But that's you buy that did you buy that for a thousand dollars the cost of one Dumbo story? Yeah
I just need to purchase but that being said if it was a Harry Potter
Look, I ain't buying a giant Harry Potter prop
No for many reasons at this point, but the bike divorced from it being Harry Potter is kind of cool
Yeah, if you sort of just had that parked like you're you had a big dog garage and you had the Harry Potter bike in
There but it was just a nondescript dirty British bike. It is kind of cool
I think it's a cool old-school looking motorcycle. I
Do agree that I think so much of it though. Yes, the
Motorcycle and sidecar aspect is really great
But what are those worth if it's not moving if you are just judging the vehicle pre movement versus a silly Dumbo
What if you what if Jay Leno were driving the motorcycle and you were in the sidecar?
What if he's driving the Dumbo like I mean
Okay, you and Jay in the Dumbo car
Would you rather have that or would you rather be on the bird of dirty British motorcycle with Jay driving and you're in the sidecar?
This is maybe the toughest question answer in my mind. No, it's not seeing Jay Leno in a Dumbo would be the funniest thing ever
Coming down the street
Separate from the ride if you're a big rev and you turned your head and it was Jay Leno in a Dumbo
1000% Dumbo locked in
Dumbo to all right. Okay. What do you what do you think? I don't even want to vote now
Say so if you're recording this officially Mike did not vote protest vote. We're back to some some tough ones
Yeah, cuz it'd be you got the fun dirty train. You got slinky dog
Slinky dog battle and that's the last one right and
Big Thunder yellow key favorite ride for me again a divorce myself from that though
the ride vehicle and the fun of
Big Thunder, I think you know, it's an old ride
It still holds up in the way that like you slide around it when you're moving and that's fun when you're sort of on a straightaway
It's fun when you're going up a hill like that all of that is still taken away from fake rocks
The majesty of the fake rocks on Big Thunder. You're still enjoying the hell out of it visually. It looks cool, too
Slinky is a different type of coaster, but it's similar
I mean, it's they're both sort of like good starter coasters
I think for for you know, you're young preteens, you know, just getting into coast maybe you're maybe you're eight or nine
Maybe yeah, you know, they're both sort of in the same zone there
So they're both
independently kind of giving you a similar type of rides
so
the thing you're gonna have to I think judge on is
Do you value realism over?
whimsical magic
Mm-hmm. I think yeah, I think what are your values. What do you believe in? Okay. I want to ask the listener that
What do you believe in in your heart?
Does it does your heart say?
I want to live sort of in a fantasy land with talking animals or
Do I sort of want to be in a heightened reality that doesn't maybe have talking animals?
But you can experience buying animals venture. Well, yeah dynamite holding animals, right?
But that's more realistic animals can hold dynamite in real life
But yeah, they choose not to but they could but they could but yeah slinky toy slinky dog toy couldn't
Actually put you in its back and you rider on a fun ride with a whole environment
I mean you are on slinky and you are in like a backyard
Filled with toys. Yes meant to look as if Andy built a theme park
Yes backyard
But I would argue in the same my same teacup argument is that?
Taking the fake rocks away from Big Thunder
It's a fun roller coaster movement thing you can take away the environment you could put slinky dog on the moon
On Neptune in a swamp at the center of the earth and you are still in a big dog
You still have the knowledge you can see him you can see slinky in front of you
You can still see that you are part of some sort of whimsical magic
Well, don't we need to bring the head of big dog productions into the big dog Jay Leno
Test again if Jay Leno is
Pulling up to Bob's big boy and he's in a slinky dog or he's in yeah, that's unfair
I mean that's gonna be here. It's always gonna be cartoon of two of her talking about. Yeah the jail and oh yeah
Yeah, of course
Fine let me just
Discuss, of course, you're in it. You're in a train but colors. I don't think we've talked about I'm staring at one right now
a very pleasing
Red and green combo and I like that tan of the cars. I think that a big thunder choice
Represents anything that's train style. This is common in coasters, but never pulled off this well
Yeah, and I think you have to pick the best of a genre
The slinky dogs in a genre of its own. Yes, I would say there's not a lot of big cartoony
roller coasters out there but in terms of
Well, I don't know if it's better than
No, well, maybe it is better than Dumbo, but it's just not as classic. Oh
Yeah, it's picking not classic throughout
Right and what is classic? It's just a nostalgia. It's just you're you've known about it longer
Yeah, true. I'm just having a time to just decide something is classic you have to judge something
You know as if they both came out today
Yeah, yeah, that's true if these rides were both new
Slinky dog I'll say this in the favor slinky dogs slinky dog is smiling
He looks happy. It's how we all want to remember the beloved Jim Varney
I thought you were gonna say like taking a trip. I thought that's what you were gonna say too
Jim Varney, I mean also that both can be true honoring
Yes, a vote for this is honoring the great actor Jim Varney not dissimilar color schemes
Sure, yeah kind of earth tones pops of green. I mean, you know, yeah, I
Think Big Thunder for me wins out if slinky dog is a little less good is a little more caterpillar
You know, yeah
If it's not such the whole his butt slinky you would get you get the butt of slinky the seat
The seat of slinky is on this ride the little tail
I'm so sorry to say FN but the FN tail a part of occurs
Yeah, that I mean look it's a big slinky you get to ride on it and it's fun as shit. I
I think suddenly I'm like slinky. I was literally about to say Big Thunder
But I'm looking at his face and what Jason said he's smiling
I can't say no to him great actor Jim Varney and his floppy ears
Slinky dog. Yes, I can't Wow. I was on the precipice of take the ride out of it a clean sweep
I'm gonna give it to slinky dog, too
I think every year we we have a round or two where
There is a persuasive argument and I think Mike made a very persuasive
Thank you. Yeah, you have changed my mind on it on a few
Mike you want to give me the next one?
Mr. Toad motorcar versus mad tea party teacup. Damn it. Oh damn it. Oh, oh
interesting
Interesting. I'm not I don't know that I have even an initial thought here. God. I'm not sure I do either
But I better think of one. Yeah
I was thinking about the toy aspect and I have never been tempted to get a toy of
The mr. Toad motorcar. I almost was more in talking about it
In winning the last round
Hmm. I have a toy of the mr. I have a Funko pop
Do you have one with a character writing it? Yeah put toads in it toads in it
Okay, and I will say this I'm very upset with mr. Brian Marriott II for buying they bought Mondo and they gutted it terrible
Oh for shame, mr. Marriott II sucks. I gotta say I I've got a couple now of the
Disneyworld 50th like Funko where like Mickey is in front of Space Mountain
And you gave us Mickey popping out of the skyliner
Yeah, and it is it is a little shocking because they do have a Florida people mover car kind of a rare
vehicle to turn into a toy and it kind of looks like shit because
They stuck the logo on it and Pluto looks cute in it, but it it's just a little off. Yes, I agree
I have the people mover Funko's as well
But like that's that's where you're getting your most ride vehicle toys these days is from Funko pops
Yeah, and some of them look pretty good and then some of them you're like this. That's okay, but
Yeah, I look as far as toys. I I like the real is I like them to look is close to
What the thing is and that goes for figures and that goes that's why I'm a big neck of guys because they do
Really great recreations of whatever they're yeah generally
Honestly, I've gotten the Funko pop I could care less about the little Funko characters
I'm just like wow how often you get a a little Space Mountain in the little sign
Yeah, and the sign have a few of those I have the space mountain one where it's just the little Space Mountain building
But then I also have Mickey in the ride vehicle, but yeah, I don't care take Mickey out of it
It's all for all I care. Yeah, you should rip him out. I could really have it
Yeah, I'm looking at these two next to each other. It might help you guys too. I recommend it. I'm looking I'm looking
I don't know if it's completely helping me, but you know what it's something big is hitting me
Tea party cup
You are controlling the spin you have a big wheel in the center. That is the same weighty
What not plastic? I don't know whatever material that the metal it's made out of
And you're physically doing it
Mr. Toad you are not physically doing it
But you could take that wheel and just spin it and spin it as fast as you can
I don't care that I'm not in control and that's the whole thing is right out of control
I just compared mr. Toad. I really thought how
More lo-fi mr. Toad style ride would be a better fit for Mario Kart than what they did
You better believe no Mario Kart vehicle in this top 32 not even discussed not even for a second
Which what a failure on the part of that right to not hit the 32. Yeah, good point
I also like the kind of cushioning of that like the we got upholstery. We have like fine
European fonts upholstery styling
brass fixtures
It's not as fun and cartoony. I
Mean icon is completely what I'm thinking with tea party, but what do I like more?
I'm starting to head to tow well the thing with toad too is that toad has the thing that I love and we I think
We've all talked about it where it's there's different names of different characters on the front and that goes a long way, too
It's not it's not sitting inside a character. You're not sitting inside badger or something
But just having the names on the cars is funny shit. It's really I don't know why that is
Yeah, cuz I don't even like those characters, but really I don't really I'm not like hey badger go back and watch
I mean, I'm watching yeah, they are still good not that I dislike no I have not watched this
We watched a couple years ago. We're like this is funny
Scott you make a per you made a persuasive argument though that I can't like get out of my mind now of the
presence of control
Toad is
What's left like toad is the only one that you control what no you know not toad
Sorry
Yeah, I'm so excited. I'm so focused on the control
It just revealed a Jason thought for maybe 37 years that he's been controlling the car. I'm mr. Toad
Oh, yeah, I go beep beep and they get out of the way
I say beep beep and the other car and the did you stores open every time that you're a judge
He steps the fuck off every time chasing itself. He goes. I am a good driver. I am a good driver
I yell spin those beers man spin those beers
Jason conducts everything like an orchestra
So yes, but you're saying that's a teacup argument a teacup argument, you know, cuz control look
We're all searching for control in our own lives
And it's really hard because so much is out of our control in our own lives and for that brief moment on the teacups
We are in control. We are gonna choose our destiny for however long it is two minutes or whatever
it's it's you know, it's a conundrum because searching for control is folly and
Accepting that you are out of control of much in your life. That's that's
Harder to do but it's very hard to do but it's something we all need to realize
Yeah, so much of our anxiety comes from trying to maintain control
But if you accept reality as it is you're probably gonna have an easier go of it. Yes
That's an argument for mr. Toad is what you just made but that became a good way
seeking control
Is
Well, well, not exactly because so in the teacup you can you do have control so you can spin or as much as
As little as you want. It's a brief moment when you do actually have control. That's your relation
Jason turned it into mr. Toad, which is a wild ride that you should just give yourself over to life
Well, I don't know if you've seen the end of parenthood, but you start to realize that life and especially parenthood
Just a wild rollercoaster
Are you talking about?
I'm assuming that's both the conclusion of the two-hour movie and the multi season
I couldn't I couldn't tell you that one. Okay. No, I just every episode of parenthood
Somebody else want to do it. I don't think I know I
It's really tricky here because
Here's what I think ultimately
Mr. Toad again the movement of it separated from the ride
The vehicles cute is cute I think and also interesting and fun
The ride vehicle itself is like it kind of jerks you around and I don't know if that's so much fun without spinning beers
I don't know if you take away the flats and the opening doors and the beep beeps. I
Don't know that that's so much fun. And again, the teacup is fun
wherever you are
Neptune the moon
center of the earth swamp swamp
This is a good this is a good thing to go back to I think it's been a reliable like very real pushing
Pushing over the edge very reliable pushing the teacup till like the extra spin. I
Decided by the way, I will say I like the brutal curved like fibreglass plastic of the teeth
Like I don't want to be in it for more than three to five minutes
But kind of like it I'm gonna go with
Teacup I'm going teacup too. All right, then I will just counterbalance that with mr
Toad, but it's impossible to be upset about that. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I mean it's the cleaner pick. I wish there was a final four that had mr
Toad in it
So I will kick the next one to Jason and that is Casey jr. Versus Tron light cycle
Oh boy, you know, you know, we don't you can just say your pick now. Oh sure. Yeah
I mean if we all want to go home soon
Yeah, I
Boy this is tough
Casey jr. Is very cute and there's lots of different options and it's very fun to see from a distance
Tron light cycle does glow
Okay, I thought we're gonna go the other this was a lock for Casey. Yeah, I mean I think it is
I think it is I I think I'm gonna throw it to Casey, but I'm not gonna be mad
Yeah, I think what we're learning at least I'm learning about myself today is that I value high quality whimsy
Over high quality reality sure, huh? And obviously the Tron light cycles very realistic
Mm-hmm
Whimsical it's a sci-fi kind of whimsy. It's like the real game grid
But I think Tron lights like oh might win and against some other things. But yes the full Casey jr. Train
You see it all
It's hard to pass that up
But it's uncomfortable
If I'm in the cage, but I don't have to write a cake think about a child
I don't have to run and think about when you were a child. All right. Yeah, I do all the time
Constantly thinking about that whole point of everything I think yes, it's a problem
Okay here let me ask this question
Do are we taking out when Casey jr. Talks and sings on the ride that we have to take that out of like when he's like
It sounds like he's has asthma and he's we're going up a hill and he's like
Is that not involved here?
No, we said that we we said the beep beep beeps were part of back to the future. They were not mr. Toad
Those are beep beep beeps in the room, this is a ride that is kind of alive and it overcomes adversity
It gets up that hill. That's true. Yes
But it's like a little train that could a different totally
Jason I know the story of Casey jr. Yeah the fable the legend
but is it what isn't it also a great story that once there was a big cool motorcycle that glowed and
It thought that it could go very fast
You know what did and it blew everybody's faces back and it glowed all the way
Here's what I'll say I'll say I'm actually gonna transport myself back in as it into a child's brain
But even a very unusual for me to do think back to being a kid
And think about let's say eight nine ten years old. I'm a kid
Which one do I want?
Outside of the ride in my backyard and I could ride around on it. The answer is Tron
Yeah, I even Casey jr. Is great. It looks cool. It's they would win against so many of these other ones. It's Tron
Wow, ooh
It's a kid honestly. I like Casey jr. More now as an adult and not as a kid because the kid I go
Neon lights motorcycle. Are you kidding me? It's Tron, but none of us have written Tron
Fiori theoretical I know what Tron's like. Okay, it lasts about a minute 15. It's awesome for the minute 15
You're gonna be like, it's kind of short. But oh wow is cool those lights in the it's like Pony Express
Which I find very fun and exciting where you're kind of like motorcycle
We were saying before we started recording I think they didn't in losing
Vehicles of a genre. Well, you know one can live on in the other of course
Yeah, and that's and I think Pony Express lives on and Tron light cycle
Yeah, I think Hagrid the motorcycle part lives on and Tron light. So yes
I really liked that last argument Mike. I think it's Tron light cycle for me. Yeah
Okay, Casey jr. The cute getting shit Casey jr. But everything else is you that's what's interesting about where we go now
Everything is cute. Yeah, all the ones that are left are cute in what I'm calling the permanent sir sentados por favor for okay good
So first one. Oh, this is interesting
Let's take let's I think this goes to Mike first and it is Dumbo the flying elephant versus slinky dog
Slinky dog versus Dumbo and we've said a lot at this point
Well some of the same arguments for both and now they go against each other, right? Right, right, right
So again, I'm trying we were trying to take nostalgia even out of it if they both came out today and I
Dumbo was not even one of my favorite movies as a kid. I liked I like Dumbo, but it was not like Peter
It was not like pan. I was a pan kid. I was a snow white kid
I
Wanted it to be Michael and the seven dwarves. I wanted snow white out of there
I wanted to hang out with the dwarves, but Dumbo I liked
But that was a weird sad movie. Yeah, and probably wouldn't have cracked my top five
I like to Pinocchio better than Dumbo so it makes it tough to go up against something from Toy Story
Toy Story is we grew up with and they made they stay so good, right?
My biggest criticism is like four is oh four is like less
Little less good of a masterpiece when the bar is master, but still like a fun movie
And still I had it on every day for a long time because of the boy and it was yeah, I was not mad at it
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, so slinky dog Wow. Yeah
I'm pretty sure about it interesting both of these
Creatures are smiling. They're both smiling. That was I think an endorsement
That pushed me for a slinky dog, but it kind of negates itself
Cuz I think both of them once you remove the part of nostalgia that again is like you see the stock report of
Disneyland of the kids in the Dumbo flying elephants once you take that away
You come out into your backyard and you see slinky or you see Dumbo both good by the way, not neither one bad
But you see slinky or Dumbo. I got more affection for slinky. But wait, do you need the whole are you saying the whole slinky?
Yes, because you would need like
In this scenario, I own that Michael Eisner house that he was selling which is like has ten houses on a property
So there's enough room for the whole slinky dog vehicle. I
It's
I think it's slinky. Okay. Oh
This is so much of what I want
This is what I want from an adult's point of view and a kid point of view this fulfills both things
hmm
Ben's it has it takes a character who was not a ride, right?
You know you have your back to the future and then you make the car and looks like the cup
It's linky wasn't a ride before but we know about him. He bends and stretches
He's drink very flexible again the right flexible to be human. He is the ride. The track is not the ride
He is the ride. The vehicle is the ride in this instance
I think like the surrounding stuff is great and it makes everything better in the
Seeing wheezy at the end saying is amazing. Amazing. But I think
this is this is
This is pure. This is what I
This is finally a juncture where I'm like, I feel like should I represent classic?
You know and like what how much of Disney is built on Dumbo? Do we need to?
We don't do we need to represent classic. Does it matter? Well, I think that's
Everyone's individual decision. It's like a gut decision personal decision between you and your God and your pastor
Yeah, your pastor. Yeah, do you want to represent classic in a tournament like this?
Jason Dino
Looking hmm
His paws are pointed up. He's got those fun paws
Again in his seat is on the ride
Imagine you're shrunk down to figure size
Yeah, and and you could go on slinky your good friend who you do like more than Dumbo
Yeah, we all like him more than Dumbo. No question. I want everyone to admit they like
Slinky more than Dumbo. Of course. I do Jason admit it. I yeah, I think that's right. All right good listener
I want you to pause this and admit it to yourself now in your car or wherever you are you're in a Starbucks
I want you to make an announcement right now to the Starbucks. You like Slinky better than Dumbo
Just yell to the room. Yes
Then run out whatever you're doing push kick the door open and run out
Wait, yeah, I know it's like class. Oh, like this isn't classic. I care about for some movie. It's boring
Not bad it's great. Yeah, but
Slinky versus Dumbo something that doesn't feel right to me, but Slinky ending up being the best
Forget the forget the past killing if you must I okay. That's what I say
I'm gonna save my classic vote. I'm gonna give it to Slinky
Okay, but there's no fucking way I'm letting Tron win this. All right, okay
Well, let's get into the pit then I might you know, then I'll just say Slinky
For anyone keeping the records. I more I think it tops the model of if you're in a cute character
This is this is this for the twenty-first. I'll be honest
I'm disappointed in both of these answers in the sense that both of them were like
I guess Slinky versus just an emphatic Slinky is the answer
So it's I think it's tough for me in a way because it's a ride that I've been on
I think only once it's in and it's in this one park and it's not like
replicated everywhere
This is I feel like it's like it's some kind of institutional guilt right that I'm supposed to pick Dumbo
But maybe you're right Mike. Maybe you can help me break through that burn the sacred Jedi texts is what I'm saying
Not paid doesn't matter not paid turns. They are not
So that's my feeling. Okay
Well, then let's let's hash this one out because this seems I think Jason is setting up a 12 angry men's scenario
We don't get to leave the room. I don't I
Tron is one of the oddest phenomena like you you were saying like you you found both those movies particularly boring
I don't think I've ever sat down and watched either all the way through I think it is irrelevant
Doesn't matter irrelevant
But it's a rather fucking the institutional stuff comes up the movements come up
Can't I can't get it out of my mind is that Tron is a thing that exists purely on
Aesthetics. Yes, like a hollow piece. It's like what what do you want a theater like but aesthetics kinder?
No, I think all right, I think that the just aesthetics is probably not a great thing for theme parks
Well, no, I would disagree with that
It is that okay
it's not completely irrelevant in the sense that I just
The argument of character that you like because it's it's basically just decide which character you like and who you want to be in
Right. So yes, your affection for the thing does come into play it comes into play
So the teacups are winning by a country mile in that respect
I mean, yeah, that Tron like cycle looks cool and it glows but I I don't have the personal affection
I I have not ridden it so I don't have the direct
Experience and it's also kind of like it's like one of those those kinder ball candies where they can't trust
Americans to have a toy inside. So it's just a hollow ball with the the toy next to it. It's just full of air
It's just full of hot air. There's nothing in the middle, but there is a toy in those they just separate it from the chocolate
So there is a toy. Yeah like over there. I'm saying Tron is kind of hollow like Tron. I don't know
I don't but the thing about the ride. I think everybody likes this ride, but the ride you got to take away from it
Yeah, well and if you guys you definitely have to take away the IP and also and what are we putting in Alice in Wonderland?
There are no big teacups in Alice in Wonderland. Then we're really off the tracks. That's true
There's no part where they get in a big teacup. They sip a teacup
I will they and they grow and shrink spin around in this
All day long if I could and I'd probably do it alone the earlier you said you only want to be in one for three
to five minutes
Yeah, but I don't want to be on a roller coaster all day
Within minutes, we're all full of contradictions. Like I love it. Is it not to be human or to be contradicting yourself constantly?
It's the most philosophical episode. Yes, which yes it has to be in a lot of ways because we're trying to yeah
To parse through this grappling with big control
I think that that the fact that you this is an instance where you can control as much or as little as you want
here and then let okay the last the last time Tron was in in this tournament I
Again aesthetically I really convinced myself of the greatness of it because it is more
Hitting me on an adult level and a child level because I've said this before I was I could not have cared less about the old
West or like old-time whimsy when I was little when I was little it was all about space
It was all about Tomorrowland. It was always always about colored lights and
That's what this has this is my teenage dream my child's dream and my my adult
Dream of a cool vehicle to ride on I wish I wish I had the balls to trip out my car
In the way you see those obnoxious cars sometimes was like lights coming
Underneath the car when they're driving at night and like they've customized their dashboard and there's different colored lights
Like I wish I could do that
I don't want to do that because I feel like I don't want to call attention to myself on the street and so I'll be
Like like pretty cool ride, huh? Now. Let me just get my three-year-old out of the back. Yeah. Yeah
It's a probably doesn't work
But I do admire it sometimes when I see it the people that have like custom lights by the door handle inside
Like you can do a lot of crazy stuff like that and that because that is a kid would have been my dream and to
Have a car that has neon bright cool lights. I just saw that the company is making a color change car
Unbelievable wait the lights underneath that the car itself. Oh, okay. Yeah
Yes
Just imagining Mike pulling up like at a stoplet like a drag racing scene and the other guy turns up
Like cool music and then Mike turns up like hey, it's a little Stevens garage. You're here with me a little Steven
Perfect aesthetic match to a toy. Yeah
This is so hard but the right yes the right
It's tough it's tough tough now the only thing I would dock
Tron is that once you take away the big rooms with the lights you are getting less lights
That is part of it. You are getting less light
There's lights on the vehicle, but a big part of that experience is going into that little that light room
And you feel like you're on the grid. I
Walk up to the line and get in line for the teacups drawn like okay, I did the virtual
Pain in the ass
We set the rules here's this is all right, let me just I've been annoyed by everything Jason said in this round very well, however, I
I I think I am gonna land at teacups
Maybe if I landed teacups now, we won't have to hear any more arguments that are irrelevant. Well, we'll see I
Think like it's something that influenced me
I'm looking at Google images of Tron light cycle and I found what I think is
Lentesta of touring plans in the Disney dish. I think this is him testing the one outside and he looks kind of uncomfortable
And I don't know maybe that's just him. I shouldn't let that impact but like as opposed to nobody's unhappy in a teacup
You know look kids all ages get represented and that is indeed lentesta and he didn't like it then it's teacups
He might have liked the ride. He just like this this specific photo. Yeah, you're going teacups, too
Well because of when because of in solidarity with when everything I just said you're concerned about him contorting his spine
Yeah. Well, yeah everything I said, I don't believe in anymore because of what you just said about
Wow, well that took a turn
Okay, and that brings us to
What the hell did I call it the the full and complete stop top two and
that
So we now are at I'm happy with the top two slinky dog versus teacups
Whoo, this could have this could have easily been Dumbo verse teacups
Which ultimately when I think that Dumbo and teacups are the two most iconic ride vehicles
Makes sense. I like that. It's both things that are silly to be in
You know, let's let's step outside of theme park super fans and let's go to your grandfather or a
teacher or a
visiting
Dignitary that like Walt would have used to I I don't even know who he was Republican senator
Yeah, yeah, think about an evil man who harmed this country irreparably and right about Walt
Taking this person and like look how silly me in a big teacup me in a giant dog
Robert bird sitting in a teacup 90 years old. That's right. Yeah
So I think we're in the right
You know, but tech is represented the slinky dog is current and we I like that we have a
2010s
versus
1955 yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's classic versus newer. Mm-hmm
Oh who wants to even start? Well, I'll say that's in favor of teacups much more
Whimsical color palette
Yeah, I mean there's a very each car though is different yeah, but there's quite a few of them
Yeah, so there's different styles range in this instance. So I think we would only be going with one ride vehicle or no
I guess it's Casey jr. We were looking at the whole train. So I guess not I guess it is the full
full slate of
Cups, it's all the cups. I think that it comes in all these varieties
I guess you have to consider all the cups. Yeah, not just and maybe we would have to I'll go back and edit something
Where we I had and say all the cups when we were start talking in the other rounds
I started thinking just now
Well, what did they look like to begin with because that's something we didn't really rule on right which era and I thought
well surely the mad tea party teacups of
Yesteryear of less yester land as I'm looking at right now
Were
Janky or hard steel cut kids in the back while the spinning happened
Uh-huh, but in fact what I'm looking at is kind of what it looks like today. It's the same sort of
Fun jagged patterns very similar color palette. I'm actually surprised
I think I think probably Dumbo has changed more right then the teacups. So you really are
honoring
1955 and something they got right pretty early
Yeah, yeah, I think if if you would call anything in media like untouchable, I think it's Mary Blair's
Use of color. Did she do the teacups? Well, I know she did I think she did Alice
I think she established Oh so much of the look of Alice
I think is credited to her and then other small world and that uh, maybe she drew the things on the outside
I don't know. It's a good question
But I think it's hard to improve which is interesting to think about because when people talk about her it's like
Oh, she would just kind of combine
She went off her instincts and her got a lot. She would combine like, you know different
pairings and oh, yeah
So there is a I'll give it this there's this simplicity of course to the cups versus slinky
Which is a big sort of unruly thing. It's a big coaster
But you know, there's something to be said for simplicity I guess of design
Yeah, you know what? I'm seeing Jason's right
I think according to one website at least that she did design them that like so these these designs on the back
So you're getting a Mary Blair vote. I didn't know. Yeah, since we haven't done this as an episode. That's kind of interesting
So she picked the colors she well, this is an interesting fact and that that pattern does feel like
Her aesthetic so you're getting some like
You know like you're representing Disneyland 50s and 60s. Yeah in this
Hmm I mean look we're not taking do with consideration
But if you want to go back and watch a classic Disney purely for aesthetics
Alice is I think the most pleasing to the eye the movie the movie
The movie is relevant in that it's it's you do maybe want to live in the world of a movie if there is a movie
In the attraction at least at least vibe wise. I mean slinky dog. It's a move. It's your friend
It's your friend slinky dog. It is yeah, it's him and his seat
Cups have handles there
I like that you step up onto a plate
Your first step is you have to step onto that little plate and then climb inside of a cup right and that there's always there's a
Little like do-si-do you got to do to fit in there, right? Right, right. I like closing that little door
I like that the door protects you but it's very slight. It's not some big scary locking mechanism
I you make a great point both closing the door and the do-si-do to like scooch
Scooch on in that's fun. Mm-hmm, but the slinky dog I find
Satisfying as well. I find sitting on that seat fun
It's not you know, it's not kind of like the people mover, but it does feel good
That's open air and you know, you're not too locked in
It's not a crazy high we haven't really even talked about harnesses at all. Mm-hmm
We talked to early on about it and we never really brought it up again, but there's not a crazy intrusive
Harness, which is rare on a coaster, right? So you really feel like
You're getting the wind in your hair on
Slinky dog and it's not ever in a restrictive way like on
In credit coaster or something, but so are you on teacups? I would say that's true
You're getting wind in your hair and maybe aren't even going you're gonna be going way up a hill
And a kid can get that wind if you're always gonna be spinning to some degree on in the teacups
Yes, yeah and on this some to some degree. Yeah. Yeah, and are we spinning on the earth?
In the same way we're already
We don't need to spin more
Now spinning let me ask as far as the sensation of spinning
I feel like people generally have more of a of a not objection but generally version aversion
Yeah spinning versus going sort of straight ahead or bouncing up and down a little bit on a roller coaster track
so should we dock the teacups in a way because I
Would say there's a probably a decent percentage of human beings on earth that don't want to spin like that because it makes them ill
I don't think so because of what Jason said earlier, which is control and I think you know
You've got your your big turntables and if you only want to spin to the degree that the turntable is right
That's one thing
But if you want to get a group together and spin the thing as fast as you can you can do that as well
That is pretty this is innovative for
1955 yeah, this is some early Bob Gerr and again, I don't know his specific participation
If I look it up in Bob Gerr was but it is stuck
I think I mean arrow developments is involved a major company again irrelevant
But if I see the name Bob Gerr, what choice do we have we're gonna say I'd rather
Tell slinky dog to go away than Bob Gerr
Well, I don't want to tell Bob Gerr to go away so now you put this on the table
It would be upsetting to me to do that
It's tough
I I know Mike what you're saying with the aversion because I think Jane avoids the teacups a lot of people
Cups to the same way that like stomach, but we did ride slinky dog last time we were in Florida
So now I love to spin. Yeah, I was spinning in a chair and a little chair with my daughter yesterday
I loved it and I'm a man in his late 30s
So are you proposing that we put your chair in it instead?
I would like to sub out the teacups for the office chair that I spun in yesterday
Let's put your daughter in both let's let her make the call I think she'd like teacups better sure
I think that she would like teacups better at this stage
Hmm
Here's I think that
With one of these choices that you represent a lot of history you represent tradition at the park
You know the you know, what's alive in the teacups is?
All carnival teacup ride the idea of the ride mechanism in general as it exists
Outside of Disneyland even like the most basic primal a ride that spins round and round
You also represent something that isn't slinky dog where you're suddenly small and you're in a big thing
You get that in this you get bright colors you get to choose one you get control
I think just like all of these facets that you would want out of any ride vehicle worth its
Weight in salt worth its salts. What's the phrase?
Whatever you feel about salt weight in gold gold nuts worth its weight in salt
That's another so great that if the added assaults in the amount of it you could sell that salt for a lot of money all
Everything you said is good, and it's it's correct, and it's a good persuasive argument
but
If you go outside and you see slinky
You got a friend there
That's a friend
Mmm, my relationship has been longer with the teacups
But three toys, but can you be friends with a cup?
I don't think that it's a requirement to be friends with any of these vehicles not a requirement
But what do you value do you do you value history or do you value friendship more?
That's my question do you value friendship with a fictional character
Right who you have not met and who you do not interact with when you're on the ride vehicle
Scott mentioned another good point not just the scooching and the door closing
But yeah that moment of ooh, I want the purple one or ooh
I want the green one and then racing to get it. Yeah, you don't get snaked
That's fun other rides pull up and they choose for you. It's just whatever. It's just luck of the draw
It's fun to be able to go pick my mind is made up it's teacups
And
Tossing it to the wind. I'm gonna give it to teacups
Wow. Well, that's it. But Mike, wait a minute. Take one shot at the buzzer. I
This is tough because I would I would rather Dumbo win the teacups win
What happened but you like slinky better than Dumbo
Ah
We could really say screw it. Okay, we could all buy it right now to give it to Dumbo instead of the teacups
No one want to do that. So an element of control you can go up and down true. There is an element of control
Uh, that would really that would really screw the rules. I'm not changing mine. No, no me neither. Well
I'm gonna vote for
You're holding up the victory party the teacups are waiting to get full with a gatorade and champagne and you're holding them up
Let them go enjoy
You just brought up a different thing that maybe that'll sway me you can fill up
The teacup with champagne and and ride
I mean, I guess you could do that with slinky too, but in theory if you are at uh, I think one of uh, uh,
Didn't like uh, nick cannon and mariah carrey one of his marriages didn't he get married at disneyland?
Yeah, yeah, or they renewed their vows or something. Okay. Well, yeah something like that, you know
Maybe at that level those two could have and should have filled up a teacup with champagne
And then swam around in it and gulped it up. Okay. Now this is yes
They should have done that
Having a teacup
You can do jason you could fill that teacup up with broth
And you could have a little like broth bath every night
Um, okay. This is an interesting new wrinkle. I yeah me and broth
Um
It's gonna make him switch his vote. He doesn't want to burn alive and brah. Yeah, I don't know
I know it's kind of uh the last few years. It's been very uh,
Bone broth has been a big like superfood kind of thing. All right on that
Tea cups are the winner of I hate to interrupt the bone broth story, but teacups are the winner
Five
It's better as a ride giant teacup filled with champagne also sounds like it'd be on the rider for the deuces our wild residency
Well, that's true. You know, all right, it could have been now we have gotten aerosmith representation in there somehow
Um our congratulations to the teacups on a well-earned victory. Hey, you've stuck in there for
Many years however long disneyland's been open. I don't care to do that math
uh, but since 1955 a classic and
You did it the original spin doctors as I like to say
teacups
and uh
Uh, yeah. Hey, um a very interesting discussion. I think we got to the right player
Are we are we all ultimately happy? Are you gonna be uh, this honestly this of all the ones we've done so far
This one feels the most wrong as far as the winner to me
I don't know why I feel like I feel like it was not bad
But I feel like we did something wrong here today. I'm I'm I am curious what the listeners think
I think this is when by making it a little bit more real of the discussion
Something you actually could talk about
Um, if if you had a group of people with this insular of interests as us
If you you should talk this out, uh with anybody you you care to you pick your favorite you fill out the bracket which will post
Um, if anything didn't make it to the 32 and it should have give us a good, uh, justice for give us a hashtag justice for
whatever, uh for the one that I liked your pitch jason of uh,
I'll say justice for nights and white satin mobile
Good idea. Ultimately, I was like was it a good ride vehicle and I looked at it and I could not say that it was
It's just kind of a default
It was just kind of a default. I just threw some I I had some in there where I was like
Like the omnibus, isn't that just a car?
Isn't that you had to take out some yeah, ultimately, uh, uh, yeah, I think ride vehicles have to be moved by some mechanism
What's more fun than the teacups maybe most of the rides we said, however
It feels right ish to me. Does it not feel right ish to you? Let us know
Uh right on all the socials, uh, which are all at podcast the ride merch is available
In our t public store if you want to get some of that and deface it in protest of our incorrect rulings
Uh, and for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode
on the vip tier club three all of that at patreon.com
Podcast the ride and maybe someday we do an episode about the teacups
Wow, wow
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gerdner
Brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on facebook