Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate hosted by three guys who consider themselves
the Kevin Stewart and Bob of podcasting.
You can distribute those however you like.
I don't know.
I'm Bob.
Sure.
Bob's the cute one.
Bob is the teddy bear.
Jason's Bob.
Jason jumped at being the cute one.
Yeah, it's a cute one.
It's me.
It would be me.
That would be me.
A cute one, me.
One of them is specifically tall.
I believe Kevin is tall.
Mm-hmm.
And Bob is cute.
And what's the other?
What's the attribute of the other one?
The strongest one for Stewart?
The strongest attribute that is?
Big cock?
Pigeon.
Yes, judging by some fan art, some art online.
A healthy urethra?
Yeah.
The healthiest urethra of all the minions?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
That's what you can imagine to yourself.
There's kind of like the water zone in this area we're talking about today.
And I think one way to make it fun is to imagine that it's a bunch of minion pee.
Yeah, it is.
That you're seeing urethral gush.
Yeah, urethral gush.
Three things I regret in the first minute.
Yeah, no, it's really off to the races.
That was, of course, a callback to the main feed episode,
recent urethral discussion on a main feed episode.
Check it out.
Which was different than the one where we talked about what part of Optimus Prime
is his prostate, right?
Oh, right, right, right.
Which a tailpipe versus, yeah, where did the tailpipe go when he transformed?
We are.
Look, this is just like some conversation
some quick stop employees would be having on the day they weren't supposed to be there.
You know, that's just what happens to us sometimes.
No, no, no, hear me out.
Hear me out.
Yeah.
The tailpipe is Optimus Prime's prostate.
Right.
This is what this is.
Sub in Jason Lee and Stanley and put in the game, me and Peter Cullen,
voice of Optimus Prime, where I'm asking them about Optimus's tailpipe.
And then and then put in us, but like looking wretched decades later,
looking just like unreal horrible.
And then and then even for more of those for another two decades.
Imagine it somehow not not having received any of the benefits of digital face clean up.
Imagine that.
Oh, my goodness.
This is it's strange that we got off to this point,
because what I wanted to do here in talking about super silly fun land,
which is the Minion, the Despicable Me, like kids area at Universal Studios, Hollywood.
I wanted to get into this because of recent really fun experiences with my son,
because now I am deep into going to theme parks with him.
Yes.
And I especially we're pretty late on this now.
But, you know, Christmas break, I got to slow down a little bit
and go back to all the parks that I hadn't been to for a little while
and do it with him in an age where he's really appreciating it, heading towards three.
And that's why I wanted to talk about it.
But here, you know, how do you mouths and potty minds?
You were the one who said the lewd thing and got off to the races.
So I'm just saying you wanted it to be wholesome, but you started me off.
I'm the one who talked about Stewart.
You opened the dirty forbidden door.
Yeah. And I stepped through it willingly.
Yes. But I'm just saying I would have been happy to keep this thing wholesome.
Stewart's attribute.
And I guess this is where I reveal because you you said right before we recorded,
we're not really familiar with this franchise.
I actually really like all of these.
Oh, I made an assumption.
Why did I assume that? I don't know.
The OK, that's good.
Well, I was watching earlier today.
I was watching Minions Rise of Gru.
I have not. I had to come here.
I've got 15 minutes left because I know the time.
And I also see this is the listeners maybe know what happens.
And Jason doesn't.
You're hearing you at a really precarious point of Gru related peril.
There's a big you know, they're all saving.
Kevin and Bob and Stewart.
Otto is showing up. Otto gets a lot of play in this.
I don't think I knew about the Minion Otto.
Mm hmm. Is he new to that movie?
Sorry. What's that?
Is Otto?
Was he been in the franchise the whole time?
He's me.
I it seems like he's got a lead.
Like it seems like he's been bumped up.
Oh, OK. So he was a breakout in one of the earlier ones.
I guess so.
And now he's like shining on his own in a way.
Not in his own movie, but I the only the other one.
I haven't seen Despicable Me three.
These are also looking up for this.
I was interested to learn that.
OK, if you want to get caught up,
Despicable Me one and two are on Peacock.
Despicable Me three is streaming nowhere.
Good. It makes sense.
Why would you want that streaming anywhere?
Minions Rise of Gru is streaming on Netflix.
And I believe Minions again, streaming nowhere.
Oh, a wonderful world that we have built.
A wonderful world we live in.
This is really where just either for the kids,
buy the DVDs or go to your local library.
I have what is going on.
Yeah. How do we we have like so, you know, a movie from the 70s,
whatever, the cult following that's what the but we're just we're dropping
despicable, despicable or falling into black holes.
Yeah. What is our where is our culture at?
There's going to be a different despicable on each streaming service.
I think in the future, there'll be a because we're all licensed.
Everything's being licensed out again.
Everyone's not going to keep their stuff in house on their own streamer.
So I think, yeah, like to be you'll have despicable me to and free V.
Is free V the same as to be no.
No, V is the is the is the former IMDb.
OK, so the despicable me rise of Gru will be on free V.
And then the third one you'll have to I don't know.
It'll be a sort of a treasure hunt to find on something else.
We share custody.
All the streamers share custody.
Yes. Of America's children, the minions, the minions. Yes. Yeah.
Well, this is I'm glad to know this, that you are if I've never watched
one of them all the way through, I have to admit this.
Mike, where were you at with?
I've seen like one and half of the despicable,
which I think are fine.
I wasn't a despicable me one and a half.
This is not like Lion King.
You're not saying you've seen one and a half.
No, I haven't seen.
No, there's not like a Cinderella twin.
No, that's not a one and a half. Right.
Well, Lion King was the only one that was the one.
I think it's the only half besides naked gun two and a half.
Right. Yes. No, no, I know.
As far as I know. Yeah, I know.
I've seen a full one.
I believe the first one.
And then I've seen some of the second one.
Well, I hate to correct you, but did we see one together?
Yeah, I I know we saw a screen.
I saw many, many years ago.
I got an invite to a screening of minions,
but this took me to the second one, the Arclight.
And I had a guest passes and I took Mike and Nick, our friend Nick Weigert.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
And you thought of Weigert.
I thought of Weigert.
I forget why he has associated himself with the minions.
How that even began.
But I have that association.
But we saw the directors.
We saw Pharrell.
Pharrell was wearing his big hat.
Delighted. Yeah.
Pharrell there in the big hat.
Oh, my God, I completely forgot this memory.
Thank you for reminding me.
I thought that was the first one.
This is crazy.
We saw the big hat, which the big hat is the thing, of course,
that sent a stone to Jason in Las Vegas into a giggling fit.
Mentioning Pharrell's big hat when he was like at the height of being stoned
at this bachelor party in the German beer hall is what sent him
spiraling out of control with laughter and then made him have to leave.
I somehow forget that detail, despite this being a five timer.
I might call it a 15 timer.
Very true. But I think this one is OK because it was a very specific detail.
I wasn't retelling the story.
The big hat made you laugh.
Yes, because there was a guy on stage, a guy on stage who had a big hat on.
And he had a witch like a witch hat or like a big hat sort of thing.
And it was kind of I think was sort of animatronics
was like kind of moving around a little here and there.
And from like a quarter block away,
like it was a big beer hall and a little stoned and a little stone is not
a really like we should probably tell the story.
Troublingly, yeah.
Which later on recently, I kind of did the math and I was like,
oh, that was probably like that was a corner of a cookie,
but it was probably like a hundred milligram cookie.
And I probably had 25 milligrams.
And I don't know what the what that means.
Well, Michael, the average that I would do would be five
and five milligrams on like a square of chocolate, five to ten.
They make a hundred milligram cookies.
That would that's like an elephant tranquilizer.
Yeah, that's right.
OK, some people with very high tolerance.
That's true. Take that much, you know.
OK, well, I find out the next day that only Mike can attest.
I was the next day like Jason, that hat was not moving.
Oh, no, that was clear.
It wasn't big either.
We regular had maybe smaller than regular than regular.
Well, I think the other thing that was unclear
and I don't think I ever got an answer on this.
It they were kind of the way they were moving.
It's like, are they lip syncing?
Is this like cover band playing?
Yes, I think that people were lip syncing.
That's what we were trying to figure out at the time.
Like there was a lot of weird bits going on.
So like it definitely contributed to unreality issues. Right.
And so but Jason was not laughing when we saw that we were very impressed
to see the directors of Despicable Me and. Yeah.
For real.
No one was laughing when these
giants of the industry came into the room.
Yes, exactly. And this was at.
We bowed is what we did.
Of course. And this was at AMC Burbank. Yes.
No, it was at the Arclight.
Just solid. Yeah.
That's how tired I am.
That's how wiger I think you all were still at funnier.
My memory is wigered and say over there.
My memory is wigered and say a word to us.
Well, put those things together.
If you experienced a full day in front of your day.
That's true. You're right.
I. We're in the crank at the viral crap factory.
Dead inside. Yeah.
As opposed to the joyful wiger, we know.
Of course.
Boisterous.
Um, well, this boy.
So you got some of that despicable magic.
I you got you got banana dust.
By the way, you really can't pretend I'm like a huge fan and I forgot.
Yeah, I saw the movie and then saw the director and the guy who wrote Happy,
which is the biggest song.
Wow. That's crazy.
But you remembered his name.
If you were like the guy who wrote Happy, what's that guy's name?
Yeah, no, I know that Neptune's I know what they did.
I love the Neptune. Of course.
You know, that's part of this this area.
I might as well say, well, so we'll hear.
OK, big picture stuff.
This is all this is this kids play area.
That is next to the Despicable Me Minion Mayhem ride.
You better believe that's its own episode.
You know how, yeah, of course.
And I part of me is wondering if another separate episode is the big minion.
Of course it is.
Yeah, of course. Of course.
Why would you even why would you use the words?
I think. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. Language in your mouth, Scott. Yeah.
I mean, there's also Minions Cafe.
Uh huh. Which I'm not prepared to talk about.
I'm not prepared to talk about that.
I mean, there. Yeah, I like it.
But you're not prepared to talk about it.
I've not eaten there in a while.
OK, I like the neon sign a lot.
But it's very cute.
And worse. And you think there's going to be more to say than all what was just said.
Oh, I didn't. I'm not saying necessarily anything.
I just I just think it's funny Jason's not prepared.
He's feeling but he has eaten there.
It's outside the you.
OK, that's a good point.
That's a good point.
If we're talking about what's in the gates, because it's it's big medieval type gates,
but all of it striving for a very specific location in Despicable Me one.
Yes. In the first one.
It is like a seaside amusement park.
And they they recreate they they made it look like a pier.
They put they put wood planks down on the ground.
And I hadn't seen again, again, my familiarity.
I don't know why my familiarity with this franchise is so low.
I've just I've never made it a priority.
I'm sure I'm sorry.
And you never is your child tried to watch it or you just haven't shown it.
He really likes a minions trailer on a Thomas the Tankin.
Oh, you mentioned this. Yes.
Yes. And he laughs a lot at them from that likes when he sees one.
Delighted to see them at this place when we go to this little land.
Yet tried full movies and does not care.
It's very strange.
He wants them in trailer form only.
He's kind of like his dad.
You know, I'd rather watch a bunch of trailers than watch him.
Sure. Yeah.
Some collections of the shorts on Netflix.
There's a few.
And those are our fun little show.
I mean, I think the thing that's odd about these
movies like the first one has a lot of heart.
It's about like people building a surrogate family.
But then there's also the minions and they really want bananas
and they slap each other like the three suges a lot.
And they're always getting up to mischief.
So they kind of counterbalance the unit
lest things get too mushy with the heart.
Sure. They they muck things up and keep you on your toes.
Yeah. Right.
And I guess I understand them.
Jason, you like to speak of a franchise more than the Shrek franchise.
Do you think I was I actually was thinking about that today?
So yeah, and I was I think I have not seen a Shrek in a while.
Yeah, I've seen these more recently.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I think they're both kind of products of their times.
If that makes sense.
But yeah, maybe.
OK, I mean, the minions are cute.
What was it? What happened in circa 2010 that led to the rise?
How is it a product of the 2010s?
Oh, well, that song Happy, the other song for the first movie.
It having a song that's in it.
The song that's just called Despicable Me, which last time
a couple of times I was at Universal.
They play a lot. Yeah, that's in this area.
And it's also in the front areas before you're even in the park.
You are pretty inundated by this.
It's it's in there with ET theme and Jurassic Park theme.
It's now this this song, which is is fine.
It's so lodged in my I never pulled it up on Spotify or anything,
but it's so just from being in this park.
I'm having a bad day.
Well, I guess I don't know beyond that.
Despicable Me.
I guess one thing I like about this area is I do consider it to me unofficially.
It is Pharrell land because, oh, there's such a strong presence in the music loop.
Yes. And which I like, I'm a big Pharrell fan, as I would say.
I love all those Neptune songs.
He's like still like making hits for like 25 years.
This guy and I love I love a ton of them.
And I like some of these minion songs for sure. Yeah.
Happy is so ubiquitous.
It's hard to even like think of it as a song at this point.
It's just such a it's like a billboard.
You what? And by thousands of times, what does the wind sound like?
That's sort of when happy is playing.
It's like it's an element part of the earth.
It's not a song. It's just yeah.
Fire, wind and happy. That's right.
But I but then there's other what there's a song Fun Fun Fun that is very nice
and that is genuinely a part that it's something that I like about being in this area,
because that's a great song, not just because it has the Beach Boys title.
I like it of its own. Right.
Sure. Sure. Its own volition. Oh, sure.
One, though, that it's a really strange.
I think I think it's all music from Despicable Me 2 is what I looked up
because there's this CeeLo song that is Pharrell produced.
That's also very lovely and retro. And oh, yeah, yeah.
But and but then you get a bunch of disco.
You get like boogie fever and then you get YMCA
Twist sung by the minions.
And then one thing that's just very it's just jarring when you figure out what it is.
And this is the only one I feel like I might have to play a hit of.
But just know that there is a place in theme park world
where you can hear a minion cover of I Swear by All for One.
Have you heard this? I haven't heard this.
When this creeps up on you, standing in the line for the little spinner ride
or in the gift shop, you just really like is that.
Am I hearing what I think I'm hearing?
I don't know the context of it in the mood.
Do you know? Do they sing it in the movie?
I yeah, I think it's like a gag.
I think they're singing it to someone.
I forget who I will say when we saw that Q&A,
I specifically remember them chalking up some of the like big success of these movies.
Is that like, OK, one of these directors is
American one is French.
So they kind of meld both sensibilities.
And then the other thing is like the minions speak in like occasionally
there's a real word or a real phrase and then it's a lot of gibberish.
Honestly, one of my notes so far for Rise of Gru, too much, too much English, too much.
They're cheating a little.
I don't like that.
They also have started saying Perfavor, which is a little more interesting.
Like I don't I'm not sure where the minions picked up Spanish.
So sort of the height of that joke of the main the joke of the minions of their
speeches, having them sing like a very sincere ballad.
Yeah.
Which I have not heard. That is good. That's good.
That's plenty. Do you stand in that that this land for half an hour?
You're going to hear it.
It's not the longest music loop.
Yeah, it's better than like I really I recall because my the the
the universal the the tram like break patio is like you could hear the Back to the Future loop.
That's what it was when I worked there.
They all back to the future days, don't I feel?
But I it like I think there was I think it was the score and I think it was the two
Huey Lewis songs and that was it.
Yeah, if you are working in a in a theme park zone where there are only three songs,
they could think which is ridiculous for Back to the Future because you could get
it.
And now I failed to produce an example.
What's the song at the dance?
Well, you need to be good or angel.
There you go.
You need Earth Angel and Johnny B. Good and then double back the ZZ Top
song that Van Halen's is a Van Halen song is he playing in the in the Walkman?
Yeah, is it like a rupture or something?
I think that might be right.
Yeah.
And there is plenty of the instrumental ZZ, the Western ZZ Top.
Oh, yeah.
Do do do do do.
Yeah.
What a failure to not include that in the loop.
Is there a bit of Mr. Sandman in the diner?
There should be.
Mr. Sandman is in the movie.
Yeah, in the movie.
Oh, no.
And it's the audio cue that you're back in the 50s.
Yes.
When you go back in part two.
You know, it's funny.
I just had this thought because I was I'm trying to figure out if I'm going to take
my parents to the Disneyland throwback night next month.
Like it goes back like and then I'm like, but then does that mean all the good rides
are closed?
Does that mean like if it's throwback night, I don't know if Star Wars land is going to
be open.
Do you know what I mean?
Why would they not open?
That seems crazy to me.
It seems a little crazy, but they do like certain parts of the park will be closed since
it's like mostly just for like the old fireworks and big band stuff.
And I'm like, well, which tell me what rides are going to be open.
Also, there are a list.
Sometimes there's a list.
There's usually a list.
I just haven't found it yet.
The one they did a couple of years ago.
And Mr. Sandman was being sung on Main Street by like a barbershop quartet or it wasn't
dapper dance.
It was some other thing and they had like a little like bell thing they were playing
as well.
And I was like, this should be in Universal.
That's true.
This is universal stuff.
They got their diner over there, although even that's not like it's not Mel's diner
anymore is it?
Yeah, I don't think it's.
Wait, there's no it's a movie theater.
There was a Mel's diner.
Is the Mel's in Orlando still?
Or did that go away?
I think so.
I think they're both still.
I don't.
Is there a Mel's diner anymore?
I don't think in Hollywood.
No, I don't think it is.
Oh, I.
Yeah, I don't know.
Honestly, I don't know.
I should know.
Yeah, it's that is very close to this minion zone where I've been many a morning.
Sincerely, let me say I like this.
This place that I would have glossed over completely in the absence of a child.
Suddenly, I'm like, this is a it's a it's a wonderful play.
I would say to any parents listening and whenever you start going, Mike, it spends some time.
Here the here the I swear.
Do you think and enjoy just like early, early morning Universal, which I will say has no
magic like Disney has.
It's not you know, you get there first thing in the morning and everybody says there's
no magic.
But I have really fond memories now of when my son's main interest was just pushing chairs
around and touching trash cans through ample opportunity to do those things at this place.
One time a great memory was him pushing a chair just through a busy thoroughfare to
try to show a minion like somebody.
Oh, you're going to impress a minion.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know how to really get my hero's attention to this loud scrape like in front of people
and in front of busy workers.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
The minimum like job interview.
Yeah, yeah.
That is something that the minions would do.
That is like that's right on on game.
Scott's raising a little minion.
Guys, boy, let me tell you something about a toddler.
It's like having a little minion.
They aren't yellow, but otherwise.
Yeah, same thing tolerates bananas.
Not his favorite.
Oh, we just got we just that was the first thing we gave our daughter.
Are you getting in?
Yeah, getting into solid food.
So not unrelated to the minions, but banana.
Not because you're not fostering a particular minion love.
No, not yet.
If it happens, if it happens, it happens.
But you know that I like I'm saying it just there's like a subtle charm to this area.
And I do associate it with emptiness.
There might be times where this land is very crowded.
They're very well could be.
Yes.
My experience has been all right, we're going to go early in the morning.
We've got to beat crowds and we obviously aren't rushing down to Jurassic or Transformers
of those things because he can't go on those things.
So we've we're kind of like, well, I want to be universal, but what do we do?
And then we go over to this area and realize that the ride is not the one ride is not open
till an hour later.
Oh, so it just becomes kind of this just it's really it's just like an empty place for like
we've spent a bunch of time there and we're the only two people walking around.
The land is open, but the ride is not.
And you just get like I guess maybe this is why people love the grass.
It's why they love the although the grass, I think grass is stroller parking.
Is that is that become officially true?
I think so.
OK, well, we'll adjust this more officially soon, I think.
OK, OK, sure.
We got to get back down there and check this new grass out.
We got a whole new grass.
We may just call the episode Toontown grass and then kids and parents at a move and all
the other stuff is a different episode.
We put our like put magnifying glasses to it, like walk around like Winslow and ski.
I'll pick a little piece of the artificial grass and we'll go and study it in a lab and
see what the chemical makeup of it find out what it's made of.
Yeah, yeah.
You got a safe.
Could a child lick this?
That's right.
The grass to JPL in Pasadena.
We set it in the jet propulsion lab to examine.
Could you grind this up and use it as jet fuel?
If so, it should not be eaten off of.
But anyway, I just like it's it's been very nice memories of walking, having this like
calm space to just listen to Pharrell and let the kid run around.
And it does have a thing that is pretty rare to find in theme park environments, which
is just a park.
There's just a little park there, just a dopey little like set of legally cleared slides.
Nothing that's hurting anybody.
Yeah, there's a playground, right?
There's a little play area.
It's nice.
It's nice to see it.
Yeah, yeah.
It doesn't always work for my kid because he does require absolute emptiness in any
playground environment.
Working on that.
Don't know if it's cool.
I hear that.
Yeah, yeah.
That might never go away.
But I don't know.
There's just like I appreciate just having those basics for kids.
And I appreciate that it looks so much like the environment in the movie.
Yes, that entrance sign is really perfect.
But then there's been the question, you could tell that the designers of the place had the
question, but how do we pack this place full of minions?
Because that scene in the movie has no minions in it.
So it becomes, well, it's this environment we know from the first movie, but the minions
are wreaking subtle havoc all over the land.
There's lots of minions to see if you were, if you're doing a spot the minion counting
type game, plenty to see all around this place.
Yeah, this would be very exciting because this would be a place that I, as a kid, I
would have been, the theme park in the movie, I would have been very excited the idea that
there was even any version of it available.
And it does look like the stuff in the movie by and large.
Yeah, it looks really good.
It's a really good translation.
So yeah, when you just add in more minions, you can't go wrong.
It's the only thing it needed.
And it's fun little tableaus, you could tell they're like, they're blowing things up or
they're trying to add splashes of paint, but the paint spilled and good little clear, you
know, in the lineage of Mark Davis, good little area.
Look at that.
I know exactly what's going on.
It's like no words needed.
There's so much, I was actually just, I found some listicle thing of, I think they were
video game theme parks.
So we've done a fake theme park, Final Four, they're video game theme parks.
And I was like, oh man, all these things look great.
And then I was doing, going through other things, you know, which in Scratchyland and
I was really like, as we wind down Simpsons, I assume we're winding it down in the next
few years.
Wouldn't we have wanted Itchy and Scratchyland over Krustyland?
I get why, I understand why, but wouldn't have been better if it was Itchy and Scratchyland.
Yeah, that's a tough thing to do.
Now you're getting into, it's kind of a fake Disneyland.
I don't know how you do a mini version of it in a way.
Yeah, but I just want to see some of the things from the episode.
And like, I guess what I'm saying is I'm like, oh, this is exactly what is in there and it
fits because, you know, it fits the theme park from the IP, whatever fits.
But I was like, oh man, if it was exactly though, as I was thinking about it.
I mean, it's a lot of the same jokes and it works and I understand why they did it, but
I would have been a little more excited if it was just like shittier.
Yeah, boy, that makes me feel old being like, being there opening week of the Simpsons ride
in 2008 because I was working across the street in the Vivid building.
For Vivid?
No, I wasn't working for Vivid.
I was working for- Oh my God, what a six year reveal that Jason worked for Vivid.
Jason was- No, the-
Pornography.
Jason was a pornographer.
He didn't know until now.
Vivid owned the building and then rented, like only used the top floor or so for offices
and then rented everything else, everything else out for temporary office space.
So I was working on like a string of dog shit reality TV show, like writer's strike filler.
Like the writer's strike was well over by that point.
But they'd already committed to the crap.
Yeah, they are already committed to all of these shows.
Can you call one out?
Yeah.
Are those bridges free to burn?
I think the one that people actually did like was called Tabitha Salon Takeover, which was
a spin off of a different haircut show.
Tabitha, I don't even know that I know that title.
Well, she was a big star on the haircut show, I think.
The haircut show?
Whatever the haircut show was.
Big star on the haircut show.
But like, are you smarter than fifth grader?
Sheer genius seems to be the haircut show.
This is five seasons on Bravo.
Really?
The haircut show?
I just remember what was the someone had a picture of themselves.
One of the production people had like, you know, some pictures of other shows they had
worked on.
And one of them was them on the set of what was Fox News's first attempt at a late night
like Daily Show?
Oh, the half hour comedy.
Yeah, the half hour comedy.
I was just like, oh, that's chilling.
I'm seeing this because it had already bombed by that point.
But yeah, I was like, they're like, all right, half day, nothing going on day.
And I was like, well, I'm going to Universal to check out this Simpsons ride.
Wow.
That's like 15 years ago.
It's like 15 years ago.
And now it's like, well, it's probably wrapping up before the 20 year anniversary of it.
Do you wish it was itchy and scratchy land?
I can see where you're coming from.
Well, I mean, they, there's a not so much.
You get the doves.
Yeah, you got the beer garden.
You got the quickie mart and like, but like the seven doves wandering like they're, they're
in the topia, the topia areas.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
I was just like thinking about how much, how satisfying it would have been if it was like
the Simpsons version of them recreating something really on a full like Disneyland parody in.
I know it doesn't, I know it doesn't make sense.
I mean, I did it interesting, but I was like, oh man, that would have been cool.
Anyway, we'll never have a Simpsons ride again.
But we will have never, I can't imagine Disney building a new one.
No, there's no, we've stuck with this before.
There's no way it's not going to just be like maybe walk around characters at like a special
DCA night.
I think that's the best we've had since as established a while back, the ice capades.
I think something that was at the ice capades in 1990 will now be at Disneyland in 2025.
That's my guess, but I hope to be proven wrong.
Yeah.
Something that like local car dealerships would do with like knockoff cups in the early
nineties.
Yeah.
You know, um, here's a little site related to universal IP and, uh, and lands and commitment
to properties.
Here's something I didn't realize.
Well, this is stemming from, I discovered that the, the ride, which I'll talk about
in a minute, the ride is called silly swirly.
Oh yeah.
It's their Dumbo equivalent.
And I was surprised to learn that this same ride is in universal Beijing opened a couple
of years ago.
Uh, that makes sense.
There's a little, it's not called, uh, this, it's not super silly fun land, but there's
a little, little minion land.
Um, but then I was like, boy, I don't know a lot about universal Beijing.
And did you guys know that this park that opened in 2021 not only contains a new iteration
of the water world live spectacular, it's an entire land.
Water world is a land in this.
Oh, I guess I didn't, I did not know that that's, I mean, I don't think it's like a
particularly robust land.
I think it's its own land.
Cause what else do you pair water world with?
But it is the stunt show, sorry, the live sea war spectacular and a restaurant.
They like, that seems so insane to me that in 20 you think like, well, water world or
a megaton bomb.
And then like, no, no, no, there is a water world restaurant.
Wow.
It's an entirely new premise.
It opened it opened in 22 that are open during the COVID.
Just like the Mariner.
Now you can just drink a big cup of piss.
What beverage is, what other beverage could you have?
It's like butter beer.
Yeah.
It's their specialized beverage.
Costner piss.
Wow.
This is so excited.
Did you look at the menu?
Can you decipher it?
The menu seems pretty like nothing.
Chicken sandwich.
I went to the official website and there is this, which I'm going to read the, uh, the
restaurant is called drifters Cantina.
Wow.
It is massive.
It's a big footprint and the vibe, you know, with it's kind of like rustic tin shack sort
of deal that in striving for the water world aesthetic, but plus food, it kind of just
looks like a Joe's crab shack.
Wow.
Post-apocalyptic barely posted like the day after the apocalypse.
That's kind of like what the one in San Diego behind the convention center looks like.
It reminded me of that so much.
Yeah.
I don't know if you've heard of it, um, drifters Cantina and I will read the little plot of
it.
Like the opening of the world.
Please see where it's been taken.
Using, using whatever washed ashore leftovers from a distant past.
The local at holers have constructed a truly welcoming and unique dining experience dive
into our seafood basket drifters catch and homemade fried chicken.
I don't like homemade because you'd like to think that chicken is a, a, a being at some
point that what you're, but when made, I guess made as means prepare.
You know what I mean though?
Does that not imply bizarre fake chicken?
Oh, I actually made interesting.
I've never thought of it that way.
One thing, but anytime that anyone says like homemade or handmade, I don't like it because
it makes me remember that somebody's like hands had to be involved.
Yeah.
I want it to be made by some sort of machine.
I like the handmade detail.
Like a very nice restaurant.
Well sure.
But I mean, I'm just saying that, that phrase or that term.
Oh, sure.
You're just picturing the hands.
That's why I don't want to think about hands touching all my food.
And if a restaurant was called the hand, a handmade's tail.
No, no.
Thank you.
My, my big thing that I always found so odd about universal Beijing is they have an incredible
whole coaster, but it's rethemed at transformers.
It's in a full transformers themed land.
Oh, but it is the same.
It's essentially it's basically the same.
Yeah.
20 plus year old ride at this point.
But it's just a launch coaster.
I think the water world restaurant is crazier though.
Oh, it is crazier for sure.
It's just was weird to see the initial concept art and pictures of like, well, that is clearly
the whole coaster, but made into a transformers.
And given that we, what we know in our hearts is the transformers ride.
Yeah.
There can only be one.
I think they have one of those too.
Okay.
That makes sense.
So they have two transformers rides.
Yes.
Whole land.
So the good people of Beijing get to have the moment of intimacy.
Wow.
Yeah, that's great.
And they get to then drink a pee.
At Toler P. At Toler P.
Is the Mariner at At Toler?
I can't remember.
He's kind of a wanderer.
He's kind of a, he doesn't associate with any tribe.
No, he comes and meets and helps the Atollers.
But he can't, in 2021 they build water world, which is a great show, but they can't rebuild.
They can't make a new back to the future ride.
They can't make a new back to the future thing.
I mean, I think they can't, but maybe they'll prove me wrong by.
Yeah, look, they turned their back on this.
They got rid of it while water world just stayed and stayed to where it's perennial.
It's like that.
I think maybe we talk about Woody Woodpecker being Universal's Mickey.
Yeah.
I think the water world Atolls are Universal's castle.
I think you're right.
There's no such thing as weenies in any of the, maybe the islands of adventure lighthouse.
But besides that, but that's never been reproduced.
So what else do they got?
What do they put in every park?
Atolls.
You're right.
I think it's going to outlast ET in Orlando.
I mean, it's not in Orlando, but it'll last out here longer than ETA.
Do they ever make a new, what if, if they, if it turned out Epic universe, one of the
lands was water world.
I'd be thrilled.
Oh, that would be wild.
Yeah.
With like a duck and boat ride.
People might be excited about that honestly.
But more than like more Potter.
You want more Potter.
Like what is that?
Yeah.
And I know the ride system is more Costner.
And like the Howie the Train Your Dragon, that's going to have a fun coaster.
I'm sure that'll be fine.
Super Mario.
Yeah, but we've done a version of it.
Yeah.
Water world land with a new e-ticket.
Costner stock all time high.
Right.
You know, that's true.
Uh huh.
So people are going to want to see a figure that from a distance looks a little bit like
him.
Right.
So I would be rancher slash governor from the yellow.
So yeah.
Water world land and back to the future land for expansions for Epic universe would be
my preference.
Yeah.
I think that's what the musical does.
And if it takes off, then maybe water world.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I'm going back to the future, but I would like to spread the leak here that water world
coming to Broadway.
Going piss drinking you and me.
I mean, look, Mike, it's possible.
They just announced this musical stage musical based on smash the 11 year old.
Did they?
Yeah.
That's your dream.
I can't.
Are you ready to audition?
I thought it was an old, well, I could have played into those characters.
I'm not right for any of those.
No, I think you're selling yourself short.
I don't know what's in the show.
The live show might be new stuff, new characters.
I thought it was either an old news story or an early April fool's joke, but like I've
seen it enough times like playbill.com reported it.
Let's get Jason cast in this.
Sure.
Let's put this turn this to main feed.
Some more people hear it.
You want, but then what happens to like Jason's doing a live Broadway show.
Jason's pressure handling is off the charts.
Good charts.
He'll be able to handle those two things.
No problem.
Kick lines, constant dancers.
Sure.
Yes.
Stay in limber.
Right.
Living in New York, which is a low pressure city.
Yeah.
He's going to be fine.
As long as he doesn't get into fights with three car former three card Monte.
Well, he's going to be hassling weed dealers every night.
Is this fake?
This fake bro turning tables over.
Hey, should I turn you in?
Let me show you the NYPD station right there.
I'll take you right to it.
Let me sing you my new number I'm working on for the show.
Wait, I'm contributing now.
You're singing.
You're in smash.
You're getting him.
He's writing the songs too.
I'm the Christian.
I'm working on like he's, he's working on the song.
Like he's working on his voice.
Yeah.
I'm learning it.
Sorry.
Okay.
But he's no, he's writing it too.
Fuck it.
He's writing smash.
He's writing it too.
And shoes.
No, it's a shame.
And is it Mark?
He's been coming up a lot lately.
He hasn't come out.
Look, he's very prolific, you know?
All right.
Well, you're better than him as, as far as writing Broadway songs.
I'm saying it here based on zero evidence.
You heard him in the country bears episode.
I'm here now.
I don't know if it overtakes the body of work of Mark.
I don't know.
I just love that one the best.
I think.
Um, okay.
So, uh, what have we?
Oh, the ride.
It was a bit, I went backwards here.
I'm going to get into the ride.
Um, they have a Dumbo type ride.
Uh, it's just a, I, I don't think the term is spinner.
I'm out of my, I don't remember what you even call these anymore.
I realized that's the wrong term, but you know what it is.
It goes around and around and around.
You control the up and down of it.
Um, and this ride is special to me cause that's like, well, I don't know.
We went to this one in sea world, but it's one of my son's first iterations of that and
getting to control it and realizing that, Oh, I'm in control of the joystick, uh, is,
is so much fun.
But one thing I didn't know until recently is what is the name of this ride?
I honestly didn't know in my head it's called super silly fun ride or swings.
Close.
No, the ride is called the silly swirly is the name.
And but I think I, I, it makes sense to me that I was confused about it because up until
very recently and I'm glad I took a screenshot of when this was the case until a few months
ago, the universal website called it super swirly again, the name silly swirly, but it's
super swirly.
And what I'm showing you guys right now is it says super swirly gets super swirly, super
swirly will soar and spin.
And that is right next to the giant logo, silly swirly.
It says the wrong name four times in my, in my, in my site here next to a logo clearly
saying a different, so that is the, that's the degree of care.
Yeah.
Um, or just a find and replace at least.
But I, you know, I liked when these things that went like, what's that call?
I don't know.
It think we can get so precious with these Millennium Falcon smugglers runs and I had
a little careful, uh, uh, dot, dot, dots and exclamation points.
I love that it at least until 2022, a big corporate theme park didn't know the name
on the rides.
Oh, sure.
Uh, I also have a very fond memory of this ride because in the spring of 2021, as the
parks were reopening in California, that was the very first ride I went on in over a year.
That was your first ride.
That was the first ride cause Jane and I got tickets.
She got to, we went to the taste of universal food festival.
A lot of parks were doing like, you know, uh, you know, you get a punch card or a tab
card where you can go eat at restaurants and there's characters walking around and you
can just be in the parks.
And we went in that day and we like got one or two food things.
And then very quickly we heard, we saw the rides open.
Like they didn't know such, so it was by the end of the day, every ride basically in the
park was open.
And this is where we had heard, uh, that they might be doing like soft opening for secret
lies of pets.
So we got in the virtual queue and to kill time before we got the virtual queue, we went
and rode the spinner ride and then did like a print.
It was a very surreal day.
Yeah.
So you're like, are you going on rides?
And then you're all that time.
I think we managed to do pets like twice because very quickly all the other rides at like 30
or 40 minute waits and like 30 or 40 minute waits crammed in queues.
That was like still a little sound to be half vaccinated.
And like at the time, like, but it was super fun to go like sit on Jurassic patio and drink
a beer and eat a corn dog.
You know?
Oh yeah.
It was a huge visit back.
Yeah.
And then we went back to return very fond memories of just like walking around super
silly fun land and going on this ride and the, the, the, the criticism I had at the
time was like, okay, this place has been closed over a year.
They couldn't have one guy power.
Why?
Like, cause a lot of it gets a little dirty.
You're saying it was dirty.
It was dirty.
They let it, they let it go to Russ super silly fun land was dirty.
Yeah.
I think when you paint stuff fluorescent, you really have to like scrub it to keep it
from getting filthy, especially that close to San Fernando Valley.
Like there's a lot of shit in the air.
Take notes.
Universal custodial Jason's got notes for you.
It's look at the universal power washing.
Give it a little power.
I give it a little.
There's water in involved in this area.
Well in half.
Yeah.
And half of it, not in this part, but yeah, I believe they, some of it is called a nearby
dry zone website.
You know, we learned about, you know, wet play and dry play, you know, from the, the
great Wolf Lodge episode copy.
Right.
And I guess that is as we established the clearest way to say it, but it's like, ah,
it's still, I don't know about that.
You still said it again.
I said it again, but I mean, there's no clear way for parents with the young kids like,
okay, this half is dry and this half is a water play area.
I think it took them a little while to get the water turned.
Hi, where can I take my children for wet play?
I is an adult ever said uttered that phrase.
I don't think so.
Not if you didn't, weren't forced to write the copy of it.
Um, look, this ride is, it's, you know, it goes around and round.
It is what it is.
But again, early, early days of getting your kid into rides.
I've watched, I've watched my boy smile so much on this.
And the vehicles are really fun, brightly colored a little bit.
Maybe you could do some feels and some power much, but there are these fun little like,
you know, like whatever the hell these monster, these aren't anything later in the movie.
Are they, they're just like random odd monsters or aliens or something, right?
Yeah.
It's just googly.
Googly eye character.
That's a good way to put it.
In the movie, the big beats are like the girls force grew to ride a roller coaster and he
starts to get sick.
And then Agnes wins her fluffy unicorn, uh, toy, uh, at the space killer, uh, raw, uh,
carnival game, which is replicated in this area.
Which they do have.
So that's like a huge, like big set piece of the movie.
And then they recreated it pretty exact.
I was surprised that their word killer appears in a theme park.
Oh, it's true.
It says space killer on top of this, this, uh, game basically, but there's, is there
a not in Disney there's that the word doesn't appear anywhere anymore.
At least did hard rock park have a ride based on Cortez, the killer, long dark ride, all
the characters.
Man, that was really realistic.
I thought it was really him.
I thought it was the real court.
Oh man.
I was listening to that song the other day.
Yeah.
Great song.
Uh, I hope of quality that Neil would approve of.
I think so.
Neil's been trying to get his songs in theme parks for a long time.
And, uh, one of these days.
So yeah, I was impressed that they, cause that would have definitely been Disney, Disney
wiped away.
That's a good point.
That's a very good point.
Yeah.
That's a good joke.
I mean, I guess it's less of a theme park joke from the movie of like just calling the carnival
games a space killer.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
Oh, it's a little play on words.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't realize that.
Oh, that's nice.
That's good.
That is nice.
Nice.
This whole area is nice.
A lot of family restrooms.
How can I ask you this?
Uh, I don't think there are restrooms in this area, but yeah, no, there is a big.
Oh, in the, the soap.
In the super silly.
Oh, in the, in the wet zone.
Oh, I guess that's where that's why I don't go over there.
Right.
I don't want to go wet.
Can you, how good is the, can you see the view from the up the hill when you're in the
ride at all?
Can you see that's another thing about it.
And it's a nice, like that gives it a boost over a say, of course there's similar rides
at a carnival or whatever, but that you have that great view of from over there, it's kind
of like, like West Valley and that view goes and goes and adds a lot to your peripheral.
It's really, it's like, okay, basic ride, get it, but vehicles are fun.
Weight is short, really nice view.
Pharrell music playing.
So some of the Pharrell's, uh, mid to okay.
Most songs and, uh, and it's nice.
I don't know.
It's, uh, it's, it's a little more going on than just some other little kid.
Right.
I'm not a perfection and this is maybe too difficult, but if you take away sort of the
nostalgia of seeing Dumbo, is this better than Dumbo?
Think about Disneyland placement for Dumbo.
Let's just go Disneyland, Disneyland placement for Dumbo.
When you're on the ride, what is the better experience?
Ooh, you know what?
You know, I being higher up on the high level, it's like a rare thing that makes good use
of the odd up on a hill and up and down nature of universal.
Yeah, you're certainly seeing more and I'd rather hear some of these Pharrell songs than
dream.
Wish your heart makes, uh, you know what?
Boy, that's an interesting, interesting question.
Yeah.
The only one side of it is just kind of a wall.
I'll give you, because it is on the, this is all on the top of a parking garage.
Yes.
And if, and I think if that, and if that wall wasn't there, I think you would feel, you
could feel like you could just jump off hundreds of feet.
So that maybe that's maybe the only thing is that wall is a little perfunctory.
Yeah.
The only thing that could edge is that I guess Disneyland at night in the back of the castle
ambience wise is hard to beat, but there's some, this has a lot in its favor.
And maybe you got to maybe give it to like fountains on Dumbo.
I do like that, you know, that there's water spouting and just the whole like mechanism
is beautiful and looks like it's true.
Being craftsman.
That's true.
Um, this area, well, one, I think it gave universal Hollywood that despicable me ride
a leg up because it's like, okay, well, when you exit, there is a gift shop like in Florida,
but then there's also the carnival.
There's the pier from the, from the movie that you like.
Um, uh, now that flushes out feeling like you're in Despicable Me for a little while.
Yeah.
Uh, Florida, um, getting a leg up cause they'll have another big despicable me minions ride.
Um, so, but then the other thing is this certainly filled a need for universal Hollywood cause
they closed down the curious George play area to build the Harry Potter stuff.
And before that, this was like a Coca-Cola themed like play area.
Coke soak.
Yes.
So just a wet play zone.
Not a dry, wet play.
And it didn't have anything for those who prefer dry play.
Yeah.
Everybody's people should really should listen.
We really should.
How have we not done coke soak yet?
Yeah.
That's weird.
Hmm.
Maybe because there's nothing to say about it.
Okay.
Well, that could be a consideration.
It's not saying it's name that we did the entire episode.
Okay.
Well, we'll do some digging.
There's a Coca-Cola like refreshment, like stand by the men of black ride in Florida.
Okay.
And that's something fun.
Uh, it might.
It's mostly just a bunch of freestyle machines now.
I think we could want a second gate on the freestyle machine is possible.
I love the freestyle general freestyle.
Oh boy.
They're so fun.
I guess I could see that.
Yeah.
I've never said out loud, they're so fun.
But I won't at this juncture, but I, maybe I'll, maybe your enthusiasm will be infectious.
Maybe I mean Wendy's leg up for Wendy's.
They have them.
They have them in the drive through.
You can like, you can mobile or a special drink.
You can tell them percentages.
Not that precise.
How does it, how do you give them?
But you can say, you know, it's diet coke and it's got some lime to it.
Like, but that doesn't have the per se.
It's not the fun precision of that app.
Yeah.
But it's mellow yellow with cherry.
Right.
Okay.
And they, they decide percentages and you just, yeah, right.
They're not going to, yeah, they're not doing the 15% cherry 25%.
Yeah.
Well, only then when you can like, you know, it looks like, like meters on a color printer.
Right.
That's the true experience.
Yes.
But that might have to be bought control.
You could do it to the percentage of it to the decimal point.
Right.
Speaking of beverages, maybe one thing to say on the way out about this episode, about
this, this area, this is outside of the gates, but if we're talking about, you know, we're
covering zones at universal.
And of course there's all this, it's, it's become kind of this bigger zone devoted to
the illumination films and just feet away from super silly fun land is of course the
Irish bar where you can go and get hammered.
Yeah.
Of course.
And just, uh, I, I figure, you know, we're calling shots this year.
I want to, I want to literally call shots.
I think that's an episode right there.
The Irish bar, the Irish bar, we can go and get hammered.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's hard to do it fast.
I guess I have to slow it.
There's where we can go to get hammered.
Hammered.
Yeah, you're going to ramp it up and then slow it down right there.
It is trying to think what like a whole second gate episode can you do on the hospital that
would be closest to universal?
Wait a minute.
That's what I, your premise is that by doing a shot, you would have to go to the hospital.
I feel pretty bad.
Uh, when I drink now, I also, also though, I, I don't think, I think there's been a lot
of judgment of this here bar as if it is just like, take your shot, like do it.
I'm going to watch you knock those shots.
This is a place that has alcoholic mixed beverages.
It does.
It's got slush.
You don't need to.
It's got a white clothed tall boy.
Well, you called the shot, you called the literal shots.
We have to do shots up there.
You're right.
A called shot sticks.
That's what a literal called shot is.
And if it does send Jason to the hospital, so be it.
So be it.
Okay.
But as we took earlier for, for your, you can handle, we talked, you can handle, we
talked about it all.
You can handle all sorts of things.
You're selling yourself short.
You're going to get, yeah, you're going to get a shot.
You're going to do fine.
And then we're going to just pound and get hammer pound drinks, not pounds.
That's one of my favorite details of the minions cafe is right by the checkout.
They see large cooler, usually filled with like Corona and white cloth tall.
Oh right.
Yeah.
Real close.
That's my only, that's like, it's, it's like overall criticism of universal, especially
universal Hollywood.
It's like, if there was just sort of a more magical way to introduce this area, if it
was just set up in a little more of its own thing where you can't see the Parisian street
right there, it would just, you know, that all this is the biggest gripe you would have,
I think with universal outside of the Harry Potter area and everything.
It's just too, everything's too on top of each other.
And it doesn't feel like it's its own complete land.
You walk down a Parisian street and then are, and then are in a theme park from Despicable
Me.
Yes.
There's no, it's not transitions or not exactly.
And I understand.
I understand.
I'm not crazy.
You can say a replica of the Moulin Rouge windmill from the super silly.
Yeah.
You can take shots while watching the water come out of that monster's mouth, basically
on the wet play area.
I don't know if you do have a view of that.
You don't think so?
I don't think you do.
Which way is it pointing?
You got a hard angle there.
I think.
Oh, okay.
Have you, have you had your son probably not ready for getting splashed?
No, certainly not.
You didn't teach him like he gets like a little shot of orange juice or something.
Oh, daddy gets used to the speed and the size.
Yeah.
Big boy shots.
Older relatives going like, and you just, you tip your finger in a bottle of the Dewars
that they're teething.
You dip your finger in the Dewars.
I think just missed our generator.
Just missed the like, you just rub a little, a little.
Tiny bit of whiskey for sleep.
No, I have not done that.
No, no.
But he's not, he's not going in the water area yet.
No, I feel like I never see anyone in this wet play area.
That was going to be my question because I've not spent a ton of time here.
And as a kid, I loved, there was a park we would have to drive like 25 minutes, but there
was a park that was like spraying water out.
And I, as a kid, five to who knows 10, like loved this park and there were slides, but
like it was spraying, like I can't even really remember how it was set up, but I loved that
idea.
But especially a park like this, that's so local.
I know there's obviously tourists, but so local.
How many like adults and kids are doing the water part of it?
I feel like I've never seen anyone in it.
Yeah.
That's sort of what I'm getting at.
It's literally running and the bucket is tipping over and dumping all the water.
Right.
It's a tremendous amount of water.
It seems like a particularly wet one of the, particularly wet, wet play.
I mean, Orlando, I feel like people are getting soaking wet all the time because you just
so hot so much of the year you get dry pretty quickly.
The Southern California climate, especially universal city.
If you're up on that hill, you're probably getting one of two weather patterns.
It's windy as shit or it's the middle of the summer and you're so much closer to the sun.
It's very dry and hot and brutal.
Well, but then also the only way you're letting your kid get soaked is if you're staying on
one of the hotels on property.
Because other than that, the kid's going to have to dry off, which I guess is okay, but
that might be a big pain in the ass and the kid's going to be grumpy.
Like that would, like it just doesn't seem like it's set up for that.
It doesn't seem like people are utilizing the water area as much.
It seems just like a, like a art fixture.
Let me ask you this.
Is there any way when your kid is a little older, when like daddy and son would get in
their swim trunks and drive up to universal for a morning of frolicking in the minions
water?
I'm so creeped out by the description daddy and son, even their little shorts and frolic
in their swim trunks.
I do think daddy going to get any swim trunks and frolic.
I go to the wet play zone.
My family would pack changes of clothes often if we knew we were doing a lot of water.
Would you, would your daddy and you go and get in your swim trunks and go into a splash
area?
Um, you know, uh, King's dominion and Doherty park both had water parks like built into the
park.
I'm not even answering this question.
Yes.
Well, yeah, we bring a change of clothes.
How is it?
The same question is asked to me and I'm tremendously creeped out and Jason just like, why?
Yes, we did.
Dornie park speaks my language.
I know nothing you said was specifically odd.
There was no, no, yes, there was daddy.
It's weird.
You say I'm daddy now and that's what I call myself and it has nothing weird about it.
I say daddy, it's daddy.
And I say that to my child.
There's nothing weird about it.
Now I say daddy all the time.
I think what you just said was weird.
I say daddy, daddy.
One of my catchphrases when I come in the room, when you're done recording this and
you go home, you're going to open the door and say daddy, you can ask my family and they
will say that one of the, my number one catchphrase in regards to my daughter is it's daddy.
Okay.
That's the thing I say.
I guess that's fine.
So it's not weird.
I know there's nothing inherently Cree.
Of course people are daddy.
People are daddy.
I understand this.
I'm aware of daddy's frolic.
Let's be honest.
It's the trifecta.
It's the dish.
It's daddy plus frolic plus swim trunks.
I think it's the amount you're saying these things, Michael.
And I think like, yeah, that's the volume.
Frawlick is also kind of a choice.
That's kind of a choice.
And the ask you ever, uh, Hey, you ever dad, daddy, daddy and son ever, uh, did I get breathy?
I would like to go.
I guess I'm adding that to it.
Well, what about this?
We leave the kids behind and then like two daddies go up together with their swim trunks
and frolic in the splash zone.
All right.
Have you been reading rich dad, poor dad?
And that says the word front.
So Jason, that's the only book I read is a rich dad, poor dad.
Now that I'm a daddy kind of like shitty kind of debunked in this way of like, yeah, it's
kind of a shit.
That guy pops up on my like when I'm scrolling through Facebook videos, I think I popped
up all the time.
I bet he has a lot of thoughts on whether people want to work.
He certainly does a phrase that, uh, there's this one historian or writer on Twitter was
like, uh, no one wants to work anymore.
This has been a story in newspapers for over a hundred years.
This is a, with old examples.
Yeah.
Uh, no, he thinks that, yeah.
Anyway.
Um, well, this is, I know exactly what's going to lead to this, that the, us daddies and
this non daddy go up to the Irish bar.
We get hammered and we put our shorts on the hospital.
We we've frolic in our show.
We'll be in, we'll be frolicing in our, in our trunks.
Uh, zero time flip.
Finally, I, I, you know, get my sunset Boulevard floating face down in the pool.
Cause I had like half a shot of sky vodka and don't shoot sky.
Oh yeah.
Got me a trouble at the moon.
Don't shoot sky.
I'm Jason face down in the minions, super silly fun land, like sunset Boulevard dead
from one single shot of alcohol.
Half of a shot of alcohol.
He started talking about a talking hat.
And then before we knew it, he was drowned in the wet play next to sewer.
No, not next to Kevin.
That's Kevin's as a playground.
Cute one.
He's next to the cute one like him.
No, that's kind of nice.
Cute, Kevin's died next to cute Kevin's tall.
Bobby's cute.
Stewart is regular.
Okay.
That's how the last thing he said, it's going to be a wild episode.
He looked at a bottle of Jamis.
Actually no, that was, I believe friend of the show, friend of the show, Kyle Moody,
but like, uh, shots, uh, once Jamis said, and I like very quickly down.
I was like, Hey, I gotta go.
I'm so sorry.
Jason had it.
Did you leave because like, I don't know what this shot's going to do to me.
This is the werewolf moment beginning.
It is.
Yeah.
Jason had a toothache that night and he rubbed some of it on his gums, um, to, to calm the,
the pain he was feeling.
And then it got too much for him and he had to go home.
I rubbed doers on Jason's gums sometimes when he has a toothache.
That's Protestant whiskey.
All right.
Open up for daddy.
He rubs doers on little Jason's gums.
So he feels better to frolic in trunks.
You survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, if the big, if it's always been there, regardless of what
we say on the way to it, join us on our new, on our, it's not even new anymore.
Get your out tier club three, uh, well I got to change the copy much like the universal
website that got the name wrong.
I'll get tinkering on that.
Um, uh, I was probably get hammered episode coming very soon.
Very soon.
Let's go do it right now.
Thank you.
Alright.
Go.