A frightened 22-year-old dressed as Snow White!
And there's the man of the hour, Ryan Perez,
who joins the boys for the first ever Oscar special
on Podcast The Ride!
It's a wonderful night for podcasts, podcasts, podcasts.
Let's begin.
The three hosts of Podcast The Ride are me,
Scott Gardner, Jason Sheridan.
I was driving over and I was like,
is anyone going to do it?
It's a wonderful night for podcasts, podcasts.
Should I do it?
And so I'm so happy.
I wouldn't mind if you did it.
You can still do it if you want.
No, that's fine.
No, I don't want to take the glory.
You can make it a wonderful night
for podcasts.
It's wonderful.
Resistance the
years.
And then the Schindler's List year, he was like,
I'm not gonna do, I mean, I don't know,
maybe he already had his fill or whatever,
but like he purposefully sat out a year
where I think it would have been tough
to be super, super funny or upbeat or whatever.
The Schindler's List song would have been
the most difficult job of his life.
He probably tried to crack it though and couldn't do it.
He probably thought about that and then he was like,
ah, I'll give it to Whoopi.
Yeah, there's drafts of a song he was trying to work out
and they were horrendous.
Yes, there were some, I'm sure he got bruised.
Even a blanch at the Hotel Roosevelt,
just like a pen and a pen, just like, what do you think?
It's gonna break me, it's the one I can't do.
I think he will do it one more time.
Okay. I hope so.
Yeah, I could see them in a weird hostless year
being like, well, Billy's open to it
and he's getting up there and one more time for nostalgia.
Yeah, was 2012 the last time he did it?
The most recent time?
Oh, I don't know the year.
He says, I've hosted it nine times.
I watched it 2012.
I think so.
Moment, and even some of that was like,
oh, I don't know if he'd make that joke now.
Like, there was a joke about Jonah Hill dropping some weight
and it cuts to the Moneyball-like people
and you just see he is really not happy.
And fair enough, because it was kind of mean-spirited.
It didn't really have like a-
Like, lay off the donuts next time.
Yeah, and then he's given, he's tossing a softball,
he's just going up to Scorsese and he's like, oh, Marty.
But that was funny, because there was just like
an uninterested, I'm assuming Scorsese's daughter
sitting next to him and she was an uninterested pre-teen
and I'm like, wait a minute, the math,
is that the one that does the TikToks with him in it now?
Oh yeah, probably.
I think so, yeah.
Oh, I haven't been keeping up with the
Crystal TikTok content.
Oh wait, no, I'm sorry, not Crystal, Scorsese's daughter.
Scorsese's daughter.
Oh right, this I've heard about, okay, okay.
Will do post TikToks and occasionally
she'll get him to be in one.
She'll like, wrap his Christmas gifts in Marvel paper.
Yes. Like Marvel comics.
Yeah, she'll get his ass.
And as usual, Marty, great sport, great sport about it.
Sure. Yeah.
He probably, he acknowledges it as some new kind of form.
You know, it's like, I gotta help.
Audio visual entertainment.
It's fun to do audio visual entertainment content,
but you know, yeah, he's probably,
he's probably on some level appreciates it,
that she's a burgeoning little filmmaker, TikTok filmmaker.
Yeah. I don't think so.
I think he probably hates it
and I'm gonna cancel him on Twitter.
Next chance I get.
Nothing I love more than holding him to the fire
every three months when that comes around.
We're all being mean to Marty today.
Since you mentioned Twitter, I have been wondering,
I have been thinking about the Billy Crystal,
like song and dance openings a little bit lately,
because recently there was the thing
that took on the life of its own,
the Ariana DeBose number at the BAFTAs.
And I watched it a couple of times
and I talked to Jane about, I'm like,
what are people talking, what is the issue?
Is this because she's out of breath?
It's because she kind of delivered one of the lines
and she's like, I think, yeah, it just kind of caught fire.
Like it's just getting roasted on the internet,
but you can see when it cuts to people,
like the older people in the,
like Jamie Lee Curtis is like, she gets it.
Michelle Yeoh gets it.
But like the younger people are just like,
what the hell is this?
Like they don't have the context of Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
What does she do?
I haven't actually watched it.
I'm aware that it's been roasted a little bit,
but what is she doing in it?
I mean, the thing that really caught on was she said,
was it Angela Bassett did the thing?
Angela Bassett did the thing.
Yeah.
Like really, truly just that one line,
slightly breathless saying, Angela Bassett did the thing
is now we're obsessed with this.
Everyone in the world is obsessed with this
really embarrassing moment.
This, oh my God, what an embarrassing moment.
You look at it, you're like, what?
Like, especially if you're looking at things in the context,
like I've been looking at a few musical numbers,
Oscar numbers in the context of preparing for this show.
And I'm like, this is, there are 9,000 moments like this
in every single Oscar's opening number ever.
Yeah.
Like.
Yeah, skin crawling.
There are moments, I've talked about this before on the show.
This comes up in theme park shows a lot,
but if I am really mortified by something
that the hairs stand up on my arm,
I get embarrassment goosebumps.
Especially the main thing I get it from
is cheesiness in musical numbers.
Yeah.
And it will happen in the next couple hours.
Oh yeah.
Guaranteed.
I guess, so maybe that's the, I should watch this thing
and see if it gives me,
makes the hairs on my arm do anything.
I mean, it's a little corny,
but I feel like award shows have always been a little corny.
You know?
And so I think what the reality is,
well the thing to blame here is
they probably rehearsed this once, maybe twice,
and they didn't clock,
this was an elaborate dance number,
this is an elaborate costume to get off,
to then run across the stage and then start rapping.
It was probably like,
oh, I don't think the stage manager thought this through.
Sure, sure.
And just like, if anybody is complaining about this,
maybe, I just assume anyone complaining about it
has not seen Kevin Spacey at the Weird Sports Awards.
Yeah, oh yes, yeah.
The laureates.
I mean, if you're missing basketball shots
and offending Tony Hawk,
there's no way whatever you're describing is worse.
Well also, Ariana DeVos did the Tonys, I think, last year
and was fantastic.
This is a very extremely capable musical.
Musical theater pro.
Musical theater performer.
And given the task of a bad song,
like what's, okay yeah, a bad song, what's new?
They're all bad.
There's never been a good musical number,
lyrics-wise, in an award show.
Yeah, yeah.
Which we will prove this evening as we do this for sure.
Ryan, in terms of your Oscar experience,
I don't wanna put the term Oscar fan on you.
Oh please don't.
That doesn't seem right.
So I wanted to poke around what would be better than that.
I don't know, I mean, it seems like you,
I feel like you have been fascinated by
or engaged with the Oscars at least forever.
I don't know how you want to calibrate
your Oscar affection or otherwise.
Oh sure, yeah, I think, I mean,
as a byproduct of really loving movies,
you're always interested in the Oscars.
I mean, if you like movies, at least when you're young,
you have a curiosity about them.
I think even as a young person, I learned very early
that the Oscars don't really have a ton to do with movies.
Sure, sure.
Like it's not like your favorite ones
are winning Oscars or whatever.
So that whole, like the competitive element of the Oscars,
I became disenchanted with like very young.
But I watch them every year
and watch them kind of closely every year
because I think they're unfailingly,
it's almost like the State of the Union or something.
They're almost like a bellwether of the climate
of the industry and the political climate at the time
and everything.
And it's also like a weird game show
where people are winning an award
and have to like pitch themselves
and the rest of their careers at you
over the course of a minute or two.
And so it's just a fascinating,
really high pressure event to watch in terms,
and also just the spectacle and everything too.
But I think they're like,
I like the Oscars in particular.
And award shows, I've never been to one.
I don't really care to ever go to one,
but to watch them is tremendous fun.
But you can't take it on the surface.
I think people watch them and they say,
well, that Oscars was not entertaining.
But if you watch on a surface level,
they aren't entertaining.
The Oscars do suck pretty much all the time.
But you have to be able to read them.
If you're able to read them and read what's like going on,
they're very fascinating.
Oh, sure.
It's like one part of the text is the ceremony itself,
but everything else happening.
That's why the slap is like the most interesting thing
because it's like, whoa,
like real hostility that maybe you could have guessed
or sensed or whatever suddenly broke through
and it became like a real thing.
Well, and you had to fill in the back,
not all of the information was there on the stage.
Because when it happened, it was like,
that joke caused that?
We all had to learn that she,
I assume I had to learn that she had alopecia.
I don't track every move of Jada Pinkett Smith
and I don't think Chris Rock does either.
So like, okay, that, wait,
and he made some jokes that was,
she was offended by years prior, okay.
Yeah.
Oh, and Will Smith is out of his goddamn mind, okay.
That's also important.
Well, the legitimacy of the moment was in question too.
There was a big debate raging of was it real or not?
I had that thought.
I definitely had that thought.
Yeah.
We were all watching it.
The four of us were all together.
We all processed the slap.
Jane, I feel like called it as real immediately.
Mike, you also did.
I was a real truther the whole time.
And I was on the fence.
I watch fake combat sports regularly.
Well, that's what, yeah,
we were trying to figure out if it was kayfabe,
but then the sound got real fucked up.
Like when the sound got fucked up,
I feel like that's when I was like.
Yeah, that muddied the entire,
like the slap itself, I feel like,
still could have felt like a bit potentially,
especially if you didn't hear the sound of it,
which was like very raw and clearly injured him.
But then once it cut to that shot,
once it cut to the screaming,
was where like, uh-oh, this would not be happening
in a bit, I don't think.
It would have been more fun after that.
If it was a bit, it would have been like a fun thing
at the end there.
Yeah.
Well, because you know, I'm an envelope truther.
I think I. Oh, right.
It would come up.
I think that, and I, and I,
and no one has told me that I have no actual
foundational belief in this,
but I do believe that Kimmel,
known for his pranks occasionally,
staged some kind of prank or whatever with producers,
probably did arrange something that went awry
and the response was bad
and they've not really admitted to it.
That's okay.
I don't have, and I, and no one,
I have no reason to believe this
just beyond my own thinking of it.
So I was already in the mindset of like,
oh, they're going to try it again.
What if this Will Smith thing, another envelope thing,
which is fake in my mind.
Do you, do you, do you have a full theory
that like they sent Warren Beatty out there
with the wrong envelope and just like hung them out to dry?
I think Warren Beatty is probably in on it.
Oh yeah, okay.
And I think there's probably a very small handful
of people that are in.
If this is, if this is.
Right, right.
I'm just wondering what your theory is.
I base it just on the idea that I've watched 20 years
or more than that worth of Oscars.
This has never happened.
There's never been a, an envelope mix up
in the entire history of the awards.
And it happens to happen during Best Picture
on a year when, when semi prankster Jimmy Kimmel
was hosting.
It was like, everyone's like,
and the only reason it's not come out is
because the initial response was not positive.
If the initial response was, wow, that was super fun,
then, but the initial response was no Moonlight,
an important American film was robbed chance.
It's, it's, it's proper chance.
Those are bad optics for sure.
Yeah, and it's kind of the more bubble gum movie.
Like, like there's sort of different films.
So you can't rot.
Like, so there's someone making songs
in the show and there's lists here.
It's kind of weird.
Yes, but I think that was the, that was the reason was like,
oh, this movie's, this movie should have had its own moment.
And instead the Moonlight people had to share the stage.
Oh my God, this back, I think it backfired.
I think it was a prank that backfired.
This is, this is some conspiracy stuff
I'm spreading on your show.
Yeah, this is like Alex Jones stuff.
Hey, come on guys.
Have you really, what are the chances
that the long walker make it out to the stage?
Ah!
Well, thank you for presenting your theories.
I, what other questions did I have for you about this?
Oh, oh, in terms of like your,
when you, like growing up and watching the Oscar,
do you, was there one that you recall as being like,
that you, where you kind of like came to,
like this one where like, oh, I like watching this.
It feels like your initial idea
of what a classic Oscar telecast is.
Yeah, the truly the best, the best Oscars
and the best award show I've ever seen period
is Billy Crystal in 1992.
Yeah.
So this would have been for the movies of 91.
And this is the year that he did,
he came out as Hannibal Lecter.
Yes.
And he did a medley,
it was the second time he'd done the medley,
but he did it, it was like just a fun medley.
It was the Jack Palance pushups.
And it was the best joke.
And they've since recounted this,
him and the Lanchard people have recounted this
enough to where I don't like it anymore.
But at the time it was very funny where Hal Roach gets up
and he introduces Hal Roach,
who's the great silent film director.
And Hal Roach like gives a speech where he can't,
he gives it off mic.
So the whole thing.
I like you, I like you, I like you.
And then Billy Crystal's response is that was appropriate
since Hal began his career in silent film.
And that brings back.
And so when I saw that as a kid, I was like, wow,
this is a real, it was a genuinely entertaining show.
I mean, I know everybody has like conflicted thoughts
about Billy Crystal now, but like he hosted that.
And when Ellen DeGeneres hosted the first Emmys
after 9-11 were like genuinely really great hosting jobs.
Like I can point to it's that.
And maybe like when John Waters,
there's been like when John Waters
did the independent spirit awards,
like there's a handful of like hosting jobs where you're like,
well, those were really good,
but that one was like a really good show, 92.
That's exactly my answer to it.
And especially, and I was of the right age
and being like a Disney kid as we all were,
that's the year of beauty and the beast.
So it's all those songs.
So they're big songs,
which has like almost immediately stopped being the case.
Like, I don't, I can't remember when a popular song won the,
or was even in competition for it.
They're all like weird.
Sometimes it's almost like they don't do the category,
but that year it's like huge songs,
Sons of the Lambs, huge, every movie's huge.
Did something from Beauty and the Beast win best song?
I think Beauty and the Beast.
But it was three of the five were from Beauty and the Beast.
It was always, and then like the Disney ones won,
I feel like every, the Disney ballads.
Yes, which always upset me as a kid.
Cause you like the more fun ones.
I wanted Under the Sea to win.
I wanted Be Our Guest to win.
Did Under the Sea win?
It may have won.
I think it might have.
But from then on it was always.
Kiss the Girl wasn't enough of a,
wait, no, or was it, did Party Your War?
I don't know.
Like Hakuna Matata did in the wedding.
Hakuna Matata did not.
No, no.
Circle of Life probably.
Or Can You Feel the Love Tonight?
Jason, Look at our Love Tonight.
That's what it was.
I'm looking up Little Mermaid.
I can only do one at a time.
I, you know what's a funny one is that
Colors of the Wind won over
You've Got a Friend in Me.
The Randy Newman ones are really spotty.
Oh, interesting.
Where it's less popular, Randy Newman ones won.
But in looking at, in general,
looking at clips of the last 20, 25 years,
I think Randy Newman has performed every year.
Since, you always have.
Did Randy Newman win for Michael or something?
Yeah, probably.
Oh, here, Jordan's got it.
That's Under the Sea winning.
Okay, Under the Sea did win.
With Dudley Moore and Paula Abdul presenting.
Wow.
What a pair.
Original score and original song.
Oh, Little Mermaid.
So it got two.
Yeah.
But I think you had the ballads from then on.
Kiss the Girl was nominated.
Sure.
It's a fun one.
Kiss the Girl.
Morgan Freeman's Kiss the Girl.
That should have been that.
The original Alex Cross adventure.
One of the great, one of the great notes.
Tyler Perry took over the role.
Is that what that is, really?
Tyler Perry played Alex.
Kiss the Girl's the same thing.
It's the same book series.
Kiss the Girl, Along Came a Spider.
Oh.
And Alex Cross.
Alex Cross, yeah.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know that.
Okay, so in terms of,
let's just start diving in here.
And I'm excited to have you for this, Ryan, also.
Because I feel like you're, you are a cinephile.
You're a fan of high art.
And we tend to gravitate to the lowest.
Gutter.
Yeah, we tend to.
Waterless toilet full of art.
I like the toilet, I like it all.
Ryan likes the toilet.
But that's where, these things, I think,
really square off on the Oscar stage.
And especially did, we're gonna be so 80s centric here,
I feel.
And I'm gonna start there with one.
I couldn't not do this one.
And this might already answer the question,
what's the most theme parky thing
that ever happened on the Oscars?
And for this, I go to 1988.
Jordan, I believe the file is Peewee One.
Do you guys know this offhand?
Can you picture Peewee Herman's Oscar appearance?
I think I've seen this, yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, this is like, I mean,
this is like designed to get five-year-olds in
and watching it for the rest of their lives.
It's so crazy.
Oh, wait, I'm sorry, stop it for a second.
The context here is that Peewee Herman
is presenting an award,
but he's been, a PA has come on stage
and whispered in his ear that there is a giant robot
that is making his way to the theater.
And he says, yeah, I'm so sure.
And then goes about his business,
and then this happens.
It's Ed 209 for the listeners.
Roll the cop when you need one.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Ed 209 is now shooting,
and Peewee is flying up into the rafters.
Peewee can fly is what we're learning.
Ed 209 is, by the way,
open fire on the audience of the Oscar.
Yeah, he's pointed more at them than at Peewee.
Yeah. And either way,
he's hitting people in the balcony.
Yeah, no, this is a mass shooting.
Yeah.
This is more deadly of an event than in RoboCop
and in the conference room.
Massive body count.
The choice to make him fly in that is the fun.
I mean, I like everything that happens.
I think that's a great, if I saw that today,
I would eat my shorts.
That's a terrific little bit.
It's really fun.
That's just fun for all ages.
It's just good.
If you want to see a little of the aftermath of Peewee 2,
Jordan, just to see it in reverse, RoboCop does appear.
You'll be happy to know.
And I skipped most of the extremely analog,
old TV mixer laser fight that occurs.
It's the wimpiest laser beams you've ever seen,
but it really goes and goes.
And then, do we have the clip?
Let's see what it is.
It's like it's a laser that using a Johnny Carson sketch.
Johnny Carson sketch.
Thanks, RoboCop.
All right, Peewee.
It's safe to continue giving the award now.
Thanks, RoboCop.
It's silence.
RoboCop just in the aisle.
Doesn't know his exit.
Peewee just lowers slowly.
He should have been sitting somewhere.
It's cool if Peter Weller would have
reprised his role though for the little appearance.
I mean.
That's good.
I mean, John Wick should interrupt the Oscars or something.
Yeah.
Like, yeah.
That'd be awesome.
They should do stuff like that.
Yeah.
You know what?
We're all so concerned, like as if nominating
the right movie is gonna get everybody excited.
Like, and then it's not gonna win.
You know, like what's the Top Gun Maverick nomination
actually gonna do in terms of like,
oh, there's movies people like it.
What they need is Maverick crash landing
in the theater.
Mini like drone control planes racing through.
When I was a kid, I never thought like,
why isn't Batman nominated for best picture?
Like, it's nominated for like visual effects or something
and then that's when you see Batman.
Like there is a time and place in the ceremony
as that was for RoboCop to show up.
Right.
And they would make a point.
I don't know that they do that kind of thing anymore.
They should have Maverick crash landing in the theater.
And then Tom Hanks's Colonel Tom Parker should try to,
you put on a hell of a show and he should try to do
all 10 accents he does as one character.
I did not kill everybody.
It is not true.
Singing to Santa Claus, singing.
This is not, why are they giving away golden statues?
They have not sung Santa Claus.
My pitch for a movie actually is Tar versus
Colonel Tom Parker.
Maybe they can do that at the show though.
It's like start with, she's like conducting,
like open on her conducting and then Tom,
and then Colonel Tom comes out and says,
no, no, no, she will not,
Tar will not conduct Santa Claus.
You sing rocking around Christmas tree.
That is what you do.
He picks up the same baton.
For him it goes limp.
And then all that he tries, I will do it myself.
And then all the tubas.
I love, they should, like, you know what?
Well, it's clear what they have to do.
They gotta get Bruce.
There's only one way out of the mess.
Like when you think about when did the Oscars
start going off the cliff?
I don't know exactly when he stopped working on them,
but I can only, you know, he hasn't been doing it
since the early 2000s probably.
Does he have a credit?
This is a good question.
We've looked this up, I think.
And it feels like he has it, but maybe again,
Jason, you have to look this up.
When did Bruce stop?
Yeah, well I know that he,
because I read an oral history of it recently.
Get Bruce's information.
Let's get him down here right now.
We should get him on here.
If you don't know also, Bruce,
but we should probably contextualize Bruce Vellanche
the kind of like.
I don't think your audience needs a context.
Yeah, okay, bye, after.
He comes up every three episodes anyway.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just said it, maybe I said it for the first time
that Ryan and I have seen Mr. Vellanche perform live
as the Widow Twanky.
Yes, yeah. That's true.
That's true, Mike and I had a special day
many years ago in Aladdin Live.
And do you remember what happened at the brunch before?
What news you received on your phone?
Yes, it was a Sunday morning
that we saw Aladdin's winter wish.
And right before we went in,
I remember I looked at my phone
and Peter O'Toole had just died.
It wasn't just a text that said he is risen.
No.
No, no, it wasn't that.
Well, and if we're addressing tales of this nature,
I think I've told you, Ryan,
the tale of you meeting Wallace Shawn
has been told on the show more times
than I could possibly count.
You've been a presence in the show ever since five years ago
when you did it by this story being told over and over.
I think it's where Five Timers came from.
Five Timers for us, Ryan, are not people
who've been on the show five times.
Stories that have been told five times.
A lot of times when I'm saying something,
I'm like, oh, this is one of the things that makes Scott mad.
Like if I bring up Brian Setzer,
if I bring up Green Day or something,
I know for sure, like I'm in the middle of it,
but I'm like, well, you know, I'm telling you about it.
I wandered right into retelling the Wallace Shawn,
Andre Gregory story.
And he was like, you've told this before.
And I went, what?
I thought it was just, like, I had no idea.
I had told it this many times.
So it's just something I say.
Also, because some of these things
are also told in our day to day life.
Sure.
Oh, sure.
It might not be Five Timers on the show,
but I have heard them in person so many times
as opposed to the clown.
I had such a good time seeing you go up to them
and talk to them and then the whole experience.
It was not even Gregory's birthday.
It was his birthday.
We all sang happy birthday.
We all sang, you thought about getting a piece of cake,
but I think you decided not to.
Oh, okay.
Which would have probably been fine, honestly.
We all should have gotten cake.
It was like a group of 20 people.
We were just like standing there to say hello to them
or something.
And we realized we were in the middle
of a birthday celebration for Andre Greger.
Yeah.
Yeah, that would have been a good,
I don't know why we didn't do that.
I know, I feel a little regretful of it.
I liked that little, that piece of it
where a detail that was important to you, Mike,
and that you've told every time it's been told,
Ryan thought about getting a piece of cake and then didn't.
Or something that didn't register with Ryan himself.
Well, he.
And then here's what makes it a great story.
Yeah, but it does make it a great story though.
It does really, the idea that I thought about eating cake
and then really kicks it up a notch.
I think it does.
I guess it indicates your respect for these men
such that you would not.
Yes, you don't want to suspect them.
Wait, so what do you find,
what is the best part of the story?
It was how excited I was?
Well, I think,
Well, first of all, it's Walsh-Sean
being part of it at all.
I love Walsh-Sean.
Because another thing that's happened on the show,
you have argued to no one about,
I've watched you go like,
and if you don't think Walsh-Sean is great,
then fuck you.
Like you've argued to no, to an invisible party about like,
I think I have,
you want to tell me Walsh-Sean isn't great
in Haunted Mansion?
He's always great.
Well, I was yelling at Jason in that.
Yeah, yeah.
I've read a few of, during lockdown,
I read a few Walsh-Sean books.
So I started to appreciate Mike Stewart's a little more.
It's gone to a different level,
especially that play that you all saw.
This is what you'd say about a grandparent.
Now I have the context to know that they've lived in a chain.
I shouldn't roll my eyes at his stories.
I used to think grandpop stories were boring and bland,
but then I realized the wisdom he was trying to impart.
I'll take it, honestly.
I'll answer the, I jumped on the,
what makes it,
what is the crucial part of the story for you?
Well, okay, there's a,
I don't want to rehash the whole thing
because there's so much stuff I loved about the situation,
including that Armand Schimerman was sitting behind us,
who played Quark on Deep Space Nine.
Oh, that part makes it come up a lot.
And I peed next to him,
and then at the middle of this, again,
this is, I've said this on the show before,
but it, in the middle, at intermission,
Armand stood up and he goes,
huh, I thought it was over.
Well, I guess we'll just see what happens next.
Which is so funny.
He forgot how a play works.
He forgot how to play.
He clearly was done.
It was a long first half.
Yeah.
Quark doesn't know how plays work.
Mike pees with Quark.
I peed with Quark, which is so fun.
I love him.
He's one of the best characters.
He's great.
All of that was fun.
It's fun seeing it in a small theater.
And then we were,
just ended up in this little celebration,
and I was just delighted by the whole situation.
I was delighted by it.
I haven't been back to the Red Cat in COVID times,
but at that same theater,
I don't think it was this performance.
It was a different performance.
I saw Philip Baker Hall.
Oh yeah.
And he was on Oxygen, and he was in his,
he was, he died not that long ago,
but I also saw him there, attending a play once,
and said hello to him.
He was very gracious as well.
You had to say hi to him before you went.
Yeah, that's cool.
Yeah, that's a little secret.
I think that's kind of a,
if you want to see like really great actors,
go see plays at the Red Cat, you'll see.
Cause a very small, I mean small theater.
It's a small theater,
but they do like plays by the Wooster Group,
and like, it's like,
you'll see sometimes stars on stage,
but a lot of times respected actors in the audience
watching, I feel like.
Right, wow.
Where's the, what city is Rick heading?
It's like downtown, it's by the Disney Concert Hall.
It's like, it's connected to that big structure.
Oh, gotcha.
And then maybe you'll get to eat cake,
or think about eating cake with one of the actors.
If you're lucky, you will get to consider cake.
You get to look at cake.
And then I think you came back and said,
Andre Gregory was telling somebody like,
you must come up to the cabin sometime.
That's a good quote, that's a good quote.
I think you did a good impression on much better.
You did a very good impression of him,
as my memory is full.
Anyway.
Okay.
Let me throw this out into what we were talking about
before that sidetrack.
Ryan, what you said about like,
you knew that the silly stuff would happen
in the effects categories.
This isn't the funniest clip in the world,
but I wonder if you'll remember it.
This to me is the epitome of what you're talking about.
That like, with those ones, that they feel technical,
but it's about the big movies that everybody likes,
and we have a little fun with these.
Can we show the clip Elijah?
Does anyone remember this offhand?
I don't think I know this.
May I have the envelope?
Young Elijah Wood.
Oh wow.
What's that sound?
Oh!
It's a T-Rex poking out from.
That's a big build.
Yeah.
You can kind of feel the flatness.
I think this is, you know, a facade style.
They only did one side of it, but it's huge.
Yeah.
You got the context when little Elijah Wood walked up.
That's little Anna Paquin there.
Little Anna Paquin who won.
I don't know what that award was going to, Jurassic Park.
But Anna Paquin won that.
The one that year won for the piano.
Yeah, yeah.
Big year for kids.
Big, big year for kids.
That's fun.
That's Elijah.
Let's see, he would have been coming off
the good son probably.
Yeah.
With old Mac.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I think I was surprised that wasn't Mac.
I assume Mac had his Oscar, he must have done.
I'm sure Mac had an Oscar moment at some point.
Well, Jason, do you have a say?
I feel like you got a list brewing or something.
Do you want to throw in something?
I need a few.
If you have, do you want to jump to 98?
Sure.
Yes.
Okay, let's jump to 1998.
This is, I looked this up, this was the year
the most viewers, like the highest rated.
So 50 million people tuned in.
Is this the Titanic?
Yeah, this is the Titanic here.
And I think one thing I think about the Oscars,
you mentioned the State of the Union, Ryan.
This time of year, it's like State of the Union
Super Bowl Oscars.
And I feel like I just always kind of related that,
of these are live events, everyone's gonna watch
these sorts of things.
All equally exciting.
Well, look, the Oscars was most exciting to me.
But when it comes down to viewers, the Super Bowl in 98
had 90 million viewers and the Oscars had 50 million.
And so I think that used to be the norm,
a little bit like 50%.
And...
Now it's like negative 12 million.
Now it's like, the Super Bowl has held steady
and gone up to like 110, 120 million a few times.
And the Oscars last year, I think was 16 million.
Wow.
Yeah.
And it's grimmer and grimmer.
I mean, as with, you know, Ryan, we watched
the train station Oscars together.
Which turned out to be a train wreck Oscars.
Not because of the movie either.
That wasn't that year.
No, that was the most...
Then you hear the numbers and you're like,
of course no one watched.
Why would anyone?
I think it's hard to come back.
Honestly, after Union Station, it's hard to come back.
You can't keep them, you can't get them back on the farm
after you've been to Union Station
with the glen clothes twerking.
And that was the fun part.
That was the only bit of fun.
That was the only, that was like the slice of cake
they considered having.
As good as it got.
But better times, 98.
Yeah.
Jordan, if you can pull up the first clip.
So just to set everyone up,
Billy Crystal comes out on a big Titanic.
He's like up by the ceiling.
Of course.
And then the ship sinks.
But while sinking, it gently lowers him to the stage.
So it kind of serves two purposes.
And there's just like two song moments in this
that really stuck out to me.
I think the Oscars too, were a good demonstration of like,
when the culture was much more of like a mono culture,
with like, here's the reference point,
and everyone in the crowd knows what they're referencing.
Sure.
Oddly, the only thing that's gotten us back to that
is the slap.
Yeah, it is.
Finally, the thing at the Oscars
is the only thing everyone was talking about.
Yeah.
But back then.
My films nominated for best picture are,
The Judge, Right Back to the Theater,
The Tale of a Giant Ship,
that started many years ago with an over budget script.
20 year old show.
The Borg was a loud director man,
who made accountants sick.
Two studios teamed up to pay for a three hour flick.
Everybody got three hour flick.
That's good, like what else?
That's so clean.
People like it.
Yes.
And then.
Some other films deserve a break,
like My Giant in Three Weeks,
My Giant in Three Weeks.
Oh, that's a room for My Giant.
I've gotta tip my hat to Gilligan,
the skipper to.
That's Jimmy Cameron.
Jimmy Cameron, yeah.
The propeller guy and the eye.
The movie star, the professor and Marianne,
here on Oscar's Big Night.
Yeah, going well.
So like that, it is clean.
It's very clean.
Everyone gets it.
It works.
There's a classic like,
and then you just leave the last one in the list,
is just the actual one.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I would do in anything similar to that.
It's funny to not change it.
Replacing the wife,
and his wife with the ice.
Ice.
It's really funny.
It's really slick.
Well, this is a question maybe,
is where does,
because I've been grappling with this in my own head,
where do we all fall in terms of,
do we like the Billy Crystal medleys?
What's, where do you put it in terms of ironic like,
or just like?
Do you even know?
That's a good question.
Yeah.
Because we loved it when we were,
I mean, we would look forward to it.
Loved it, we paid, everyone got it.
I think, you know, it's a few crossovers
with theme parks for me where it's like,
oh, I know the reference before I saw the thing.
Like I knew this joke about Gilligan's Island at Titanic
before I ever saw Titanic.
I have to give credit for,
I have to say that these like,
Mark Shaman arrangements are good.
Like they're, they're like,
they flow in a way,
like as to whether or not these are good or bad,
like lyrically they're corny or whatever.
They, they're not always like the most inspired,
but like I do like listening to them as well.
Like, you know.
And he pulls them off music
and it utilizes the full orchestra that's always there
and sounds great.
And it makes it feel like elevate,
it doesn't feel like some talk show bit
because there's a grandeur to the orchestra,
to the stage.
And soon to have a theme park credit to his name
because he was one of the people
behind Rodgers musical from Hawkeye
that they're putting in California Adventure.
Mark Shaman is really?
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
I mean, he's good.
Yeah, everything his name is on is good.
Ryan, when you,
I don't know if it was last year when you were doing this,
but you, you were like ranking the Billy Crystal songs
on Instagram,
Yeah.
which was a delight.
And to see ones that you particularly responded to,
do you recall what was number one?
I don't offhand.
Number one was the Full Monty was in the top.
It might've been like number three or two.
And it wasn't really ranked by the best.
It was more ranked by what like was lodged in my head.
It was more like a subjective rating of like,
of a line.
And if I think about it sometimes while I'm driving
or something that it's the thing,
but number one was the year it was the,
he had done all the movies for 1990.
It was in 93.
So it would have been the movies in 92.
So it's unforgiven, few good men or whatever.
So he sings unforgiven.
If it's to the line,
it's to the music of unforgettable.
Unforgiven a few good men sent of a woman,
the crying game.
And if you get a man,
that's the list of all five nominees.
Now before I slide down on my knees,
da da da da da da da da da da da da da,
Mr. Saturday night.
And everyone's like,
which he was plugging at the time.
The film.
And there was talk that maybe he would,
the film would be up for Oscar.
I think David Paymer did get an Oscar nomination for it.
Oh really?
But, but, but yeah.
And so he was, it was this thing.
It was just so raw.
Yeah.
Him wanting that, that, that, you know,
a joke, but also like I made it.
It's kind of like my giant, you know, kind of like.
Right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very, very bald, I guess.
The one that I think I told you this
when you were posting those,
the one that's lodged in my head forever.
And I couldn't even remember what movie it was for,
but it was, it was George Clooney for sure.
And I mean, now I know what it is,
but the song I just remembered was
George is cracking up because his wife is shacking up.
And then he's got in a comatose.
And I don't remember it from there.
Yes.
Yeah. That's the private descendants.
The descendants.
And I had to look, I only,
I only in a list later did I realize that's like,
that's some Hawaiian hits, like pops.
That's like a Don Ho kind of song.
Oh, the Hawaiian tie.
Or it's, or it's too like a traditional Hawaiian song.
I don't, I don't know exactly, but like, yeah,
I couldn't place the melody on.
Isn't it in the Tiki Room, I think that song?
Dun ka dun ka dun ka dun ka dun ka.
Maybe. I think so.
I don't know the name of it,
but it's, I think in a lot of stuff.
I, this brings me to a question that I had,
and I wonder if we could, if we could just do,
put on our writer, put on our Bruce hats.
Do we think that we could think of a plausible
Billy Crystal song for this year's nominees?
And I say that, and I don't think we,
we don't have to flesh out the whole thing.
Just be the vaguest idea of it.
And with this, I don't mean to make it tougher
to tie your hands behind your backs,
but I remind you of the Billy Crystal rules,
which are it, preferably a song from before 1959.
Oh, okay.
And, and if possible, you know,
with the Jonah Hill one being the exception,
a song that is nice to the people involved.
Right.
And he likes them.
Yeah.
That's just, that's just, that's just bonus points.
But does any, at this point,
what you gotta do is just like,
and I don't look, I don't know a lot of these songs,
but if we, maybe we can work backwards from like
the Cole Porter catalog or a song from a musical.
Yes, you have to know the great American song,
Rodgers and Hammerstein song.
That would help.
Like my favorite things.
I know we did once.
I think if we can think of a,
just a song from a musical at all,
I think we could go backwards.
Yes.
Well, okay.
Let's just take a title.
What's a title from this year?
With Bright.
What are the movies?
And then, and then rhyme it with something from there.
Well, Tar has, oh, thank you, Jordan.
Oh my God.
Oh, All Quiet on the Western Front.
Okay.
Women Talking.
Oh, here, let me, well, let me admit it guys.
Cause since I came in with this in the pocket,
I did, I did this, this thought exercise
on the couch there in a little while ago.
And she said, oh, you know what,
what about like a boogie woogie bugle boy?
And I thought for a second, and then I think,
wait, can I remember it?
I think it was, oh, it's there,
the fuss and feud and fable men's of Phoenix AZ.
All right.
Now you're talking.
But don't let me take fable men's off the table.
Oh sure, yeah.
You know, Tar, there's a lot of rhyme schemes for,
everything everywhere all at once.
I think, I think there's probably something in like,
you're the top gun maverick.
You're the top, I think that's Cole Porter.
And whatever, and we're gonna give you no static.
You know, and you're the top Tom, we love you Tom.
Yes, we genuinely love you Tom.
The song was nice.
You would only agree to be here
if we didn't make any Apatow style jokes about you.
I actually thought of one for top gun maverick as well,
which is, okay, it was,
start cheering for Cruz.
Tom's flying the planes.
Oh man.
He wants to bring the theaters back, maverick, maverick.
I should have texted you guys, we could have come in.
I cheated here.
You were, yeah.
Is there one for like, does anything,
oh, go ahead, Jason.
I think I have one for Avatar,
but it's a little bit of a journey.
Sure.
Like the film itself.
Like the journey.
Yeah.
Again, Cole Porter song to lovely.
It's delightful, it's delicious, it's the Navi.
I think that's great.
That's right on.
Thank you.
What about like the lonely goat from Sound of Music,
like lonely Eekron or mighty Eekron.
The mighty Eekron, yeah, assuming.
I mean, if you use that phrase.
Like, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, Eekron.
And you can switch it to the, what's the other,
the animal, wait, the, wait, the whale is the,
Pyocon is what, why am I not remembering this?
Wait, Pyocon.
Toqun.
Oh, the Toqun, yeah.
Yeah, well, you could go through all the ee-hoo and toqun.
That's how you switch it up.
I would also propose a Gershwin,
like someone to watch over Navi.
Does anything scan with Oklahoma?
Yeah, maybe.
Could you, well, you could just do,
I mean, you would think maybe he would do Elvis
with an Elvis song, but I kind of like the idea.
I think that would be the cheat.
It would be, yeah, like, right, you know.
But you could also just like, oh, it's Elvis.
It's the most fun movie of the year.
That's what he would do.
The plot lures great, but look at Tom Hanks' waist.
Okay, how about this?
And I hate to break the rules of this, but.
You can, I mean.
But the song is over 20 years old,
and it is another thing I say sometimes to annoy Scott.
This Everclear song, Everything to Everyone,
comes into play.
Or like, damn. Maybe Billy's daughter would.
Damn, damn, damn.
You think that you're everything to everyone.
All at once. All at once.
The idea that he would do that.
I like the idea that Billy Crystal,
like what are some of the newer songs?
Yeah.
This is when you're writing for it.
Oh, I know, Everclear.
Oh, well, this is one of the hottest
everybody's still talking about, Everclear.
This is one of the hottest rock and roll songs
around, Mr. Crystal.
Okay, good, I'll go home.
I'll look at it.
Send me a tape.
Oh, listen.
You do what you do.
You go to the parallel universe.
You try to go everywhere.
I had another thought also,
which is that you would do,
like, you know, it's about a conductor,
so you could just go to Tar, Tar, Tar, Tar.
Oh, yeah, you could do a classical.
Well, Beethoven is definitely more than,
older than 1959.
Tar, Tar, Tar, Tar, Tar, Tar.
She didn't.
She made her.
And then Crystal.
And now she's dead.
She's getting canceled.
How about, I mean, it's not that old of a song,
but like women talking around the sewing circle,
women talking.
And you know.
Oh, Pretty Woman.
Pretty Woman.
Oh, no, I think he would do early rock and roll.
I think now that's what he would bring fresh to the table
for the 2020s.
Yes, he'd be like.
He's doing rock and roll now.
Right, right.
I like that.
Any other quick hits before?
Are we missing?
No, wait, we got them all on screen right now.
The Banshees, that's just a weird title.
You know.
You got to learn how to.
It's something about like, inner Sharon, is that right?
I don't know how to say inner Sharon.
Like, I can't think of the song, though.
I feel like there's jokes,
so I feel like I've heard that title said
multiple different ways.
Yeah, inner Sharon, and Sharon, inner Sharon.
You say inner Sharon.
I say inner Sharon.
Inner Sharon.
Let's call the whole flick great.
That's a, all right.
Wow.
We put on our Bruce hats.
All right, all right.
That's wonderful.
Some of these, a more recent host,
I always love the joke,
when Hugh Jackman did a musical medley,
and they were just doing a weird dance,
and he said, the reader,
I didn't see the reader.
That was really funny.
That was a great joke.
Yeah, and it catches, I like when he laughed while doing it.
I think Jackman was kind of, who we liked lately.
Do we like, I've liked all the Kimmel, I'm happy it's.
Yeah.
I'm happy it's Kimmel, because for the first time,
we will get a joke on the Oscars about the slap.
Yes, all right.
I like it when there's a host.
That's what lately what I enjoy.
Controversial stance.
When there's any host present.
For some reason, Kimmel does it twice,
and then they go, all right,
we need to lay off the whole host thing.
Yeah.
After that envelope that he did the first time,
but not the second.
Why did the host disappear?
Now they're just back to him.
Yeah, yeah.
Really strange.
I was looking up some older ones,
because I was trying to think pre-Billy Crystal,
and they were much more reserved affairs,
usually Johnny Carson hosting,
and he would get some lines in,
but then there were some weird moments, like 1981.
The day it was supposed to happen,
John Hinckley Jr. shot Ronald Reagan.
And so they pushed the ceremony 24 hours,
but then in a weird turn of events,
they already had a pre-taped welcome from Ronald Reagan.
So Johnny Carson is talking about Reagan
being in a hospital room and requesting a TV
so that he could watch the Oscar ceremony,
and then they cut to a videotape
where he's in the West Wing,
talking about the magic of the movies.
And it was just very weird.
The other weird-
From the bottom of my intact heart.
Yeah.
That's when they said,
we're going to cut to a video of Mr. Rao.
I was like, oh my God, is he in a emergency room?
We're gonna cut to him in the middle of surgery.
Yeah.
And just so you know, Jodie Foster didn't,
she's not impressed, sir.
Yeah.
America Soldier's on.
Mission not accomplished.
But 11 years before, I found an odd segment
I didn't know about where Bob Hope and Fred Astaire
gave out best documentary and best documentary short.
And this was purely a way to set up Bob Hope
to kind of pimp Fred Astaire into doing some dancing.
And this is 1970.
Fred Astaire was born in 1899.
So he was 71 doing this.
And he's still pretty good, but I was just like,
wait, how old is he when this is happening?
And the answer is he was 71.
From the 1800s.
Yeah. Wow.
Terms of kind of questionable performances of that nature.
I'm gonna head to some stuff that Ryan brought to the table.
And this is 1983.
And well, the first performer in this list
is Liza Minnelli, makes sense.
This is how they open the shows with this musical number.
Ryan, would you like to introduce the rest?
Oh yes, this is 1983.
Now I actually don't know where, I think this sat
probably at the beginning of the show is where I think it does.
I think so, yeah.
The performers, it's a medley led by Liza Minnelli
who had done the show before.
Natural, gifted, when you think of,
what basically Billy Crystal is parodying
to some degree is something that Liza Minnelli would do wonderfully.
Yeah. Dudley Moore, who was her co-star in Arthur,
not a musical guy so much, but you know,
could choke his way through it.
Richard Pryor and Ed Walter Mathau.
And if you have the question, can those people sing?
Prepare for it to be answered.
Let's do Liza Minnelli.
There are thousands of craftsmen and women too loaded with technical skills.
There was many a worthy crime.
And also, and if it was a little unclear how that divided up,
Dudley Moore gets through his little part OK, but then he coughs
and then goes to Pryor who just doesn't, he loses it.
Yeah, he does not have it.
He's trying, he doesn't seem embarrassed or anything,
but he is just not.
So why would you think of him to sing?
Yeah, so I'm more amazed at is why did they agree?
Like now no one agrees to anything and they're like, yeah,
we'll come out there and try to sing with Liza Minnelli.
Yeah, I think a person now would be like, like my sense of I mean,
I was starting to bring this up earlier that Bruce,
I know that Bruce Philanche at least worked on the kind of notorious
Anne Hathaway, James Franco Oscars.
And that one, I guess that 2011, I looked it up to that 2010,
2011, where the last one she was credited.
Oh, well, OK, OK.
That might have been the last one. Yeah.
But I, you know, I mean, rightfully so given how it went,
it seems to me from this oral history of that one that I read,
and I was like very, very frightened and copped to it several times
during the show was just kind of out of her wheelhouse.
And she can sing, though, and she was still and then prior,
just like, yeah, sure.
Like zero nerves.
What I would say is like the Anne Hathaway that failed might have been.
I don't think that one failed as a failure of Anne Hathaway's hosting.
If anything, she was the capable host.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know. I haven't gone back and rewatch it. Who would?
But like at the same time, it's like that probably maybe was maybe.
I don't know. There was some element.
She's she's if anything, she's closer to like Eliza Manelli,
who can like she can go out and carry the whole thing. Maybe. Yeah. Yeah.
That one, because I went and looked around for like,
are there clips of that for this episode?
And it's just kind of it's just that the whole thing is off.
There's no moment that's the drug.
Yeah. Mainly that just doesn't.
No, no, I just like it's they aren't that crazy to look at.
It's just even the oral history said it's not that one thing was really bad.
It was like death by a thousand cuts.
There's like a mood in the. Yeah, I remember that.
Yes. The whole night versus like, yeah, doing something crazy.
James Franco, I think like by the time he came out and dressed as a woman
or something or there was some kind of drag thing that didn't play.
And by then, you're really not right.
Well, this is what we got.
This is the one idea that they agreed to.
There's one more of can we play math out as a math prior to just to get one more
hit of that sweet math that was singing.
I wouldn't have thought that the loser of the fun.
I just didn't know what he like.
Maybe he's like an old man.
Maybe he knew how to sing.
But then the answer is this.
And what about tonight?
Now there were 2000 taxes and cummerbunds
waiting for people to wear and buy those are of Hello Dolly, by the way.
Oh, right. Totally unfamiliar.
Yeah. Come on, Bonzo.
We look to the sky.
But he's like singing to a different song.
It's yeah, he's all he's got on beat.
Pretty nice even tries to help her line says now.
What do you think now? Now?
Now, now, now, wait.
But but, you know, as as kind of disastrous as this is,
they just laugh their way through it and it's fine.
And it's all made up for by what Ryan you alerted me to at the end of the clip.
Can you play number three?
They didn't know the audience remembered this song by the time this thing happened,
which is just legit good that we explain the voting procedures.
So here to read the rules, here's Mr. John Maschietta.
Know that name off and you know who this is.
The voting procedures work like this.
All Academy members vote on nominations for the five pictures of the year.
Oh, the fast talk. Yeah.
Micro Machines.
They remember sending those nominations.
That's that you get you get the idea.
I mean, that's just that's just funny.
He gets a huge applause at the end.
Ernest Borgnein loves it. He's like, ah, I love it.
That was probably before the Micro Machines campaign.
Ever even. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
It might have just been like something he was doing for bits and
options or something. This guy.
If campaigns are on the table, have flow.
The progressive lady and the guy code Gecko have them come out together like, well,
we don't usually share the stage.
We don't usually share the spotlight.
Well, and the guy from the Hulu pool.
Yeah, please. Oh, yes.
Hulu executive before.
Yeah. Let's get you out there.
I'd love that.
What does everyone here want to host the Oscars?
No. Sure. Would you do you like that?
It's really I'm asking you like as a kid, was that something you were like,
I like to do this as a kid?
Yes. Now, you know, it's just such a like trap.
Like nobody comes out a lot like you're damned if you do damned if you die.
And I think it's possible because of podcasts, the right.
You guys could be asked.
It's well, it's possible.
We've I've been trying to get us to host the Theo Awards, the theme park awards.
We've been turned down just even getting free tickets to it.
I think a hosting trio could be in your future.
And I think take any hosting job.
I think host. I think when people like it's amazing to me that they can't find a
host for the Oscars. That is absolutely mind boggling.
Right. That they that there's not comedians.
And I'm sure there are. There has to be a small list.
Don't you think? Yeah, I think the list.
I think the list is too.
The list is too small. Yeah.
And and and too many people are too afraid of I don't know.
I guess what happened there and it was just like one thing is going to be
pulled out and their career is going to be over, I guess. Right.
You know what I think? I think they I bet what we don't know about
is that I wonder if they aim way big.
Like you always hear they want Dwayne Johnson.
Yeah. And then maybe they try that for four months and then it falls apart.
And then they have to scramble.
And then like people who actually would be good at it are not available
or they have to go to like their third choice on the I bet they lose a lot of time
pursuing. That's why Hathaway and Franco happened is that they were trying
Timberlake for a while. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Which would it because the whole idea was like who do young people like
like last time it was Steve Martin and Alec Baldwin, which was good also.
Like that's a strange calculate.
Then the next year they just completely flipped.
I think the extra was Billy Crystal.
Like, who cares? Oldest, oldest thing.
Oldest back. Oldest new.
Yeah. Oh, good.
Well, I have a clip
from a way that the ceremonies used to begin,
you know, which was everyone arriving while a narrator
named who you're seeing.
I love those.
And I I forgot how much I liked them.
And then I discovered a moment where I'm like,
well, this is a thing we bring up on the show.
We like like the old Disney parades or like the old clips where it's like
the fifth Mickey, like it's not the A or B voice for Mickey.
It's like the D or E voice they got. Oh, yeah.
And this is kind of just one of those unscripted moments.
Jordan, if you can bring up it's labeled 1996.
And this is they're loading people in.
The interviewer who is going so fast is Oprah Winfrey.
This is not current, like last 10, 20 years, Oprah,
where she is sitting down and thoughtfully slowly conducting.
She is rapid fire going like, who are you?
What are you wearing? What are you here for?
You know, that sort of thing.
And she is talking to
Nicole Kidman and her then husband.
Well, she's just talking to Nicole Kidman. OK. OK.
Hello, Mr. Kidman. How are you?
To die for. That's what you look like tonight.
Just to die for. And you were.
What do you think?
You're presenting.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, my goodness.
Introducing babe.
Introducing babe. Yeah.
How do you feel about that?
For the listener, Tom Cruise is back here saying nothing.
Of course you do. Yeah.
Love this choice of colors.
Hasn't been acknowledged. Oh, thank you.
So he's Tom Cruise standing there.
He's got the biggest Cheshire grin on his face the whole time.
At one moment, he had turned to a bandstand to wave.
And you just hear dozens of people scream in excitement
because one of the most famous women in the world has waved to them.
By the way, he has not been named on camera.
Yeah. No acknowledgement.
And but my favorite thing is that a very relatable, very human moment.
He doesn't know where to stand.
It's like he doesn't know where to go.
Well, they organize these.
Now these things are little sets and you have marks and everything.
Yeah. It's a whole like geography is like they know exactly where they're moving people.
And in some of the other footage, you can see people arrive
and suddenly like jump and wave to someone in the press crowd
in a very elegant gown.
And it's it's clearly Joan Rivers.
But that she used to be like the big exciting part of the pre-show coverage.
But this footage was so funny because Oprah Winfrey is just talking to Nicole Kidman
and clearly wants to talk to Nicole Kidman.
But it's just an odd run of questions.
Like you're here to present, babe.
She's like dissing. I mean, it's a kind of a diss.
There's no way she doesn't recognize Tom Cruise.
And then the very last question is, I have never seen you in that color.
Like she's like commenting on the purple dress.
Is this why Tom would later go on a jump on her couch in an angry manner?
You know what? I'm going to get your attention.
I'm getting it now.
On this show, Mama Needs a Movie that I do.
We recently talked about Interview with a Vampire with Alan McCloud.
And I was reminded of this is this is babe.
This is 95 in 94.
Tom Cruise went on Oprah and Oprah was like, I don't like this movie.
Oh, she said she showed the movie to some whatever.
They screened the movie for her.
And the audience or whatever.
She was like, I didn't like the movie.
I walked out and prayed with my friends in the lobby.
Really?
Oh, I think there was an I think that might be awkward.
Oh, this is all tied together now for me.
Oh, OK.
This is key.
They later made up with the couch.
But I think that might be post Interview with a Vampire awkwardness.
Wow.
That's really fascinating.
Yeah.
Wow.
Which seems so wrong.
That adds another level to it.
I just could not get over him just walking right through between the two of them.
And then just it's just a big grin after he waves.
And everyone just seems a little uncomfortable.
Like everyone and Oprah is not doing a good job.
That thing where you talk into the mic and then hold it over to someone.
Yeah, you're not supposed to go like, so funny.
Yeah.
Like, this is so beneath Oprah to be doing this.
But all three of them are such like longtime professionals.
It's just a weird like pick up.
It's just a weird moment.
Sure.
Wow.
Well, it was saved by the presence of Martin Landau, which drove the audience.
Martin Landau.
And that brought the ratings up.
The stern face of Martin Landau.
Oh my goodness.
There's a little more Landau to come potentially.
You might even see if you can spot a Landau later.
Let me get to another thing that, Ryan, that you brought in, which let's go back to Crystal
and to jump around.
And this will take us to the 2004 Oscars because we've talked about the opening numbers,
but we have not talked about the opening films where he felt very revolutionary at the time.
That he's inserting himself into all that was like a new in his bag of tricks.
That was a new trick.
I feel like in the Titanic year, which made that one big too, that he's in Titanic.
He's talking to the guy who drops off at the top.
And I feel like the first few were great.
But then this one 2004 were getting a little dicey, I feel.
Yeah.
And then they'll continue to be dicey after that.
Well, yeah, this was I was searching for in particular 2000 because that was the year
that he did an American beauty parody.
And that has been that scrubbed.
That's really.
Wow.
Good luck finding that one.
But this is 2003.
This was the movies of 2003.
So Lord of the Rings was the big movie and they kind of cut it, I think, more in a trailer
form.
This is probably this is directed by Troy Miller of Dakota Pictures up the street.
Yeah, this is I think this is from the ceremony that year.
Yeah, and this is I just I cut it down to what I feel like are the crucial moments,
the moments that hold up the best.
So here's the highlights of the 2004 opening.
I must control.
You must.
They are counting on you.
That's funny.
I haven't been to the Oscars since they were taken over by the evil wizards.
You mean the orcs?
No, the Weinsteins.
He's blind in one eye, but I ain't deaf.
Oh, no.
2004 blackface.
Now we're in the rings.
Nothing would stop his journey back home.
Stop this war.
Shame on you hobbits.
Shame on you.
This is a fictitious war.
This Lord was not elected by the pocket.
Michael Moore shows up to be crushed.
Yeah, that'll show him for wanting a war to end.
Yeah, give me some advice.
Light him up, Bill.
And Jack hands the magic sunglasses, the magical sunglasses.
This has several endings, I feel.
Light him up.
And then he puts them on.
Kill him, baby.
Is it kill him, baby?
Light him up, kill him, baby.
Keep it all in, Troy.
Keep every...
I'm going to give you a lot of options.
Keep them all in.
Keep it all in.
Keep that steady cam spinning and spinning.
What's that contraption you're writing around on there?
It looks pretty cool.
That's a segue.
Interesting.
This is full disclosure, and I'm not going to say anything here,
but there's a friend of ours, a friend of all of ours,
who worked on this exact opening.
Oh.
Who might be listening and worked on this and is flashing to a lot of memories,
and I am not in a position to tell their stories,
but I just want to broadcast this message that if you ever want to tell the stories
about the 2004 opening with Sammy Davis Jr. and the magical sunglasses,
we would hope that you would consider us to be the venue should you decide to go public.
And you're not talking about Jack Nicholson.
All right, fine.
He started listening after we showed all those pictures.
With him and the hoagie in the boat.
Yeah, with him and the hoagie.
That happened last week.
He really likes that.
So he's like, I love the attention, guys.
Thanks for remembering your love.
Finally, nobody's building me up these days.
Yeah.
By the way.
Light them up, good boys.
Jack Nicholson, primo seats at the 2012 Oscars and those 1970 Fred Astaire Oscars.
Always.
That's the thing.
We love it.
Jack's in the front.
It is fun when Jack's in the front.
It is exciting.
Yeah.
I won't lie.
He ain't going to be in the front no more.
When the days are over.
Yeah, that's true.
Mike, do you want to throw anything in?
Oh, yeah.
I know you brought a couple clips.
So both these clips, I think.
So what I like about the Oscars, especially at this era of the Oscars, like 80s ish, is that
Hollywood has changed, but the Oscars hasn't.
That's something that kind of is over now, but there's still obviously the music.
They want musical.
They want some schmaltz.
But I feel like when I'm watching some old clips from 80s, I go, what the hell?
This guy's alive?
And then especially when they're talking about certain movies.
Let's start with Jordan, the file named Liberace.
This is 1982.
And I was watching the 1982 Oscars.
We are so far into punk.
We're like beyond punk now.
Well, right.
So much has changed culturally.
Right.
And movies have changed.
And we're still doing.
I've read this over metal as in.
Yeah, I've read, you know, I've read movies change in 1969.
I've read the book, Easy Rider, Raging Bull, whatever.
Yes, the rebel.
I read the book.
But it was of the celluloid back lot.
It's 82 and Liberace is going to play a medley of all of the scores of the movies of the year.
Light them up.
So let's play this.
Just a little bit of it, just because I like seeing Liberace.
So he's played a little intro.
He does a little joke up here.
The theme from Rads.
Thank you very much.
Well, I've done my part for motion pictures.
I've stopped making them.
That joke goes pretty well.
The writer of that screenplay, he's gone back to writing books.
His name is Irving Wallace.
No applause.
What?
Smatter applause.
He's just rolling through it.
I never stopped attending them.
In fact, ladies and gentlemen, I'm enchanted by the music.
1982.
I think it's consistently the most original music written today.
Mr. Conti, will you help me remind everyone of this year's live comedy?
Bill Conti.
Oh, yeah.
Bill Conti, a lot of years.
Beginning with Chariots of Fire.
Well, that's cool.
I mean, it's cool.
I like it.
And I don't have the full...
You'll listen a little bit of this.
Listen a little bit of this, but then Liberace is an awesome piano player.
It's nice for him doing this.
This is good.
It's cool.
And then he does all of these.
This is the year Angolden Pond is nominated.
iconic score.
So I don't know.
From Angolden Pond.
I mean, this rules.
I love this.
The titular song by Joe Strummer.
So you could stop playing it.
And then he does...
Stop making sense.
I mean, I love it.
But yeah, again, it's just like it's funny because he's old school Hollywood, but it's 82.
Can I do one from 82?
Since we're talking about that.
Oh, yeah.
This is Ryan, actually.
And another thing that I just think is good.
This is from...
Oh, what did I call it?
Did I call it Sheena Easton?
This is a performance of the Bond song for Your Eyes Only.
One of my favorite.
It could be my favorite Bond song.
And they...
Ryan, as you put it, this is a rare occasion.
This is just the Oscars turn into a stunt show.
This is close to a stunt show as I've ever seen it be.
There's a little bit of song, but then things get real stunty.
I wonder who produced it.
Oh, yeah.
And you got the real henchman, by the way.
I don't know.
I am not a Bond enough person to...
Oh, yeah.
The old...
Richard Keele.
He's the big tall guy.
What a gown.
Sheena.
Morgan Discoey here in 82.
Yeah.
A car pulls up on stage.
Is it Bond?
Who is it?
Well, it's a dancer.
He does a kick.
Maybe that's...
I guess it's...
Later you find out it's Bond, but he's in an orange jumpsuit.
It's weird.
He stabs someone with a sword.
James Bond and his fucking sword.
Lasers!
That's the same laser from...
The RoboCop.
RoboCop.
Guitar wailing.
James Bond.
And it looks like the universal The Cone in the Barbarian stunt
show.
It looks so much like that.
It's multi-tiered.
Whoever produced 82, I got to hand it to them.
I like both of these things.
When was the last time a fake punch was thrown at the Oscars?
I don't know.
We know the real one.
I know.
We know the real one, but I just want to know...
When was the last time a wrestling...
You say a worked punch.
Yeah.
They don't pull punches.
I think they did stop doing this kind of thing.
Strong?
Yeah.
I think everyone would like it.
It's a bit like we're going to just do...
The Avengers are going to fight on the...
The Avengers should fight.
None of them are famous.
It's all just generic dancers.
It's just dancers.
Dancers are just pretending to fight with big high kicks.
Just get the Rockettes to dress as the Avengers
and have them high kick each other.
People would like it.
Did you have another one, Mike?
Yeah. Let me go quickly.
It's, I believe, 1987 and I was looking at some lists for things.
I was just looking up bad Oscar moments.
And the intro to 1987, which I had to do a little hunt for,
and I found it pretty easily.
Again, sort of the juxtaposition of the movies that came out
versus wanting to do a big Hollywood number
of something that would be in the 40s or something.
So I'll let this unfold.
There's a lot of elements that I enjoy,
but you'll be able to tell pretty quickly
which ones I like.
So there's the dancers.
Star Trek 4 logo.
And they're dancing on the movies that came out this year.
And they're appearing behind him.
So you have to listen to some of these.
The fly.
The fly is in the background as they're dancing like it's an old school.
So listen to the, they'll start singing soon.
It's Anna and her sisters in the back.
Anna.
Platoon.
Platoon is Salvador.
OK.
And they're like, these dancers are like,
they're like dressed like newsies or something,
and they're shimmying and they're big high kicks.
And we love platoon.
So here we go.
Here comes Dom DeLuis!
Telly Savalas!
Sloppy Telly!
I cleaned up for the big night!
Pat Morita!
Yeah!
Wow!
Does it seem a bit under-rehearsed?
Yeah!
This is a guys and
dolls reference.
This is like Walter Mapp out singing
a regular song.
Famously!
I'm a man of two
and platoon and got
blue velvet and salvador
Star Trek 4!
I want some more!
El Salvador!
And I'm here and this is Thursday
here!
This is 1987!
This isn't
1965!
This is 1987! Decades after
the Brando Sinatra
guys and dolls.
Maybe there was a revival.
Blue velvet came out this year!
The only
thing wrong with this is you shouldn't open
with a show stopper.
How do you top it?
We should have thought of that for
Billy Crystal. He would do
you got your western front, it's all quiet
here,
and the Germans are running in with diarrhea.
She's tar!
That
is a song that you can
if you look on YouTube you can find a
million like high school productions of
guys and dolls. And that is an
opening number.
That's like a great search to do.
Were you in guys and dolls ever?
No I was not in guys and dolls ever.
Unfortunately. But that is
very fun that people have cut
compilations together where you can just find
that element of the song.
Because it's watching 15 year olds in
ill fitting suits try to do the
three people singing slightly
different things at once.
It's very similar to
Dr. Deluise.
You gotta get
telly. It's 1987.
Who do we
gotta see?
I found that clip in there for some reason
like a browser closed.
And then I was like searching for it.
And I found
the opening when the hosts come out.
And I go well Cheryl Ladd
and William Shatner hosted the Oscars
this year? And then I went oh wait this is a Golden Globes
show.
I was like when did William Shatner host the Oscars?
Oh okay. Golden Globes.
Got it.
That goes to show you though what Billy Crystal
that's a really good context of
the Billy Crystal thing though.
Of what it was reactionary
of what it was reacting against.
So when Billy Crystal showed up and did what was
essentially an ironical version of that
it was
like a funny parody version.
You forget that
context. I recently
rewatched the first one or the second one
and he did couch it as like
I know you don't want one of these big
musical numbers. It's so
annoying. He did that for like three years.
And I think when younger people look at it they're like
oh that's corny. He's doing like
a medley and like no he's
doing a parody of what was
persistent on the Oscars for
many years. You have no idea
how bad it was. Yeah. Which maybe
takes us into the
big ones that are remaining. Oh yeah.
Are from 1989.
And
are we going to move on to
89 because we need to spend a little
time in 89. Oh yeah.
I have something for the end but I'll
save it for the end. Okay sure.
So
89.
So I mean I don't need
to say the whole context. One thing
that happened in 89. The context
is this is not the worst thing that had.
Although that's up for debate because
Ryan you put this on your list.
I'm honored to have apparently exposed you
to this one. You didn't show this to me first.
And your argument
was this is the listeners might know
where this is heading. Like what are they saving
as the worst thing that ever
happened on the Oscars. You might
know. But this is a solid
candidate. You said maybe this is worse.
This is more skin crawling to you.
This is the most
oozy.
Like you talk about your hair
standing up. This is the hair standing up for me.
I think I've ever seen on any
award show. Yeah maybe
ever. Yeah
this is the clip
is called Stars of Tomorrow.
And this happened deep into the show.
And these people are introduced as maybe
the future winners
of Academy Awards. The sequence
starts with Blair Underwood and
Holly Robinson who by now we know
for the many Oscars they've won
as have everyone in this segment.
It actually is a high percentage.
There are a lot of people in this who've done
great things. It's not bad.
It could be a much lower number.
You maybe could have forgotten about all of
these people.
But wait was there one more. Oh the only
other piece of context. I've tried to be a little
like sparing with these clips and these
ins and outs. But this one I'm like I
think you have to just sit in it
and deal with it. Maybe we'll cut it off. And if you can't
take any more. Okay we'll tap out. Yes please.
Are you going to show the intro?
Yeah. Oh wait well not the people
not Bob and Lucille.
Okay well that's a little bit important
that Walter Mathau comes out and introduces
Bob Hope and Lucille Ball who are
about as legendary as anyone
is at that time. And then they introduce
this. They get an intro
a legend introduces two
legends who then set
up this. Let's
hit it.
Someday I'll be the one who walks up here accepting the prize.
And he's at a podium where you would accept the Oscar.
Someday my Oscar's come home.
I don't know who Holly Robinson is. She can sing.
Is she Holly Robinson Pete now?
Oh god. And I forget
sitcoms, big TV shows.
And now there's dozens more.
Like Joey Fisher later from Ellen.
Hey little spry guy. Keith Kugen.
Jackie Kugen's
grandson.
Wow. I just realized that.
He's from Adventures in Babysitting.
Tyrone Power Jr.
It's not the people themselves. It's this number.
Ricky Lake.
Spangly jacket and hat.
I got some Alora Harden.
Who's that busting those Michael Jackson
moves? Is it Michael?
Oh, Cory.
Cory.
Still wearing that jacket.
I made it up through that.
I mean Blair Underwood and Malora Harden have worked quite a bit.
But this is such a
weird pressure to put on someone.
It's nothing to do with the actors.
Yeah.
It's everything to do with who put it together.
Like what jokers put this
song together? Well according to
Lucille Ball at the beginning,
it's Marvin Hamlisch, then the
winner of several Oscars.
What did Marvin Hamlisch
do?
Big ones. Way we were.
Yeah.
Fred Ebb wrote the lyrics, the lyricist of
Cabaret in Chicago
and the song New York, New York mentioned
earlier. Well, I'll say.
Major cred. What I will say about this number
is that it's not a good
song. And there is a, you can tell
literally by the progression of
notes and the idea that Ricky Lake
and Julie Fischer are on
a stage singing a song that's like
ra-ta-ta-pa-pa-pa-da-ta-ta-pa-du-da-da
or like
da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
That's bad.
That's not a good, I'm sorry
Marvin, that's not
Rat Packers should not be singing
that style
of like and Hollywood
tonight will find me here on the
stage.
It's just not a
good song.
Skin crawling moment for me is
it was in that clip when Ricky Lake says
the word statu-etter
I'm a statu-etter
I hate things like that
like made up words and Broadway
song. Oh that is
so lame.
There's a lot of nepotism on
that stage. Let's face it. Tyrone
Power Jr. is there.
Eddie Fischer's daughters or So-and-So's daughters
It's like two Eddie Fischer daughters.
It's like if the New York Times
NEPO article were
instead of an article it was a
stage show. That's what that is.
I'm gonna make, I'm gonna make the best show
you've ever, Sam Levinson
and
and and and and and they'll scream
when the idol premieres
on HBO I'll take it
over from Amy Simons and here
we go. You know what? It's not
a fix.
It's
not a fix I have. Well it is a
maybe it is a fix. If you just take
everyone's name away
from it it's not gonna make
the song sound better but
then it doesn't put like the pressure on
everyone to get the
when they don't get the Oscar in 30 years. You know what I'm saying?
Then it just looks like a stage of young
performers. That's right. Everyone's sort of
on the same level. But you don't know who
the fuck they are. I know
but then they're just sort of like nameless
actors and you're saying oh look at this
young actor like it's not putting any
pressure on the specific performers. I'm not saying
it's good. I'm just saying it might be a little
bit better unless like presumptuous
that we're just like ordaining these people.
Maybe that's what the audience saw.
Maybe the audience was like who are these talented
singers?
So it was appropriate for the people sitting
in the theater. Yes but at home
being introduced to
I would have
fired my agent if I was like
later on like Patrick Dempsey
shows it like Kristen Slater is in it.
It's a wild thing to watch at
full length but like
it's such an embarrassing way
to be presented I feel. Yeah.
Well never stopped Corey
Feldman from doing anything.
He takes the lead in this next
little part. And he was also famous then.
He was famous. He was even the star of a bunch
of movies. Maybe it's just that he said yes
and that like maybe they were getting
desperate and he's like can I do my moves?
Fine, fine, whatever.
Let's just get a little bit of like
I don't think Marvin Hamlisch wrote that into the
performance.
Plus some of your moves.
Corey we can't bring out the angels
but you can bust your moves.
You can bust my stars of tomorrow
too. Like minutes past.
This is so long. Like
a bunch. I skipped a bunch. And then
it gets to this.
Woo! Wow!
Woo!
Corey Feldman
does Michael Jackson
dances but not as good.
Work it.
I think you're going to footloose?
No. It's just no. It's generic.
Keith Coogan slides
and wiggles.
Wait, does it split through though?
Say what?
They're holding, waiting for some cue that
didn't happen.
Say what?
This is one more of these. I don't think I want to see it.
I think I'm done with stars of tomorrow.
The sword fight.
Christian Slater's in a sword. Alright, Jordan's
making us.
You wouldn't want to be seen doing
this. Do you want to be seen
watching it? I don't want to be seen watching it.
Then this guy
walks to a podium. It takes a long time.
Don't know who he is.
The Oscar goes to.
Run back, run back, run back.
Everyone at the stairs.
As fast as you can. Hurt yourselves.
They'd all spill to the bottom of the stage.
They would be the best thing that ever happened.
They should do a salute to the movies
that may win in ten years.
Oh yeah. Try to guess?
Yeah, just guess the names.
Finnean's Love.
What's that?
Guessing titles?
You'll be on the floor when I'm the star of Godfather
4.
Yeah, it's all sequels.
When I'm taking home the
for playing Rain Man again.
I'm taking home the gold for
When I play Rain Man Jr.
Rain Man
Rising. Definitely
be great.
Amazingly, this is not
the worst or
longest musical number
involving a low brother
in this year's Academy Awards.
Because now we go to
the inevitable where else could it be?
And they've had a lot of chances to do
something worse. They've done things that are more
notorious and
stranger and slappy.
But they have not done anything this
crappy. And it is
of course the
Snow White sequence.
Have we all had experience
with this?
You can't not run into it.
I feel like mostly in
montages. I don't know
if I've ever seen a big chunk of it.
It's like it's
War and Peace.
I've seen it all.
I've seen Red Sea Pieces.
Spin on the lid. Spin in the queue of crap.
I studied it in college.
My thesis was on it.
I was showing the big
ones. This one.
I've seen a lot of Tar movies and this one.
I'm waiting to show it to my child.
Let's just
dive right in.
We can do more context.
Let's just see what the viewers saw.
First we're in the
lobby. We're outside the Oscar Theater.
And then Army Archered.
A reference no one's had to know for the
last 30 years.
To their credit
was well known as
he's the guy that
introduced people.
He greeted you.
He was a variety writer.
He was a variety writer. When I first
moved to LA the first celebrity
I saw when I was living in Westwood
going to UCLA was Army Archered.
I saw him at a screen. I went to
the movies. I saw Nurse Betty.
Three months after
it came out and Army Archered was like a
row behind me.
It actually
distracted me. I was like
Army Archered. What happened with me and Armin
and Andre? We're sitting behind us.
If I cough weird he might put it into
a review. Oh no.
What if I end up at the
star?
So
he's in the lobby
of the theater and
he introduces the special guest who
is Snow White. Let's see the first
one.
And now ladies and gentlemen here's one of the great
legends of Hollywood. She's back with us tonight.
Miss Snow White.
Good evening. Oh good evening Mr. Archers.
It is so exciting to be here tonight.
I'm a little late though.
Can you tell me how to get into the theater?
That's easy Snow.
Just follow the Hollywood
stars.
Follow the Hollywood stars?
Oh! Follow the Hollywood stars!
A couple of star costumes
walked by her and then the stage
is full of them. This is what would be
like a high school fashion show.
89.
Wait did I leave in
the stars? Did I leave in her talk?
I guess I don't have her.
Then Snow White comes
in and
walks through the front
row, like the first couple rows where the big
stars are and she sings
to this. She sings an amended version
of I Only Have Eyes For You. Yeah.
She's bothering
the Glyne close.
She wasn't ready to twerk yet.
Exactly.
She was nervous back then.
Even the twerking she was freaking out because she wasn't sure if someone was going to appear
at the ceremony and start singing
to her.
She was trying to distract everyone.
It was a panic move.
She's singing to
Robert Downey Jr.
and Tom Hanks
and Michelle Pfeiffer.
And
according to this woman's
recollection, Eileen
Bowman, the actress,
who is a complete unknown.
She's never done anything on television.
This is her first time on television
we're watching and it's this.
And she has to go face to face with all the biggest
stars in the world. And she
was very nervous but she got to the
stage and she saw her friends
who were the dancers who were the stars
and she thought maybe I will have some fun.
And she tried to take Michelle Pfeiffer's
hand who gave her this look like
get the fuck away from me.
And refused the hand.
And she realized uh oh this is not
going to work and I have 11
minutes to go.
She goes down the aisle.
There is one person who is
very sweet and nice to her and that is
Martin Landau.
Which like just holds
her hand and oh
which is in keeping with things
I've recently heard about Martin Landau.
I'll see you later.
I'll see you after the show.
You have time to write your number down. I know you're doing a thing.
But um anyway
maybe now I just
that's what the viewer got without
context. So the viewer is
baffled. Why is Snow White, who is
this? Why is it Disney Snow White
but who is playing? It's like at a theme park where
who would this you don't know who the
actress generic person is playing.
The greater context here
is that this is the year that
Alan Carr produced.
70's 80's mega producer.
Did a lot of musicals.
Did Grease.
Great. Grease.
Did this Village People movie.
There was a massive bomb at the time.
Can't stop the music. I've been in Alan Carr's
home. What? Really?
Formerly owned by Alan Carr because
I've been in Brett Ratner's home.
He bought the
home owned by Alan Carr. Has an
underground disco.
He's filled with all his stuff.
He has like Clockwork Orange props?
Yeah he has a collection of props including
the phallus from Clockwork
Orange. He says it was real. Actually
now I'm doubting that. Not anything about it.
He might have been lying.
Anyways that was a weird thing of its own because
because
Ratner was
thought he could produce it.
I think at the time when I saw him in his
home he was trying to get Eddie Murphy to host
SNL.
He had that ability that he was enough
of the Murphy whisperer. He thought he was like
a Murphy whisperer. So he was trying to get Eddie Murphy
to. I can talk about this now because I don't
hope to never see Brett Ratner again.
Let's all
hold his arms. Listeners too.
Let's all just hold hands through the podcast
space. That's kind of the inspiration
for it follows. You just in the
distance see a fuzzy Brett Ratner
following around. You're like oh I hope I didn't
see that again.
But yeah he was like he was like I can get Eddie
to you know Eddie's going to host SNL for a
Tower Heist or whatever they had done.
And then that didn't
happen. And so when years later it was
rumored or they were basically
set up I was like this isn't going to happen.
The chances of this happening.
Anyway but it was all Alan Carr's house.
Wow. So he had been
and his Oscars fell apart. So he
it was the curse of Carr.
Exactly.
There's a car curse. And not
a car scene.
So that's Alan Carr.
Oh well
that's good Conti. Yeah.
He's deep in party mode here.
He was like a he was a party guy. I think he
was a manager. Hosted a lot of part work
with Hugh Hefner.
So in addition to being a big producer
of stage and screen
everybody knew him from
parties. So it just made sense
that and he
in taking over the Oscars he actually
said he what he said was I don't want
it to be one of these boring stodgy affairs
like we've been having lately. Meaning
all the ones we've just been watching
the year before was Robo
Coffin at
2009 in Peewee. That was a boring
year. Alan Carr's mind.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The fascist
robot showed up. No thanks.
Let's party. Come on. We need
glamour. We need elegance.
And that's what I'm going to do.
And we need the longest musical
number ever attempted on live television.
Yes. It goes. Yeah.
OK. We've all watched the entire. I mean it's almost like
if we really wanted to punish ourselves we
could just watch it and do commentary.
Do we really want to. We're adults.
We have been a lot of lives
talking for a while. Yes. Yeah.
No I'm not suggesting it.
But that's really the way to experience
the pain. But I kind of I've called
I think it's also what's bad about it is that
like there are as we have seen
almost every year the musical number is
bad. But
what's unique about this
Alan Carr produced thing which I really
do think the
the burden falls on him. I don't think
it's Snow White. I don't think it's Rob Lowe. I don't think it's
Eileen. What's her
name. Bowman Bowman. She was
a young probably talented person
Vincent Price and Coral
Brown. It's a price and Coral Brown. Certainly
not. It's not Roy Rogers and Dale Evans.
I'll tell you that much. They just sit
and enjoy. By the way probably the last
time I saw their appearance they
any of those people ever made on the Oscar stage.
Oh yeah sure. Yeah. The last round of applause
they got was in this thing.
Merv Griffin also comes in.
Merv Griffin's doing a whole singing number.
But I think what it is
it's that you sit
just when you think it's going to end it goes
for another three minutes and just when you
think it's going to end it goes for another three minutes
and just when you think it's going to get it goes for another
three minutes. There are different movements of it.
It's like a sweet
it's a Russian nesting doll.
It really is that there's like
sets within sets within sets
which now we're doomed to do as we
describe it here at the end of the episode.
OK you said some of the things
that happen.
She makes some stars
very uncomfortable and then
is reminiscing about times in old
Hollywood. And the reason any of
this is happening is because Alan Carr saw a
show called Beach Blanket Babylon
in San Francisco. Big
campy show that involved that was this
it was like a tribute to the 40s and Snow White
takes you through different 40s
scenes. He's like I'm doing that.
We're opening the Oscars with that
which none of none of us know that
like this is the viewer
is like has no sense.
A viewer I was trying to really
context I was trying to put myself in the mind of a
1989 viewer. The viewer thinks this
is Disney. They know Snow White
from one thing which is Disney. And this
seems like a disneyfication of the
Oscars before Disney has
had its ups with this is early
in 1989. Little Mermaid
doesn't come out till the end of 1989.
So Disney's still in the doldrums
of like Disney's not like cool
like now if Shrek
came out not Shrek that's not Disney.
But now if like there was an incanto opening
or something people go oh it's cool.
We're not a big hit song
or yeah yeah yeah. This is not the
Snow White is no longer cool at this moment.
No and it's clearly it is so much
the Disney Snow White. The character
and the voice absolutely.
And apparently and the costume
is from a Hollywood Boulevard rental
place because it's a little
off. They put rhinestones
on a Hollywood Boulevard rental
costume. So she's
recalling her Hollywood glory
days and then suddenly
the curtain opens and you're at the coconut
grove and
the ambassador ballroom
and then of course who
else would be there the emcee but
Merv Griffin of course
and he's of course singing I've
got a lovely bunch of coconuts. We know
we know he did that song.
That's not just a song you faintly recall
from like preschool or something.
1989. 1989.
Merv Griffin. How many of
those locations. Not the Emmys either.
Were standing. How many
of those located the coconut grove
and the ambassador
the ambassador.
That's yeah.
Merv Griffin's notably
so he's a talk show host.
Talk show host producer. Producer of all the game shows.
And it was considered kind of
like a lame guy.
Like a schmaltzy guy in the 70s.
Let alone
89. But a nice guy.
But still 89.
What? Why?
It has no association
with movies that I am aware of.
By the way when I first watched this I was delighted
to see him. I'm not saying I wasn't.
I know that Mike Carlson was delighted
to see Merv Griffin. But I don't think Alan Carr
did it for me 30 years later.
Unless
it is. Yeah it's a tenant.
Unless it's a simulation.
Which we've been talking about lately.
We'll have to ask Mr. Slap.
By the way
Ambassador Hotel notorious for where
Robert Kennedy was killed.
That's what that is.
Still not the worst thing that's
happened.
Not demolished until 2005.
Yikes.
Very much what you're saying.
So what now? Who now?
Merv Griffin? Huh? And then he
introduces a bunch of people. All the stars.
Like alright Alice Faye.
I'm going to be honest I don't know who Alice Faye is.
Dorothy Lamour.
I kind of know that name.
Somebody on our Patreon.
Cicharise is in there.
I don't really know Cicharise.
I'm going to be honest. Somebody on our Patreon
was suggesting this before Club 3
but we brought it up to the big stage.
And in their suggestion they said
it's a bunch of introductions of movie
stars only Jason would know.
Cicharise probably the most. Cicharise
has a big dance number in
Singing in the Rain. And the
apocryphal story
is that like oh well she her legs
were famously insured for a million
dollars. Oh and she's the one who's like
okay in this. She does like a big kick.
Yeah she did a lot of kicks.
And she's still got it.
But most of the people as they start
rehearsing this thing. And Alan Carr
has it in his head and all of the greatest
stars will be there. But he's picturing them
30 years ago. Merv Griffin at his
height.
Okay if this were 60's Merv Griffin
no problem. Oh my god.
It would have been cooking.
The audience would have been turned on.
We've got Merv Griffin centuries.
If you've got Vincent Price.
Vincent Price is here.
Vincent Price hot off Dr. Goldfoot
in the bikini machine. Now we're
talking.
But 89 Price?
No way.
So they have to start like okay maybe we can't
have all of these people be in the musical
number. Maybe we say their names and they wave
politely. They stand up from a table
and leave. Assuming that they're able to
do that. Well you need the Coconut Grove audience.
I mean who's celebrities have to
be enjoying the Merv Griffin performance.
All of it. Roger's,
Vincent Price is crazy. Sorry
is it Vincent Price's wife?
Well there's a clip that I
think it's on a Gilbert Godfrey podcast where Michael
McKeon is doing. They're doing dueling
prices. And they both have very
good prices. And Michael McKeon points out that
Vincent Price always. Vincent Price
I don't know if I'm wrong to say
probably a gay gentleman.
But was married to this woman Coral Brown.
And the speculation would be that he'd always
say her full name and title.
And the actress, my
married to the actress Coral Brown.
You could say it like that.
The woman, the female actress.
Is there a sexualism I...
Right.
So yeah I don't know
a movie or anything. All I know
her is from this clip. So this is a little
like can my wife
come along on the...
That was I believe his speculation.
Now who is your wife again?
The actress. Coral Brown.
That's what
Michael McKeon says. I don't know
for sure. But
yes. So
all the big stars. To get Vincent
Price you gotta bring Coral
Brown. Right.
We've talked about
Vincent Price being on the
Horror Hall of Fame
awards.
Which would be after this.
So Coral Brown would not be with
him. I'm not sure when she died.
But he at least...
He would go somewhere without Coral is really what I'm saying.
I think. As long as he was
being honored in some way. Yeah. For the
Horror Hall of Fame he went to his backyard.
That's right. Yes.
He was via... I think he went in person one year.
Okay. He was there one year.
But yes. His backyard for one of them.
Produced by Alan Carr. I think that's what he had to do
after this. He took over the Horror Hall of Fame.
But
hey. They realized it
can't just be a bunch of old fogies.
We gotta get some young blood
in this number.
And that is when Snow White
meets her blind date. Let's go to Snow White
too.
Meet your blind date, Rob Lowe.
This is so wild.
I just watched it
a couple hours ago again.
Oh Mr. Lowe.
I'm such a fan.
Really?
Processing him being part of it. Beyond what's
about to happen.
I mean...
No.
Now the performance here.
The way he chooses to sing
is so...
What is that goodbye?
And then...
Okay.
This is a year
after the thing too.
Actually. Well it's a year after
the thing happened.
The thing is not public.
So it's about...
But they don't know the camera rolling line
that he ends on here?
He's still in movies.
He wants cameras to be rolling.
That's an often confused thing.
It was
public right
soon after this which was part of the curse
of the sequence.
About like six weeks after. Which in 1989 time
is like six days after.
He already
took such a big career hit from
this. And that adds
to it.
I...
And if we aren't afraid of being struck down
by the Doughboy's curse we can talk about
Rob Lowe a little bit.
We can't talk about Rob Lowe?
We'll try.
We can't talk about...
I mean...
The most insane...
The voice...
I've thought about...
Grubby and sleepy...
Forever... And the voice crack
on it. The delivery is
so... I...
You can't... I mean... I...
I don't know if he ever thought he could sing.
It doesn't feel... It feels like he was asked arbitrarily.
As with Richard Pryor. It's like doesn't matter.
Big star. He's gonna be great. A big star
can probably sing right?
And then he's just thrown to the wolves here.
Yeah. I mean you could talk... Again people can talk
sing. There's like...
You can get away with a lot.
As long as maybe you're not doing a weird voice.
Dudley Moore I feel like...
Richard Pryor following Dudley Moore
already doing the talk sing.
That's unfair to Richard Pryor. You can't...
You can't let everyone do the...
Yeah. You gotta throw some other
ringers in there.
Don't have three talk singers in there.
Yeah. Sure.
To Rob Lowe's... I think Rob Lowe can sing.
Some.
The thing I read about this today was that Rob Lowe
did this performance
and then went backstage and was mortified.
I believe Rob Lowe is on the record
for telling this story. He was on some show.
He went backstage and Lucille Ball
was there to comfort him.
And held his hand and said I really like your singing.
A young man. I didn't know
you could sing so well.
He had a blue smoke in his face accidentally.
Because remember she introduced Stars of Tomorrow
right at the beginning of this.
She's had her own debacle for the evening.
By the way that's the only universal character
I want to tell me that she's proud of me more than Optimus Prime.
Oh my dear boy.
If I could go in a tiny room with Lucy
and it's filled with smoke.
What a singer you are.
You're wonderful.
Gary thinks you're wonderful too.
Who's Gary?
Gary Morton.
Gary Morton. My new guy.
My new husband. I'm not so thrilled with him.
But he's nice.
Michael you're doing a great job.
Were there any
Ornette's children in the Stars of Tomorrow
segment?
Oh I don't think so.
Too old maybe.
They were the Stars of Tomorrow in the 60s.
Yeah in the 70s.
Here's Lucy it already happened.
They missed their chance.
He sat with Lucy
for an hour. They held hands
and they talked about Hollywood
and then she passed away.
Again the car
curse. She passed away
like five six weeks later.
This was her last time on television I think.
Really?
Oh my god.
To introduce Jolie Fisher and Corey Feldman.
It was the last time she was.
Immediately after.
At this point it might bear mentioning
that I did the show Moonbeam City
for Comedy Central. Rob Lowe
was the main voice on it. Ryan Perez
was a writer for the show.
And you may recall
that maybe I
wasn't so vocal about it.
Tell me if I was. To me
when it went to. Wow.
To me
when it went to series
when I realized we were going to have an opportunity to fill
a lot of episodes with Rob Lowe.
Priority number one to me
became we have to get him to sing.
Being a fan of this
we have whatever reason we could possibly
find to get this guy
to sing. You in fact
wrote an episode. A fantastic
episode of the show called Cop Con.
That is full of like
themes and it's a very
prescient piece about
police brutality and police
violence. I should say so.
Check that out somewhere if you can find it.
Possibly on the way out
the door. You know it was on Pluto.
Before I came over here. The legend of Circuit
Lake. Oh there you go. Pluto TV.
They do air it. Yeah yeah.
It really means a lot to me that they air it.
You can see. Well in that
one you can see the line that you wrote which delighted me so
much. An episode that's a big tribute to
Free Jack. The Emilio Esteves. Oh yeah.
Free Jack. And that has the line
now I can free Jack
into the system and jack off
that dazzle no bag. Oh there you go.
That delight. That made me so
happy. The first time I saw it.
But anyway you wrote this episode. There was
I give you entirely the credit for like the
like the like the
weighty quality stuff in it. And I think
my main contribution my only contribution
was we should get Rob Lowe to sing
a song in it.
And I believe he sings two relatively
close back to back in the show.
He sings like a rockabilly song.
Yes. Yeah.
He sang at Rad's wedding.
Oh yes yes. He sang Cop this Town
and he sang Wed this
Bride. Which is all
on Spotify. I forgot that it was
Cop this Town. I'm very
proud. I don't know how much singing.
Rob Lowe had done since this performance.
If he sang on Perks
and Wreck I don't know it. There's not a
lot of Rob Lowe singing out there. I made
it a point. We're gonna get some time with this
guy. I make you sing in a song
a song which to tie a bunch of things together
was the song that we put in
just because I thought Brian Setzer
is stupid.
That's the song.
I'm gonna have him sing a dumb bad
Brian Setzer song.
Did it cross your mind though of like
you think you do roll it
on a river.
Oh we did.
I guess I wanted to get him into a new
bad genre. A new bad type of
songs that dad bands would play.
And
just about that experience recording
it I will say that is the number one most
fun thing I got to do
making the show. Making him sing that
song was so much fun. However I
was a little bit disappointed he was not
a worse singer.
I kind of thought I was gonna get the
grumpy and sleepy. But he's a
perfectly capable dad type
singer. I thought
he was not. I think he
I bet he was like collapsing under the pressure
of because I get 42 million
people. Oh and I
wonder what the direction was because I feel like the direction
was like you're really into her.
Like that felt like that's
where he's coming from. Yes I mean
there's a shot later on where
it's like a downbeat moment and
it's like a zoom in on him. He's looking at
her. Yes. And it's like
he's playing like in love.
This is like a dramatic moment in the middle
of a. Yes. And lust I would say.
And lust was so white. Yes.
And I feel like it. It's very
sensual. The whole thing. It's still not
as weird as when Travolta grabbed Adina
Menzel's face in that Oscars.
That's the most scary
moment I think of any Oscars.
They thought they were gonna fix it
with that. Alright this Adele Dezime
thing was weird. Let's make it right.
Let's get them together and then
can I touch your face?
Can I touch your face?
I want to
take your face.
You're so wickedly delightful.
He's like squeezing her skull.
Those are the most wonderful
nostrils I've ever put my fingers
in. It's such a mafia like
threatening.
Anyway
that is not the last of the Rob
singing because then things kick into gear.
This could have been the end of the entire
what we watched a little bit ago could have been
the end of the whole thing. That could be two whole
separate numbers already. Yes.
But Snow White 3.
I don't think he's bad.
He sounds better here I'll say
than before.
Well they also gave him a thing that is not
what he... Rockabilly
this is your genre. I figured it out.
We figured it out.
Oh boy.
But really in that part
it's less him and more these
the animated
mama.
Is there any...
Was it just meant to be like this will be
just the kitchiest only appreciated
tongue in cheek or are they thinking people are
going to really respond to this message of keeping
cameras rolling.
Hollywood's been rolling for years and we're not stopping
not tonight.
I think that makes more sense that it was in
line with like a sincere celebration
of Hollywood and also
I'm going to be an Oscar winner.
That's the skeleton key into understanding
this is that like. Oh right.
This is it. Also by the way
this is the end.
Like Billy Crystal takes over the next
year. Like this is the last one you ever got
of like the old ways.
No irony.
I think later on they said it was
kitschy but that's what feels like a cop
out. Yeah. I think
Alan Carr is like we are celebrating
we're bringing the glamour back.
It's going to be full of sparkles
and sparkles on stars that look like
the backboard to a high school
science project. Yeah.
When is the Tina Turner
version of that song come out? So it's fairly
recent I guess as far
as you know 60s.
Oh yeah.
We know she had a different but she had a newer
version. Wasn't she had a newer version of it as
a hit I think. Rollin on the river.
Am I wrong. I don't
know the ins and outs of the newer
or am I thinking of didn't she have there was a
performance or something. Am I crazy.
I don't know. Jason saved me here.
She had an 80s resurgence.
Is that what I'm thinking of. I don't know.
I don't think we're within the decade.
I'm trying to help out here. I'm trying.
It's a little bit like saying it's a
reason like people don't cover Stevie Wonder.
It's the same thing like Tina Turner is like
that's also not an easy
task. Like go sing.
Go sing that actor.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
This is meant to be like a show stopping
number. Go sing that song associated with
Tina Turner.
It's only the most dynamic performer
in the world. You guys got this.
This is your first time on television. You could do a proud
Mary. Right. You're not singer.
You very scared. Twenty two
year old who's never been on television before.
Just be Tina Turner. Go go go.
Also what made what maybe
should be said is that behind them are
tables and place settings.
But those are people who then like
in that part of it they're swaying their
heads back and forth and they have flower pots on their heads
and then they all stand up. It's like be
our guest. It's a bit
of pre be our guest. Be our guest might have
got that idea from that possibly. Yes.
Yeah. The Broadway inspiration
comes where you least expect it.
This thing this goes and goes.
And you say all right that coconut grove. All right.
Are we are we done. We don't know the coconut
grove moves away and the
revealing a Chinese theater. OK.
Now surely we must be no. Then
part of the Chinese gate moves
away and there's a
kick line and then a different part
moves away and then the
top of the Chinese theater
becomes the top of a wig
on Snow White's head.
Yeah. And it zooms out from
this and there's wowie
and the and then where else can it go
but Snow White having the biggest wig
in the world.
But then she gets covered up by
a flight of stairs that Lily
Tomlin walks down. Yes.
And by the time all this has transpired
this has been 11 minutes
of live television. This is almost
Super Bowl halftime show length
and they still have stars of tomorrow
to go. They they stopped. And by the way
Lily when Lily Tomlin walks down
she has a good joke.
Uh huh. Yeah.
This is a Bruce. This has to be
you got they got Bruce. Yeah.
The joke is
I agree to do the show if they could
only come up with an entrance.
OK. Yeah.
Pretty good joke. But on
the stairs behind her
there's like a gag where
like a guy's like somebody's
reaching for a shoe or something. It's like a
Cinderella. I don't know what it is. It's like a shoe
on the stairs. They do not convey what it is.
I think it's Cinderella.
But it's Snow White.
I think it's good.
And then there's like a
performer like Hamily like reaching
for the shoe.
And this is going this is fighting
that's the worst thing I actually think in
that number is that all
could be forgiven if she
could just come out and say hey you know what
I want an entrance or whatever.
The joke is and it keeps
going. It's like it's it's
it's it's it is cursed.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well and the car curse
unspooled through the as we said
Lucille Ball
passes away.
Watching this
performance in the theater
Jeffrey Katzenberg and Roy
Disney Michael Eisner is
attending to the parks in Orlando.
He gets on the phone to the
entire Disney legal team and says
are you watching the Oscars. Yeah.
All right. Do your thing.
Lawyer Disney lawyers stay up all
night so that they can have
at 530 in the morning a
legal document ready to review
which by that afternoon is sent
to the Academy. We are suing
you for unauthorized use of Snow White
because they did not
clear it. They did not. And they're
thinking Snow White's in the public domain and they use
it in Beach Blanket Babylon.
Well not that Snow White with those
colors and that voice.
Yeah. Yeah.
So and another bit of context
as soon
as this is over as soon as it goes to commercial
break finally after 11
minutes the very first thing it cuts to
is a Chevy Lumina commercial
which is a cross promotion with the
about to open Disney MGM Studios
theme park in which there's
Chevy Chevy Luminas are pulling up
outside the Chinese theater
and Disney characters are coming out including
the dwarfs. So
to a viewer they're like
oh Disney did that. If I'm
seeing a Disney commercial right now
surely Disney was
part of it. So they it's in the
press within 24 hours we're
suing the Academy. They have to
issue they ended up settling it. They didn't go
to court or anything. They just apologize
profusely. Frank Wells got Frank Wells
called the producer immediately.
So this guy he's on the phone
with a bit like hey how you doing Frank.
He thinks he's calling to congratulate
not so good. Disney's not happy.
So immediate lawsuit right out
the door. Then guy
hangs up the phone then gets another
all right. You hear about the letter. No what's the letter.
There is a letter going out
that's going to be in all the trades from
a group of esteemed actors
criticizing the performance.
Do you guys know. I don't know this.
OK.
This is a letter.
The 61st Academy Awards was an embarrassment to both
the Academy and the entire motion picture
industry. It is neither fitting nor acceptable
that the best work in motion pictures be
acknowledged in such a demeaning fashion.
And this letter is signed by
among other people. Julie Andrews
William Friedkin Stanley Donin
Blake Edwards
Billy
Wilder Paul Newman
and the main
person who pulled this together. Gregory
Peck. Wow.
Wow. Made a point of
we have work to do.
I've written a letter.
This
cannot stand. Wait
so. I an animated
mama. An animated mama. Bill Friedkin
Bill Friedkin
here saying
that's not how you open an Oscar
ceremony.
Wait OK. This is
independent of the Disney lawsuit. Yes separate.
It all happens with it like in one afternoon
everything unravels for this
entire production team. I mean I
feel like Mary Poppins is telling you you
suck. That hurts.
That really hurts.
Was not
practically perfect in every way. The stress
of this killed Lucille Ball.
Just watching it.
Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe she hadn't like maybe
maybe she hadn't watched the opening
really. She's like quick second of it. Found out
later. Oh I complimented that
boy. I was wrong.
Gary taped it. I was so nice to the
boy. Gary showed me the tape and
I thought I was dreadful.
And I decided to pass
away.
Gary I'm gonna die.
And all my affairs.
Gary
you're good for nothing.
As for Alan Carr
it's he like
he went into a restaurant the next day
expecting to get a standing ovation and
instead no one would look at him.
He never produced a film or a television
show again. And
the
Oscar's producer Gil Kates
many years later said
if he had just made that number shorter
I think he would still be alive today.
Oh my gosh.
I mean he's right.
He's probably right.
So the joke I made about Lucy is true.
I think so. Yes. There's a
body count. So he had to go. He basically
went into exile.
Yeah. Yeah. He was like embarrassed and
ashamed. There's a whole documentary about him.
It was apparently a huge deal when there was
he thought I want to
re-release Grease and get all the love about
Grease again. And it probably helped start
the fire which now like Grease is
eternally popular. And it was like a
meaningful thing for him. So he got like a little bit
of like glory
at the end. But like he
didn't do anything new. He was Mr.
Hollywood. Before that Billy
Wilder somehow created
a new Norma Desmond. He just
wouldn't leave his house.
I'm doing it for real this time.
So
yeah this might
be the most cursed. And now I'm worried
that something bad is going to happen to us because we talked
about it. Oh no.
I think we're fine. I mean I think it's over
it's also overstated.
I mean like it's not I think in context
it's not it is bad. It truly
is terrible. But like
Dom DeLuis and like
I mean that's two years before.
Like what are we imagine that
was 12 minutes. Maybe that's
the issue. It was quicker.
I think yeah I think that is
what it is because we have seen
performance.
I think that's the lesson to take away. There are
performances of comparable
shittiness.
But it's really just
what are you asking people to endure?
Sure.
I would have still partied at Alan Carr's
house after this.
Who gives an underground disco?
Yeah who cares. Yeah you said that about
Brett Radner says that he had a disco in his
house and that is from Alan Carr.
Wow. Yeah.
We all want that in a mansion
of ours one day.
Yes. It's a little flying
too close to the sun kind of
story. Yeah maybe
something else needs in your house. Maybe a disco
floor.
Yeah boy.
You have a brighter spot.
Well you know it turned well obviously
there are no hard feelings in the long
run between the Walt Disney Company
and the Academy because it's
aired on ABC for a long
time which the Disney Company has owned for a long
time. And
I was looking up because
for a while I couldn't find it
they were doing it this year.
They would show the Oscar broadcast
on the Main Street Opera House.
They would show that in the Main Street Opera
House on Main Street and
Disneyland. Yes. This year
what I saw they have
and they have this every year a big step
and repeat and giant Oscar statue
at the Grand Californian Hotel that
you can take a picture with
and a milkshake with a bow tie on it.
You can buy in
California Adventure. But
something actually of merit
at the Carthay Circle
Restaurant on loan
from the Walt Disney Family Museum in
San Francisco they have the
Snow White Oscar
with the little Oscars. With the seven
little Oscars. With the seven little Oscars.
So you can go see that right now
in the restaurant that is a
replica of the theater that Snow White
premiered in. That's pretty cool.
That's pretty good.
Well that's nice. But that's I don't know
that's not my Snow White.
My Snow White is a petrified
inexperienced actress who's
chased out of the business put on a
gag order to where she can't talk about
this for 13 years.
True fact also.
Really? 13 years? Yeah I think so.
Now she's spoken about it. But
yeah to me Snow
White has to be couched
in tragedy.
I mean I don't know where else
to go from here. We've fully explored
the depths of will the
will the ceremony
this year have anything
as memorable as this?
Will Michael Eisner step in somehow?
Because this is back to back. We just
on a Patreon episode discovered that Michael Eisner
put an end to a regional
Los Angeles kids show called
King Koopa's Cool Cartoons.
What? Just recently?
No. In the early 90's.
He wrote a letter to, this is again according
we talk about it on Patreon but
according to this Wikipedia one of the writers
on the show said he wrote a letter to Barry Diller
and got the show cancelled.
So we're learning just like obviously we knew he was
powerful but this man wielded so much
power and will he step in
this year is really what my question is.
Well he's expending all of his power this year
making sure those pesky crank anchors
don't show up and cause mischief.
I'll bet you. I mean
I'm just glad he left Aladdin's winter wish alone.
That's you know.
Because Ben
Verin didn't know what he was
in that production. Oh my god Ben Verin
was in it. It's so fun. I think he
was like hey everybody Disney like he
didn't know. So the whole
go back to Aladdin's
winter wish. There were
elements of it that were clearly just ripping
the Disney version off. It wasn't totally
Disney because Bruce Flange played
the widow Twanky which is a character that does
not appear in the Disney
Aladdin but Ben Verin was the
genie and he made a joke
about the Lion King
and he referenced the character Mufafa
from Lion King
and I don't think he
knew the character but obviously somebody like threw this
name at him and he just did his best and
honestly that was the most fun to see.
It was great seeing Richard Carn as the
sultan but Ben Verin
as the genie truly I was very
excited to see him.
This is Alan Carr level casting.
I mean if Carr could cast.
Well you gotta go
to the stage to get Carr level
quality now. Ben Verin was on a show called
Jubilee Zoo when I was a kid.
As mayor Ben and he had like
an animal nose and it's
terrifying but I was a big fan
from back then.
But we just should
honestly just remember it as the day
that Peter O'Toole died.
Yeah that's maybe a moment of silence
and we'll hear it.
Okay and
Ryan Perez you survived
Podcast the Ride.
Well you got it.
It's an Oscars episode you gotta have an in memoriam.
That's right. Oh yeah exactly.
But now 34 minutes of show everyone.
We're still
going. We got we reached a
down point but now we're coming back
for the best actor best actress.
Well let me be like Armie Archer and say
hey what irons do you
have in the fire. Let's exit through the gift shop.
Mr. Perez is there anything you'd like to
plug. Oh boy Armie there's so
much going on. Oh yeah no if you want to
hear me talk about movies more go over
to Mama Needs a Movie where
my co-host and Raymond talk about
movies a new movie every week.
Scott's been on the show. We got everybody's
going to be on the show you know. It's one of
another podcast to add to.
I know your podcast options are many.
But consider adding
one more movie podcast.
And some of the stars
you have coming up are crazy.
Jolie Fisher. We got Jolie Fisher.
We got
a Chad
Wood.
Ricky Lake.
They're all going to be. We got Tyrone
Power Jr. Oh geez
I was going to say I was maybe
not going to listen until you threw that one. I was waiting
for Tyrone Power Jr.
I heard Gary Morton is going to be on
this.
This is a
first turn. Pull up the logo.
There we go. Mama Needs
a Movie. And I don't know wait in what
order these things are coming out but I'm either
going to be on it sooner or just been on it.
And I'm talking about Mommy Dearest.
That's right. Oh wow.
A movie I've never seen. Should we put
that up before the Oscars or after the Oscars?
Maybe before the Oscars. Well people are
going to be thinking about Faye because
of her involvement.
Maybe and again we
all remember she got out of there fast.
She actually read the name
and then was never seen from
never seen again as opposed to Warren Beatty.
That's true. So
relevant.
She might have really been the
She read the name though.
So I don't know.
My conspiracy theory I think still stands that
maybe they
were in on it. Maybe not. Whatever.
You know what you
were saying was
the trickster Kimmel was maybe
it. But think about who's presenting
it. The ultimate criminal
Bonnie and Clyde.
The writing is there. It's all
there. You just have to look at it.
One last heist.
That might have just been an Oscars
producer who's been doing it so long
was still mad that the movie started going
when they nominated Bonnie and Clyde
that's going to took a turn.
No nice movies
for the nice people.
Well yeah well check me out on there whenever
and other episodes.
You're great and it's great and so happy to have you
for this Ryan. Thank you so much for having me.
You guys I haven't been on the show since
I was in. I would think I was
in the first 10 episodes. Yeah.
At the time I did nots Berry farm
and I legitimately thought you guys
were going to do like one park per show.
That's what I thought.
Maybe you'll do maybe you'll do like a
few more because you'll do the lands. Each
land each land will
get an episode. I never would have thought you guys
not only have you guys done a great show
you've done it now for a
such an enduring show and
I never thought you would get as granular
and as entertaining as
this. No this is neither.
It's been a great joy to watch and
listen to this show.
There's multiple episodes about nights
and white satin.
That level of that level of
I never would have thought
you guys could
do it but it's great. Thank you.
You harken back to another time like
that nots Berry farm would only get one
episode. Now we'd be like
an episode for each pie.
Each pie available.
That snuck in early. Each jam.
You got away with something.
We didn't know our pace as has become a catchphrase
from the Cars Ride. Slow down
you ain't racing yet.
We're going as
slow as we can as we roll
next week with more infinitesimal
topics. Thanks to
Jordan Katz for producing this episode.
You can watch this on the forever dog YouTube
channel. You can find us on all the socials
at podcast the ride and for three bonus
episodes every month check out podcast the ride the second
gate or get one more bonus episode on
our new tier club three.
What you're saying. We have multiple tiers
of this stuff even. You find
all of that at Patreon dot com
slash podcast the ride and it was
so great to have you and I'm you know
have getting Ryan having you back
after so long talking about all this great
stuff. I feel really high. This feels like a high
moment for me. But keep in mind
that when it's your highest moment
that's when the devil comes. You gotta watch out
you gotta watch for
I think I see something. Oh no
I think I see something. Oh no. It's
Brett Ratner. Maybe it's just Dom DeLuis.
Ah ha ha ha.
Forever
Dog
This has been a
forever dog production. Executive
produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner
Brett Baum Joe
and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
please visit forever dog podcasts
dot com and subscribe
to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get
your podcasts. Keep up with
the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team
and liking our page on Facebook.