Forever... dog.
Warning! The following podcast contains slow-moving objects, shells, and little games that gave
one of the hosts a little trouble.
This is Mario Kart Bowser's Challenge on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks that's like an unstoppable red shell
aimed at your funny bone.
Right?
I'm Scott Gardner, Sean Puchase and Sheridan.
I admittedly don't know a lot of very specific Mario Kart things, so I was like...
I wouldn't call that one very specific.
That's a pretty...
Well, you really don't if you don't know the red shell.
I know the...
I don't think it dawned on me.
Is it like that in The Ride, too, that the shells operate differently depending on color?
If you can believe it, I didn't get a good sense of what the specific shells do in the
Mario Kart Ride, which we're talking about today with our third host, Mike Carlson.
I want to explain, too.
I remember I have to cue...
I want to cue something up for pretty early, maybe in the podcast.
And then as you did the intro, for a second I kind of gave...
I was like, hmm, I give like a good nod and I forgot I was on the podcast.
I forgot I was involved in it for a half second.
I went, oh, yeah, because there was a dead space.
I'm very afraid of you to admit that.
I have had moments like that, you know.
Oh, yeah.
We've noticed yours.
Oh, jeepers, thanks.
You're usually looking, I think, at like a fact or something.
You'll be looking at your computer sometimes.
That's true.
You do go down.
You do go downward a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Well, I make the notes and then they're far too small or disorganized for me to actually
utilize sometimes.
Get that font bigger, first of all.
You're like, we can look over and you're just like mouthing like the name of like a ride
system or something.
And you're like trying to...
Or milk.
You're just trying to say milk, right?
Water coaster.
We've given you such a...
EMF ride systems.
We've given you such a neurosis on this, but you're just like, don't say milk, don't say
milk, don't say buka de bepo.
Is it pepo or bepo?
Ah, shoot.
I just said beka.
Wait, buka de bepo.
Buka de beki?
I found a new way to say that wrong.
So yeah, so it was a good remark is what I'm saying.
Great.
We're all agreed.
Did you find what you were looking for?
Yeah, yeah.
I know what it was.
Does this need to be organically woven into?
Well, I mentioned it, I guess.
I don't really know.
Feel free.
We in general...
Look, overall, we are talking about Mario Kart Bowser's challenge or as for some reason
it's known in Japan, Mario Kart Koopa's challenge.
Right.
Yeah.
Sure.
I guess he's more King Koopa there.
I don't know.
Yes, he is more known as King Koopa there than Bowser and Bowser here.
But I don't know, maybe you had a different way to intro this, but I guess I'm just going
to do it now because right up top, there's a very important thing we have to talk about.
Sure.
Because I don't like when stuff like this happens on the podcast and I have to just
put it out there and say it.
Are you doing some pennants?
Yes, I guess you could say that.
Yes.
So I just want to put...
Okay, I'm just going to make sure this is playing here.
On the last podcast, the Riot episode that was live, new, I said a statement that was
incorrect.
And I'd like to apologize for that statement.
I said that the Toadstool Cafe shared a kitchen with the Lorelaut Panda Express.
Right.
And I said it confidently.
I thought I knew it because honestly, I've heard it from two different people, two different
places.
One unsourced on Twitter, of course, and then a friend of mine who goes across the Inside
Universal Message boards and said that there is...
You did couch it as a rumor.
So give yourself that.
Okay.
You didn't say it was a rumor.
Yeah, but I said it confidently and I don't like that.
And I would like to formally apologize to the audience for misleading you.
Toadstool Cafe has a separate kitchen from the Lorelaut Panda Express and that Panda Express
has not been moved because there's some sort of a licensing agreement and they couldn't
just get rid of it blanket.
The Panda Express earned its right to still be there.
Correct.
Yeah.
So I just wanted to do that up top.
I hate to bring the show down early, but there it is.
It's brave of you.
It's manly of you.
That's the way to be a man.
Thank you.
It's a way and age to own up to it.
And just try to improve and try to be better.
Thank you.
I just don't want to be the George Santos of the show after this and then after the whole
Frank Marshall situation where I incorrectly said that he spoke at the Jurassic World
opening ceremony.
Well, you have to get ahead of these things before I get ahold of them and certainly before
Griffin gets ahold of them.
That's...
Yes, exactly.
Like me, we can handle.
If this ends up, if the ball ends up in Griffin's zone, like, oh man, if he shows up in the
group text, you're done.
He's coming here.
We're going to do a full hour on the kitchen and he's gone to the kitchen and it's impossible
to share the space.
The outlets, the electrical outlets wouldn't even make sense in the same...
There's that cord long enough to reach to keep food hot in the hallway.
I assume there'd be like a hot hallway that would keep food fresh as you walk from the
Panda Express to Toadstool Cafe.
Fundamentally, there is no way that they could share a kitchen and it would make sense.
You couldn't heat...
You couldn't make a hot hallway is what I'm saying.
That's what it requires for food.
The two locations are so far away that that hallway has to be hot or else the food...
And I know for a fact that all of these establishments, especially the Panda Express and the Lower
Lotta Universal is incredibly concerned with your food being piping hot.
Oh baby.
You're the Panda Promise.
Yes, that's right.
That's correct.
Well, I think it's appropriate that you do that, Mike, because I think there's a little
bit of making amends and a little bit of redemption, I think, that we're aiming for with this episode
in general.
And allow me to explain because this is our second episode about Super Nintendo World,
which we two weeks ago covered in a broader sense.
And now we're back to a kind of more focused on the Mario Kart ride.
And in between, almost immediately after, we got to go again to Super Nintendo World.
And full disclosure, this was with press perks.
We were part of the press and we were there for a press day.
And therefore, the crowd was cut in half, in more than half.
Into a third of what it would be.
A quarter of the preview.
Might have been a quarter.
Yeah, yeah, that actually might be correct.
So there were a lot less people.
So that is important context.
However, getting to experience this land again, but with that context, I started feeling like,
I think maybe we cut this place a raw deal because I don't know if the listener felt
this way.
But I think after we recorded, I certainly was feeling like, boy, that was a grouchy
episode that we recorded about Super Nintendo World.
That's how I felt.
And I'll ask you guys how you feel.
I don't incredibly regret it because it was very crowded and there were some difficulties
to it, but it did.
I think we came in with a lot of negativity that stayed throughout the episode.
And as soon as we were there on this other day and got to experience some of these other
things, I felt fun and positivity.
I felt what some of these other theme park bloggers and vloggers because they were all
a glow.
And here we are grouching and complaining.
But what do you think?
It's tough because we look, we do try to keep it real on this show.
OK, so sometimes, you know, I go, OK, everybody because, look, everybody wants some access.
That's nice.
I beg for access on the show regularly.
So, yeah, we want it.
But then we don't we don't always play the game at which might jeopardize that access.
Now, we've seen now Disney.
We have no hope.
We will never be on Disney's list.
No, no, no.
Who they go because you have to be 110 percent positive.
You have to be a Disney princess in terms of perkiness.
You have to be like who's who's like the most positive one, like the enchanted, whatever
her name is.
Yeah.
Is that right?
You know, everything's like you have to just be so hyper positive about it.
So we're out there.
Universal, we're on the line.
But we we still we want to be we want the sexist, but we want to be positive, too.
And I don't know.
This is all honest.
Yeah.
So so we're straddling the line there.
But also, it's like we went as civilians that day.
This was our experience.
This is how we felt.
That's a valid thing to do.
And I said, look, I said nice things.
I said some glowing things about the land and the way.
And I still feel that way.
I did.
I feel it all did.
Yeah.
So I did feel we were a bit grouchy and I was like, is that right?
Do I did I not get the ride exactly?
We'll get to the ride because that's what the topic is today.
So there were some things where I was like, OK, we didn't get a chance to sort of do everything
in a comfortable fashion.
So there was a question of like, I'm sure we're missing stuff.
I feel it's a bit incomplete, but knowing that we'd have a part two pretty quickly,
I at least felt pretty good about that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, and we start doing some of these things and I'm expressing to both of you guys, you
know what?
I'm having a lot of fun and I'm a little worried that we are kind of harsh land.
And Mike said, I kind of see where you're coming from.
I might kind of agree.
Jason said in a quote, I will never forget.
It's really funny.
I think Comcast can take that.
I don't care.
I love that recording.
And I like driving by the opening ceremony was going on as we're wrapping up.
We saw I saw a little of the fireworks driving down Lancashire Boulevard.
But yeah, I don't know.
I didn't think I think I think I gave some pretty light jabs.
But like, I don't know, it's going to be so gnarly for like the first six plus months.
This is true.
I didn't view it as that we I was not concerned about harshness to Comcast.
I just thought we maybe just came off like grouches.
That was my concern.
Oh, well, I felt pretty ill after that first round of food before the second round.
I did like what I had better the second round and I felt normal.
What you're saying the food was the 11 a.m. spaghetti.
Yeah, the 11 a.m. spaghetti.
And which was not on the day that we recorded.
But it was still lingering in your mind.
It was decaying your mind.
He was keeping it real.
I was also a little disappointed by the sweets.
And then, of course, the second time around the matcha cake.
I was like, OK, I like this one.
Yeah, I'm going to go right after you.
Now maybe it's different tastes and maybe they were different on different days.
I think you were kind of harsh on that tiramisu.
Yeah, it didn't taste like any tiramisu I've ever had.
It didn't know.
That's right.
That's not like fine restaurant.
I also I'm on edge because I think we're saying this word wrong.
Yes.
So I think I saw somebody mention this tiramisu is what I believe it is.
I've heard both.
OK, that's how I've always heard it.
But maybe I'm saying it completely wrong, too, because I believe me, I've made plenty
of gaps on this show.
Well, including I don't want to leave myself open because you know what I did last time
about that song again.
No, you know what?
I didn't get to have it the first time because Chef Toad didn't make enough.
And you're right.
It's not like some like great restaurant tiramisu.
Right up.
You guys are saying tiramisu.
Tiramisu.
Tiramisu is how I always thought it was.
But again, I don't know.
We're putting an emphasis in the middle.
OK.
Yeah, but again, I'm not really teaching you.
I'm just this is how I always heard it.
But I don't know.
Yes.
Could be completely wrong.
I like it.
But again, I don't have the best track record with Inside Universal Studios Hollywood Food.
Have had wonderful meals at CityWalk at pretty much anywhere I've eaten at CityWalk.
Wait a second.
Do you not remember the CityWalk saga?
Did it all just vacate your mind all of a sudden?
Let me remind you about Wetzel's Pretzels, my friend.
Oh, well, that's like a take.
I'm at real restaurants.
Yeah, no, I forgot about the Wetzel's Pretzels saga.
You had wonderful meals at Bubba Gump.
We had a nice time.
Yeah, we had a nice time and nothing was wrong.
My food was, you know, fine.
That's hardly the definition of wonderful, my friend.
I was looking at the whole experience.
Scotty, you're trying to be positive.
Scotty, you're trying to keep it real.
I'm trying to keep it real.
You want the guy to be positive and he's trying.
It is a thing I've worked on there.
Don't say the first thing that comes to your head.
Don't say your initial reaction.
Sit on it for 30 seconds.
I was going to bring this up later in the show, but I think the land in this attraction,
in general, I think a lot of recent stuff in recent years, Avengers Campus, Galaxy's
Edge, I have come to appreciate more as time has gone on.
So yeah, Pandora, I think I liked immediately.
Pandora was an immediate.
Pandora is pretty great.
Yeah.
Well, in terms of stuff that is good, well, here's a big difference.
Is that this time, in addition to the lighter crowds, Jason, the first time you had the
power bands, we now, Mike and I now had the power bands.
This gave us the ability to play the mini games, the games which get you the key.
Nowhere you collect the key, which get you, sorry, you three keys.
Get you access to Bowser Jr.
You can play three different games or you can repeat games.
You can play one game twice or three times.
They get harder as you go along.
Oh, that's a way to get the three keys.
You can keep going.
Okay.
I also just read that they are doing, I think Carly posted, they are doing standby for Bowser
Jr.
A standby line for a little while.
Where you do not have to get the, yeah, which is good because again, I think these lines
are going to be so crazy that it's going to be tough to like stand in three different
lines in order to get to another thing with a line.
That's all going to be hard.
But look, if we take crowds out of the equation, we had the bands now, we're able to play these
games.
I loved these games.
I had so much fun and I feel like I was watching them the first time from the outside like,
oh, that's it.
It's a Goomba on a roller thing.
Playing it is a whole other, I thought these were all delightful.
Agree disagree?
Yeah, I liked the, I did like the games.
I don't think I'd wait more than 10 minutes for any of them.
I agree for sure.
And a $40 add on to do any of them is a little steep.
It's significant and I don't love the idea that like some of the strongest attractions
in this land require the band.
You know, it's not like I've never felt shut out of the lightsaber experience in Galaxy's
Edge.
I don't want that lightsaber.
I don't care about doing the show that much and that's a much greater expense.
But this I'm a little weirder about where like it does stink that it takes $40 to do
some of the best stuff there.
I did see that if one person gets the three keys and goes to Bowser Jr. they can bring
a few people without power bands.
Oh, what the limit is.
Oh, that's good.
This might be another Carly nugget wisdom.
If you're staying at the hotel, you can bring some of your friends to the club in Vegas
is what you're saying.
Oh yeah, basically.
The V.I.
We just said Bowser Jr.'s VIP language.
Yeah, which is what I did to in Vegas a couple of years ago.
I got a loud sigh when I did it once in Vegas.
Oh, we got a loud sigh.
You bring you bring in like six guys in their mid to late 30s and that's it to a club in
Las Vegas.
They don't really like that.
They don't care about that.
Believe it or not.
Let me tell you something in Los Angeles in the world of podcasts, mid to late 30s guys
are the most in demand demographic.
Right this way, sirs.
There's two city blocks in Los Angeles where we're on top.
I got more.
I mean, it was just me and Jane, but I still got a guy going, yeah, no, it's not here.
Take these risks.
That's not going to work.
Just escalator.
When we were in Vegas, they were trying so they were trying to write reasons to not let
us in.
It was like, OK, well, are you staying at the hotel?
I'm like, yeah, we are.
We're here.
There's a car.
OK, well, you have to have passes for this.
Well, we get these free comps.
We talked to our guy.
We met a guy outside and he gave us these comps.
OK, all right.
Hold on one second.
Like going to figure out like looking what can we do legally to keep these guys out?
And then like they were in where they were.
They were in like gang attire.
No, look, they are not gang attire.
I had the name of two.
I did at the front desk.
I'd like a couple of front desk people.
And even the guy at the club was just like, fine, I don't want to deal with these two
weirdos.
Yeah, we just waited a while and we just outlasted their patience basically and then went in to
off the record club at the Park MGM in Las Vegas.
So anyway, I was going to say about the four.
So it is like a magic band.
It's like a snap race.
You are right.
It does not perfect like the magnet on it.
It's first of all, I like the feeling of it.
I like it.
It's like, yeah, but it does have some kind of like bunches up here and there on me.
You are right about that.
I'm not sure if they'll fix that for the next round of them.
But the whole, I will say this because you're saying about like paying to do these experiences
and you wouldn't wait 10 minutes and we'll come back to this thought.
But the thought I had is like, this is going to be worth it for you if you're living in
Los Angeles and you're coming here a couple of times a year.
That's a real like that's where you're going to get the big fun, I would say, out of all
of this stuff versus the one person who's coming once who might not even know all this
stuff exists.
Yeah.
And it's confused by some of it.
Unless they're really motivated to.
Unless they're very motivated.
I know about this stuff and I want to do it, which might be listeners to the show.
I mean, I just, my overall thing, I just, I think this is all going to be great in 2025.
I think it's all just got to die down.
But like once it is not super slammed, now we have like a range of little experiences
that are, you know, an odd little underground corners.
That's not really a thing that's been in Universal before.
And like we were saying last time that it's great.
It's a great cartoon world you enter with heights and when hefts to it, you know, it's
all going to be ultimately great for the Universal landscape.
It's just, it's going to be a tough, tough for six months, I think.
Okay.
Well, I do give them credit because they have been running virtual cues to get in the land.
And I think we all think, you know, I think we can all say on some level, that's a bit
of a pain on the other Pete's waiting on a six hour, four hour line, like what have you.
And wait times, I've been looking at wait times the last few days on this and like,
how is it generally affecting the park?
And wait times are still kind of low.
Like it's very much, you think of Disneyland as a locals park, but universal Hollywood
is to an extent too.
I mean, you got a lot of tourists certainly.
But a definitely on weekdays.
So wait times are noticeably lower for not for this brand new thing, but for all the
other stuff.
Yeah.
Everything else seems, I'm going to throw a bummer out.
Mike Scollins, friend of the show we had on was there the other day.
He said Mario Kart ride 220 minutes wait and then it broke for an hour.
Oh geez.
That is rough.
These are rough numbers.
That's hard.
Yeah.
I saw it at 240 one day when I look 240.
What gets longer than this?
Maybe we're ignorant.
Florida listeners could tell us like, Oh, this thing was busy in five hours for months.
But like these are some of the biggest numbers.
I feel like I've heard.
Oh yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
And this city for sure.
But this is, you know, we still, we're hurting for rides out here too.
So like anything that's new is just going to be astronomical for like six months.
It's like, there's not many other places for people to go at this point, but that is still
even higher than I think I've seen.
And somebody correct me if I'm wrong.
I don't think opening summer transformers was ever that crazy.
It should have been, but I don't remember going.
It was just the people were too like emotionally bereft.
You know, it's just such a, such a weighty experience.
It's like, you know, the, you know, people don't go see the whale over and over again.
Right.
That's true.
All year, you know, you got to let it sink in.
Yeah.
And you go, and you go back and see the whale again.
Right.
How many times are you guys up to on the whale?
Seven.
I haven't braved the screener.
I think I'm running out of days too, cause sag words are Sunday.
Shame on you.
I took a day and I saw the 1040 and then I stayed in the theater.
I had a popcorn lunch and then I saw it again and then a jujube snack.
And then I saw it again.
I took a whole day, just four, no five whales in a row.
These mini games, I'm going to, I didn't also didn't realize they had their names.
They don't have like clearly labeled names, but I looked up the names and the names are
all good.
I liked the names.
Goomba crazy crank.
That's one where you spin a crank.
You got to spin it fast enough to make the Goomba fall backwards.
So satisfying when it works.
I don't think that's the hardest one in the world.
That was my baby holding shoulder that I was really leaning on and it was pretty sore because
I was really cranking that thing.
Yeah.
I was really, it was like a Jack in the box kind of crank, but much bigger.
And I was going to town.
I felt like on it in my mind, I was like doing like a Hercules thing.
Oh, like just this thing was going so fast.
Everyone was like, Oh, look at the strong man.
One of the labors you have to do.
It probably looked to please Zeus.
I would do anything to please him.
Yeah.
Um, you really, whatever as much cranking it as you had to do, please them.
If it pleases Zeus, I will crank it.
Let it sit there.
Uh, in, in order.
Then we played Piranha plant nap mishap.
This was the turning point where I'm like, yeah, I'm having a lot of fun.
And I think we were being a little, this was such a blast to just really quick premise
here.
There is a big sleeping Piranha plant and you were in a little patch surrounded by giant
alarm clocks and those are going to start going off and you got to hit all of those
things so that he does not wake up.
Yeah.
And this is a good one for a group because we all three got to play it together.
They're all lighten up red.
This thing I've never have.
I felt more like I was on a Nickelodeon game show.
That's exactly what I was about to say.
Yeah.
I'm literally going to say like, this feels like a live action game show in the middle
of a theme park.
Yeah.
Kids game show and winning feels fantastic.
The only thing missing is, uh, that, that host, uh, uh, Phil, I don't remember his last name,
the video arcade guy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
What is the song?
We did that was great and you did the best and now we're going back to the stage.
I don't know if you remember this about Nick or Kate.
He would always improvise a little song.
Really?
That guy.
I give it up.
I think that must've kept it interesting for him.
Every episode of Nick arcade, good host.
I don't remember that.
Like them.
Uh, look at if you watch an episode, um, that's great.
That was fun.
Koopa Troopa power punch.
Uh, in this one, there is a green shell going back and forth, uh, in and out of a pipe and,
uh, you have to cause a chain reaction with pow blocks.
You have to hit it at the right time so that another one goes and another one goes and
you have to, which will hit the green shell and cause it to shoot up and hit a Koopa Troopa
with the same green shell.
Very tragic.
Yes.
Sort of a good cannibalism.
You feel like do it.
Yeah.
Um, but, uh, but you know, that's more of a, like, that's not a running around game.
That's more like, like, uh, you know, reading the room.
That's like getting that, that rhythm right.
Yeah.
Um, and I enjoyed that a lot.
You guys did it and I, I didn't do it.
I can't do it.
I don't know why.
I was not sure what I was doing wrong.
The accuracy on these power bands is it's not a hundred percent, you know, thank you
for letting me off the hook.
You might have to hit it a few times.
Well, it's the same technology at the very base.
It's the same as like the tap to pay credit cards, I believe.
Oh, really?
It's that same, same sort of thing.
Think about how many times that's not worth it.
Yeah.
Apple pay.
Sometimes you really got to shove your phone onto the little console there to get the
Apple pay to work.
Yeah.
I've done it.
It's the same premise.
Yeah.
I think though, at least towards the end of the day, somebody told me that an employee
told me that, uh, actually you don't, at least this is true of the coin boxes.
Yes.
I don't hit them with the band.
You do it with your hands.
You just do it with your hands.
So it's a little farther away.
Yeah.
We learned that at the end of the day.
This is the tough thing again about people, even people that are fairly well educated
about what's going on is that there's so much crap to know to get in there and to really
like, like experience all the fun stuff.
Yes.
And like, there should be like a big book, phone book size, like the guide before you
go in there.
You are given a Nintendo power is back.
That would be cool.
Any Nintendo powers that give you all that.
That'd be great.
You get a very charming map with the, um, power bands.
On the app?
No, in the, in the box.
Oh, you do?
There's a map in the box.
I threw the box away.
I know.
It's very easy.
It's kind of like hidden down in the box.
Well, I need a, I need a manual to tell me not to throw away the manual.
You watched me throw away the box.
Uh, I think I learned about it after that.
Oh, so you didn't get the map either.
No, I held onto my boxes.
So I just threw my bag in my backpack.
Really didn't see the map.
It's also the, um, like infographic kind of cartoon in the phone app that tells you,
yeah, you have to get the, uh, did you like do your username and stuff?
You created one.
Okay.
So we should say that too, before you even start doing these mini games.
And we probably said this on the other one, but you go in the app and then you pick a
unique username.
Yeah.
It cannot be like they're running out of them basically.
Oh, well, I tried multiple names and was denied.
Oh, what'd you, what'd you try?
I was trying, I, my first one, I think I tried Michael Luigi with the L's, you know, bridging
the gap between the name.
It said invalid name.
And then I was, I think I, I tried Michael Luigi 69 and it said, this is not an appropriate
name.
Please choose a different one.
A tad body.
Please choose a name.
Choose a number that is less body.
And then I said, I tried Mr. McFistario and they said no to that.
What?
I don't know.
Maybe.
And then I tried, uh, Luigi Carlson.
No.
What?
I said no on that one too.
I didn't know about any of this.
I got mine on the first try.
Yeah.
So then I did put, I believe Mr. Mike Fisto is my name.
That is my official Nintendo.
Well, no complaints for you.
Got your, your dream.
You got your wish to be Mr. Mike Fisto.
Yeah.
But I was trying to add fun Mario stuff into it before.
So I got it fine.
I was happy with my name, but it was just like, I got seven different tries before they
accepted one.
This is great.
Like, you know, remember when any social media has the handles, you know, it's, they always
say it's, this is like internet real estate.
It's only one chance to grab these names, uh, whether it's Twitter or Facebook or whatever.
Um, and I got mine's a little basic.
I kind of off a bird.
Oh, I went for Scott.
Oh, really?
That worked.
I got Scott out, but maybe Oh is not so maybe if I tried Scotty, Oh, that would have been
out.
Maybe Jason, what was yours?
I don't remember.
Was it anything fun or was it just like, might've just used been something I use when I just
like, God, I gotta make a login for this.
What do you, what's your go to?
I don't want to, you don't want to say, I don't see your email.
Is it your email?
I don't think it was my email.
It might've had my full name in it.
Okay.
Does it have, is it like, is it just Jay shared in your social security number?
Sometimes it's not social.
It's my social, but not one digit, so we'll never figure that out.
All right.
He said, I don't remember as he flashed to entering the name loves that pussy.
Oh, that did go through the mention of the mere mention of fist got him flagged.
You did, you did one with one was a dollar sign and one was a Z. You got it.
You cracked the code.
Yeah.
Well, I said pushy.
Oh, smart.
Um, so I like these games and then the, the culmination of the games that you get access
to this Bowser Jr thing.
I loved the Bowser Jr thing.
Oh yeah.
This was really like this actual like Nick arcade and the level type thing.
And I thought it made the most good of anything in the land, including the ride.
Unfortunately, we'll get to that, but I think it did the best job of making you feel like
you are Mario or you are in a video game, which is a big promise to have to keep up
in super Nintendo world.
Yes.
I guess if you're listening to this, you don't care about necessarily spoilers, but I went
into this room pretty cold and you're all in like front of a big video screen and they
basically are like projecting your silhouette onto a digital screen and stuff is coming
at you.
Blocks are going.
So if in real life you jump like three times that amount on the screen and like hit a block,
which looks really silly, but fun and it feels, you kind of feel it.
There's, and there's enough like little rumble, I feel like to it that you sort of, it's,
you feel like you're jumping like Mario.
Yeah.
This is, and this is one of those, cause I think that in general, there's a, I don't
want to say like infection in all of a, of a imagineering and creative right now at theme
parks where you have to be the experiencing this and you're the superhero.
That's a little too much for me in general, but I will say this does kind of fulfill the
promise of it.
Like as far as everything's in recent memory that are like you compete or you participate.
Yeah.
You throw fire.
Uh, I was gonna say fire flowers.
That's not what it is.
You throw fire balls.
Yeah.
You get a fire flower.
That's, that's a huge thing to get to do in super Nintendo world.
That's a thing you want to do.
And it is a fun and it's like, there's no goggles or anything.
They figured out a fun prac, like kind of practical way to do it.
It works.
It's not as buggy as other things like this.
And then at the end they try to give you kind of the feeling of the whole group jumping
and landing on the flag.
Yeah.
That's another big, like, yeah, that's fun.
I think we talk about this kind of stuff a lot, just the, like when you hear the premise
of the thing, what are the, what, what do you want to do?
Yes.
And then a lot of them are in this little, this nook, it almost feels secret.
Honestly, you go through little corridors and the, the actual experience room is little
in the queue.
Yeah.
It was great.
Oh, the queue has got pictures of baby bow or Bowser Jr.
Oh, there is very cute.
Very cute.
Bowser Jr.
I learned in current Canon is bought Bowser's only child.
Is that right?
Yeah.
The Koopalings since like, what is this?
Oh, forgive me.
It said in 2012, our current story is that the seven Koopalings are not Bowser's children.
Bowser's only child is Bowser Jr.
Okay.
So those are relatives.
They're like his nephews or something.
I think they're just as well.
Oh, no pun intended.
But now Miyamoto was at that.
We did not get to go to the opening ceremony, you know, and I, this wouldn't be an episode
about a new thing without me bitching about not getting to go, getting, getting one good
free thing, but being selfish and wishing he got to go to the one where Miyamoto, Mr.
Miyamoto was there, Mario's dad.
Yeah.
That's what I was like, Oh no, cause we were recording and then the ceremony you, you told
us we were recording while the ceremony was happening.
I was like, ah, I want to see Mario's daddy.
That's what I want to see.
But oh well.
I guess a different free day where we got to, we're over on the land that was very empty
was, was pretty good.
I'm glad we didn't.
I'm glad we weren't there because if I'd been next to you and you had, he'd come out and
you had said Mario's daddy, I would have had to like, no, I'm with these guys.
I'm with ordinary adventures.
I'm a daddy too now.
Mario's daddy.
I'm a daddy too.
I believe, I think maybe he told the story here.
Anthony Gio once recognized a Shiguru Miyamoto and like Hollywood and Highland, it was during
an E3 and like went up to him and like, was like so excited to meet him.
Wow.
But this is like 10 years ago.
There's no way that's the first enthusiastic American who has just gone up to him.
100%.
I assume he has like a Donkey Kong style, like gorilla guard that swats away.
So annoying, a video game fan throws a barrel.
She's Gio running up.
How Highland just gets a Gio eats a barrel to the face.
He keeps an eye out for the nearest pits wherever he goes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Um, I, another thing in this, the, um, we talked about the, I'm going to coin a phrase
and lack of a better one.
We talked about in runaway railway.
For me, it was the little chipmunk candle costumes from that Christmas short, uh, for
you as the lonesome ghosts.
Yes.
The mirror, the, the stand.
Um, I'm going to, I'm going to call this the object gasp.
This is something, if it is a property that you care about, you were hopefully as with
their, you know, Millennium Falcon, the biggest full of object gasp.
And I had a big one.
My biggest one was the, I had to look up what it's called the Koopa clown car, which is
like the, the clown bowl with the little propeller on the bottom.
The Bowser flies around and at the end of three, Mario three, I think.
Super Mario world, I believe is the world is the first appearance of it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, that I see one of those physicalized relief.
I mean, the land is full of stuff like that, but seeing, being in a small room, I think,
and, uh, and I'll throw Mike's term in intimacy.
That's right.
I had the intimacy feelings big time.
I had intimate feelings seeing the Koopa clown car and a big Mecha Koopa, the windup.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Like just, I don't, I'm not usually an object gasp kind of person.
There's not a ton of big IP where I like, Oh that, but these are, we've been seeing
these things our whole lives and you imagine how like, just like bright and vibrant.
And I mean, the only thing missing is that I couldn't hug them.
I know they're evil objects, but I wanted to hug them.
I feel like we could have, I guess you couldn't have touched it, but in my mind, I think you
could, I was like, Oh, it's close enough to do it, but I guess they probably don't want
you doing that.
Weren't paying attention.
You could have, um, I guess elsewhere in the, um, you know, getting look moments of intimacy
with let's say characters who we've all, this time we got to do photo ops with Mario Luigi
and princess Peach.
I think I'm just going to set you up, Mike.
I know there was an aspect of these meet and greets that you were excited about.
So if you have any thoughts to share.
Yes.
Uh, yes.
So they, uh, Peach talked, I, which I like, this is not the main thing I'm going to talk
about here, uh, which is nice.
And like, it was all fun and the character faces look good.
The costumes look good.
All of the hair on the characters, the human hair didn't look real, but kind of looked
real.
Was that enough for you?
It was more than enough for me because you wish you could have their hair equal.
They had, yes.
They all had like seemingly like realistic human hair.
The Mario Luigi had realistic mustache hair.
It looked like it was sort of like very, like immaculately combed or something like the
mane of a pony, like a prize winning pony.
Like it looked like, I, I, maybe I'm describing it wrong, but all of a sudden, like when we're
taking the photo with the characters, I look over and I'm like, is it real?
Is it hair?
If you do these photos, absolutely.
Just like, don't be so focused on the camera.
Turn to the side and get, get a close up look at this hair, which is it's, it's hair 2.0
as far as I'm concerned.
Yeah.
We're all, we're all running up the back by not having hair as good as these mascots have.
What I like about the photo is that you two and Mario and Luigi are doing the like jump,
the punch in the air.
And I'm just, I've got a dipshit wave going on.
And I did have a moment where like the photographer said, power up.
And I thought that's just what, okay, they don't want to say smile.
They'll say something land appropriate.
And as soon as I did that, I was like, oh my God, are they doing the jump behind me?
That's all right.
Everyone's you.
Most funny is, is knowing that I have heard that those Mario and Luigi heads are real
heavy and that visibility is low.
That real pony hair is really heavy that they use on the heads.
Yeah.
Seem like it.
Yeah, there's real, there's silver in there.
There's a little silver, you know, give it some life.
These people can only have, you can only be Luigi for two days or else the cancer risk
becomes so high.
Yeah.
The radiation on those things.
It's like the old movie monster makeup where it's like, oh no, how many times do you play
that character?
Oh no.
It looks cool.
You know, and you want to be remembered for how you looked on the screen and not how you
died seven years later.
Yeah.
So those were, those are really fun.
I mean, that's really fun.
We like to take photos with the characters, you know, that was nice to get to do that.
Again, yeah, you're going to have to wait probably a long time.
Yeah.
This is my only, that's the problem.
That's what I don't go back on from the, from our, our grouchiness the first time around
is that like, look, it is going to be tough.
I, and it's where you do wish that they had carved out more space for this and not created
this dense landscape of just like, there's eight things to do and eight very long lines.
It feels like, yeah, I mean, I go and know it's a space issue, but it feels like you
could have done like some little cat, like, cause the, uh, sorry, I'm thinking when you're
walking to the Bowser Jr thing, there's fun little hallways.
And if they had like a fun little hallway into like a less themed area that has more
character meet and greets and that had some seating and it wasn't as like impressive or
crazy as the, like the main part of the land.
Sure.
It feels like stuff like that.
You're like, oh, that would have really moved the crowds around a little more of this open,
especially this opening summer, not just this one courtyard that can feel a little oppressive.
Like you, you're kind of anxious to get out of there and not certainly not to go wait
in another line in the one courtyard.
Yeah.
I am pretty used to theme park crowds at this point, but I think it's the being surrounded
by walls.
Like the crowds and the walls.
That was making me a little anxious.
I think it is like there's like, we were feeling like where, um, what was the, like, like we're
a hamster in a shoe box or something a little bit.
And there's like so many hamsters in the shoe box because the walls of Nintendo are so high
because they really do.
It makes you feel immersed immersed in there.
Like almost, I guess any other than like maybe Diagon Alley or something where Diagon Alley
is pretty much, you can't see outside of it.
But other than that, yeah, this one is smaller than that.
So you really feel like you're in a little shoe box.
But you know, actually you can see outside of the land because there is a problem with
the sight lines.
This land is a real problem with sight lines and we need to talk about it.
I mean, you can see the panels.
You can see the panels of the walls, they should paint over those, but you know.
Some of the other like, yeah, look, you can't get rid of the, like, do you want the land
or not?
The place they had for the land has a big universal skyscraper in there and they can't
get rid of that.
Hogwarts is in front of an NBC universal building.
Yeah, that one's worse.
You can see it.
That one actually is worse than some of this Nintendo stuff.
And also, well, here's let me go back to my situation with the grass.
Oh, yeah.
I came around on the grass.
I ended up liking the grass.
Even if I share the opinion of the tweets, I if I don't like the tone of the tweets,
I still hate them.
I'd rather see somebody I disagreed with who wasn't being fucking annoying.
That's how I feel.
Actually the sight lines of sight.
Also, it's a comedy pod.
Go yell out what are the other million psycho theme park news websites that aren't supposed
to like another fight at the Magic Kingdom like, oh God.
Yeah.
According to certain news sources, there are bloody drag out fights every single day in
every single theme park.
Yeah.
I, there's one more thing before we get to the land.
This a little bit of a also a sequel to the episode from two weeks ago.
There was another visit to the toadstool cafe.
That's correct.
Which gave Mike a choice.
Do we double down on the same behavior of the first round with the escape with the food?
Or do we just give it a go?
Less people.
We try to have the toadstool food in the fun toadstool environment.
Yeah.
But what's more fun for this show?
That was, I got to see it in real time.
And I'm so glad you caught a little of it.
I was afraid you're going to miss it.
Right on the tail end.
Yeah.
It was a little late, but I got there just as, as crucial decisions were being made.
So I ordered soup from the toadstool cafe.
They had the-
The hollowed mushroom soup.
They had-
I bowed to Andrew Grissom, an apology.
They did have the soup.
But the short ribs while on the menu boards had already sold out.
The press loves their little short ribs.
Toad has not made enough of the little short ribs today.
The heated hallway is broken and we cannot bring your short ribs from the kitchen in
the long haul.
It could be lukewarm short ribs.
That's okay.
As warm as Chef Toad.
A special event, not judging.
No points deduct for the lack of short ribs.
Also probably shouldn't be eating short ribs at two o'clock in the afternoon.
At least it wasn't 11 though.
It wasn't 11.
Yeah.
So you're 11 AM spaghetti with too many meatballs.
Too many meatballs.
What did you have for lunch that day?
I skipped lunch.
Okay.
Cause you probably ate some.
I ate a late breakfast and went, yeah.
What was in my stomach was a little tiny candy bag from It's Sugar.
Yes.
You were texting me your It's Sugar as I was parking.
I was in It's Sugar and I went, oh my God, they have, they have a little like cases of
Pez like individual Pez you can put in the big bulk candy bag.
Yeah.
The fun of Pez without that pesky toy.
Well, here's how I find out that you text candy stuff to Jason.
Of course.
And text Mandy stuff to Jason.
He texts me candy stuff.
So all we text each other X-Men shirts and candy stuff.
Oh yeah.
And some of these X-Men shirts.
I found one I really liked and messaged the seller.
I said how much?
Oh yeah.
I said $1,000.
That's vintage.
Fair enough.
Everyone's got to make a living.
I'd value it.
If it were mine, I would value it at that too.
Yeah.
So, so yeah, I ate a little candy, but then yes, I ordered the mushroom soup.
Because again, as I revealed last time, big mushroom guy, a big, big mushroom guy.
Oh yeah.
That's right.
So yeah, I ordered the mushroom soup.
I ordered a, what's the lemon smash thing?
What's it called?
Oh, the honey lemon, lemon squash.
Yes, the squash.
Yes.
And then I ordered the boba things in it.
And then I got, what did I get?
The dessert.
I got the, not the-
Did you get the tiramisu?
Tiramisu.
Yeah.
That's right.
So yeah.
So I, here I tried, so here I tried to get ahead of it.
I didn't want to be like on my heels trying to figure it out, playing defense.
I want to play offense with the good people at the Toadstool Cafe.
And I helped.
So I asked, I immediately asked the person at the counter, I want, you know what?
I'd like to eat this outside if it would be possible.
Could we get, and then like she looked a little bit like, why are you talking to me about
this?
But she said, oh yeah, maybe we have, they could get like some sort of a to go thing.
And I was like, I don't remember.
But so then I asked again, there was a person who takes you to the table.
Again, I was trying to stay on top of it.
I asked this poor person, oh, by the way, I'm going to probably end up taking this.
Cause you think, oh, oh yeah, we'll, we could get you a to go, whatever.
Everyone was just trying to pass the buck.
Everyone was really nice too.
Everyone was really nice.
I don't know where the, what is he talking about?
No one has ever wanted to not eat in the silly cartoon.
Why would you want to do that?
The food isn't good enough to eat outside.
What are you doing?
So then a very, very, very nice like manager of the establishment.
Like I got the sense that he had some sort of like official, like I'm just kind of monitoring
the situation and making sure everyone's good and everyone feels like they're being taken
care of or whatever.
He was a really nice guy, a foot and a half tall, big mushroom for a head vest.
Seemed a little overwhelmed, but it's okay.
When he jumped, his legs kind of like went in the air.
He like hovered there for a second and then he came back down and a big turtle captured
him and you never saw him again.
Yeah.
Uh, but he made the big mistake of asking how we were doing.
And I explained what I was looking forward to him.
Well, the third person in the totes look, I was being nice.
I don't think I was being rude.
I was being self-deprecating as well to know that I knew this was a bit silly.
And he was like, he's like trying to figure out like, Oh, you know what?
We're not really, we're going to, we're going to work on getting a to go soup situation,
but we don't really have that happening right now.
Again, because if you don't know the soup come, this is the best display of food in
the restaurant.
It comes in like a, not ceramic, but like a sturdy feeling plastic.
Yeah.
Like a big one, not one of the, the Mario mushroom.
You get a big plastic toy to drink your soup out of, which is fun.
It's a big Mario mushroom.
But then he goes, he, he kind of, I forgot, I should have really remembered exactly what
he said, but he goes, well, he goes, you know, we can get one of like cupcake to go.
Hey, we can try the cupcake to go container, I guess, if you want.
And I go, yes, thank you.
That would be really great.
He goes, okay.
So he went to the back, he came out with it and boy, this worked like a charm.
He did joke like we're not liable for this.
Yes, he did.
That's good.
First hammer.
And cause I was like, I think, I think the soup would probably fit in a to go box, but
uh, well we were going to do like a regular to go box.
You put like a hamburger in, which was really going to be messy.
That was not going to be a good idea.
It was a sturdy, it was pretty sturdy.
Well yeah, but it was, but that's not what I think there was like, it wasn't just to
go container, like a bigger.
Each one of those kind of, um, uh, paper ones, kind of cardboard kind of card stock paper
that the inside is a little glossy as like a coating.
Sounds horrible.
That one is still not super soup.
That's insane.
Also the wider you get to see it.
It's like, the amazing one just brought like an Amazon box and put my soup in there.
Uh, uh, so, so he brought the cupcake container, boy worked like a charm.
I poured the soup right in there and I was like, yes.
And then I took the drink and I took the Tierra missu and I took it outside every time I'm
going to say it.
So much worse.
I don't think we're saying it right.
Okay.
Now we fixed it to Tierra missu.
Say it like Edwin.
Uh, uh, uh, and then, yeah, so I took it outside and I was just sitting with a to go cupcake
container, drinking my delicious mushroom soup.
Drinking.
I was Ukraine.
Take the spoons.
So you're going to have a container sipping, sipping the soup.
Now you said the word delicious.
Yes.
And I, um, I'll leave it to you to describe it.
I didn't taste it so I couldn't say the look of the soup once put in the clear plastic
container.
Um, we made a little video and I think we say it in the video, but the, the look of
this brown fluid was somewhere between gravy and vomit.
I've eaten a lot of mushroom soups.
I thought it was kind of par for the course, but I think it's the, that it's in a fun
mushroom and then you remove it from that context.
It was just this like brownish gray.
It divorced of the fun.
Yes.
It looked pretty busy.
This is something you would eat at a, at a bus station.
It looks like, uh, uh, you're like, you've had a problem like with your stomach lately
and you've been like puking a couple of times a day.
So like here, we're going to give you a container to, to take a sample of your vomit.
So it looks very clinical.
It's like a clear plastic thing and it's like, yeah, like a grayish thing.
They're like, you puke, okay, puke into this little plastic dish and then bring it in and
we'll analyze it at the lab.
I think you're being a little unfair to both vomit and soup.
I've had a lot of experience with vomit and I can't say I've ever had gray one.
Well, in my scenario, there's an issue.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I'm saying this is not gray.
What color is your vomit?
It's kind of like orange ish or sometimes the, uh, uh, biolish yellow.
Orange always really?
No, not always.
I can't say I vomit.
We're the ones a year at this age.
You know, thankfully.
No, no, no.
Last time you puked.
Um, great question.
Maybe when I had COVID.
Oh really?
I think I got a little queasy.
Okay.
Um, uh, I do remember one time a few years ago where you were, uh, I was feeling ill
and you said, oh, you should try zinc.
So I went to write it and got zinc pills and I took it on an empty stomach and I vomited
nearly immediately because I didn't know.
Watch out for that.
Yeah.
So I, I eventually I would eat like a handful of Cheerios or crackers or something with
it and I know it works for some people.
I don't found it really worked for me.
That's when you put the, uh, put your zinc tablets in that pes dispenser and you just
kept popping them.
It looks like Tweety Bird.
Tweety Bird has betrayed me once again.
You got the 12 zinc before you threw up.
Wow.
Uh, yeah.
So, uh, did it, did it taste like gravy vomit?
No, it tastes, it tasted like, like good Campbell's mushroom soup.
It wasn't like, again, it wasn't like some sort of, uh, what delicacy type mushrooms.
It was very much like solid canned soup.
It's cream.
It's thick.
It's creamy.
Uh, yeah, I would assume for outdoors, your lips, hot summer day, a good sipping on a
soup.
You know, we've all been there.
You know, I never related to the, the John Mellencamp sucking on a chili dog, but sucking
down some soup from a plastic container.
Now that's my summer.
That's my summer.
I heard loud coins go off in all directions.
Yeah.
So, uh, I liked the soup.
I thought the soup was good.
Um, quick service soup was good.
Okay.
Well, now that we've described the quick service soup and recounted some of Jason's zinc vomit
memories, I think we are now ready to talk about Mario Kart Bowser's challenge.
This is the big ticket item at the land.
Uh, it's the, it's the big ride, the only ride in, in this version and, uh, woof, where
to, I don't know where to begin.
I am now worried that the positivity cliff that we are precariously on will suddenly
decay.
If you go, okay.
Well, if you glance at the reception section on Wikipedia, like it's like it says, like
there's a reception.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
It has already gotten, and I was very shocked to find one of my, uh, you know, criticisms,
uh, their criticisms for this and some other rides.
Oh, okay.
I'll be with that in the, in the, in the name of positivity.
Sure.
I'll let us build up to it.
I will also say in the name of positivity, excited in the line, excited on the ride,
laughing and giggling on the ride, got off the ride, smiling up a storm.
That is, that was my reaction.
Sure.
And I will say listeners go on this ride, have a fun time on this ride, but I think
maybe the more your thoughts spin around.
Your expectations is the nice way to say it.
Yeah.
Okay.
The queue and all the stuff is amazing.
So great.
Let's be, let's be positive here.
Oh, great.
So good.
That big statue of King Koopa, Bowser right at the start.
Really good.
I just like everything they made into a practical statue effect picture is per like truly like
perfect.
Yeah.
And really exciting to see your dream taken from your dreams.
Oh, and kind of like environments that you don't get to see.
Like they're, they're, they're, they're inventing stuff in there in the ride.
There's things that are more directly from a video game, but I don't maybe now forgive
me.
I'm no Mario expert and I've, I'm maybe not caught up with some of the last few games,
but it seemed new to me to be in some kind of Bowser office in which he is plotting,
where you get a sense of the method behind the madness and you see the blueprints for
bullet bills and some of the things that he attacks the Mario and Luigi with.
And you see like his, uh, uh, uh, schedules and appointments like have lunch with Iggy
and Roy.
Like that you, because you sort of, it is funny to think about Bowser being the, uh,
mentor of a lot of the bad guys or just the person corralling a lot of the bad guys.
And this feels like being in the office of a very important man.
Yeah.
Yes.
Which is, yes.
Fun.
I actually, maybe that is referenced somewhere and I'm forgetting what it is, but that is
very fun.
All of it is really like just feels like it was made with like the most, I don't know,
care.
That sounds stupid, but the most like, uh, uh, I don't know, perfect recreations, I guess
right.
Which is what I've already said.
I still believe though, I, I have many times said, I think universal has taken the lead
in terms of spending and, uh, uh, you know, and really that they've done really grand
attractions lately while Disney's kind of like dressing up photo opportunities and stuff.
I think they're taking the baton a lot of ways, but universal Hollywood still remains
low and immersive environments.
I'm like, I got to take a thousand pictures kind of environments and, uh, this is that
big tie.
Everything's aligned.
Yeah.
Every bit the equal of, of runaway railway in terms of so much to look at and fix that
on.
But the ride itself, I don't, I don't, I don't like it that much.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
This is such, okay.
The reason this is, and it's not just because last time we, maybe we felt like we were
negative or something, the reason it's so hard for me to say this is because doing Mario
Kart is a dream, a childhood dream.
It's I and everything else leading up to it.
You can tell the passion, the love of all of it, the work that went into it.
And even the ride itself, I feel like effort and money went into this brand new technology.
You feel like the F like you feel the effort.
It's like the love guru.
You felt the effort in that movie and things that we love.
It's the effort.
You feel it.
You know, this guy, you know, Mike, you know, creative tried, like they were trying to do
something.
I like it.
Yes.
And you're like, I'm going in here, babe.
This is going to be my favorite thing to love guru.
It's going to be my favorite thing.
And okay.
Then maybe this is not completely a fair comparison as far as quality level of movie quality of
the ride.
There's no sitar version of extremes more than words.
It's not a similar thing.
It's not the quality levels are not the same, but it Bowser's kind of like, you know, Republic
cereal level super villain.
He's not a nuanced character like guru tug at my foot.
He's not like guru tug at my poota.
Yes.
I completely agree.
You know what?
Toad gets punished.
He gets flattened by that thwomp much in the same way that similar similarly diminutive
verntroyer the hockey coaches made the subject of physical violence.
No love guru.
Poor verntroyer gets the shit kicked out of him and love guru for some weird reason.
It is so funny.
I, I, we might've said this before, but we can't.
I'm sure as far as two and three celebrating, having fun with this.
And now love guru would just fuck him up.
It's so mean.
Make fun of how he's over and over again.
Anyway, but we're talking about the ride.
That's right.
So that's, so that's really the reason.
It's not that I feel like I have to make good for the thing, the last episode we did, but
I I'm still holding out hope that like, I'm going to like it.
I'm still, we're going to go.
I've talked to a few people and the people that like it seem like, you know, by ride
10, you know, you get, cause like I can, that's even what I was saying earlier, or it's like
going a lot and doing it like, okay, you'll know all the ins and outs.
Now you'll see that like you're collecting coins and that's fun and you'll get on the
leaderboard and that's fun.
And now you know everything to do and you know exactly how it works because there's
a lot to this ride that I didn't know anything about.
That's kind of confusing.
You're being prompted.
Cause we should, we should step back.
You're the ride is like, you're in a big go-kart.
You put on like a fun Mario plastic hat and you attach AR goggles to it, which then you
go on like a dark ride, um, which are the Mario Kart levels.
And then in the AR glasses, you see the other racers like all of the Koopa Troopa stuff
and cartoon characters and other effects and onscreen prompts and graphics.
The main, your steering wheel gives you two main abilities.
One being to turn when they, when there's arrows and they tell you to turn and the other
being firing shells, so you're firing shells with these prompts and characters and a ton
going on in those goggles.
Yeah, a lot going on.
I think maybe I'll say this, maybe too many shell.
Like it to me at some point I was like, I feel like I'm not, I feel like I'm in a shooter
game now.
Like the driving became secondary to blasting people's shells.
Like imagine the first part of the Cars Land ride, car, radiator Springs racer.
It's going slower.
You have goggles on and you also have to like, it are pretty rapid pace shoot shells at Mater
and the other car.
Oh, not Mater.
Well, maybe Mater other different cars.
So you're kind of watching this digital video game on your goggles and then there's a real
life set behind you and it doesn't, my brain wasn't accepting these two realities as one
it was after a couple of rides.
Blended together for, yeah.
I will give it this credit that when there are, there are big physical items and characters
in all of these rooms.
Yes.
Like you get a piranha plant and you get the chain chomp and it's cool to see those and
you know the difference between what's in your goggles and those things, but there's
also screen effects here and there and characters that appear, you know, huge characters that
appear via screen primarily in that first ride.
I was like, I'm not exactly sure what's in the room and what's in the goggles now very
clear to me, but I, it is such a, an overload of visual information, which again, the first
time I was like laughing a lot just at how much it was.
And I was kind of surprised to look at ride throughs and go, Oh no, that was, that was
on the wall.
That's in the room.
This was only in the gut.
So I, at times it all fused together in a way that worked for me.
Cause yeah.
So you're going, so yeah, you're going through a dark ride and there's like, you know, imagine
like a, the haunted house in Mario Kart or whatever.
And it's like, the set looks perfect.
The practical set is real.
And then you're like seeing like, yeah, you're, you're watching like part of a virtual boy
on these glasses while it's happening.
And then after that, after that you'll kind of stop by a big screen and they'll be like
Bowser on it and you shoot shells.
So like that stuff to me works a little better.
Cause you're not, your brain is just looking at one thing versus trying to balance out
a video game and the sets.
Yeah.
And the, the confusion that comes from turning and moving and watching the characters that
are doing mostly the same thing overlaid, but it's still a little jumpy.
Yeah.
I mean, I definitely, I think a lot of people have been on this ride have been deep into
the ride and off the ride and going like, did I do it right?
Did I have the goggles on?
That's what I'm saying.
It's a little like that.
That's it.
That's how it's supposed to look.
Yeah.
It's, it's a little, uh, well, in addition to that, I think Jane and I got off the ride
was like, I'm a little dizzy.
Like I don't.
Yeah.
I found my focus would go be, I would either be focusing on the set or it'd be focusing
on the, the AR.
Yeah, it doesn't.
Yeah.
I think a lot of this stuff we're seeing lie and we're, we are the beta testing.
This is a generation one.
This is a PlayStation one.
And maybe you're saying maybe a ride down the road cracks the road.
I think, I think, yeah, it, it might, I don't know if they just jump.
Like I really like toy story mania and sometimes I have a lot of fun on a buzz late your Astro
blasters.
Um, but I feel like this, uh, spider-man, uh, web slingers, I feel like is simpler than
this.
Like he tells you, like how to do this, but you know, the room where they're explaining
to you what you're going to do is very, there's a lot of screens, there's sets, um, there's
fake like a racing outfits and stuff.
And I happen to like focus on the one screen and Jane was still looking around and she's
like, what do I, what do I do?
Like I was like, oh, it's all info.
I was, and I was like, okay, I think, I think they're probably going to show us how to do
this three more times of where you get on the ride.
And sure enough, that was the case.
So like they did repeat it a lot.
Um, and I'm sure the infographics are, are helpful, um, with international travelers
as well, where it's like, oh, no one's speaking English, but it also was very busy.
Infographics.
I think you can feel that it's, it must be the same video as in the Japanese version
because it's, it's very Ikea manual or like, let's, let's say as few words as positive.
Is there any, are there any words in the video?
I mean, there's word, there's like titles on screen here and there, but I think they
made those animations to work anywhere, which is smart for that reason.
But then you're left a little confused about specifics.
It's really the, it's the anti guardians of the galaxy.
Yes.
Like here is all the information and backstory in the world.
The anti David Danipour.
You can ride without ever thinking about the hands thing, you know, you can just like,
oh, I stumbled into this thing and they're here, you know, um, this you kind of need
to know.
You kind of, you're not exactly sure which information to do this.
It's a lot of information and, um, eventually got it.
I think reading about it after they're like, and each car works together.
And I was like, I didn't know I was supposed to be working together.
Yeah, I thought I had to get to a hundred shells or a hundred coins.
And I think everybody individually has to get to a hundred, but you all do, but you
all do, which I didn't realize cause a Bowser one-handedly when we did it.
Oh really?
I don't remember on mine and yeah.
So if, yeah, if, if team Mario wins, cause this is like a, it's a general challenge that's
been issued by Bowser to everybody who's getting us.
So you're on team Mario.
So you're on the good guy's side, not the bad guy's side.
Uh, if it says team Mario at the end, then you won.
If it's team Bowser, then you, you didn't, I honestly don't recall.
It seems probable that we lost.
Uh, um, boy, one thing I, let me, let me just really say.
And if you didn't get this already from me mentioning that 220 minute wait, this is,
this is a single rider.
If there ever was one, you missed some cool rooms, but like you'll see, come back and
see them in a couple of years.
I think you would be psychotic to do.
I liked the guy, I liked the queue, everything I saw the queue.
I think you'd be crazy to do that long of a queue.
And also I don't think this rewards you being in the same car as your party.
Because like, you should only do this if you have children, if you're a guardian to people
who need to be in the car with you.
Otherwise, if you can split up, split up.
It does not matter.
And I say that because like, sure, maybe you could celebrate, Hey, we did it.
If you're in the car with who you came with.
Uh, but not really because you have big clunky goggles.
You know, you literally can't, if you're, you know, if your mom's in the row in front
of you, she can't turn back and look at you because she's got a big clunky thing on her
head.
I actually heard this from a neighbor who went and they're like a little anxious on
the ride because it couldn't tell if they're like child, like six or eight was like freaking
out as you know, it was hard to like just look over and check on them because, uh, even
I didn't think like, let me try taking out the AR.
I think one of you said you tried like Scott.
Well again, and I feel like I'm falling right into what Mike was saying.
We're like, you're getting the reviews of the 10 time visitors.
We're saying, well, if you do this and if you know this is good.
My review was I liked it more the second time without the AR, the point of the ride, like
what the whole thing is designed around.
And I did like it because I just, I just wanted to know what was in the rooms and I wanted
to see a chain chomp without all this stuff.
I wanted to see the, you get a thwomp outside.
I keep talking about how I like seeing a thwomp, but I really like seeing this one in this
room with an animated face with a screen face, uh, uh, piranha plants, the amazing, um, the
especially and I looked at, I, you want to say it's Luigi's mansion, but it's actually
twisted mansion.
A lot of, uh, most of this stuff is kind of pulled from Mario Kart eight.
I didn't realize, um, except for rainbow road, which is N 64.
So it's a little bit of a mix, but twisted mansion is the level and it looks that one
especially you're like, I'm so glad the clutter is out of the way because twisted mansion,
it's this like, you know, it's this optical illusion set where it's bending all crazy
and the screen in the back makes it look like it's an infinite hallway that's bending in
an impossible way.
And there's chandeliers swinging back and forth and that room, especially I'm like,
I'm so glad I'm just looking at this without a bunch of graphics, not letting me appreciate
the great set design work.
It's like you're driving in your car and like a couple like characters like got on your
windshield and they won't like, if somebody put like pictures on your windshield of the
Mario characters while you're driving, you're like, what the hell?
Wipers on you're like, I'm trying to see what the wipers are smearing it more than help.
Yeah.
So we put like a big decal.
So we put like moving decals on your window or you're driving.
You're like, I'm trying.
What?
Am I hallucinating?
I, yeah, I, well, it's kind of like in Mario Kart when you get squitted on and now you
can't see what happens in this.
I actually pull that effect off pretty good, but it's like an entire game of being squitted
on you get squitted on.
Yes.
I don't would be the word, but I went with squitted and it's fun.
Squitted.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I mean, maybe the AR goggles, but like with less like a digital characters and carts just
constantly in your vision, absolutely.
You know what?
Make it feel more like an early Mario Kart where there's a, there's a few, cause the,
cause the further you get, they are chaos and it's great.
That's the appeal of, I love every, I've said, this is the only video game franchise I've
kept it.
I love every Mario Kart, no matter what, and I love that they're crazy as hell, but I kind
of want, Hey, let's go, think about this thing about back to the future, the ride, how the
whole idea of it was you got, it's one car, it's Biff so you can focus on Biff and then
you don't end up nauseous because you have a focal point.
I think maybe that what if you're after Bowser only and you just, and the chaos comes from
what's around you and not like, yeah, there's 20 characters at all.
It's a little overwhelming.
Maybe another character every now and then, but I think like, have like, have a little
randomized video at the beginning and it's like, you are toe.
Like I was like, wait, are we just us?
We're not one of, wait, hold on.
Yeah.
We're just four humans on a kind of regular car.
We're just here.
We're on the, we're on the base car from Mario Kart eight is what I found out.
If you don't customize and pick all of the kooky vehicles that you have at the beginning
or that you unlock as it goes on, you know what everyone wants to be in the first car
old, you always, you want to be Mario and you want to have basic car.
You don't want to have all the crazy flying.
I think that's a big, like think about just how excited you are at the mirror.
You're on the snow white ride and Oh look, I'm bashful this time.
I'm sleepy this time.
If it was different ride vehicles, you just that.
That's a more exciting, different every time than the interactive element.
Yeah.
I think the randomization, like the randomizations on the two guardians attractions now at this
point.
Um, and I of course can't think of any others, but let's say guardians, uh, mission breakout,
the knowing there's a different song, you don't know what song you're going to get.
I think that's more fun.
Like I think that's more fun than most gamification then like, yes, then you're in control of
all these thousand things that don't really add up to anything as opposed to the, just
the impact of, I got me with your best shot this time.
Yeah.
You've waited in line for a while.
Get ready to do some tasks.
My man.
Yeah.
I don't know kids.
Like, do we know, do kids like this?
Maybe we're old.
Maybe we're some old guys saying like not getting it or our brains are too slow.
Let well my counter to that is this.
All right.
Kids like playing video games.
They want to be in control.
So we've created this video game like experience where they can control everything.
Uh, sort of where you control, you don't control the speed or the path, but you control some
of the things going on in your goggles.
So your control is what?
25%.
You know what you have 100% control of Mario Kart, the video game, which I think a kid
would rather do.
You know, this literally gives you less of the Mario Kart experience than Mario Kart.
Well, look, when I said, you know, are we too old for this?
I look, that was kind of rhetorical.
I know we're young guys at heart.
Okay.
We can, we would be right in this if the kids loved it and the kids got it.
I was just trying to be nice and trying to act like we maybe we're trying to be philosophical,
but no, we're smart and young.
That's the thing.
So we would know if this were to young and we, and especially you Mike, get what teams
are into.
Thank you.
Yeah.
You know what?
I was in hot topic before when I was, was waiting for Jason at city walk.
That's the, that is the primary way to tell.
Sorry.
And that's the big thing, Mike.
You're still cool.
You know, I am still cool.
Thank you.
You know what?
Speaking of, I forgot to tell this anecdote at the hot topic at city walk, zoo TV pops
were on sale edge.
Adam and Larry were on sale, but not Bono as the fly.
So I was so excited.
Cause it's like, so many teens had bought it.
No, no.
So I got so excited.
I go, Oh my God, zoo TV.
You too pops are on sale.
I think it's like buy one, get one for a dollar.
I go, I'm going to get all four of these.
It's going to be $20.
It's going to be like making out like a bandit here.
And then I was like, Oh no, where's the fly?
Where is he?
And I went over to the regular priced pop section at the hot topic at sea walk.
And there he was up on the regular sale shelf, the fly.
So I'd have to pay regular prices and then it wouldn't even work.
Cause it was buy one, get one for a dollar.
It wouldn't have added up.
I'd have to get two Larry Mullen juniors.
Well, I don't believe that you don't have an alert set up on your phone to get like
a discount fly, uh, funko elsewhere.
I do, but it hasn't popped up yet.
Oh, okay.
But this is what I'm saying.
I'm in hot topic.
I'm looking at the deals that the young people see.
Okay.
The ultimate landscape where young people go to share ideas about what is cool and what
will be cool next.
That's right.
I saw a Funko pops of twisted the, the clown based rap group that were like kind of on
ICPs label, I think that maybe have been around for 20.
They were on the psychopathic records family.
I believe twisted was in the psychopathic records family.
So I saw that, but yeah, young people like me.
You know, if Michigan is to be believed, then young people, if young people in Michigan are
excited about insane clown posse, therefore it must be true in the rest of the country.
Yes.
I mean, I'm not there.
I mean, look, we joke about a hot topic and Spencer's gifts are probably keeping malls
alive.
I'd never see, I never see those closed.
I'd like to say, could we all just agree?
Thank you.
Hot topic.
Cause they, they've changed with the times, you know, they're from when we were younger,
but they still are very relevant to the kids.
That's how I feel connected to the youth.
Oh, sure.
And Spencer's.
We all do.
Spencer's has so many like sex stuff.
Spencer's has had a lot of lives.
Spencer's has changed a lot over the years.
The Spencer's in the Galleria.
It's just like there's a whole wall of sex stuff in there.
I hope that you're not implying that one of the things that teens are into is sex.
Well, I would never, they shouldn't be.
I wasn't.
So they shouldn't be either.
There's one constant, whether you're a teen in the nineties or today, you don't like sex.
Same deal.
We did, when we were in Japan, we did Mario Kart VR.
Lindsay and I did it and it was awesome.
And it was the same one.
I think there was like touring around here.
There was, I forget where it was.
I didn't go here, but we did it in Japan and it was awesome.
It was like people were shrieking, like the size, like the scope of everything.
Like when you were in there, it just felt like such better VR than I had ever done before.
And you were in a little chair with the steering wheel.
And I remember, I think it was a big chain shop and Lindsay, like it came out as Lindsay
like shrieked and we're like, this was incredible.
And I'm sorry, this was, what is the, is it all in the helmet?
Is it all in the helmet?
Yeah.
So it was just, yeah, completely digitally rendered like a regular Mario Kart.
It looked.
But you're in a car and it's so the car that you're steering is combined with.
So you're sitting in a seat that looks kind of like a car and you've got a steering wheel.
This was in like an arcade or a VR kind of place.
Okay, I was just making sure you weren't driving through the street.
It was not because I went to that.
That's not in the, I don't think you went to Joypolis.
I don't, I don't believe cause that's on there.
That was on this like little Island almost.
Okay.
What am I thinking of something else then?
I'm trying to remember what the name of the place was.
It was all VR stuff.
Yeah.
It was a Sega thing.
Maybe it was a, I forget what the name of it was, but it was all enclosed.
If it was a Sega thing, you got to boot up that apology.
So wait, well, it wouldn't have been a, what are we saying?
It wouldn't have been a Sega thing.
You're right, you're right.
Why am I getting this confused then?
A tentative piece.
I got to look where that is.
Tentative piece for Smash Brothers.
Well, you know, Sega and Nintendo now are, they are a little more, you know, together.
But there's Mario Olympic games that nobody likes.
That's right.
They've done one of those a year.
I've never played a Sonic and Mario game.
I have pictures from when I was little that I drew of the two of them, Mario and Sonic
getting along and going on adventures together.
I was so obsessed with this idea.
You dreamed of a better world.
And I would dream of the game.
I would almost do not do it in anything that was in depth as far as game design.
But I used to imagine what the game would be like of Sonic and Mario.
And it was not them competing in the Olympic games.
In the real cities where the Olympics were held.
Yeah.
That was not, it was maybe got a little more fantastical than with Nagano or whatever.
I was like, Oh, Mario's going to fight, you know, Dr. Robotnik.
Oh, that's going to be cool.
And the Sonic will have to fight.
I'm like thinking of this and then I was not thinking.
And then like Tails will throw the javelin.
Tails will throw the shot put.
Like that was not part of it.
And they still have yet to do.
I don't know.
I wonder if that's even on the table, but you would think that at a certain point that
would have been the big, the big ticket item was to team them up in like an ultimate platforming
game.
Team them up.
Everyone wins.
What if they switch powers for a level or two?
Fantastic idea.
Mario goes fast and Sonic's got to go slow.
Mario's got to take all his clothes off and he grows like little spines.
Whoa, he's got to look like Sonic.
This is what?
This is what a year thing.
Mario just wearing Sonic's shoes, no clothes.
He kind of grows like flesh colored, like whatever the porcupine like spines or whatever
you call it.
No, well Knuckles has spines.
Why did you, why did you make my nice idea all nasty?
I mean it's better because he looks like Sonic.
This is what happens to your brain when you don't like sex earlier in your life.
It reroutes into strange places.
But then Sonic puts on the overalls and he gets a mustache.
Sonic wears a mustache.
And it's got that voluminous hair.
It's show pony hair that Sonic's wearing under his snout.
So that's, yes, that, but it was not, it was not competing in the freestyle swimming.
It was trading clothes.
Do they trade clothes next to each other?
Do they watch each other change clothes?
Yes, they do watch.
You watch it and there's a prompt that you do participate.
You like hit the A button and you take off the overalls and then you hit B and you pass
them to Sonic and he struggles to get them on and he gives his shoes.
I like.
It's nothing erotic about it.
It's just a purely, it's just for the, it's the only way they're going to defeat Bowser
and Robotnik together.
These buddies trading clothes, we do it all the time.
That's right.
Real masculinity is being comfortable with your body and others.
The animal bodies.
I think the thing you went to was called VR zone.
Okay.
And the thing was called Mario Kart arcade GP VR.
Was it in Shinjuku?
Yes, that was what it was.
I got confused.
I apologize.
Thank God we caught it here and I wouldn't, didn't have to do it in the next episode.
No, don't get the song out.
But no, it's awesome.
Like I understand why that's on the table when you're talking about the big flagship
ride for the first Nintendo theme park land.
Like you, oh man, we wouldn't it be awesome if you get to be in the car and you get to
do the shell stuff and all, like I get it.
But then there was probably somebody and I don't know that, but it was like, it should
be practical.
We know we have done a lot of screens here.
We've done a lot of screens and maybe we don't want to do that.
We want to build practical things cause that is so impactful for people and it'll be like
different than what we've done before.
And then all the ideas came together much like Indiana Jones and kingdom of the crystal
skull, all these different ideas and like, let's try to make all of it work at once.
But that one worked perfectly.
What are you saying?
As assuredly will the next one.
Oh yeah, that did.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, we, I mean, we both, I think came to the same conclusion of like kind of wish this
was just a super Mario world dark ride.
Well, that's a different, yes.
I said in the last episode that I felt like we were getting a Mario cart too soon.
Yeah.
I mean, they're also building this for Orlando and Singapore officially announced Orlando.
I think I've heard the rumors so much.
I didn't realize it hadn't been officially announced until that event.
Right.
We're late about it here too.
So yeah, no, I, that would have been good to start with, but obviously, you know, you
can start with Mario cart.
It makes sense.
It's just like, I felt it's just like too ambitious and it's a little ahead of its time.
And really the first Mario ride.
It's a big deal to be that.
And you want it to be just so classic, you know, in the way that Harry Potter has pieced
off different elements of Harry Potter, but the first ride needed to be very, let's hit
big beats and nail big beats.
And I think they did.
I did.
I mean, I, on a positive thing, it did have a moment of delight for me.
Again, I'm not even, I know Rainbow Road, even I remember that one.
So when that kicked in right towards the end, I was kind of delighted by that in a way that
like, I really liked the thing in the Jurassic park boat ride where like you see the giant
Mosasaurus and it kind of cracks the glass a little and splashes and then you get splashed.
I think that's really fun.
And so like I, in a similar fashion, I think the Rainbow Road a bit was fun, but just park
ride a dress where we're right.
There's a big drop at the end.
There's a big, so this is a problem here.
So at the end of the ride is the Rainbow Road and Rainbow Road rules.
I've been obsessed with the Rainbow Road my whole life.
They've never gotten it wrong.
Every Rainbow Road is better than the last 80% of my life.
I've thought about the Rainbow Road once a week, like, like starting with Super Nintendo
Mario Kart, like my sister, my whole life has been a Rainbow Road.
I love rainbow candy.
I love Rainbow Road.
And you have rainbow Johnny Pops I got from sprouts.
The other, they are delicious.
They're like seven different colors, not just a normal like bomb pop three colors.
No, these have like seven different flavors in them.
I'm obsessed with the rainbows.
Thank you for explaining what Johnny Pops are.
Cause that is not a universal reference.
I did not know where you go.
Oh really?
You didn't know?
I thought it was cereal.
Oh really?
I should show you.
Uh, Johnny Pop has like a cute little like boy with glasses on it.
Oh, okay.
Well I like that.
Yes.
Uh, I know you, I, I'm surprised you don't know what those are because I feel like those
would be a brand.
Now here's the thing.
I spent $6 on these popsicles.
That's a lot for pops.
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
But the flavors are good.
They're better than normal flavors.
You're well, it's a big challenge to good.
The good humor.
So, so, um, yeah.
So like what happens is that's the last part of the ride and this ride does not go fast
at all.
No, not at any point.
And it's not us like griping that we needed to go like, Oh man, it's only going 10 miles
an hour and we want it to go 60.
No, it goes one mile an hour basically the whole time.
Very slow.
It's the same thing they do with Fast and the Furious.
They made like a thing where it's like, okay, what's a big part of this franchise going
fast slow down a minute about, uh, you know, and I, I feel like that's why they're again
a rumor that they're building a big Fast and Furious roller coaster.
Ah, something that goes fast.
Something that goes very fast and very simple to explain.
So you go, so you turn this thing and it's Rainbow Road and I'm going, okay, I'm a little
mixed on what I feel about this ride, but here we go.
Rainbow Road.
There's like a kind of starry effect that happens in your AR goggles and then you're
in the ground lights up.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
The huge rainbow pattern on the ground on the track.
And then the goggles try to trick you.
The goggles try to trick you into thinking you're going fast in this Rainbow Ro, uh,
Rainbow Road room and you're not going fast and I'm too smart to be tricked like this.
I know we're not going fast and it's not given it.
It's so promising and then you're like, no, I didn't do it.
I didn't feel it.
It's set up as the finale of the ride.
It's a big thing.
We've all thought about our lives.
This hurts me to do, to do this episode.
I am in pain to do this episode.
I really am because again, everyone works.
I know they worked so hard on this.
I know they did.
Yeah.
But does the blame ultimately lie with the like the at the top decision makers who were
like, yeah, we could do Murray cart and here's the space it can have.
I don't know.
It's a good question.
If it was a space thing and they said, okay, well, so, cause it's a space thing, then it
can't have a big stretch like radiator Springs where we go fast.
I don't know if it's that or it's just that like they were, they were sure that they wanted
to do the AR component and because of that, you can't go fast.
Yeah.
And then people will be puking up gray mushroom soup on the Mario cart ride.
If you're going every day, like if I'm, I think, I mean, if I'm trying to imagine doing
AR while you're on that stretch in radiator Springs and it seems insane.
Well, wait a minute.
Orlando's getting the donkey con coaster too.
Yes.
Yeah.
So you can, you can puke your mushroom soup up there or any of the other numbers of epic
universe roller coaster.
Well, yeah, but I, my stomach was more settled on a roller coaster than it is getting like
two forms of media at once.
That's more of the issue.
Yeah.
I ate a big, uh, uh, like a big thing of Chinese food and went right onto a credit coaster
at once.
I drink a big beer, did big thing of, uh, of Chinese food.
And then we went over and I remember going, Oh, I shouldn't be doing this.
This isn't a good idea.
I was fine.
I felt better after that.
I yeah, actually I handle roller coasters and, uh, pretty well.
And most drop rides.
Yeah.
Well, I love, you know, I love a drop ride that's except with the legs dangling, but
if it's inside, if I'm inside in a little box going far up, far down, I'm loving it.
That's my favorite, like sensation as far as big show rides.
But yeah.
So it's like, again, yeah, the, I don't want to belabor the point, but I mean, look, they
didn't have a huge plot of land at universal Hollywood.
They demolished a bunch of sound stages, but that only gets you so far.
Because obviously it was probably the answer to that.
Yeah.
Cause obviously the land there is bigger.
So obviously they knew they had more space to work with, but I wonder, was it designed
with the idea that it can slot nicely into Hollywood and then slot wherever into Florida?
I don't know.
I don't plan was, yeah, maybe they had to think of all those factors, but transformers,
like there's two levels to it.
And I don't know.
There's some, they can't all be the best ride ever made.
My, that's the thing.
They can all be transformers, but, uh, yeah.
So I don't know.
Let's let's talk, uh, solutions as if, uh, we would solve anything because they're not
going to get rid of it and making it, but what, what is the ideal?
What is the Mario Kart ride of our dreams?
How do you actually do it?
Before we do that, and maybe this plays into it, I have something that is starting to become
a recurring narrative in like new rides and stuff that happens every time.
And it happened with this and it's starting to feel like, is no one learning a lesson?
Like what are you doing?
Like, you know, the, the test ride, the test seat at the entrance of the ride is this like
a recurring thing, a Tron, they have it.
And it's some people like physically cannot fit in the ride.
And I have heard, I think there was like on the local news, there was a universal rep
or PR person or so was like, well, it's because the seats are designed for little children
and then like a certain size of adults.
But it's like, you need to put more variables and like, you need to put more than just like
one or two kind of accessible rides because it's, it's odd.
It's happened with forbidden journey.
It's happened with this Tron.
Tron is a different seat though.
Right.
Or am I wrong?
Doesn't Tron have a different one or two little car kind of, yeah, yeah.
Tron doesn't have that, right?
I don't know.
From what I've seen, I haven't heard that it has that, but it, it's also very-
Pets is a problem.
I've seen a lot of pets.
Pets.
Yeah.
Um, avatars, I think is tough.
Um, size wise, uh, for a flight of passage.
Yeah.
That was, that was one.
And then they got in a real, I think they may have solved the issue with river journey
where it was like, there was no wheelchair accessible vehicle.
And it's like the, it's also, it's also weird on another level cause like the test seats
also become photo ops.
So some people are testing to see if they can get on it.
Some people are just taking pet and that, I don't know.
That's just so odd to me.
Like it's strange.
Audition and via people might not know that's what they're supposed to be doing.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
Figure it out.
Like you can build, you can build bigger.
Like I don't think it's the designers at fault.
I think it's probably the budgets, you know, as usual, it's the money.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Well, whatever our fixes that we're going to say here would fix that problem.
I think.
Oh, absolutely.
We're going to, we will definitely fix it.
I think the other level of weirdness is these places spend so much marketing of like everyone
can come here.
It's like, this is a very accessible place.
Then you get there and that is not the case on some.
Well, to the billboard say universal Hollywood, the most accessible place on earth.
No, no, I just, but I mean in the market, I swear there's been like stuff of like people
with disability and like they're like, these are safe places to travel to.
You can come to this destination experience.
Uh, it sure.
Well, yeah, it's weird that it keeps, I don't know, it's happened to us.
Especially.
Yeah.
It's really universal, I think too.
So it's not so good.
Um, but what is again the like, and solutions is the wrong word.
It's really like, what, what is the blue sky?
What is the, let's go back in time.
Um, yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you, if you could have been in those rooms, what is the Mario Kart ride?
Well, I would have handcuffed myself to the desk until they listened to me at a certain
point, but yes, I think, I think it's probably like just rip radiators springs off and just
add, like just still steal it.
Sure.
And it's a big, like it's, it's darker or it's dark ride scenes that you're slower
for and then you get fast at the end.
Yeah, and there's a little bursts of speed and oh my gosh, you almost hit, you know,
Bowser, you know, whatever.
And then at the end it's rainbow road and it's probably inside.
You almost hit Bowser.
Yeah.
20 feet rocket rod straight away.
You almost got him.
And then like, yeah, like you're gonna, you know, there'll be a couple in the same way
that the, that on the poos, honey hut and in the, uh, runaway railway, there's like
vehicles that are just robots or just like a, a figure of like one of the other character
racers.
So you get the sense that you're racing against the actual characters.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
And then you go in and out.
I mean, there's also a version of it where it's just like an elevated it's like, it's,
I don't know if they, do they have any wifi controlled like Disney style rides?
I don't think so.
No, no, but it's like that to like runaway railway technology and you're just kind of
zooming around this room.
And well, you don't have a speed problem there too.
I was thinking about this too, cause yeah, it is like Disney completely did what it should
be, but they can't access that technology.
Literally would have to be something different, but they're patenting patenting patenting
patenting.
What did I say?
It's not panting ting.
I know that.
Panting, panting, we were, I was up late for the, they are panting,
Tiram Tiram,
Yeah, that's right.
Right.
Sure is.
It's late.
Uh, uh, yeah.
Like they're, they're doing all the weird, cool stuff.
Like there's different crazy things that they've like put down on paper that they might use
one day, like stuff where like little houses like kind of open up and different, like big
show building things for like a live show where the audience moves up and down.
Like they're doing crazy stuff or working on crazy stuff here and there.
So I don't think it would be too big of a stretch for them to figure out a version of
what Disney does.
Yeah.
Um, I think, yeah, I, I, I think they, it is, they got caught on one detail, which sounds
cool and it's, I think we were open to how this could work the whole time they were developing
it, the idea that you're seeing your opponents and the goggles and that, cause that is, it
is a big part of Mario Kart is, you know, crazy high.
It's not even just that there are other racers is that they're like spilling out in crazy
ways with shells and banana peels, but speed, you do need speed.
I think it's more important.
I think if there were just occasional brushes with other cars, that would be plenty.
And I was thinking, I was thinking of another route and tell me what you think of this,
but okay.
Here's a, here's a ride that feels, uh, nobody's ever complained about that.
That wasn't exciting or that was slow, even though it's a little ride, Mr. Toad's wild
ride.
Yeah, for sure.
That is like, is that not a more intense mad cap experience than Mario Kart?
It for sure is due to tinier vehicle hairpin turns, barely missing stuff the entire way.
And I'm not saying use that ride track, but is there, is there a way that's a little more
lo-fi and where you are whipping around or it's somewhere between that and a wild mouse
where it could be almost the same plot of land, but you pack more in.
And I like the idea of right.
Vehicles being smaller because Mario carts are smaller.
You think about like little Mario and little toad in their car that matches them.
Is it not those go-karts are small.
That's the fun of being in a go-kart.
You feel speed more because they're close to the ground.
They're little.
Yeah.
And so being in a big weighty car kind of makes that impossible unless you're doing,
unless you're doing radiator Springs and it's incredible massive technology that's letting
you go super fast.
I started dreaming of a, a Mr. Toad that is in a building the size of transformers and
imagine what you could pack into that and half of it, it could be like the mummy where
you know, like there's, there's little scenes you go in, but then you launch and a bunch
of really fast stuff.
I know we're not describing a launch mechanism, but like, doesn't that sound okay?
I got a, I got a truly, this is okay.
This is good.
This is very, very good.
I think you, if you like, if you did a ride like that, but say it was Mr. Toad, but there
were eight different ways you start the ride.
So like, you know, there's eight cars and there's four people per car and basically
how you load the ride is that everybody gets in the car and then all eight cars start out
the same.
So it's basically, it's closer to, you know, practical sets and stuff, but then the cars
like a Mr. Toad were eight cars going separate ways and going in and out and weaving in and
out of each other, even in not something that has like the most epic scale would still feel
like Mario Kart.
Well, yeah, and you could even have like, you don't actually need eight different paths.
You could have like two or three different paths and cheat it.
In my version, you need eight.
Well, your blue sky version, you would get eight different traps.
Because you would feel like there's a, I guess you could do four at once or whatever, but
then the ride capacities, I'm trying to think practically here as well.
Well, sure.
But I also, I know we're blue sky-ing, but eight altogether.
That's like, you've never seen a ride like that.
That's crazy.
Well, that's why we're breaking new ground here.
I know.
That's what you should do, but imagine like the, all right, like the thick, just like
in terms of how thick every turn and room has to be to have the room for eight entire
tracks.
We can try six.
We can like, we can blue sky this, but like, imagine you're going, everyone has their own
kind of separate thing and like you go, you go in one room alone sort of, and all of a
sudden like Bowser, a big like, you know, practical Bowser, you almost hit him.
He zooms right.
You go left and all of a sudden you're like head on with a different car full of humans.
You go, you split off there, you go in a little different room and you like, you again, another
show scene with like a different, like a Koopa Troopa or Princess Peach or something back
out and then the end is like maybe a little faster kind of stretch somewhere.
Yeah.
I think what you are, what you're each describing, like Scott, you were talking about like classical
themed entertainment tricks and design and like stuff where it's like, um, you, that,
that makes stuff like Mr. Toad, which decades and decades old, like still hold up and feel
like you're out of control.
And Mike, you're talking about like little variations, little randomized things like
those randomized songs from guardians of the galaxy.
Right.
And you get into the different little carts and they're a little, and yeah, you feel like
it's, it feels a little bit more authentic to the experience.
You feel like, I don't know, you're getting a cohesive experience one way or the other.
I was about to say a different, a totally different idea would even be something like
flight of passage where you build little cars and then stick the cars in front of like a
crazy screen.
So you're going to do the VR experience except that maybe like it's like flight of passage
where all you can see is screen.
Like I almost kind of wish it was just that if we're going to the video game, let's do
the craziest version of the video game we can do like some high budget digital flight
of passage where you've got a steering wheel and there's some interactivity.
Right.
And maybe it's just shooting shells and you don't steer as much.
I found the steering really stupid.
Yeah, it's not, it's nothing.
Because you don't steer it.
It just says like, oh, steer right.
And then you're all supposed to go right.
And I think you get points for doing that, but the car doesn't react to the steering.
Yeah.
It would be impossible to do that with a car full of people.
So it's like, it's like, it's kind of like the Millennium Falcon thing where it's like,
it's an overthink here.
This is an overthink to get everybody to do something to make it feel like the experience.
It's like, if you're not going to be able to steer the car, I don't want to pretend
to steer the car.
That's I understand like the having that there so you can aim the shells sort of works more.
Get like, uh, you know, make it rise the resistance, make there, there's a character on board
doing the, if you were on with a little, with a, with a towed head or any other character,
I, that's pretty fun.
They're driving and you're out of control because they're bad drivers.
You know, you don't, you're missing a couple of things here.
You're missing, you got no drift.
There's no drift.
That's a huge part of Mario Kart.
Drift is fun.
Yeah.
Apparently if all four of you work together, you'll get the points and you'll drift.
And I think what the car itself will drift or it's just like tells you you're drifting
tells you where you get the coins worth it.
Is it double dash?
Is that the one where you kind of work with a there's two, two people in the car or it's
you and a computer character.
You have a computer.
Yeah.
And that's the one.
What they were trying to cause they, I like that they picked little elements from different
games.
There's secret stuff too.
This is what I'm saying.
Like I will be going on this and there's like secret boxes and blocks to hit, I guess on
the ride.
And there's a bunch of hidden little things that do seem fun to try to explore.
But if it's like dad should be going on this, I'm talking about a random dad, not me, but
like a random dad should be going on this first time.
Any dad should be going on the first time and going, Oh, pretty, that was cool versus
like so, so yeah.
I know it sounds crazy after all this complaining.
I did say that I got off like, Hey, that was fun.
I do think you will feel it's just, I think it's just thinking about what could have been.
I think completely there is a better Mario Kart attraction.
And I also, I do agree that maybe there's, although I think you're, you're damned if
you do it down, if you don't, because if they did a Mario dark ride, everybody would be
saying why isn't it Mario Kart?
I think the ride had to be Mario Kart.
Right?
Oh, probably.
I mean, yes, it could be a Mario dark ride where like a chunk of it is Mario Kart.
Like, I mean, I think ultimately, yeah.
When it was being built to be like, Oh, it should have been Mario Kart.
That makes the most sense.
And then if it was awesome, people would not have said that.
But yeah, I mean, I get why the first one is Mario Kart.
It just, it's, it makes the most sense.
And it sounds like you're in a ride vehicle.
Yeah.
You're not a plumber walking on foot.
Yes.
Yeah.
Mario doesn't have a, well, if you were, you know, what I'd like to be in is like the, you
know, the big boot or whatever.
Oh yes.
Was that when he hops around in, in Mario three, one of our sagas weren't, didn't you get in
a big boot?
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, I believe I did.
Very satisfying.
Yeah.
I look back on it fondly.
You were in a big boot.
It was, it was wonderful as all our meals.
I think, but, but Mario is like intrinsically, you can design a rock because you just go
through a pipe or is it super Mario galaxy where you go to different little planets.
Yeah.
And you go and like, you get stuck in their orbit and you shoot around like you're in
an Apollo mission.
You're trying to get home.
It feels like a designer stream.
It's like, okay, guess what?
You can either go to another planet or a down a pipe and you can go anywhere.
Well and you could go to new Donk city.
Sure.
New Donk city from, from Odyssey, Super Mario Odyssey, which is so fun.
What happens in new Donk city?
Oh, you're just going back.
It's like, it's kind of a very like high risey kind of city and you know, you swinging around
on like poles and stuff.
Like a Coruscant kind of thing.
It's a little more old school than a Coruscant.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I see.
It's like New York city.
Oh, I remember.
New Donk city is a lot like New Donk city rules.
But you can bother people.
There's like regular, yeah, there's like a human.
Yeah.
And you're doing a bunch of different stuff.
Mario Odyssey.
Well, you guys should pull it.
Get, I mean, I guess you could just borrow my switch at one point, but you really should
play Mario Odyssey.
Yeah.
Yes.
With Cappy.
Oh, right.
I mean, he has different outfits and you can mix and match his outfits, little pants and
his shirt.
Oh, just pinstripe suit.
Okay.
That's really good.
Look at Mario.
Just look up Mario Odyssey outfits.
You can put him in like a full tux, like a full like white tux with a big top hat.
I think I've been over your old apartment and you're like, Oh, I've shown you his outfits.
You got to look at some of these outfits.
He gets in like little trunks and stuff.
Oh my God.
Santa?
Yeah.
Oh, it's so good.
He's got an ax in his head.
He's a zombie.
And Cappy is like a ball gown.
Yes.
You can put him a ball gown, which is really fun.
And then you collect all these outfits as you go and you sort of dress him.
That's a big part of Zelda too.
What's fun is like in the last one is that Link gets a lot of different outfits, but
those are more practical because like there's big like wintery lands and you give him an
outfit that keeps him warm.
You can't like Jason, when he stripped him naked, that would not be good in the winter
land.
And when Jason lit the horse on fire when I had first got the switch many years ago.
But does Mario Odyssey give you the option for him to take all his clothes off and put
them on Sonic?
No.
So the answer is yes, we will not rest.
I know we will.
And we will keep dreaming of better Mario ride.
You do also, what you're saying about pipes and stuff, Jason, is like maybe they're, I
don't mean, you don't want to just do, I don't like, I don't want another, I don't want a
Mario forbidden journey, but you know, flying behind him when he's got a cape or the mushroom
or the, I'm sorry, the raccoon suit or like, or then now you're, and then suddenly you're
underwater.
The Tanooki suit.
The Eastern New York with Jimmy Fallon does.
You fly with him.
You go underwater.
You go through a big pipe.
You know what?
Oh my God.
This is a horrifying thing I'm about to say.
Go ahead.
When in the end of the ride, when the, when the, the tonight rider shoots the tube and
you go from the moon down back to New York city through the tube, that is more like Rainbow
Road than the Rainbow Road part of Mario Kart.
You think.
I have more of my skin is crawling that I am saying this.
Is it not a more satisfying?
Jimmy Fallon is more Mario than Mario.
You think Jimmy Fallon and the Tonight Show band and the audience should get the universal
cup.
Oh, we didn't even talk about it.
Which I really like is that you're racing in the universal cup, which is really great.
And they use the universal music at the end, a little part of the stain.
The glow.
So that's really fun.
I think that's pretty funny.
I just say it's a cute kid story really quick.
The last time we went to universal together, we went on the star way, which he likes in
general because he yells steep the whole time.
Starway is one of his favorite things, but they play music throughout and he doesn't
know most of it.
He doesn't know staying alive, but the universal fanfare plays.
And then he starts yelling something and we're like, what is he yelling?
How does he know that it's at the beginning of the Thomas, the tank engine DVDs.
So he's yelling Thomas DVD.
Thomas DVD.
He's so happy that we're, we're on a steep thing that's playing the Thomas DVD music.
I like, uh, that's, this is some of this good dad stuff for your life.
Oh, I'm seeing, I've been on the star way a million times why it might even have lost
its luster through a child's eyes who thinks that a DVD is starting a 15 year old DVD and
then he'll get to see a minions preview and an ad for a vacation to a hard rock resort
in the Bahamas where Barney is.
Oh, I watched all the VHS.
I will watch every trailer again and again when I was rewatching the movie.
That's like, see, that's what they're hoping for.
They're hoping kids go on that star way and they pointed all the newly painted sound stages
at the peacock dots and it's peacock peacock dots.
Oh man.
Yeah.
That's like, if I got to go on a ride that was just a new line cinema logo or some, like
I got to like a part of the start of some video or TV, like that was associated.
I met, I got face to face with the DreamWorks Fisher boy.
I got to cast a line with the famous boy.
Maybe that'll be in the Texas park.
I better do the Fisher boy.
Anybody's listening who's working on it.
You know, if you cannot build DreamWorks land without a, an intimate moment with the DreamWorks
Fisher boy, I don't think I realized for a long time that that was a boy sitting on the
moon fishing.
I thought it was like some creature monster.
Yeah.
It was like a, Oh, his outline.
He's a little boy, a little boy down into some sort of liquid.
No, he is.
He's sitting on the, on the end of a crescent moon, which size wise makes him, uh, you know,
like a, he's like a several miles high.
I mean, the joke, you're, you are right, Jason, that if he was real, the DreamWorks boy would
crush our town and everyone we know.
Yeah.
People just horrified.
Oh no, it's a quarter.
What's up?
What?
What is that?
Something's coming down from the moon.
He's got a giant line.
He's fishing for us.
He's fishing humans.
It would make more sense as the DreamWorks logo.
Because at least you have Ron Howard behind the scenes and he was Andy Griffith show,
little boy.
That's true.
They were always walking down the fishing hole, started every episode.
There was a, yeah, the credits credits.
Here's an idea.
There were no credits.
They're starting.
Yeah.
The credits.
Start of every episode.
Yeah.
Your idea for free, like everybody's monetizing their in-house IP.
DreamWorks is not doing anything with the boy.
Horror movie with the boy where he, he comes down from the moon and we see what the fuck
happens.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, let's get on that too.
A lot of great ideas today.
Oh, sure.
I'm sure there's gotta be Blumhouse offices on the back lot.
We know there's Amblin office.
There's this giant Amblin like compound back there.
Oh, what if the, wait a minute.
This is all Spielberg.
DreamWorks fishing boy does battle with ET.
ET?
With Elliot?
Oh yeah.
Elliot fights the moon.
They fight Elliot.
They fight past the moon and the boy gets mad.
Hey, I'm the only boy around these parts.
And ET's healing touch has to help Elliot win.
You know what?
Fishing boy versus bike boy, no matter who wins.
The audience wins.
The moviegoer public wins.
America's hearts win.
Speaking of boy, I just want to show you the Johnny Pops boy right there.
Do you see him in the top right corner?
Yeah.
It looks suspiciously like me.
So surprising.
I haven't seen it.
Another food mask.
Oh, he's exactly like Jason.
Oh, jeepers.
Jeez Louise.
He's on every pop.
Jeez Johnny Wevin.
You've been eating your own pops.
You know what I was thinking about recently?
I feel like I cannot remember ever eating an official bomb pop.
What?
I've had bomb pop flavored things.
Well, it was chocolate boy.
You never had like just a standard bomb pop with the white, red and blue?
We were like popsicle or icy kind of, what are the sleeves called that you push?
Oh, oh, oh.
Yeah.
Why can't I think of the name of the official, you know?
Otter Pops is the official brand.
Otter Pops is the brand one.
Yeah.
But I don't know what you would call them without.
You guys are on your own here.
You've never eaten an Otter Pop?
I don't know if I can start this.
I think I know.
You know those like little like plastic sleeves.
Yeah, I know what Otter Pop is.
I don't know what the bomb.
Well, bomb pops are different.
Bomb pops are just the red, white and blue.
It's the red, white and blue.
It looks like a rocket ship.
Looks like a little missile.
I've had heart seltzer as bomb pop.
Jason never had a bomb pop.
You've had a bomb pop.
I don't think I've had a bomb pop.
Red, white and blue popsicle?
Not at a bomb pop.
I'm not even like saying you need to do it.
I'm just surprised as a kid you wouldn't have had one of them.
I don't know.
Missed that one.
Huh.
You've had a dreamsicle though.
Oh, all the time.
It's got dreamsicle?
I've been on a dreamsicle drive.
Well, of course.
But you've eaten a dreamsicle?
I believe so.
You're not sure though.
It's been a long time.
Really?
I'm not you.
I don't have.
I don't have a weekly dreamsicle shipment.
I don't drink alcoholic dreamsicles as my go-to beverage.
But this is not yet.
I don't have a weekly dreamsicle shipment.
I don't drink alcoholic dreamsicles as my go-to beverage.
But this is not yet.
This is not.
I'm asking last week, did you have a dreamsicle?
I'm saying the first 20 years of your life, did you have a dreamsicle?
I said I think I did.
Is this not sufficient for you?
It's not.
It's weird.
I need to have concrete dreamsicle memories.
Yeah.
Well, but for sure.
To escape this episode.
Did you have a Flintstones push-up for sure when you were a kid?
Yes, all the time.
Oh, yeah.
What about the Mickey Donald ones that were shaped like their bodies?
I don't know.
Jason, you know what I'm talking about?
I know what you're talking about.
I don't think I gravitated towards them, but I do kind of remember eating the shit.
I think I remember eating the bodies.
Eating Mickey's head, yeah.
Okay.
Well, that's sort of a memory.
You see these articles like, do you remember this?
If you're a 90s kid, you're like, you're not sure enough about it.
I'm a 90s kid.
Remember it or don't.
Don't ask the question.
I am upset with the articles.
I am yelling, yes, of course I remember.
And I'm saying not only do I remember being a 90s kid, I also know what kids are up to
now too.
I'm relevant in all decades.
I remember that and I know exactly what 2020s teens are up to.
I'm at the hot topic.
I'm handing out bomb pops to them.
I'm telling them about my idea for Mario and Sonic to switch clothes in front of each other.
I'm irrelevant.
Look guys, here's the, I'm going to make another comparison.
I think that just in similar, in recent theme park dynamics, I think however you feel, even
if we come around on it, if we like, I did like it the first time we might ebb and flow
on this ride, but I think ultimately it is the Millennium Falcon Smuggler's Run of Mario,
of Super Nintendo World.
It is the, it's all right, but I hope that the big one is really great.
And the big one, unfortunately for us here in Hollywood is the Donkey Kong coaster.
And we don't know if we're going to get it.
We don't know where it's going to go.
We don't know if they'll get the clearance to demolish Transformers forever and put the
Donkey Kong coaster in there.
Demolish the office building.
Demolish the skyscraper.
Build it on top of the Transformers building.
That sounds great.
Just go vertical.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Love that.
Yeah.
Make it higher.
But I mean, am I right though?
Like I think now all hopes are on, like I think we still need our e-ticket Nintendo attraction
and it's a bummer because I'm not sure we're going to get it here.
They are getting it in Japan.
We know they are.
They're just building it right away at Epic Universe with it.
And we'll do it there, but I hope we get it here too.
Yeah, I know.
I think I get a feeling that we'll have it.
I just don't, it probably won't be before it opens in Epic Universe, I'm guessing, but
who knows?
I hope I'm wrong about that.
But yes, now it does feel like, yeah, it feels like we want for the definitive ride.
It doesn't feel like this is it.
And I'm wondering what people will say after they ride.
I know a lot of people have done it already, but I wonder if this is, I feel like it's
going to, I don't feel like we're being, this is not going to be unpopular, I don't think.
I think most people probably will feel similarly, but maybe I'm wrong.
I think so.
I think they tried to have too much game, too many game elements and like, man, we tease
sometimes about how much people talk about story, but like, I was kind of missing, like,
ah, kind of could have used more of a A to B story on this one.
Sure.
Yeah.
I think William Pilken's better.
Ah, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, you get the buttons.
You get tactiles and say, I know.
And they give you, you really feel that.
You're in the actual cockpit.
It's exactly the same.
The video, there's the ride itself leaves stuff to be desired.
And I, you know, my, my complaints about the actual, like who's doing what and it's a little
too busy and there needs to be a different ride, like a level basically.
But you get that sweet coaxing.
You get the coaxium and, uh, yeah.
It has to stay as cold as a bomb pop.
Yes.
Ooh.
Which is very, a Johnny pop, which has to be extra cold.
Cause they're expensive.
They have to be, they have to be kept.
I have to bring a cooler to the sprouts.
You need a cooler hallway.
I need a cool hold what hallway from the sprouts to, uh, our house and underground tunnel,
underground, cool hallway pops.
But until you have that, uh, uh, yeah, Hey, we're open.
I don't know.
Uh, curious what everybody thinks is this controversial or not.
Um, but for now you survived podcast, the ride.
The only reason I'm going to stop you is because I think you said contra, controversial because
of universal purpose.
No, I said, it's a contra very calculated.
If if it's a universal hot take, then it's, uh, I think it should potentially controversial
going forward.
We should be saying controversial before, like give that as a disclaimer before that
I liked the tiramisu.
Is that controversial?
That old improv habits.
No mistakes.
Only gifts.
Yeah.
That's right.
Especially not for me.
It was not a mistake.
It was very much done.
It was on purpose.
Um, so yeah, I don't know.
Uh, we'll, we'll see what people think.
And you know, I mean, mainly I'm feeling like we're a little harsh there.
You think Comcast can take the hit?
Yeah.
I think they can.
Jason thinks they can.
I want to apologize.
What they charge for cable and internet.
Well that's look, Jason speaks for himself.
I want to like to apologize to Comcast.
All the good people at Comcast.
You already did for saying that they cheaped out on that kitchen and shared with band express.
Yeah.
I made a lot of errors and I apologize.
I actually know what I don't apologize to the people of Comcast.
I'm apologizing to the company, to the entity, the corporate, this corporation is a person
that's got more rights than us.
We're so sorry to Comcast.
Um, Hey, for three bonus episodes every month, uh, including one that we just did about the
beloved, but unarchived local show, King Koopa's cool cartoons, uh, and other bullshit like
that.
You can go to podcast, the ride, the second gate and our VIP tier club three.
We'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
Um, so on behalf of my co-hosts, Mike Carlson and Johnny pop, thanks for listening.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett bomb, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.