Forever...
Dog.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a theme park podcast hosted by three men whose only problem with
going to the DMV is that the queue isn't themed enough.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Scott Gardner.
Oh yeah, if you give us something to look at instead of just the ugly mugs next to me,
you give me a story, you give me an original DMV character, you make it seem like a mission
that I have to go on.
Yeah, and a narrative immersive with like, yeah, like either like a car that's not a Disney car's
car, but like an original DMV creation.
Oh sure, yeah, yeah, a talking car that's like, you know, like you don't get to get in me until...
Right, yeah, he's really cocky about it too.
Jason Sheridan, you have any thoughts on that?
I want someone in me.
Well, I would say I don't even need the theming if you were to have the DMV on just like,
another thing that's going to come up a lot today, massive scale.
If the DMV buildings were just gigantic, and I realize I'm probably describing a
bureaucratic nightmare.
So you want the DMV to...
1984 Brazil.
Oh, interesting.
So you want it to not only have like a more of an immersive cue, you want an e-ticket DMV.
I just big, just like huge.
Big budget DMV.
With like small rooms, big rooms, there's a cave, but then there's a big palace.
Yeah, there's little puzzles where, yeah, but it's a cave and it's got the lowest ceiling.
It's like the room we're in right now.
Like it is a regular ass ceiling that you are traveling.
So I mean, I wouldn't call this a cave, but yeah.
You do like an eye test with somebody dressed as like a princess or something.
They have like administer the eye test.
Sure, or any one of a number of costume characters.
And then it would be like letters in a different like fun made up language.
So it wouldn't just be the normal American alphabet.
Yeah, so it's testing your vision, but you also have to go by your gut sometimes.
And yeah, and spikes and ropes.
And if you drop the, if you pull the rope, you hear somebody fight.
The Indiana Jones, Q, specifically, it seems like is what we're just,
we just, all we ask is that the DMV be the Indiana Jones line.
And it would be the most popular place, I think.
And we've really solved an issue here today.
Yeah, well, productive episode.
Yeah, we could stop now and it would be a great podcast.
But we won't.
Mission accomplished.
Yeah, because we got a whole thing to talk about.
Uh-huh.
We have a good work here too.
We're globetrotting today.
We get to look at a nation we've never discussed anything from.
That's exciting.
I know it is.
But let's bring our guest in.
She reviews films for the New York Times.
She hosts the movie podcast Unspooled.
It's Amy Nicholson joining us.
Hi, everyone.
Hi, how are you?
I'm so excited to be here.
I want the DMV to be more like,
did you ever see that old Nickelodeon game show, Finders Keepers?
Oh yeah.
I'm a big Finders Keeper.
That's my favorite one.
That's my dream.
That's all I want Escape Rooms to be, is like a big giant Finders Keepers.
You get to tear through like dressers and drawers and upending things.
If you could go to the DMV and open Matilda's drawers and start rifling through,
try to find the magic pen that you need to stamp your card.
That's all I want is more action.
Yeah, sure.
If they can give you that on the way, then you forget the logistics nature of it.
If it's like Finders Keepers and some of the mess makes sense,
but some of it they just kind of need mess in bulk.
So there's just a drawer full of ping pong balls, just kind of arbitrary.
Yeah, right.
Well, that'll pop on camera.
I don't know why this young child's bedroom is a drawer entirely full of ping pong balls,
but why not?
Totally.
Or what if at the center of the DMV was a big statue of Gavin Newsom?
Now I'm merging it a little bit into Doubledare, but you had to crawl up his nose.
Oh wow, yeah, or fall out of his nose.
Whoa.
Yeah, and there's like goo in there.
There's like snot, like Nickelodeon slime and Gavin Newsom's nose.
That would be fun.
I have one more punch up to this.
What if you don't have to or get to have your driver's license at the end of it?
Let's eliminate the driver's license part of it, too.
So now what we're describing is a fun maze adventure without that boring part.
I think we fixed the DMV completely.
OK, yeah, yeah.
So it has nothing to do with like handing out license or revoking.
No, because that's like, you know, after everything we've set up now,
doesn't that seem like kind of a letdown, like kind of not a fun finale?
Instead, it should go out on like a three minute ride or so.
OK, yeah.
Or hear me out.
What if at the very end, after you've like dug through the ping pong balls,
after you've climbed through Gavin Newsom's slimy nose,
what if they take a picture of you with whatever you look like at that state,
covered in goo, covered in pudding, and that picture has to follow you around for the rest of your life?
Whoa.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it will like if you get pulled over by the police,
will they see like it would come up on a screen or something?
They'll be like, oh, you covered in Gavin Newsom's, sorry, Gavin goo, Gavin goo.
It seems like you already ran through it.
I'm going to let you off with just a warning.
I think, you know, everybody puts so much pressure on their driver's license photos,
and I think maybe it's that's actually a path to a better picture because you're caught
unaware, natural, having been through some really strange experiences.
But despite the goo, it might be a better looking picture of any of us than the one we actually have.
Yeah, you're probably right.
It's more you because it's like it's so natural.
It's a natural photo.
It's organic.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, no, thinking they should make us all do it at puberty,
and that should be your online dating profile up until you find your person.
Because it's more if you see the real them coming out of the goo,
you see are they a frustrated person?
Are they overjoyed?
Are they gleeful, maniacal?
Yeah.
It's a really good shortcut.
A way to just like see someone's actual base in a way.
Wow.
Would anyone ever date again if that was the case?
Should we in the first place?
Well, that's a whole nother.
Yeah.
That feels like a good conversation starter, though, putting up like your high school,
your high school, like the fake gown or the fake tuxedo.
They take the Velcro off you and then they put it on the next purse.
Oh, you're saying you're calling it fake, the tuxedo you would rent when you go to prom?
No, no.
We did class photos and it was just like the false front of a tuxedo.
Wait a minute.
This is really weird.
I didn't know what you were talking about.
You just got a fake tuxedo.
Cancel the topic of the episode.
Cancel this topic.
Sorry, Amy.
You did a lot of research.
We're going to talk about Jason's fake tuxedo you wear in high school.
Well, because then it was like a fake gown and pearls for the girls and for the guys.
It was like if you went to an old time, like old West photo where like everyone's like a cowboy
or a can can.
That sort of thing where it's just like you put your arms in and then they Velcro off the back
and then they take the photo and take it off and do it to the next guy.
This is unbelievable.
Wait, have you ever heard something like this?
No.
Does it have a bow tie?
I want to make sure I'm picturing this.
Yeah, there's a bow tie.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
But for the women.
Okay, there's kind of like a base of tuxedo, which that's strange enough.
You want your class photos in a tuxedo.
But then like women are going to want more variance in what they're wearing.
They don't want to all just be in pearls with multiple options.
This is 20 years ago at this point.
Sure.
But I'm sure it went on for a little while after.
But my question remains where there at least like here's the purple one and here's the
green one and here's the yellow one.
I don't think there was.
Everyone was like dressed like Marge Simpson.
I think you would go up and you would do too.
You would do your formal one and then they'd give you like a graduation,
you know, mortarboard and they couldn't trust kids to wear a shirt and tie.
No, other schools did this where it's like you got to pick what you wanted your senior
photo, what you were wearing or what you wanted it to be.
So if you wanted cowboy, you could have cowboy.
I think you could.
You could pick if you did it yourself.
Like it's like you can put in whatever one you want, but you're on your own if you don't
want the tuxedo or graduation gown.
Okay, I have to back you up a little bit.
Yeah.
I went to an all girls school and we did have the pearl thing.
Yeah, we had a pearl thing and it was sort of like a black v-neck tunic that they draped
over us.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And then I brought my own pearls from my grandmother because I was like, I need this
to be a little personal.
But if you didn't bring your own pearls, wow, but bring your own pearls to the all girls
Catholic high school graduation.
I just realized how I sound.
But yeah, then you had the vest.
But because it was all girl, I've never heard about a Velcro tuxedo with a bow.
That's just blowing my mind.
I don't know how that would even fit because a drape is a drape, but a bow is something
else.
Yeah, like I'm sure if you look at them, it's like, oh yeah, there's like an inch long gap
on that collar.
How fast can you get us this photo of you?
Yes, well, before the episode comes out.
How many minutes will it take?
Well, we can just look, let's give him a week.
How many seconds does it take to you get?
Here's the thing.
If I do this, I'm going out on a limb because I don't like this photo.
I don't look good at 17.
On a limb.
In a fake tuxedo at 17?
I've got very small glasses.
My friends were encouraging me to get oval glasses, but no one said make it a little
bigger for your little doe face.
Maybe go a little bigger on those ovals.
All right.
Can we put, we'll pay wall the photo at least so you know it's okay.
Sure, sure.
So on the highest tier on our Patreon, you can see this photo, I think.
Okay.
That's how we'll do it.
Then for Amy, I don't want to make you show us that photo of you, but I just, I do just
want to see a page from your yearbook with like 40 girls all wearing the same fake dress.
That's the weirdest thing ever.
I can easily get that for you.
Okay, great.
I can get that for you today.
Okay.
I'll give it to you for free even.
Oh wow, thank you.
No permission from the girls.
Doesn't matter.
We're not looking at your faces.
We're looking at your weird tunics.
Sorry, Kathy.
I'll just apologize now.
Wow.
Oh my God.
I gotta calm down now.
Need to palette cleanse.
Yeah, I got too excited there.
All right, all right.
We have a different topic though today.
It's a place.
Here's the thing.
I was watching videos and I feel like I got the name.
I don't, somebody say the name of this place.
I've heard it like three different ways at this point.
Amy, do you know the actual name of this place because I don't feel it's secure enough saying it.
We're all putting ourself out on a limb by.
Before I came here, I actually tried to look up the pronunciation too and I heard three
different ways.
So I can only say it the wrong way, which is the way I've always said it.
Sure.
What is it?
Latte World Adventure.
Okay.
Latte is the way I heard it also.
So that makes me that was the last YouTuber who said it.
I saw multiple sources that are low.
I saw low.
And I maybe trust these a little more because they are in they are in prints.
They are in more official articles and the bloggers.
I don't know.
Do they know?
I think we just got to say anything goes.
Okay.
And listeners, if you live for listener knows for sure, you're going to have to cut all of us a break.
If you if you look on YouTube and you look up, you know, the latte Lotte Company,
there's a Korean news network and I saw three different anchors and I heard three
different pronunciations because the one guy was British, someone was Australian,
someone was Korean.
So I kind of got it every which way.
It might help if we go to the origin of how it was named this in the first place.
Yes.
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh, wait and wait and just very really quick.
This is a theme park in I mean, it's a mega complex, but this is in Seoul, South Korea,
and you have been to this place.
I have I have I was there for a film festival and we took a day off and ran around and had the
greatest day.
Oh, geez.
Great.
Okay.
Very excited to hear about it.
But yes, the the backstory of the company feel yes, feel free.
Okay.
So Lotte is a giant corporation.
Like think about the giants that we have here in America and just ascribe it one of those.
I'd say it's maybe bigger than Coca-Cola, Walmart size.
It's huge.
Wow.
And it started as a candy company.
Part of the story behind it is that the founder is this man named Shin Kyokoh.
He grew up on a pig farm, you know, during the war.
He wanted to be a novelist.
But so he was very broke, one of 10 kids.
And he's when he's like a very young kid, he goes from Korea to Japan.
He smuggles himself over on a boat because World War II history,
World War II is about to start.
It hasn't quite started yet.
But they're, you know, under the territory of Japan at that moment.
So he sneaks over there on this boat.
He doesn't have a lot of money.
He tries to figure out how to make some money.
And World War II happens.
He starts seeing these American soldiers giving out gum to the people in Japan after it's over.
And he's like, I should have a gum company.
So he's like, I'm going to make gum, but I need a name for my gum company.
And because this guy is, you know, a young aspiring novelist, or he had been, he read
a lot of literature and he was really obsessed with the works of Goethe.
Goethe, like the novelist philosopher from the 1700s.
He goes up to Goethe is like a huge influence on Kierkegaard.
Why am I saying all of this right now at the beginning of this podcast?
No, no, it's interesting.
Oh my God.
And it's actually actually well researched and well presented information.
Yes.
We strive to, but we miss sometimes.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
So Goethe, you know, I also have down here that he's a massive influence on Mieche Young.
Okay, sure.
I just want to be able to say all these fun names.
Goethe, his breakout novel was a novel that was called something like The Sorrows of Young Werther.
And that's this love triangle where like a guy dies, spoiler alert,
but the guy is in love with a woman named Charlotte.
Gotcha.
Maybe you see where I'm going with this.
Yes.
So he loves this book by Goethe with a girl named Charlotte.
And he's like, I could take the name Charlotte and use it to be the name of my gum company.
So he cuts off the char and he goes with lot, I guess.
Lot, which again confuses it because it's a new way to say it.
It's totally a new way to say it.
Yeah.
But so that is how lots, latte, lotte.
Should we just pick one?
Yeah, I guess so.
Latte though makes me think of coffee, obviously.
Yeah, that's a little confusing.
Lotte?
I think it's okay that it reminds you of coffee because that's the first time I came across it.
Right, right, right.
Because he expands really quickly.
He goes from like gum to booze, vitamins, hot dogs.
Canned coffee is how I first had him in Japan.
They sell a lot of canned coffee with the brand on it.
Then they expand further.
They go into like clothes, hotels, movie theaters, banks.
Chemicals, I saw.
It's a big chemical company.
Yeah, shipping, coordination of boats, electronics.
They own a baseball team.
This is just an everything company.
The most popular baseball team in Korea, I saw.
They own and made the biggest baseball team.
It's insane.
I had not heard this word before.
You just came across the brand name in Japan organically.
Yeah, but then if you start looking for it, you'll start seeing it everywhere here.
I mean, I live in Koreatown, so when I go shopping at my grocery store, it's everywhere.
But yeah, if you keep your eyes out, they're just massive.
Their company headquarters in Seoul is like 123 stories.
It's the sixth biggest building in the world.
And this man, Shin, lives forever.
He doesn't die until January 2020 at the age of 98.
Setting up this secession style showdown with his two kids.
There's a lot of lawsuits.
He's actually sentenced to four years in prison for tax evasion when he's 95.
But they're like, you're so old and you're about to die.
It's cool.
This is the backdrop of Lotte World Adventure.
Wow.
What a dynamic, exciting.
Disney is maybe the biggest company with theme parks, but this almost feels like some bigger,
more unfit, like Pfizer has theme parks or something.
Yes, yes, it does.
A big, weird, nefarious company.
It's almost closer to Comcast.
And that Comcast has a movie studio, a television network, internet and cable and phone service.
But if I can also...
The other thing about this company, I had never heard about this before.
And it was very fascinating to learn about this.
In South Korea, Lotte is a company called a Chebol.
And these are massive conglomerates that are controlled by one person or one family.
So again, very successionary.
Of course, this company, there was some money malfeasance.
They were raided a few years ago, investigated by authorities.
But I watched a Vice documentary called South Korea's Untouchable Families to set that up.
Because I think Lotte, it's not even one of the Samsung and Hyundai, or the massive Chebols.
And this one is big, but it is not on that level.
And the whole thing is that everyone is proud of these companies for saving the economy.
And by saving the economy, I mean in the 1970s, the government just went,
all right, you're doing cars, you're doing semiconductors, you're doing...
Just gave them money and power and stuff.
And so, I mean, it's a little comforting to know there's another country out there like ours,
where it's just like, oh, there's five big companies that rule your life.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Yeah, I know, with a particular, slightly different lineage.
And the weird factor of that, they love this, we owe the Chebols everything.
But then around the time that the founder of Lotte starts having problems,
there's a wave of, now we're mad at all of them.
Now we're going to try to root out corruption in all of these.
Because not only is there the Lotte stuff, after which, yeah, so they decide,
never mind, you don't have to go to jail because you're old and falling apart.
Too old for jail.
But we are going to take your daughter, your daughter's going to jail,
and we have some questions for your vice chairman.
And like, oh, questions, really?
Yes, I'll be with you in a minute.
He commits suicide hours before he is supposed to talk to investigators.
So that all is happening.
And then Samsung, as you mentioned, Jason, the executive chairman,
the biggest person in Samsung went to jail around this time.
It was in jail for years.
I missed this entirely.
Samsung's a major brand here.
I never heard the story that the guy was in jail.
And then similar, he was not, it wasn't an age thing,
just at some point he was pardoned because like,
you are too important, you have to get out of jail.
So he is the fourth wealthiest person in South Korea,
was just in jail for a long time and also separately charged criminally
for illegally taking propofol, the drug that killed Michael Jackson.
Wow.
We didn't have to say what we know what propofol is.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Conrad Murray heads here.
Yes, of course.
This is all some fucked up shit.
This is crazy.
Yeah.
And then there's like for every one or two that do go to jail,
there's like 10 more where it's like sentenced to five years,
commuted to three years probation.
Like the craziest one in the Vice documentary was the,
one of the family members of Korean Air.
They were in, it was, she was on a flight.
She was on a Korean Air flight.
She was served macadamia nuts in the bag, not on a plate.
And she demanded they turn the plane around.
And they did.
And then they did.
They did.
And she kicked off the head flight attendant.
And she got in real trouble because that,
the whole country was like, no, because this is like,
this is also a major safety hazard.
You're making a massive like 747 or whatever,
like do a 180 in the air and come back to the airport.
I just want to, like it is a blue satin v-neck tunic and pearls that I'm borrowing from SETI,
put on the idea of having that much entitlement that you would
ask to turn the plane around because your macadamia nuts are in a bag.
I just want to feel that power for a second.
Yeah.
Perfectly, it would never occur to me that bag is not the ideal setting for macadamia nuts.
Seems fine to put can perhaps those cans with the sharp lids
that I'm always worried I'm going to like slice my wrist on accidentally.
Oh yeah.
But I mean, I guess, yeah, if it's,
if it's like a bag is kind of like a peasant's way of eating,
you would never want to eat out of a bag if you're,
if you're a certain level of society, right?
Touch a bag.
I mean, it crinkles.
It's a filthy texture.
Now, you know what?
I'm against bags now.
Yeah.
You know what?
Maybe I, yeah, I don't want bags either.
Maybe I want everything kind of like in a glass jar or something.
Like a glass jar seems like a classier way to do it or a diamond encrusted jar.
You know what?
Turn this recording studio around.
Jason certainly had a fit on a plane about nuts before,
but it was, he didn't make them turn the plane around.
It was just probably that weren't this story.
Oh, I'm just kidding.
I thought you knew something.
No, no, no, no.
Biscoff cookies?
Where's the peanuts?
I don't care if kids do have allergies.
Well, it would be funny if there's some viral moment with Jason that you didn't know about
that was online where he's throwing a fit about nuts on a plane.
It would like it passed.
Yeah.
No Scrapple.
Scrapple not available on this flight.
Eight nuts in this bag at these prices.
It was like an early viral video.
It was like an e-bombs world viral video.
I see if it was like a couple of generations ago.
Right.
Yeah, you needed WMV to watch it.
I feel like the biggest difference here culturally,
like yeah, we have these mega conglomerates and the ultra-powerful families.
I feel like I hear that plane story and I'm like in America,
that would never even make it across our desks.
It would be like, yes, sir, plane turned around.
No prob.
No one mad.
It does seem like there's a shared like consensus, like a shared,
what do they call it?
Like a reality because they interviewed some students who were starting either college
or getting out of college and they're like my three jobs I would like.
I would either like to be at Samsung or Hyundai or I think it was HK was the other.
They were just like fully committed to the hallucination.
Wow.
To the reality of like, it's very good to work for these companies
and they do so much good for us and it's just like, oh man, this is bumming me out.
But how different is that than people being like, I want to work at Google.
I want to work at Meta.
No, it's really not.
That's the thing.
We just have the issue that our companies like crash and burn and turn over more frequently.
These ones have been caked in.
Sure.
Yeah, we got one weird bank up in Silicon Valley and our phones might,
our apps might stop working on Monday because of the weird bank or whatever.
Is that right?
Wait, that's between now and when the list is sharing this.
That was like a month or two ago.
We passed it.
Oh, okay.
That was that bank that failed.
Yeah.
That was going to end our apps?
Well, it was just like, oh, a bunch of companies do payroll through this bank.
So like everyone at Vox is not getting paid next week.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
So it is interesting because it's like, everything is propaganda, but it makes it
feel more like this place is propaganda then as well, where it's like you like us as a company
and here's how much you like us.
You're going to go on our rides now and it will make you like us more.
Nothing like the American totally different.
Totally different.
We talk about week after week.
100% different.
It wasn't like the original Tomorrowland was just little exhibits from different companies
that were killing people with chemicals and lead.
It was pure.
It was the intention was pure.
They're not to advertise Monsanto.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, so that's it.
Like, do you know any of this going into this place or is it just, hey, there's a weird theme
park next door?
I just know, hey, there's a weird theme park, but you start to get a sense that
it's very unusual when you arrive in this park is insult.
You can take the subway to it.
We took an Uber to it.
It's not like the hassle of going to Disney or something like that where it's in LA, but not
really in LA.
Yeah, actually better planned than any of our theme parks.
It's right there.
And when you show up, I thought we were in the wrong place because it's just a mall is what
you see.
Like you get dropped off.
There's this giant archway, a huge clock, and then you walk in and it is a mall.
There's a Chanel and there's a 7-Eleven and I kept thinking we must be in the wrong place.
And we're walking through this mall of just normal stores.
But every so often you see something weird that's like, oh, OK, there's a mural that looks
like it's from ancient Greece on a column, but it's a little cat girl and she's holding
a staff and she has a bow.
You're like, that's a little abnormal and I don't know what that is.
And there's a guy named Donkey Digger.
There's all these characters.
Maurice and he's dressed like a Roman emperor.
He's a pig.
He's got a little mustache.
She's holding a bunch of grapes.
And you're going through this mall and you're just going down and down and down.
It's kind of my recollection.
Like you're going through escalators and stairs and thinking we must be off.
And then you go through a doorway and just kind of boom, you realize that you are in a theme park
and the theme park is in the mall and it's structured mall-ish.
You can stand on the railings and look down.
Kind of imagine maybe like a four-story spiral where you're at the bottom looking up.
You can just see all the rings of the theme park unveil itself to you like a seashell at once.
Interesting.
Did it feel at all?
Because watching videos, it almost reminded me of like Vegas, like the mall parts of Vegas.
Like it seems similar where it's like there's like, you know, sky painted on the ceiling
and then there's a very expensive clothing store.
But then you go and you're roller coaster your feet away.
Yeah, it definitely has that.
Well, it has that sound like the Vegas sound.
We know everything is just noisy and overlapping.
There's no store stores like normal stores.
Once you get inside the park of the mall,
there's no Chanel in the park.
There's just stores where you can buy, you know, ears for mascots who didn't seem like
they played a big role.
I couldn't find stories of the mascots anywhere.
But like I bought a pair of fox ears that had a cactus in the middle of them.
Whoa.
Yeah.
And I don't know who that was, but yeah, it was a nice little cactus, like a succulent type.
And my boyfriend bought Dalmatian ears.
My friend bought a cat that had a polka dot bow.
Um, and then what you start to see is like just tons of overlapping chaos,
because since it's not a theme park structured around a narrative or like the fairy tales,
like we have in Disneyland in particular,
it's kind of just structured around ideas of things that make you feel like you're somewhere else.
So there's ancient Greek kind of things, Egyptian things, French looking areas.
A lot of ancient Egypt is kind of the main theme.
A lot of that.
A lot of ancient Egypt.
Right, right, right.
Yeah.
Just to feel like you're somewhere else.
But all of them kind of clash in, especially if you have a view of this whole massive
like arena sized atrium, you're seeing like 20 different themes all jammed next to each other.
Yeah.
They're all just sort of right on top of each other in a way that's overwhelming,
but kind of magical because everywhere you look is just something fascinating and strange.
You know, a pharaoh next to a robotic dinosaur.
Wow.
That's pretty cool.
I was going to say like that's the, we're always like,
look, we're always so upset when things aren't like separated in theme parks.
You know, we don't want like this.
They talk about like sight lines.
You know, if you can see a Comcast building in Universal while you're in Harry Potter or Mario,
it's upsetting.
You know, it's a theme park fans.
But also if it's like there's themes overlapping, you want everything sort of contained.
But this does seem interesting.
Literally everything on top of each other.
You can see it all at once.
That almost maybe is good in my mind.
I haven't been there obviously, but I maybe I do like that.
Yeah.
I like the mall aspect very much.
And that you get this, you got a giant mall walk before you're even
like the indoor nature.
I'm deciding how I feel about it.
I feel like in Japan, I got to do a lot of cool packed hyperactive indoor environments,
but there is something still like unsettling about it to me.
I don't know.
Did you feel anything off about the indoor nature?
Well, as a very pale person who sunburns and gets sweaty and Korea's really hot in the summer,
I loved it.
But yeah, it's discerning because you look up, it feels very brightly lit in there,
but you look up and there's these hot air balloons running around the ceiling.
But they're like light up rise that are attached to the ceiling on a track.
So you can take a hot air balloon and just sort of go around the entire upper part of the park.
And you can look down.
There's a there's like an ice skating rink.
So you can watch people ice skating in the summer while you're up on this hot air balloon.
That's on the roof.
That sounds good.
It sounds like if city walk had like a people mover on the top of it.
Yeah.
Wouldn't that be awesome?
Because we could see city walk from above.
Yeah.
We want to get all the beauty.
And I'm gonna say like, I'm a big fan of the indoor mall theme park.
One of my favorite places I've ever been to in my life is Kazakhstan
because their weather is either like extremely hot or extremely cold.
Where I was, it's like very high up on the steps.
And so most of their stuff is designed to be taken place indoors.
And one of their malls is shaped like a yurt.
And inside this year, it also has just like roller coasters kind of going around the top.
And then also a beach with like imported sand from the Maldives and water that you can soak in.
Wow.
It's incredible.
Like everywhere you go is just amazing.
Wow.
Geez, that's nuts.
Have you been to Mall of America ever?
Yeah, I have.
Also a fan of that?
Yeah.
Yeah, with the cheese curds.
I don't know why we can't get cheese curds in Los Angeles.
So I've never had the cheese.
I've never been to Mall of America, first of all, but I've had cheese curds, I think.
Where they're like deep fried and all squiggly.
And it's like when you bite into them, they yell at you.
They make a sound.
They're squeaky?
Yeah.
You're backing me up on that.
Have you had Jason good cheese curds in Los Angeles?
Yeah, I have.
Because near where my mom lives, there is a very nice cheese shop run by Mennonites.
Oh, on the East Coast.
Yeah, on the East Coast.
And they sell both cheese curds and they also sell deep fried cheese curds.
And it is delicious.
It's like artery clogging, but it's delicious.
I've had them here somewhere and I don't remember where.
And they were okay.
It's catching on as like a bar food, like fried pickles, I feel like.
More and more sports bars, I feel like, have them on the menu.
Canada, a lot of that too.
Yeah.
Cheese curds?
I mean-
Did you have them there?
Yes.
Yeah.
Not my deal, but I'm glad I tried.
I want to imagine they're good because we all carry around cheese sticks like they're
something healthy.
Yeah.
So I don't see really the difference between a cheese curds.
You peel the cheese stick apart, you have these little curls.
Sure.
And then you get to put your hand in there and it's really fun.
Why don't I like the word?
I think curds is-
Curds is weird to me, yeah.
Like curdle?
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe it reminds me of the process.
Right, industrial nature of it.
Blood curdling scream maybe is added to it.
Yeah, it's close to some more negative words, I feel.
Yeah.
Okay, so maybe that's it.
But it's just cheese.
Plops.
Gone plops.
Cheese plops?
That doesn't make you think of anything else?
Not me, no.
What do you mean?
All right, we'll think of it.
The cutify plop and then we got it.
Cheese drops.
Sure.
When somebody has a blood curdling scream, does that mean that the person screaming is
having their blood curdle or that it curdles the blood of the people who hear it?
Oh.
Hmm.
Blood curdling.
I think that's a-
The quality of the scream would suggest that it makes people's blood curdle.
In the vicinity.
Yeah, I think so.
Right.
How does blood curdle?
It's a good question that I-
I've never broken this phrase apart.
Yeah, I don't know the answer to that.
What is that, biological process?
Yeah, how do you curdle blood?
Yeah, does it literally happen?
Does it like harden, thicken, become more of a gravy texture?
I guess it would kill somebody if your blood curdled.
Yeah, if all of it did.
Right.
At once.
Yeah, so if it's a blood curdling scream, it could make the screamer
curdle and it can make everyone around them curdle.
So it's sort of like a self-inflicted banshee wound?
Hmm.
Yes.
Nice.
Wait, so where- wait, wait, wait, banshee wound is very specific.
Because the scream of a banshee would kill-
Yeah, it kills you, right?
Kill or wound or maim at least.
Yeah, but could- but does a banshee scream curdle blood or does it do something else?
Does it like blow out something in your brain or you have an aneurysm or something?
I-
It's so loud.
As somebody a little Irish, I feel like I should know this.
Well, Jason and I don't know anything other than we know that the X-Man banshee-
Yeah, I've been thinking about banshee and his daughter, Siren, who's also-
They both have similar screaming powers and we know that that can just hurt-
I think they can adjust the level of scream so they could just stun their opponent.
Yeah, they can use it to stun, they use it to fly.
Yes, they can also scream-
Don't look into that.
We don't know exactly how it works, but they have like little wings on their costume
and they fly with the scream as well.
Yeah.
I wonder if they screamed at a cow, if they could curdle the milk inside the cow
and then they could make the cheese curds?
This is- this is a good idea.
This is a Mythbuster-
That's a very good- I like the unique use of powers,
because I'm sure that's never been done before in the comics and it's been 70 years of whatever,
50 years of X-Men? How many years?
Sure.
I mean, very many years.
60, yeah, 60 I think.
I think like 60.
If you guys don't know this, then who will?
Well, X-Men is the late 60s, right?
I just watched an anniversary livestream and I don't remember the number plastered all over it.
We don't want to remember because it will say how old we are.
It reminds us how long we've been looking at these comics.
You want to hear X-Men is-
X-Men.
15 years.
15 years of the X-Men.
Right, yeah, yeah.
It's also going to get overshadowed because 1963 is the first Avengers too,
and they're like, you know, they're going to get all the love because they made so much money.
They're so popular, you know?
Right, everyone loves the Avengers.
The biggest event of 1963 was the starting of the Avengers.
Yeah.
Of course, for-
Lasting.
The most important event in film, maybe, you know.
Can't wait, bring them on.
I think you've written before you want three times the amount of Marvel movies coming out of a year.
You said it's not enough.
It was the headline on one of your articles.
I'm just very excited that I feel like when I look at the landscape, they are dying,
and it's wonderful.
They're definitely dying out, and it is time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not because, even if like-
Well, we have the comics.
I have the comics.
I still have the comics I wrote when I was a kid.
So I'm not like, if the movies go away, it's okay.
They're not going to go away, but if they go away, it's okay.
Also, if they don't go away, just something else too, I think is the-
I think it's the cultural monopoly that is the-
Of course.
The irritating thing.
If they were to keep doing that in their corner, but also there's lots of other more
inventive movies to check out.
The only thing that Marty Scorsese said, which made me more excited about the movies,
is he called them theme park rides.
Yes.
And I was like, yes, he's right, more, more.
What he intended as an insult.
I know.
Yeah, little did he know that Marty, that's the problem that we're not getting enough
theme park attractions of these movies.
They all get delayed and cut.
E-ticket, we want more E-tickets, Marty.
Well, and Mike, that was a little like Carol Burnett telling you on her ear,
that was a little message to you because you're friends, you call them Marty, like you're buddies.
Of course, yeah, me and Marty.
Just like Marty Short.
I don't know if you know this, we're friends, so I say Marty.
Yeah, yeah.
Very casual.
Okay, to go back to your journey into getting through the rungs of this multi-tier,
what is it, like it's four stories, the theme park part?
Yeah, it's four stories, and if you took a different turn in the mall,
you could go to an aquarium that's on a different side that I never saw.
Or there's also like a folk museum, which I didn't get to, but I think it's sort of
mannequins of different clothing periods throughout Korean history,
something like that is maybe my guess.
Wow, and this, yeah, the entire property by the way, yeah, there's the ice,
there's a classical concert hall in this facility too.
It is the largest cinema in Asia which boasts the biggest non-IMAX screen on Earth,
like the biggest regular screen, 35 millimeter, so that's, there's a lot of biggest throughout
this entire, because that skyscraper also is like the highest observation deck,
and this is the, Lotte World is the biggest indoor theme park, and like
just biggest record breaking throughout this thing.
Well, the ice skating rink is huge. It's got a giant glass ceiling a few stories above that,
letting in all this natural light, but then there's so many parts, like watching videos,
there's so many parts of this park that feel very intimate, again, because of the low ceilings.
There's like gift shops or some attractions where it's just like normal room size ceiling.
Yeah, normal. They have a panda express there if you get hungry.
It's sort of like being in a mall panda express, except it's classier. It's sort of brown, nice wood,
a little beige. It's got a sign that says like established 1983. It had two giant stuff pandas
in the front, so that it's just a little bit of like normal inside of the chaos.
Did you eat there?
Yeah, I did. I went to, the first thing we did is when we got there, we had ice creams at this
place called the Pharaoh Snack, because that was right by our first ride, and we got giant soft
serve cones. I feel like mine was grape or raspberry. I can't remember because we found
out very quick that the lines were short, which I've heard online that the lines are like crazy
long, but when we were there, there was almost no wait at all. So I bought an ice cream thinking
we were going to be in line, and then immediately they're like, you're on the ride and you can't
have that ice cream. So all of us were just holding ice cream, and we shoved them completely
into our mouths. It got through it, which was fine. But the meal that we had was from a place
that specialized in hot dogs. And so, you know, they have like the plastic hot dogs outside,
so you can pick which one you wanted. And I got this one called the white snowing,
and it was covered in a white cream that I believe was garlic because they have a hot dog also called
the crunchy garlic. And so it had all of that, but then also just powder that I think might
have been Parmesan cheese. It was a little bit hard to distinguish, but it was beautiful.
My friend got the bulgogi dog, which is gorgeous. They had one that had kind of the
rice cakes, I think, on it. Wow. These are extremely innovative hot dogs, an area where often
I find innovation is lacking. Yeah, well, lacking, but also then you try innovation and it's
not well executed and unwanted on my part. Yes, that's true. I mean, hot dogs of the month that
one Disney bar, those are the bad news. We went to Disney. We did an episode last year and we ate
every hot dog at Disneyland. They're all the same base dog basically. And then they just throw a
lot of crap. You ended up just like in basics, more so, but these sound like you sound like they
may have mind blowing. These are good. These sound like good conversation pushing forward.
They're much more innovative than the ones Disney had. Yeah. Korea is the innovator of hot dogs,
right? Corn dogs, right? Corn dogs are very intense. That is a true thing about Korea.
I don't think I know this. Oh yeah. Like if you go even here to the Koreatown mall, it's like at
fifth and Western, they have a really good corn dog place. It's like at the studded
french fries that are embedded in it. They're really textural kind of modern art looking hot
corn dogs. Whoa. Yeah. Door boys just did a place. I forget what it was. They just reviewed a place.
I should look it up, but yeah. When I wasn't even really that familiar with the corn dog phenomenon.
Yeah. There's a whole world. I mean, Korea is just really innovative. I feel like that will be one
of the, well actually no, and I'm going to take that completely back because everything in latte
world is such a direct rip of Disney. It's enchanting. It's enchanting. It's yeah,
it is strange how stuff is either like, Oh, that is a gag directly from the Indiana Jones ride.
But then there's other things where it's like, yeah, this is so much of everything. You can't
say it's a rip off because it just is all things, you know? Yeah. It's such a mashup. And like,
you should say that, you know, Shin himself, the founder of Lotte world has kind of a history of
taking things and making them his own. Like there was this huge fight when he was getting the candy
company off the ground where, you know, Pocky, the chocolate dip sticks. Sure. They accused him
of stealing the idea of Pocky to make his own company, which he calls Pepero. They're also
just chocolate dipped sticks. Huge fights back and forth. And he wound up winning because he,
I believe blocked Pocky from being sold in Korea. Whoa. Yeah. And then he formed a holiday called
Pepero holiday, which is a holiday in Korea where everybody buys his and gives them back to each
other. So he's I feel like we could just say he stole Pocky. Yeah. Probably like he's not going to
his ghost isn't going to sue me, but yeah, steals it, makes it his own, becomes incredibly successful.
Wow. That's all of a move also, like started that word. All right. It's Eminem day in America and
you have to buy Eminem and exchange them with others. That's interesting. Even just about
like copyright, whatever, like food. Like I'm, I'm, I should look into it because it's interesting
to me how like you can sell the same cereal and just call it something else. And it's like a
little bit different. Like it just tastes a little bit off of like rice crispies and just call it
like crispy piece, crispy pieces, not crispy pieces. That sounds bad, but there's gotta be a better
until you think of one, call Chris crispies with a C and then like a Z at the end. Yeah. Well,
spies like the store brand of frosted flakes is sometimes called frosted flakes because it's just
a description of what you're selling. I think. Oh, that's interesting. There's one or two where
it's just like, they get away with the same name because it's just a phrase. That's interesting.
Oh, wow. I mean, I wonder if there is, you know, like there's a movie that just came out, Guy
Richie's the covenant. If like, does Kellogg say like Kellogg's frosted flakes and the possessive
makes it singular. I think that's right. That movie also like, it doesn't, that's one that doesn't
feel like a real movie. I guess, cause I feel like doesn't, hasn't Guy Richie had like two or three
movies out lately and this feels like a faith flicks movie or he had operation fortune.
Ruse de Guerre. I think that's what it was called. Sure. Right. Yeah. And this is very serious one.
It's actually pretty good. Oh, yeah. I was startled. I had to review it and I was like, here we go.
No, it's really effective. It's very flawed, but powerful. Oh, okay. I was proud of Guy Richie. It's
getting over the top positive reviews because everybody's like, I can't believe Guy Richie made
a good film. Have you ever seen the film that he did with Madonna? We just watched that.
Oh, swept away. No, I've never seen that. I was trying to explain that to my girlfriend
recently because she was talking about Madonna's boyfriend or husband or something. I was like,
but she divorced Guy Richie along swept away and just her eyes glazed over while I was trying to
remind like, no, swept away. Remember it was real bomb for both of their careers.
It's wild. Like I love Madonna. So I'm coming into this from that direction. But when you watch that
movie, you just think he hates his wife. Like he hates her. She's never been filmed to be unattractive
in the way that that film shoots her to be unattractive. Even when her character is
supposed to be hot, he films her like she's a witch and it's just hostile and mean and everything
about her is terrible and in a way that has no warmth to it at all. And it's not supposed to be,
I think, as bad as it is. It's just, it's so toxic when you watch it. And I can't believe that she
didn't like divorce him as soon as she saw the first daily. Maybe she never saw one. No, actually,
no more room in this theater. I see some chairs. No, don't worry about it.
Recently, I was like, this person's wife is in this movie and they've been written to be
the meanest character I've ever seen. Now I want to take a guess. I feel like I have a guess.
Go ahead. Is it Jed Appetizer?
Yeah, that's not who I was thinking about. But that's a good thing.
Well, no, Jed writes all these great moments where his wife gets to have fake sex with
many of Hollywood's hottest leading men. I'm not sure what that one says.
That's a trade off. The character might be mean, but at least there's a hunk involved.
So that's good. And neither of these instances,
though, are when someone, they make themselves very ugly or very mean or they're going through
such struggle to try and win an award. It's not that presentation.
It's definitely not that. It's definitely not that. It's definitely that. It's like she could be,
because part of the story is about she's marooned on this desert island with just this hunk
who she's mean to relentlessly, so mean to him, and then he's mean back.
But she's in full sunlight and he somehow figures out how to shoot her so that her
face is covered in wrinkles. And he's like, that's going to be hard to do.
A beautiful woman on the beach. Yes. How do you arrange it with the worst harshest? Who's the hunk?
It's this guy whose dad played the hunk in the original version of it, because it's based on
Alina Wirtmuller film from the 70s. That's supposed to be about toxic masculinity and
domination. And it's a really tricky, brutally ugly film. And I like the idea that Madonna and
Guy Ritchie were probably watching this movie, like in his movie theater and talking about it.
Or it's because I don't know why else you'd make this movie and then had the idea to do it.
And then it was just cruel and punishing and terrible. But they watched art house films
together is my theory, which is lovely. It makes them feel like me and my boyfriend watching
Criterion. And I appreciate that. And if you picked one and said, let's let's do it.
Yeah, they got the son of the guy from the first movie to be the guy in this movie. I don't think
he really ever made that many other films. That's a really strange guess. I've never seen this.
You know, I guess I don't know. Maybe there's something up with Guy Ritchie's eye because
maybe it's just me. I thought that his presentation of Will Smith's Jeannie looked really ugly and
weird. I forget. I forget that. Yeah, that happened that we saw it, that we did an episode on it.
Went to a theater. Yeah. We reviewed it for the show. Yes. That's right. You couldn't go to that
was one of those. Now you can't go to a movie theater. And before we could just like waste time
on this. We saw we paid money. We visited a place to watch that. There are a lot of positive
memories from 2019 for whatever reason, that one doesn't bubble to the top.
You're kidding. Yeah. OK. OK. The theme park. OK. So now we've gotten your your you had to down
a popsicle later on. You had some ice cream hot dogs. OK. Yeah. But now you're OK. You were
tired. Rides. Let's get into rides a little bit. What was the what was that first one you were
about to go on? Yeah. The first one that we went on was a ride called Pharaoh's Fury. Yeah. Yes.
And Pharaoh's Fury is probably the showpiece ride there. It's like a really elaborate one.
And it is just you enter like it is the Indiana Jones ride. You know, there's fair. There's a
hieroglyphs everywhere, really setting the tone. You get into a Jeep. The Jeep has a steering wheel
that you could pretend like you're driving. And it even kind of kicks in with a little blast of
like the John Williams horns. But it's all Egyptian themed. And you're just kind of driving
around and there's like crocodiles and dragons and like the blasting air dart kind of gun thing.
Oh, you got that. All right. And creepy shadows on the walls. And I swear, as I was riding it,
I felt like we were taking the same turns and drops as the actual Indiana Jones ride. Like it
didn't just feel like it was taking the idea of it. It really felt like somehow they had a blueprint
of the track. Yeah, maybe. Yeah. It's you can't copyright a little shape. You can't copyright a
road shape. Yeah. But it really felt like it had those same kind of mirrors. There's a part where
you think this giant thing is going to fall on top of you, sort of like the rolling boulder,
and it plummets down. It pretends like it's crumbling around you. So you start hurrying
and jerking back and forth. And, you know, the whole theme park is really obsessed with the color
neon purple. So there's a lot of like neon purple lighting and stuff to make it feel a little
distinctive. But yeah, it felt like it felt like I guess it felt like the Indiana Jones ride.
This ride is to the Indiana Jones ride as like if you were in the 80s and a kid wearing like a
mask of Indiana Jones was trick or treating at your door. That's sort of what it felt like.
I guess maybe it would be like if Harrison Ford was trick or treating at your door and he was
wearing a mask of Aladdin. Right. Sort of like that. You're confused. Now I'm very confused.
That's the effect. But it was awesome, honestly, to like be in a mall and then be on this ride.
And I still don't quite understand, even having been there, where all the track is in the mall,
because you just see the entrance from kind of the archway of it. And it's just there. And I
don't know where the track goes. It feels like a magic trick. Like you just sort of disappear into
a portal. Yeah, I can't remotely think of the physical layout of this place. Now it works
because every ride through I watched, like how do they have that too? Wait, so this ride goes
way up into the rafters. But then also there's a rapid ride. I don't know if I've ever seen an
indoor rapid ride. So where the hell does that go? And then there's a whole like underworld area. And
I don't like my mind is boggled by thinking about this all fits in. You have to like build the
structure knowing all that was you can't like add on as much. It feels like that. Seemingly. Yeah.
Like Disney can add on because it's land and it's outdoors. This ride, you mentioned Indiana Jones,
there's a moment, there's a gag they do in this where you're in a dark section, there's bugs on
the walls and the headlights flicker on that is one for one from Indiana Jones. Yes. But that said,
there's a moment in this ride where you're going into a big statue of Pharaoh's mouth at some point.
And there's like a projection above you that like draws the eyes up. And then there's a roller
coaster style drop. And I don't think I've ever seen that before. Oh, it reminded me of the boulder
drop. But yeah. Oh, okay. Yeah. I put it. Okay. Yeah. That makes sense to me. It does that similar
gimmick where it draws your eye up and then the drop is below you. And I will say there's a lot
of rides here that are focused on going in and out of people's mouths. Yeah. Well, I saw this crazy
clown train kind of situation. Fantasy dream. Yeah. Did you go on that? That's my favorite ride.
Oh boy. I was going to save it for the last one. We can save it. Also, up to you. If you want to build to it.
I'm happy to talk about it. I'm happy to talk about it. I do want to say really quick. So we're
talking about the indoor part of the mall, right? Yeah. I didn't know until the very end, maybe an
hour before the park closed that there was an outside part of the mall that there's this place
called Magic Island, which is connected to it. And when you exit through the bottom of the mall,
I think it was, then it opens up and you're like, oh, there's Sleeping Beauty's castle.
And it just is the castle, but it's all lit up. And I've seen online call it Magic Castle. But
we saw there, I think it just said Hotel Castle on the sign for my pictures.
It is just the castle all lit up. Yeah. And then it is so, that is the most Disney world ripoff
aspect of this by far. Yeah, it did a good job. It's a, there's a ripoff thing. I've seen worse
Disney ripoff theme parks in like a band. I don't, I need to like try to catalog. Where are all of
the weird ripoff castles? Cause I know there's like an abandoned one in China, but I don't know the
deal with that. But yeah, this is a, this is a thriving, vibrant Disney world ripoff. The weirdest
thing about it is when you get to the castle part, there's all these photos everywhere and they
actually are stills from the Disney Snow White, like stills from the actual Disney. And that's
where I don't know how they get away with it. There's also like kind of a really creepy looking
mannequin of Snow White that doesn't look like Snow White in the slightest, just sort of lying
in a bed, you know, as though she's knocked out unconscious, but yeah, several stills of just
straight up Disney Snow White. That's the part that's the most audacious. I'm proud of them.
But it is this part of the park where fantasy dream is the greatest ride. And by the time we
got there, the park was closing. So we rode this road ride three times in a row by ourselves. It
was the greatest thing I've ever been on in my life. Awesome. Wow. It's that great. Okay. Okay.
Great. Great. I stumbled across this in the, this is the, uh, the YouTube channel attractions,
three 60 that has a lot of great ride throughs. They just called their title for it was unique
and creepy dark train ride. Um, yeah. Accurate. Is that too, is that too harsh? Do you love it
more than that title? That doesn't sound like anything I went on. It's not creepy. Okay. Maybe
it's a little creepy. It's not dark. It is like, it's like being inside an electric crayon box
and it's not unique at all. Cause it's just, it's a small world, but redone with candy.
Yeah. With the latte candy, the famous candy. It's a nod to the roots. That's great. Um, yeah,
it's like a lot of, I feel like the count to me was like, there are 200 alive lollipops and candy
canes and flowers and flowers. Yeah. It, the, the candy connection makes a lot more sense why the
ending of this ride spoiler alert is just a mini candy amusement park. It's amazing. And like,
it starts off kind of janky. There's like this, you go into a clown's mouth, but there's also this
hand painted clown on the wall that looks like it's from the sixties. Like this park opened in
89, I think, but the painting and the font looks like 1960s, you know, it's kind of wild West and
neon orange. There's a lollipop who looks like he's under arrest and a clown is a very classic
clown kind of yelling at him. And then, yeah, you go into this clown's mouth and there's all this,
these Willy Wonka esque neon tubes, like rainbow tubes kind of coming at you. Like in the boat
ride type. Yeah. Yeah. So you're going through that and it kind of twists and turns and you're
in this little train car and then just like stuff gets going on a grand scale. You go through this
marsh where there's an Aladdinish wizardy looking guy, but then these doors open and it's just like
instant flowers and mushrooms. It's, it's, you know, when Roger Rabbit, when he enters toon town,
that's what it feels like. Yeah. And everybody's just singing at you about, I mean, I'm assuming
it's about how great candy is, but I don't speak Korean, which, you know, it really cuts down on
understanding a lot of the mythology of everything happening in this park. But yeah, there's like
bees who are inside giant mushrooms and they pop out at you and they're playing trumpets.
There's random little bits of actual fuzzy stuffed animals that kind of don't go against the shiny
plasticine texture of everything else. Like, Oh yeah, look at this scary cat with dilated eyes.
Yeah. This is very upset to be alive. Like she's cooking. Yeah. Kind of a Mr. Rogers,
like a cousin of whatever that cat. I forget the name. There's a room with a lot of colored
spheres and a very large man. I don't know if he's supposed to be a genie or wizard. Yeah. Yeah.
This guy, it's like these beautiful colored like war. He's sort of genie ish. Oh yeah.
Very robust beer. But that's the beginning of the ride and towards the end of the ride,
there's like a Merlin like figure. And if you squint, it's like, wait, that's a large Merlin,
but it's also a fox. It's a large Fox. He's cute. I think I like this Fox. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
He's cute. This is really like, I feel like as a kid, I wanted a candy land ride really badly.
And I don't feel like this, they're a good American candy based ride. I don't think so.
Not Hershey's chocolate world. I mean, you're not getting like the color. Yeah. That's what I
said. It gives you like, you know, gumdrops and jelly beans, molly pops. We've talked about
before. I was not a chocolate kid. I was a multicolored candy nerds, sprees, tartan tinies
kid. So this feels like fulfilling that promise. Yeah. There's kind of a part in the ride that
feels like it's covered in smarties. It looks to me, to me, it looked like Dr. Mario. Oh yeah. But
yeah, I think it's definitely supposed to represent the smarty landscape. Yes. This is, yeah, this is
my dream, my childhood dream of like a candy land that you can visit. Is this the best candy ride?
Listeners, if you have been somewhere with a better candy ride, let us know. Yeah. But it seems like,
I don't think this is going to be the hottest take in the world. This might be the best candy ride.
Might be the best candy ride. I don't know. Cause like what are the other Hershey's,
Reese's cup challenge at Hershey world or whatever, but that's still like, I don't know. It's shooter
and it's not as magical. Chocolate's a little rough, I think, cause you're dealing in brown
and brown's a little dark and fun. You have to put colorful costumes on top of the brown
chocolate characters. You have to give the, but like a, a brightly, an every color in the rainbow
candy ride. It's vibrant already. Cause there is chocolate in this ride. Right, right, right.
Please include it. Certainly. Like candy. Hershey's kisses, naked Hershey's kisses.
Yeah. Those are really, there's like a, there's a crazy, I think, I think this little, this little
kiss is high. I think he's going nuts. He's on a trip. This is, I think just watching a video of
it on one end of the spectrum of like, this is the strangest ride I've ever seen. The other end of
the spectrum is this ride. Is it pronounced V Paz salt cracking? V Paz salt cracking. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where's that? What was that again? I've already forgotten where the ride is.
This one is in Europe and it's based on a beloved like drama series, like a house on the prairie and
of green gables kind of drama series, but it's a ride based on very mundane events.
I've seen this ride. I don't know why I've watched a YouTube of this ride, but I have.
Perhaps through Eva. I know she was, she was repping this after we talked about it. I believe.
I think I was watching a movie that, or I heard a reference to the story it was based on as well.
Like what a beloved story it is. It was like Holland or something. Swedish is, I'm sorry.
I was right. Yeah. Yeah. Cause it was a, it was a TV movie or a show. Astrid. It was a limited
series TV, TV series or limited TV show that was very beloved and heartwarming from the writer of
Pippi Longstocking. It's a theme park all based on Pippi Longstocking. And of course the story
Carlson on the roof. Oh, that's right. Also by this author with a K though, not to see.
So that's all the way at the end of one spectrum. Cause it's strange. There's a ride and it's very
mundane of like, well, we've got to get home. It's almost time for dinner. Like, and then
there's this where it's like, well, there's a magical creature. And then you go through the
candy cane, a amusement park, and then there's a wizard. Like this is just so much of everything.
It is. And it takes this twist right at the end where you're going through just delirious,
happy candy. Everybody has their hands up. They're screaming. There's a lot of black light.
All the candy canes seem drunk. And then right at the very end, when you look to the left,
there's a bunch of candy behind jail bars. And it just, they look sad. There's the definitely
appealed Hershey's kisses back there. And I was watching the video I took with my boyfriend,
like, you know, second or third, right. And I just heard my boyfriend say in the saddest voice,
why are the, why aren't the presence? Wait, what is it? He said, why aren't the presence
escaping from prison? Because there are also little wrapped gifts there too. But yeah,
they're all just behind these bars and there's a sad, very overfed looking dragon on the other side.
So it's almost like, don't have too much candy or keep away from candy or this candy misbehaved.
And it deserves to be eaten or. But is this maybe the candy that they've like somehow like
litigated out of the country? Or like, that's a pocky company. Right. Don't eat the disgraceful
hockey game. So he's like punishing the candy that he's been able or what's the gentleman's name who
ran it or owned it. Yeah. Yeah. Like, so he's just, yeah, maybe these are representations of
the candy he has put out of business in the country. They're being detained. He's holding
them in a cell unless they give up and say, all right, we will not try to do business in the country.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know if there's any. I don't know if there's been an interview
with the Imagineers who did this. Wow. I mean, I like, you know, it's rare, but a common component
of a lot of the most fun, weird, dark rides, especially is punishment stakes. You know, it's
Mr. Toad, obviously you go to hell. There's a dark side to your actions in this. It's not all
fun candy land. Some of the candies have to be in jail. It's the Caribbean is jail. I really love
that Sanrio Pearl and boat ride. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Where the character Bad Bats Maru is. I forget
what he's up to. I want to be Tom, though. Yeah, yeah, that's right. He's trying to like pervert.
Uh huh. Yeah, yeah. He's trying to like take a peek at something he's not supposed to see. And
then later in the ride, he's getting punished. He gets spanked in the ride. And this is the kind
of weird I like. I love every one of these rides with punishment in it. Maybe this is needs to be
a recurring theme more often. Yeah. Now that I'm thinking about it, there was a photo op in the
mall where you could pretend to be in jail as well. And there are these two giant toddlers in that
they can sort of the guess they look like the kid in who from Roger Rabbit, but it was like dangerous
oversized toddlers with teeth sticking out in jail uniforms. Oh, my God. Almost like Tweedledee and
Toodle Dum, but like toddlers. Yeah. And the lack of context of knowing if these are characters from
the Latte universe, which really doesn't seem like they had on if like the people weren't labeled on
the way in. Right. Like Maurice, I wouldn't have had any idea that there was a story. Yeah. Do they
live anywhere else? Are there like are there TV shows in the the Latte verse? Yeah. I mean,
I'm so curious, like these characters are on the front of the website. And I love the look of these
characters, but they're all dressed in like school outfits. Are these the primaries? I wonder if that's the donkey. Yeah, that must be Donkey Digger.
Yeah. Well, let's talk about these characters a little bit, starting with the basics. And we've been
not sure how to say this word, but I feel like undeniably their Mickey is Lottie. Lottie, right. Because now it's spelled with a Y.
It's Lottie and Lori. And one is in kind of a tux with some red. And then one is in a dress with red
and polka dots and a bow. If you can imagine that outfit and that if it reminds you of any other
sure main big characters in theme park world. But Lottie and Lori. Mike, do you love Lottie and Lori?
Well, I'm looking at the different I'm looking at this newer these these versions of them.
Whoa. Which I think are awesome. Kind of like they're like that's like a network hip or sort
of throwback. It's like schoolhouse rock a little bit. Yes. That one dabbing on the side. Yes, he is.
Yes. That's why I really like it. If it's an out of date dance, Mike loves it. That's right. If he's
doing the Macarena, I'd be even more thrilled. But yeah, yeah. So he represents the Che balls hitting
the dab on the people of South Korea. So that's Lottie and Lori, I'm assuming, right? I guess so.
Yeah, these are very different than I'm looking at these more like Disneyfied versions on their
website. Right. So so yeah, certainly from these and they're all in little it says blooming world
school. So I think that's maybe like they're back to school, like, you know, how they have like an
event at Disney or something or Tokyo will have like the Halloween season and they'll have the
Disney characters and like different outfits. But yeah, these certainly are cute for sure. And I
like them. Yeah. And then I think I saw the ones you're talking about. Yeah. Yeah. Here's the
vibe. Just pretty like classic. They're going for classic Disney. Yeah. I mean,
I mean, Lori is Lori is ripping many off hardcore here. Yeah. As far as her look.
But she has her own interests that are different than many.
Lori, who spreads warm love is the symbol of Lottie World Adventure together with with Lottie.
She has such a good heart as a courteous friend. She's always spreading warm love to many people.
What are you just saying that if she's the opposite of many, many is a bitch?
I didn't know not the opposite. I'm just saying I've never specifically heard of any
interests many has in warm love. I don't think many has any. Many always makes me think of
one of my friends once profiled Hallie Bieber, Edo, who is married, of course, to Justin Bieber.
And she said she walked into a room where Hallie Bieber was as Justin was in the main room living
his life and Hallie was just sitting on the bed looking out at nothing. Not on her phone,
not reading a book, not watching television, just sitting on the bed. And that's how I've
always pictured many. Wow. Like no real like vacant. If she's not with Mickey, then what's
going on? What's the point? What's my point? If I'm not with Mickey, my identity is standing next
to this person, this character. It sounds like that's not Lori. Lori seems like she's busy
spreading warm love when she's not with she's she's she spreads warm love to many people all
the time. And she and it's an after the fact she is also the pretty girlfriend of Lottie.
It's not the first thing in the right. It's after the fact. So that speaks to some some
unique identity. There's also like 10 or 11 other characters listed on the website.
We'll get to them. I was just wondering if pretty girlfriend implied the existence of,
you know, a different girlfriend, the smart girl. She is the pretty girlfriend of Lottie.
Lottie is dating three different animals at once. What animal are they? I saw. Raccoon
as the but they are more it's a lighter brown than I associate raccoon. Yeah,
Fox. I thought they were foxes at first. They're sort of chipmunk as well. They look like tails
from Sonic. Sure. A little bit. Mm hmm. And he was a fox. So I guess they are they are
light raccoons. Right. Does it say anything about Lottie hitting the dab in that description?
Lottie loves to hit the dab. He knows he's he's our friend who nurtures his dreams with a bright,
warm heart. So if a dream of his was to do the dab, then he would surely nurture that dream and
probably do it. OK, that's cool. The only information I can give you at this time.
All right, Jason, other characters? Yeah, go ahead, please. Well, Maurice is a little pig.
He's the wine expert. You mentioned Maurice. Yeah, little must a little and in their stock photo,
seemingly drunk at the moment. I'm a Maurice fan. Is he your guy? Maybe of all these scouts of
these guys. And look, it's not do I like him more than the French aristocrat? Yes, I do.
Do I like him more than the bulldog woman who has like looks like big testicle jowls? Yes,
I do. Yeah, it's I'm just saying it's a low bar. And yeah, I like the drunk pig.
I wonder if the existence of Maurice, who is holding wine, as you pointed out in that picture,
is why they do have a ride called Drunken Basket. Wow. Because instead of teacups,
their ride is called Drunken Basket. It is just baskets spinning around, but it doesn't seem to
have an alcohol theme besides the name. Like the middle of it is just a giant animatronic snake
coming out of a croc and kind of opening and closing his mouth. And I was wondering what the
baskets were made for. Like I Googled, like, how do you make soju or something if it's like a
traditional drunken basket event? But Maurice just looks like he's holding a nice pinot. So
maybe it's just an idea. Yeah, I know. What he's holding looks very delicious to me. I think he's
got good taste. Drunken Basket, I don't know, is the idea that like the basket that's spinning
around will give you a drunken feeling without even consuming alcohol? Maybe that's the it is
like the notion there. Alice in the teacups is all like, obviously, it's they're just talking
about drugs. And that's like, they're simulating what it would be like if you were hallucinating,
I think, on the teacups. That's your view of what the teacups are? Well, the whole Alice is,
she takes the potion or whatever. But we're just talking about hallucinogenics. So it's like it's
trying to disorient you. But yeah, well, that's other parts of the movie, though, the teacup part,
she's having some tea. But it is interesting that it's teacups in that ride and not vials or
something. That's true. Not the magic vials. Yeah. And I would say hallucination. But I think I
think you're bringing this air. You think so? Yeah, I've never thought I have never thought of
the teacup ride as being a simulated hallucination. No, Jason. I think there was probably already
half a dozen companies making spinning teacup rides. And they're like, oh, we want one of these.
What is it closest to? Oh, yeah, Alice has a tea party. You don't think Bob Gurr was thinking when
he put together the teacup ride? I assume he did. He was like, we're going to simulate a trip in here.
I don't know. Well, I don't know where he stands on the hallucinogenic enthusiast's
scale. Because there are some that are pretty on the record as pro. Rolly, Rolly, he just passed
away. He was pretty upfront that he's like, yeah, I did some drugs. Sure. So I don't know, maybe
we'll look into it. Maybe I'm wrong. And that and you'll well just just take a bunch of
hallucinogenic drugs and tell me which one is exactly like spinning around for two minutes.
Well, you know me, I'm always doing hallucinogenic. So not necessarily hallucinogenic per se, but I
got to say, like taking a few hits off a joint and then watching fantasy dream was kind of a bad time.
Oh, really? That was kind of a little bit. Oh, Jace. Oh, no. All of the rides, the jungle,
the rapids ride and the other. I was just like, I regret putting this off into the evening.
I regret doing it. Fascinating. I didn't know this was part of your research sometimes that there was
there was a little bit of stimulation involved. I had already watched a lot of like day in the life
kind of we're going to Lotte World and I watched the Vice documentary and then I was I find I don't
know. I was having a hard time looking I think because Attractions 360 kind of more describe
the I think I looked up the Lotte World website, found what their English translations rides were
and I was having a harder time finding those. And then once I found a few ride throughs,
I found all of them. That's all very interesting. Now, what were you smoking, dude? What were you
puffing on pretty chill Indica? But still there was a lot going on in that fantasy dream where I
was like, this is the strangest thing I've ever seen. Jason was keeping his lips zipped in the
world talking about how wonderful it is. Best candy ride and then you're thinking of terror.
I liked it. I was just like, oh man, this is there's so much happening here.
Jason look, in case you didn't know, I mean, Jason is the wild one of the three of us because he
takes six hits of weed a week. Wow. Mr. Loose Cannon.
I'm going to try to sound cool when I say this so that you take me seriously. Like I know what
I'm talking about, but like does, does blaze in bro? Does that help you feel like you're on the
ride? Like when you're watching now you're speaking his language. Now you're talking to him.
I finally called me bro. It's been 300 episodes now. Now he's connected. Now he's locked in.
That I think is helped more by the size of the screen. Like on a bigger TV, it does feel more
like then what do you do? Do you plan for the biggest screen you can find and try to pretend
like you're on the ride? I usually just like, as I'm going through stuff, I throw stuff in my,
in like a playlist on YouTube or watch later. You're not answering my questions. Do you sit
in front of a big TV and pretend you're on the ride? I sit on the couch and watch it. And then
I type on a computer, my observations. This is much more boring than the bit you're looking for.
Yeah. We're looking for some fun thing where you're like blazed up and then you like kind
of go up to the TV and like hug it and watch the screen. Yeah. Like I don't have a big wingspan,
Mike. My arms don't go very wide. It's your old TV and you know what it looks like. I gave
Jason my old TV three years ago. So yeah, it is a big TV. Yeah. Um, but yeah, you don't get that
close. No. And you don't like bend your, you don't bend your body around like you're on the ride.
No. No more often than not, I like hit the 15 seconds back because I was typing and missed
something. It sounds like you take one hit of marijuana. Yeah. You sit and point yourself on
the couch and you just like stand still really like rigidly. And then you start typing furiously.
You know, one of my favorite fast sides is sitting very still and watching things.
Very Bieber-esque move. I have to ask, did you toke up and watch fly venture?
Their California Soren version. I missed fly venture. I think I didn't there because again,
there's so much stuff here. How, how, what does that fly over Seoul? It flies over hell. It's like,
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fly venture is, it starts like it's real and you are in Soren,
you're in the little chairs, your feet are dangling, giant screen. Everybody's moving around.
It feels real, but you quickly go from overlooking the ocean, like you're like Soren.
Then you're in this avatar land where there's all these floating pools with waterfalls leading from
one pool to another. So you kind of sail around these pools for a little bit. And there's these
neon flying fish. And then these thunderstorms start to happen and you go into this wormhole.
And when you come out, you're flying over at this desert with all these like impossible
cliffs that are just really jagged and you're going into these goalies and these birds are attacking
you. Then there's dinosaurs because there's just dinosaurs. If they can put a dinosaur in the park,
they're going to put a dinosaur in the park. Then these fireballs start coming at you and this rock
monster starts attacking. And then you go into- Oh, I just landed on him. He's so scary.
Then you go and see the sea out of him. He has glowing blue eyes. Wow.
Oh, this is a bad trip right here you're describing. So if you were blitzed out of your mind-
This is what he saw when he watched the candy ride. He saw this instead.
Then there's like lightning and tornadoes and hurricanes and lava.
Lava birds. This is, I mean, it's very inventive, but it's terrifying the lava bird.
So on top of everything else, they fit a flying theater in this building.
Yeah. That's insane to me.
Yes. What was the, when you were sitting on it, what was the like, was it like Soarin basically
where you was just kind of an open chair and you were like hanging out?
Yeah, exactly like it. It was exactly like Soarin. I don't remember they were piping in smells to go
with everything. Like magma smells. Magma smell. What does magma smell like?
Just like, I don't know, like burning, just like charred. Yeah.
You could probably just do incense and then it would work.
Incense, yeah.
It's just big cyclones. Yeah, you're right. This is some very end of the world shit.
This is for a genre of ride that is typically like the wine tour of rides.
This is maybe the only one I've seen that is scary.
Yeah. Even the music is a little Roland Emmerich-y.
Oh my God.
Yikes. God, I missed again, the size of this place. I didn't even see the words fly venture.
The great clunky title fly venture.
Fly venture. Yeah.
It looks cool though. Oh my God.
Interesting. That's like, cause in Disney world, they have a Pandora ride, an Avatar ride where
you're on like a mighty Akron, you're on one of the beasts. But that feels much more like appropriate
for a ride like this with a lot of action. Like in a motorcycle position versus like just chilling
out in a chair in the sky. Yeah. It really felt like you were going places you shouldn't see.
Interesting.
Yeah. But you know, to even just keep thinking about the scale and how they fit things in,
the longest ride by far is their knockoff of Pirates of the Caribbean,
which is called the Adventures of Sindbad. There's an extra D in there.
Oh, we love our Ds in our Sindbad.
Sindbad, yes. We've talked about this before. Sindbad.
It always feels so weird.
Is Sindbad real? Are we wrong for calling it Sindbad?
I don't know. Well, look, culturally, our Sindbad is the standup comedian who does not have a D.
So that's, I think, what is stinging our ears the most is that we, the one that we know doesn't have
that extra D. But maybe, I guess the story. Oh my God.
Who, again, you know, first kid is my main Sindbad pop culture.
Of course. But I think, yeah,
I think maybe the real story. Most?
I do have the other D. Yeah, there's a Tokyo Disney ride that we love,
but I think most places we were looking at it. So it does have that D in there.
Whoa. It's weird, doesn't it?
Yeah. This is like my mandala effect. I never knew it actually had a D. I was making fun of it the
whole time. The joke is on me. I think there's-
We've had the same thing. There's a stunt show in Islands of Adventure in Florida that always,
yeah, it was like sticking in our head the whole vacation. Sindbad? Sindbad?
It's why it's so upsetting. Yeah.
I think there are like American versions of Sindbad that call it Sindbad, I think, without the D.
Yeah, there are. So I think, yeah, there's, but I think maybe around the world, it's more
D Sindbad than non-D Sindbad. Do you think when our Sindbad, like comedian Sindbad,
goes to Korea and tries to order a coffee and he gives his name is Sindbad, they add the D?
Yeah, yes, I do think that. And does it confuse it with any other Sindbad's who are waiting for
coffees as well? I think it happens all the time when it's over there. Korea problems.
The Sindbad ride you mentioned, you're right, it is very long. It takes place seemingly 90% in caves
and again, very low ceilings, real low clearances on this.
I mean, I love this. This is what I want. The intimacy on the rides is what I always talk about
and that's what does it. Low ceilings, close quarters. I like feeling like cozy like this on
the ride. I think Jason's concerned. I don't think you like the, I think you're feeling claustrophobic
just thinking about it. Well, you know me, I like enclosed spaces. I was just amazed at a place
that's so grand in scale, like a giant atrium with a giant ice skating rink, an indoor amusement
park next to an outdoor amusement park. I was just taken back by how many things feel so intimate.
Yeah, yeah. Well, I guess, you know, to pack them all in there. Mike, you were talking about the
only the like lack of expansion abilities and I think one of the only times they were able to add
something else was like, because where else do we go? We can't really go outside. Well, there is
this recently, there is this level of the mall that we could take over that is as everything we're
describing very low ceilings and they were like, how do we justify it? And it became like this
world of goblins and trolls, which is called what it underland. Did you go to underland? Was
underland there? I don't know if we did. It feels like we we did go to some wild rest wild west thing
where we were riding horses. We did go to this astro blasters knockoff where you're shooting dragons.
I feel like these things are all in the basement together. Wow. But goblins, I don't know if I saw
goblins. I think maybe I don't know. Again, it's hard to track the zillion things here. So yeah,
I don't know. It's the only way they can fit all this in is to take them all out. Low clearance.
We did go on their space mountain knockoff, which was called Comet Express. And the structure is a
lot like space mountain where it's a dark ride. But the one difference they have is that your
seats rotate more like you're in the Haunted Mansion. Yeah. OK. Yeah. So your seats can kind
of wobble back and forth as you're in the dark ride. And it's not perfectly dark because they
on purpose have a bunch of black light planets and aliens surrounding you. So you're sort of
zooming in the darkness. And then sometimes there'll be like a giant Saturn or a giant alien
yelling at you. That's good. Yeah. That's what I want in space. In space, in Disneyland, there is,
I've said this before, and I don't know, there is a giant like either it's an asteroid or it's a
planet if you look, but you can't see it because it's too dark in there unless it's like the Star
Wars overlays happening. It's a little brighter. But I want to see planet. I want that because
space, I understand, is actually dark. I don't care. I want big, colorful planets. I think you
get that in France. Yeah. I was too scared to go in France, but I believe you get that there.
I saw a review of this ride, several reviews or comments about Comet Express that said this ride
is better than at least some of the space mountains. OK. Yeah. Like maybe not that that
France one or Disney. But like, I know it's heresy to some people to say that the Florida one is
bad, painful and it's a refurbishment or the Tokyo one, which they they're blowing up and just starting
again. But that's a pretty good review of Comet Express better than some space mountains. Yeah.
Yeah. Seems good. By the way, all of this is situated on a lake. I don't know if we've said
that yet. This whole massive complex, there is a lake and the Magic Island part is like built on,
I guess, still she would say you take like a footbridge out into the Magic Island part.
Yeah, I guess I just thought the lake was fake or like fake. It's real. They just built this on
a body of water. Yeah, I don't quite know how the body it looks pretty sizable. The wall.
So maybe it is fake. No, no, no. There on top of it. Like Mexico City.
I don't know the geography of Mexico City to say either way. Like Key West.
Like the lake that the Toothsome Chocolate Emporium is on in Orlando.
Now we're talking about Seven Seas Lagoon in Orlando. Yeah. Now that's a body water.
I also go ahead if you had something. Oh, well, I this is a long tangent. Did you have something?
We mentioned school uniforms earlier. And when I was watching some of these, like,
this is my life in Korea or like I moved to Korea now. So today I'm going to Lauday World. And
I'm one of them just very casually said, it's popular to dress in school uniforms at Lauday
World. There's a couple places to rent school uniforms nearby. And I had to rewatch this whole
segment of this video. And then I found I did find a news article from a Korean news outlet.
I think that works in conjunction with the New York Times. And this is countrywide. This is a
thing that you can do. You can rent a school uniform close by to change into change out of
your clothes, change into the school uniform. And then you go to the theme park. And I was like,
oh, God, is this going to be weird? And it seems just like we just like taking nice pictures in it.
And it makes us feel like we're kids again was the justification. And it is very popular. Like
there were rows and rows of like shirts and vests and pants and ties and skirts.
This is what they should have done for your school pictures.
You should have been renting school uniforms for the day.
Yeah, we never wore school uniforms before. But for the pictures, yeah,
it would have looked a lot nicer than the shitty fake tuxedo. My takeaway from this is that
Disney fans are leaving money on the table. Yeah, not having like rent Disney bounding, rent clothes
that look kind of like characters. Rent uniforms. Jason and I heading down to Anaheim at 8 a.m.
We make a quick stop outside of Anaheim to rent little boy school uniforms. We put them on. We
have the little shorts like the Angus Young from ACDC, little shorts, little schoolboy outfit on.
And then we go to Disney and feel more like kids than we already do.
Why do I feel like a country that invented Pizzagate will not get the joke?
That's fair. Yeah, that's currently eyeing the operations of this company and hoping for any
slip up like, oh, I think it's like a pedo place, but I know I'm watching them.
Ron DeSantis is furious at the rent, the business of renting little schoolboy outfits to adults.
And you by the, your plan, you are insisting that, and thank you for leaving me out of the plan.
No, I think you didn't want to do it. No, I did not. You rent me correctly.
We'll meet at the bar at the hotel at lunchtime.
Also, it's possible you already own your own little schoolboy outfit
and you'll just meet us down. Okay. You're not renting like Jason and I are.
Yeah. I bought the finest schoolboy uniform. That's an investment and I'll hold onto it.
And it encourages me to stay in shape so I don't outgrow it.
You know me, I'm thrifty. I'm no sucker. So you're going to get a better rate on a big lolly outside
the park and then you carry the big lolly into the park.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. As long as it's not too big to fit through the metal detectors.
Yeah. Yeah. I could be a part of that. It's so big. It's not clunk. Sorry.
You're going to have to lick some of the layers off of that before I can let you come in.
But my other thing about the school, everyone in the school uniform rental place
seemed like they were having a blast. And then when they were in the park,
all taking pictures together and taking pictures next to rides and stuff,
everyone seemed like they were having so much fun. I was like, oh, I kind of get it.
And then if you do the rapids, your nasty rental school uniform takes all the chlorine water and
then you can change back into your regular clothes. You are on board 100% for this.
Oh, that's a great idea. And I think about it because we didn't do the splash rides
because we didn't want to get too sticky. Yeah.
Wow. That's maybe a good idea theme park wide,
I guess, is to let clothes absorb and then you leave those clothes.
Renting clothes at theme parks should be a whole business out here.
Or before you go into the parks, at least. Yeah. I mean, I said that it's a good idea,
and yet I do not want to do this myself. The fact that you use the word nasty before the water was
part of it. I guess I don't want to pay money and then have nasty clothes handed to me.
Well, no, the clothes seemed very pressed, very clean, very dry, clean. They seemed a good shape.
Like the headmaster of the school would not be upset with the quality of the clothes
because they have to be authentic to your school experience.
They imagine a headmaster and try to uphold the headmaster's quality.
You're representing your fictional school when you go into this park, so you've got to look neat and
tidy. I mean, I will say as a person who had to wear a school uniform, did anybody else have to
wear a school uniform? No. I did. No one took out of school. Yeah, it wasn't so embarrassing and
restrictive. I really like polyester pants and shorts. They're just so easy to wear. They're
very breathable. They don't wrinkle. I'm wearing polyester pants right now. It's hard to find
polyester and I would like to see an embracing of polyester as a wardrobe choice. We've really
demonized it. It became this like 70s relic leisure suit. Do you find it comfortable? I guess I
haven't worn a lot of polyester yet. You do find it comfortable though? It's not like a scratchy
ear-taining fabric? I'm a person who can't iron and so polyester pants, you just feel a little
bit slick all day. They're amazing. Sorry, tiny polyester. My aunt is trying to make me pants like
my favorite pants, but we can't find the polyester anymore. They don't sell it. So we're having to
buy vintage giant pants and then cut them down to be my size of pants. Why is that? Why don't they
just sell like big, you can go to like a fabric store and get it? No. Yeah. We've really been
checking. Wow. And so I don't know if anybody has a beat on polyester out there. Anyways, sorry,
but if I could rent polyester and wear it all day and run around, it's a miracle fabric. Sure. And
then you just throw it in a garment bag at the end of the day and put your t-shirt and jeans back on.
Yeah, sure. Miracle fabric. I had a lot of bad experiences growing up of like Kmart dress,
like really shiny, too slick, uncomfortable polyester pants, I feel like. Because they
didn't have a lot of options in the husky boys section. So I feel like it was the mix of limited
selection and like, well, it's going to grow out of this anyway, you know. I made my fortune selling
husky boy polyester. Selling husky boy polyester. Son, you're going to take over for me. Suits and
shirts in the nineties were like really baggy too. And it's come back around, of course. Yeah.
You're only getting huskier, so there's a lot of opportunities for you. You're taking over the
business. I don't know about that. We never hear about the child obesity epidemic. I feel like we
were hearing about 10, 15 years ago. We don't hear about it anymore. We're onto other things.
Yeah. Where's other focuses? Yeah. Yeah. The woke agenda. C-E-R-T. Mine. Mine. Yeah. Yeah.
The Borg. There are all these kids. They're all doing those Borgs, those gallons of water with
vodka. What's the Borg? Do you know that soppy boys just did this? This is like the college
getting fucked up. Like, did you ever do Edward 40 hands in college? I've heard of it, but I didn't
participate. So this is. Don't spike the levels, Mike. He wasn't accusing you. It was a simple
question. I played flippy cup, but I did not do it. This is like the new get. It's like, OK,
you pour out half a gallon of water. You pour in like a handle or pint of vodka and then a
full one of those meal flavoring things and you shake it up and you just drink that and it gets
people insanely fucked up. But also hydrated. It's called Borg. Borg. Yeah. It's named after
my favorite Star Trek. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Why is it called? Do we know why it's called Borg? I don't
know why it's called Borg. Interesting. But I think it is. It's not like the vodka tampons of like
10 years ago or whatever. It's not like the Tide Pods where it's like, oh, this is made up. Like
two people did this. Like two couple of people. Yeah. This is a real phenomenon. And the rest of you had to write
articles. Yeah, this is a real thing. Is somebody listening? Is multiple people listening right now
or doing this? Yeah. Are you doing a Borg and listening to this show? Let us know. Doing a Borg
and watching the videos I bet would be more fun. Sure. Than the Smoke and Bees. Ride through video.
You see. Ride through videos are best paired with Borg-ing. For Borg-ing. Yeah. I don't know if I'd
Borg and do FlyVenture. Yeah. Yeah. That's the hangover ride. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It depends. Yeah.
Could we real quick go back and just, there's a few more characters we haven't talked about.
That's true. We missed everything. I apologize to go back. Yeah. Yeah. Uh-huh. So the characters,
yeah, we talked about Maurice. We didn't, there's Lippy Louie, who's the aristocrat.
But then I want to talk about Toulouse. You guys see Toulouse? You know, I don't see Toulouse. Oh,
wait. Oh, sorry. Oh, Toulouse. Oh, now I go. Okay. Does Toulouse seem like another character?
Yeah. Jason knows what I'm talking about. Yeah. Scott, you know what I'm talking about as well?
There's a character, of course, in the Duffy verse in Disney named Gelatoni. He's an Italian painter
cat. This guy- You're making a big leap that Amy knows the Duffy verse. I'm not saying she knows.
I explained what he is. I put it all, all the context I had is right there. He has like a stuffed
animal. There's a whole world of stuffed animals. It's much more popular in the Asian parks than
here. And one of the characters is an Italian painter. The only Duffy I know is Patrick Duffy.
So I'm really glad that you guys are giving me this. He has his own Duffy verse as well.
As a step-by-step fan. But I wonder, yeah. So I wonder who came first, Toulouse maybe came first.
Who do you think came first? You know what we've been, you've been looking at the whole history of
this park together. Think, look inside your heart. I don't want to admit. You know who came and give
credit to your pal Gelatoni for coming first. Okay. Yeah. Toulouse looks a little phoned. I mean,
some of these characters like, okay, white bear, the darling of the North Pole. He's got overalls
and a cockeyed hat and a little ice cream cone. Sharon cat, the glamorous and pretty cat. And she
has like a gown on and a feather boa. And human breasts. She's a cat with human breasts. Just
I'm going to make sure you see this too, Amy. Only two human breasts or six? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well,
unless there's others under the gown that we're not seeing. You know, she's got Jessica rabbit.
Why do I feel like Sharon cat is going to move in on Lottie? Oh yeah. But maybe, yeah, maybe it's okay.
Maybe that's part of it. Part of the relationship. Yeah. Which kind of Lottie's girlfriend do you
look? I already have a pretty girlfriend, so you have to find another quality if you want to be
another one of my girlfriends. Do we feel that Sharon cat and Jenny hippo are sort of in our
Helen test where we feel like sometimes the female characters get less fun names than the male
characters? Hmm. You're in Jenny Sharon cat and Jenny hippo, which I do like sort of the like just
a regular name and then an animal, but it does feel like it's not as fun as digger donkey or
burger Meister or Toulouse. Even Lippy Louie. See, I think Sharon cat and Jenny hippo have a little
bit of character, but like Burger Meister, the German bulldog, Mrs. Burger, talkative wife of
Mr. Burger. Like those, I think are a little more fun names. That does not pass the test. Yeah, yeah. When one character, when the male
character has a name and the other one is just Mrs. Male character, then that does not pass the test. I think we're in the zone
of that, of the Helen test. Yeah, a little bit. They're getting lazier for sure. I'll tell you one
thing. The character Fiddler does not pass the test of not being a ripoff of Jiminy Cricket. That's true, yes.
That very specific test. Now I will say I did not see a lot of lore with these characters, but I do
believe they all showed up at one of the two parades that we saw because there's an indoor
daytime parade where everybody marches around and then there's a nighttime parade called Dark Dreams
and everybody marches around again, but everything's like covered in black lights and there's
more Arabian stuff, more genies, more lights glowing, but there are people inside of these
marching. But I didn't even know their names, honestly, so I'm really glad to get to know more
of the names than the ones that I saw statues of. I wish they were more central in the park.
You got to do extra research. We've talked about this lately, needing to have extra reading materials
for the thing in the park to make sense. To know the lore. It doesn't seem ideal. There's something
about like, oh, now I've learned more and it enriches the experience, but it seems like you should
kind of know who they are and why they're having a parade. I want to know why my ears have a cactus.
Oh yeah. None of the, because I had this character tab open and I looked as soon as you said that and
I don't see no character with a cactus head. I cannot account for that one. I'm not sure. Any
listeners, if you've been to this place, do you know this pathology really well? Do you get cheese
curds in LA and do you know why the cactus is there? The ears seem very popular. I feel like
one vlogger immediately walked inside and there was an ear stand and everyone was buying ears.
I think I have a picture of my ears. I'm trying to pull it up to show you guys.
I think most importantly, if anything you've described, if there is a good picture of that
hot dog, I feel like we need to see it and the listeners need to see it. Send us whatever.
Can I bring up, I didn't realize this. I think I saw the name years ago whenever this happened,
but there was a viral video. Do you guys know what I'm talking about? That was basically showing
a ride that was kind of like a giant drop that looks crazy. The gyro drop. Yes. That's the name
of the actual ride and someone did some special effects to make this ride look extra insane,
where it would be drop up and then like these like, like chairs would kind of drop out once it was at
the top of its, we're seeing it. We're seeing the cactus. That looks like a little like, that looks
like a nice little like cactus pear kind of thing. Yeah, that's fun. In the succulent. I wonder why.
It's a very attractive plant. Why is it there? I don't know. That's a riding fantasy dream,
by the way. That's fantasy dream. Wow. That's great. Yeah. But no, you're right. There are like gyro
drops and the whole thing, because in addition to the rides, there's the carnival ride section,
basically where they've also got bumper cars and all the gyro droppy swings, the pirate ship,
all of that. Yeah. So yeah, but they, somebody made this to look like it was some insane,
like a torture torture device, essentially as if like every you're on this spinner ride and it goes
way up on a tower and then every single seat is separately deployed and drops flies out of 50 feet
in one second. They all swing around completely untethered to a vehicle, right? Like they're going
to get sucked back in and then the entire tower drops 150 feet. It's a really well done video,
except that you're watching it thinking this is just not physically possible. There's no way this
thing could move this quick. So this is the, yeah. So cause this was going around, I believed it.
All the car like seats drop out as you go up and then the thing just spins around and it does look
like you're torturing a bunch of people at a very high, a high distance. Oh, that looks awesome.
Which I assume a human being could survive this, but it looks scary as shit.
Too good to be true. It's just Guy Ritchie style drops like visual effects. Right.
Incredible CGI. The people who created the genie created this. We're learning now
is that the same CGI wizards were able to have a little respect. That's at least
Sherlock Holmes book of shadows level quality. All right. Fair enough. You're right. If we're
wanting to attend anything else you want to shout out ride wise, what it's just like,
let's just like grab bag anything else that was, that was fun that you got to go on in this place.
Well, I want to actually grab bag something that's right around the corner.
And it is a theme park that opened before latte land. It opened up in 1983.
It's called Yungma land and it is more of like your, your county fair kind of place.
Where there are like this, the spinning copters and the octopus who like scrambles you around
and the, and the carousel and everything about that. But what is special about Yungma land
is that when latte world opened, it just like killed it, totally decimated it, like ruined it.
Nobody went there anymore. So they finally shut down Yungma land in 2011, but they kept it open
as just a place you can go to, to wander around a destroyed and abandoned theme park. Wow. And it
is amazing. Like it's so wild. I think it's $5 to get in and there's this groundskeeper there
and he just lets you do whatever like total free range. They have the giant swinging pirate ship.
You can climb on it. You can climb on anything you want like ladders and everything. Like you
can climb on like these big laser trains they have that sort of look like they were maybe a space
ride back in the day. They have just everything stored together. So if you wanted to see like,
um, you know, okay, kind of, uh, you know, like those supermarket rides, even that they have for
little kids, we can ride a little car up and they have just like stacks and stacks of them just kind
of heaped together outside and you can kind of climb on them. Everything's a photo op. You can
just run around and just do whatever you want in this place. Oh yeah. What I'm looking at here is
like some kind of spinner ride, similar to what we talked about at the Bo craft where there's like
airbrushed rock star. Yeah, they've got Madonna on it. They've got an airbrushed Madonna on it
and also a Michael Jackson. And like bad era Michael Jackson and then maybe I don't, I don't
really recognize if these are, we're supposed to know who these are or are they? Cindy-ish? Lopper-ish?
Cindy-ish Lopper. Yeah. Uh, Julio Escaglaceus. I don't know. But then there's photos of this is
just like, this is just this ride with nobody on it, but then there seem to be photos of people just
in the middle. Like they got to climb on and kind of surf in the middle. Like it seems like a
potential for a danger maybe, but also like it's cool that the guy's just like, I don't know,
your own peril, just go run around. I don't care. They don't make you sign a waiver at all. It's
one of the most freeing places I've ever been in because you can just climb. You can climb.
There's everything is overgrown. There's weeds on the different roofs at the only facilities they
have is like a bathroom stall and I think like a, a little, what do you call it? Concession vending
machine, a vending machine where you can buy like sodas. And that's it. Otherwise it's just like,
you pay the five bucks, you can do whatever. And if the guy who kind of keeps an eye on things,
not to tell you to stop, but just to make sure nothing gets stolen, I guess. He does this one
thing where there's this giant pool of water kind of by the carousel. And I thought that it was just,
you know, a leak or a mistake, but it's this deliberately filled shallow pool of water that
the guy does, because if you're nice, he'll take your camera and he'll take the most beautiful
photo of you you've ever seen where you're reflected in this pool of water in front of
the carousel. And I have a Samsung phone cause I won't do iPhone stuff. And so he like grabbed my
Samsung phone, switched all these buttons on it that I don't know how he did. And I've never been
able to figure it back and took just like the Spielberg photo of me and my boyfriend kissing
of my life. Wow. Did he pose you too? He posed us, he directed us. I'll dig this out in a second
too. And it's just stunning. Wow. So this man is an artist. This park is amazing and it's just
frozen. There's like tiny little kids roller coasters frozen in midair. And I feel like if
you wanted to jungle gym up there, he wouldn't stop you. Wow. Did you do anything where you were
like, this is dangerous? Did you climb on anything? When I climbed, I did climb the ladder in the
center of the pirate ship because the pirate ship is my favorite ride. And so I, yeah, I climbed up
there pretty far. I got covered in mosquito bites. So there was a minute where I was like, I should
not have worn shorts here. So I'd recommend not wearing shorts there. Yeah. We've got on roofs of
things. Oh, no, the best one was, you know, those little carnival rides that you can go on where
you're sort of sitting in, it's like a kidney bean shaped metal chair and it's all enclosed. So the
ride can flip the metal chair around and around. Do you know what I mean? So yeah, you can get in
those and he'll just, he does not give a shit if you're pushing your friend into circles. Oh,
really? Okay. That seems dangerous. That was probably the most dangerous thing we did. Wow.
This is kind of a dream to do this. It feels both scary and exciting. Yeah. And there's this
statuary everywhere and it's broken. There's a tiny cop man by the entrance and his hand is broken
off and there's sailor moon and she's just beat to hell. She's just like, like somebody just like
ripped her stomach out of her chest. Yeah. Is it, oh, scary. And the $5 is like an official like
booth you give the fire or is it, you just slip the guy $5 like he is sometimes at the booth,
but yeah, very casual, very casual. There's not a ticket or anything. And I don't think I saw
anybody else working there. Wow. There's like one employee. Yeah. This feels like a dream.
It's magical. It's so magical. It's almost as good as latte land. Just getting to run around
this place for 90 minutes. It's just like the flip side of the coin. It's like, you know,
here's the fancy high tech one. And then that, that killed this park, but they found something
cool to do with this. It's like, it's like a good dismal land or something like a park, but you get
to have fun running around. It's not, yeah, it's not making up, making a point about, yeah, no
politics in my failed parks. They, they ran the numbers of like, okay, it's too much of a liability
for the backpack urban Explorer guys to come into this abandoned place. But if we open the
gate of the abandoned place, it's less liability than we're just on a walk around park. And that
keeps our bills lower than letting the backpack guys break in every other way. That's smart.
It's smart to turn it around on the backpack guys. It's magical. So both sides, I mean,
both of these places just like utterly trippy dream. Like you get your, you get your world of
200 polished candy canes and lollipops, but then you get your several decaying figures as well
that you can climb on and kick. Yeah. You're decaying walrus that you can just mount.
Wow. If you ever wanted to mount a decaying magical South Korea is the place for you.
Jeez, that's beautiful. Well, I don't know any, any closing thoughts here on the way? I mean,
this makes me want to go. So yeah. There's this like a monorail that has like a little character.
Oh yeah. There's also a whole like cute animal monorail. I know that looks really great, but
yeah. So there's probably plenty of stuff we could talk about. Yeah. And there's, and if you want the
Lotte world experience at home, there is a, in the spirit of them ripping things off, there is a
roller coaster tycoon mobile game ripoff Lotte world tycoon, which is a one star pretty universal.
So man, I'm going to play a terrible mobile game and not get the experience of this place.
You can too bad. Jeez, but Hey, thank you so much for, for bringing this to the table here.
A wonderful place that I'd like to go. I don't know when the hell we'll get to go, but listeners,
you gotta go. I think mainly you gotta go to, to the Yama land, right? At first. And if you have
time, go to the right. The giant one. Thank you for letting me revisit two of the most magical
days of my life. Oh my God. I'm so, I am so glad you could. Jeez. And thank you for bringing them
to the table for us. Amy Nicholson, you survived podcast, the ride. This is wonderful. Let's
next to the gift shop. Anything you'd like to plug? I, yeah, I do my podcast with Paul Scheer. I'm
sure y'all know and love that man. He's the greatest. Yeah. Yeah. And our show is just called
We started by doing the entire AFI top 100, going through all of them and seeing if they were as
good as people said they were. We ended up kicking 60 of the films up from the AFI list off the top
100 and now we're just rebuilding. So we're going on little detours. We're about to do young
Frankenstein. Oh, cool. Oh, wow. We're filling in the holes that weren't filled because it's just
like, we love Spielberg. He gets nine movies. Sure. Sure. Yeah. I, uh, do you like then, do you pick
those like, is that just things that you've suspected should be on there or that you're
passionate or why? I like, or are you dipping into like, uh, numbers 101 through 200? How does
that, how does it work? We are following our curiosity. So it's been nice. We did in Bruce
earlier this year, a movie that I deeply, deeply, deeply love. And then Paul made a case for us to
do John Wick and I got to talk about what's wrong with John Wick. So yeah. Yeah. Um, is Guy Ritchie
sneaking on there? Is he gotten one? You know, I do kind of want to go back and watch Locks
Dock and two smoking barrels. Oh yeah. I haven't watched that in a while. That and Snatch. I remember
both being, liking them a lot in high school. Those were cool movies at the time. They were very cool. Yes.
Like that and Boondock Saints. They were cool. And we were cool too, Michael. Well, yeah, of course.
We still are. Yeah, we, of course we are. There has been no cultural fade to Boondock Saints. No.
Exactly where it was at the time. No way. Well, yes, check out Unspooled. Check out all of Amy's
writing and check out, please send us some pictures if you can. I'm so curious to see some of these
epic shots you got. We didn't even talk, we didn't even talk about, I want to talk about Pitbull today,
but we didn't have time. Are you like, that's right. Pitbull. We've talked about Pitbull. Yeah. The greatest
live show on the planet. But that's, we don't have time. So sorry. You come back and we'll talk about
Pitbull. We can talk about Pitbull and we can talk about the steam park in Guatemala. Oh wow. Yes.
Oh, that's great. Yes, please. Anytime. As you're bringing us some stuff we truly have not covered,
taking us to real other worlds. And there's not been a full Pitbull episode, certainly that. So
that's high on the priorities now. But thank you so much. As for us, you can find us on all the
socials at Podcast the Ride. Merch is available in our T-Public store for three bonus episodes
every month. Check out Podcast the Ride the Second Gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP
tier club three. You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride, as well as,
it just depends on Jason's feelings about it. Once he sees the photo, if you put the high school
fake breakaway tux photo on, if you make it for the world to see, or if you pay wallet.
I, oh, oh, it's my decision. I guess so. Is that right? Yeah, I guess it should be.
I well know I'm stuck. It really shouldn't have been. Although we should have an official vote
here maybe, Scott and I can all vote you. Seems like that's already been decided. Amy, vote.
I believe that you should get the addresses of all the listeners and send them a physical copy.
That's what I vote for. Go back, get the negatives from the high school photo taking place.
And you pay for the shipping. You pay for the photos. You pay, not Scott and I, you pay.
I vote for that one as well. That's what I'm voting for.
Okay. All right. Wallet sized high school photos of Jason coming to all the listeners.
To your mailbox soon. Yes. Okay. Bye.
This has been a forever dog production, executive produced by Brett Boehm,
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.