Hello there subscribers, hello there patrons. This is Scott Gardner joined by Michael Carlson,
Jason Charrod. Oh boy, it's hush tones, it's hush tones here because anticipation is building
because we are so excited to unleash the next big announcement in podcast The Ride History and
genuinely I'm thrilled about all this stuff. This is a multi-tiered announcement. One leads to
another, one builds to another and it's all one big beautiful ecosystem. So let's get to it.
The first thing to announce is the next big podcast The Ride theme month, theme celebration,
whatever you want to call it and it is this. Podcast The Ride Sin City Nights, a celebration
of the themed entertainment of Las Vegas, Nevada. We've been talking about this for a while. You may
have even caught that we have not done a ton of Vegas. I think we did the Star Trek experience,
but we've been pretty sparing and a lot of the things when we say on Twitter, hey,
topics for second gay topics for main feed, so much of the biggest stuff that's left, so much of
the meatiest stuff that's left from current to 90s to probably insane 60, 70. There's so much,
I don't even, we don't know what it's going to be yet, but boy are we excited to cut loose on that
Vegas shit. Yeah. I mean, there's just, I, this could be a yearly tradition. I'm not saying it is,
but it could be with the amount of stuff there is to cover. Oh yeah. I'm saying it's the only one.
Yeah. Unless it is very poorly received, but I can't imagine knowing what we have to talk about,
knowing what's in the arsenal. Either it's poorly received or every episode is 20 hours long.
So either way, it's possibly possible. Yeah. We don't know. Very, very possible. I know. Yeah.
The endless running times might come back this month because we are salivating.
Cannot wait for podcast the ride sin city nights, but there's more. And the more is this,
the centerpiece of podcast the ride sin city nights will take place on Saturday, July 22nd
in Las Vegas, Nevada. As we put on our first ever live show in Las Vegas, or as we prefer to call it
podcast the rides, big Vegas groove blender. We guys also, you guys say groove. Let me do
one more time to say the rides. Big Vegas groove blender. Yeah. I sure bought a harmonica. Oh yeah.
That's right. Well that's the, Hey, save it for the show. Okay. All right. Fair. Will the show be a
live podcast episode? Yeah. But will it be 50 minutes of sweet harmonica playing possibly
when in Vegas? Yeah. It's the national instrument of Vegas. That's true. National is not the right
word. It's not a nation, but it's the, you know, they love it there. Let me tell you as a Vegas
expert, they love harmonica. It couldn't be more true. And yeah, you're going to be going to see
everything. We're going to have our, uh, uh, hard pack with us. Couldn't think of the name. Oh yeah.
The hard thing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're out there looking for talented camels as we speak. Yeah.
If you are a camel or Noah camel who is a dexterous at the blues, please tell us you are
joining the heart. You can join the hard pack 2.0. Yes. Uh, the best camel blues band in America.
Absolutely. Will there be sword swallowers? Yeah. You bet. Will there be swamis? You bet your ass.
There will be swamis. We got so many swami resumes right now. We're just sorting through them. Yeah.
They're just, they're covering our houses. Um, so it, the big stuff, uh, uh, coming up for this and
mainly just excited to, you know, the live shows we just did were a blast and we're excited to
bring that energy to Las Vegas on Saturday, July 22nd. Uh, though this will be at the space LV,
which is just a few minutes from the strip. Uh, excited to check out this venue. Uh, uh, please
come out if you're in the area, come out if you're not in the area, maybe come out, make a thing of
it. You've been looking for an excuse to go to Vegas. Uh, maybe there'll be some other little
treats we can do. Uh, if, if people make the trip, we'll all meet up at the heart attack grill
or something. Oh, basically we all, we're all doing some challenges. We all, we all the owners,
we all say, yeah, that's not happening. Uh, no, probably not. Uh, but we'll work, we'll workshop
some other ideas between now and then, oh wait. And I forgot something. The swami, no, I said the
swamis know what I forgot was this will be the very first podcast, the ride live appearance of
the great Eva Anderson. Yeah. Eva Anderson joining us for this. She's not here, but she will be not
joining us for the announcement. Uh, but you know, we can pray if you need proof that she, I have
text messages. We have the receipts to prove that she, she will be there. She's excited to be there
and to do this. Uh, the best guest in podcasting in the greatest city in the world, right? Next to
Buena Park, next to Buena Park. Next to Buena Park. We got to figure out a Buena Park live show too.
Uh, but you know, first, first things first, we're building to that. Yeah. We're starting,
we're going to number two city and then up to number one city. Eva Vegas enthusiast. Yes,
indeed. Yeah. Yeah. Oh boy. I can't wait to see what we settle on with her. There could be a
thousand things to talk about. Uh, and we will toss all of it into our big Vegas groove blender.
So excited about this podcast. The rides big Vegas groove blender with Eva Anderson,
Saturday, July 22nd tickets available in a link in this post and also at the space LV.com.
Cannot wait. Hope to see you there.