Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain
un-PC dinosaurs, wind jammers that can't jam in the wind,
and emotionally charged berry goo.
Rachel Bloom introduces a cavalcade
of her favorite old school rides from Knott's Berry Farm
on Podcast The Ride.
This has been a podcast, where you don't lose
a r tropical
of ready-made grocery store funnel cake.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Mm, I have a lot of thoughts on that.
You think it'd be like a taken-baked pizza?
Yeah, I do think it would be like a taken-baked pizza.
Okay.
Scott Gairdner, do you think it would be like that as well?
I guess so.
I don't know enough about the, wait,
but don't you need the oil and the bat?
Like, there has to be a big vat at some point.
Yeah, there's a lot of machinery needed
in a grocery store to make that.
So yes, it would be, that's why they're not doing it,
I think, is because it just takes up too much space.
But you're describing a version
where we don't need a method at home.
We don't need a big open vat of oil in our homes
in order to finish out the process.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
It's not a take home.
Because that sounds dangerous.
Oh, I see, yeah, because what Jason proposed
is that you would have to bring it home and make it.
All right, I disagree with what Jason said.
I think it needs to be made in the grocery store
and you can take it home.
Well, Scott voiced my concerns.
Is that like, yeah, a big element of funnel cake
is the hot burning oil.
So I'd be concerned, like, yeah,
I don't think you could just do it in an oven.
You just have to get a big drum of oil outside.
It's an outside thing.
It's only if you have yards or patios.
Right, and like you have an artisanal pizza oven
maybe if you're wealthy or something
and now you'll have an artisanal big drum of hot oil.
Big drum of hot oil.
It's like the deep fried turkeys
that always go so well for everyone every Thanksgiving.
Like there's so many wonderful videos of people going,
wow, this is so safe and fun and delicious.
Wow, this is so.
Let's post our success.
Let's post a video of how well it went.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But let's bring her in.
We have very exciting topics to talk about today.
You know her from Reboot and Crazy Ex-Girlfriend.
Returning to the podcast, it's Rachel Bloom.
Welcome back.
My God, so thrilled.
Hey, thanks for joining us again.
Nice to see you again.
Oh no, I just spilled a ton of green juice.
Oh no.
Oh jeez, we're gonna have to vamp.
Okay, so back to see this.
She's illustrated exactly what the problem is.
If you can spill green juice at home
then a big open drum of oil.
That's fine.
It's why a more industrial kitchen like grocery store.
I think you would have to,
you just want it to be available in more places.
Yeah, because it's so theme park specific.
That's okay, don't worry about it.
Seems like it's going fine.
We don't have eyes on it.
We can't see the disaster.
Only Rachel knows what she did.
It was only a shot.
It wasn't a full 16 ounce bottle.
So it could be worse.
Doesn't it better that she did this here
and not like on a talk show or something?
I think it's hard.
In a limited, in a five minute window.
Now one whole minute of it is gone cleaning up green juice.
Here we can stretch.
She can deal with this
and we can still have a big art conversation.
We're playing it like it's live.
Yeah.
This is what's fun.
I mean it's almost like, you know.
Yeah, no, we're trying our best,
but like Drew Barrymore would have a lot of fun with this.
That could have been bad.
Wait, let me close my door.
Our family won't see.
Drew Barrymore would have a lot of fun with this
and she'd be very reassuring.
All right, luckily my computer was raised.
I just, I recently had fried my computer's motherboard
by spilling hot sauce on it.
Oh no.
You've just been down this road, this exact road.
Listen, I'm not the most graceful, graceful person.
This tea's probably gonna spill at some point.
Oh sure, okay, we'll be ready for it.
We love, you know, you don't get a lot of physical comedy
on a podcast, it being an audio medium,
so we think of pictures.
Nor should you.
I'll be fine, I don't know how funny that'll be.
I enjoyed it.
I hope, as long as it wasn't stressful for you,
you know, we're good.
No, it was great.
I wish I'd given you more of a, whoa, whoa, beep beep.
Baa baa.
We can edit those in, that's perfect.
You gave us ADR, we'll plug those in.
Very, hey, very wacky soapbox racers kind of,
crazy Spike Jonze sounds is what you just did.
Yes. A segue.
So yeah, we're talking about a whole grab bag
of old Knott's Berry Farm rides.
Yes, a delightful request on your end to just,
to say you wanna talk about old Knott's Berry Farm stuff.
You were after our hearts with that.
Well, like, I went to Knott's Berry Farm
as much as I went to Disneyland as a kid.
And you have these, I loved amusement parks
from a very early age.
I think we've talked about this,
and I grew up in Southern California,
which I believe you did too, right?
I did, yeah.
Yeah, but like, Valley, more so,
so it was all a little further.
Where were you again?
Manhattan Beach, we were far.
Yeah, that's not close to any of this, I guess,
but I mean, sort of south a little more.
I'm so jealous though, that Knott's was in the picture
as much as Disneyland's, that's great.
You know, my parents, I think, liked amusement parks.
Also, they could tell how much I loved them.
And I was an only child.
So I didn't have a sibling to compete with
of where we were gonna go.
And my parents just were down to go to amusement parks a lot.
We had a year-long pass to Disneyland.
We never had a year-long to Knott's,
but we went quite a lot.
And when you have these early amusement park memories,
it almost feels like they were a dream, right?
There are these like deep, there are these deep memories
and no one ever talks about them again.
And especially with the thing like a place like Knott's,
Disneyland has so much more of a history
and a lore and a fan base around it,
because Knott's is local.
Very few people are talking about it.
Like I went to Knott's,
I'd forgotten that the Tampico Tumbler closed,
which is one of the rides I listed I wanted to talk about.
And I was just at Knott's with my friend, Sarah,
and I asked an employee, I was like,
hey, do you guys have the,
because I think it used to be called the jumping bean,
but I was like, you know, the ride where you go like,
whoosh, whoosh, whoosh, whoosh.
I forgot it was called Tampico Tumbler
and they had no idea what I was talking about.
And so there's a part of you that thinks,
did I make that up?
Yeah.
Was that a dream I had?
Because when you're a kid,
you kind of live in a half dream state,
but I didn't.
It existed. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, everything's, when everything in a theme park,
especially is like big and surreal anyway,
and then memories get hazy.
I feel exactly the same with Knott's especially.
Where, yeah, you're right.
It's not like, up until only very recently,
maybe, are people like really listing out,
here's what all the stuff was.
So like something like Knott's Berry Tales,
I don't know if you got to do that
or if that was gone by the time you went,
but like I had the haziest,
like maybe I went on a ride with bears and berry juice.
And I also, this one's I'm wrong on,
but I had the haziest memory for a long time
that there was a Smurfs ride at Knott's.
And there is a Smurfs ride in the world,
but it might be in Dorney Park, it's across the country.
And I don't think I went there, but who knows?
I sort of like these like hazy, scary,
am I making up this ride or was this a dream?
It's kind of fun.
Yeah, there was one at King's Dominion,
a long, long time ago.
Maybe I went, wow.
Maybe like even before the Paramount ownership.
Okay, huh, huh.
But your memory was you went on it?
I have the vaguest memory of Smurfs
and I remember that they were below me.
I remember like as if they were working in a mine,
but am I just conflating that with the mine ride?
But I don't think I would have confused Smurfs
with realistic, ash-covered, like mine workers
like you see in that scary Knott's mine ride.
Weird.
This is where you start to get into Mandela affection.
And there are things I remember that my parents maybe don't.
And so then if I bring it up and they don't remember,
I feel crazy.
I mean, that happened directly with Berenstain Bears
when the whole realization happened
on how Berenstain was spelled.
I have distinct memories of my father making jokes
that the Berenstain Bears were Jewish
because it looked like it could be Berenstein.
That's why I remember it was EIN.
And I called my parents a couple years ago and I said,
how do you spell Berenstain Bears?
And they said, STAIN.
And I said, you're not my parents.
I've been switched.
I'm not your real daughter.
You're not my real parents.
I belong back in the other universe, please.
Wow.
This is your matrix.
This is getting yanked out of the matrix.
Funny example to use because just like last night,
I saw an image going around Twitter from one of the books
that revealed that Mama Bear is 27 years old.
Really?
Yeah.
No, no.
This is as a child.
If you'd asked me as a child,
I would have guessed 54, 62, just off hat alone.
Look, bears used to age differently back in the day
when these characters were created.
Wow, 27.
That's revelation.
Oh, that hat is just so unsexy.
The hat does a lot of the work in the aging.
Look, she looks terrific.
Don't get me wrong, but that hat is wild.
Yeah, I mean bears age pretty well.
Bears don't crack.
Sure.
As they say, bear community.
They sleep a lot of the year too.
She's gotta style herself better to de-age.
Well, she's constantly wearing clothes
that she's going to bed, I feel like.
It looks like she's always going to sleep.
That's the thing.
She's depressed.
She needs to, they don't have antidepressants
in that world, I guess.
That's too bad.
My mom's, somehow I was allowed to read
my mom's teenage diary at one point.
And she said, it's mom's birthday
and my brothers and I just got her some potato chips
and a pillow, because all she does is eat and sleep.
Oh my goodness.
And I'm like, grandma was clinically depressed.
Wow.
Not something to be mocked and needled with mean gifts.
Wow, what a different time.
Different time or just my family continuously.
Anyway.
Has this gift been given since though?
Has this been a generation?
It doesn't sound like the word, honestly,
regardless of that potato chips and a pillow.
Jason, that's a good, you're an expert.
And both very practical.
I feel like my family is very pragmatic.
We all like and give gift cards.
And it's fun to have them.
I think they're fun.
I always thought they were fun.
And now I feel like people use them as like,
oh, it's a toss off gift.
I love a good gift card.
And my parents, okay.
My parents are and have always been huge fans
of Barnes and Noble.
And whenever I had a gift to give someone in high school,
my mom would say, well, if you buy a Barnes and Noble
gift card, you can pay for it on our account
and we'll get points and you'll get a discount.
So for like, all of my senior year of high school
and maybe some of college, my gift to my peers
would be a $20 Barnes and Noble gift card.
And you know, worst case they can go get coffee,
they can get a chachki.
No one was ever unhappy about it.
That was great.
Yeah, when my parents would ask like for extended,
oh, someone wants to get you a gift, is there anything?
I'm like, well, Borders or Barnes and Noble,
it's always fun to go there with gift cards.
Borders you can.
Maybe I'll go to Barnes and Noble
and buy up a bunch of gift cards.
And that's just my gift from now on.
And I'm like, it's also a little bit of a go fuck yourself,
but I kind of like it.
Yeah.
They could get a Funko pop now, you know.
Oh, that's one of the many, many stores
that's converted to the Funko economy.
That's probably one of the main things they sell there now.
It's Starbucks coffee and Funko pops
of like J.J. Abrams or something.
Which I've seen in the store.
I'm saying that from experience.
Oh, you're not just being flippant, yeah.
No, I'm not being flippant.
I've seen a J.J. Abrams Funko pop in a Barnes and Noble.
Makes sense, gotta stay watchin' out.
What personality he is.
Yeah.
Imagine if you have a toy of him,
all the adventures he could go on.
Sure.
And you know, that Funko pop saw you as well,
cause you know, big glasses.
What?
J.J. Abrams, he has his big glasses.
Oh, he saw me because he did.
Yeah, he saw you back.
This is his big glasses.
All right.
I guess so.
I guess.
All right.
Are you saying that the only people who can see at all
are people with glasses?
Are you saying toys can see humans
if they have big glasses?
Well, I see different level.
I see through your skin to your ligament.
You know, we say the truth, those glasses wearers.
So glasses can show, glasses show toys, humans, I guess,
is really what I'm getting from you.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
We have another episode on that.
Foggy sentence.
We have to unpack what Jason said later, I think.
Oh my God.
Can I ask before we dive into not stuff,
can I ask the parent question,
cause you have a daughter now, correct?
Oh yeah.
Are you theme parking it up with the,
are you on the other end of that now?
Are you indoctrinating her, the best indoctrination?
I am.
And I wasn't forcing it, but we brought her to Disneyland.
So she's three and she's been three times already.
Which is a lot.
These are my stats, exactly.
We fit it in three times before he turned three.
So he was free, three, three, free.
Okay, so you get it.
First time she was like,
I was like, how is she liking this?
And then the second time was when she was like, oh yeah,
no, this is on.
And then, so we went for her birthday and she loves it.
And I think what's interesting is seeing her,
the way she reacts to rides,
really taking me back to how I used to react to rides.
That you either, you kind of instantly fall in love with
them.
Well, it's like you instantly fall in love with them.
So when she went on the Astro Orbiter at Disneyland,
we had to ride it for four times.
Wow, wow.
And I thought it would be too fast for her,
but she glimpsed it across the park and she said,
I won't go that.
I said, okay, it's fast and it's high.
And she loved it.
Insisted on going all the time.
And the first time she went on it, she closed her eyes.
She got a little scared,
but then she wanted to go on it again and again and again.
You're always on, I guess what I'm saying is it reminded me
how is it when you go to amusement parks as a kid,
you're always on that tipping point between exhilaration
and fear.
And that's what's exciting.
The fear is what's exciting.
So we took her on Mickey and Minnie's runaway railroad.
Is it runaway railway or runaway railroad?
Railway.
That is runaway railways.
Really separates the men from the Ian McKellans.
We took her on that and she closed,
there was some parts she loved,
the Daisy Duck teaching dance class.
She loves Daisy Duck.
She was obsessed with.
And then there's a part where a mallet smashes,
is look like it's gonna smash you.
She got very scared.
And she came off the ride saying, I didn't like that.
But then the next day she just wanted to watch YouTube
videos of that ride.
And I remember that.
I remember you're fascinated by what you fear.
And I had that for years with upside down roller coasters.
I knew all of the stats about big upside down
roller coasters, but I wouldn't go on one.
I was too scared.
And then finally I went on one which was Windjammer
at Knott's Berry Farm.
That was my first upside down roller coaster
because there was one loop.
One of the rare upside down coasters where there's
just one loop, it was very fast.
I remember it.
It was one quick hill going into a single loop.
And it was like once I crossed that Rubicon
I could go on anything.
Wow.
That's a cool, I think that's the thing you can rediscover
as apparent is the theme park as gauntlet.
That there are many challenges for all ages.
These are things to strive to at three or at eight
or at 12 or whatever.
Or at 37 to 40.
Yes, as a person who wouldn't go on Splash Mountain
until several years ago, yes.
Sometimes it never ends.
Oh, is that because of the drop?
Yeah, my biggest thing is drop.
And especially, it's easier for me to do a drop
on a track where it still feels controlled.
But I think something where it is pure gravity
feels very naked and vulnerable and uncomfortable to me.
The three of us are scaredy cats going into this podcast
to start a podcast about roller coasters in some ways.
We're scared of them.
And Rachel, I forgot to, I should have brought this up.
Last time you were on, you suggested,
because I was going to Six Flags,
that I do Twisted Colossus.
That was your recommendation.
And I did Twisted Colossus.
And it was one of the scariest things
I had ever done in my life.
And the restraint, the harness also hurt me.
It was uncomfortable.
Oh no, I'm so sorry.
No, I mean, it's good.
Again, you actually encouraged me to get into
part of the gauntlet that I had not gotten into.
And when I go back to Six Flags, I'm going to do it again.
I'm gonna conquer it, somewhat conquer it
next time, I'm hoping.
But it was very funny, because you did encourage me
to do something that I was scared to do,
like go on a crazier roller coaster.
So thank you, I guess thank you, yeah.
This is the only you can decide for sure
if it's a thank you or not.
No, it was, it was.
Because again, it's like, well, I didn't,
it felt like when I was little, and I was like,
oh, should I go on the ride?
Should I go on Big Thunder?
And like, oh, I loved it.
I mean, I was scared, but I made it out.
And that's part of the fun of like going on a ride,
because you're like, am I going to make it out?
Yeah, I did.
Usually.
I'm glad I gave you that experience.
I'm sorry the harness hurt you.
I had that experience the last time I rode X, X2,
at Six Flags, the ride was really bumpy.
And we may have talked about this last time,
but the ride was really bumpy,
and it really fucked up my neck.
God.
And it was like, yeah.
And not even like, well, it was fun, but I'm in pain now.
No, it was a little bit like,
something's wrong with this ride.
Like they need to smooth it out.
They need to get the harness better.
Like it didn't feel, it didn't feel safe.
Yeah. Sure.
Like for my body, like, I mean, the ride felt safe,
but like for my body.
Yeah.
As opposed to, so I went on Hangtime at Knott's Berry Farm
when I was recently there, which has replaced Boomerang,
which was one of the rides that I remember.
Hangtime is intense, and you have to keep your head back.
If you don't keep your head back on that ride,
you will get kind of fucked up.
Yeah.
But if you keep your head back, it's awesome.
Yeah, we did, Jason and I did that one.
And that one is fun.
Like that one's fun.
If you're, once you get out of the complete, you know,
on your back. Yeah.
Well, you don't.
Rising up part of it.
I feel like you didn't like the hang.
You didn't like the looking straight down for a beat.
We've.
And I really didn't like the vertical.
We've talked about this on the show, thrills versus chills.
And chills, to me, is the sort of slow acceleration,
the one where they're dangling you.
Psychological.
Psychological are chills.
And I'm not as big of a fan of chills as I am of thrills.
I like thrills.
I like thrills too, but we also, you and I at some point,
rode Ghost Rider at Knott's, which is the wooden coaster
that they built in, goes kind of around the marketplace
and the parking lot.
And, you know, I've ridden a lot of wooden coasters
and I just went on with my glasses.
And like after the first few seconds,
I was like holding them the whole time because it is so intense.
I was so caught off guard by that coaster of like maybe one of the,
it's really good, but it's maybe one of the most intense coasters
I've ever ridden and I was not expecting it.
Oh, that's really interesting.
Because I, because when Ghost Rider, I love Ghost Rider so much.
Yeah. And I haven't ridden a ton of wooden coasters because
uh, they, I grew up here, so like there wasn't, there wasn't one there.
There wasn't one at Disneyland.
Knott's had this one, but it was like not great.
And then Colossus was like a kind of very smooth roller coaster.
Anyway, I feel like it's one of the great rides out there,
but I can't tell because I haven't been on a ton of other extreme
wooden coasters, but I think Ghost Rider is so good.
Yeah. Yeah.
I grew up on the East Coast, so there was a good amount of wooden coasters.
And I think in the Midwest, there's even more.
But it's like I, as a kid, I could just take the bumpiness,
like the intensity of that.
But yeah, until I was like 12 or 13, I was terrified of going upside down.
I don't know what I thought would happen if I would enter
another dimension or something.
But like, I think I thought I was falling out of the car.
Yeah. When I was a kid, I thought, oh, I'm going to go upside down
and like, I'm just going to fall out of the car.
Like that's I truly just very fundamentally.
That's what I thought might happen.
Yeah. Cartoons just imprinted on.
So like your daughter, we were scared of mallets, anvils
falling out of like the cartoon.
The loop goes, the carriage goes in a loop and then falls into the car.
When it gets back down, you had an actual fear.
See, for me, it was much more.
How am I going to feel when I'm in that loop?
Is it is the feeling going to be unpleasant?
Is it going to be so intense?
But you but that's interesting.
A material fear of I don't like this shouldn't be possible.
It shouldn't be possible.
But yeah, fear of unknown for sure.
Like, yeah, how am I going to feel? Is this really going to be
it's going to be like a tilt of where all where it really like pushes
on your stomach and you feel it or yeah, what is it going to be?
Upside down is, I think, kind of overrated in terms of like it.
I think we all built it up in some way.
And then it's not that crazy.
At least to me, it's not like the craziest thrill in most cases.
It's visually daunting in the way that, you know, Astro Orbiter
from a distance is visually visually very appealing.
You know, yeah, it depends how fast you're going on the on the loop, too.
Because like the yeah, yeah, I have got I guess the loop is negative G force, right?
And that's negative G's and then positive G's is a hill.
I don't know.
I think positive G's, I think positive G's are like the humps, the airtime
and the negative G's is the pressure on your head.
As I've gotten older, I I'm I
it's not like I don't like it.
I'm just I feel the same way.
It's it's fun, but.
It's not the it's not necessarily the most intense.
Part of the ride, like a good hill going into a steep turn
is just arguably just as kind of thrilling and intense as
as a ride with many, many loops.
That's something that I'm reaching now is
I'm not necessarily afraid to go on any rides, but I am hitting.
I feel my body starting to
feel the weight of these coasters in a way I could I could go to
I could go to not Six Flags in high school and be fine.
And now I have to eat a big breakfast.
I have to be eating throughout the day.
I need to have a stomach that is not hungry or I'll get nauseous.
I need protein in my body and I need to space out going on roller coasters.
I can't go on them.
I have to pace it because otherwise I will get nauseous.
And that never happened before.
And I'm glad that I can still go on coasters.
But the pacing, my pacing has slowed down.
Like if I were to go to Cedar Point, which is still one of my dreams,
I would I would have to make it, I think, a multi day
journey. I would I couldn't I wouldn't try to cram all those coasters in one day
because my body can't do it.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I've I've had this thought like, oh, I'm going to have to like train
or keep in shape of in some ways so I can go on the rides of the future.
Because I do want to because, you know, there's going to be cool rides
when I'm 70 years old and I want to be able to do it.
So I have to be in some shape.
My neck has to be not like cramping up.
I have to figure out how to.
I don't know if it's just doing more yoga.
I'm not sure what diet you got to think about to. Sure.
Yeah, every facet of it.
It's a little more astronaut for everybody.
We need to we're all kind of astronauts as we are.
Or these are astronaut shape 30s.
Well, and at five one, if I'm not careful, like my head will just ping
pong ball on those shoulder restraints.
And like I can kind of tell the upkeep quality of a coaster
on how much that that's happening.
Sometimes I get off and go like this is going to get refurbished.
I may have gotten a slight concussion.
Let me ask.
So that's one of the.
Oh, good. That's one of my memories about Windjammer,
which is one of the roller coasters.
So Windjammer was, you know, first roller upside on roller coaster.
I went on. It was a roller coaster at knots from I don't know the years, but opened
probably late 90s closed mid 2000.
So so despite being called Windjammer, it would close whenever there was
too high of a wind.
Yeah, it was a it was a badly.
It was a badly made made ride that that unfortunately replaced the
crazy soapbox racers, which was, I think, a bad decision.
And I do have a memory.
The first time I wrote it of coming off of the loop,
my head bouncing against the shoulder restraint.
Luckily, they really padded it because I think they knew it was going to happen.
But but even then, I was like, oh, this is weird.
Yeah, not even three years in.
This seems like the rarest.
I didn't know this story at all,
that it was seemingly notoriously bad and resulted in a lot of lawsuits
that kind of ruined the company.
I think not. I think nots did not end up winning the lawsuit, but it destroyed
the reputation of the company that built it, who also built the New York,
New York roller coaster, which from what I've heard, I haven't been on it
from what I've heard from people who have.
That should be enough to destroy a company's reputation on its own.
That's a terrible role.
Has anybody done it here? Yes.
Yeah, it's fun. It's bumpy, right?
I haven't been on it in a little bit, but if I remember,
it's pretty for a steel coaster. It's very bumpy.
It's pretty bumpy.
Yeah, the company was called Togo International.
It's a big Japanese company, and they they started an international
subsidiary and their main projects were
Windjammer and like New York, New York,
and that subsidiary pretty quickly closed.
And now there is a different company that updated the track
and ride cars on New York, New York.
I don't know that it's any better.
OK. Oh, but they just divorced even from like if they need new parts,
they don't even talk to the place
because I don't think this division exists anymore.
Yeah, this is a thing that happens sometimes.
Like Disney got in this with one of their
maybe primeval or one of Triceratops, something in Animal Kingdom,
where it's like, oh, this ride is closed a lot in recent years
because the company that built it doesn't exist anymore.
So getting replacement parts is near impossible.
Oh, jeez. Weird.
And you went, Scott, you didn't go on this, right?
What on Windjammer? This was two.
No, no, no. And yeah, it was at what?
So I was in like sort of middle school to early high school.
This was a very scaredy cat time for me.
So no Windjammer Surf Racer.
So in theory, this is supposed to be a racing ride.
But it seems like the racing was never really committed to.
They just they did not launch the two cars at the same time.
So you weren't really racing.
I do remember watching the cars.
And it was like you'd ride in these blocks of cars.
It wasn't even like a.
I think that's part of the reason was closed.
It was it was like only kind of one car.
It was it was that
I remember watching these two cars going around the loops
at the same time, and it was very cool.
But I think that's maybe the reason it was shut down is because you didn't have the heft
of a long ride car.
You just had this one little thing.
And it made the why is it when you have a like.
On a crazy mouse coaster,
why are the why are the drops more intense
when you're in just like a one, you know what I'm saying, like a one.
Yeah, as opposed to a smooth, long thing, there's something about that, though,
where you feel it's like good as opposed to like me.
Yes, those are awful to me.
I'm still not a fan of that.
Yeah, I don't know.
They have the less you have with you.
So much of a train, you're so much of that for me is psychological.
Yeah, for some reason, I feel very comfortable when there's a long line
of people, a bunch of friends are on the ride with me in my mind.
And I'm like, well, nothing's going to happen to all of these people.
It's about like, I don't think it is.
I'm saying for me specifically.
Sure. But yeah, there's something movement, though.
There's a I'm sure there's something in physics.
Yes, explains why things are kind of more intense.
It's closer to what I was saying about Splash Mountain that you're for me,
where you're in a little log and not the safety of a big long.
Yeah, well, it just feels feels crazier.
Goofy's Sky School, which is this like the scariest ride at Disney for me.
That sensation of almost going off the track and it's because you're in a little tiny car.
Yeah. And it's like, I know that's yeah, the idea is that like they're
making you think you're about to fly off the track.
But that's by far the scariest ride for me at Disney.
And Windjammer also had a loop it.
So the wild mouse loop combination, not really done very often.
Maybe only this. And that's interesting.
Yeah. Then it didn't work very well on top of that.
So yeah, and it would it seemed like, yeah, you would get a concussion on it.
So people sued because they got brained it like they got brain injuries.
I don't know if any if any individuals.
I think the knots was really unhappy on the Wikipedia.
I'm seeing that the fact that they couldn't operate during medium winds,
that wind jammers jammed in the wind, they knots called it an embarrassment.
Yeah. Wow. And then they just left it there and didn't deconstruct it,
but didn't run it for a long time.
And also, I missed this one that at some point on apparel company,
presumably called Windjammers, challenged the coasters name
and they had to change it to jammer for a while.
Oh, that's really funny.
What a combative three years.
This is a disaster, seemingly. Yeah.
Yeah. It's I just looking at the pictures of it.
It's just it seems like it could have been fun.
I just I don't know why.
It was it was fine.
I would say, like on the list of things, I'm sad aren't there anymore.
It's it was like a a pretty like not good roller coaster,
as opposed to the the parachute jump, which was awesome.
And and you still have the knots tower with the sky cabin.
Yeah. So I'm like, why not just leave the parachute jump?
Yeah. Why did you do that?
I'm not sure about that. The parish.
Yeah, I kind of miss when I wasn't paying a lot of attention to knots.
I miss that they took out the parachutes, which I always associated with it,
because you can see it or you could see it on the horizon
before you got into the park.
Like it's part of it.
It's if there is a not skyline that's iconic at all, parachutes are part of it
is part of all the ads for a while as they celebrated 100 years.
Like those are back in the mix.
Like, remember the parachutes?
But it's been a long time.
The beautiful Buena Park skyline. Yeah.
Well, and the great part of the parachute jump was and that's one of the home
movies I found like the great part of the parachute jump is that
it was the first intro to a drop ride that kids could have.
Yeah. Because it was gentle.
You were standing up in a cage like with your parents.
So it didn't drop you that hard, but it just gave you a little sensation
of what a drop ride was like.
And it was super it was super fun.
So I should say I went through my mom years ago, gave me all of our home movies.
So my my mom,
my mom and grandpa both videotaped constantly.
And I have 72 DVDs worth of home movies that my mom gave me.
And at some point I had them digitized and I put them all on my Google photos.
So I have all of my home movies, including like home movies
from like my my dad's family in like the 40s.
Wow. I have them all.
It's awesome. So I so then Google has like a really cool.
I mean, it's spying on me, but like a really cool thing where I can just put in
amusement park and it'll show me any photo or video that I've had
at amusement park.
So I was able to find home movies at nots.
And one of the ones we have is a parachute jump and like, yeah, it's awesome.
Geez. Yeah. Wow. Wow.
Wait, do you have it? Can we see you?
Yeah, I do. Yeah. Yeah.
Do you want me to share my screen? Yeah, sure.
Please. Yeah. Here we assume technically this is fine.
Yeah. OK, great.
All right. So this is me, my dad and my friend Dallas on the parachute jump.
Yeah. Oh, my.
Oh, oh, my God.
I thought you were in the line. That looks like a line cage.
That's interesting.
You're standing up. Yeah.
That's really weird.
Odd ride mechanism.
It's like a it's kind of like you're in a shark cage
and they pull it up into the air.
The opposite of a shark. Yeah.
The direction.
Wow. Wow.
You're on the left or right. Where are you?
I'm on the left of the hat.
Well, you're happy.
You're talking already reviewing it.
So it was once up and one down.
Two big visors, rainbow visors, big visors.
My family also, we are wearing
I don't know if you noticed, we're all wearing matching sweatshirts,
except for my friend, because we went to we'd recently gone to San Francisco
and we did a thing where you could sit on a dinosaur
and look like you were all riding a dinosaur.
And we got that photo put on a sweatshirt,
which I feel like people don't do as much now.
Getting a photo, like getting a photo on a sweatshirt,
considering how many photos we take, we all of our clothes,
when you think about it, could be photos.
It's true. We don't we don't.
Why don't we do that anymore?
Yeah, that's weird, because I feel like Uniclo or H&M
like often will sell just like a baggy sweatshirt
with just a square or rectangular photo on it.
But we're not opting for it at the specialized.
Yeah, because you see at Disney, like the people have like maybe
special sweatshirts, but it usually just says like grandma's turn in 75
or something. Yeah.
Like it'll be a custom made sweatshirt, but it won't be like photos.
But that was a thing. Was this just my family?
My parents know my OK, because my parents have a have
numerous sweatshirts of me as a kid on them and they'll wear them
to shows of mine. Oh, really?
Very cute. Yeah, it's very funny.
And I feel like I should start
doing that, like maybe I should get a sweatshirt of my husband
that says like my pudding and just and just and just wear it around.
I think, yeah, for sure. You should do that.
He'd be proud. Yes, that's great.
Sure. That parachute ride,
I feel like I would have warned my parents out like they would have been like,
all right, it's your turn to go on.
He wants to do it again.
But as a looking at it, I'm like, this is a little terrifying drop
getting dropped in this little cage.
Standing. I would have.
I remember the idea.
I remember my parents suggesting that we do it and I and just know
like, no, no, no, no, no.
Look, you just get in a cage and then it drops.
You. It's not funny. Stop suggesting it.
Like, yeah, even the badgering me.
I'm like, this is not one of these things that'll be funny that I'm overreacting.
I'm shutting this down, which probably they just made fun of me more. Right.
I did this. This is a hazy memory that came back.
You're thinking about these parachute, the like just a cage.
That doesn't seem I need something to hold on to.
This is why I have the bars of the cage.
I guess so. But that sounds they're just rattling.
That's not safe.
I'd want to go to the ground also.
Yeah, it wasn't.
It probably wasn't safe, but it had been around since like the 70s.
It was the symbol of Knott's Berry Farm. Yeah.
It's a thing we like to rides that are kind of intertwined,
like the sky cabin and the parachutes.
Like, yeah, there was an original like concept art for Disneyland
in the night that the Indiana Jones ride would be a temple
that the Jungle Cruise boat would be changed to go through.
And that's just two rides going in between each other is so fun.
Oh, I love I love that. And it's so rare.
Yeah. You have the Disneyland railroad that gives you a brief glimpse
of Splash Mountain.
The people mover used to give you a brief glimpse of Space Mountain.
Yeah. And Star Tours.
Yes. And Skyway used to go through Matterhorn.
So a lot of them are used to.
Yeah, the Skyway is because they still have that in Disney World, right?
No, it's gone for a while.
Oh, yeah.
So I thought they took it out of Disneyland because people kept
opening the doors and and jumping out and getting injured.
But did why did they take it out?
The sky was sky cabin was awesome.
I think the liability on both of those were a nightmare.
There was a guy who like jumped out or fell out and ended up in a tree.
Yeah, it wasn't the only reason, but I don't think it helped.
Sky Jump, I don't know, like of, you know,
not to not to bring everybody dead.
There was there in there was a suicide on Sky Jump.
The first death that not in 1983 on Halloween night even.
But it was it ran for a long time after that.
So that wasn't why.
It's actually kind of crazy that they just like, well, what do we do, gang?
Put our heads together, not adjusted in any way in the wake of the suicide.
Nope. Still a cage. Still good.
No restraints.
When you think about it as the most like, yes, that is the most
suicidable ride probably ever.
Yes, it's a shark cage with the top open.
Essentially, you just got one jump and then you're
nothing holding you in there. No belts, nothing.
And someone had climbed in the last few years, someone climbed to the top
of the sky cabin. Yes.
And then just hung out there.
And then eventually, you know, they got him.
Or was that the other one?
Was that was that Supreme Scream?
And is that the correct name?
Oh, I don't know.
That would be very to climb to the top.
I mean, to climb to the top of any of these would be dangerous.
But Supreme Scream.
Oh, I guess so.
You're never against if you could climb the tower.
The Supreme Scream
cars are never flush up against the pole.
So I guess you'd be fine.
That's so high. That would be so scary.
One of these for sure.
It did happen recently.
And the guy got down safely.
You know what?
I don't know if there's enough time to put a stunt into the new
Mission Impossible dead reckoning.
But a Tom Cruise stunt off of this thing would be really exciting.
Oh, sure. Very high.
Well, in getting to see him, you know, go to an amuse.
That's one sequence that we've never seen in a Mission Impossible is a big
in and like, yeah, run amok in an amusement park sequence.
I think we'd all like to see them hunt to that.
Yeah, no, we would.
I don't think they've done that on Fast and Furious either.
Oh, that's true. That's a good point, too.
Like a car riding in the roller coaster track.
Oh, wow. Oh, it's on the. Yes.
Yeah. On the track.
They have to perfectly steer to the contours.
Oh, that's great. Yeah.
Because it also if like it's too twisted, Colossus has two tracks,
like maybe one is the roller coaster and then one is the car.
And like they have to get somebody on the roller coaster.
So like they're trying to jump from the car to the actual roller coaster car.
That'd be well.
Or because roller coaster tracks are much more narrow than cars.
But so but if it's a racing coaster, you have two wheels on one track,
two wheels on the other track, and you are the roller coasters right behind you.
Oh, that's good.
You don't if you don't get fast, stay fast enough.
That roller coaster is going to demolish your car. Right.
Well, that's like you have to drive faster than gravity to stay ahead of that.
I guess that's what I'm saying.
I guess that's what I'm saying, which is a big that's that seems like a challenge
that Toretto in the game, if he was going to do it.
Could do it. Yeah. I'm in the family. Yeah, sure.
As long as with the power of family behind them, with the power of family behind them,
it's more powerful than gravity.
It does seem like one of the comedy like that Ludacris
would would get up to in those.
He does all the gags and stuff.
I believe ended up in space and enough enough.
An old car with a jet engine strapped to it in space in the last one.
OK, great. Yeah.
So, yeah, roller coaster is not washable.
Yeah. Yeah.
I would have been missed a bit.
Oh, you know what?
Iconic thing as part part of the sky jump tower, which is still there, but the
the big knots K, that's an old school.
Oh, yeah. It's thing which they replaced.
It's now like it's now an LED K
so it can flash all these different colors.
And we were all there for the the opening of the new K.
What a moment. You were there.
We got a we saw the K turn on.
We didn't go on any rides.
We just saw the K.
But I I. That's awesome.
It was special. Well, that was also that was like things are starting to reopen
post pandemic. So truly like a K turning on was like tear inducing.
Well, I have an insane email because I I know the nots PR people
because one time a bunch of crazy ex a bunch of us and crazy ex
like went to nots for free.
I have an insane email I sent.
Oh, boy, this is probably July 20, 20.
So my daughter's three, four months old.
It's thick of the pandemic.
I had a very traumatic March 20, 20.
I gave birth. My friend died.
Covid a week after she was born.
I had her. I had a rough go.
And I have an email that I sent to my Disneyland PR contact that says, hey,
I know the park is closed, but I have to imagine
that you guys are running the roller coasters.
Is there any way I can just sit on a ride
while you're running a roller coaster?
I haven't been on a roller coaster because I've been pregnant.
I was pregnant. I haven't been on a roller coaster in almost two years.
I'm having a rough time.
Can I please just sit on a ride and then I'll go and I'll pay any.
I'll pay you. I'll pay you like and I won't.
I don't I'm not going to go around the park.
I'm not I don't expect food. I don't expect the bathroom. But.
And she got.
She's like, um,
I'll check with my contacts.
I don't think that will be possible.
And it's a it's a it's a crazy thing to ask.
But, you know, you miss 100 percent of the shots you don't take.
Yeah, it literally never hurts to ask.
The worst thing is they get a little mad and then probably forget about it.
But also, maybe you made their day.
Maybe that was like, you're not going to believe what happened to me today.
I got to tell you this story.
Yeah, and it makes sense, right?
You have to run the coasters. Right.
Yeah, they're there. There's all some where you have to keep them from being rusty.
Can I just. Yeah, just just sneak onto it. Sure.
Yeah. And they're making zero dollars as it stands.
It's like, right. I was like, I will pay you full amusement park admission
just to be on one ride one time.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I was I was the one who was assigned
the duty of like a 2020 early summer pandemic.
Me and my girlfriend put in an order.
They had opened the Nantes chicken dinner restaurant for pickup.
And I went and we went down and it was so surreal to like
there was only like 10 cars in the parking lot and half of them were workers.
And I was like, I have to walk under the roller coaster to get like
I hadn't been in a park. I hadn't seen a roller coaster.
I hadn't used a public bathroom in months.
And it was just so bizarre.
And there was just like, yeah, public bathrooms open.
And it was just the cleanest thing I had ever seen.
But it was just so bizarre to be standing there holding our dog
underneath Ghost Rider and no one's around.
And it's like perfectly quiet.
Mm hmm. Wow. Just being near.
Just let me touch a roller coaster.
Can I hug a roller coaster? It was at that point.
It's like, well, the pie and the chicken will keep.
I think we can walk around.
And you would be you, Jason, have been emailing them every day.
Can I please have a chicken, please, please?
Finally, they opened it up chicken while touching a roller coaster.
I don't even like that much.
White meat is so dry so often, but I'll take it.
It got so sad. All those things.
Did you ever go to any of the things where it's like, OK,
we are opening Disneyland, but not restaurants or stores.
You can just be in there.
Nothing is open.
There is nothing to do.
And it is cold. But you can go.
I went to one thing like that that was it.
I think it made me feel worse, actually, then.
But I wanted to.
I was curious if it would make me feel better.
Yeah, we drove a car through Six Flags.
Oh, right. In Christmas time.
Oh, they had opened up.
Oh, yeah, that was the thing.
In 2020, you could drive your car through Six Flags
and they would have like, I don't know, lights.
There would be some lights.
The light shows were pretty good.
And then there would be some people dancing.
And then at the very end, like a sad Daffy and Bugs.
Well, yeah, but I didn't wait at you said you saw a bug.
I saw a bug.
Bugs was on a break.
And I was like, well, there was no finale.
And then we just left.
Although we did get a hunk of fudge on the way in.
We got complimentary fudge on the way in, which was nice.
I just delivered to your car.
You're in a mask.
They're in a mask.
A mask.
Where a hazmat suit hands you fudge.
That's where we were at not long ago.
Yes, I remember it well.
Did you do any of the like what do you do?
Or maybe you couldn't get out with with young baby at the time.
But did you have any like, well, this is a sure a sad attempt
at trying to get theme park fun.
I did a drive through drag show.
OK, cool.
Sat in sat in our cars and watched a big drag stage.
That was fun.
I did a Sinus Pia drive through with Death Becomes Her.
That was very fun.
Oh, that's fun.
That was it. We were really, really careful.
Yeah.
Yet we still got covid in in late December, in December 2020,
because my husband had an eye infection and he had to go to the eye doctor.
And he wore an N95.
Geez.
But he got it. He got covid from there.
So we all got it anyway.
We are so cautious.
We are.
I mean, we're on the more careful side of people.
And we have had covid more than anyone we know.
Wow.
Geez. It's like you're because you're more cautious.
So I don't know.
It's just karma.
It's weird. Bad luck.
But especially
it was rough before we were vaccinated, but post vaccination,
it's, you know, not as bad.
Yeah, yeah.
Sure. Let me just make sure we get to more of the nuts stuff.
I, you know, let's I want to make sure we get a little time in for Wacky Soap
Bugs Racers, because as we so what are the sads?
We kind of went backwards here.
But the you know, this this problematic,
multi types of lawsuits.
Windjammer Coaster opens is gone in three years.
This is the spot where now it's accelerator, which is the one
that's like a pretty fast launch.
It's pink and there's like one big loop is the or one big towers
kind of the main facet of it.
But this spot was it was first a motorcycle ride.
It was called Motorcycle Chase until 1980.
And then I guess it's a cursed spot because this was starting to be
a problematic ride,
not not in a cultural sense.
Yeah, it was canceled.
Yeah. Yeah. No, it was not.
They didn't have that then.
Motorcycle Chase. OK. Yeah.
I'm looking at pictures of it. Yes.
This was you. You were basically up too high.
Like it was cool to sit on a motorcycle.
But if this ride came to a sudden stop, you're really screwed.
Like you're barely you're barely hanging on.
There was a problem with the center of gravity on the ride.
But they wanted to keep the track and they wanted they don't want to start
from scratch. And a guy named Eddie Soto, later an Imagineer,
realized, well, what if we just it's the same track, but you put everybody lower
and then maybe we can salvage this thing.
And that was the core of it.
But on top of that, he creates this experience that's this wacky,
unique, singular cartoon world.
This is like an auteur.
This is I really never I knew this thing existed,
but I never looked at it too hard until prepping for this.
Boy, this ride seems great.
And you got you got to do it.
It was awesome.
It was so fun.
It was the perfect I wrote this when I was five or six.
So it was a perfect it was one of the few like family
I think the only thing I'm the only family roller coaster not had.
It was great.
And and you see you're you're still kind of above the track.
So it felt a little surreal.
I loved it.
It was awesome.
It seems so fun.
And in theory, OK, so the racing, which often doesn't work on a lot of rides
and really didn't work on Windjammer, the idea with this
is that it's kind of like a bobsled competition where if everybody works together
and leans and uses their own center of gravity, that you maybe like,
let's work together as a team in the soapbox here.
And we can actually maybe shift our weight and win the race.
I don't know how true it was.
But it seems like people actually did try.
And what a cool dimension for a ride that you maybe there is an actual competition
that really works. It's not arbitrary. Yeah.
And tons of painted original characters.
I think there was some animatronics to the there was an announcer animatronic.
Yeah. Of like these animals and cute lions and clients and bears and stuff.
Cats. I did.
It did remind me, too, of the Warner Brothers or not.
Warner Brothers, the Hanna Barbera.
That show was just called Wacky Races. Yeah.
So similar, very similar concept.
But like this is a whole universe of characters exclusive to this ride.
And I think this and Berry Tales are the ones that I hear most about.
Like, oh, there's commemorative merch.
There's there's a very thorough.
Eddie Soto has a very thorough Wacky Soapbox Racers website, like Memories Web.
Check this out, Rachel.
Wacky Soapbox Racers dot com.
It's I have never seen such a complete archive of a website
from the people who actually built it.
You can see like people painting and prepping all the characters
and what the old ride looks like and why it didn't work and how he fixed it.
I it just and you keep scrolling and scrolling and more and more pictures appear.
What a great sight.
This is really watching the ride.
Yeah, you bust through the doors.
Oh, yeah, this is really.
Doors fly open.
It has that kind of madcap like the Mr. Toad kind of deal.
You know what I was saying about I don't know, Rachel,
I don't know if you've been on the Mario Kart ride yet.
Not yet. We all maybe don't like the ride.
Maybe we can just be as simple as that about it.
Don't feel the best about it.
The racing feels arbitrary and it doesn't.
And it's very slow.
And they're trying to make the race nature of it all happen in the goggles
that you're wearing. They are goggles.
And I had been saying, is it a wild mouse?
Is there some jankier way to feel more like Mario?
I think this is it.
This seems more Mario Kart than the Mario Kart ride.
Yes, for sure.
This is yeah, you were kind of mentioned it, but like this feels like
the one of the pieces of not identity,
basically, that went away when they started like.
Because it's original.
It's original kind of IP.
It's like original lore.
Right. And the Berry Tales was that way, too.
And now you've brought it back in a less lesser version.
Yeah, we never talked to an episode about it, which might indicate.
I don't know. We liked it.
I liked it. Have you done that, Rachel?
The new the new Berry Tales is like a shooter shooting pies.
I have I haven't.
It's maybe I have.
If I have, it's very forgettable.
Well, because that took the place of the dinosaur ride.
And the dinosaur ride was awesome.
Yeah. And that also had its own IP.
It had its own animatronic character who was a doctor that was like.
And I remember he go, we go, we're going back back
50 million years.
And it was this character.
It had its own story.
And any ride now that has its own story has been taken out in the place.
Well, I guess Berry Tales is its own IP.
Yeah. And it's been. Yeah.
And they brought that back.
But like the only way you're getting not IP in a theme park
is if the theme park can't afford IP. Right.
So we need our cheap parks.
We need not to have no partnerships with anything
or else we don't get these delightful original worlds.
The story is on a lot of these.
And I had kind of heard versions of them over the years.
But it's like it all depends on like how well the park is doing financially.
Who's in charge?
Like eventually when Cedar Fair buys Nats Berry farm,
the guy is in charge and he makes an effort of like,
we're going to put in dark rides at all at all of these parks.
And I only learned this from an expedition theme park video.
When Cedar Fair bought Nats Berry farm,
that was their first time running a year round park.
Oh, that had never occurred to me because all the other Cedar Fair parks
are in places with cold winters.
So they close, you know, for for parts of the year.
But Nats is open year round.
And he kind of like committed to like, let's get some dark rides in there.
Let's revitalize the ones that are in there.
And that was part of the big, the big change.
Eventually, the family, the kids, the Nats kids sold off
the park to Cedar Fair and then Cedar Fair kind of they know rollercoasters.
So they start putting in that stuff.
And then eventually when this new guy takes over,
that's when you start to see a lot of revitalization efforts at Nats.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Personality put it back in. Yeah.
And yet the Kingdom of the Dinosaurs fell into the crack.
Like, I didn't realize this thing.
They just let it rot. They stopped running it.
And then people just started going in there and stealing stuff or
breaking parts of it.
Or like, it's very it's awful what happened to the.
Brett, can we see it?
I think I sent an ad for Kingdom of the Dinosaurs just to go back to the
to happier times, which imagine like it is 1987, I believe.
And you see you were like this is probably the beginning of kids
being obsessed with dinosaurs.
It's like I don't know that that exists as much before the 80s.
Oh, wait, they're not this one.
But the although, you know, while you have it open, this is another.
I like this clip, too, which is weirdly I played a part of this years ago.
This is this is I don't know one of the hosts, but the other one is
Gary Owens from Laughin.
Oh, I recognize.
And they they were hosting some dinosaur show and they went through the ride
as part of this, but I didn't play this moment from it.
Just pay close attention to the animal that they point out on the ride.
A sloth.
There it is. A three toed sloth.
A sloth. A sloth.
It's a sloth. Look.
Oh, it is a sloth.
Yeah, it's a three toed sloth.
This are we how do you get sloth?
Is the guy just is the guy just dumb or do we not know what that part?
Or is it not a new area mania at that point?
Is it a regional thing?
Like just a weird I had never heard sloth.
Oh, it's a Pennsylvania thing.
No, it's not a sloth.
But that's unusual, because sloth is one of the seven deadly sins, isn't it?
Like, that's right.
That's what they want to differentiate.
Yeah. Oh, maybe.
Maybe he's like, yeah, he's very religious.
He studies the sins and he's like, surely it can't be sloth.
That would not be a nice name for an animal.
Like how we learned the planet's name was Uranus when we were kids.
And then all of a sudden it was like Uranus was the way people were pronouncing it.
And I suspect it's because we have to do something.
I call bullshit on that. Yeah, it's Uranus.
It's Uranus. Yeah.
It's just deal with it. Fuck you.
We give kids a little bit of fun.
Let them play with the naughty word.
That's a fun day in school.
When you figure that out.
Yeah, I feel like I pretended for a while.
I felt like, hey, Uranus, ha ha ha.
I get it. I did not get it.
I didn't know what it was.
Yeah. Here's the on a cleaner, more wholesome note.
Here's this commercial. It's wild. Yeah.
Over 16 million years ago,
the most ferocious creatures the world has ever known
mysteriously disappeared.
Oh,
introducing kingdom of the dinosaurs.
Mom, guess what?
They're not.
That's that. Oh, that's very cute.
Thank you, pal, missing for that video.
Yeah. Imagine.
I mean, like, imagine seeing that in that year, if you're a Frady Cat kid.
And the ride does not reflect the that like fast cutting
psycho screen.
And the ride wasn't that the ride was.
When I went on it, it was we're going back in time.
It wasn't scary. It was look at these amazing dinosaurs.
Yeah, yeah, just very, very gentle, calm, like sort of an eerie air.
But then none of the dinosaurs do anything actually upsetting.
So that's that's a bit of misrepresentation.
One of them said off color remarks.
Right.
But if you just plug your kids ears.
Yeah, it was very weird.
Suddenly, like at the end of the ride, the T-Rex was like, women can't drive.
And it was everyone coming out of the door, like confused.
Everyone's like the very end of the ride.
Did you hear that too?
Do you? Hey, a comet said in for us,
well, I'm probably whipped by Uranus.
Yeah, they put that on a shirt, though, that in the retro merchandise.
Oh, sure.
Dinosaurs saying women can't drive and millennials wear it now, ironically.
So and they but all the right operators are instructed to say, no, I.
I didn't know. I never did hear that.
You're crazy.
Dinosaurs roar is what they do.
I don't know what you heard.
Yeah, I guess they're just so amazed.
You must be the crazy one.
Every employee is gaslighting.
The origin is the first gaslighting ever done.
So yeah, it's very fun.
It was that movie and then the ride.
30 years later, but so on and on with it.
Yeah, this was why do really well, I do really quickly.
I look at home movies are mostly boring, but I do want to just play
one more thing that I have, which is the old roller coaster boomerang,
which is where hang time is now.
Boomerang, which formerly was corkscrew.
And then they changed it to boomerang.
I don't know if it's a different ride or if they just gave it a new code of
paint, but this was like
the only multiple upside down roller coaster at knots.
And in 2001,
when I was in eighth grade, I somehow got my dad to go on it with me.
And my dad had been on upside down roller coasters, but he was
he was getting on in years.
I have kind of an old dad.
So my dad was born in 1945.
So 2001, he was.
He was his fifth.
He was early 50s.
So I do want to just play you my dad's reaction after going on boomerang,
because it's very funny.
So this is all right.
So this is us here.
It'll be you can edit around the boring stuff, but it is quite fun.
All right. I don't have clips of parents.
We've done surprisingly little.
Your song with your mom.
That's true. All right.
Can you see? Yeah.
All right. So here's me, my dad.
All right. Let's see.
OK, sorry, I should have.
Oh, boy.
So we're joking, huh?
Have they changed?
Anyway, I'm going to sign up.
OK, so my dad and I go on Boomerang.
My mom is filming us on Boomerang.
Let's see how much you can see.
Can't really see much.
Where are we? All right.
There's our car. Oh, my God.
I don't know.
I would never go on this.
Did mom always sit it out?
She said, right?
She's never been on an upside down.
Oh, OK.
So you can kind of see us.
Yeah. Oh, there you are.
I just looked it up.
We're right.
Oh, we're right there.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's commentary.
Boomerang, right?
I don't know where they are.
I don't know what they're doing.
I don't know. I don't know why they're doing it.
I don't know.
So here we go on Boomerang.
All right, you'll see our faces drop.
There we are.
It's a big slow lift back and then it drops you and then you do the thing
and then another then you get stuck again and then you go backwards.
OK, so.
It's my dad getting off the ride.
In the white shirt.
Yeah.
That was worse than I remember.
OK.
She's out of the will.
Oh, my God.
No, it was.
Did you see me?
Did you see me on the loop?
Yeah.
What do you say, Alan?
How was it?
No, you know why it was worse?
No, wait, I'm trying to get his face.
It was an experience that nobody really needs.
Give her a picture.
They make you up, they shut you up, they took you down.
Oh, my God.
I'll never be the same again.
OK, bye.
Bye.
So that's what I wanted to.
It's an experience that no one really needs is like kind of a great way to sum up
roller coasters in a way.
Yeah, if you look at it, if you look at it, why?
Why would anyone do that?
Why would anyone do this to themselves?
And then later in that movie, I get the camera and I'm like,
Dad, Dad.
And I'm being playful.
And he's like, I need to get home.
He's clearly nauseous.
He's like, I need to get home.
Stop filming me.
Oh, wow.
He's kind of in a bad mood.
Yeah.
And he wasn't kidding about the will.
You guys have revisited this once a decade.
No, I'm out.
Yeah, yeah, I'm out.
Yeah, he meant it.
Yeah, man of his word.
He said it with a smile, but he means business.
I mean, there's a few great things about that footage.
One, your dad's reactions are so good.
Like, you can't script lines that good.
The other thing is your mom, like the camera's a little shaky
and then she finds you guys in the car and she perfectly
captures the release.
She perfectly captures the drop.
She killed it.
Yeah.
And I don't know, I love home movies.
Like, if I love watching home movies of my own, I love
watching other people's home movies.
I just think what an amazing time we live in that we have
ways of documenting.
We have primary sources of our lives.
We didn't have that until really recently.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, and the grand scheme of humanity.
Yes, really.
That's what I'm saying.
How lucky we are.
It's crazy.
And then it shifts in the fun of like, here's old, here's 2001
DV versus like old 8 millimeter or whatever.
We have the last and we're like the last, we're the last
people that will have like old looking stuff, old looking
video.
Like in the future, like our kids are like have like
perfectly clear videos documenting so much of their
lives now.
My kids live fully 4K.
4K life.
It's only going to grow 20K.
Yeah.
50K.
Yeah, I have a photo of my daughter, like photos every
day in very high quality.
But like, I think it's fun that all our home movies still
like kind of feel like the past.
And I guess, I guess photo resolution will get better
somehow.
So maybe what I'm saying will be wrong in the future.
I feel like how the 90s, the 80s and 90s did, which is,
I don't know, just a little bit janky.
Yeah.
I like that our, our, when we were kids feels like old.
I like that.
That's fun.
That's what I'm saying.
It takes a little pressure that it's not like totally crisp
like the evening news now.
Like your, our phone is the same as like some films or
some like broadcast TV, but like watch it doing this show
and like combing through YouTube, like home movies.
I'm so grateful for them.
And it's so cool to see people like loving these attractions
and stuff, especially for ones I never got to do.
Yeah, yeah, really.
No, and it's, yeah, it's kind of neat that it's like
archaeology, that there's not like the crispest footage of
wacky soap box or kingdom of the dinosaurs.
But yeah, especially because both those two have similar
stories of like towards the end, they let it go to rot
a little, like they didn't, they didn't keep it up.
There's other ones like Boomerang stuck around till 2017.
So you can find HD footage of it, which is surreal.
When did we go?
Was it 2016 for the first time I went?
Was 2016 maybe?
No, it was before that, 2014 I think.
Was it that far away?
So I did Boomerang and I think it hurt.
I'm pretty sure it hurt my neck.
It really felt like it like compacted my neck, my vertebrae.
And I did, like I hated it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Maybe like one of the worst rides I ever went on.
So you're in Rachel's dad's camp.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was not, so I probably just was like going, ah, afterward
and not saying anything funny though.
If I could, as we're winding down, I have a couple of clips
I like to play that, and especially like to get your
thoughts, Rachel, as a musical person, a musical fan,
because all of this is music oriented.
And we skipped through some different like shooting
eras as well.
I know when we talked about Nott's many, many years ago,
I showed a, they made employee music videos every year
in the late 80s.
Oh, great.
And I had showed an I Love L.A., I remember,
but I don't think I showed this one.
Brett, we just call it employee song.
And I'm a fan of this one too.
And it's, the production value is kind of crazy.
Like they got a real crew to come film the employees
singing and dancing.
How many jobs is that true of in 1989?
Good point.
OK, Nott's Berry Farm!
Ghost Town!
Rory Twoniesh!
Count Snoopy!
Fiat of the Lane!
La Sencha!
Bigfoot!
Calling out around the farm.
Ready for a brand new beat.
Summer's here and the time is right.
While dancing in the street.
Dancing at the May Game.
Dancing in the street.
Down at old school row.
In gasoline holly.
Dancing in the street.
All we need are smiles.
That's the bulk of it, I'd say.
There'll be good times everywhere.
Wow!
Yeah, look at that.
The spirit here, fully committed to.
And that's just internal or is that for the public?
I think that's internal.
I think that was for a summer party.
Wow!
To get, to like light it.
Those are camera moves and that.
Yes!
That's a production value.
They got a drone somehow before...
Yeah, yeah.
The first drone.
That's amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
That's pretty great.
That maybe speaks to the spirit that was around there at that time.
And then you got this and this is just camcorder.
But do you know about the association over the years with Elvira at the Halloween events?
Yes, I remember this.
I've never looked into this too much.
I know Doug Jones has said the Elvira show was so great and I think she only recently
stopped doing it.
But this is probably late 80s, I think.
But if we could pull up the Elvira.
And I don't, okay, I heard that and I don't know a lot about Elvira to be honest.
This clip makes me like, okay, I need to dig in much further because this is the most kickass
looking thing ever.
What do I want to do?
I want to be a dragon.
Is that Elvira or an Elvira impersonator?
No, that's her.
That is her.
She really did a bunch of shows every year at Knott's Berry Farm.
And in this case, a big dragon head in the back.
It's getting hit with a laser.
Yeah, laser's like carving up the dragon.
Like trying to kill it, trying to blind it.
She was really big.
And it was one of my first, like she dressed with her boobs out and she was sexy and she
was ubiquitous.
I feel like she was everywhere.
And it was this thing where like as a kid, you're just exposed to this like really sexy
woman and everyone's like, okay with it.
And you're like, okay, yeah, I guess this feels, it felt very adult, but coded adult.
Sure.
And it's also like a Halloween thing.
So you're like, well, she's dressed for the season.
That's what's like, like I feel like maybe that's part of it as well.
Maybe that's my headcanon for it.
I don't know.
The overlap between spooky and sexy is very confusing as a kid.
Yeah.
Did she start the correlation between the two things?
Now I just want to go on an Elvira deep dive.
Yeah.
I've only done, I don't know, I've never seen that movie.
I've just read, she's a lesbian.
She's been with a woman for, her name is Cassandra Peterson.
Cool name.
Yeah.
I know a little Elvira stuff.
I've seen the movie.
She made a good ad for the, in that universal Halloween award show.
Yes.
You can party with her at universal studios if you won the beer contest.
She's probably, I would guess the most famous horror host of all time, which is a whole
genre of performer that I'm pretty obsessed with, which includes like Svenguli and going
back to many different people like Paul Thomas Anderson's father and stuff, the great Goulardi
of course.
You have an hour ready to go.
The hour is about to spill out of you.
I would love, it's at the end of the episode.
Many parties.
I know, I want to talk about it.
There's a certain hour where you leave Mike, I'm going to go get another drink.
You come back and he's talking about Goulardi and Svenguli.
Graduate school thesis about horror hosts.
We do need to do more Elvira stuff though in regards to Knott's Barrier.
I want to know about this dragon show.
Why is the dragon there?
Is the dragon an enemy?
Is the dragon a friend?
Does Elvira have to slaughter the dragon?
Oh the dragon's, come on, the dragon's a friend.
Yeah, that's true.
It's a monster situation.
It's probably a pet.
One more thing really quick.
And this is, I want to see if we all agree.
I labeled this Knott's earnest song and I think you'll agree this is a good title.
And I'm curious if this sums up everybody's feelings about the place of which we're all
pretty fond at this point.
But boy this song goes for it.
This is from some documentary from 1984.
I couldn't believe the heartfelt nature of this song about this theme park.
But I think we might, I don't know, it might sum it all up for us.
Can we play this, Brett?
You and I must try.
Start up a new life somewhere.
I'm watching parachute footage.
To be a part of the land and sky.
If we're worn out, broke down, tired and hungry, fighting ourselves, and a love for the country.
Not very far.
Then just a slow shot of a bunch of berries barely lit.
Jason, are you okay?
Jason's not going to be here.
He's going to get too riled up here seeing those berries.
This little part.
No mistakes, no regrets.
Together we can make it all the way.
This is the most emotional song.
I love it.
That is a Scott Garner song.
I feel like that has enough chord changes.
The chord changes are like your chord changes that you like.
There are a little bit unexpected.
And there's a lot of them.
Synthy noodling.
I was trying to place what that is musically, and I think it's somebody trying to place
a song on a Wings album.
I don't think they accepted it, so you had to rewrite the lyrics and make it about Knott's
Berry Farm.
Is there somebody kind of carpenter-sy about it?
I'm a huge carpenter.
The earnestness of it.
I mean, at this point, that song is how I feel about it.
If that didn't exist, you would have willed it.
That harmony blast is crazy.
Your sheer force of will would have made that reality.
If that song didn't exist, it would have just come.
If I could use AI for good, I would use it to create that.
Maybe I did somehow without knowing it.
And then that whole, no mistakes, no regrets.
It sounds like she's trying to get someone to have sex with her at Knott's Berry Farm.
Maybe so.
Look, there's this parachute ride, and we got about, there's nothing in the way.
No harnesses, no mistakes, no regrets.
We can get up there, have sex really fast, and then drop and have a great experience.
Or it's more innocent than she just wants to split a pie with someone.
Because there's that long shot of the pie.
Oh, that close-up.
It looked very gruesome.
It looked like innards.
Yes, it was not the most appetizing.
That's a pile of organs for a really intense surgery.
But that looked good 50 years ago.
That pie looked good.
There's another part, we're not long after it, there's just a shot of a dark vat, just kind of a dark purple vat
spinning around as the lyrics are like,
We can climb to the sky, anything is possible.
There's another one about, we can build a home by a model tee.
Start a new life, erase the old one, begin again.
Were they trying to build a Celebration Florida, but just for living in Knott's Berry Farm?
If so, I'm in.
I'm totally in.
Do they have enough land to create a little, or can they?
They've got some kind of dirt lot where they do overflow parking.
If you build into the parking lot, you can make a way.
If that rockin' bruise in Buena Park ever goes out of business, that's a nice plot of land pretty close.
How could it?
Well, you're right.
The sound business plan provided by Gene Simmons.
Sure.
No, it's unlikely.
But that carousel footage, Rachel, earlier you were talking about memories of these places and they feeling dreamlike.
That carousel footage seemed very dreamlike to me.
Seemed very like a child's memory, kind of an askew angle and you're kind of half remembering it.
It's not totally in focus.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
It seemed like it was trying to hypnotize us so that she could cook us and eat us.
I mean, that's always on the table.
Look, after that song, I would have done whatever she wanted.
Whatever is happening, I'm bored.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah, a thousand percent.
Yeah, that music, that good, yeah.
If she wants to kiss me, fine.
If she wants to cook me, fine.
Either way is fine.
Kiss me or cook me either way I'm yours.
Let's go on the soapbox race.
Start a new life there.
Might die to whatever.
All on the table.
I go with it.
It's the last decade where you could like burn your ID and then drive east or west until you ran out of gas and start a new life.
I live here now.
Yeah.
Well, if that journey took you to Buena Park, then you're set.
Anything closing, Rachel?
The warm and fuzzy feeling, I assume it applies from your Knotts-laden childhood?
Oh, I'm literally going to go on Etsy right after this and look for a bunch of vintage Knotts t-shirts to buy.
Sure.
Beautiful, wonderful, great.
Glad to get you into that state.
Rachel Bloom, You Survive podcast, The Ride.
Thank you so much for joining us again.
A great pile of stuff to get into.
Exit through the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug?
No.
I mean, I'm doing a live show, so check my Instagram to see if it's in your city.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
Oh, you're touring.
Oh, wonderful.
Yeah, a little bit, yeah.
Oh, geez.
Great, great.
Are you in Muppets, man?
I'm on, I'm literally in three seconds of that.
Oh, okay.
Oh, well, they're so, okay.
Well, good.
Look for the three seconds.
Hey, and thanks for everything on The Writer's Strike, too.
Thanks for being outspoken about this stuff.
I watched the panel you did for the rap with Kate Cannon and other people, and just thanks
for being outspoken about these things because they're important.
My pleasure, yeah.
And it's also like, I don't know where we're at with shouting out things because there's
been a general lack of talking about, okay, well, how do we make the studios hurt the
most?
Where's the line?
So it's confusing.
Yes, yeah, yeah, very much so.
But as you talk about bizarre situations for writers that everybody finds themselves in,
it makes everybody feel less crazy, I think, to pull these stories and share.
Oh, good.
I'm happy to help.
Yeah, I mean, the negotiating committee members can speak on it so much better.
But yeah, it's a while done.
Yeah, yeah, no kidding.
Well, happy strike to you.
Happy rest of the strike.
Yes, happy strike.
Happy strike.
And hey, as for us, thanks, Reddit, forever, dog, for producing the episode.
You can find us on the socials at podcast the right, merch in our T public store.
But go buy some Knot stuff instead.
We'd all like to see that logo.
Very thorough store website, Knotts Berry Farm.
Like right now, currently, the marketplace has a store.
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Good for them.
Check out podcast the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three,
where we talked about Berry Tales a while back.
That's a fun companion to this.
You will find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride.
Knotts Berry Farm.
Do anything you want me to do.
Swallow me up.
I am yours.
Beautiful.
Yeah.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe
Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.
Thanks for watching.