5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
May the third be with you.
It's the Star Wars-esque day here on Pod gets the Ride.
The second gate. I of course am Ben Scott Gerdneros.
You got it. Joined by Michael Carl Rissian.
I like that, that's good.
And, okay. Alright, I'm just gonna try it.
And of course, Jace Sheridindoo.
Oh, Mace Windu.
I was like, should it just be Jace Windu?
But then there's not enough of the real name. I don't think.
I don't know. Look, these are up for grabs. The Supremacist is new.
We've only ever done the Halloween names. But why not?
We're sort of making a tradition. I think we've loosely done May the fourth week episodes.
Star Wars names seems like... So if you got a better one, or you give me one down the road, Jason, we'll make sure you're hooked up.
I gotta look at the list of the Podracer names.
Do you want me to list them? For the first time in my life.
Yeah, yeah, go for it.
So Bulba, Juan Sandage, Team Toppa Galeys.
Jason Sandage? I don't know if I like that many better.
Yeah, no.
Something was weird about yours. But Jace I thought worked fine.
Yeah, there's gotta be... Yeah, whatever. We'll figure it out.
Look, we're workshopping. But I think that's it. Look, I think we can keep doing that every year too.
Yeah.
Assuming that there are any more. They just might have to get a lot more tortured. And we're okay with that.
But I like that we've been doing these little Star Wars things. And I think it's perfect here today because it brought us to the...
I think maybe one of the key pieces of Star Wars mythos, the 12 minute Donnie and Marie Star Wars sketch.
Yes.
We're so on topic.
Right. This is one of the most famous ones. All seriousness, I feel like this deserves more attention versus the holiday special.
Which definitely has the crown of Star Wars crap of this era.
But this is a stalwart piece of Star Wars crap, certainly. And I was less so... I maybe had seen this once a long time ago.
Yeah, but this is... I almost think maybe... There's an argument to be made that this is better Star Wars crap than the holiday special?
I think, well, there's... You know what? The brevity, I think, helps. I think that it packs it all in.
It feels a little more on brand, oddly.
Yes, it does.
Despite not having the full actual cast. Only some of the actual cast.
Some of the actual cast.
Which is pretty impressive.
This is Lucasfilm approved, I saw.
Wow.
And that's why they were able to get real R2-D2 and C-3PO in there. They don't look cheap.
This is completely the suits, yes. For a show that you know would do crappy suits. Of course they would.
But then you see real C-3PO and R2-D2 come out.
Yes.
You know, to that end, this happened before the holiday special. I think at least a year before. This is in the year of Star Wars.
Right.
Star Wars is at the top of the summer and this is at the end, September of 77. This is way before the Muppet Show with Mark Hamill.
Which is probably the most legitimate end of Star Wars variety.
Yes.
Which is an area that if you can imagine we're all interested in.
So it's a little low-key important, I think. I think I'm with you on your premise completely, Mike.
Yeah, and it is also like I was just looking into it and like George Lucas, like it was a request perhaps.
I can't tell if Donnie's making this up or not because Donnie talking about this because like Donnie hosted like a Force Awakens screening when it came back because he's such a big Star Wars fan and he feels like they're a part of it.
Because they were one of the first big places to promote essentially Star Wars.
He claims he was like asked by George Lucas to do it because they had a big like audience of kids.
Oh.
Yeah, that is true.
That he was asked or they were kids.
Well, no, that they had a very big like young audience. I read a thing about that Donnie Marie show of like when it was confirmed that Donnie was dating someone officially there was like a steep drop off.
Oh, of course.
Of young women watching.
That's the famous thing where you pretend like when Homer becomes a star and the B-sharps and his manager tells him he has to pretend he's single because women want to have sex with you.
We want them to think they can and he explains it to Marge and she's upset.
Yeah.
So, and yeah.
Now I feel like now we I feel like the culture is different.
Now I think we stan our relationships.
Yeah.
I think we we make our fan cams and we we celebrate and I mean me I make fan cams of all of my favorite celeb you couples.
Uh huh.
I made so many of Taylor Swift and that guy I need not say.
I won't say his name anymore in fact being that he's out of the picture.
You moved on to Chalamet and Kardashian though.
That's your new fan.
Is that one real?
Yes.
What? Is it really?
A Kardashian. I forget which Kardashian.
Could be any of them.
Yeah.
Okay. Well we need to figure out who it is because so Scott gets more invested.
Is it Kim?
I don't know.
I know the names of the Kardashians but I'm not sure which ones are dating who.
Meanwhile who's next for Pete Davidson?
Marie Osmond?
This guy dates everybody in Hollywood and next Utah.
Could be.
Oh God.
He's dating the big asteroid worm from Empire Strikes Back.
Typical.
We saw her at the Knicks game with him.
Sorry it's Kylie Jenner and Timothée Chalamet.
Okay.
That's sure good.
Alright.
Well a scoop from our gossip correspondent.
That's right.
Cub reporter.
Cub reporter specializing in gossip.
I have on some like email spamming thing.
I got signed up for the Elite Daily newsletter and it's terrible and I have not unsubscribed.
Because I like seeing which of my zodiac symbols or which Coachella act or whatever.
I think yeah.
It seems like you love it.
Seems like you love it.
You keep giving us this Elite Daily scoop.
Sure.
You parlay this into an Elite Daily shop.
Immediately sued by Elite Daily.
But then offered $50 an article right.
Something could go up to $52.
So we're talking about this is potentially the first Star Wars sketch on television right?
Couldn't it be?
And an official one.
I don't think Saturday Night Live had covered this.
Saturday Night Live is very new at this point.
This is probably the first thing ever with song and dance and accurate Star Wars costumes.
Yeah.
So yeah.
Watching it now it's like we've seen this so many times but this was fresh and innovative.
Yeah.
I think that's probably what everyone watching Donnie and Marie every week was thinking.
This show is fresh and innovative.
Should we take a second and explain what I sent you guys a couple days ago about the show itself.
Donnie and Marie.
Yeah.
I think on the Sid and Marty Croft Facebook they explain.
Listeners you're probably checking this already.
You're probably already on the Croft group.
Well I of course follow Sid Croft on Instagram.
He's like 92 or 93 years old and he does Instagram Lives and he did one with David Copperfield a few days ago.
Insane.
Blue 32 discussed between them?
Talked about Blue 32 a little bit.
Wow.
Sid loves Blue 32.
He's going to go out there and see the show again.
He was explaining it to David.
David is kind of goofing on him the whole time a little bit which is kind of funny.
Seems snarky.
A little snarky to this guy but obviously David loves him because Sid has all the stories about opening up for Judy Garland and the old days and Judy saw me do my puppets and she loved it.
We opened up at the Sands or whatever in Vegas and David loves those stories of course and then David showed off his puppet collection which is epic.
That's the only way to say it.
I know.
I heard about that in Elite Daily.
David Copperfield shows Sid Croft epic puppet collection and 100 people were watching this video by the way and I'm one of them.
You are one of them.
It does not at all look like Batman's Batcave of the stuff he's taken from all his adversaries.
Yes it does look like.
Oh yeah the last piece of information from that is that David explained that he just completed on one of his islands the Cave of Wishes.
Whoa.
And he doesn't get into what that means.
He just explains that they have 11 islands and that you can go there and we're told of course one of them being Mushikei which we've talked about on the show before but that it is some sort of like attraction that you can experience on one of the 11 islands.
He doesn't say which island it is but he says we know we've just completed the Cave of Wishes.
I'm concerned about what some of Sid Croft's wishes might be.
Is there a cap on the kinds of wishes that can be granted in this cave?
I don't know.
Sid Croft's wishes might just be to have a TV show on the air again.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
And I'm concerned that.
A puffin stuff, a girl one that I can kiss.
Well yeah.
I'm concerned that you are going to try to figure out how to get into David Copperfield's Cave of Wishes.
You should be concerned.
So anyway if you don't know we've talked about Sid and Marty Croft made a bunch of shows, Brady Bunch Variety Hour, they produced HR Puffin Stuff, all these I would say visually interesting kids shows.
I would say scary.
I would say most terrifying acid trips of 70s kids television but then also you kind of forget dominated this cheesy 70s variety genre.
In prime time.
As well.
Brady Bunch Variety Hour ultimately Pink Lady and Jeff.
I forgot they were also Pink Lady and Jeff.
One of the most notorious flops in TV history.
Horrible show.
But the beginning of it, this was before there would be no Brady Bunch Variety Hour without this.
David also brought up the theme park, the Sid and Marty Croft theme park as well.
He's like you know it's CNN now and I see the escalator is still there.
And he's like oh yes I went there once on a tour and they exaggerate.
They talk about the park on the tour but they exaggerate some of it.
David goes what are you talking about, what do you mean exaggerate and he goes I don't remember.
And that was the exchange.
Fascinating.
Don't just put this on Instagram.
Get this in a more public forum.
That's right.
So anyway Sid and Marty Croft both still alive.
Both still yeah.
They both are.
Both of them still alive.
Wow.
So yeah they posted this about Donnie Marie.
In 1975 ABC executives Michael Eisner and Fred Silverman approached us about making a Friday night prime time show.
They told us they had two very talented kids and that they wanted to work with but didn't have any idea what to do with them.
So we went off and developed a show concept consisting of ice skaters, musical numbers, comedy skits,
celebrity guests and occasional musical adaptations of famous films such as Star Wars.
This concept would eventually become the Donnie and Marie show.
So our guy Michael Eisner yet again appears.
It's crazy when we're not even looking for him.
We're not looking for him.
Just something is strange on television or we see a clip of it way later.
Boy we got to talk about this and somehow he ends up being involved.
Yes.
Here's two things I want to say and they're two shots called and I know what the year is almost over essentially.
You're half over.
I think shots calling is permanent.
Shots call is permanent.
It could be for next year.
I could call a shot for next year.
You know how in May you're saying the year's pretty much over.
That comment and that comment turn a phrase.
That's true.
Basically Christmas.
Two shots called.
Let me see what's more exciting to call.
I have a guess that one of these I'm not going to like.
There's one that you're going to be upset about.
And I'm going to guess that excitement for both of them is not the first word that comes to anyone's mind.
For us one of them is exciting and for the other one I think Scott's going to be like he's going to roll his eyes.
And I think maybe we said this already years ago when we did the Sid and Marty Croft episode.
I'll start with the one that we're going to agree on I think.
Main feed Michael Eisner episode.
Yeah.
Just we got to have to find a way to present it where nobody thinks that it's the interview because I don't want to see a wave of people going oh I know it's not.
We're going to put in the title not an interview with him.
I'll reveal to you I sent another email to try to get him at our live show and it did not get no one responded.
The one that's coming up.
Yeah.
This week as people are hearing this.
I just sent a cold email again being like hey we're doing a live show.
Well wait.
All right.
Spoiler audience.
Not Michael Eisner.
Wait you sent it really?
Yeah.
And just said like will you come be in it?
Well I did a whole I explained you know we were the guys that hello.
It's our account that has the hello because that's what got a response one time when we got the no to be on the show.
And then I said you know I think I made a big I made it like an emotional plea essentially like I think Michael doesn't understand that the love that Disney fans have for him the nostalgia.
And I think we think it would be really fun for him to experience that live because he doesn't get to do that.
And we want to I didn't say well throw the softest ball questions at him.
But essentially I did.
So I made a little plea there and I was like you know it's a cool place.
I said like it's a cool place too.
Oh that'll help.
Yeah.
Would you like to leave the biggest compound in the history of Malibu and head down to MacArthur Park.
That's right.
We'll hey we'll get somebody to park the car for you.
Yeah.
We'll get a buddy.
You don't even have to worry about that.
Well Jason will park Michael Eisner's car for him.
There is a garage right around the corner and it has the most unhinged handwritten how to pay for parking sign you've ever seen.
See that Michael.
You gotta see it.
So I'll keep sending emails periodically just you know what.
That's how this happens.
You know you got to be a tenacious.
Jason knows he's a cub reporter.
You gotta be tenacious sometimes.
Those who dare when you know.
So send it.
Sometimes.
So yes you're right.
We have to make sure people know this is not an interview with the man.
This is just we're looking through the whole career.
Yeah.
Well if you know and if we do that we can talk about because I was curious if there was any mention of Donnie and Marie in his book work in progress and there is not.
But he does refer to the first thing he ever produced for ABC as an ABC executive which was that he got he flew to Pebble Beach and got Bing Crosby to serve as the host of a special edition of the ABC.
The host of a special about Marine World and then all right what do we need now I need the hottest musical sensation of right now the young rascals and their song Groovin and the special is called feeling groovy at Marine World.
Wow.
First thing Michael Eisner ever produced for television was a theme park special.
Yeah.
He like settled in this genre.
That's where he started.
Marine.
It had a water skiing elephant in it.
It's not on YouTube though so if anybody can find some odd way to I would love to review feeling groovy.
We're all going to have to we're going to have to have to head to the Paley Center and like we're going to go through the archives.
Yeah.
Be handed the dustiest VHS or beta tape you've ever seen.
That's a three hour episode I think.
That's gotta be.
Yeah.
I think Marine World is kind of like the Van Nuys bush gardens or two lesser extent.
What is it?
Geauga Lake Geauga Lake where it's just like gone totally gone.
Why does face the earth at this point.
But you know there's people out there it's like that was their Disneyland and now it just belongs to the dustbin of history is Marine World.
There's one there's a place called Marine World Africa USA that is up north that I would love to cover because the name is so insane.
But then is this me in the Marine World in is this the one that's like now Trump is a Tory Orange County.
Yeah or not even there like Rancho Palos Verdes kind of oh I don't I don't actually know I think or it's near like where Trump owns a bunch of golf land.
Yeah I think it's one of it's just one of those things where it's like it's very recent history but we I don't know like it's like how there used to be a much more elaborate pier theme park in Santa Monica.
Oh both.
I think both.
Yeah.
The also Marine World has this there's some like there's some special where the Munsters visit to know we got we got Marine World we got separately feeling groovy of Marine World separately Michael Eisner and separately your other idea.
Do you have a guess what it is.
No.
No I'm worried.
What is it.
It's a Sid and Marty Croft thing.
In 1962 they were asked by Six Flags to become the creative heads of the amusement park.
I don't know if we've gone over this before.
No.
And what this meant.
Six Flags was around then.
Yes.
This was shocking to me so I was like Six Flags okay we got to do it.
But what that really meant is moving in their adult puppet show Les Poupées de Paris the first adults only puppet show featuring naked marionettes.
Oh no.
Yeah.
This is why I'm worried about them in the cave.
You should be worried because there's naked marionettes in this and this is what they were doing before.
So this was at many Six Flags across the country this show this naked marionette puppet show.
In the 60s.
That's what this says.
So we got we have to do it.
It's like hair.
We have to do Les Poupées de Paris.
This was the counterculture and Sid and Marty Croft and their naked puppets were at the forefront.
Right.
So we got to do it.
Anytime I hear like adult puppet show look it's very talented puppeteers out there it's very specific field.
But I can't help but thinking about being John Malkovich.
Like John Cusacks like stressed kind of sad puppeteer character.
Sure.
Well there's a lot of adult puppet shows I feel like now.
So maybe you just need to get more acquainted with Terry Fader Jeff Dunham and other other.
Well see we got into this and our text with Eva those are ventriloquists.
Oh yeah.
You're right.
I think puppetry and ventriloquism are different.
So like Puppet Up which is the Henson dirty puppet show at Knotts.
That's puppets.
That is puppets.
Yeah.
So I think the other voices they're hidden.
They're hidden.
Also it's got puppet in the name so I think you got to give it the benefit of the doubt.
Right.
And is puppetry of the penis puppets.
It's about to say no.
That is puppetry of the penis.
It's just using a penis as a puppet.
It's putting the penis into different shapes.
Yes.
OK.
So we will do puppetry of the penis too on the second gate.
I'm calling that shot and we will.
Yeah.
I mean we'll do it.
Sure.
With our penises.
It's going to be a weird one to listen to but we will try our best to describe all of
the different myriad of shapes that we can tort our penis and testicles into.
Well it's theater of the mind.
Theater of the mind.
As they call it.
So yeah that makes sense.
So yeah anyway that's up top here just because of.
Six Flags Dirty Puppet Show.
Yeah and looking into Donnie and Marie in general.
Eisner comes up.
Siddharth and Marty Croft in their dirty puppet show at Six Flags comes up and we got to do
it.
Well this this might explain why they were maybe on some level at odds with this production
because it's funny that they got their start with these naked puppets seemingly.
Yeah.
But then here they are producing I feel like the epitome of squeaky clean just like the
most if you were to use a negative word maybe toothless.
Oh kind of you know just like the most like the blandest entertainment I feel like is
the Stoney, Marisha and the Osmonds in general.
Yeah.
Who related also really I like I didn't realize got their start in general at Disneyland.
They're just they're brothers in the park harmonizing with the dapper Dan's.
Right.
Unpaid just for fun I guess.
And somebody a Disney entertainment person saw them.
Who are these wholesome fellas?
I think no Donnie at that point.
I think that I think I saw the older brothers.
This is exactly the Jackson five scenario.
Right.
In the younger one younger ones I guess both really shoot past the right main older brother
lineup.
But the Jackson's end up like on the full version of the show where we were with the
Star Wars.
There's a full like hour long.
Yeah.
And then it's yeah I watched two and there's 12 minutes or so of the Star Wars but they
do bring on the Osmonds sort of as an afterthought the other older brothers and I will say I
don't know the names of the Osmonds like I know the names of the Jackson's.
I don't I some of them kind of little ugly.
Wow.
What a take.
I just I just yeah the toothless most boring guys doing a disco number and it's just like.
And they're not lookers either.
I don't know because Donnie well that I'm I'm not saying that so much for me so much as
Donnie and Marie always had fan base of like oh they're lookers you know.
You're saying compared to their brother and sister.
Famous.
Yeah.
I mean it makes it look there was an era in entertainment where our singers were all
like 50 year old just right kind of unremarkable looking men.
Sure.
And I think the Osmonds were I actually I cannot picture these Osmonds you're talking
about I mercifully did not watch the entire hour but I that just might be the case.
I like that they're just kind of I could see they're just they're just guys.
I'm a man.
It is very much like that especially when it's like Donnie and Marie and a younger young
Chris Christopherson a young compared to now.
I don't know that he was ever looked young but he was kind of handsome and had a big
hair and a big beard and stuff.
You know these four brothers.
He does.
For sex appeal.
He does a scan like kind of like a bit with Marie where they're like asking each other
for autographs and then they do a song and it's a little it's a little like you know
their foreheads are leaning on against each other which is very funny because they had
just cut to Chris Christopherson's wife and daughter in the audience.
Oh no.
Your family is what I certainly hope this is just for entertainment.
I don't get any.
Marie is very young here too.
I believe he was around when it started.
I saw he was 18.
She was 16.
Yeah.
Chris Christopherson.
Yes.
They said been going for a little while.
I think by the time they did the Star Wars one.
Yeah.
But early 75 or 76.
I don't believe had moved to Utah yet because at some point the Osmond machine took over
production and moved it to their facilities in Utah.
Yes.
Kind of fascinating.
They were just they were on the KTLA lot.
Yeah.
Here in L.A. and which I believe is where the Brady Bunch show is also filmed.
And then I feel like it was maybe a twofold decision.
One was just to be closer to the church and so that the church could like because they're
the big Mormon family.
And so like if right if we do this in Utah then the church can be closer and make sure
that they approve of any foreheads that are touching and suggestively during a song.
But also might have been to get rid of those crops.
I think the crops don't make the move.
And that was a way to like well this is done now by Osmond Enterprises.
Who would want to get away from these two guys?
What could possibly make you not want to.
I mean let's say you know in theory you were a person who's been on this podcast who has
interacted with the crops.
What would make them want to not be around the crops as much as possible.
Hypotheticals again.
To me it's all hanging out with the crops is like going to Lidsville.
The famous Lidsville show they did with Charles Nelson Riley where Butch Patrick went to do
a giant hat and went into a magical land where hats talked.
You know that's what I picture it being like kind of a fun party where everybody hangs out.
You want to come to our house and then you go in there and the window talks to you and
the church talks to you and like would you like a drink and then the drink talks to you.
Who wouldn't want to hang out with these guys.
Right.
Perfect time for all.
And then like all right so now that we're all here the talking chair and beer there's a lot of nude
puppets in the basement.
You want to see our nude puppets?
You want to go to the basement and see our nude puppets?
Don't go in the guest room.
Paul Lind is in there.
He's still paying off his ABC contract.
So.
Well now I'm going.
Paul Lind is alive.
It will go anywhere.
Paul Lind is.
My guy.
That is I saw the reason why Paul Lind was like a regular on this show was because he still had time left or hours left on his ABC contract.
Paul has a sad story which bumps me out.
But here sometimes you watch Paul performing and you can kind of see him not want to be performing and I feel like that's what is the case on the Donnie and Marie Star Wars sketch.
Like he doesn't really have it in here.
There's a little bit.
Well just like the fire might be out.
He's still great.
He still does his job but he seems a little tired.
Yeah.
And maybe the spark is kind of gone.
Scott he gets to do a little more in an earlier sketch in the episode where he is working at the Hollywood unemployment office and Farrah Fawcett comes in.
Marie playing Farrah Fawcett.
Yes.
Oh OK not Farrah Fawcett.
And the game is she is an airhead.
Oh boy.
Yes.
That's kind of it right.
That's the whole thing.
There's a line in this.
Yes.
This dumb airhead.
They kind of there's a Red Fox sketch earlier too about playing pool.
And this had to you got to you probably fell out of your chair because there's a couple of Music Man references in this.
Yeah.
There's a river.
She goes something about River City and playing pool as if it's the got trouble song.
Which is I believe incorrect.
I think they were playing a different kind of pool.
They might have been playing snooker in Music Man.
Oh OK.
Different different thing.
Real quick just to set up all the players involved here.
One another one of our guys is involved and we're talking of course about the Lanch.
Yep.
When it gets to those credits I was immediately like all right what writers we got here.
Who's writing for the court knowing what was around the corner.
There's so many podcasts the ride guys involved here and yeah of course it's the Lanch.
Yeah.
It's always Bruce the Lanch.
If you have a question about a hokey piece of sing and dance and comedy.
Yes.
Writer of course of the full Star Wars holiday special and then he seemingly cut his teeth
writing for this.
Yeah.
He spoke of the Utah move and how it really defanged the show and the show got much worse.
And I believe this this sequence is right before the Utah move.
Uh huh.
It's a little bit.
It's maybe the premiere of season three but it was a little bit into season three that
they make the move so that they can run every sketch passed them because the Mormons were
so invested in the Osmonds as like there these are the main ambassadors to America of the
church.
So they would you know they'd like cancel songs that Bruce talks about that how there
was some like could have been a hit song presented for Marie and then they're like no this is
about a divorce.
No.
Why?
What do you mean?
How?
And then he pitches why doesn't she do don't let the sun go down on me and then delights
in the fact that he instead got Marie Osmond to sing a song with the type with the words
go down on me.
Right.
Bruce yes.
Bruce got his wins.
Yeah.
Subversive.
He did his little twists and turns.
But yes he's he's here too.
He's here too.
Paul Linde is here too.
This is really the fact that I didn't watch the entire thing.
This might speak to that compared to you guys my Paul Linde tolerance might be somewhat
lower.
Really?
You're not a Paul guy.
I cannot say that I am a Paul Linde guy.
Did you like Uncle Arthur on Bewitched?
Did you watch Bewitched?
I cannot tell you that I have strong vibrant memories of this is one I know I'm disappointing
you might.
Herman Munster's doctor on the Munsters?
I didn't know he was Herman Munster's doctor.
Yes he was.
He gets to see very well.
How about Bye Bye Birdie when he's singing about kids today?
Oh he's kids.
He's heads.
Okay.
Yeah.
He was on Broadway too.
That's a good song.
Yeah and he gets to sing here as well.
I am not the Paul Linde expert that Mike is but I could tell that there were some moments
in this some segments in this that were a thing I like from old TV shows people kind
of barely getting the lines laughing through sketches.
Which is funny because I love that.
I love like Bob Newhart and Dean Martin doing that or Red Fox popping into the Osmond show
but like in modern sketch comedy I hate people breaking or getting stuff fucked up.
But I love it.
You and Lauren have a lot in common.
Me and Lauren.
Yeah.
Okay let's get do by the when you get the draft on you don't start improvising you got
I think Marie at some point they're doing this pool sketch.
Have you given that lesson to you?
You were doing a little like that's that's the thing that that's the thing that personally
bothers me.
Red Fox and Marie just says during one of the she's like oh that was my line.
Yes during one of they just let's in there.
Well this is one of that like I'm always curious because I okay this is something I think about
the hokey end of Disney variety specials especially because like all the Disney world specials
and anything that Disney's producing in the 70s and early 80s are like Donnie and Marie.
It is still like this thing as like it's the ice angels and then it's always like whatever
we can think of to have like a hundred people in red white blue uniforms and like big puffy
skirts and like I'm always watching stuff like this and thinking this is the late 70s
early 80s is when like all my favorite music comes from this is like such a countercultural
time punk is happening and then yeah this and I was like September 77 when this is
ever 23rd 77 when this airs like what else is going on the next day the very next night
after this airs is the season three premiere of Saturday Night Live like the much cooler
end of like the show that is blowing up this kind of thing Steve Martin hosts musical guest
Jackson Brown first appearance of wild and crazy guys like the molten core of when SNL
was cool and countercultural is happening literally a day after like hey Princess Leia
we gotta go back gotta get you back on the jet plane and then and then the other pop
cultural like contrast that I like a lot the literal day the day that this airs is
the day of the release of Steely Dan's Asia possibly my favorite album in the world a
timeless piece of music to me I feel at least one of my top ten for sure like you could for
the first time hear Deacon Blues this this day yeah and then go home and watch this some a song
where they go chew baka baka baka yeah I've said this on the Oscar like there's this 70s 80s period
were of like changing tastes where there was still old stuff happening simultaneously like
on TV is fascinating because like Liberace being on the Oscars in the 80s feels weird to me yeah
but isn't it like wait no that was earlier 80s I was like is he singing songs about Oliver Stone
movies not quite that but fire and on Golden Pond yeah the movies are a little more like those
fitted but this is post like Scorsese like movies have gotten prettier and crazier with that so
Liberace this is what this is the culture they were countered to yeah yeah yeah and you forget
these things were like right next door to each other around yeah and and by the way anybody any
Steely Dan fam listening this that what I just said is not the only crossover between Donnie
and Marie and the Dan check this out
like I bought that Warren and the brightest orange laser suits you can imagine
and then I'm just gonna leave it playing through the introduction of the guests
did
did Donald Fagan feel like throwing himself off a balcony when he saw it if he saw this or was
he just happy to get a check yeah it depends on how many zeros were at the end of that check
yes I bet they found a way to make it not very many that is true yeah I don't look I have no
room to talk on this we just watched a movie called the Siegfeld Follies this is not a movie
about the Siegfeld Follies this was made in 1945 and it's all the MGM contract stars making a
movie in the style of Siegfeld Follies so unconnected sketches and elaborates musical
presented a premise as if I understand what Siegfeld Follies is you got to go all the way
back to the early 1900s and they were the first Broadway shows okay and got to go back you've
got to go back all right I will this is like showgirl Lucy Lucy is in this and so is William
Frawley doing a sketch with Fanny Brice who I didn't know was still alive sign me up Fanny
Brice and Hume Cronin my man sign me up Hume Cronin I'm the fucking there you're there more
of Mike's guy Lucy does show up in this clip at the end if you know what I'm talking about
so yes so so they do a full show it sets up this 12-minute show stopping number at the end the
first Star Wars parody of all time yeah just four months after the release of New Hope yes still
fresh in people's minds and they do and and speaking of I guess the right guys they do the
of course famous opening crawl there's some jokes in there about the Empire like being a threat to
cleanliness thrift and good dental hygiene and there's a little polite way patriotism patriotism
real beliefs right you get patriotism's now the person who does this crawl narration also does
Darth Vader's voice not James Earl Jones it's one of the Scott's specifically even guys thorough
Ravens are all Ravens I was delighted I by the time we made it to this and like well we got an
episode here right yet another incredible iteration of my favorite voice of all time the most insane
engaging deep voice open the fantasy the way he's been he's in this and he gets to be Darth Vader
yeah it makes all the sense in the world the tiger is Darth Vader yeah yeah right and he does a good
job like a first animal like is that that's not him no yeah it's a bit of a it's a softer Vader yes
you know I'm the power of my force you could tell he doesn't have that I'm not sure that he saw
Star Wars I think I like about anything like this we're like you can tell people are some people
involved are getting caught up really quick with like yeah it's kind of no it's like a it's a Buck
Rogers flash Gordon and this guy's like a pilot and this guy's rad and so so what they would they
would say my force so definitely yeah everybody would for sure like well not if I can get you first
with my force perfect yes you sound like Lucas you could have ridden the thing yeah Vader at the end
of the sketch kind of does like a poochie like I have to go now my planet needs like he kind of
kind of gets just walks off he got just leaves the whole thing doesn't make too much sense no it
doesn't it is an original Star Wars story before Mandalorian this is a for TV only right really the
first non cinematic Star Wars story so slow so let's let's set the story right so Donnie and
Marie come out and they are dressed they are they are Luke and Leia and again well after some footage
of just kind of realistic clinical solar flare yes and there's gonna be more realistic footage to
come as well that don't blend that does not blend in well for the universe of Star Wars but
they come on this is just gonna give you a vibe of like what we're talking about entertainment wise
so there you go that's that's the vibe of this this whole yeah Darth is gonna get us watch out
for Darth again one of those my foot the Darth and his force lost in space all the Star Wars
characters always saying they're lost in space that other reference we know we gotta go on a
Star Trek to prevent more Star Wars a vague understanding of what the movie is about is
really really good I wonder if Bruce had seen them Bruce maybe it's in the movie maybe he's
the expert I imagine that in this writers room he's the youngest gun that's probably right that's
probably right oh sure you're one of their kids how many of the rowdy of the writers coughed to
death during the production of this number Pauline kind of had the vibe right for an imperial officer
for a second he had the hands behind that he was looking stern he had his hands behind his back
yeah I think he could have been in the movies I actually think you are right that he could have
played an imperial officer yeah why not he looks like the one that gets choked out by
Vader for sure the officer yeah yeah but yeah yeah so so that happens they come on this is
insane but I'm letting it pass but you just you two just both said yes Pauline could have been in
Star Wars moving on bigger career he got pigeonholed is the guy who like shakes his waggles his head and
I think he got stuck doing that but he wasn't you where's the proof that he's has other moves in my
heart the proof is in I be at our movies he's done it in Star Wars it's not fair even get he was
typecast I'm saying more that a lot of those imperial officers are choked out after two or
three lines and just kind of come on and say something sort of dry or sort of stern besides
grandma Tarkin wait I get choked out in this while I'm in sign me up my safe word is force
so so yeah so they come on they do Barry Manilow song writers to the stars I like I like that song
actually yeah not this version necessarily yeah but a lot of the songs are just they do in the
shower just the songs this has at least a few words changed yeah to be Star Wars with some of
it it's just like there's doing this song well cuz later stormtroopers come out dancing which I
loved I love the dancing yeah sure I mean they're and then they get ready they do the song the
temptation song get ready yes so they come out and this is also the precursor people try to
claim online that this is this gave Lucas the idea to make Luke and Leia brother and sister
eventually in the third movie because of course Luke and Leia in the first movie like Leia kisses
Luke or no that she kisses him in the second and Empire Strikes Back but it seemed like they were
at Dustin for some sort of romance in the first movie maybe mm-hmm but George denies this George
denies that the Donnie Murray special gave him the idea to make Luke and Leia brother and sister
wonder if any variety shows impacted how they handled the the Disney ones where there's like
seeds of romance here and there between different characters and then in the end they are confused
and don't know what the fuck to do about any of it I wonder how that make a bad idea that's a good
point I see a little bit of a spark here well actually shit run I don't know Chewie's dead
no he's not they should there any variety shows where they just came out and announced things
that could happen and then none of them did happen it's the episode 9 was inspired by like
a music festival where the stage collapsed yeah hey that's great in the weirdest places I like
when in night in 1977 the real suits of C3PO and R2D2 walk out to no applause no applause no
should we anyone excited about this now what are they what are these tin cans red Fox also
when he appears doesn't really get an applause break I guess cuz he was in a sketch earlier
but also I did read that Donnie and Marie a lot of those musical numbers are lip-synced live well
that's this there's an odd thing where it's like I can't tell if it's all being done live
because some like Anthony Daniels is doing C3PO he seems like they almost like dubbed his lines
in yeah there's a weird quality of quality to it and the same thing with red Fox red Fox is and
like what's the do you catch what is fake Obi-Wan Kenobi name that's impossible trying to find what
was or trying to hear it and it's really hard it's muffled it's either okie-pinnockie or something
like that okie-finnockie which is a real place or river maybe it's that yeah but he appears sort
of is just an image above them he's not actually live on stage and that feels completely disjointed
disconnected from what they're doing well in that in the real and in the years moment I just played
when Donnie says hi welcome to our show that's lip-synced the dialogue is so they might be like
a Disney ride pre-show ride video where they just would always screw up the audio and they'd have
to go in and dub it oh sure that red Fox does get a laugh for the line this year Sanford he says
he's from the planet Sanford but he says this year Sanford has no son yes well you left out
the part where there's like four lines between those things and it's the longest walk I know
you're going you said Sanford where to say son say son say son and he said well then moons it no
come on get to it say son yeah I don't know if this was a valanche maybe this is an early
valanche he hadn't figured out how to cut two of the sentences before he got to the punchline
maybe yeah he's just learning the rhythm at this point because he's so he's young here he will by
the time Crystal steps up to the Oscar stage Bruce will get there much like a young Luke looking at
the suns and dreaming of his fate that was Bruce valanche picturing the Oscar do do do do do do do
we sing Billy Crystal's head just feel it to Billy Crystal heads this one is this show is like
Bruce valanche is running through the swamps of Dagobah and he's flipping over stuff oh yeah the
Yoda and his backpack is just like a distant Osmond like uncle or father going like I don't
think we should do that the church won't like it do we really want to have Suzanne Summers on
her mere appearance is scandalous yes I'm Tago bond you're just telling him he's not ready yet
to go right for the Oscars jokes are not ready not prepared you are double entendre is offensive
but Billy needs me he's out there I know he is the his his moment of getting electrified by the
Emperor you know and saying father father help me is when the David Letterman Uma Oprah moment
does land which I think I don't know I think that word plan that makes sense they're both
famous people everyone knew that was called out as anything we have all watched just he just
garbage piles of worse comedy than Uma Oprah since it happened yes insane that people were
mad about yes I'm not saying that moment is elevated we've yes we've consumed so much
worse since like I'm begging for Uma Oprah yeah I also feel like Letterman himself has made that
whole thing like he's he's kind of cast a shadow on it because he also yeah somebody he or somebody
else who were like he got asked back to hosts and he's the one who wants to push the narrative
that he did such a bad job and everyone hated him and then he didn't go back blah blah blah so
I think part of it is also him bragging rights yeah and make yeah he seems cooler than it so
yeah you got Chris Christopherson is Han Solo who I don't know he's not I'm not thrilled with him
his performance here yeah I guess yeah but then now this this is one though not that he's good in
this but like this one this is one where I'm like I feel like there's a world where Chris Christopherson
was Han Solo just in terms of like he's cool yeah yeah just like his prominence I shouldn't
say not throw them he just doesn't have anything that fun to do yeah he doesn't really do anything
but like in a long shot you put him in the Han Solo shirt and vest he's a cool-looking guy like
Chris lean against that doorframe yeah that works that's enough that communicates the idea cool guy
yeah does he do he does a song right yes and I can't I don't know the name of it I found the
names of all the songs well doesn't he do here let me just let me fish around I might not be there
exactly Chewbacca is with him now oh okay yeah yeah yeah yeah I have that ring done and this oh
here's the part that's it they don't say boom shakalaka they say chewbacca so that's one of
the changes you didn't you didn't have the most important piece of that where r2d2 realizes he
can't get up the ramp and so just goes off camera and then they they come back anyway a moment later
because there's a joke about like this is the same planet it's like yeah but the landing was
perfect yeah what is he don't know yeah they say bye and wave and then each day they leave him there
yeah they leave us random on this island which is mainly made up of sparkly stairs yeah say island
or planet planet planet yeah Peter Mayhew is in the Chewbacca outfit Peter Mayhew was there doing
this playing Chewbacca crazy and so also again what you're this this is the first that Anthony
Daniels and Peter Mayhew played the characters again after the movie right unless there's
something I don't know about but this is but before Empire Strikes Back yeah this is the real
sequel to Star Wars Anthony Daniels in his book finally remembers his appearance on the show except
that he thought the lines he was given to say his C3PO were so dreadful that he decided to cut most
of them from the script so he refused to say some of the lines I guess that's what he's claiming
here and then they get they get that back and like oh so mr. robot man doesn't like guard jokes
well let's see where this flash in the pan goes we're gonna prey on that for sure I mean what could
he see he's a sinner in the Lord's eyes for impersonating a human shape and C3PO is an
abomination shall not be in the likeness a robot shall not be in the likeness of a man no art those
are 2d2 he's fine they were disgusted they saw him drinking a cup of hot tea what would be a
valanche joke for the road like a danger Will Robinson or something like what would be the
valanche loose robot joke in 1977 I mean danger Will Robinson is the only robot that was famous
up until then right yeah I don't know like you deserve a gold medal for that landing um please
don't melt me into the gold but that's pretty good Bruce is throwing that one out yeah all right
next let me talk about the Paul in number real quick here Jason did you recognize this song that
Paul sings a few a few of them I did not or I could not place that's okay I just it's a it's
from on a clear day it's from the musical and it's called I don't know the musical okay it's
a song called come back to me I didn't know it either I had to search the lyrics to find it and
they cut to Paul and and he's in I guess a control tower of some kind he's wearing an
Imperial officer outfit he's got the ice princesses walking around in like vague stormtrooper looking
outfits and he's just looking at the like looking at the screen and it's just a picture of a real
like rocket a modern-day rocket old grainy footage yeah and he sings this song
yeah
don't want your notes
of course, what a force can you be?
come back to me
he seems crazy in this so I this is what j i like if you just dial it a little bit in one way
I feel like he does seem like an unhinged imperial officer
which yes, yeah, so
He could be a first order. He could be yeah, he could be any any of these characters. I feel like
Uh with the right direction an irving kirchner
You know has the delicate hand to take paul linds performance and make it fit into the universe
Now you picked him and not george. Are you saying george is unable to direct actors? We know that
Are there moments like with I don't know, uh, hayden christensen where you feel like maybe you didn't know the right thing to say faster more intense
faster more intense
I think that's george's famous direction really let them know that you don't like sand
Yeah, just make sure you communicate that you don't like them. Great job paul. Great job paul faster more intense
Uh, so I guess paul is watching as an imperial officer. This is supposed to be the heroes in that rocket
And that's the best they could do it took me a couple watches to figure that out
That I believe he's watching. Yeah, this is just occurring to me as you're saying. Yeah, he's watching
han luke or in leia in in chewy in the rocket
That the spaceship they just got into it took me forever to figure that out
I go
Why is he watching? Why does he want him to come back and come back to me doesn't really make sense
But I guess the idea is oh they've gotten away from imperial officer paul linds. Yeah, that's the idea there
This is all very thin soup the mechanics of this. I completely agree
But paul lind gets to sing a song from a musical and he really he really does belt it out
Yeah, uh there
and then yeah, and then he's just sort of
Uh with a bunch of the ice princesses who have like helmets and ski goggles on I love these costumes are great
These like more shapely
Female designed stormtrooper. These are good. This is this is an innovative part of the shapelier stormtroopers
Yes
The lady stormtroopers have almost like a heart on their
Chest kind of
Uh, I don't know if that's what it is. I don't think it looks like almost like an upside down star trek symbol
Um, they have shoulder pads their wardrobe these these utah osmond oriented
Hired costume designers. They're sad. I think they figured it out. Yeah, and they're sassier stormtroopers
Um, and then paul and is very upset
Um and darth vader comes in
And yells, I guess we could play a little bit of this. Let's let's hear
thurl's darth
Just a little
No planet all no planet all no planet all it is I darth I'm just going to use some of my force
I like this guy. He's a little I don't know. He's he's sillier. He's cookier
That no planet all on that's a very like
Jokey delivery no planet all no planet all no planet all
Oh
This guy they're the best I also I learned a thing about him. I didn't know also that he was the
Uh for decades. He was the voice of this thing called the pageant of the masters, which is in laguna beach
they have it every summer and
It is a laguna beach in orange county where disneyland is um, and you might know from arrested development
There's this there's this thing it's in an episode of the show where people get together and
Recreate paintings. Oh, yeah using sets and makeup and costume
And that is a real thing that happens in this outdoor amphitheater in orange county and apparently for many decades
The live narrator of it was thurl ray of its trust
Um, and I got interested in this thing because the venue where they have that is where erin and I got married
Oh really?
Holy shit in the grounds of not in the it was not an amphitheater and we did not invite you didn't
3000 people but and you didn't recreate a painting for your wedding? Um,
Just a general tableau of what a wedding would be like, but no no specific wedding from art history
No, like dower photo where you guys are recreating american pastoral like you didn't have a buddy
It's like all right. He's got the ring and you've got the pitchfork. Do not forget that pitchfork
No, no photo reference
Uh, um, oh the only thing well right after we got married though. I did have every there was an announcement made by the dj of
um
Uh, all right. Anyone who is at this wedding who was in the video sex offender shuffle, please proceed to the wedding area
because
Uh an old video of mine if you don't know that one, uh, everyone who's in the video was at my weddings
We were able to do a full cast photo. So there was that there was somebody had the phone out like, okay, wait
I was over here. I was looking mad. Okay, I was being creepy in the
Um, so the the grand cast reunion happened a lot of minutes after here at this place no history
Yes, some involving thorough ravens croft and some not american goth
I was just about to get on your ass
I was done talking and I apologize. It looks very pastoral and that's why I got that's true
I didn't want our listeners furious for jason all the raw
All the filip roth heads going like why is he bringing up american pastoral
He was thinking about a book because jason's the reader of the good jason reese the book guy
He subtly tells us
On me limp mic stand, I know the feeling
Leave it in
His line at one point that I liked was I didn't expect a standing ovation, but what's so funny?
Because they all kind of laugh
At one point all the uh ice angels. Okay. Yeah, right
Um, so yeah at this point, I mean the narrative is now they've been caught I believe
Or they're about to be caught I guess well
They leave the planet and then just come back to the same planet, right?
And they don't change anything about the back so it's not like they went somewhere else
Um, they come back to the planet
And then this is when the sort of more traditional storm troopers
Swarmed the stage in addition to the ice princess. Yes, this I have this moment
You're right side
I do really like the like west side story kind of like group snapping. Yes of the storm troopers
This might be the highlight number. I think so. Yeah that first shot
That's kind of like low angled and then they start bouncing I was like, okay, I like that and then when they get to the chorus
It's just like oh, yeah, I just like this song. This is fun now
Because everyone's menacing
Uh, you know the osmonds and chris christofferson and chewy but no one has any weapons
They're menacing them by like one two three one two three like bouncing towards them. Yes dance intimidation
Yes, there's no blast I don't think yeah, does anybody have a blaster no one has a blaster
No, so lucas did not let them borrow the blasters for this
For some reason I don't know but he did but there were this it is real costumes. Yeah
They arranged chubaca that's too close. Like there's no way
Whatever prop department could put together these yeah, it's the real chubaca real darth vader real storm troopers
It looks like yes some of them they get this so right and then the set's so wrong
Just this this sparkly pink world. I mean, I like the sets, but it's just not star wars. Yeah, it's they
I'll say this
They tease an episode that I did watch and I'll just say it now they do a wizard of oz
12 minute
Show-stopping finale on their next episode that involves lucille ball
And that one feels much more like they put time into it than this one. Yes, they know what it is
Yeah, do they say lucille ball?
No, I can tell you the whole thing. No, not ruth buzzy. It's it's uh, uh ray bulger
Actual cast member playing the scarecrow yet again, except if he looked wrong and bad. That's right
It's lucille ball as the tin woodsman. It is paul williams. Oh williams. That was the horse. Who's great
Yeah, uh, and it is paul lind and they don't say it but paul lind as the wicked witch of the west
Oh, okay, and he's around the thing and yeah, it's so so no, it's not ruth buzzy
But that whole thing it feels like the songs some of those might be originals and if yeah, they knew what that was
More than than some of the old time
Coughing writers knew what this was you must have flipped your shit when they said lucille ball's gonna be in our wizard of oz
I absolutely did. Yes, and then paul was back here paul's back
Yes, and lucille singing with ray bulger and marie osmond. Yes
I wanted I was like fuck this show. I want to talk about the wizard of oz
Put lucy in the star wars lucy in star wars doesn't feel right generation-wise either
It doesn't feel like lucy should have been alive when star wars was out. You think she saw it
Yes
Because she produced start she was involved in the creation of star trek. She didn't create it
But she was it was she you're saying lucy was an avid sci-fi enthusiast the stars. She loved the stars. She loved
She loved the gorn lucy loved the gorn on star trek
I love the gorn gary always hears me talking about the goal. I love gail gordon and I love the gorm
Is what uh paul lind would say about work opportunities here today gorn tomorrow
You could have been that's it that's if he's in a star trek number playing the gorn playing. Yeah
Yes, it showed which might have happened
Also if blanche had to work on some star trek thing and he had to have said he had written that for somebody
That feels like too easy pitching it forever. I pitched it in the 60s. I pitched it for every movie
I pitched it to jj nobody took me up on the slide. That's his great white whale
Is no one using here today gorn tomorrow, right? Well if we ever get on a star trek cruise
Maybe you can say that live on stage and it'll bring the house down
Yeah
Mic drop moment. Yeah, I don't know how we get on a star trek cruise in some capacity of performing but it's possible
You're talking I was gonna say we'll get on it by buying a ticket
But you if we have to perform on it, I think so. Hmm. I think we could do that
You know, I don't think so. So your dream has now become to be a cruise ship performer
On a star trek cruise with all my favorite people over 70. Yes, what are we doing? We're doing the this podcast
I don't know. I don't see why I just thought of so I have to work it out in my head a little bit
We have friends the george lou's talk show did the joe coe cruise, right?
Sure. Yes. Great. So they're our hookup to the cruise community. They're on there
We're in there's comedy shows sometimes on the jericho cruise like I feel like these are one step away
We do know somebody actually who is does a lot of stuff on the star trek cruise
But I don't know it doesn't answer the question what we're doing on it. What is this person going to demand of us?
What do you need? How we need it so bad person? I don't know who it is
I just look I just want to like sip a mai tai with armin shimmerman. That's all I want to do
That's really all this is so the getting you're saying that by guaranteeing that we're the performers on the cruise
It's a free ticket to yeah
And then like because we're just the riff raff armin's not drinking a mai tai with just anybody exactly
Once he sees that we have a performer's pass, then he's going to treat us with that respect fellow
Craftsman hello, please here. I bought two
I had a feeling i'd need be needing to share and then I can share with him the anecdote about wallace shawn's play
And sitting
There is a tale that i've woven podcast after podcast non podcast after podcast
And mr. Shimmerman when you hear it, I think you'll agree. It's one of the finest tales
Maybe it's just podcast the ride presents the story
And we and we you two sit there while I recount the story of going to see wallace shawn's play
And andre gregory directed and sitting behind me there. I was me mike carlson. Yeah
Little did I know I was in for the night of a lifetime
Let me set the stage
Several soft-spoken men are going to see several other soft-spoken men to a soft-spoken performance temptations get ready plays
I was all nervous because I couldn't find the email
What would the box office say if I couldn't show them the ticket email but it turns out they just needed my name and id
Poof got over that hurdle. I wonder if anything else is gonna happen
And then we have armin act out what he said
Oh, wow
That would be a killer thing armin playing himself in the version of the story
Oh, my neck hurts these seats when was the last time they updated these seats?
That's what he said right that was no I can tell you what he said I've said it a few times I've heard it so
Many times yet. I cannot remember what this story is so boring the bartender
What's what did he say?
Okay, it was it was a 17th fucking time. You two don't remember what he said
There was a long play and the first half would be lapping up the story if it was interesting
Jason
Barely pays attention while we do this podcast the first half of the show is 90 minutes and it was very long
It's a long story so by the end of the first day you're like, oh it's kind of a long play
Whatever armin stands up realizes there's a second half to the play
He thinks it's done and he turns to his wife and he goes, oh, I thought the play was over
Well, I guess we'll just see what happens next and then goes to the bathroom
So my joke did have the spirit correct
Yes, it was a very similar but armin was expressing what the whole audience was expressing like oh there's more, huh?
Okay
And he said it all like that and he was very positive about it
But it made me laugh made us laugh just imagining you sitting at the bar talking to him and the bartender sliding over a napkin
Sir, there is a raving man who wrote this is a five-timer at the end of their end of the bar
I don't know what it means. But uh, he said you would
This look it's possible i've been over here
Um, you know you guys have been chatting but since you finished let me come to you
Hat in hand hand in hat. I forget which
Had to say how wrong I was
That story shook me to the bone
I am so glad it's been told again and I can't wait for it to be told again and again and again
Well on the pot we'll get paid for it on the cruise. At least we'll get a free cruise ticket out of it
I
When the listeners add up how many times they've paid for some of the same stories over and over
And they'll figure out what a good deal it's been
The hits, uh, that's just the arman shimmerman chestnuts
There is no amount of money. I will not keep giving them to hear. Yes tales of arman
Weave your arman lore
At the what are they gonna do go to multiplex see the fucking black adam
Turn on netflix watch the russo brothers ai flicks. Yeah, right
They're in the right spot here with the russo brothers new ai
Dreams you can fashion all kinds of stories where arman shimmerman says something quietly to his wife at the beginning of an intermission of a play
You can even you can even mike conjure a version where jason and I remember what happened in the fucking story
And we applaud we
Have fun every time. Yay for mike lift him up above our heads
Uh, uh, it's something we'll figure we're gonna figure this out. I'll force you guys to do this somehow
I don't know how but we'll we'll figure it out somehow
Uh, anyway back to star wars. Well, it sounds like here is an applicable quote what you're almost saying is
I I vow by the power of my force I shall return
I vow they will like the story on the ship
Da I will tell the arman shimmerman story again. I vow to tell it again the story will strike back
The story the story strikes back. That's now that okay
That's the now we have to retire five timers and whenever we retell a story now we say the story struck back
The story strikes back. Ah, the story strikes back. Yeah, scott
Can you just confirm after he says that quote that's when he just like walks off stage left. He took
Yes, yeah darth vader's, uh defeat in this is walking away
Yes, and uh paul lind's defeat is wookie putting wookie putting a kind of firm hand on its one shoulder
For saying it's only turned his lesson wookie pudding
wookie pudding
Uh, uh, I you know what? I'm on such a star trek high after the season of pacard
I just like I don't even care about this show anymore
This episode or not the episode this this to this donnie marie, uh-huh I go star trek's better, you know
Than donnie and marie. No star wars in general. Wait, sorry. Okay. I'm on such a better than star wars
Yeah, yeah, i'm not such a star trek kick right now. Okay. Okay. Yeah, that's in my star trek phase. Mm-hmm
So what has anything happened recently with star wars that would devalue?
Your opinion of it somehow
There's just a lot
Maybe I like some of it. I like some of it
I believe sir. We just discussed vect no crew. That's true. I like that. He has capable
We played by flee. I do but if you were a star trek fan
You right now had a season of star trek pacard where all your old favorites and when I say old favorites, I mean old
Favorites are back together on their spoiler alert old ship
And anyone who likes any of this is like riding a high
It's all anybody wants to talk about if they are the fan of this persuasion
Whoa, so you're saying you can go home again. You're saying it's not true that sometimes things are here today going tomorrow
Wow a red foxesque walk
Even somehow even slower than
Executed yeah, I guess let's finish out though talking about this. Yeah. Yeah, let's get to the end here
Uh, um, so there's a leaving on a jet vader leaves and they sing leaving they sing leaving a jet plane
Basically just the song they don't even really change anything about it. Yeah, that's what I can I understand star wars
It's that movie about jet planes
Yeah, you got it. Yes
Uh for whatever like they couldn't even be bothered to write an original song
Like for this or or like use the star wars theme and put lyrics to it or something
With bill murray's famous saturday night live
Sketch he put lyrics to star wars. They didn't have they they weren't innovating like that. Right?
Um, they they didn't think anyone would recognize the song. We know it's popular songs of the day. That's true
Um, so yeah, there's a big number everyone's on stage
Everyone's celebrating pauline is in is in like he's roped they tie him tie his hands in rope
He's like tighter, please
Is that all you got
If I if I'd known this is where things were heading I would have I would have been a little more bad land ahead
No one did it like pauline by which I mean no one has ever delivered dialogue in that fashion before since
Well, except for ronda santas
Oh, yeah. Yeah, there hasn't been such a good shaking head delivery since the recent ronda santas press interviews. Yes
He's the new king he's the new if he was more pauline desk i'd be in favor yeah
But I just sent this
Paul would send him up if he was still around
And i'm sure bruce too. I mean bruce is around but I don't know
He's not really writing on these type of shows anymore. There hasn't been as of this recording
There hasn't been a de santas on snl and lauren's probably like we need a lind type. Yeah, we don't have a lind. That's true
uh, um, so
anyway, this uh, uh was a special I didn't know I didn't know about it it popped up on instagram and I went well
This feels right up our alley and of course as always all of our characters appear
It's almost as like we make them wish on a piece of like we see some schlocky thing
We make a wish and then like michael eisner appears. We make a wish in a wishing cave in a wishing cave
If you see yeah if you see something on it's like I guess we're drawn to our type of stuff in our guys
and not the guys in the sense of like
Tillman for tita guys our other guys and we still have yet to differentiate between types of guys
But these are also our guys like capital g and lowercase g
Is the capital for the I think is bad. Yeah, so the villains are bad
So bruce and thurl and paul are lowercase g's. Yeah, there are there
You're this is mark marron guys as opposed to these are these are our guys. That's good. Okay, that's a good distinction. Uh,
My question is here. I just just let's let's wind it down. But
one thing that I like about this is that
It like I kind of like that. They just dove in not knowing the mythology
I think it's crazy how people are too strict and serious about mythology of this or anything
If this kind of show was on today
more recent property
How do we do how do we do a musical number?
That paul lind can factor into and play a part in yes. Yes, that's I mean star wars especially right now is yes
There's too much. There's no there's no hoopla. There's no
fun party happening with it
Um versus the gorn on the star trek cruise who's just like an alcoholic party monster
You know, there's that at least and like the lower dex is a show with people we know that are on it
And I actually i've watched a little of it and it's like a weird
They're a little it's a little looser over there in star trek land is what i'm trying to say
Yeah, yeah, they get to have a little more fun. Yes. It is not lower dex in the success of it proof
That if you have a little more fun, it's a little it might pay off just sometimes
That the one that's flashing to me, I mean in terms of a lind part
And like obviously and it's like it's a it's a serious mythology
Uh, it's a very like there are no laughs in avatar
So if there was if there was something on today to do like a very
Avatar
variety kind of song and it's maybe it's then you gotta have lind as
Uh avatar corich
And there's gotta be some well, it's do you have the pitch?
I'll let you do it. Uh, because like he would have his own like kind of reveal moment because if you've seen avatar two
Uh, you know quarich is now and as a navi
So at this point paul wakes up he's blue and he goes i'm blue
Like that's what else you want
Yeah, yeah perfect. Well, I guess you want like I mean this implies that all these people are still alive
But you need like oh well paul williams is spider. Oh my god
I was gonna say paul in his grown-up spider. Oh, no, not grown up. I cut the hair
Let's do high maintenance
Let's do the de-aging thing with like harrison ford in the indiana jolt like let's do that with paul now so he can play
Himself when he was younger as spider still around so he could do it. That's what i'm saying
Yeah, yeah, do it like mark hamill and mandalorian de-aged. Yeah, do that technology
And have paul play his younger self as spider and he's what he sings like you're walking into spider webs
Leave a misagenda call you back. Yes like an old time
Yeah, well his spider is always spinning his webs right villains are getting caught in I think it's great that's great
Yeah, I was still hung up on um
paul linden star wars
Because then I in my head I just started saying thron. I don't know what's wrong with this thron today
About admiral thron the extended universe
Yeah that they're begrudgingly putting in the tv show well not well, so felony's not
This is a whole other conversation. That's the timothy's on he likes it
Yeah, timothy's on wrote these three novels that are kind of some people consider the actual
I haven't read them. I know the stories, but I haven't read them because again i'm not a reader like jason is
um, but
There's three novels that are sort of what happens after the main trilogy and to a lot of people that's you know
Lucas mary damara jade these these other characters that were thrown out when they made the disney sequels
And the main villain of the whole of all three of them are a guy is a guy named grand admiral thron
He's a blue guy and they have I think he's appeared on the mandalorian or boba fat
I think he's been in some of the cartoons some of the three yes, he's for sure been in there
But like he's going to be uh the villain for whatever so jason is imagining paul and singing about him
Grand admiral thron the only you guys can answer this is paul linda thron
Well thron seems scared no
Thrawn seems a little colder paul's a little more bombastic
So so what 70s the people are dying to know what 70s variety show mainstay could be thron. Oh, gregory peck
Did gregory beck do that many varieties I think he was on some I could be wrong
But a lot of the johnny cash. I mean, that's the thing there. Yeah, they did all do this kind of thing
They were all on stuff. Um
So, yeah, there's a lot yes if if we were doing extended universe stuff vincent price
Yeah, great price is good, but it would be funny to see paul linden the big white officer outfit and the blue face paint
Yeah, well
Would be a joy to see him doing anything. Yeah, quite frankly. Um, so
Yeah, I was I have this is one of those things where I have to say something that I don't want to open up
I just have to say it get out of my head because I was just reading about it
Are you breaking up with us or something? What's going on? I'm so sorry. I'm leaving this podcast to do a star trek podcast
Look, I probably will not make fun of the armin shimmerman story again
I like I can't handle it
My mental health is taking a toll when that story gets mocked because every morning I wake up and think it's a good story
I'm gonna do it again next time one of these days. They're gonna get it. They don't understand. Uh, no, no, uh,
Just we're talking about the thron trilogy. I was reading about the shatner verse
Which is a oh tech war no
But I love tech war and I want to do an episode about tech war eventually
Can I start packing up the gear? Well, you guys go turn your mic off and we can be done with my laptop
William shatter's tech war is another original show that he had which we need to talk about
Uh, it's a future show with no budget about a illegal drug called tech
Everyone is good looking for tech
William shatter is like not the star but the main character is a character named jimmy johnny cardigan
johnny cardigan is like on the like stopping people from dealing tech
And yes, it's not track. It's tech t. E. K
William shatter's tech war. Hey, i'm really sorry about this
And there's so much
I gotta find a moment to distance myself from mike here. This is what I want to talk about but tech war there's many shows graphic novels books
I'm sure william shatter never wrote a word of them, but he is credited as that speaking of william shatter's writing though
However, I do want to talk about you're not done eight or nine novels called the shatter verse that william shatter
Is credited as the writer on where he writes?
Himself his character captain kirk coming back to life after star trek generations
And they call these books the shatter verse and he has a whole nother alternative narrative where captain kirk thrives and has
other adventures past
And there are eight or nine. It's just like him and captain picard going on adventures and he is the writer
I'm sure they're ghost written though, but this is this is like the
Your adventures of still talking about this after we leave the room. Yes, leave the microphones on yes
And yes, I also honestly think I thought I thought mike was down for the count
But then he came back to life and got to talk about the entire shatter. He's talking about a played straight garth
Marengi's dark place
Satin
It is not funny. I think i'm full honestly
I I do have I kind of think a full podcast about william shatter's career
Is sustainable. Oh just an entire what you mean a sat not to say i'm not distancing my say
This is a separate podcast. Yeah. Yeah, but it's probably a good idea. There's so much on there. Yeah. Yeah
No, you're getting into music. I like to work band. It has been I love it
It's gonna be a long long time. Yes
Um, he's got like 12 albums
Wow, this man does not want to die and he is so adamant not to die. He will take anything that is offered
Uh, so anyway, you mean tech well tech to keep himself alive
Wait and and by the way, uh, if if paulin was in a tech war, um variety
Skits yes. Yes. Um, geez, what can what does a guy got to do to get some tech around here?
All right, you survived
If you want to dig even deeper
Join us on our vip patreon tier club three where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free
I believe disneyland smoking area is now officially coming. Yeah club three
uh, so that's on the way and
Um, I think I should end this with the exact line that donnie and marie ended this episode and every episode with apparently which is
May god keep you in his tender care
I hope he does
How tender