Five, four, three, two, one.
Okay, welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
Pull up a seat everybody, I'm Ant Scott.
Let me introduce the kids, there's Jason over there.
Hey, no slouching, no slouching Jason.
Oh, get off my case, Ant Scott.
Well, you're not gonna get dessert
if you would talk back like that.
Yes, I am.
Ah, whoa, I'll kick you out of my kitchen, I don't care.
I should be so lucky.
We, and there's Mike over there.
Hey Mike, elbows off your microphone.
Take the elbows off the mic.
Oh, I wanna put my elbows on a microphone.
It's not polite Mike etiquette, okay?
Oh, what a fiddlesticks.
Now you sit tight and watch Dick Van Dyke.
And you boys, both of you, finish your dry facts
or no riffing, okay?
Oh, look what Rosemarie is up to on this one.
Okay, that counts, that's a dry fact.
You're saying the name of an old ad, that counts.
Okay, that's fine, you're off to a good start.
Okay, let me know if you need anything else.
Hey guys, we're talking about the 50s
primetime cafe where that's an amended sample
of the kind of thing you might hear.
I think I haven't been myself.
Yes. We'll get into this.
Oh, here you go, take the ball and run.
Well, I was just gonna say, I went when I was little
and I have no memory of it.
But yeah, I'll just say this.
I think it's good we're doing this
and we haven't just reviewed it.
I found that, because I know people will probably say,
oh, they should have gone to it and they should have reviewed
it, I don't think so, because I think we need to do
a pre talk before, because I do want to eventually go,
when we go back to Disney World, I was like, oh,
I should do this, because then we can talk about it.
Sure, but this is more, look, this is the kind of thing
I think we're allowed to do.
Oh yeah, for sure.
We're not a restaurant review podcast,
we're a themed experience review podcast.
So we can analyze what the experience is
and whether or not we think we'd like it.
And yeah, there's food there, but it's within
a broader umbrella of theme, right?
There we go, get off our backs.
Here's what I wanted to say that I think is important
and maybe this is gonna take us right off the rails.
I'm watching all this, I'm reading this stuff
and I'm like, man, you know what?
This place gives me the creeps.
Really?
Because I think about it pretty warmly.
My family, I checked with my dad, I was like,
we went there, right?
And he's like, yeah, we went on that trip we took
where we took your grandparents to
and we all ate there and they were really tickled by it.
And that was 1991 and we have not been back.
We became a Mama Melrose family
and occasionally sci-fi died in.
We're a Mama Melrose family.
Yeah, everyone liked that and everyone could agree on it.
So, and it's very cold in there.
Oh, and the Orlando sun, it's a little more pleasant
than shoveling down meatloaf and pot roast mashed potatoes
in 100 degree weather.
That might be the case, but we don't know the temperature
and that's one thing we cannot, having not been recently,
it might be plenty cool in there.
We can't rest a judgment.
Well, right, and that's gonna be in whenever we have
a follow-up episode because yeah,
when I say this place gives me the creeps,
I'm like, I would like to experience and see
if it does feel as bad as it looks to me now.
I watched a number of vloggers go
and all of them preface their meal with like,
look, this food isn't amazing,
but it's all right, it's pretty good.
Yeah.
This is, look, I have read opinions all over the map
on this subject.
That might be what I would guess,
but then I've read kind of the opposite.
Let's finish our dry facts before we go much further.
This is a restaurant, it was an opening day restaurant,
I believe, at Disney MGM Studios,
which I will never stop calling it, Hollywood Studios today.
And it's in kind of the like,
it's pretty early as you're entering the park
and kind of like the general studio,
before things get too themed, I feel.
And the general deal with this is,
I guess there's a couple things to say about the theming
and what this experience is
beyond being a restaurant in the park.
It is themed after 1950s kitchens.
So every table that you sit at is a little miniature set
of a 1950s kitchen, and those kind of like,
weave in and out of each other.
Right, yeah.
And every table, maybe not the very small ones,
but at least a table of four has a TV
that is playing a medley of classic moments
from 1950s television.
So we got that much right.
But I would say that the headline aspect of it, to me,
has always been that the server does what I did
at the beginning of the episode.
They are a family member who is nagging you
about your behavior at the table
and whether or not you finished your vegetables
and are using the right fork or whatever.
So it's like, you're back into the 50s,
but also into like the time of the housewife
who's concerned about manners and no desserts
until you finish your veggies and all that.
Does that explain it succinctly?
Yeah.
It's a Disney version of the server yells at you thing.
Yeah, Edna Bebex or Dick Slaster.
Dick Slaster's word, yeah.
Dick Slaster's word, of course,
the famous Dick in his last resort.
Uh-huh.
So you could join the-
The real Bill Dick.
If you eat everything, you get in the clean plate club,
you got a little sticker.
What a club, I know I'd be ashamed I have not joined it.
Yeah.
It sounds like the club 33 of a clean plate club.
Sure, yeah.
But if you're bad, I saw videos
where someone had to go stand in a corner.
Great.
Now let me, okay.
Now that we've said some of these basics
and some of the things that might happen to you
in the restaurant, I might kind of double up
on what you were saying, Mike,
and say that I've never been to this place
and I never had any desire to go to this.
But when I heard about it in like a hotel information video
or whatever's giving you a preview,
the burn bombs guide to the park,
I think I specifically requested not to go to this place.
I, as a child, I hated the idea of an extra mom.
Why would you want that?
Who is a stranger?
I am being double parented right now.
I, and man, I could be, by the way,
I could be terribly wrong.
I might go to this place now and like it, appreciate it.
But as a child, I was like, please no.
Please do not make me do this.
Yeah, well, I think my primary reason
for saying this, Chris, is not necessarily
the interactive element, which I will agree with you
in some ways that it's not always what I'm looking for.
I would say it is not ever what I'm looking for.
Anywhere, there's, you know, you encounter this with like,
you know, the Star Wars, Galaxy's Edge,
they cut a lot of the character interaction
and I'm just quietly like, yeah, too bad they cut that.
I wouldn't want it.
I'm fine, I don't want to do this.
I've had a good time, like maybe once every three years
in something where I have to talk to a character,
but that's about my pace.
It's a little immersive, that terrifying immersive theater
that even took us through that one time.
Yeah, that was interesting.
But I had to take a deep breath
in the moment where it became clear
that there are now characters meandering around this space.
Now that you say this,
we really have to do this all together
because I would like to see what happens
with Jason and Second Mommy.
I would like to see what exactly is unlocked
because I think you would like that.
I think, yeah, I think I'm going in lucky.
I'm a big gravy boy, you know?
I might be a little stinker,
I might be a little wooden boy,
but I'm a big time gravy boy.
You're not a little gravy boy,
you're a big gravy boy. No, not at all means.
I like my food very wet with sauces, not with condensation.
Would you agree with me that you're Mama's little gravy boy?
I'll be Mama's little gravy boy, yeah, sure.
Okay, when you're at Mommy's table,
you'll be whatever Mommy tells you you are.
Sure.
I also, I like the sampler platter they have,
which has like the backstory that it's like,
oh, it's a plate, it's Mom's favorites,
but it's like a plate of leftovers that was in the fridge.
So you get pot roast and meatloaf and fried chicken.
But then when you see the video,
it's like, oh, I thought this would be a task,
but it's like, oh, it's a little
reasonable scoop of everything, you know?
Okay, well yeah, we're not in Mike's zone
of the pre-airport family style.
No, it's not. Thankfully,
they portioned it out.
They were smart.
I think we could go and I think you could get one
of the servers to like quit their, quit her job on site
if you committed to the bit of being her son.
I mean, look, I will, I will.
You show up in like the night before Christmas stocking cap
and like underwear, like butt flap on a nightgown
or whatever.
Oh.
Well.
When she, well, anyway,
there are all restaurants quitting
if they see somebody with a butt flap walking by.
That's too much, you're right.
It's indecent.
But like maybe like propeller hat
and then like striped shirt, big lolly.
Yeah.
And then like little Mickey's little red shorts
kind of a thing.
Well, he's broadcasting.
He comes in, all of this is presenting a challenge.
Then the big lolly is defiant to mommy.
Right, yes.
That he would come in with outside food and outside sweets,
which are gonna get way in the way of his dinner.
Yeah, my mouth's gonna be a mess.
There's gonna be stuff all over.
There's gonna be food in my cheeks.
My cheeks are gonna be too rosy.
They're gonna yell at me
for not putting on enough sunscreen.
Mommy, my cheeks are sticky from sunscreen and sucker.
And now bits of meatloaf are sticking to me.
I'm your little dirty boy today, mommy.
I was gravy boy yesterday, but I am dirty boy today.
And then the woman just like performer
just like breaks character, throws the apron down.
We're done here.
We're done here, I'm done here.
If there's gonna be somewhere else in this goddamn park,
I can work and if not, I'm heading to Universal.
If you recall when we did Delusion.
I recall exactly what you're gonna say.
Yeah, we ran into one of the actors
from the experience afterwards, like in the bar,
like cleaning up and getting ready to go home
or wasn't on the street.
There were two interactions where performers told you
you were difficult during the situation.
You were difficult.
And I was like, well, hold on, ma'am,
you were playing a Nazi and you did have a Luger
to my head at one point.
So like, I thought I was playing along.
This is like immersive like narrative
where we went back in time and we had to turn a robot on
and there was a bomb, Delusion, the big blade.
And Jason thought that it was more like
we're improvising dialogue with the performers
versus we're sort of just following people along
a narrative of a set, you know,
bunch of lines that they say.
We're just following that.
Jason, I think was under the impression
that this was some sort of interactive thing
where we could influence the actual story.
We could not influence the story.
And he learned that when he tried to like,
instead of just like quick follow me
and he's like, you got a light Mac?
He like did like a weird old time voice.
And then just the performers stopped dead.
The performer did not know what to do.
Like looking around like,
this has never happened before.
Everyone just follows me through to this next room.
Most of the people doing this performance are usually,
like it's not somebody who wishes they lived
in the time period that we are conveying.
Two different performers, I think approached you perhaps.
You.
And they were like, what the, what was that?
So I think you were under the impression
that it was a different thing to your credit.
Sure, yeah.
No, I thought you were supposed to do like the,
you'll never take us alive, man.
Yeah, you thought you were, yeah, yeah.
Lady?
Right, but they were like, look, we got six more groups.
This is the last show of the night.
You were the second to the last group.
And I have a software job to get to tomorrow morning.
I have a day job.
I lost my place of the lines in my mind
when you did that, kid.
This is how much Jason's heart cannot harbor hate.
He can't even handle a fake Nazi in front of him.
No.
You give it right back to him.
Sure.
Not even pretend, sir or madam.
So I think though mother at the 50s primetime cafe
will be more interactive.
Cause she has to be, she has to be,
she doesn't have just a set script.
She knows she has her, you know, main things she says,
but she's going to have to be improvising the whole time,
the whole meal.
Yeah.
But she's never faced a challenger like Jason before.
That's true.
Again, we're talking, we're getting towards the era
that you would like.
We're getting towards a back to you,
heading back in the womb direction.
Yeah.
Being a little, little dinner boy.
It is not, it is not reality.
It's the reality that exists in a television or movie screen.
Also what you'd prefer.
Scott, as a nervous child,
I think I was more along the lines of you.
I was like, oh, they're going to yell at me at this place.
And I was like, thank God there's four adults here
to take the attention, you know.
This is you at six.
You, this is me.
This is all a latter day Jason transformation.
You weren't eating it up at six.
No, I was probably a little precocious,
but like the level they would like,
as opposed to 37 year old annoying,
which I am now a lot, as I've been told sometimes.
Sadly drifts off.
But it's real.
Mostly immersive performers.
Mostly immersive performers, people of my life,
castmates, coworkers, you know.
But yeah, I, and I think, well,
I think my interest was always too, like,
I always wanted to go to a drive-in movie theater.
So like a drive-in movie theater inside
where they give you milkshakes, like.
They don't give them to you to pay for them,
but yes, otherwise.
Yeah, sure.
I'm not sure with your parents.
You're missing words, but yeah.
I, yeah, well, I don't know.
I would like to see, I mean,
I'm going to be silent in this,
I think you and I might sit back and watch.
That's fine.
I think we were like, almost like we're
on the crew of a play.
We just were all black,
sort of just kind of keep quiet in the background.
Kind of subtly indicates we're not even.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're not meant to see us.
Exactly, so we're trying to observe more
and then Jason is fully on display
as whatever version of little boy,
little gravy boy he wants to portray.
These are my dad's.
They're, do you remember the sprocket sketch?
Sketch when I say that.
No, but thank you.
But then we have to be related to mommy.
You have to play it like she's your actual mother.
But they're aunts, they're aunts and uncles.
Oh, but I thought.
And your cousins.
I think maybe she's in the kitchen.
Right, you're right, because this, okay,
excuse me, you're right.
The servers are. Relatives.
The aunts and uncles.
Cousins perhaps, even two.
Right, okay, so that's going to be trickier.
It does, it, look, it waters the whole thing down
that saying auntie is not as creepy as mommy.
Not by a mile.
That's true.
But you know, I still, I think, you know what?
I think he could still creep out.
I mean, I do have a practical concern with this
is I don't often have a huge appetite in Florida.
I feel like the heat and the humidity
just makes me pound so much water
that I just feel, honestly, sometimes bloated
a lot of the time.
This is the humidity.
Did you not just describe yourself
as a big, wet meat boy or whatever he said?
I said I'm a big gravy boy.
Yeah, Scott, we all contain multitudes.
Just because it doesn't mean I suddenly don't like gravy.
He's a big gravy boy, but not in Florida.
When he gets to Florida, he's never hungry.
Something lighter, something lighter, you know?
Today he is a big gravy boy
because we're recording this in California.
So if you had this, if you had mom's plate of leftovers
here now, you're devouring that.
You're getting big and wet, no problem.
Yes, I think too, because a lot of the mom,
a lot of these foods are novel to me.
We weren't a big meatloaf or pot roast.
My mom would make it occasionally.
Fried chicken was mostly shake and bake at home.
I think it's gonna be, you know what?
I'm going back to the server thing.
It's gonna be fine, because you're gonna tell the aunt
what mom does.
Mommy wouldn't let me do this and stuff.
That's how you, yes.
Because mom, it's so much less annoying
if mommy isn't said frequently.
The exact same thought coming into this,
that I was like, I mean, look, admittedly,
I might have lumped you into this.
I was like, one of these two guys would go there
and say mommy incessantly.
I finished my meal, mommy.
I'm not gonna say that to a stranger.
It's all fun in this safe space
of the three microphones here, but I don't really feel like.
When you're looking into the eyes
of someone you've never met.
A five-year-old student, or an older,
actually one of the videos,
it seemed like an older gentleman.
I'm not gonna say mommy to that guy.
It seems like a place maybe people take that role
and do it for a long time.
Well, yeah, when you find somebody
who is good at the performance aspect,
I feel like they wanna hold onto them.
I hope they're giving them raises, but I don't know.
I do have, I have a few times more recently
been at the bar, been at the TuneIn Lounge.
This looks good.
I didn't know about this bar.
Like, I'm more comfortable with the TuneIn Lounge.
I think the TuneIn Lounge is where I'm comfortable.
Yeah, I like the TuneIn Lounge.
The TuneIn Lounge, a lot has been scaled back,
since COVID.
TuneIn Lounge, I think it's mostly people waiting
for the restaurant and cocktails to go.
Used to be you could just hang out at the TuneIn Lounge
and you could get the full food menu
without having to do all the damn bits.
But my family, I do remember once we went and we ordered,
we were just getting like sodas.
I think my dad ordered a beer.
I think I was probably in high school.
And we ordered like the thing on the menu
that said fried cheese,
thinking it was just mozzarella sticks.
And it was a giant clump of cheese with raspberry sauce.
I think now it comes under it.
Now it comes, at the time it came up top of it,
now it comes under it.
My dad does not like strawberries or raspberries
or any berries with the seeds
that can get caught in your teeth.
So he was like, ugh.
Is that only in Florida or country-wide?
Everywhere, everywhere.
That one applies all over.
But I was looking at the menu and I saw it's 20-some years
later, it's still on the menu.
Fried herb cheese, what do they call it?
Is this, oh no. Jelly cheese?
Fried, yeah, fried herb and garlic cheese.
Fried herb and garlic cheese.
And it's like a big, it comes with fruit
and like some crostini or bread to spread it on
because it is not like a stringy cheese.
It's a spreadable cheese?
It's a spreadable cheese.
Which, like a brie?
Like a bourzin, like I think, is that what it's called?
Something like that.
But I did look up like the raspberry and fried cheese thing
and I did, only recently found out,
this is like a Simpsons joke, this is an Albany thing.
In Albany, they serve fried mozzarella sticks
with raspberry melba, which is pureed raspberry
and powdered sugar to bind it.
Maybe I heard a peach melba.
You're stumping left and right, you're throwing stumps.
Another old dish.
So I don't know if this is, I'm assuming.
Someday, peach melba's coming up on the show
and it's my time to shine.
But I don't remember why I looked this up.
Maybe 50's Primetime Cafe came up in conversation
and I looked up fried cheese and raspberry sauce
and I got an Atlas Obscura entry.
Don't pretend you didn't have a dream
about peach melba and started.
The whole stretch of you explaining food
is like we're gonna clip this and send it to Florida
for your audition to play Grandpa
in the 50's Primetime Cafe.
There is some grandpa entries.
There's a lot of roles Jason can play there.
It's little boy or very old man.
That's potentially the outcome of this.
If he goes toe to toe with server,
it's either I quit and I don't work here anymore
or here's a job application.
You got the goods.
If you defeat the server, you have to take their job.
If you out old timey the server, then you win.
Can I get my equity card?
No.
There are some roles at the Florida parks
where you can get an equity card.
There should be a good amount of those I think.
But yeah, so this is a thing I found out.
The fried mozzarella with raspberry melba.
I'm assuming this was at least a partial influence
of serving this appetizer
and a bed of raspberry sauce, this fried cheese.
You got it.
Sounds like somebody's gotta get to Albany ASAP.
Despite all the time I've spent in central New York,
I've never made it up to Albany.
It's the themed entertainment in Albany.
Oh, there's gotta be something.
Because now this is how we justify any vacation for us
is a tax write off.
What is the dynasty typewriter of Albany?
What is the hip theater in town?
Is gonna have to someone listening to this is in Albany.
Or it has to be. It has to be Albany.
You would think.
So let us know.
Do they have like, I don't know,
do they have an escape room?
Anything counts.
Was there some sort of immersive
where we could do improv with the performers?
Yeah, and they don't like it.
The other thing that, the other reason I went
to Two Nitten Lounge just a few years ago was
I kept, I saw people mention there is a food item.
There's a peanut butter and jelly milkshake.
Oh, I saw them.
I think that people is pretty well regarded.
People like that.
And somebody, I watched one of the vloggers
and they showed it in like a paper cup
and it looked like puke.
It looked terrible.
Yeah, it does look puke when you combine those things.
For sure.
I bet it's good.
I don't mean to completely be negative here,
but it looks bad from the video at least.
It's hard to imagine.
I guess I've liked peanut butter
and dessert form plenty of times.
Yeah, I mean peanut butter works in anything, really.
Yeah.
So I can't imagine, yeah, and again,
if it's a fruit, it's probably the sweetest jelly possible.
May as well, jelly may as well be a dessert already.
So I can imagine that tastes good, but.
This is, it is raved about all across the board.
This is a quote from Eater, from the website Eater.
The PB&J milkshake is the closest thing
in all of Disney World to real actual magic.
What?
There is an Eater article that is very fawning,
very, very crazy.
Extremely.
It blew my mind in terms of,
I thought this was like a weird remnant of 1989 MGM studios
that in my head it was like, oh, they're still doing that.
I wonder if that's all right.
I probably won't go
because I don't want to have somebody tell me
to take my elbows off the table.
Cut to, I start Googling, Eater says,
the 50s primetime cafe is the single best restaurant
at Disney World.
Gosh.
The best restaurant in all of it?
Does that count?
Are we, are hotels in the mix?
Right.
Or is Disney Springs in the mix?
Is this, are they just trying to be provocative?
That seems absurd.
Especially given that then, Jason, as you said,
vloggers are like, you know, pretty good.
Like that's the best that you get.
Even I would say that Mike's hero, Mr. Morrow,
was not even the most positive man I've ever seen
in any media.
He didn't go black and white when he ate it.
No, he didn't.
That's the mark of the best food around
is that when Mr. Morrow, I don't know if you know this, Scott,
when he eats something and he loves it, he's chewing.
And then he, all of a sudden the picture changes
to black and white, it slows down and he adds music.
And that's how you know he's eating something
he's fallen in love with.
He hasn't done it in a while though.
Well, he said he's been doing it more sparingly.
Yes. Oh wow.
I think he's gotten pickier.
He's a steak guy.
So when he ate a Peter Luger's,
and I think even when he ate a steak of the Tam as well,
he did black and white.
Yeah.
So this is his Paul Hollywood handshake,
to put it in British baking terms.
It's only, you know it's special if you eat the black
and white. Right.
And no black and white in this.
Hey, wouldn't that be the place for it, right?
Perfect. Black and white.
Well, so it shows you then.
This is a thing that I have not really been
in a long, long time,
but it's a thing that exists in theme parks.
Where it's like, oh, I think I just like knowing it's there.
I think I would be very upset if I heard it would,
I would be very bummed out if I heard it close.
Really?
Yeah. I think this and the Brown Derby and Sci-Fi Dine In,
which came along a couple years after this.
But do you think it's more because it feels like
the park you fell in love with at such an age is dying?
Sure. I think that's it.
I think like there's still some remnants of like
the old Hollywood angle, you know, of this park.
Right.
There's still a lot of place making stuff
just as it just becomes disparate.
The heart of MGM studios would slowly be.
Sure.
Sure. Yeah, yeah.
Well, you get that, you get the classic feel here.
Like this, you know, because I think you've lost that.
I mean, they've certainly lost the theming of the park
in a lot of ways.
But if part of it to you is seeing something black and white
at some point, that's kept alive here.
Yeah.
It is a bummer that you can't just go to the bar
and get all the food.
It seems like it's like a pass through bar at this point.
Okay.
It does seem like these things maybe are the closest
you have to like opening day,
like the classic attractions essentially.
Basically, yeah.
The great movie is gone.
So what else do you have that feels like, well,
that's been here the whole time?
Yeah, sure.
What else is open aid?
Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
Spectacular.
Star tours opening day?
No, no.
Later on.
Yeah.
There were barely anything was opening day
because they barely had it open.
It was like, yeah.
And the, because all that back lot stuff's gone.
You got no New York street, right?
That's all.
Wow.
Is this it?
Is it Indiana Jones in this?
I think, right?
And unless you count the-
Brown Derby.
Oh, Brown Derby, okay.
Yeah.
Dinosaur, dinosaur ice cream.
Right.
To the existence of the lake in general.
Probably all those Hollywood Boulevard stores.
Crossroads of the World statue at the entrance.
That kind of big needle thing that is in Hollywood
and you, I've only ever just driven past it.
It's not in a convenient spot.
It's not a safe spot, I don't think.
I think you run away from that as fast as you can.
In Hollywood.
It's like a offices and strip mall kind of thing,
but there's like nothing there.
It doesn't seem like anything's open nowadays.
Is this the only Disney, least like American park
that doesn't have an opening day ride?
Wow.
Still, I think.
Are we forgetting something?
Yeah, maybe we're forgetting something.
They didn't have a lot of rides.
Yeah.
Kind of was great movie ride and the tram and, huh.
Could be.
So it's 50s prime time cafe.
We didn't realize when we got into this
how heavy the burden is of 50s prime time cafe.
Yeah, really.
All of tradition is gone.
I viewed it as, I was thinking how it kind of stands as,
it's nostalgia for 80s nostalgia for 50s nostalgia.
Oh, for sure.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Being there and the whole, the like kooky kitchen
and the googie style, the crazy bulgy shapes and stuff.
It feels like fondness for that really spiked in this era
with Nick at Night.
Right.
There's just like, there's such an 80s component to it too,
which I think makes it double nostalgic in some way.
And this is why it creeps me out.
Because as I think we've talked about on the show before,
Nickelodeon commercial with the beehive hairdo lady
who's your mother, it was like, finish your chores.
There was a commercial like that for things.
Bubble tape.
Bubble hair and it was the 50s,
the 80s, 50s aesthetic in the background.
I find it unpleasant.
Which usually involves mashed potatoes and mayonnaise.
Yeah, she's like, gotta.
Meatloaf.
What's the general feeling on meatloaf here?
I feel like meatloaf was portrayed
as like kind of a gross food in the 90s as well.
Like that was something.
I think it worked on me.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe this is immediate construction.
Maybe I'd like some meatloaf.
If it's good, it's good.
It is good, yeah.
The Boston Market opened in my town,
originally called Boston Chicken.
And we were, that was one of the best things there
was the meatloaf.
You can get decent when Clifton's reopened downtown in LA.
Oh sure.
I don't know if you ever ate there.
Maybe once, yeah.
And they had like a cafeteria.
I feel like they, I feel like in the first few months
it was like, they had so much you could get
nine stations and then as the months went on
it was like, we have one station open
and you could get a hamburger.
I don't know what it's like right now,
but I like it was a great place.
Open for events.
Yeah.
And it's got the Tiki,
if you ever been to the secret Tiki bar at the top.
I don't remember.
Oh man, we should do Clifton's actually.
We were there at a party.
That was supposed to be an episode.
We were at a weird party.
Was it a funnier die party?
We were at a weird, yeah, funnier die party.
I was at a funnier die, were you guys there?
I wasn't there for that I don't think.
Whale, the rapper Whale I think.
Wale, is that how you say it?
It's not, or is everyone wrong?
I'm not gonna try.
Wale, yeah.
Whale, is it Whale?
You sound more confident Mike.
I know I'm 90% there.
It is not Whale.
It doesn't feel like it'd be Whale.
It's no way it's Whale.
He was on a show at the Staples Center
and they booked him for this
and he came over and did two or three songs
and then he was out of there is my memory of it.
He was at the Staples Center
and then he came and did songs at Clifton's?
Well I think it was feature guest artists
at someone else's concert.
All the money they saved from using actors,
they paid Whale.
Wow, where'd all this come from?
How do we have hundreds and hundreds of.
50K for two songs.
That was the D.A. would be like,
all right a year of crunched budgets
and ooh sorry, ooh we can't, sorry.
No, we're not gonna do that, sorry.
And now hey, Merry Christmas everybody,
please welcome DNC.
Wait, DMC?
You called it DNC?
I think I said Anne.
I said Democratic National.
That's where their black money.
They did not do a miniature version
of the Democratic National.
Their dark money was coming from,
they had DNC dark money.
Yeah, yeah.
That's why you gotta confuse the DMC.
It is a black bag operation.
I think that was what was quietly
funding in front of your die, yes.
No, and then you look up what DMC is,
what he gets for one night of party,
of just doing Walk This Way
and yeah, that money would go a long way
to getting people some benefits or something.
DMC, he earned the money, he deserves that money,
but when you look at the budget,
maybe an actor should have gotten more than a zero.
He would stick up for their part.
DMC, he'd be the first to say,
give it to this guy, to this DPU,
we run into the ground.
Yeah, so we should do it Clifton's,
because there's a secret Tiki bar.
I'm surprised, maybe you just didn't know it was there,
because that should have been open for a call.
Oh, I was there, yeah, with the boat, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there's a boat up there,
and it's behind glass, it's like a secret thing,
you have to push on it, and there's a secret staircase.
Yeah, it's great.
I don't remember.
I was drinking, whatever this was,
I was drinking a ton, so who knows.
Well, we'll go up there if it's still available,
I don't know, maybe it's not.
My memory is the secret door was open
just like the bar was that evening.
That might be the case, for a big event,
it might be like, we're not gonna let it be a secret.
Yeah, wait, I might have the same deal,
like it wasn't a secret.
Yeah, maybe they just said it opened.
That's why I don't remember it.
Okay, that's fair.
Not drinking to excess.
Yeah, because every time I had been there,
you had to like know and push on it and go upstairs.
Okay, what else about, wait, you were saying,
okay, we were saying creeped out by the 50s nature of it.
50s, yeah, I don't know,
and the whole, and the strong emphasis on the table manners
and not fun to me, I don't know.
I think that the sort of like the proportions
being a little bit exaggerated feels unnerving
when it's recreating real life
versus when it's like Toontown proportion,
like a Toontown aesthetic.
Like when it's Toonish, you go, okay, yeah,
but like it's a little bit surreal, it's a little odd.
And then I think I've seen this applied
in like a couple different like haunted mazes
over the last few years.
Oh yeah.
There was the Paranormal Inc. maze at Knott's
that ends when you're in like a 50s hospital
and you walk, like you basically, you go to hell
and then you come out into like this hospital,
and I've talked about this before on the show,
which is a really cool part.
Story strikes back.
Story strikes back, and it's like old music
playing on an old radio and everything is a little odd
and there's a nurse who's got like a beehive hairdo
or something, and then I was like, yeah,
this is the creepiest.
So now I like, I've taken that like old time aesthetic
to mean like something sinister, I think.
You don't like beehive hairdos, I guess.
Seems like a main thing.
I'm anti-beehive, I like the B-52s.
I like, you know, I'm pro it,
but in this context and in horror maze context.
You wanna see it remixed or commented on,
you don't wanna just see it.
I know, it can be a straight ahead beehive hairdo.
I don't need a sort of like a subversive take on it.
But I don't think you like it being,
I don't like you like somebody who is mean and stern
with a beehive hairdo.
That's true, yeah, I don't.
But that might be it.
That's a trope, I feel like that's a trope we grew up with.
Far side too.
Yes.
I like the far side, but would I wanna hang out
with one of those far side ladies?
Probably not.
Right, or the monsters in character we've talked about.
Roz.
Roz, yeah, she's got the beehive.
That's a trope, you know.
Maybe what needs to happen is there needs to be a pro,
nice beehive hairdo character movement
in this country, in this world.
Does Marge Simpson not count?
I know, it is technically a beehive,
but I never think about it like that.
It can't be being that it's like double or triple a beehive.
Yeah, it's something to me.
Yeah, yeah, don't put it in that box.
Yeah.
I did laugh to myself when my dad was like,
oh, your grandparents really like this.
And I'm like, looking back, I'm like,
wait, they had like half this stuff in their house
in the 90s, they had a four mic kitchen table.
That's why they liked it.
Yeah, I guess so.
And they were the ones who, you know,
my parents were born in the 50s,
but I don't know, they have too much memory of it, you know.
I will say like decor wise, it seems great.
Like props are fantastic.
They did a good job. It's well themed.
It is well themed.
Or in thrift stores or whatever.
The TVs themselves are fun and custom,
and they say Disney on them.
And I remember also thinking I would,
now I would like to go and watch the 50s stuff on the TV,
but I don't want to get berated while I'm doing it.
I have to say, however it pained me as a kid,
I would not that, but like half of it I would like,
but I was so nervous about that.
And not wanting meatloaf either.
One of the vloggers said,
if you don't want to do all the interactions,
you can tell them I'm a little shy.
Oh really?
So perhaps they would pull back from the aggressive,
the aggressive language they would use.
You might also be able to say like,
hey, I don't want to do the whole thing.
Like I'm heat stroked and I just kind of want a sandwich.
I think you maybe could be more direct,
but the shy thing is a little bit more of like a sly way
to do it.
Which I never really thought of.
I knew at the one in the wilderness lots,
the whisper whisper and Canyon cafe,
there's like a flag on the table that if you put it up
or down or something that signifies like,
if you're, hey, I don't want to do the whole fucking thing.
What is the whispering?
What is that?
I think they're a little rude to you.
And if he asks for ketchup,
they'll like bring you 10 bottles of ketchup
and start throwing stuff.
Which place at which hotel?
At the wilderness lodge.
Really?
It's right in the lobby.
Did you know about this?
No.
Interesting.
And they're mean, but is it like a woodsy?
I think it's like quirky with the, yeah.
So they're like, they're coming back from chopping wood
all day and they're a little irritable.
Yeah, it's something like that.
And they make you eat a cow pie.
I don't, I'm sorry about the ketchup.
I didn't know it was a faux pas.
I just like it on things.
I don't want to eat this cow pie.
Nope, you gotta do it.
We need to do, we should do more like on this weird stuff
that's in hotel, cause I didn't even know this.
I've never heard that name, I don't think.
Like I didn't know about this restaurant
is what I'm saying.
Oh, right.
But like there's, there are little things like that
in all the hotels in Disney worlds.
Like that piano player who's at the,
help me out here, I've stayed there.
Port Orleans Riverside.
Riverside, yes.
There's like a piano thing with a little bar there.
Tissin looks mad that you aren't coming up
with this stuff.
No, no, I was mad cause I was like,
Port Orleans Riverside.
What is the cumbersome name that you changed it?
Cause they used to call it Dixie Landings
and there was pushback.
They were like, don't call it that.
Right.
And Dix Nunes was like, full steam ahead.
We're calling it that.
And there was that like older gentleman
who I think passed away who would always say hello to you.
Something, there's a bunch, there's a number of those.
We gotta tell you, I remember there was like an old man
at the hotel who says hello.
There's a number of old greeter.
They're doing it, old man who says hello at the hotel.
But then there was someone.
Michael Scott.
There was like a novelty pianist at Riverside.
Riverside as well.
Wasn't there like chatter?
Like one of the guys that was like.
There was chatter, yeah.
About one of those guys.
Was it one of the two?
Was it the piano player or the old man who said hello?
I don't remember which one.
One of those two guys was inappropriate to guests.
Soft cancellation.
How do you know this wasn't just that one pervert
was talking about your butt when you were a child?
My specific butt?
Yeah.
I don't, but I feel like.
That must be a themed thing.
I read it on a blog.
This is firsthand.
Hello my baby, hello my honey.
Wow, look at that tall guy's tight ass.
If you go, oh, you know, maybe it's just like,
it's like the prime time cafe or the other thing
or it's interactive where there's a pervert
who will make inappropriate comments to you
if you go to Riverside, Port Orleans Riverside.
The local pervert that they've installed there
and you can do improv with him back and forth.
But remember, it's you're being transported to a time
when being a pervert was still legal.
Yeah, specific.
Before anti-pervert laws were enacted.
Yeah, so we'll do the episode about the pervert.
The Port Orleans pervert.
Unless I look it up and it's really bad
and then you'll never hear this part of the episode.
One thing we haven't mentioned
from the 50s prime time cafe.
Did you read the liquor menu?
Did you see the tab on the menu?
The section that was like the liquor.
It's called from dad's liquor cabinet.
Oh, right, yeah, yeah.
And all right, that's a little unnerving.
There is some nasty.
See, I was like, I think it's fun.
This perfectly illustrates our views on,
get to go back to the Irish bar episode
when you're like, mom and dad need their medicine.
That, I just think that's a weird way to phrase,
that was a weird thing in TV and movies.
They will always talk about dad's liquor cabinet
or something and I.
You jumped to that's where the gun is.
I never experienced that.
Behind the bottles, the guns back there,
maybe more than one.
Oh, sure.
But one of them was the Fireball cocktails,
Fireball, Cinnamon, Whiskey and Rum Chata.
That's not in dad's, that's not in the 50s dad.
Yeah, I don't think so.
If they're gonna stay on theme,
they should have it be just like Scotch.
Yeah, as bitter as it comes.
No ice.
Yes.
Scotch.
They don't cool it down.
You pour yourself a full, the mug I'm holding,
you do that entire amount as I am right now.
Full coffee mug of creme de menthe.
Yeah, it should be, they should stay on theme.
You know what that upsets me now,
now that you've said it, that part upsets me
that they put Fireball in there.
Dad wouldn't be caught dead with that.
The Eater review said the cocktails lean towards sweet,
but a bourbon on the rocks is hard to mess up.
So you can do very dad drink.
But yeah, leaning sweet does not seem right.
Not 50s, government.
Yes, because they're all trying to either subdue themselves
from fishing through the rest of the bottles
and getting the gun,
or trying to build up the courage to finally get the gun.
To get the gun, yeah.
The gun is in all of dad's minds.
When the liquor cabinet is in play
and the drink taste should follow.
They would use the Tommy gun from the great movie rides
sometimes in the early days as a prop
in the 50s prime time.
In the 50s prime time.
We weren't that far from the 20s at that point.
So people might've, a lot of dads
might've had their dad's Tommy gun,
because their dads were professional gangsters.
It was the 20s.
We pay for this nice house we have.
They quickly did away with the thing
where you would have to talk down the dad character.
You're not in Okinawa, you're not in Okinawa anymore.
It's just shell shocked.
Immersive theater.
It's just a Don Draper type.
You can't blast cigs in the 50s prime time cafe anymore.
You know why you think that mad men and other things,
I think maybe that's also contributing.
Because I think back then it was like,
remember the 50s, sock hops, happy days, blah, blah.
Now the 50s, because of mad men and other things,
were like the 50s were bad.
Betty Draper is like mommy's little helper jitters got you.
Yeah, I think maybe there's been,
there's less of the rosy 50s in our imagination as well.
Maybe I'd be more down with the server interaction
if things got a little more Betty Draper.
Yeah, sure.
If like, if it's not just that you, like take it further.
I keep putting my elbows on the table.
So then there's like a genuine threat with a knife.
Oh yeah, yeah.
She starts scaring everyone.
Mommy, why?
I apologize.
She's like, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
She's like, drop the, or, or, you know, it'll be good.
Like there's a point when like a door closes
in the back of your shoes.
Oh my God, your father's home.
Everyone be quiet.
Just be good, be good, be good.
We can't have him yell at us again tonight.
We'll just be good.
And like, you have to be very quiet
while this like angry man walks through the whole restaurant.
Every table has to just be like silent.
Well, and you could convey, you could involve the TVs
in that like kind of a nuclear test pattern
kind of thing comes on.
So if you see the, if you see the alarm,
that means everybody shut up.
Yeah, that's like the volcano going off in Trader Sam's.
You have to duck and cover.
Right, once every hour it happens where dad comes home
and it's bad news, cause he's had a bad day at work.
Oh, this is great.
And they, you don't have to illustrate it.
You can, you use your imagination
of what dad having a bad day means for you.
It's not going to happen as long as everybody is quiet.
But that like, you know, he, all he does is just stomp,
stomp around and there's one cough
and it makes everybody jelly.
Everybody claims their forks and knives.
And he has to, it's like, it lasts like 20 minutes too.
He goes to the bathroom and you have to wait
and you just like, it's so quiet in there.
You can hear him going to the bathroom and then he gets out.
He like changes out of his work clothes.
It's long, like a hearty thick piss.
You hear it no matter what table you're at.
It is the longest, loudest stream.
And he's got, and look, we've talked about on the show,
he's got some issues as far as your Aether is concerned.
You can hear it start and stop like 10 times.
That's not helping things at work.
That's not helping things feel better.
90 seconds of the pee is just a struggle.
That's also part of it that probably he, I don't want to go
and I would never accuse him of this
cause I'm scared of him, but he's at the office
having an affair with his secretary.
Yes.
He's maybe having trouble performing.
Are you having problems down there in general?
I hear you, you've been having problems
with your streams, right?
No, no problems.
His certainly, he's getting guff from his side piece.
That's absolutely what's happening.
There should be an argument off state.
There should be an argument in the kit.
You like ask, can I have some more napkins?
Can we have more gravy or ketchup or something?
And he just goes in the kitchen and it's like,
oh good, the stranger who lives here sometimes is home.
I pay for this goddamn house.
And then a tea kettle flies out of the kitchen door
and smatters.
Ketchup is two dollars a bottle.
We're just going to let this loser kid
just take as much ketchup as he wants.
When would you, when would you ever been at a grocery store?
So that's the fun thing you wait for once an hour
to have happen.
That would be more what I, that is truly the era
and I think it's more appropriate.
Yeah, yeah, I agree.
They're putting too shiny of a gloss on it.
That's right, yeah.
So if they do that, I'll book a flight tomorrow.
I hope they send me to Korea.
The real, we should open a bar on the real 50s
primetime cafe.
The legit.
Shut down, shut down in one day.
Many complaints, children crying.
Well, they maybe didn't get the word out of it.
Why did they still advertise it in like a fun
Johnny Rockets kind of way?
The dark side was not indicated whatsoever.
Yeah, but the peanut butter and jelly shake was great.
It is great.
They definitely pulled that off.
You know, they're playing the American graffiti soundtrack
and that's always fun.
I mean, that's either, in either version,
that was the music of the time.
So Wolfman Jack was on the radio in both versions.
What do you mean?
He was loud enough to muffle the yelling.
Yeah.
Wolfman Jack should show up too.
Well, they were trying, they couldn't get the rights.
It was Wernherbrough.
They were trying to get like a Tom Cruise stand in
or a Tom Hanks stand in to go like, he's what?
From what?
He's what?
From Elvis.
Oh, okay.
He's what?
I held out at the last possible second, I go,
I hope I know what Jason's talking about.
I thought it was Forrest Gump.
What's this gonna be?
Colonel, Colonel Tom Parker.
Jason think he's in, Tom Hanks in American Graffiti?
No, no.
Maybe he's in more American Graffiti and I didn't know.
It's like half an Elvis movie,
half a Colonel Tom Parker movie.
I gotcha.
I hear you now.
Sandy Claus.
Sandy Claus will come out.
He's the Sandman.
Snowman, snowman.
Snowman, not a Sandman.
He's a Sandman, we're all in the Sand business.
Oh, we don't want them going to sleep.
They can't get the money out if they go to sleep.
We're all just making Sand, don't you see?
Just the best, one of the best voices I have ever heard,
like no known geographical place that voice,
kind of Czechoslovakian, kind of American, kind of Southern.
From a foreign planet.
Colonel Tom Parker's from space, who knew?
Yeah, he originates from that hotel in Vegas
where the Star Trek experience would eventually be.
He grew up there.
Underneath it, where the family taught themselves
a language that only they speak that sounds like that.
I was curious about the Loop,
about the 50s television loop.
Yeah, I looked into this.
When I watched some of the Loop,
the user Sam's Disney Diaries posted a lot of specials
and things we've watched over the years,
posted some approximations of the Loop plan
on the little TV.
Interstitial graphics are fun.
It's a lot, you're getting some big ones that you would know,
like a Father Knows Best or a Dick Van Dyke show.
And then in-house things, it's Mickey Mouse Club
and it's Spin and Marty.
And you get the opening at Disneyland.
So you get your, you're open the Fantasyland Castle.
I'm really happy to see that.
But then I was like, what's the stuff I don't know?
I hope you flagged the same thing I am.
Yeah, I also flagged one.
Oh, I don't know.
Well, what did everybody flag?
Topper.
Ding, ding, ding.
Yeah.
Three for three.
I gotta look into Topper more.
Yeah, Topper seems great.
Can I, I don't wanna step on anybody's explanation of Topper.
Go ahead, go ahead, it's okay.
I would really like to introduce the listener to Topper
via the voiceover that, and this was on Wikipedia,
but apparently this is how an episode of Topper would start.
And I don't, if I know nothing,
and this is what they say at the beginning of a show,
I'm watching the show.
Yeah.
It is this.
Camel, America's first choice among cigarettes,
presents Topper, starring as Marion Kirby,
the loveliest ghost in town, and Jeffreys,
as George Kirby, the liveliest ghost in town,
Robert Sterling, and Leo G. Carroll as Topper.
Birk, birk.
Oh yes, and ah, the deadliest ghost, Neil.
And that cuts to a dog.
It's St. Bernard.
It's a St. Bernard, oh great.
St. Bernard who loves martinis?
Yes, and yeah, so apparently, so this,
I guess the gist of the show was that it's,
it's kind of a pre-Beetlejuice scenario
where the owners of a house died in the house,
and I guess the dog too, I don't know how
or what would happen to also make the dog die.
They died, they all died in an avalanche, scare.
And the St. Bernard was sent to rescue them,
and he also died.
It wasn't their dog, that was a rescue dog?
I believe it is a rescue dog, that's what I saw.
And he has to, that's the rules of the afterlife.
If you, and if somebody goes to rescue you, human or.
You're stuck with them.
Firefighter goes to rescue you from a building,
doesn't make it, he lives with your family now.
Man, yes, so that's, oh yes, well so,
and you were saying, so the dog is dead too,
so then it's that, the title, Topper, is from Cosmo Topper,
the new owner of the house.
I think there was a band called Cosmo Topper,
now I know why, but Topper lives in the house,
and the house is haunted, so like invisible props are,
or props are flying around on strings and stuff,
but it seems like the main gag is that martini glasses
would get emptied by nothing,
because that's the dog drinking the martinis.
Yeah, the dog loves to drink martinis.
Yeah.
Jeez.
This is a favorite show already,
we haven't seen an episode.
I love Topper.
And based on a movie as well.
Whoa.
Books.
Oh, I didn't even see that.
Some bestselling books, I thought.
Really, so Topper was a series of books?
I thought so, I might be confusing it with someone else.
They made 78 episodes of Topper.
Oh my God.
In like three years, I think, let me see, it was.
Is that like more than, how many episodes did Succession
had, which just ended?
About 40, I don't know.
Yeah, I don't think there were very many.
Topper went, if you're judging purely on quantity,
Topper is way, Topper is twice as good as Succession.
53 to 55, 30 minute episodes, and they did 78 of them.
Which means probably, I don't know for sure,
but let's just ballpark three martini gags per episode
times 78.
Yeah.
I don't know the number, okay, that's 234,
which means like probably more instances of a crew guy
saying, we still can't get the glass gag going.
Get off my ass.
We will do another take when we get the glass gag going.
You didn't have to write this into the show.
It's impossible, I'm telling you.
Cut it, we've done it, we don't need to keep doing it.
They've seen enough of the times of the dog,
and like, oh, just like the most depressed.
Cary Grant was in the first one, by the way, the movie.
Wow, is he Topper?
He was George Kirby.
He's the liveliest ghost in town.
No, wait, yeah, yes.
Lively.
And then there was like Topper Returns.
Yeah, Topper Returns was the sequel.
The books were called Topper and Topper Takes a Trip.
I have a feeling that's not gonna be a conventional trip.
I feel like those ghosts are probably going with him.
Oh no, it's gonna be nice, normal, relaxing,
but I'll be glad they took the trip
and no glasses will disappear mysteriously.
Cary Grant, not in the sequel, and then not in the show.
That's like Jimmy Stewart in an early role of his.
He was like third or fourth build
in like the third or fourth Thin Man movie.
Oh, well, I think Cary Grant was first build in Topper.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, because he was the liveliest ghost.
Sure.
There was a Topper Goes to Las Vegas episode, too.
Oh wow, we gotta watch all of these.
Oh man, we're doing a Vegas month.
I think it's clear that one of the episodes
should be reviewing Topper Goes to Las Vegas.
Yeah.
Listen to that, wait, I'm gonna say this really fast.
There was a special introduction for that episode.
This is Cosmo Topper, bank vice president,
loving husband, and no, he's not a magician.
George and Mary and Kirby are doing that, ghosts.
Yes, a handsome couple who were swallowed by an avalanche
and came back to spread a little joy
into a sedate businessman's life.
And that's their ghost dog Neil of St. Bernard
who couldn't save them.
That's what you get for drinking on the job, old boy.
Right, because the St. Bernards used to have
little barrels of liquor around their neck.
Yeah, why is that?
Oh, it'll kind of bring someone back to life, I think,
and warm them up temporarily.
But they had to deliver that to a human
and make them open it up.
The St. Bernards couldn't smash the barrel.
No, I don't believe that was on them.
Okay.
If at some point hands had to take over.
Yeah.
There was a 1973 Topper returns.
Wow.
With Roddy McDowell as Cosmo Topper Jr.
Oh, I like Roddy McDowell.
I always like Roddy McDowell.
Yeah, Stephanie Powers as Mary Ann Kirby.
And then John Fink as George Kirby.
Well, I don't know who that is, but big shoes to fill.
Yeah, really.
To play lively as a ghost in town.
When was the last time in a meeting at a network
somebody said, you know what we should do?
Bring back Topper.
Probably 1972.
Probably sooner than you think.
Well, it probably happened at Viacom
because Sumner Redstone,
one of the only living executives who remembers Topper.
Get one of those real life couples,
Ryan Reynolds and Blake Lively or Dax Shepard
and Kristen Bell.
Like that's what rings for me.
Oh my God, oh my God.
There's another Topper TV movie, 1979
with Jack Warden as Cosmo Topper.
Oh, I love Jack Warden.
Jack Warden is the greatest.
Jack Warden's second only to Keenan Wynn
in the category of Grouchy Old Man.
Rue McClanahan is Clara Topper.
Oh my God. From the Golden Girls.
Wow. Wow.
We have so much Topper verse to explore.
Wow. Oh my God.
So many episodes of the show, right?
Then books, all of these movies and revivals.
I think let's just get quick agreement on this.
We're all just gonna convert this into a Topper podcast
from here on out.
Yes, for the, at least just for the next five years.
Yeah, we'll pick up theme parks again.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, so then, yeah, that's fine.
We all agree, right, Jason?
Yeah, Topper time.
Oh, we're changing the name too?
Yeah. Hey, great.
You can keep the feed.
The socials will still be,
we will tweet from podcast to ride,
but the name name will get converted to Topper time.
Yeah, that's right.
And you're gonna wanna keep it bookmarked there
even if you hate Topper time.
Cause we're gonna get, cause I promise,
when we come back in five years,
first thing Space Mountain.
We're gonna do it.
So just hang on just five quick years.
You can wait, right?
You can wait.
You're excited.
Everyone listening now is just as excited about Topper
as we are. Everyone's chanting Topper, Topper, Topper.
Yeah, so.
Oh, so I guess Invisible Dog shows are theme parks now.
Comments that we all send to each other.
I don't think.
Be very curious. If you write those comments,
just know we send them to each other.
We see everything.
We're like the all seeing eye of Mara.
We're like the ghosts.
Yeah, we're like Invisible Dogs in your house,
draining your drinks and making fun of you.
Do we miss anything?
Oh, we, hey, the dessert menu comes on a View Master.
That's cool.
Oh yeah, that is cool.
That's really cool.
I don't want, even though I'm saying it's creepy,
it is, it looks good and it is fun.
What I like is that it's,
there's such a variety of places to sit.
It's not like also uniform.
I like that about Biergaard's restaurant
that there's different wings.
Yeah.
And this is sort of similar where like,
you can get a pretty different experience
depending on which table you're.
Kitchenette, is that one of them?
Yeah, which is another Annette Funicello album
I'm gonna make.
Okay.
The kitchenette about all different household items
you can use in your kitchen.
Oh, I wish a toaster was my boyfriend.
Yeah.
Because that's whatever I want.
Mike's hearing about AI and he just has a legal peg
with the phrase like, kitchenette.
Annette sings about items.
Yeah.
Private, publicly like, oh yeah, it's a shame, the AI.
It's a shame, it's weird.
That's one of the days we are gonna strike
because of the AI.
Private, privately, oh boy, my hundredth Annette album.
Music only for me.
Office supply Annette.
My man's as sturdy as a three-ring binder.
There is, there are a lot of these, you know,
you hear the AI is generated a new Jay-Z song or something.
And I don't, I have yet to see an AI perfectly recreate
Annette Funicello's voice,
but I imagine it's only a matter of time,
or I imagine I'll have to do it.
I'll have to, we don't wanna put it in there.
Well, nobody's inserting the information maybe fast enough.
You have to start compiling every clip
of her voice that exists.
Right.
And then put it into the AI.
And then so that we can properly defile the memory
of this long deceased woman.
Yeah, there's a lot, I don't know, I get a lot of record,
like it'll be like, oh, if Billy Joel sang this old song
or whatever and you listen to it and you go,
this sounds like absolute shit.
Yeah.
But sometimes there is okay,
but a lot of them just sound like garbage right now.
One of the most interesting ones is it's like,
they take Paul McCartney's song New from the last 10 years
and they put like John Lennon on it.
They put the other Beatles on it, kind of interesting.
Oh, the other stuff.
He wouldn't have let New come out.
No, that's what would have been fine.
There's your mistake, the idea that he would just be singing
background on New.
He would have sang, I think he would have.
I think John at 70 would have been interesting.
He would have relaxed.
Yeah, I don't think, I think he was on his way to relaxing.
I like this one, my Valentine.
It shows a whole new side of you.
Kisses from.
You could have been a torch song singer, Paul.
Kisses on the bottom or whatever that album's called.
Oh, Kisses on the Bottom.
Nothing weird about that one.
I don't think he would have been as interested in that.
Have you done your record yet with Rihanna and Kanye?
Do you need a fourth?
I like the cyber truck.
Like all the.
Oh yeah, he does say that on New.
You can just see, yeah, that John Lennon
did just say the most stunted, like unnerving.
Everything is very ghoulish.
It's gotta be a little ghoulish.
At the end of New, he does say, I like the cyber truck.
That was the most, I was so stumped.
Thanks for jumping in, Mike.
You might say I've never finished listening to this song.
Yeah, yeah, so that is, Jason's right.
So anyway, Net.ai coming soon.
Yeah, did we get it all?
I think, I guess we did, right?
I guess, yeah, I do.
Again, I wanna reiterate, I like the way this looks,
but the aesthetic now creeps me out,
and I do want to do it.
I wanna see what it's all about.
I'll get the peanut butter and jelly shake.
I'm gonna get that Albany delicacy.
Oh, the fried cheese.
With the raspberry, yeah.
I guess I have to get the meatloaf
to see what it's all about,
see if Eater's right and it's the best restaurant.
That is a heavy meal.
You're not gonna be able to hit a clean plate club.
Well, first of all, don't challenge me,
because I will join the clean plate club there, I believe.
That's doable.
Oh, we gotta make sure that we do it
with mere hours before you gotta get to the airport.
Okay.
So that there's some stakes to you joining the clean plate club.
How many hours before the flight leaves
do I have to do this, do you think?
One and a half.
Well, I know.
I'd have to be seated at one and a half or?
I'm not sure.
I think you gotta match the conditions of last time.
Well, last time I wasn't so in danger of missing the flight.
An hour and a half would really put me
in a troubled situation.
You should be walking through security at that point.
Well, you know me.
I like to walk through security about half hour
before the plane. You're like Indiana Jones
reaching back for his hat as the temple door.
Yeah, and I don't like to be like that.
I have done that, but I like about a half hour
before the plane leaves, I'm walking through security
and through the metal detector.
Insane.
That seems weird to me, given the,
you're worrying otherwise.
I don't like to fly too,
so I like to almost kind of give myself,
I've said this about raising a kid,
when you don't have time to think about,
I'm so worried about getting there.
It's like, I don't even have time to sit
and get stressed out about being on the plane.
I'm rolling through, you go there,
I have to go to the bathroom.
I mean, it's usually 30 minutes is pushing it.
45 minutes is a little bit easier
because that's when the door's open generally.
So it's not maybe that dire,
but I like kind of not having to think about it,
like sitting and relaxing to think about
that I'm going to go on a plane.
So it is preventing worrying.
I think so.
I think that's part of it.
And yeah, when you're not sleeping
because you have a little baby,
it's just like, you don't have much time
to worry about the things you were worrying about.
I have plenty of time to worry about,
but there's a lot of things
that I don't have time to worry about.
So that's good in some ways.
Fuzz up that brain and then just fill it.
And then just any spare time,
fill up with 700 alerts on your phone
and looking for new AI songs.
Cloud, yeah, it's really just a cloud up my brain.
Now available on Tubi, Topper.
Oh, I see Toppers on Tubi.
Tubi or Pluto or one of those.
Is there a Topper channel on Pluto?
There very well could be,
but it's also probably just like on
your old Malt Shop memories TV on your antenna.
Roku has those, Roku has like completely made up channels.
You'll find like vintage wrestling TV
and it's like the most basic Microsoft paint image
of like a TV with like a wrestling ring in it or something.
And you're like, this looks like a child made this picture.
And then you click on it and they have stuff on it,
but you're like, who's behind this?
Like there's not really much of an editing process
that I'm keeping things off Roku TV.
Boy, how things have fallen from the good old days
when you could turn on the network
and watch something quality like Topper.
Of course, do you think whatever that network
that Debbie Dunnings show about the Dude Ranches,
do you think they have Topper on there?
Oh, the Voice of Rural America, whatever that is.
Voice of Rural America TV has Topper streaming.
Maybe, it seems like an antenna TV go to.
Yeah, I don't know, but there was a streaming component
to Rural America TV or whatever it was.
Oh, wait, okay, there's one other thing.
They have stopped doing this at the 50s Primetime Cafe.
The first reservation of the day,
the first family of the day, they would take like a picture.
Oh yes, right, right.
With the staff as it was like a memento
and be dated like, if that day was like September 21st, 1952
or 55 or whatever, and they would hang it on the fake fridge.
Okay.
But there's not, that's just, they would do that once.
Was there, or is there a person that comes around
with the photo, like you're in a buka de bebo?
I think they would do that for the first people
seated that day and they would do it again every day.
I think that scale back, that one.
No, not an upcharge like a buka.
Like a buka to what?
Oh God.
We're waiting.
I even said it once.
De pepo?
No!
How did you still not get that?
This has been a runner I've longed for.
What was the bet?
Pepo.
It is Pepo.
It is a B.
Yes!
That's, but doesn't that say?
Where does the P come from?
I don't know.
You've seen it printed.
It's up big in a place that you are at all the time.
Because I thought with the B made it sound like B pole,
but you're telling me P is a B pole?
I'm telling you.
I'm telling you P is the B pole.
Someone said the translation when you misspell it is B pole.
What does that mean?
B-E-E-P.
Hole.
B pole?
Yeah.
One of the, it's just a nonsense word.
When you misspell it, it translates to B pole.
Does it mean B pole?
You don't remember the continuity of your own podcast.
I remember a lot of those.
I don't know what it translates,
turns into B pole is.
So you're saying buka de pepo,
which is what you say means some nonsense word
that's when it's translated.
I think that's what it is.
Yeah.
Okay.
Huh?
I went from elated to confused so fast.
Yeah, that was some of the words I've understood
the least in a long time.
I've been called that as well.
I've been referred to as that.
What?
You make people go from elated to confused real fast.
You've been accused of doing that.
Accused of doing that.
Yeah, yeah, I see now.
It's one of my favorite runners on,
and now that I know that it's a runner,
you try to cash call buka like it's your friend,
but it's really just to avoid saying the last word,
which you still don't know.
Because I've eaten there one time.
Yes, but you are in,
we did a whole podcast about it
where we covered this topic
and you pass by the word bepo in a place you go,
like at least once a month.
I don't pass by that part of it.
It's all the way back there.
It's all the way back.
I honestly, I said buka de bepo.
I saw it, oh, it's funny, Jason,
the thing with Jason, whatever.
And then you repeated back just the first part of it.
And I went, my little devil on my shoulder was like,
I was like, I gotta see, I gotta see.
Cause I just said it.
So I felt like it wasn't gonna be such a thing,
like a cold thing.
Cause I had just said the name of it.
Cause no one on earth calls it just buka.
It's not a shortening that has ever been done.
Cause no one likes it enough to do it.
Well, no one likes it.
No one likes it.
It's a horrible restaurant.
Really, really bad.
Really bad.
Sucks tremendous shit.
Somebody might've called a buka to be fair to Jason.
I just, I just, yeah.
If you even maybe even say buka,
I wouldn't have asked.
So it is funny.
Mind your B's and P's, Jason.
No dessert unless you get your beppos
and your pep-pos right.
No.
Your insolence.
All right, that's it.
This episode is over right now.
You use that attitude and we end the thing.
I'm lighting the curtain on fire.
This is, you are gonna end the restaurant.
It's a weird bad seed kid.
Oh, that's good too.
That's good backstory in your pocket.
You're not just a bad kid, you're the worst kid.
Yeah.
All right, you survived, I guess,
the ride to the second gate.
I was worried we peaked too early in this episode
and thank God we just, we ended here.
Well, yeah.
What greater peak is there in listening or talking?
From City Walk, I think, right?
It comes back to the first City Walk saga.
There's so many years where you could've learned
that it's a beppo.
I could've made time to learn the official name
of the bad restaurant.
No one likes according to you.
It sucks.
These things are important.
You must learn the name of the awful garbage
for the place I only ever regret going to.
I hope you don't regret coming here to the second gate
and if you wanna dig even deeper,
join us on our VI, I'm just gonna reverse it,
on our VIB Baitreon tier, Club 3.
I'll put a random key in there, Club 3,
where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.