Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains musicless carousels, Survivor, The Ride, late period
Stan Lee characters, and the empty promise of meeting an old prospector.
All this plus Scott's trip to California's great America.
On today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride where we know you can't spell make America great again without
great America.
I'm Scott Gerger, I'm shown by my Carlson.
I wish I could say you're wrong, but you're not.
It's just true.
I'm not making any assertions politically.
Either way, Jason Sheridan.
Folks, there's two.
There's one in Santa Clara, there's one in Gurney, Illinois.
It doesn't make any sense.
I don't get it.
But I do now.
I do now.
Sloppy branding, sloppy branding folks.
The Marriott Company drops the ball again.
Messy Marriott.
This did answer my question.
I was like, how do we end up with two great Americas?
I never knew.
I know.
Really confusing.
I mean, we could talk about this for a second here.
Today we are talking about California's great America, which I didn't realize was the official
name.
It's gone through different owners being that first word in the name, but California's
great America, technically the name.
This is one of those things because I always have trouble sorting out the great such and
such parks because there's a lot of those at Six Flags.
It's great escape and great adventure and then great America too.
I thought, what is up with that?
This is not Six Flags great America, but there is a Six Flags great America.
I didn't know why, but it's because they both started at the same time.
That was the brand name was great America.
Because they were both started by Marriott.
Isn't that a weird thing in general that Marriott had theme parks?
Yes.
Also, it's funny how quickly they're like, we don't want this anymore.
Pretty fast.
It's late 70s.
They're putting these up by early 80s.
No thank you.
What surprised you about it?
That other than it was not just an easy print of money or did you just realize we are hotels
and that is what we are?
Yeah, it's a good question.
It makes sense that a hotel company would say, hey, let's add some rides.
I suppose so.
It makes sense in that way.
They build places, they build buildings which you need in theme parks.
That said, the Marriott brand is pretty sterile I would say.
I have no particular associations with Marriott.
Red letters.
The letters are a little bit like Disneyland.
Kind of medieval looking.
That's probably why they thought of it.
They're looking at their own logo and they're thinking, wait, you could put a silly kid's
word in this font.
There was a Marriott hotel.
I mean obviously there's Marriott's everywhere.
There's a Marriott hotel by the airport that we would sometimes go and buy like a pool
day pass and just go swim in the pool.
I don't know why we did this actually in hindsight.
You can do that.
There's apps now to get day passes.
Oh yeah.
To tell you where you can go.
In preparation for Vegas, I found an app too to get on guest lists for different pool parties
and club events.
You can filter it by decibel level.
There is a loud.
If it's blittingly loud, you can dial in exactly the number.
I think there's a Sunday night late, like loud pool party that I'm the most excited
about.
I believe it's a Sunday night.
So I'm trying to get a, I think I had signed up for the guest list by now.
So yeah, I'm on, I've seen those apps and I'm on a different app.
I'm looking at all the apps.
Why are you the most excited about it?
I don't know.
It just is, I like, as I've said, I like being in a pool with a lot of loud music.
You have a couple of drinks and I don't know, I like being in the water.
I like it when it's very, I like it when it's really warm, like being in the water.
And you still like this in a, in a more germ conscious era and post COVID.
Outside.
I'm not going in like the middle of like a massive humanity somewhere, but like.
But at some point there's a bro peeing on your knee.
Well if that's, I'm getting out of the pool.
I see something.
Well if you see it, but you're never going to see it.
That's how it gets you.
That's the tax you pay to get like a super soaker of like well vodka shot in your mouth.
Yeah.
Cause there's kids peeing.
You got to insert some bro pee.
There's kids peeing in the family pool.
No I agree.
Yeah.
That's always a concern with pools in general.
You're in pee.
It's no, there's no, there's no debating it.
What's happening when you were.
It's just a matter of is there like drugs in the pee?
And at the party I'm talking about, there will be pee full of drugs.
Are you worried that it's going to get into your pee mixed with your pee and let's say
you suddenly have a job interview that requires a drug test.
I know that.
I know that happens to you all the time.
Commercial auditioning.
Don't they very often give you a drug test to make sure you can be in the commercial?
That's true.
And because of my filthy drug users and ads of any kind.
Because I'm in my thirties, my urethra has widened too, which will let in more pee.
Or is going to water it in.
Yeah.
Oh, you're leaving yourself wide open.
Vegas pee will enter my urethra.
So yeah, that is now that you say that that's a concern.
So I could just like sit in sort of like a bench or something and enjoy from afar.
So it's up to you.
I'm not going to tell you your life.
I'm just, again, I'm approaching with confusion because I still struggle to understand.
I'm just curious why this one was there like a photo?
Is there a particular DJ like Marvin, Marvin Globe?
DJ Marvin Globe is spinning at this one.
I would be excited to see DJ Marvin Globe, but no, I'm actually the novelty for this
one for me is that it's at night.
Oh, that's the reason.
For me.
Yeah.
Generally these are during the day.
So that's what is exciting to me is like, well, what is it like at night?
Is this one on a roof?
I don't know.
Oh, okay.
That's a good question.
I'll look into it further.
We'll click again on the app.
Roof, not roof.
Make sure that's clicked.
Yes.
I want the roof.
The roof is more fun.
Yeah.
Whereas I prefer pool with like free water and music at a very reasonable octave.
I do too.
Yes.
I like that too.
But I mean, it takes all kinds.
It takes all kinds.
I'm so excited to discover Vegas that is readily available as an option.
What is?
Pool.
It's like, oh, you can get water so you don't get dehydrated.
The music is very low.
You're shocked by the presence of pools in a city of hotels?
No, no, like chill pool.
I think I had mostly been hearing him.
Were you ever surprised that there are chill pools in a city that's nothing but hotels?
No, I guess that's not what I was saying.
I was afraid that I would end up like, oh, this hotel is pretty nice.
Is the pool going to be annoying?
And it wasn't.
Which is it?
Which one are you talking about?
A specific hotel?
Park MGM is mostly where I stay.
Gotcha.
Yeah.
I don't think Park MGM has a douchey pool party.
They have a high, they have a different like club that is a pool club that's like closed
right now where they would have like the DJs DJ.
But that one is-
Is that at Nomad?
DJs DJ.
As opposed to Jersey Shore cast members.
Right.
I mean, the pool was all open so early.
So in the morning they're playing very low light jazz and then as the hotel wakes up,
then they play clubbier music, but it's not overwhelming like Mike likes.
Yeah.
Well, but I'm saying this, the place they had the Nomad, whatever, that's actually,
the music is louder, but it's much more chill.
It's not like, okay, it's not an annoying wave.
That's the hotel within a hotel.
But you want annoying.
Annoying is the box that you're checking.
No, I understand that.
I'm telling Jason for future if it was open.
I do like the annoying thing.
I like both.
I'm a man who I contain multitudes.
Come see us in Vegas though.
Yes.
Oh, please.
Vegas Rides Big Vegas Groove Blender, which at the moment does not have a water component,
but we are open to it.
If there is demand-
I'm open, yeah.
We can discuss with the venue the possibility of flooding the venue.
Yeah.
I would be for it.
It might be in their best interest.
They might want the Space LV where you can buy your tickets.
The spacelv.com might want to become a water venue.
July 22nd.
If they know what's best for them.
Yeah, July 22nd.
But that's a trip that's in our future.
I am excited to talk about a trip that is a little bit in my past because not only are
we talking about California's Great America and talking about some very interesting shifts
of ownership.
If you're a fan of shifts of ownership info, oh, this one.
What park has ever had more shifts?
But also it is a bit of a trip report episode because I went up to California's Great
America a couple of weeks ago, a family vacation, which was very delightful.
The most ambitious family vacation that I have tried, the longest trip that I've taken
in a little bit.
It's the first in a long time that I've had to get out the big suitcase.
All of my trips have been small enough for the small suitcase and I got out the big suitcase
and in cleaning it out, I found a receipt for the Schomburg Bahama Breeze.
Oh, can you remember?
We were different.
Man, there were so many less children in the picture.
So many less bouts with COVID-19.
Zero at that time.
Multiple now in this group and for the world.
So I harken back to a more innocent time, but with a kid in tow.
This was very exciting for me.
His first flight, that was a big thing about this, which went really well.
He's been talking about planes ever since, planes that pass by, which you might hear
in the recording of this episode with an open garage door.
Try to not mind it if you hear a plane.
Instead of about my son's excitement, who every single plane he's seen since then, he
has said, that's my airplane.
Oh, wow.
He's taking ownership.
Yeah.
Knows the planes.
He knows which plane he was on.
He knows the Southwest colors.
A huge experience in his life.
So I'm coming from that one.
He gives rave reviews to the general experience of riding on an airplane.
So that's a big landmark taken care of.
In general, this trip was done partially because, let me take you back to the land of last summer.
Anyone who subscribes to Club 3, our VIP Patron-on-tier, if you saw the video that I put together on
Twitter, you know that my wife, Erin, and I last year took a day trip there and back
in the same day to San Jose, California, where we went to rent a car, take it through a carwash,
which looked like an old riverboat in Campbell, California, which is one of the adjoining
cities.
San Jose, Campbell, Santa Clara, and then a bunch kind of in the same district.
Legitimately one of the best days of the marriage of our lives.
It was so great up there.
And we noticed a myriad of family entertainment while up there as well.
So the gears were turning.
This might be great to do with the boy.
Could be great to do as just as a very easy, unambitious flight because you got to love
that much like Las Vegas, one of those like you're in the air and then you're down within
the hour.
Good for a kid who's skittish about flying.
And also like a great area where the airport is not in the bizarre place really far away
where airports always have to be in big cities.
A bummer about traveling in general, right?
Doesn't that always that's a real kick in the morale.
I feel like when you're excited to get to the city and then like, oh, God, where is
this airport?
Yeah, it's never as close as you want it to be.
No, but rarely.
Yes, yes.
And in San Jose, it is I don't know what it just this area has a hold on us for some
reason, especially after two really pleasant trips.
And in the lead up to it, a lot of people were definitely asking why, though?
People from there were asking, why are you going to San Jose for four nights?
And some of that was the lack of ambition that it's just, well, it'll be a little mellow.
And we had we had some family up there who we got to visit, but also a ton of family
friendly stuff in the area, as discussed in the previous episode, the world's largest
Chuck E. Cheese, where we got to take him.
And I'm going to put a pin in that and talk about that in a future thing.
I'm also going to put a pin in Gilroy Gardens.
You guys heard of Gilroy Gardens before?
Is that that's unfamiliar?
Yes.
It was new to me, but I watched some videos about Great America and one or two of the
mentions Gilroy Gardens because the Cedar Fair connection.
And the previous Cedar Fair Connect.
Yes.
Cedar Fair used to own them.
It's a park way south.
Basically, I always it was always framed to me as a garlic themed theme park.
I now have been there and that's that's not exactly right.
That's not the whole picture.
I'm going to put a pin in that and talk about that down the road to the city of Gilroy,
California.
Is is there big marketing is that it's garlic capital?
Yes.
Yeah.
Sometimes of the year, I think you drive by and even just in passing by.
It smells.
Reeks of garlic.
Yeah.
Not so much when I was up there.
So it might maybe it's not all year round.
But again, I got more Gilroy Gardens thoughts.
I'll get into that later.
Also really close to Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk, where we got to go only 45 minutes away.
We had to go on a day where there were no rides open.
So I have nothing to say about those dark rides.
That sounded really great.
I love talking about those a while back.
But you remember how that place had like the those they were built to be like like speaking.
Speak of the devil, like a big dirty pools for 1920s people to just kind of like big
baths, basically the height of entertainment back then.
You had to stand around in a big bad.
I don't know.
They hadn't invented the word douchey.
And I don't think they were calling it a pool party.
But you might have.
I Mike, you might have liked being around back then.
I bet I would have with like your loud decibel, decibel splitting ragtime.
Ragtime.
Now, Jason can get into something like that.
Some piano, some loud piano where he's partying like raging.
Sure. In that case, they just have to like blast that through the biggest horn in the world.
That's like how little can we funnel that thing into the piano?
And how do we have to build it like a hundred times bigger than any tuba?
Just blast that through the hole.
That's not what it is anymore.
There is a pirate themed mini golf that might be the best mini golf I have ever done.
So I find that like animatronics climbing up a rope.
There's a really that goes up and down like Disney caliber climb cycle.
If even a Disney.
Hey, you know what? Indiana Jones stays in one place.
He doesn't climb. So this thing climbed many, many feet.
Wow.
So I was impressed by that projections.
Whole thing. So cool.
So that's that's just all, you know, some of the background of of being up here.
Well, one more thing I want to mention, I got to spend some time at a mall called Valley Fair,
a gigantic mall up there that is a super fancy mall.
First of all, Italy got an Italy there.
This is like the opposite of some malls die and just descend into.
There's only three things open and one is the army and one is the Navy.
But some some just get gifted by the earth, like all the like fanciest restaurants.
So this mall thriving packed huge, so big, in fact, that it is on the exact border of San Jose and Santa Clara.
And it splits down the middle.
Like, so there's entire districts of the mall in one city and then another,
which I don't think ever had much bearing on anything until in 2014.
And NPR did a story about this. San Jose elected to up the minimum wage.
And Santa Clara stayed at what it was.
I think that was eight and the other was ten great amounts of money.
But two dollar minimum wage on San Jose side.
So if you worked on the San Jose side of the mall doing essentially the same job,
and it's literally down to like shoe store over here, shoe store over here.
One is eight dollars an hour. One is ten dollars an hour.
In one case, there was a gap that was split.
It was right on the line that was split down the middle.
And the gap had to call one of the cities in question and say, what do we do here?
And they said, well, you got a couple of options.
One, you could log employees time on either half of the store.
Like, all right, how much are they on San Jose?
How much are they in Santa Clara?
Is men's in San Jose or is kids in Santa Clara?
How do you log that?
Which I mean, they ended up choosing the option of just raising the wage for everybody.
Thankfully, the gap made the correct decision.
However, I do really I wish that they had had to operate for a while
with the logic of like that you could be folding a sweater on the exact line
and you have to calculate the effort and time that it takes to get each sleeve.
Or do you just fudge it?
Do you like always do you do any work that you got to do on the San Jose side?
Yeah, I think that worked to your benefit.
Yeah, you would have to fudge it.
You would try to do everything you could on the more.
Yeah. The higher paid.
Well, I guess it's like if an employee or if a customer needs help, like, excuse me.
And then you got to go like, yeah, yeah, I gotcha.
Over here, please.
Yeah, on this side.
Yeah, no, but I'm looking at some shirts over.
Yeah, no. Bring them over here, though.
Yeah.
Or you go and like move the whole rag, just drag the rack into the other side and go,
yeah, so here we go.
That's a good move.
That's a good like employee revolts.
Assuming the managers would not stop is just like get everything.
Oh, yeah. Over there.
Yeah. Maybe it's just like one kind of like dumb stooge employee
who doesn't realize what's going on.
Yeah. And you leave him to like,
I think it needs more sweeping over there in Santa Clara.
I see some dust bunnies.
OK, yeah, whatever you need, skip.
Poor guy. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sweet Santa Clara dummy.
So funny. Anyway, that's just that's some of the oddity
that I got to like like truly great for days.
Recommend the area in general.
But great America, the main reason to go and also
something we haven't talked about with in getting to great America,
there is a ticking clock.
We don't know how ticking it is.
We don't know how fast it's ticking. Yeah.
But a bizarre announcement was made that the land has been purchased.
They are going this park will be no more in two years, in five years,
at least 10 years, unless it all goes away,
unless they decide this plan isn't happening or there's a big economic hit
or something. I'm not sure.
But a we a Jay Leno tonight show level bizarre
too ahead of time announcement that great America will be retiring.
All right. Prologis, it's yours, buddy. Yeah.
Hey, you make it make it number one, just like I did in five years.
It's going away and rather go out on top.
This park, we have to say, is no Johnny Carson.
So Cedar Fair sold the land to Prologis, Prologis,
a sinister sounding real estate concern.
You know? Yeah.
If they have a lot of real estate in Silicon Valley and everywhere,
then that's who? Yeah, probably not.
Yeah, shady. I bet.
But who knows?
And so I'm interested in this kind of conflict at how weird it is
where it's like Cedar Fair owns the park, Prologis owns the land.
This had been kind of the case in the past where like Santa Clara,
the city of Santa Clara, owed the land and then so and so around the park,
you know? Mm hmm.
But yeah, they've been in this situation before when Marriott,
when yeah, cowards Marriott got cold feet and bailed on the whole thing.
I'm never staying at a Marriott.
I do. You can't trust them.
You can't bail on me staying there.
Yeah. They showed me out the window.
They're quitters. They're quitters.
Yeah. You work in Marriott.
You work in Marriott corporate.
We're on to you.
There's a couple of things at play.
One, this is the way they talked about Six Flags Magic Mountain
back around 2008 or so that that land was going to be turned into condos.
Oh, OK.
It just never happened, which could potentially Great America
could be saved because the city of Santa Clara, I think, has said like
that land is only, you know, zoned for theme parks.
Oh, but well, but they couldn't have like that.
They I feel like there's already discussion of other things will be there,
of offices or whatever. Yeah.
I imagine there's there's possibility they're not going to build another theme park.
Surely. But one of the other hurdles they've had to deal with over the years
is the overflow lot for the theme park is the parking lot for the stadium
where the 49ers play. Yeah.
Levi's Levi's Stadium.
Yes. Which you see when you park there.
But it's right up to it.
Well, which is maybe a good thing for
offices or residences, right?
To be where the action is.
Yeah. To potentially 49ers.
I mean, because then you can get one of those like, what's that thing in Anaheim?
They're building, they're building like, I mean, it's we're going to get some new
shop or attainment district.
Yeah. Like I forget what it's called outside of the pond,
which is not the pond for many years, but it's got the dumbest name I've ever heard.
Yeah, we did an episode on this.
We talked about it came up.
Yeah, it was definitely part.
We haven't done a whole episode about the forthcoming Anaheim
entertainment district.
What's the name? It's so silly.
I mean, I'll try to find it.
Yeah, because there already is something down there.
Like there's a Golden Road Brewery and there's a lot of apartment buildings
right next to the Angels Stadium,
which has multi-use parking lots for the convention center for theme parks.
You can build the world's largest Golden Road if you demolish Great America.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah. The entire.
Yeah. The whole thing.
Brewery. Yeah.
One video I watched said that on the days when there are games,
they cannot open Great America.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Oh, I've been to Levi's Stadium for WrestleMania 31.
Oh, sure. Oh, really?
Yeah. Ah, so I've been there for.
How was the venue?
It was very new at the time, so it was it was cool.
So it was high tech, like pretty high end stadium.
Yeah, I think it was a big pain in the ass.
Like it felt like they hadn't gotten there, like
letting people in protocols down.
Because we're like outside for like hours, would felt like.
But then it was fine when we were in there.
That what I was looking up is called OC lowercase vibe, all uppercase.
And but not an eye and exclamation point.
That is what the mark our words.
There will be so much analysis of OC vibe when OC vibe is open.
Yeah, it's going to it's going to be a whole year.
And one thing for sure, OC vibe, it's definitely going to open
and it's definitely going to open like in that initial pitch in concept arts.
Yeah, yeah. These projects always come to fruition.
Exactly how they say they.
Uh huh. Yeah.
Look better than they did in the concept art.
Every business runs fantastically.
Jason, yeah, you don't want to run afoul of the same
Toontown grass people that are going to be mad at you for judging a place
based on blue sky concept art.
Oh, that's true.
So there's going to be people defending that strip mall.
I just want to warn you.
Well, due to the due to recent
mergers and finagling events, the those people are the
saw the sovereign wealth fund of Saudi Arabia bringing you OC vibe.
No, that's not true.
OK, I don't know.
It could could be possibly.
So you're saying it is going to open exactly like it looks.
They're going to get the PGA tour.
They're going to get OC vibe.
Oh, yeah. All the prize assets.
By the way, I was in Toontown a couple of weeks ago
because I wanted to make sure I finally saw the whole thing.
There were still walls up by part of the grass.
What?
I think they've come down like days later, but I went there.
You still haven't seen all the grass.
I saw some new grass, but I don't want to derail us here.
Well, again, we'll put a pin in that.
But then I was like, but there's walls up for this other grass.
Yeah, it's like late May.
What's going on with this grass?
I also I don't want to derail either, but this is was part of my day.
I part of my day at Great America was solo so that I could do grown up stuff
while the kiddo napped and then mom and kid joined.
And and we did kid stuff.
And what I will say, the most lit up he was the entire time
there was when we found the simple pleasures of a plot of grass.
And it was the same grad, the most artificial in the planet Snoopy area.
And he was going nuts and a lot of kids were going nuts.
And it was not lost on me that it is the grass making him go nuts.
But again, then I would go, OK, so these Disney diehards are getting militant.
They are canceling me slash us because we aren't super on board
with something that Great America planet Snoopy has had
for probably 17 years or so.
This is Disney's innovation.
You know where they have a big plot of grass?
The Empire Center, the big outlet by where we live.
There's the and that.
Yes. Well, yes. A big chess set, which my son loves.
But you know what?
Yeah, you know what it is? OK.
Grass and a big chess set.
You know what Disneyland had the one that had open?
I haven't seen the new grass, but the one that was in question at the time.
You know what it had grass and no big chess set and nothing to do.
And yet people all the grass, I will die for the grass.
And it didn't even it wasn't even up to the caliber of what the
boring Empire Center's had for probably over a decade. Yeah.
And where are these?
Why don't these people have like their dis Twitter?
But why aren't they imp Twitter?
Well, we should be.
We're at a better.
That's up to us to be.
Yeah. Yeah.
And Disneyland is out of the excuse that Great America has, which is
appears to be, you know, I've only seen it in photos and videos.
Long stretches of asphalt.
Yeah, a little bit. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's not all the most charm.
It is in a very charming area, I will say.
And if you were on any ride with elevation, then there are,
you know, nice lush hills to look at and parts of the park feel pretty nice.
But other parts are very like,
you know, state fair, like just big open tract.
I'll I'll talk about my experience a little bit.
Do we want to get some things out about the history of this place
beyond the history that is that is doomed?
And then we will discuss whether or not the doom is justified.
If we need to save this thing, if we need to rally against prologists
and blow up the headquarters like cyber nine, do we need to do?
We need to save this blessed plot of land.
But but first, history, anything we're excited to talk about
or that you learned about the history of this place?
Well, the the Carousel Columbia.
Is that what it's called? Yeah.
It's a two story carousel.
If you've probably seen it and not realized you've seen it,
it's been in lots of TVs and movie.
Lots of TVs and movie TV shows and movies.
I think that's very charming entryway, like a nice fountain and trees and stuff.
Like that always looks pretty good.
Kind of an interesting counterpoint to a lot of those former paramount parks
have the kind of Wonderland, which we just talked about, has the big mountain.
Others have the are the, you know, Eiffel Tower replica.
Yeah, yeah.
But similar in that there's a big like kind of reflecting pool kind of thing.
That's the big, you know,
whatever landscaping to draw your eye and the logo kind of
like in the bushes and the topiary form.
And then, yeah, I agree.
This carousel is really nice looking and a really great entryway.
And so they have the same thing at the Six Flags one.
Do you see you recall this?
You went there somewhat, right?
A couple of times.
OK, not as many as I should, because I was scared of most of the rides.
But yeah, I went a couple of times.
I did the tune stuff.
But yeah, yeah, this is basically the same.
OK, that's my memory of it.
Very confused about that.
You know, we we copy and paste this same history.
We just did it with Canada's Wonderland, any of the King's Parks,
King's Island, King's Dominion.
There's been so much recapping of it was Taft broadcasting.
And then it was
and then there was a Hanna-Barbera deal.
And then it became paramount.
And then and Cedar Fair took it over.
So it's some of the same steps of all that.
But with the confusing thing that it was instead Marriott at the beginning.
And then there was a divorce like the parent trap.
Yeah, one child went with.
Wait, wait, what was it first?
One child went with Kings and the other child went with Six Flags.
Right. And they weren't allowed to see each other.
And I hope that they can get together some day and other adults
bring their parents, but the Marriott Corporation back together.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Wouldn't it be nice if Marriott could buy them back?
Yeah. Yeah.
Bring it all back.
Full circle. It's really gnawing at me that they're that it's
it's just not as it was supposed to be. Right.
These are in their in their blood.
These are Marriott parks and it drives me crazy that they don't get to.
Keeps you up at night.
I can't speak to the Six Flags one, but I will say, having been like,
you know, a regular Kings Dominion goer when I was a kid.
I think the different it it just seems like there's a little more care
put into the design in Kings Dominion and Kings.
Like you can kind of see just looking at pictures and videos that like,
oh, someone else built California's Great America.
Like, it's just a little less thoughtfully planned out.
It's a little less themed.
You know, you can kind of tell it's had a lot of owners
because like a lot of stuff has changed or been updated.
You know, that is accurate on the ground.
I will say I was wondering that.
I mean, we can go back and forth between history and and my story.
And I what you just said, Jason, about like that entry way
and you're going to pull and you get that two story carousel, which is very like
that's a good theme park icon.
They couldn't do a castle.
They couldn't do anything really showstopping, but it's a really nicely kept up.
It feels like, you know, that that nice big building on Catalina or something.
Just kind of like, oh, yeah, you know, kind of classic or historic,
even though it was only built in 76.
This is a 76 park, I believe, bicentennial mania.
I think is why it is great America.
Yeah, 76. I'm fairly certain.
But you go in and that looks really nice and it looks really nice in photographs.
And it's what they stress on the website.
And you see it in films like Beverly Hills, Cop 3.
They use that.
This is the park where that was filmed or all the exterior stuff at least.
And then as soon as you get past that, once you get around that carousel,
you're like, oh, no, it's a six flag.
Oh, shit.
It's like that is a facade, like that is a wall for a minute,
keeping you away from what's behind it and keeping you in the state of like,
this is maybe a nice little Northern California gym.
And I can't wait for my son to join me and see all of the wonder and charm.
Oh, no, shit, shit, shit, shit.
This is trash.
There are 40 competing signs.
All the music doesn't make any sense.
It's like a left. I feel like for a lot of it, there was just a loud
midi of Europe grand old flag.
Oh, so annoying.
Booked a ticket up there, though.
He loves the cool party music.
I'm a big patriotic.
I love I love that song.
I'm a big Mass Effect guy.
I know.
Like, oh, they were putting pins and things as the theme.
We're just regular.
So many things like we're voodoo conspiracy theorists.
It's like this episode is a voodoo doll.
But yeah, truly, I like it is a really disappointing thing
because you're around the car and like I here's I have the sense
that this was a charming place at various times.
I think when it was kind of a relatively non-corporate park
in the 70s and in bicentennial era, I bet it was really nice.
I got a shade of that when, you know, it was really nice to do
was a skyway type ride.
They had like a gondola sky buckets kind of ride.
Eagles flight, I think it was a patriotic name or as I think it has
a different name depending on where you board.
But I was really looking forward to that.
I'd really like to do one of those because those those barely exist
anywhere. They don't have them at Disneyland.
And the building that I boarded from had a really nice wood carved eagle
that felt very American adventure or even like critter country or something.
I was like, well, this little corner and there's some forest back there.
Like like this corner of the park feels a little Disney to me.
And so I think if whatever you found in the late 70s
probably was very charming.
My mother in law, Dan, I think really enjoyed this place as a teenager growing up.
I bet there was charm in the 90s Paramount era.
I know you like you like those parks. Oh, yeah.
And like there's something fun about this.
We're just talking, you know, the the chance that a cling on could be
on the coaster next to you.
I think they like pumped a little bit of life into all those parks
and seemingly this one, too.
So I think there's been eras of this place. Yeah.
But I don't think this on death row era
is necessarily one of them.
It's very funny that so many of them, it's like you got to ride
the suspended coaster flight deck.
And it's like branding looks really familiar.
And you look it up, it's like, oh, it used to be Top Gun.
Yes, it's another one of those.
I forget how many of these there are in this world.
But another where it was a Top Gun ride and now it is called Flight Deck,
which seemed very good.
But I did not go on this coaster.
I did not go on a lot of coasters and it was not for lack of trying.
I to my credit, I know you might put me in the WIMP category
as you would have any right to do given my history.
However, I tried. I definitely tried.
Did you go on anything resembling a coaster?
I did. I went on Patriot.
In course, and with the thing I had to prove that I am one. Right.
And appropriately, I was in line next to a guy
with a T-shirt with drawings of you might think I'm going MAGA with this,
but in fact, I'm going T-shirt with Joe Rogan and Crystal Leah.
Well, why are they like everybody in that podcast?
Yeah, anybody? Everybody in the Avengers of the I'm just asking questions.
I'm not sure. It was more the comedy side.
There could have been a Theo Vaughn.
I didn't know.
Oh, sure. Really hard to I did not stare at this man's chest.
I think he is a person who would not have been comfortable to see this shirt.
I bet it exists.
I bet the right Googling would, you know,
Rogan, Delia, all stars of comedy and thought and wow,
I'm going to find them and not not having your mind in a cage, man.
That's what you Google.
Patriot, though, I liked a lot.
Brave for me, I would say there's loops and there's corkscrews.
And it was a five on the famous
Cedar Fair one through five. Oh, OK.
Fear rank or thrill ranking scale.
So I did a five.
I would like some high fives.
OK, yeah. Is that the scariest coaster you've ever done?
I wouldn't say so.
It was not as intense as that the one at
not that I was suddenly brave enough to do.
I bet one's probably the most and it's no it's no rock and roll or anything.
It's like fairly.
I hope that flight deck is probably a little more ambitious.
And some of the other ones.
Did you see the there's a single rail coaster there
open in 2018 called Railblazer?
It has a red track that looks really insane.
Yeah, the way it moves, like even just on video, it's like, oh, wow.
That looks odd.
I got to I that maybe had to book a flight because it's just like,
I haven't even only done one or two of those single rail coasters.
Yeah, I've had trouble getting my head around what those are and how they work.
And but it's yeah, it's it's wild.
I mean, it feels very it feels like it's 3D printed or something.
It just seems so fluid and precise and and, you know,
bendy, twisty in a way.
You've never really seen a coaster be.
It moves so fast in such a way where you're like, is it out of control?
Are those people in trouble?
Yeah, that was not a candidate for me.
I was not going to do that one.
I really wish I had done a ride called Gold Stryker.
And I was even attempting to do it.
It's right at the entrance.
And it seems kind of in the family of Ghost Rider.
It's it's wooden, but pretty like hefty and crazy.
It's not a seaside kind of wooden coaster.
It's it's it's a big boy.
We're talking about a big boy here
where it goes really fast, 53 miles an hour, I think,
which is almost in credit coasters, top speed.
And I got into the line for it even where the first drop really thunders past you.
It's wild, like the sound you're hearing over and over again is intense and scary.
But I wanted to do it.
I swear I wanted to do it.
This just became a case where, OK, one of the one of the like pleasantries
of other parks that this place is lacking are accurate signs of wait times.
Nor is there like an app, I don't think that's really telling you anything.
So you're just trying to eyeball it.
And I even passed by this right at the entrance.
And I saw a sign that said, wait from this point, two hours.
Like, no, I'm not going to do two hours,
because this is also the kind of place where the you are not exactly
getting top tier queue entertainment.
We can debate about skippable queues.
I would say I would I would love it to see the defense of most of the queues
at a place like this or in fact, a six.
It's not what they do.
It's not what they're in the game for.
That's not their bread and butter. No, no.
In fact, in the I did stick with it for a while.
I was in the line for a while.
I tried to take in some of the queue entertainment,
which the only one I remember was the music video for that song.
It's a quarter after one.
I'm a little drunk and I need you now.
Who does that?
Yeah. I don't know.
I don't know. It's out there.
It's on all the time, but I don't know. Yeah.
I didn't feel like watching the music video and I scarcely see
how it is relevant for a ride. Lady A. I was right.
Oh, that's a lady. Yeah, I see.
Is that now is that from post a or was it when there was a pre a when it was the pre a?
I think Antebellum was your old name.
Don't say it.
Oh, it's not the solo artist who was already called Lady A.
All right. They took Lady A. Yeah.
Yeah. There was no other way they could have.
They should just they can't just gone a lady.
We're a lady. A plus lady.
Yeah, that would be good.
I like the name of that.
That's like the name of a like a covers band that would perform on a riverboat.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. A plus lady.
Anyway, I wanted to do this, but was there a front of the line pass option?
This occurred to me when I was deep into my park visit.
I was too deep. I went and asked.
It was one hundred dollars.
A little steep, I think.
I think I could have done that for much less.
Really good triple A deals for this place also.
So that's a little probably sent a podcast to ride press email.
Yeah, like I'm a little that angle. Yeah.
Yeah, I know a story about the it's called the dying days of great America.
We want to come see how shitty it's got.
They love that kind of coverage.
Go any presses, good press, you know, 100 percent.
That's true.
Hunt Ghost Rider is 56 miles per hour at knots.
Wow. Wow.
Because I guess it's scary.
It's really scary.
Oh, that was an I think the more I shaking, I think, is the thing
that still freaks me out on.
I don't like the rickety.
Yeah. Yeah.
When Jason and I went on Ghost Rider the first time, it was like the speed
kept increasing and kept increasing and the whole thing is vibrating.
Which doesn't feel good.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a good it's a fun ride, but it's scary.
There's there's also the the Cedar Fair trend.
And maybe I'm just a worry word on this, but like
you put your bag in this little cubby hole, this Ikea furniture
cubby hole and the thrill of will it be there when I get back?
Yeah, that's right. Yeah.
I do this so seldom that I forgot the D.
I had a visor with me.
What am I to do on my with my visor on a patriot?
I already forgot the name.
I yeah, but I thankfully there was no visor.
Sure. Oh, OK.
I was that was when I tried it down the pants.
There was a moment where I before I realized there were cubbies,
I was trying to shove the visor down my pants and loop the visor velcro
and through my belt loop.
Belt loop. Yeah, belt loop.
That was usually safe.
I used to do that when I was younger.
Big fanny pack.
I mean, I would have had to exit the line.
Yeah. Then try to maybe ask Mr.
Rogan D'Alia to loan hold my spot.
Oh, I thought he had a fanny pack on as well.
And that maybe he would give it to you.
Yeah, yeah.
He's probably plenty generous.
If I'd explained, I was a podcaster, too.
Oh, yeah.
You know, you might say I'm kind of in the same scene with those guys.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, we use microphones, too.
We've been meaning to.
We've been meaning to have D'Alia on.
We really kind of it's like we always think about it.
And then like, I hear he's a big parks guy.
Like, yeah, those guys are controversial.
But a couple of weeks ago, we said that we didn't really care
about the jungle cruise at Disneyland.
So it's sort of a similar situation.
Well, we're saying things that like the public doesn't even want to utter.
Yeah, we said we said an episode was about Canada's wonderland.
And then we mostly talked about Deloitte's.
That's the kind of shit we'll do.
That's the crazy.
That's I'm curious.
I am curious if we if we missed anything about Canada's wonderland that was crucial.
There's got to be some there has to be some juncture in this show that is like
a like a it's not the sieve.
What catches thing a bucket beneath the it's like a bedpan.
Yeah, the podcast, the ride bedpan is what we'll call the episode
where we catch all of the loose droppings from topics that we
doesn't that sound pleasant to do?
I think it should be.
Look, I've been advocating for doing all the episodes we've done already.
Do it again before we get to things like Space Mountain.
I've been saying this for years now, and I think you just stumbled on a perfect
framing device for it.
Oh, yeah. So the drop to like like a fight, like big fight.
Well, no, but the bedpams saying Scott just came up with a good branding.
It's like what did you say?
Don't act like the two is a new idea.
You just thought you guys are begging for twos.
You're playing.
We love it.
But I like your waste metaphor to your waste.
When you can't get out of bed, I call it too.
When you could call it a bedpan.
Yeah. Call the mind someone who's better at extra droppings.
Yeah. P.T. It's P.T.R.
Leavings. Yeah.
Look what else plopped out of this topic.
Great. Indiana Jones.
Buckets full parentheses are
semi colon.
And then, yeah, the Leavings podcast, the right Indiana Jones
pocket, sorry, presents Indiana Jones, the ride
lawn clippings on clip.
The ride is in there, even though it's that is the right in there
because it's in our title or we're recalling it suddenly.
Indiana Jones, the ride.
You know, that's the great thing about blue sky.
And there's no bad idea.
And you know what that shows that we haven't talked about Indiana Jones
in so long. I forgot what the name of it is.
I have to go back over it back before we do a bunch of other stuff
that is essential to cover on this show.
Mm hmm. Yes. That's what it proved.
I thought it just topic number one.
What is the ride's name?
This episode cannot move forward until we get clarity on that.
Yeah, we didn't probably talk about it enough on that first episode.
We don't we just blast past to the names.
We kind of say them and then we move on. Big mistake.
But we should we it's possible we could spend a good
half an hour of every episode just saying the name.
Yeah. And pitching other names. Sure.
Yeah. Blue Sky, it leaving money on the table.
Yes, we are. OK.
But basically what happened here was I just like there.
I was meeting back up with the family again.
And it was it seemed clear to me from the imprecise signs.
I had not yet reached the sign.
Then who knows if I could trust it, the sign that said there is 60 minutes.
I passed by the 90, but I had not passed by the 60.
Kids going to be here soon.
I don't want to be like daddy's got Coaster and to do
was that worth it to me?
I wanted to go hit the grass with him.
So I had to bail on Goldstriker.
But I and and I had put a lot of eggs into the basket of another ride.
Again, heading for it.
The closer. Oh, possibly.
Can I say real quick, Goldstriker has like an old prospector
on like the logo for it, which I really like.
That is enticing, of course.
I like that. But why are they playing Lady A videos?
I know that's the case.
No, it should be like, you know, like that should be what the vibe is.
It would be the easiest.
We could take a day and all of us take turns.
We only buy one pair of overalls, one beard.
We don't need a shirt because we would only wear the overalls. Right.
We just the three of us just looped through different prospector
themed pre ride videos. Yeah.
You know, bucket of props, a bunch of gold coins,
maybe a lightweight mine cart pickaxe, whatever it is.
We would knock out 10 in a day and distribute them.
I would do it for free.
I do it out of the kindness of my heart. Yeah.
And I feel like I we would have to do it for free,
knowing the going rates for theme park entertainment and videos.
But it seems it's inexcusable that you have a prospector in your logo
and not a prospector in a video.
100 percent.
How could they should be responsible for this should be the Cedar Fair.
People should be more ashamed than the Marriott cowards. Of course.
This is this is this is shameful.
And we could fix all of this within a week or two. Yes.
Oh, yeah, we can turn this place around.
Maybe that's what we have to make.
We got to put our any six flags.
We could do it, too, by the way. Yeah.
Because we've said this before.
This is not some like classist thing.
This is just like a major corporation with millions of dollars
decides to let things rot.
And then it's seeming as inconsistent and incoherent.
The money's going elsewhere.
It's going to weird roller coaster haircut
of ventures and to clearing up lawsuits and stuff.
You get a little bit safer.
Yeah. Lift that morale a little bit.
And what's going to lift the morale more than a lot of great videos?
Reprogramming of music.
Mike, I know you want to get in there around in Riddler's zone
and make sure that Batman Forever soundtrack is blasting.
Meet and greet with Chase Meridian caught out.
Mean with Chase Meridian for sure.
I'll probably have to record sound delights for the songs
because we probably get sued if we they don't want to pay for Kiss from a Rose.
So well, that's well, I, you know, I was going to say Lady A is playing.
Well, that's true. That's a real.
But that's that's some licensing. Yeah, you're right.
That's true. Possibly.
So maybe it would be fine.
This is through, by the way, was through
whatever in-house entertainment provider was
is getting the chance to do the right videos, which is called Fun TV.
So Cedar Fair made a deal with Fun TV, who made a deal with Lady A. Right.
But I don't know what Magic Mountain's doing.
I don't know if they have a deal with a fun with a fun TV competitor.
Oh, man, that's a good question.
We got to figure out if they do, because, yeah, if they if they have fun,
TV has a deal with the flaming lips to do,
put bad days from the Batman or the offspring for Smash It Up.
I don't know. Is there an offspring song on there to smash it up?
I believe. Yeah.
To smash it up, factor into the film.
The song is in the movie.
I believe when Robin takes the Batmobile for a joyride.
Oh, briefly hear it as he like pulls up or something.
But it's not a big featured thing.
Wow. So you could you might call it Smash It Up.
Robin's theme. Yeah, you should call it that.
Robin's Rebellion.
The The Flaming Lips song is in the is in Riddler's Hideout,
which is really a fun. That's very prominently.
Yeah. Yes.
I remember when the flaming lips were getting more popular and like,
do I know this band? Sure you do.
They're in the Riddler scene. Of course.
Certainly, you know this.
OK, I feel like I missed something.
I mean, I started getting into my day and I'm about to land at where the
where my boy arrived.
But I want to make sure we don't miss a couple of things history.
Yeah. Why? Oh, well, I got a not late enough one.
Yeah. At least in terms for us. Yes.
So one of the companies that
Marriott splits into eventually becomes that airport
company, HMS host, and an early iteration of it was the same.
Was the one running those cheers bars that we talked about.
Oh, that's why we know HMS host. Yeah.
I will for sure remember that in 30 minutes this time.
You're still getting to make some room in my brain.
Marriott Services Corporation is very confusing.
There is so many Marriott
Marriott companies at one point or another.
This is I don't want to derail, but you're more of a Sheridan than Marriott.
Family. Yes.
Uh, sure. I feel like we're more of a Hilton family.
It's a little on the nose for us to say.
No, boo. Just say you're a Sheridan family.
It's where we're sharing. OK, great.
Yeah, you're Jason Sheridan.
That's what people want to hear the other part. Yeah, great.
That's all right. Now everybody's excited.
Hampton Inn Holiday Inn Express give you free breakfast and, you know,
I mean, a great breakfast, too, I bet.
Oh, and it's good. The wettest eggs you've ever had.
I'm out of breakfast.
You used to just be like pastries and cereal and coffee and juice.
And then at some point it expended out to like
they don't have a kitchen back there.
So I don't know how they're making these eggs and bacon trays.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, a complimentary breakfast where we stayed,
there was in the Hilton family like Hampton Inn,
was it an embassy suites? Possibly. OK.
It might have been omelet bar in the free.
Oh, are you kidding?
When do you find that? Now that's living that now.
Yeah, that's that's great.
Evening reception, free glass of terrible wine.
So happy.
Well, yes, kiss.
Yeah. Oh, I have to say this.
And it's another it's another sidestep, but that's OK.
There's a big article about the reopening of Casa Benita.
Oh, good. Yeah.
Couple days ago.
And there's so many things about because they spent like 40 million dollars
renovating it. Wow.
Insane amount that they didn't expect.
Geez. And one part of it was at the kitchen.
There were no stoves because they steamed everything for decades.
So they install the install actual like stove, stoves and stovetops
so they could cook things.
I guess it speaks to how much people were fond of the place
and the theming that they tolerated steamed beans.
Yeah, I guess. What do you mean?
I can't I get so hard for me to picture all that food
being made with. I know.
I but then I love more than a nice steamed carne asada.
They brought yet.
But the whole articles, I think it was New York Times, the article
they brought in like a top chef to come in and like do the new menu.
And she's got like her own like like liquor brand or something to it.
Forget. But it's very exciting if you read about it,
because it's the dumbest,
greatest place that's now been restored by some millionaires.
This is so by some by some of the richest people on earth
who aren't using money for evil, as far as I can tell.
This and like Quentin Tarantino with the Vista and the New Beverly.
He bought both of these great theaters and have restored.
These are at least versions of very rich people
keeping things open that aren't like financially viable
necessarily just for the fun of it.
This isn't keeping it open, but Drew Carey.
Yeah, all the writers meals at Bob's Big Boy,
a restaurant that at one point was in the corporate family of Marriott.
Yeah, look at that.
50K a week, I read. That's insane.
A true big drew. Thank you.
Yeah, he helped my wife win on prices, right?
Yeah, he's helping the writers win this terrible
to help to make their their price right in this fight. Sure.
I needed to make that rhyme. Of course.
Um, I have a little I got a little history thing.
Yeah, the pair, the Paramount era.
Actually, well, Paramount's not really part of this Beverly Hills, Cop 3.
We've discussed this.
The park Wonderworld has come up in the fake theme park Final Four
as a movie.
This is a boring movie that I've watched too many times.
It is like an action film for grandpas.
I don't get them too excited.
But as a theme park tribute, it's great.
I like seeing now that I've been there, I like sort of being able to spot.
OK, now I know the display of the land.
I know where this is. Oh, that's something they added. That's not there.
I actually appreciate the way they were able to take it from something
that's more of a regional six flags and like make it feel elevated like Disney.
I feel like they understood that difference that to make it pop on film
and be more of a magic park, we got to add this and characters and
theming and such.
I didn't know that. Oh, sorry.
I also I forgot the ride is gone.
I was so sad to discover the ride is gone where George Lucas did his cameo.
Yeah. Where Axel pushes him out of the way and he says, hey, hey.
So I did. I really wanted to recreate the hey.
I would agree with the exact right background.
But that ride is is gone.
That's where, honestly, a lot of the big set pieces there on some
like swinging buckets kind of thing.
It's all gone.
Should have been a historic site for what George did, but it's not
not too far from Skywalker Ranch, I believe, at least in the same part of the state.
God be why they got him, right?
Yeah. Pretty easy commute for George.
Yeah. OK. I now
want to click on some things to send to you guys.
As I mentioned this, as I mentioned, another film
that shot up there right around the same time, potentially the same year.
This is a film called Getting Even with Dad.
Of course.
This was a movie with Macaulay Culkin and Ted Danson.
I recall it as a movie.
One of the movies that gave me that formative early thought in your
in any child's life when they realize, oh, movies can be bad.
Like one of those for sure.
That's like, wait a minute.
But I liked Home Alone.
How could this be bad? Yeah. Yeah.
How could a movie be bad?
I OK.
Oh, man, this this texting might not work out so good.
Well, let me get off the Wi-Fi, because there's something that's important
to send you this movie.
The use of the park in the movie is basically
let's kill a bunch of time and send the kid on the kids into the ride
and the dad and his friends are not.
And they don't like going on all the big roller coasters.
So they are, you know, everybody is like, they can't handle the speed
and they're stumbling around after and they're queasy.
It's pretty typical stuff.
But there's something that I almost missed.
It's like a blink and you miss it, where you think it's just
Macaulay and Danson on rides.
And but when you feel look at some point, I was looking like,
wait a minute, what's going on with their faces?
And they're trying to do the thing where it works better in cartoons, right?
Where the thing is so fast, the ride or the centrifuge is so fast
that your face is getting blown back.
Your cheeks are shaking. Yeah.
They attempt a different way of conveying this.
And it's oh, it's coming.
It's I'm so sorry.
It's going so slow here, but we could just cut it out.
Let's pick it up when you guys see the stills
from this ride that are being sent to you right now from the scene rather.
Oh, oh, oh, there you go.
Mike got him. Jason, any sign like, oh, man, what is this makeup?
I yes, they use prosthetics. Oh, my God.
Do it at first. I was like, do they put in like lip pieces to make their lips
really wide, like something you'd have to wear at the dentist?
But no, they did like squishy.
They're given like almost like the bottom half of animal face.
They look like rat creatures.
It looks like a rat version of Macaulay Culkin.
Macaulay Culkin looks like Steven Tyler in one of these shots, too.
He does. You're right.
Now we know Steven Tyler looks exactly like Macaulay Culkin
with extensional extensive facial prosthetics.
My God, this is awful. This is like Brazil or some.
This is some. Yes, it's I think it's like Dr.
Moreau, a little bit more.
Yeah, these if you didn't know that this was supposed to be Ted
Danson and Macaulay Culkin riding a roller coaster, if these creatures
just emerged from shadow in a scene, you'd expect them to just be
screeching in horror.
The key. Maybe they go eat from a bucket of gruel.
It's like Joe.
They got hit with Joker gas or something.
Oh, yes. They got the permanent smile.
Oh, it's like doesn't the Joker do that to Jerry Hall and the fur?
Like, well, I fixed her up good.
Yeah, she has a smile. He kills Jerry Hall.
Oh, he kills Jerry. OK, OK.
But she has a smile, too, I think, because that's something the Joker would do.
I know. Yeah, he does that to the newscasters in the movie.
We're talking about the first movie. Yeah.
Well, yeah, it's pretty jokery.
Also, just combined with the like with the
it looks like Macaulay's eyes are completely black.
Like it looks like he is he's like consuming to some plague.
Yeah, I mean, it looks like he's midway between
in like a werewolf transformation.
Yeah, there's that's the most like Brazil skin stretch scene.
Or I'm trying to think of another movie, more modern movie.
I was going to say Star Trek Insurrection, but that's not as universal, is it?
Well, I was going to say it's right around the same time.
But Beetlejuice, when they realize they can like when they're ghosts
and they can like fuck with their faces and. Oh, yeah.
Alec Baldwin makes his head real long. Yeah.
Yeah, those are all good comparisons.
Why did this need to happen? This shot is five seconds long.
That was my question.
They put them in prosthetics and then make Nick this.
You made this child go on a roller coaster wearing this shit on his face,
making him look like a rat boy.
They thought it was funny, I guess. Yeah.
They were funny.
Let's make this kid like a fucking rat, a little rat boy.
This kid thinks he's so big.
He thinks he's got more money than we do.
This is the hottest box office drawing of the decade.
Let's see how he feels when he's a little rat boy.
You could see what he can buy with rat.
Oh, they won't sell anything to a rat boy.
No one takes rat box.
Oh, you're a hideous abomination.
Sorry, rat boy.
You could take high.
If you can get some high res photos of this, you can mock up a movie poster
of this and be like Macaulay Culkin is rat boy.
Make it look like a 90s and people go, well, that is him.
What is his front?
Like they'll know it's fake, but they'll be like Sam things.
Does anybody remember Macaulay
when Macaulay Culkin made a rat boy movie?
Is this a I maybe this is a I got it.
He's the best AI I've ever seen.
They did AI that looks like terrible prosthetics.
Yeah, he really knows.
Yeah, particularities.
Well, try it.
Prank your friends.
Try to make your friends think there was a rat boy movie.
Um, that's that.
I also.
This is I can't believe how much there is, but I can't not bring it up.
Did you guys come across a ride in the history of this?
I had to move.
I have more stories from this trip, and I moved them to the second gate
mentally because, like, oh, we need some space for this.
Like, I'm not going to I'm just going to say it.
Say, yeah.
Survivor, the ride.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did you come across this now?
Did you? Yeah, when I was looking through.
Yeah, yeah.
Barely barely caught it.
Survivor, the ride.
Yeah. Huh?
Not the band, right?
Which although I have the tiger was a pretty good basic roller coaster music.
Yeah.
That's licensed to anything.
Parking at that license.
No, this is an official CBS licensed ride.
This was the ride based on sensation TV series Survivor.
Yeah.
Huh? 2000.
Yeah. What do you say? Six?
I think so. Yeah.
Um, so that.
All right.
Well, just imagine what Survivor, the ride could be.
Just try to.
Yeah. You know, because you're it's like, you know, it's perilous situations
and you're on an island.
Yeah. And is it a maybe it's a rafting ride.
It could be that strong water.
I've never watched the show too much.
So I can't pull any big specific, but it's certainly a vibe.
You could see why it would be a ride.
Yeah, of course.
There's plenty of the location would be good for some sort of themed entertainment.
It's got all the like, you know, dad likes palm trees.
So the right is palm trees and like it checks a lot of boxes.
There's a water park being the Survivor theme water park.
You know, something in that family.
No, this is this was a spinner.
This was like a big it's like a big roulette wheel looking thing
that on a little roller coaster track that goes up and down in a hump and up and down.
So it's like it's not, you know, it's like an elevated.
I don't want to just say off the shelf.
It looks like probably be a fine ride to have.
The ride is there now.
Still, I passed by the ride.
It's called Tiki Twirl.
Oh, yeah. I saw that.
Right. It is closed now that I've said that.
I'm not sure.
But, you know, so just a ride that you would.
So how do you turn something that now is just generically Tiki Twirl
into Survivor the ride?
And to do this, seemingly.
All right. You guys will know this name when I bring it up.
Dave Cobb is the name.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Like on Twitter seems like a very friendly guy.
Works in Universal and Warner Brothers Dubai Park and the Men in Black Ride.
And it's and I think the main way this survivor ride is remembered
is via his YouTube channel, where he himself has posted the pre ride video.
And I will say for his like they clearly thought, OK, we can't just do this
with our limited resources and our fun TV.
We need to get somebody who knows how to take a property and put it.
And I remember, oh, I think I've heard him talk about this on something
on season pass or some other podcast. I'm not sure.
Where so I commend him for the work he did to like.
All right. Limited budget.
We're going to make the best that we can out of it.
And I could see why he put on his YouTube channel. Great.
That said, this is the most confluent pre ride video here.
OK, so this hose, the hosts of this are Ethan Zahn and Jenna Marasca.
Based survivor heads will know that they are from the show.
From it as far as I can go.
Here is them explaining what you need to do to get on Survivor the ride.
Do you have what it takes to be a survivor?
Here's your first challenge.
Just up the pathway, you'll be assigned into a survivor tribe.
When you reach the challenge platform further down the path,
your tribe will be divided into four groups, orange, blue, purple and green.
Once assigned to your color, enter the challenge platform
and take your place on the color you are assigned.
Your challenge is for your tribe to make as much noise as it can.
You see, the louder you are, the wetter the other tribe on the ride will get.
Anyone care to?
Did you process any of what you just heard?
I heard orange and they said tribes and they're going to put
they're going to put you into different teams.
Yeah, you got to get four different colors and you got to make the most noise.
So that way the other team gets most wet.
Jason got it. Jason got it.
Jason goes, you got to follow your tribe, make noise, get the other, get them wet.
Right.
And then what this means is that there are sensors under you and you.
So like you're in the line, but then you're into in a little like pre show part
where you get another video where these same hosts
teach you like a clapping and stomping pattern and they record your noise.
And off of that, they determine who made the most noise and there
and who made the least noise.
And the tribe that got the made
the tribe that made the least noise will get the most wet.
So when once they're on the ride, they get sprayed with a bunch of water
from a Tiki face. Right. Got it.
Yeah. OK. Now let's learn the rhythm.
Stop your feet in time with the drop.
Next, you'll add hand claps.
I've got a cloud cloud.
Can I try to do this?
Can Jason try to do this real quick?
Oh, you go back to the start.
OK, well, it keeps looping. Just try it from here.
Finally, you'll have a chance.
My original tribe name was Jabiru.
They're ready.
My original tribe name was Baran.
You mean boring.
I'll say Jabiru.
Then I'll say Baran.
Then you answer.
Ready? Jabiru.
For it.
It's like advanced drumming or something.
Oh,
huh.
Jabiru boring.
Huh.
Boy Jabiru boring.
Jabiru boring.
Huh.
All right. Well, OK, listener, who made the most noise?
Team Mike or Team Jason vote with your
but shout to the person next to you.
Shout like Jason's name to the person next to you and see how loud they spit on you.
Yeah.
It's the at home version.
How loud they spit on you.
My words don't make sense anymore.
I got lost in that.
I don't know if I'm coming out of it.
Yeah, you might not.
I mean, I admire they're trying to do something here because you can't.
What I'm like a survivor.
I'm not a big survivor guy.
I've watched maybe two full episodes in its 20 year history.
I've mentioned a friend of mine, John, was on one season.
So I saw some of those.
But these aren't things you can do in a line for a ride.
These are well, yeah.
And look, challenges.
They show a bunch of people all like happy smiling, doing the chance together.
I contrast this with who I saw as the main audience at this park,
which I would describe as teenagers practicing their public swearing.
Teenagers getting used to how does this work?
Yeah. How loud do I yell?
Fuck. And does shit work in every setting?
And then it's kind of a minor to that major, I would say,
public punching of their friends in the arm.
Yeah, that is mainly what people are concerned with doing in this park.
So it's hard to imagine those same teens going job are a boring.
But again, this is not Dave Cobb's responsibility.
The whole thing with these, you put it in and then you're not responsible
for what the audience does or in most cases doesn't do.
That's still a blue sky to think that that's going to
the audience is really interested in doing that.
All right, everyone, get ready to stomp and clap.
Do you remember your tribe name?
I mean, they're all similar rhythms, but three rhythms you have to do simultaneously.
It's hard for us.
Yeah, it's like the hands, hands scanning, putting hands in the air.
I think now we're at like 50 percent.
I feel like people put their hands in the air on the Guardians, right?
And that's much simpler than that.
And that's all you need.
I don't need everybody.
If only one of your mugs does it, that's fine.
Oh, OK. Put your put your hands in the air and clap like this.
Clap, clap.
All right. Let's learn the chant, everybody.
I'm going to say job a row and then Groot's going to say group.
OK. And then you go.
Are you familiar with a four on the floor rhythm
that a disco drummer might play?
That's what we're going to be doing here.
Just watch this basic drum tutorial.
You know, it'll work at home, too.
Maybe you could pick up the sticks when you get back to your house.
This is Casey in the sunshine pant.
I want you to copy the drum pattern identically.
OK, and we're going to sit here until you learn it.
If not, we ain't getting on this ride.
You know, you could perform CPR by doing the rhythm of staying alive.
Keep that in mind, too, if any of your friends get too shocked
when we're getting into the gantry lift.
Yeah. Dave Cobb's YouTube channel, a lot of great theme park stuff on.
They're also notable for.
A few years ago, uploading the most thorough video record
of the Islands of Adventure preview center at Universal Studios.
Oh, yeah. Your favorite.
I mean, everyone was thinking of the sacred text.
Your favorite show.
Everyone besides Jason was thinking sacred Jedi text.
Shaker Jedi video video text.
Um, the people in that video also, God bless them.
But like, OK, now's the time.
My tribe was named this.
It's a boring, similar sounds like more like boring.
These are not the most like that's not they didn't read teleprompters on the show.
But they are a little stiff and their chemistry is nil,
which is why I was surprised to learn at the time of this recording, they were dating.
They look like they'd only just met each other.
It's the chemistry of Helen Hunt and Bill Paxton and Twister.
And yet they were filmed together and they were together.
So that's Survivor, the ride and ambitious.
Is that the right word? Yeah.
Yeah, I wonder what is your end to them for trying?
What's your dream survivor ride?
I mean, I don't know if I have jungle cruise.
I guess so. Yeah.
As a boat, they kind of take sure there's two boats at the same time
when you're competing against the other one.
OK, OK. Yeah.
Challenge boats. OK.
Yeah. Jungle cruise boat with tribal challenge.
Yeah. And Jeff Probst is the host of the pre ride video.
Really? Yeah.
And a really realistic Jeff Probst robot.
Oh, yeah. Like the Shaman of Song at the end of it.
Yeah. Yeah. It's the most advanced animatronic.
No, no naked kiss.
Remember the naked guy?
Richard Hatch. Richard Hatch.
That was his name. Mm hmm.
Is he in prison?
One of them was money laundering or something.
Yeah, one of them went for financial crimes.
Never saw it, but I know that man's name.
I'm sure it's Richard Hatch because he's got the same.
Right. This is I knew this.
Richard Hatch was a gigantic sperm donor.
He thinks that he thinks he has fathered 200 children.
Wow. Because he donated his sperm hundreds of times at the cryo bank
in Fairfax, Virginia.
Post survivor. 30 bucks a pop.
No, before. Oh, pre survivor.
No, this is college. Yeah.
So he he has hundreds of children.
Wow. Yeah.
I thought I was like, let me make let me make sure there is a Google footprint
of this. And in fact, it's him saying it.
Yeah, I did it.
I got 200 sperm babies. Wow.
That's why you would think you would go for a lot more after Survivor, too.
So he should got back in the game. Got back.
Hello, old friends.
Richard, can I just confirm?
Did you say that Survivor ride opened in 2006?
Yeah, that's another good point.
So they like that was when they were wrapping up the Viacom tie in.
Oh, yeah, right. Yeah, I know.
Kind of weird to do a new one around then.
Yeah, something new that deep, that far past in 1892.
The only time they ever did anything new, really.
Well, you did have Italian jobs, stunt coaster.
I've always forget which which you can also learn about on Dave Cobb's YouTube
channel. I think he was part of that as well.
I don't remember which parks had Italian jobs, stunt coaster.
Canada's Wonderland. I don't know.
Well, I did. I let us know for the droppings episode.
I remember the detail about this because it was at Carowinds and King's Dominion.
And I've always talked about like there was a motion simulator theater
1993 theme to the Tom Cruise movie Days of Thunder.
Yes. And it was very exciting.
And I loved it. And then a few years later, the theater that it was in
at those parks renamed it to the Paramount Action FX theater.
And it debuted with a ride called Jane's Bond 007, licensed to thrill.
And then after that, another guy.
Now we got to cover all of these. Yeah.
Yeah. I think some of them are online.
There's some generic ones called Dino Island, 3D Meteor Attack.
But then a ride based on Stan Lee's seventh portal.
The web comics company he established in the late 90s, early 2000s,
that very quickly declared bankruptcy.
There's a deep dive on like Stan Lee's other superheroes.
The last 25 years of Stan Lee's career.
Non-Marvel characters, including those.
The character Strip-O-Rella, who did have a TV show.
Yeah. And many others, like many others.
There was a massive push at DC.
There was a run of specials of what you'd call a one shot
called Stan Lee creates the DC universe.
So it's all the DC characters, but Stan Lee redoes their origins.
Like, well, what would Stan Lee's Batman looks like?
You know, I've never read those.
I didn't either. You guys haven't read them.
They didn't look great.
I was a kid. That wasn't so interesting to me.
At that point, we had seen so many Stan Lee's blank.
Yeah. So anyway, because that could like, could you imagine if Stan...
Scott, have you ever thought about if Stan Lee thought of Batman?
Why no? Would you like to think about it?
Absolutely not. Go away, sir.
Can I push you off a platform or into a lake?
What if Batman just sounded like Stan Lee?
Well, all right, that I'm on board with.
Yeah. He should have let him.
He was a very old man.
Pow boom.
I make the difference between me and the other Batman's as I make the sounds.
There was a good series of pictures.
I forget who posted this on Twitter.
Someone was like, has anyone have you ever looked at the pictures of Stan Lee
before he chose to become a cartoon character?
And he is just a bald man in a dress shirt.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
He didn't have the look.
He didn't have the... Yeah.
Pretty quickly after that, I think he went to the glasses.
The naked Stan Lee picture?
Huh?
There's a naked Stan Lee picture.
That he took on the Marvel couches.
Yeah.
Full front?
I think it's in front of his penis.
He's got a pillow.
I think he's got like a whole pillow in front of it.
If you look up naked Stan Lee, it's probably...
It's cast to be the one.
Sir, I'm leaving this one to you.
Just do it quick. Just look up...
Oh, it's already in your history.
It's in your most recent.
There he is.
He's naked with a comic in front of him.
Oh, it's a comic.
Yeah.
Well, that's good.
It's real skinny.
Stan, you'd expect no less.
He's probably 55 here.
And it's 1970.
The Action Theater now presenting an up close look at Stan Lee naked.
Action Theater presents Stan Lee full frontal.
Well, the James Bond one too, it's a flip of a coin.
Either it's like, oh, it was a big deal because they got Pierce Brosnan
or more likely it's James Bond shot from a distance or in a hazy profile
and they did not get Pierce Brosnan.
One or the other.
It has something to do with Pierce Brosnan or not.
Well, you've led me to my final destination.
Not my final destination of my trip.
I mean, what happened after...
You know, the rest of my day was going on kids things.
He liked the grass.
We went on...
All he wanted to do was carousel.
So we went on carousels and none of the carousels had music.
Oh, no.
So that nice beautiful carousel we were praising at the beginning,
you get on and it's silent.
Really?
Yeah.
So that's great.
And then another one, then like a Snoopy one and there's not even the
Peanuts theme, just silent carousels.
Was there ambient Snoopy or Charlie Brown music?
Very general, I think.
I don't know.
There wasn't the famous Peanuts theme?
It might have been or it was still...
And I need you now.
I think it's just that point park wide.
Again and again.
Nothing but.
It wouldn't surprise me.
So, you know, little disappointments throughout.
Actually, one to one, really quick.
I remember during the pandemic, we did an episode about Snoopy theme
parks and stuff.
And in that episode, I was pining for a ride called Camp Bus.
It was a boring, bad pandemic time.
And I was like, we're going to be out of this someday and I'm going to get my
kid on Camp Bus and it's going to be glorious.
And we're going to share a father son moment together.
And that's that's not to Berry Farm is what I'm talking about.
And I haven't talked about this in the show, have I?
I don't think so.
We went on Camp Bus.
It was exactly what I pictured and more.
It could not have been better.
We were in the front row.
I have pictures of he and I just like shaking our heads around like
maniacs. The ride went up in the air and it gives you a little thrill.
There's like a little whoosh, like just enough for a kid, a little bit of
butterflies in the tummy.
And he looked at me like he could not believe what it just did.
Not scared, just like, whoa, things can do that.
And I'm like, yes, they can, son.
I have much to show you.
This was a victory of all victories.
I never got to say this.
Camp Bus was such it's so funny that I pegged it on the show and I was
like, oh, it was everything I wanted.
Camp Bus.
I will love these words for the rest of my life.
So we get to Planet Snoopy at Great America where they have the same
thing. It's the same ride mechanism.
It's just a vehicle.
It's on big pendulum arms and it swings up and down.
And this one is called Flying Ace and it's the same except it's creaky and
loud and doesn't give you a thrill of any kind.
It's much slower.
He didn't care as much.
So just comparing the two, it's the exact same ride and yet just enough.
Not good maintenance.
Just a little.
It was no Camp Bus.
So I have some negative things to say about things in this park.
But that gets us to this point, which is this actually, I'm going to go all the
way back.
This became the first thing that I did of the day after making one and a half
rides.
I was at the park trying to find a coaster that did not seem to have an
insanely long unthemed line.
But I had my eye on this anyway just from the website.
And Jason, you brought it up and it's in the place you were just talking about
the former Action Theater.
This is the only park that still has the Action Theater.
It's the exact same layout as Kings Island.
I remember seeing it in 2005.
The same building.
And this is a coaster park.
If you like this park, I think it's probably on the strength of the coasters.
It is not a dark ride park at all.
Nor is this a dark ride.
But I lit up at it because wait a minute, this might be the one thing with
theming and a story.
And I bet it's a little janky, but maybe that's a little bit fun to talk about.
Mass Effect.
I don't know one thing about this very successful video game series.
Are you guys players of Mass Effect?
What do we know about Mass Effect?
Never played it.
Vaguely familiar with what it's about and photos of it and little videos of it.
So I'm vaguely familiar, which is I think I know where this is headed.
I have watched my brother play it.
It's like a sci-fi RPG kind of game.
I don't know any specifics about the worlds or the beat.
I think you can customize some avatars.
I think that's part of it.
So you mean like most video games?
I'm just naming features that I know.
He's just saying what he knows.
Yeah, I'm just saying what I know.
I know the story.
I'm sure there's online elements.
Yeah.
So, well, this is where I'm at.
You know more than me.
I don't know a thing.
But isn't that where you want to be?
Does this not take me back to going on star tours and I've never seen the Star Wars movies?
It's kind of perfect if you think about it.
This is what you want.
This is a chance to experience.
Yes, an IP with fresh air.
So, ride, I leave it to you.
Bring me into the universe.
Tell me what I need to know.
And at this point I am desperate because again, it's a big park.
I've done one and a half loops.
I am pretty tired.
It's hotter than I expected.
And I just want to get on something.
So it is 1.45.
And I walk up to the ride which has a sign.
Strangely, which has specific times like it's the Waterworld stunt show or something.
I think this is a simulator that's just going all day.
But instead it says showings at 11, 1, 2, 3, whatever.
That's odd, I think.
But this time's out just about right.
It's 1.45.
Maybe I get in for the two o'clock show of Mass Effect New Earth.
The first thing I pass is some big black plaques that are in memoriams to people who died in space.
That's scary.
That implies some peril.
I wish I could say more except in the photo I took the plaques are extremely dusty and scratched up and impossible to read.
And that's not Imagineer dust.
No, that is not carefully placed Haunted Mansion dust.
I think, I'm pretty sure that those are the elements.
I move to the next part of the queue where I am next to some trees and I am watching some screens again playing fun TV.
Fun TV in this juncture is stills of rock and roll artists.
Informing me of things like Dave Matthews band released their tenth album Walk Around the Moon on Friday.
That is fun.
Thanks for telling me.
What else you got?
Compilation of Willie Nelson's 90th birthday concerts last month are getting a limited theatrical release.
I don't love that tense.
I think you messed up a verb in there or something.
But I'll take it.
What a fun fact.
Thanks Fun TV.
Then they play the full trailer of Disney's Little Mermaid.
Then about to release.
I don't understand why that's playing here.
But all right.
It's better than looking at nothing.
Also side note, my phone is dying and I need to get ahold of Aaron soon.
So an option for me is not looking at my phone or being entertained by anything on my phone.
So I leave it to Mass Effect to entertain me.
The next part of the queue I encounter is a 16 year old in a bright red polo like they'd make you wear at an AMC theater.
And he's been out in the sun.
His face is as red as the shirt and he is dripping with sweat.
I see his name tag.
I don't want to say his real name.
But it was a very put upon name like Erwin.
He was in that family where you're like, oh Erwin.
Everything okay Erwin?
So let's say Erwin.
I walk up to Erwin and he calls me forward and he says, I know it says 2 but it's going to be 2.30.
Are you okay with that?
Yep.
I'm going to have to be.
I'm tired of walking.
So Erwin looks up at the tiered waiting areas.
Five of them.
Not like bleachers but big concrete that step up stadiums for a theater that's going to come.
So when the doors open you can go straight ahead into the row.
Yeah, exactly.
So he looks up at the tiered waiting area and he goes, okay.
Two, four, six, eight, twelve, fifteen.
He's counting every person in the entire waiting area before he can let me up there and determine, okay.
You can go into row five.
And I go up into row five.
Row five is Bedlam.
There are just a bunch of people meandering around.
It's like a 3D movie.
People aren't organized yet.
Nobody is standing on circles and there are no circles or numbers.
There is no particular way to organize the people.
And that's okay.
Except that it really seems like Erwin down there needs people to be on some numbers so that he can count them.
And figure out how many people went into every area.
Because I start staring at Erwin.
And every four people in the area are going to be on some numbers.
And every 45 seconds he does another round of like, two, four, six, eight, five, six, seven, eight.
Like counting everybody in the entire.
I watch this reset so many times.
And I'm looking at my row and it's mostly teens and they're all milling around.
And some of them are behind the others.
And then they shift around and start punching each other in a new way.
So Erwin's previous count cannot be his new count.
He's got to do it again.
So, oh, making it all the more stressful is this.
And I discovered this before I went around the corner.
There's like big plumes of smoke bursting out too.
Of this area.
Seemingly getting in Erwin's face.
And this seems to bother him.
And that's adding to the stress of Erwin.
And then I get up into the waiting area.
And the smoke is still coming.
And I'm like, is somebody vaping around here?
Is some asshole making it harder for Erwin?
And just doing big billows of smoke over and over again?
That's disrespectful.
Then I realize it's coming out of the ride itself.
There's some vent next to a big future cyborg guy.
I don't know.
And smoke keeps emitting.
And it makes Erwin jump every time.
Just adds to it.
Presumably.
Look, he had the energy of first day.
It could have been his first day.
But also it could have been, I don't know, his third month.
I cannot.
I didn't sense that this person was great at it.
But I'm like, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
I didn't sense that this person was great at handling stress.
I'm not sure.
So, again, phone's almost dead.
I can't look at the phone.
So I have to use what's around me to entertain myself.
I turn to the TV sets.
The TVs are playing nothing.
So that's not going to do anything for me.
Not going to bring me into the world of Mass Effect.
I look above me at the filthiest light I've ever seen.
I look down at my 3D glasses.
Which are scratched to the point of non-visibility.
That's the point of non-visibility.
They are so scuffed up and stained.
As if somebody has just breathed fog onto them.
Right then and there.
Interesting.
Then I realize my main entertainment here is going to have to be poor Irwin.
And I look down and he is counting and counting.
And then every once in a while, people will come up.
And he seems to have a handle on the situation.
And he seems to be leading them up to a particular place.
But then they will hand him a pink piece of paper.
And the pink piece of paper destroys Irwin's world.
And then he's like, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
And he's like, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
And he has to take the piece of paper.
Go to the nearest podium.
And by podium I mean trash can.
He has to roll the pink piece of paper out on a trash can.
Look at it very carefully.
Look at the fine print.
Whatever it teaches him shows him that these people have a right to be in here right now.
And he's got to fit them in.
Even though there's a lot of other people and he doesn't know how to count them.
So after every pink piece of paper, another round.
Two foots.
And he's like, I'm going to go to the bathroom.
He's getting so so stressed.
Adding to all this, here's another nice
thing about this park.
They don't have updated signs to tell you how long
the weights are.
And they also don't have signs that say you must be this tall to ride.
What they have are poles.
Poles that are not mounted.
And that don't have a bottom.
Poles that just have their color coded.
And the color coding tells you if
you put it up to a person.
Or tall enough to ride or not.
So as all this is happening, as he's counting people
and looking at a piece of paper and smoke is going off.
Then he'll like stumble a little bit
and fall back into the pole.
And the pole will go flying.
The pole keeps falling.
Just put a sign up there.
Can this park not afford nails?
How hard is it to just put an
arrow once?
And then Erwin doesn't have to fumble with a sign.
How is he going to help the humans
defeat the aliens at this rate?
I do not have a good feeling about
our trip to this new earth.
Nor do I know what it is or why I'm going there.
If things are finally
coming to a head with him.
At some point I watch him mouth just the big word
SHIT!
It's so clearly shit.
And then he gets a phone call
but the phone that he has to answer
is on a little table and he has to get
down on his knees to answer the phone call.
And he's in like clean nice
khakis because it's a movie theater uniform
and he's on and like uh huh uh huh
uh huh. And then he gets off
and I see him start to mouth an F.
He's going for a bit
and he winds up as if he's going to yell to the heavens
FUUUUUUUU but then
a cute girl passes by him
who's his co-worker and then he
plays it cool. He stops the FUUU
right in the middle like
everything's fine with me Erwin.
He's really
trying to like because maybe
I could date her if I show my management skills
are good enough.
So then he forms a new plan
and the new plan is to
yell to the person next to me all the way
in the back. Hey can you count how many people
in your row?
But he's deploying the
guests now?
Again, Great America
I say
it just puts some splotches
on the ground. It doesn't have to be anything
you don't have to design like a special mass effect
shape. No one knows what it is.
Just like dump random
splotches of paint on the ground and tell people
to stand on those and now Erwin
can do his job. He can get the
girl and he doesn't have to make us the
guests do the work for
and the guy who he points to just goes
me? Really loud and then Erwin
realizes what he said like wait yeah
that doesn't make any sense. I can't make
you do it. It's my job.
And eventually things are finally
the spotlight is taken
off of Erwin because the
pre-show video starts and
I'm so excited because I can finally understand
what is going on with this new
earth. Will there be some sort of effect
on my mass? What do I need
to prepare for with this
ride? So the video
starts and then it stops
and then it starts again and then it says
HDMI signal lost and
there's a big pause and then the video
starts again and the video is very
quiet and all of the teens
swearing at each other are very loud
and luckily I'm the closest to it but if you're
all the way in the back you're not here in one
portion of this video.
Luckily I'm in prime position.
I filmed some of it. There's a logo that tells
you that you are getting on mass relay
getaways. Okay
so it's like a star tour. They're going to take
me to the stars and then this thing
happens. It's like a very pleasant travelog.
Okay I understand this.
This is going to be one of those rides where you think
it's a nice trip somewhere but then things go
horribly wrong. I understand this.
It's still so quiet
and when it starts there's people
who they introduce their
names and they're too quiet to hear.
What I heard was like, hi I'm
Richard Comet and I'm
Sarah Pluto
and we're going to take you to all
the way to Oktus and beyond.
Did your names
have like Comet and Pluto in them?
I didn't hear them well enough to know
is it Oktus did you say?
Why is this so quiet?
Just turn up the volume.
It gets a little louder as
I am taught that you are
going to Terra Nova.
That must be the new earth that's
in question and they start telling me
about the great things that Terra Nova.
Amenities may include hover cabanas,
anti-gravity massage,
then,
I'm sorry I'm going to take my best guest,
four star gourmet
ion fish for dad.
I'm not positive
about ion but it was something like
that it was a science word.
I couldn't tell you.
So dad's going to
only dad and not mom or kids are
going to like the ion fish.
I like the way they're presenting this so far I'll be honest with you.
I mean I'm in at this point. This is mythology.
Ion fish,
do you play mass effects? Can you confirm
our ion fish?
Is that your health? Like you get your health meter back up if you eat those?
It's your Popeye's spinach. Make sure you
catch enough. Yeah, tired dads
love ion fish.
The main difference between
earth and new earth is
on earth you have fish, on new earth you
have ion fish.
So remember you got to get your blaster
out but also be fishing at all times.
Make sure you catch enough fish.
And then it's interrupted
and then a different two soft voiced
news reporter comes on.
Hello, it's Neil
Phonak reporting.
Neil Phonak, is that it?
I don't know. Anyway, he says
that things are not good on Terra Nova.
It's that kind of thing. Uh oh,
I'm scared. What am I going to do?
By now it's been 45 minutes
from the time I stepped into the skew
to this point so I am ready
to find out. So I get
inside and there is a big screen and
a bunch of, look it's 40x chairs.
It doesn't look super fancy
but I'll take it. I'll take whatever I
can get. Happy to be inside. I want
to get my eye on fish. I'm so excited.
There's also
the production value of a little
like bridge platform
in the center of the screen and there is a
performer out there.
This is like a T2 3D.
I get to see a guy. Yeah, they got an actor.
There is an actor in the, I mean
that's beyond what I expected
out of this simulator thing.
And he's talking to us. He's got
a spangled star captain's
uniform on.
He seems a little nervous.
You know, like an Erwin of the skies
basically. But he's going to get us
through it. I was really waiting to see
if Erwin would then also be
the actor.
Like the Popeye Village situation.
I watched a ride
through this and I was like, oh my god
is Erwin the captain?
Oh no. I am sorry to say
we left, we leave
Erwin outside at this point. I wish there was more
to the Erwin story. I just, I wish him
well and I mostly wish him circles on the ground
so he doesn't have to count over and over.
Tough job. Not his fault.
Great America, get your act together.
No, different guy
who is a little bit comfortable with
an audience and he's telling us like
boy, you guys are in for a treat to head to
Terra Nova and hey, you might even meet
Commander Conrad Reynolds.
I hope so. Boy, I look
up to that guy a lot. Alright, well
and then suddenly
we are off. We
are on a high speed
mission to Terra Nova. We're going
through like a big loading dock area
and we almost missed something and there's like a hologram
lady there and
it's full of danger and music
and loud sounds and excitement and then
eight seconds later the ride stops.
It goes
black. It goes totally black.
For a second I thought maybe we hit something
and that was something in the ride.
But no, clearly it becomes, this is
just gone. So now
Erwin too, the more comfortable
Erwin has to
stall, improvise
something that I had to do as a universal
tour guide but I didn't have
to do it in universe of Mass Effect.
So all he has
at his disposal are the boring
things that I've been telling you the listener about
for the last ten minutes. He has to say
like, well, what are you guys
going to do when you get to Terra Nova?
I think, you know,
this guy looks like he's excited
for Daddier, looks excited for that Ion
Fish.
It came back. Wow.
I was so glad I clocked
it before. But you, you're
going to like it. This guy right here,
he's going to be maybe having
extra portions of Ion Fish.
Hey, do any of you folks know
how to plug and
what is it called, an HDMI cable
in?
Unfortunately we are still on
regular Earth. Not
Terra Nova, Terra Oldva.
And here we are still at the
hands of cables that we get from
Best Buy. So if you know anything about, if anybody
any former Geek Squad members here, you might
help us out.
So he also then, he
just, part of the stall
is that he gets really wistful about like
I gotta say though
Commander Conrad Reynolds.
This guy, he
I just really
admire him. He's so
Commander, they really
are a great commander, aren't they?
He says.
I don't know if that was a, yes, is that
like a forward thinking language?
Pronan wise or is,
does he just talk weird?
I'm not sure, no way to know.
But he gets really emotional about Conrad.
It makes me even more excited to meet Conrad
Reynolds. So I'm
very excited when the ride starts again
for one frame,
then eerie
silence, then a new voice,
someone less charismatic than Erwin
or new Erwin gets on and
says, oh, unfortunately at this
time, do some
difficulties, we're going to,
you gotta, you gotta go.
You gotta, you gotta, wow, you have to leave.
And that is
the end of that experience for
me. There was no ride.
There were no eye on fish.
There was no Conrad Reynolds.
I watched a
little girl burst into tears
at this situation.
More nicer, I'm sorry,
more charismatic Erwin as to like,
I really,
we didn't want this to happen.
We wanted to go. But it's,
safety is important, you know.
I'm so sorry.
I just hope, I hope the rest of your day goes better.
And then we all file out
our offer, nothing. We don't
get pink pieces of paper like
Erwin was being handed
by other, we get nothing. We get
for what now has been an hour of my
time. I'm not compensated
in any way. The families
get nothing. My reward is
exiting quietly through a dark
hallway with occasional cutouts
of characters I did not get to meet
in Mass Effect New Earth.
I don't know why there's a big lizard
captain. I'd love to know.
I still haven't watched a video
of it. You shouldn't. I don't, yeah.
In a way I don't want it. Jason, you did. What
did I miss? There's
bad guys. The screen
has your cannons show
up. The ship starts blasting.
Guys, you're flying all
over the place. Do you
remember anything about, did you meet Conrad Reynolds
and was he as valorous
as lore has told?
Okay, see, I
think I met a friend of his and I thought
he called us Conrad Reynolds.
But
I could have misunderstood
exactly what was going on because
video of 3D screens
not in 3D, you're
catching 50% of it. That's interesting because I was
going to say maybe Conrad Reynolds was like a performer
and they could just change gender so you
would say they're just because you could
depending on who it was.
But if it's also the audience, that's interesting.
We shouldn't investigate this.
They might have been mistaken
in calling you that. I don't know. This is a shame too
because this is apparently
the last operating action
theater. Yeah, they're all gone.
With a long line,
briefly had the Fantastic
World of Hanna-Barbera when that left
Universal. I forgot.
Briefly got to have another
ride's droppings.
Yeah.
Here, you take this. Take this shit we
don't want anymore.
Wow.
I guess it's at Six Flags but it's similar to
that Justice League story I have.
We actually got to go on the ride but
we had another situation where we walked into the single rider
and the guy was like, oh,
single rider?
Single rider? And we were like, yeah.
And then there's a full line of people and he goes, oh,
right this way. And he just slashed your GEO and I
onto the ride without
the glasses.
How do I make this go away?
What's the fastest way
to make this? Everyone is
taller than me and madder than me
and hotter than me
temperature wise.
Someone will clock me in the face
if I don't wrap this up quickly.
This is
so for a while, I'm like,
that was my day. I don't know if I have
time to get on anything else.
Luckily I did but that's essentially
I missed what is probably a really
good wooden roller coaster. Yeah, you could have waited.
Yeah. Because I had
so much greed for lapping up
eye on fish that
it blinded me to the potential
problems of my journey.
I never made it there and I'm stuck
here on shitty old Earth. It made
you appreciate your wife and child
more. I took them for granted
thinking about that. Big
play to eye on fish.
Here I was thinking so much
about my love and admiration
for Conrad Reynolds. I didn't
stop to think that A, Conrad Reynolds
might be me and 80 other people
depending on Erwin's
count. And B,
I have a wife who is
every bit as valorous as Conrad
Reynolds could ever be. You know what they
say? They say
give a man an eye on fish.
He'll eat for a day
and teach a man
to eye on fish and he'll eat for a lifetime.
So what does that mean for me?
I guess. It means you
have to find your own. It's what you just said.
Your own Conrad Reynolds and your own
life is more important than
someone else's journey to meet
Conrad Reynolds. The eye on fish are
the rewards that I
reap when I, or once I've
sowed them. Which do I do first? Yes.
What do you do when it's fish?
There's gotta be, there's a lot in the
Bible about fish so it's probably
I could clear up a lot about
this I think if I,
I need to go to church
clearly. It's what I'm learning.
Future church. Well
that's that. So if you can imagine
by the end of all this I had some not so
great feelings about Great America.
It also came to pass that at the
end of the day I was like I cannot
wait to not have dinner here.
Oh the joy of
not standing in a crowded subway
line that's twice as expensive
as, so I
we got out of there and went to Italy
and it was glorious especially in
the wake of all that.
And I
don't know. I
at this point I
Jason you were
saying maybe you want to
go. Maybe you gotta try that new coaster.
How do you feel after everything I told you?
I don't know you know it is
kind of a morbid
interest in the way
very much of like
there's like one or two
charming things, there's one or two like
really new things and
the rest is very similar to a
dying mall. Yeah. Yeah.
And not a fancy mall. It straddles
two city lines and it's two different
pay grades. One of those old shitty ones.
No Italy. There definitely is no Italy.
There's a big Michelada station
and
a very chaotic
Starbucks. I'm starting to
think that I don't know
my final
statement on all this. I've complained a lot
about this place. I had
some fun. It was nice to watch Erwin
and I guess Erwin you really made it the day
special. At the end
of the day, even after all that, what I
would say
I would still recommend, get up
to Santa Clara, go to NorCal,
get up there, take your family
up there. Then turn around,
go way south and get to
Gilroy Gardens, a
vastly superior theme park.
Wow. Incredibly superior theme park.
What a tease. No mere garlic
theme park is this. It's
wonderful. It's great at Gilroy
Gardens. If you could only pick one,
of course go to Gilroy Gardens.
And you know what? The only way to make
it better, somebody from
Gilroy Gardens offer poorer Erwin a job.
I know that's not his real name, but figure out a name
that's close. Get him down there.
It's the only way to make the Gilroy Gardens
experience better. Get the best entertainer
they have.
What a great tease for the future.
So that's that. Gilroy Gardens,
incredibly charming place.
We'll talk about it on the second gate. This
place, I might have to say,
do what you're doing. Burn it to the ground
for insurance money. Wow.
If you grew up there and you have nice
memories, I hope that... Go fuck yourself.
Sorry. You had a dumb
childhood and you were
wrong. And we are right.
Scott doesn't want to save Barney Old
Field's Redwood Rally.
Is that even there?
That is an attraction that used to
be called Barney Old Field Speedway.
Barney Old Field?
Yeah, I don't know. I think this is like
their old time
cars.
Also, one of the lands in
that has since changed names, the
land names.
This was very funny to me.
One of the lands used to be called
the Great Midwest Livestock
Exposition and County Fair.
That is
too many words for a theme park
land. I think it's now just NorCal
County Fair. Barney Old Field,
a real guy, a real racer.
How about that?
I hate to say it.
I don't think it's enough to tip
my opinion. I am
going to have to pass at this
time. Am I glad I went up there? Hey, it
helped fuel this trip, which was a wonderful trip.
But so much for the wonder. Gilroy Gardens.
That's going to be on the second gate. As for
this You Survived podcast,
The Ride, thank you for listening.
We walked right into it.
This is Great America. I think this is
we're putting this out, I believe, on 4th of July
weekend, where next
week we'll be off on the main feed.
But in the middle, wet your
appetite with a little
bit of garlic and a little bit of
talking about Gilroy Gardens. And more from
the trip that I had to cut from this,
notably lacking in Chuck E. Cheese
thoughts. Always a bad thing
to not. So if you want
your chuck, you're going to have to go to the second
gate, pal. You're paying for that.
Open them wallets.
These horrible voices we've accumulated.
Mickey Mouse, Chuck E. Cheese.
It does get worse and worse.
Harjo after Harjo. Hey, I'm
chet to like, ehhh.
Yeah. Enjoy
my voice. I sound
like what McKally Coulkin, the Rad Boy,
looks like.
Hey, merch is available
in our Tee Public Store. Find us on the socials
at Podcast The Ride. Go to Podcast
The Ride, the second gate or Club 3
at Patreon.com slash Podcast
The Ride for the previous NorCal
thing for the car wash.
That's on Club 3. Gilroy
Gardens coming to Club
2, second gate. You've never
called it till right now. But again,
my brain's breaking from Rat Boys
and Survivor
Stomps. So, better wrap it up here.
Forever
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott
Gardner, Brett Boehm,
Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our
shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your
podcasts. Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam
and liking our page on
Facebook.
Thanks for watching!