Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, that little screen in front of you, it's not just for playing little ping pong games,
okay?
It's a cockpit on a jet fighter that's pointed at a place called the Information Superhighway.
So if you're a cyber nut like me, strap yourself in, hang on tight and try not to wet yourself.
That's my little intro, that's my little cyber intro for today's podcast.
The podcast is the ride of the cyber gate.
I'm Scott Gardner, cyber Scott Gardner.
Mike, I don't know how to do this fast enough.
I'll just put all those things on.
Mike cyber, yeah, yeah, mainframe, cyber.
Mainframe, Mike Carlson.
Great, mainframe, Mike Carlson and Jason Superhighway then.
Why not?
Yeah, I was going to say jacked in Jason.
Oh, that's good.
Jacked in Jason.
Well, that's the attitude.
That's the grit.
That is the attitude.
This special has that we're talking about today.
It seems very likely like one that you have not heard of, but we're excited to talk about
it.
It's called Cybermania 94, the ultimate gamer awards.
It is just, it is a wonderful two hour mess of cyberpunk and hacker culture and that information
superhighway shit and CD-ROMs and the future is here and the future is now and the craziest
graphics and the most camera moves you've ever seen.
This special is something.
This is a real time capsule, a very specific type of 90s.
It's a masterpiece.
Hell yeah.
I'm so glad you feel the same way.
Yeah, as I kept saying today, I watched it honestly this morning.
I kept saying there's a little treat for me around every turn.
Yeah, there's a new fun thing from all the different things that I like or I'm intrigued
by.
All of a sudden it hits you, oh, it's an old, old actor that suddenly appears or his picture
appears.
There's a younger actor.
All of a sudden there's just some completely head scratching little documentary in the
middle of it about hackers.
You go, what is this?
It's just like every, because these things tend to like, anytime we've done some one
off award show or whatever, you're like, ah, there's some funny stuff in there and we like
it and it's great.
They can drag.
But they can drag.
They certainly drag and you try to find the highlights.
There was just one I already don't remember.
This thing we're talking about today filmed at Universal Studios Hollywood.
So you get your shots, you get your overhead helicopter shots, all that stuff.
I like anything that was shot at Universal Hollywood in the 90s.
But we just watched one that started so strong.
I forget what it was called even.
It was like some Olympics that included every kid from every show of that era.
All the TGIFs and all the Nickelodeons and like the Fox, whatever.
So we're like, oh, we are amped on this thing.
And then it just got a little boring.
Of course it's exciting when they're playing games on the Miami Vice stunt show set.
But after the fourth round of the same thing, you kind of know all the tricks up this thing's
sleeve.
This, we didn't finish it.
This thing, I cannot wait.
It's around every turn.
They keep spicing up.
This is an innovative award show entertaining at all times.
Yeah, you're right.
It doesn't have one thing that it does.
Oh, it's just funny that it drags an old actor out.
We haven't seen.
It's got 10 moves.
If it's a ride, I talk about moments or types of moments.
It has 20 types of moments.
An old person using technology terms wrong or clearly they're using the term and they
don't know what they're talking about.
This happens regularly, but that's not all.
It's so much more.
Yeah.
An impersonator of a famous woman gets burnt in the face.
Why?
What?
Right off the bat.
Pointlessly.
When this thing came on, I didn't think that would happen.
No.
You know, when you first told us this, I think within 15 seconds of you saying it, I went
in, I think when you told us the host, I was like, I'm on board.
And I was like, and then you kept talking about it.
And I think at the time I was like, oh, I don't, I think we're on board.
I don't think he has to sell it to.
And then I realized looking back, I'm like, I think you were just so excited, but didn't
want to spoil any of this because there's some stuff where I was like, not in a million
years would I have expected some of these appearances by people who would be bigger,
people who were big at the time, people who continue to be big.
There's no way to predict.
Like, if you're watching the MTV movie awards from the same year, you maybe know who you're
getting.
You know, who is in big movies at the time or who is gettable or on MTV a lot.
This thing, there's no way to predict.
If you put a gun to my head at every every before every presenter announcement and said,
name a thousand names, I would probably not guess some of who's coming.
I almost think that if you've made it this far here, go watch this.
If you like watching this type of weird and old nostalgia type entertainment of something
you never saw before, actually watch the whole thing before listening to us.
Yes, this one's good.
This is I don't think this is one where we're like rescuing the fun moments.
As we said, it doesn't really drag.
It is really good.
It's on YouTube.
The user is learned to counter easy to find.
And I totally agree.
So then this can be kind of a kind of a talk along.
I absolutely agree.
Go finish it.
Aaron felt that Aaron was devouring this thing.
We could not wait to.
I'm so glad we have more of this special left.
I wanted to drag it out all week.
Yeah, 17 notes.
I want it like 17 bullet points in addition of clips.
I have so many clips.
I have so many.
I assumed you're writing down anything I was having a reaction to it and then I had to
start formatting it because I have to break this up or I'm going to forget.
Yeah, I know.
We're all coming in with the same energy.
It's a pile.
It's confusing, but just like the special itself.
We should clarify.
It is two hours in the YouTube video.
That includes the very good period appropriate 1994 commercials.
Yes, because they bought this other time.
They're all related.
This is all about like a lot of it is video games.
So there will be awards given to games that you know or grew up with unless you're younger
than people.
OK, unless you're a certain age and then you don't know any of it.
But, you know, it's relatively accessible, I think.
And the ads are for big games of the Arab to they're all planned or just about computers
or about movies stemming from video game franchises, which I forgot about.
I somehow never saw that movie.
Me neither. I kind of want to do it.
I want to track it down either.
Yeah, that is that is intriguing to me because I love those.
I spent hours on those video games.
Yeah, in that case, we just spoiled that one.
That is Double Dragon.
The movie with Scott Wolf and directed by a guy who directed most of the big Phil Collins
music videos.
Oh, my God.
Yes. All the credits were great.
He directed Dennis Miller's stand up specials.
It's an insane body of work.
I forgot his name.
By the way, if we haven't had this up, you said Dennis Miller and I'm just like,
Dennis Miller comes up in this fucking thing.
Like, there's so many people who come up in this thing.
Like I was saying before we started, I watched some of it yesterday and then I was going
to bed and I saw I had watched 90 minutes and there were still 30 left.
And that was a negative thing.
I was just like, I can't believe there's more.
Like, it's just kind of pummels you.
Yes, you're exhausted in a good way.
Exciting things.
Theme park day.
Well, let me now attribute all of this excitement to one of our listeners, one of our patrons,
Robert Denby, who alerted us to this.
I don't think even in a pitching an episode way, I don't think that was the intent.
It was related, honestly, to Charles Fleischer, who appears in this and we'll get to that
when it's his time.
But we just talked about Charles Fleischer and the weirdness of Charles Fleischer when
talking about another great special, the Disneyland 35th anniversary.
And thank you, Robert, for the paragraph explaining everything that was to come.
And I just like the phrase Cybermania 94 just jumped out at me and like, huh?
OK, that needs to be meditated on a little more.
And within the just just to say some of what Robert said, and I'll let him introduce
really the first big notable stars who call to you.
There's an amazing attempt at a video game award show called Cybermania 94, hosted by
Leslie Nielsen and Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
Did A.I. create this for me to watch?
That is exactly that is something that we said.
Like by the time a certain band who we talk about all the time appeared out of nowhere.
Erin and I said, I'm worried that we fell into an A.I.
trap and that it is being live created for us.
And we especially started thinking that when an award was accepted and two names were
said by whoever was accepting the award and Erin said, I know those names, my parents
know those people.
They were people like in the periphery of Warner Brothers.
They were like media executives at the time and they were thanked in a speech.
And Erin texted her mom and said, do you know these people?
And one of them, she said, yes, this guy, really nice guy.
Why are you asking? Is it because that person died last week?
Huh? What?
Somebody that Erin has never mentioned or or like once maybe has like and this person
passed away last week.
What do you mean? That made that got me freaked out.
Maybe we are. And look, Robert, thank you for this.
And you're suggesting unless you are an A.I.
creation who's trying to snare us in some kind of A.I.
trap, I don't think so.
I trust you. You're a second gate subscriber.
So I trust you.
Or it's like it's like we are living in a simulation and the simulation realizes that
we've kind of like we're getting towards the end of YouTube crap that we haven't seen.
Yeah, it's like we've got to start just creating stuff for because they're going to
lose us. We'll stop watching.
We're almost out. We've almost fully.
This keg is tapped.
So we think until something like Cybermania comes.
This is a trick by the Google Corporation.
Giant Net is going to come over this garage and get us shit.
Shit. Well, this is the kind of like cyber paranoia that much of the special warns about.
And that is the tone of a lot of the games of this era.
But let me we'll get back to Leslie and J.T.T.
But another thing, Robert said, Cybermania 94 is a great time because it's trying to be a serious
celebration of video games when a lot of people thought FMV was the future.
But it has Kids Choice Awards sensibilities and bizarre interstitials to keep the audience's
attention, including a guy in a balloon suit who just wanders around stage while Leslie
Nielsen is talking.
I. Yeah, that's a great description.
Why does that happen?
I've now that I've watched it, I don't have any further understanding of why it happens.
No, because I was watching on my computer and I was like, oh, is there like a famous person
maybe? And I looked and I was like, I don't think so.
No. And once his balloon is popped, I didn't further recognize the balloon man.
No. Yeah. There are famous people later that do a little bit famous to me and Jason.
Yeah, I assume they would be.
Yeah, not to me.
Very excited. Again, that's a late third quarter, fourth quarter.
Oh, my God. They keep them coming.
I got a clip from the last sentence.
It's said in this thing.
It never stops. So thank you again, Robert.
And Robert mentioned something called FMV.
And I have to admit ignorance on this.
I didn't know what FMV was a phrase also used by my friend Tyler, who I sent this to
as a big CD-ROM guy who as he was watching this, he's like, I know every single game
that is being played. So he was excited about it.
But I had to I'm a dummy.
I wasn't paying attention in this era.
I feel like I missed the boy.
I wish I knew the CD-ROM era better.
But FMV is full motion video.
And so while some of these are more typical games, you know, like Street Fighter and
Mortal Kombat, there's also a lot of games that you've never heard of because the CD-ROM
era ended not too long after this.
I guess just general kind of Internet world superseded that.
And the CD-ROM boom went bust.
But full motion video is like if it is interactive, but there is also there are also
videos, usually very small and very tiny boxes that move the game forward.
If I am remembering correctly, it moves very choppy.
Like it looks a little it's very a thing that'll come up later.
It's very Revolution X.
Big time. You know.
Well, and also like if you if you guys ever have you made GIFs, have you like gone in
some GIF creator program?
It's when you're like trying to make the file small and you have to limit colors,
they kind of end up looking like this.
Like a lot. You can tell there is not the full wide range of color information that
a usual video would have.
I find the aesthetic very charming and I love seeing a big pile of that stuff here.
Yeah, I do, too. And I remember at the time being very like every people.
This would get people like if I was at a friend's house or they were at mine or be
in stores and be like, wow, look, a little movie on the computer.
Yeah, through like the 90s, I think the idea was like, OK, this is the future of like
video games and entertainment, which I guess is sort of like a way to do VR, which is
just shooting it. It's not graphics.
It's just actual video. Yeah.
Because like the sky, we talked about the Scottie Pippen Sega CD game, which had a
lot of like in like actual shot footage of Scottie Pippen.
Right. And I played a game called Star Trek Borg, which was just an episode of Star
Trek Voyager, essentially.
But then you would click on parts of the screen to decide what you were going to do.
Oh, so like good.
It was kind of I mean, it was kind of cool because it had John Delancey who plays Q
and he was like being like snarky toward you.
And then he'd ask you to do something or ask you what you wanted to do and you click
around. Oftentimes, I didn't know what I should be doing, but it was still kind of
cool to play like it did kind of live up to the idea of you're like in the game.
But ultimately, I don't think ultimately it wasn't so satisfying for like versus a
video game. Yeah, it was an interesting time because like even watching this, you can
see people like what is a CD realm?
Like what how far can we push this?
Should we try this? Should we try?
Should we try more of these M&MV videos or should we try more like gameplay gameplay?
Yeah, they're figuring it out.
And it's also a pretty crucial juncture, one that I don't think I was fully aware
happened, which is as with any big media trend, when when do you pull the trigger
and get celebrities in on this?
When do you start using recognizable actors?
And that's what happens.
That's what's happening here.
And I don't know how long it lasted for, but it really flashed me to how like it's
really it's just like every flash in the pan.
There's always the like and it's going to be the next big thing you'll see.
Oh, you'll see everybody's getting in on it, whether it's when all the celebrities
start doing podcasts and then abandon the field to die or the NFT.
No, it's all about NFTs.
And then by the end of the year, it's not even close to all that NFT.
Like we've lived through so many of the quibbys.
It's all about it's going to be all about quibbys.
Yeah, all about videos you watch in the bank line.
And it just just reminds you like, boy, I guess it's been this way for a long time.
There's always an insane boom.
And then the technology is left standing and it just sort of becomes integrated in
much more.
Yeah, somewhat reasonable way.
Friendly. Yeah. And like all of the things that are specifically for this media kind
of fade away and die.
You can sort of feel it happen.
Like, I don't I don't think we're I think things will be happening with VR and
Oculus and all that.
But like I remember a lot of people I knew took general meetings at some like we're
you know, we're doing interactive comedy videos for the Oculus.
Remember all those everybody?
Yeah, I do.
I'm sure you're all still in stitches that you're I don't even know if they got made.
And we're all rewatching them.
For sure.
And of course, with all these things.
Well, and as with your relatedly, aesthetically and the era like Disney quest, you
know, of course you're going back.
You're definitely doing it again.
Yeah.
Of course.
I think well, yeah, we have seen a lot of these, as you said, NFTs, VR, all of this.
We're seeing AI right now, which is now become clear.
It kind of sucks.
It pretty much sucks.
And there's a big article, I think just this week, a giant article of the sheer
amount of human labor that goes into, quote unquote, training these VR systems.
Oh, OK.
Are you are AI?
AI. Yeah.
I was an article about like AI school, essentially.
I feel like I saw it, but didn't read it.
I think it's it's a thing where it's like being farmed out to other countries.
And it's like this computer isn't learning.
Humans are doing massive amounts of data entry.
Yeah.
To try and like get the gist of something.
But I'm sure those humans doing the data entry are being fairly compensated and treated well.
Oh, yeah.
Pennies on the dollar.
That's a nice phrase.
People say that in a complimentary way.
People love a penny. It's lucky.
Yeah, we just I mean, I'm sure we've all seen the AI secret invasion credits,
which is like, oh, this looks like talk shit.
Like this looks so ugly.
And it's like this is it.
I is a new this.
So you're right. I thought about that.
And it's the crazy thing on that is that Marvel has published countless comics
called Secret Invasion, pages and pages of art that they could have just pulled from.
And it's just like, oh, no, you got this weird goo.
Our abstract muck.
Yeah. Well, to be fair, look, I from to my eyes, the Marvel films have always celebrated weird goo.
That's right. That's what every one of them is to me.
But you're right. This is even worse looking goo than usual.
This is even worse.
And it's always funny when Disney, a company that's so like hyper focused on their image
and their family friend, they're like they just step in it.
Or is this like you are missing the motion of the you're missing the ball so hard on this?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, it's it's almost a relief to see this in this AI era that suddenly that doesn't feel like
you were not talking about AI all the time two months ago.
And now it is just all that we I hope that this is a flash in the pan.
And look, I will admit, I don't like any of it.
And we're fighting against it with the writer's strike right now.
But would I like a fully AI generated award show?
Absolutely. Yeah.
I would. If only they would do something.
If only there was something as fun and aesthetically bizarre as Cyber Mania 94.
Yeah, there's not there's there's there's a couple I don't want to be in.
I'm not going to be like I love AI or anything, but there are some Twitter accounts that make like
fake AI 80s movies.
And I go, have you seen these?
Not those now. I go, oh, this looks good.
There's stills. I mean, there's stills, but they don't look they don't look as gooey as
what we're talking about with the secret invasion.
But yeah, there's select select ways that AI will just be in our lives within the next decade.
If we can have it around a little bit, but kind of like supervised by smart people.
Sure. Then that's that's how we should be doing it.
You can make online bill pay like a little less annoying.
Like if you could just automate this, you know.
Sure. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't want AI paying my bills, but I don't either.
But I'm just like, what if it's working to earn the money and pay your bill?
Oh, sure. Then maybe like to get what do they call that?
The games where like and you earn you earn money when you play this this mobile game.
Oh, yeah. I don't know.
What are the? Yeah, I know what you're saying.
I've seen those before, but I'm going to I'm trying to find this AI just to see.
They're called they're called sure things is what they're called.
My investment you can make my ticket to the top is what I like to call them now.
So, yeah. All right.
This this show, November 5th, 1994, a magical day, a magical evening.
This is put together by the Academy of Interactive Arts and Sciences,
which I guess is a real thing. It is still a real thing.
I think they do a different award show now.
They did not keep doing the manias.
Apparently, there was a Cyber Mania 95, but it was broadcast online exclusively
and it received much less numbers than it reminds you of it.
Is this not kind of like, oh, do the streaming movies not make us
the same amount of money or get the same amount of eyeballs?
And now I heard two hundred and ninety million people watched Red Notice.
Yeah, yeah. Well, that and Spencer Confidential.
Definitely I saw that on the list.
I know we've all been talking about Spencer Confidential.
Let's all just think about our favorite moment and star from Spencer Confidential,
a movie that we definitely know the existence of.
I mean, Robert, just the name Robert Cope's got to be in that too.
Yeah, he might be. What is it?
Oh, my God. Well, Spencer is Mark Wahlberg,
and it has Post Malone as someone named Squeeb.
Also, that feels very CD-ROM to me.
It feels like the name, the kind of generic title
that feels like a movie, but is a little bit off and somebody with a weird,
you know, bleep, bloop kind of name. Yeah.
They might have stolen it.
This might have been a CD-ROM in development and Waldo stole it.
Anyways, so this thing.
I mean, if I was skeptical at all,
my skepticism went away when I saw the first shot of the award show,
which is the devil starts with the devil
who like forms out of flame and you're like, oh, this is where we're starting.
This is some boring shot of Dorothy Chandler Pavilion.
Kicking it off with the devil.
And then you're and then immediately a title that says
the gate to the mind's eye. Yes, yes.
I love those minds. I compilation these compilations of insane
at the time cutting edge now, weird old CGI.
And then you just watch Minds Eye stuff.
You watch a digital knight flying through a flying through a tunnel.
And he's like he's like kind of a floaty mermaid creature.
But the back half of his body are like
chrome whisking tongs.
They're spinning around.
It's the weirdest. Whoa. All right.
We're off to the races here. I love it.
Hey, it's still the future to me.
So real to me. Oh, yes.
I'm still I'm waiting.
I like I want the early 90s future.
And who could object to it?
I am surprised of all the apps I use on my phone.
No one has like tried like, you know, a reminders app or a
notes app or something that involves you soaring over a digital city.
Get to do that.
It's like a big journey just to like punch in dentist four o'clock.
Yeah, milk, eggs, bread.
There was a whole everything, I think, starts out in a like,
oh, we're going to do it in a fun way.
And then it ends up just in like a very functional way, which is almost like
there was a program called Microsoft Bob in like 1996 or seven years.
Know what I'm talking about? No.
Microsoft Bob was something that came with our computer.
And it was like an animated like living room.
And there was a little dog, I think, in the room.
I could be wrong, but there was like a there was like I like cute icons and stuff.
And the idea was that you were going to like put your schedule in and you log
on to Microsoft Bob and maybe put like a CD in a drive and log in, click,
go into like the living room.
And then like you would like have all your stuff.
I mean, I'm misremembering some parts of it, but that the basic gist of it
was this like cute little way to organize your life.
We had something like as my family, we were like, all right,
we're going to get a home computer.
We're going to commit to it.
You have to be very careful with this.
You got to be very respectful with this.
My brother did do something to it that made a crash.
And eventually they got it working again.
But it ran, I believe it was Windows three point one.
So right before Windows 95 and it had a like very
it had a different kind of home screen that you could toggle
between different icons or a house.
Like each you would go through a house in each room would have
like games, software, you know, digital houses.
Yeah. So this is what I'm showing you guys right now.
You would go to this door and it would be like a knocker
and there would be a little dog in the corner.
And that was your dog. So that's your living room.
And then, you know, you'd go to your letter writer.
You could write a letter inside the program.
Checks, your checkbook, your financial guide.
You could go to an Internet like an explorer, a different.
Yeah. Well, you would have a calendar, you'd have a clock
and it would all be a fireplace.
You have yourself at the digital fireplace and you could like
customize, I think, the room a little a little bit.
This dog's giving you tips and hints.
Yes. So this was all like, OK, we're going to make all of this
sort of functional stuff fun and you're going to go into your little
digital room.
But of course, after a few years, people like this is a lot of work.
Yeah. So why not? Yeah.
Straight to my calendar, to the calendar.
By the way, your brother, did he break the computer
by creating the babe of his dreams within the digital realm
and then putting on his helmet and then like getting getting all the cyber way
with her and then the computer burst into steam and smoke?
No, I think he just typed something in DOS.
MS-DOS. Oh, damn.
Yeah. No one. Unfortunately, no cyber babes. Yeah.
OK, so intro has happened and then we enter the stage and it's at Universal
Hollywood. It's in the Conan, the barbarian stage,
much like Horror Hall of Fame.
And they use it.
It's it's like most of that stage is just so intact.
So there's big like stone snakes and there's lasers.
There's big, chuggy rock music.
And we welcome our hosts, Leslie Nielsen and Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
But like both in tuxes.
I like that, that it's all this like, yeah, don't go, don't go.
But then still just tuxedos for everybody.
Right. And it's also the oldest man that's the youngest actor.
Yeah. I mean, I guess Walter Mathau and Jack Lumbin are still alive, but he's,
you know, he's 70s at this point.
Picture of Mathau hosting this. Yeah.
Yeah. But the biggest movie star, the biggest old movie star
and one of the biggest young movies, these are movie star.
They really got relevant.
This is the year of the Lion King.
Naked Gun still right in the rear view. Yeah.
I it's I think it's a great host.
Love the host.
Yeah. Them together is very funny.
The classic comedy duo.
I don't know if there's any particular chemistry,
but I do like watching them together.
Anti chemistry.
I'm sure they got along. Sure. Yeah.
They do a good job individually.
Like it makes sense. Yes.
You know, JTT is so slick.
He is so slick together.
Charming kid.
His tux looks cool.
He's got this kind of like Southwest tie cut.
Yeah. I'm talking about how I got to I got to wear a tux
finally at a wedding soon.
I might go in and say, hey, give me the JTT.
JTJTT, I will say this, has so much inherent charisma.
And we haven't talked a ton about JTT.
I will say if you were just listening to his delivery,
he does have sort of like a bad early 90s kid delivery.
As far as things.
Dad, dad, dad. Yeah.
Dad, dad, dad, dad.
It's so funny now, because now I feel like any kid actor
has to be able to enunciate perfectly.
They're like these Disney Channel star kids.
They sound like adults.
There's none of that weird like
like that's as charming as a kid can be. Right.
Now you're just you got to be right at right to it.
You have to be just as good as an adult delivering comedy
and pausing, knowing what to do.
But yeah, JTT, I was like, oh, yeah, I can see JTT's charisma here,
but he sounds like a kid doing an award show.
It makes me miss that.
It makes me miss the the kid charisma ceiling.
We used to allow this.
And I think we drive kids crazier making them go above the ceiling.
Of course, because they have to like be adults or much earlier.
Yeah. Yeah. Too much.
Well, they're also like also kids are just on YouTube and like, yeah,
extremely popular on YouTube when they're six in certain cases or younger, probably.
Yeah. Yeah.
They get very polished at a very specific type of delivery.
Yeah. Some of it.
Some of it's OK.
Some of them are pretty good.
Yeah, a lot of them are good.
And then some of them do transition to like actual act like I.
Well, they were already actually acting.
Probably. But like Timothy Chalamet wasn't one of his big things was
was viewing like Xbox Game Controller.
Maybe I really I don't know.
I like that.
Yeah. Can we look at that?
You can find it.
Much old Chalamet. Wow. Sure.
Hmm. Was this like Tim?
It's Tim O3.
And then it's the two E's, but they're backward.
There's three.
I would love it when he was I didn't know he was a content creator.
I didn't know that either. Wow. Just like us.
Yeah. OK.
Well, there's hope for him starting really young and really handsome.
And there's hope for us.
Yeah, we're a couple of years now younger than he is when he started. Yeah.
Yeah. OK.
And then now to boot up CyberMedia 94,
a very special guest, please welcome the first lady of the United States.
And then a hell of a chief plays.
And then a Hillary Clinton lookalike comes out
and she tries to hit a button on a computer,
on a big desktop computer that will start CyberMedia.
But Leslie notices that it is not plugged in.
And I'm loving this because this is some classic naked gun.
Yeah. You can tell exactly what they're going like.
It was always impersonators of the big public figures.
Love this live on a stage at Universal Studios. Love it.
So he plugs in a wire and you can't really tell what's wrong with it
in particular, but maybe it's a surge.
There's too much power all at once.
Because after kind of an odd delay, then there's a big explosion
that's kind of clunky and seems to just actually hurt the lady.
Yeah. The first lady. Yeah. Yeah.
It's very just like it's it's kind of alarming, I would say,
you know, in a not funny way.
And she real quickly turns around and smears like grease paint on her face.
But like at the cartoon bomb.
Yeah. Yes. Yes.
I do like I like that.
Since everybody's fine, I'm allowed to like it.
But it is. But the way just how how big it is and how close it is to her.
For a minute, you're like, is this just the was this bunch of people who hate
Hillary's? It's just like we're going to work if we burn up Hillary on the stage.
I mean, I guess that's what they were going.
I don't know if they hated her at the time, but certainly they felt like
she was a funny celebrity to hurt.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
I guess she's only mildly hurt cartoonishly.
Yeah. Yeah. Like coyote style. Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
This is later the venue for the Bill and Ted
topical show where you could see it going further.
Where I don't know what would it have been like that?
Well, you know, that she gets like caught in a sharknado.
Yeah, that's better. Yeah.
Or like and it's and some sharks went down on her.
Leslie Nielsen swings his arms too wide and he's holding a club.
The car safety feature.
And he like smacks her off the stage with a club.
Oh, that's a good one. Yeah.
Oh, they should. Yeah.
If they'd some if the plugging in didn't work and then the backup was the clapper.
But the clapper is too powerful.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
What if Angelina Jolie came out and she stuck her leg out from the Oscar
dress and tripped her?
How about that? The famous leg? Yeah.
You know, that doesn't say that is inaccurate.
What they would Bill and Ted would have done. Yeah.
Oh, and then we do get a very good then things kind of taper off.
And those are the deal.
So says, I sure hope she has health insurance.
Hello. And then you and then they introduced the show.
And there's so much smoke from that gag that you can't quite see them
and they can't quite see the screen.
And what you get here is really, you know what?
Why this is such a great use of Leslie Nielsen is now we've,
you know, he's becoming a little too aware, like an AI has learned too much.
Yeah. By the end of by Naked Gun 3, we've gotten progressively broader every time.
And I still like Naked Gun 3.
But, you know, there's a little bit of a taper off in how much they work
because he's he starts to think I'm funny and which is making silly faces
and being a little too broad.
And then once he's out of the Zucker realm and we're doing spy
hard and wrongfully accused, we're way off the map.
It's not working anymore.
But here we've put Leslie Nelson right back where he belongs,
which is reading a bunch of stuff he doesn't really understand. Yes. Yeah.
So he's funny again. Yes.
And he tried like he kind of like smiles and laughs sometimes at the awkwardness too.
But yes, he is completely out of his depth here
in regards to the all the subject matter that he's talking about.
I'm going to play a clip that refers to something we'll loop back to.
But just as an example of that, this is the one I have wanted.
This is one of Leslie's introductions.
Viva Las Vegas.
The city of Las Vegas is now shedding its cable
or rather as gambling image for one of computer gaming
from two bit hoods to gigabyte hard drives from colorful
sociopathic characters like Bugsie Siegel to colorful
sociopathic characters like Goro the monster.
Ralphie. All right.
Yes. I don't know what I am.
Goro the monster.
Gigabytes.
Hard drives. Gigabytes.
Changing it's from cable to for gambling gambling to.
I mean, it is. It's and we've just done Naked Gun 3 where the Oscars get mucked up
because he's doing everything and he's Phil Donahue and he can't read the teleprompter.
Like it's that live on stage. It's great. Right.
Yeah. He's trying to get the words right.
Yeah. Yeah.
Or also, I like that they are so to pair with the characters like Bugsie Siegel.
I think Bugsie Siegel had been dead for a good 40 or 50 years at that point.
Well, yeah, he's a classic reference. Yeah.
That was I'm saying.
He's saying now that used to be Bugsie Siegel.
Now it's Goro the monster.
Goro the monster.
Goro the monster is as iconic was as iconic then as Spencer confidential is today.
So Spencer confidential.
Do you know what Goro the monster is?
Goro is from Mortal Kombat.
Oh, he's the four.
You see the movie Mortal Kombat? Yeah. OK.
Oh, so it's not a Las Vegas thing.
That's them saying that now that there's gaming in Vegas,
that now that we don't think of Bugsie, we think of Goro.
Yeah. Have you ever seen the first Mortal Kombat?
No, that feels like you should see that too.
The movie. Yeah. OK.
I think you should see it. I think you would like it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Because it's got Christopher Lambert just doing this voice the whole time.
And he's got a funny wig on.
And Goro is the bad guy.
There's Shang Tsung and Goro.
And I only know really OG Mortal Kombat stuff.
But Goro has four arms or six arms?
I forget. I forget.
You have four or six arms. And he is a puppet.
He's a giant puppet.
So it kind of doesn't work.
And they clearly have to work the fight around his limitations.
So Johnny Cage, who's like the cool actor guy, fights Goro.
And it's gross. Goro is gross.
Goro is hideous.
Oh, boy. Yeah.
I think you would really I think there's there would be stuff in there
you would like.
Well, I got a double feature with double dragon, maybe.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's perfect.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's really good.
As if I can watch two movies in a row and you might have lost that ability with parenting.
I that Mortal Kombat brings up a good point, which is
hell of a year for video games.
But the ones that I don't know about you, but I would say are like
foundational games that people still go back to or get on other platforms.
Stuff that's mentioned like Mortal Kombat, NBA Jam,
Doom. Yeah.
Those don't sweep these awards.
Yeah, true.
And the big ones are up for these.
The big ones that are nominated are, yeah, still feel like they loom really large.
And yet, yeah, it's a lot of a lot more obscure ones.
That's definitely true.
Mortal Kombat is a hundred Mortal Kombat's a new Mortal Kombat.
Like one is announced where it's like almost a prequel, I think, to the whole Mortal Kombat.
OK, so that yeah, the lasting power of some of these things is pretty crazy for them.
Yeah, not to the big ones are the best game award nominees are
are Doom, NBA Jam, Mortal Kombat, Super Street Fighter two and Myst.
And Myst was obviously very of its era, but it's like but we all know it.
I feel like that's like the one I didn't play a lot of these.
But I remember I don't I couldn't tell you one detail about it,
but I remember the vibe.
I remember getting very lost in it.
And that's sort of like that.
I don't know that what that CD-ROM feeling of just like
wandering and there's objects and and this was the mist was good.
And it gave you texture.
It gave you mystery.
Yeah, I think I have it on my laptop.
You can buy it in the Apple App Store.
Oh, really? Like five bucks or something.
You can buy it for like a tenth of the price or something.
Wow. Well, I mean, what this whole thing is about
is really just introducing you to opening you up to that.
It's it's not just games, you know, there's there's so much that
the consoles can do and computers can do.
And a lot of this is conveyed with an extremely inexplicable piece
hosted by by poor man's Dennis Leary.
I say that with both the guy in mind and also the style.
I mean, every interstitial video piece in this thing, it is like it is.
The camera is always zooming.
The camera is always shaking.
Yeah, it is always touching there.
It's that thing where it flips around and then there's a color tint
on the other side and there's a sound effect for everything.
Sometimes it's like a hannah barbaro.
And then like stock footage will illustrate something.
An old bomb going off.
It's the most this is such a celebration of hyperactive editing.
Yeah. And I almost feel like this is the like sometimes you see parodies of it
and then you watch something old and you go, oh, I can see.
It's maybe not as extreme as I remember it.
Not this whole special.
This whole special is like so aggressively that style of 90s in your face.
Yeah. Like this is the most 90s thing I can recall watching in a way.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. So relentlessly 90s, but not in that really specific.
It's it's like dark, grimy 90s.
It's as you get there's this like if you were doing, you know,
90s night on the cruise ship, you might be like a more neon
say by the bell thing. Right.
But I remember a lot of this.
I definitely remember a lot of like the Internet is coming.
Computers are coming and it's scary and it's like all green.
And we're zooming in and out.
And we're not just filming a person.
We're filming the monitor with a feed of the person.
And we're zooming in and out of that.
We're like it's it's about media and multimedia, man.
Yeah. Staring sitting in a comp, USA, staring at like a display computer
that is just you're not going to be able to do with this.
The display computer is just playing a loop.
OK, you're not going to be able to touch that now.
Like that will do nothing.
It's just set to play this loop of zooming over a digital city.
OK, yeah. Yeah.
And it's going to cost thousands of dollars for you to get anywhere near this.
But buckle it because it's coming. It is coming.
So if you're not, you know, you can't afford it right now.
But when it when it is here, if you're not ready, you're fucking you're dead.
You're gone.
Kill you.
You don't understand this advertising.
You will be ordered into Comp USA and you will be put into some kind of machine
and you will be sliced to bits.
It's another thing where it's like we're trying to sell you on the idea of like
what the Internet will do, what can do in video games,
what future video games you'll play.
And it's like, by the way, you're going to kill you.
You're fucked.
Do you understand that the Internet's coming and we will dismember you?
You don't know. Yeah.
Yeah. Yes.
And how any of this was supposed to if really what needs the like hurl
it needs to be gotten over is your parents buying a computer.
Cybermania 94 is not going to help.
No, keep them scared.
Yeah, really?
The this the first PSA really is a couple of things.
One, it seems like it's about to tell you not to huff paint like,
and you don't want to huff paint.
That'll damage your brain.
Like the other thing is it's got this insecurity
like video games and comic books.
They have never shaken this where they're still doing like
and we're not just for kids anymore, you know?
Yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of PR going on during this award show.
They view this as the public coming out for our industry.
So we got a lot to explain.
Yes. And I think we have with video games, like video games, still
video games, pro wrestling.
There's all these different things that are still thought of as like porno
in a way when like especially video games is like way more successful
than movies and TV.
Billions of dollars.
Amount of money and the amount of like different things like rules,
union stuff that should now be implemented for the video game industry.
Yeah, like from people who actually program stuff to the voice
talent and writers and stuff.
I hear that there's some video games that have actually been played more
than people have watched Spencer confidential.
Oh, really?
Seems like that doesn't add up in my head, but it doesn't sound right.
But I guess it doesn't sound right.
Here's some of this this leery esk man.
There's a whole universe of interactive media available today
that'll let you do anything from learning French and a box and piloting a starship.
We the people of this show must try spark balls, please.
Does it? Shatner.
Ray Steller Shatner.
We've all heard him talk.
That is exactly how he talks.
Yes.
Did he dove that part?
Yeah.
That also that's all like black and white and with a blue tint and a boxing ring.
And that that tone you just heard listener, imagine that for five straight minutes.
That is such a long piece.
At some point, there's a reference to how like, you know, it used to be that,
you know, you do it for you,
play video game console or arcade game for 25 cents a pop.
And then two pieces of toast come out of a toaster.
And 25 cents is burnt into the toast.
What is this? A shoot had to be done for that.
That's just one little part.
They had to get the little kitchen corner and the toaster.
And that's just one of 500 cutaways in this entire thing.
This is so you compare this to an episode of comedians in cars getting coffee.
And, you know, you can see the straight line from how we got there
with all those inserts of the coffee being made.
And, you know, this is obviously like they started in a more aggressive place.
Now it's in a very calming place to calm you.
Yes. Yeah.
These cutaways are like as they feel as related as the
the coffee that Jerry and friends aren't drinking.
Of course.
Stars start to appear.
Well, can I say, do we did they put this impression in on purpose?
Oh, yeah. I don't know.
I don't know, because Bill Shatner, William Shatner is doing
the voiceover on this special when he announces categories.
That is a part I didn't want to tell you guys.
I wanted you to learn that to experience that on your own.
I got so excited when I heard the man's voice.
He's never really and he's uncredited.
Never. It's just a subtle thing that it's Shatner
reading a bunch of copy, a little like one sentence explainers of video games.
And he sounds angrier and angrier as this goes on.
A lot of the onstage, the presenters that get
feel like they have contempt in their voice.
For it's like they don't understand it.
And you get your gigabytes and mo mo dams like, you know, they
they didn't get prepped at all.
Like, you know, can we just do a little of William Shatner
announcing the best portable nominee?
Yes, please. Because this is just so great.
So I love this.
There's a couple of great things about this.
Can we hear that?
For the best portable are Aladdin.
Join one of Disney's most popular characters on a breathtaking journey
through fire, sand and air.
Wario land, Super Mario land.
Wario Super Mario.
World to explore and he's charging by the hour.
No life to this.
He's charging by the hour.
Just don't worry, he does.
Hold on, let me see if he gets out. Skip to.
He announces and home alone.
And then he says the wrong name for that.
You know what I'm talking about? No, no, no, no.
But Gameboy Donkey Kong.
He announces this game as Gameboy Donkey Kong.
Gameboy Donkey Kong. That is not the name of the game.
But it's probably how it was listed.
But nobody corrected him. Just snip that out.
There's a number of times where the reading of the nominees
and the text on screen do not match.
Yes. And so, yeah, he is just he sounds madder as they go along.
There's one where you can feel the very like the like annoyingness
of the copywriting, like he has the right energy for some of it.
Like the line he says in that one is he's big, he's mean, and he eats bananas.
Nuff said they made him say no.
You got an esteemed actor made him say no.
I feel like I've I've talked to someone who is directed.
I've talked to a couple of people who've directed him.
And can you imagine that he is somewhat of a difficult?
Well, you heard the outtakes.
Oh, wait, what is that famous outtakes?
Oh, I think it's a documentary of some kind. Yeah.
You see, it's incredible.
I mean, he's just I think he's a guy who doesn't suffer fools
and just wants to do his thing and not be noted.
And he is very aware that there is a thing that you want out of him.
And the thing is this I do, Shatner do that shit thing that is not real.
So he has to deal with directors who probably won't look him in the eye
because they grew up watching him and like, could you just do that thing
where your voice goes up and down and you are still still to them?
I is that what you want me to be?
That's what the outtake is.
The guy tries to know him, but I don't remember.
Guys should maybe I'll just I'll play it and I'll cut it if it's if it doesn't go
because I don't have this like a perfectly queued up.
But yeah, it's so it's so wonderful. Yeah.
OK, I'll cut this.
This is William Shatner,
and I would like to invite you to take a journey with me into the 21st century.
So take the next few minutes and listen very closely.
You'll be amazed at what you hear. OK.
Um, can there be a little more excitement in the beginning?
It's so scary.
It sounded like really laid down, really super laid back.
Well, I'm I'm I'm saying,
OK, I'll try and do that.
That's to take to.
This is William Shatner,
and I would like to invite you to take a journey with me into the 21st century.
So take the next few minutes and listen very closely.
Well, speak up.
And maybe you better do it.
Do it the way you hear it.
Tell me, do it for me at all.
I mean, just don't give him a read.
Don't give him a read.
Zasting him, though, he's trapped.
He's doing it.
You to take a journey with me into the 21st century.
So take the next few minutes and listen very closely.
You'll be amazed at what you hear.
Is that the way you'd like me to do it?
OK, ready? This is William Shatner.
And I would like to invite you to take a journey with me into the 21st century.
So take the next few minutes and listen very closely.
You'll be amazed at what you hear.
OK, so I think that came pretty close.
This is the scariest shit.
No, no, I was I believe that you asked that was about the way you did it.
I wasn't just.
God, this isn't worth it. Move on.
I insist.
Now, what I want you to do is on pay.
Is that a satisfactory to you?
I should have just kept my mouth shut.
No, because if your mouth were open, you'd have popped some pills in them.
So do the next paragraph for page two.
Well, I don't know. I really don't want to.
Because I think you're actually have a better, much better.
No, I don't think I do.
I would like to hear you read the second paragraph so I can do it that way.
You know, I really felt I looked at the different things you did.
I really like the first one.
No, I like it better the way you did.
Oh, please. Please replay.
All right. All right.
That's yeah, I think that's his thing.
He like tries to he tries to snare you.
Yeah, you'd be like he presents a little like a pit for you to fall in.
Yes, I think I heard a story where he like did an entire session
with a Scottish accent to see as like a test to see like,
will this person stand up to me and tell me not to do a Scottish accent?
If he's a man, he will.
Everyone hates him.
The original Star Trek.
Walter Koenig, a couple of days ago,
who played Chekhov on the original Star Trek, tweeted about how he liked
William Shatner's performance on Boston Legal.
But the first part of the tweet said Bill Shatner is not a friend.
But, jeez, he had to say that he had to say it.
I could not say it. Yeah.
Here's I don't think he's right to behave that way.
But those first two takes he did were pretty good.
I know. Yes.
That shows you why not to give the line reading.
He's a pro. Yeah, that is why did he do it.
Did that guy fall in that trap?
Here's this is my favorite thing he says in the show.
Return to Zork.
Your world is falling apart and everyone is counting on you.
Yeah, very good.
He saved the underground.
Return to Zork. Return to Zork. Return to Zork.
Just Shatner saying Wario.
Yeah, I'm like, this is worth the whole special. Yeah.
I didn't know that William Shatner's ever said Wario before.
And he said Mario. He's one of the guys saying Mario brothers.
He says Wario, but then Mario. Yeah.
So that that you can tell you could get sense him getting testy
as it goes on and probably like we'd already did a return to Zork.
Well, no, this is for the graphics.
We're honoring the graphics. Oh, very well.
Well, let's do another Zork then.
You can really see.
I wish they had the outtakes of that.
Zork gets a couple nominated.
Yeah, Zork was looming large.
I was trying to figure out what was up with Zork.
It is Robin Lively and Jason Hervey from the Wonder Years.
Of course. Yeah.
Oh, oh, wait. And I forgot.
I totally forgot. I have a clip of Zork.
This is a part of Return to Zork where you you enter a building
that is labeled Old Mill and then this happens.
Who are you?
Don't matter.
Won't you, Rob? Of course you do.
You're given the opportunity to accept some rye whiskey
from a hillbilly in a digital room.
In this clip, the person just keeps accepting rye over and over.
So it's just wants a bra.
Of course you do.
What's the bra?
So that's something that happens in Return to Zork.
Can we get Return to Zork on Steam?
I got to see. Maybe.
Maybe.
Where they can download it on Switch, my Switch.
Is there a return to Return to Zork?
Some other things.
Some of the bigger presenters of that particular award,
Matthew Perry and the next Karate Kid, Hillary Swank.
Yes. Soon to be Oscar winner.
Really funny.
Another thing about this award show that is unique,
the winners are read off of Newton.
The Newton. The Newton.
I freaked out when I saw one.
I didn't realize it at first.
And then someone said it.
And I was like, oh, my God, that is a Newton.
These weird little, it's like an early Apple device
and it has like a lid that has to be lifted.
Yeah.
And then once Charles Fleischer gets up there,
he ruins the whole thing and says that the screens don't work
and it's just written on tape.
So it's just an unnecessary product tie in that doesn't work.
And they kept it in.
Yeah, they did.
Which is funny.
Well, I think at some point this was a live broadcast
because there's too many screw ups.
And they say taped in an earlier time,
which means that it aired live somewhere once.
Right.
But there's too many weird lags for it not to be.
Otherwise, they didn't cut it.
The Newton.
There was a bunch of generations of it,
but it was like Apple's answer to the Palm Pilot.
Yeah.
You know, I was reading on the Newton Wikipedia
and came across this one, which has come up recently
in the 1995 under siege to dark territory.
The main character, Casey Ryback, Stephen Seagal, of course,
connects an Apple Newton PDA to the telephone network
of the hijacked train on which the film is set
and sends a fax to his workplace, which is then forwarded
to Admiral Bates Ryback's contact at the Pentagon.
Wow.
The iconic film and iconic character, even more than Spencer,
used a Newton on film.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, this was a big era for the Newton.
Big TV placement, big film placement held by Hilary Swank.
Yeah.
It was quite a time to be a Newton.
This is also it's a big it's a big night for a bunch of people
you've never heard of because I mean,
I understand this is going to be like game developers
and software people, but they all kind of come up
and are mostly not ID and they don't say who they are,
what they are to the games up there.
I don't know.
Or like do that little accepting for doom.
Otherwise it's doom.
And you go, hell yeah.
I can picture doom, blood, doom is cool.
And then just some guy gets up, doesn't
explain why he's important to doom, just talks,
isn't interesting.
I guess it's almost like did somebody just literally go,
well, should we put their names up?
And somebody goes, no one's going to give a shit.
Who cares?
Like that's what else would be the explanation.
Every other award show has a title.
A chiron.
Yeah, a chiron saying something.
They had already sent Shatner home for the day
and they're like, oh shit, we forgot
to have him read the names of the nominees.
And he's already mad it was a cold lunch and not a hot lunch.
Ha ha ha.
Hey, can we give you a call if we need?
No.
No, you can't.
Don't even finish the sentence.
Don't call me for anything.
When you just provide a club sandwich, that's what you get.
I've mentioned many times I'm in many, many different Facebook
groups where I lurk and I forget which Star Trek-based one it
is where all these people were talking about going months ago
to meet Shatner at a con.
And you could see the fear or you
could read the fear in everyone because they were like,
you know what, he wasn't so bad.
Every comment, people were terrified to pay $250
and walk by him and take a photo and say something.
He actually was nice.
He asked me what my name was.
All these comments were so sad because of the reputation
he's got for being such a pain in the ass.
The best he gets is actually.
Actually was pretty good.
He said he looked me in the eye.
He did basic human pleasantries.
OK.
I played earlier this Viva Las Vegas.
But the aftermath of that is something
that happens a couple of times in this special.
It becomes clear that we are not just
watching one outpost of Cybermania at Universal City.
Cybermania has spread across the nation.
And our first stop is Las Vegas and specifically
to somewhere called Virtual Land at the Luxor.
Wait, let me remember where this.
OK, this is him.
This is the intro.
Your intro.
OK.
Yeah.
Well, if you tell me if I don't have what you have.
But this is some JTT that taking you somewhere.
First up is a brand new virtual and Luxor Hotel in Las Vegas,
Nevada, where Sean Alex Thompson started the new series.
The news is standing by with some avid gamers.
Pause.
Hi, we're here.
Virtual Land, the world famous Luxor Hotel in Las Vegas,
Nevada, where as the name implies,
it's virtually a land filled with every conceivable
interactive and video game known to man.
But we're all presently glued to the TV, or a lot of us.
And we're watching what?
Cybermania.
No cue needed there.
Behind me are a lot of cyber punks,
I guess you'd call them, whoever has the idea.
Yeah, you definitely call them that.
Yeah, a bunch of cyber punks.
And there's all these correspondents
who do these pieces from different arcades,
none of whom, the kids do not really give them
the time of day, they don't know what it is.
They are, especially in this case,
they all just stay with their backs turned,
playing the games.
Don't acknowledge that they're on television
or the television host behind them.
There's this old square bothering them,
where it's like, I am almost done, stop.
I have almost beat Goro.
37.
I'm at Goro.
Get off my back.
Goro the monster.
I got Goro.
Goro the monster's here, and I'm defeating him.
Fuck off, turtleneck.
This guy's probably 36, whoever that guy is.
Yes, yeah.
You could not know less of what he's talking about.
You could not have more disdain for this job.
Oh, he really hates it.
Right after that, he makes a joke about,
this kid's playing NBA Jam.
Well, probably next up is gonna be NHL Jelly, a bet.
Probably, and there's no response to that,
or it gets what it deserves, that joke.
By the way, he's from a series called The News,
as JTT says.
That apparently was a syndicated sketch show,
filmed at Universal Florida in this era, right then.
And that show aired nightly.
That was a nightly sketch series.
Was that available?
There are some clips with the worst audio you've ever heard.
A couple of people have preserved it,
because of Who's Aligned cast member,
Brad Sherwood is on it.
Oh, wow. Okay.
But otherwise, I don't think this is a particularly
well-received show.
Now, hold on a second.
That's The News with a Z, I should say, by the way,
if you're looking it up.
And he is at the very new Luxor Hotel in Las Vegas.
He is not at Universal Florida,
but there is a segment from Universal Florida later.
Oh, yeah, yes.
Yeah, yeah, because CyberManias,
they gotta go to the East Coast.
It's spread over there.
I think most of the arcades shown in this special closed,
I don't think many of them made it big.
This particular one, Luxor,
Virtual and Luxor closed in 98.
Oh, also, I forgot, there's also one of the kids
who barely turns around to acknowledge him.
So, now, what does that do?
What'd you just do there that, I think this is about NBA Jam.
What does that little plus up he did do?
And the guy just says,
it makes you have special people.
And he just has to move on from,
what is that?
I have no idea what that means.
We've talked about this before,
where you watch Masked Singer,
and it's like, that feels like AI generated
in a lot of way too,
because it's been edited to death,
to the point of just like nothing feels real at all.
Things have been cut and sweetened,
and the Disney specials like that,
and stuff like the recent Disney specials.
Yeah, just nowhere.
And then this thing is the complete opposite.
You'd think they wanna prep a kid, maybe,
for one or two of the interviews.
Yeah, really, just like have a couple on hand.
Yeah, we talk to them, they know what they're gonna say.
But Local News does that.
The Local News gets a person,
and then they cut, and they ask,
or it's a pre-take.
It's weird that that would be the case.
They would just, ah, we'll wing it.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I was gonna say,
the one from Universal Florida,
I think because the presenter,
or the mainland street person,
I don't even know what to call them,
the correspondent is relatively young,
and a pretty lady, and just knows,
all right, where are you from?
Where are you from?
She just keeps it moving.
Are you talking about Andy Carvalhas, Jason?
Yeah, I don't remember.
I don't remember who that,
well, the one in Paramus, New Jersey.
Is she famous for something else?
I don't know.
I wrote down the throw to her.
We go live to Andy Carvalhas in Orlando, Florida,
for this report from the Namco Cybertainment
Coney Island Arcade.
What a mealy-mouthed thing.
That's so crazy.
Namco Cybertainment.
She mostly gets lucky with the charisma of her kids,
but then there's this kid in a shirt that says,
Jesus freak.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She says, who do you think's gonna win tonight?
And he says, me!
She says, no, what video game you think is gonna win?
And he doesn't know what to say to that.
And she has to keep asking a couple times.
Yeah, that's a good segment, though, I think.
That's a much, much better segment than the other one.
Yeah, yeah, she gets more out of it.
A better segment, but the first jump,
what did they say?
I had to go back was the Paramus, New Jersey.
We now cut to Will Arnett.
You know what?
You said it.
Well, I was just gonna say Jason, Andy Carvalis.
It sounds like Jason has a little crush on Andy Carvalis.
That's all I wanna say.
Well, I just think she did a good job
because she was not a tightwad in a turtleneck
or a very overwhelmed Will Arnett
that seems like he's about to be absorbed in a crowd.
I wasn't saying you were being bad.
I'm just saying.
Okay.
Sorry, you're gonna have a crush on Andy Carvalis.
You're gonna have a crush on 1994 Andy Carvalis.
It's being Pete Candy Carvalis.
We're here live in Paramus, New Jersey.
I'm Will Arnett.
This sounds older.
And we're in one of the biggest arcades in America
and also one of the loudest sports world
here in Paramus, New Jersey.
Has also closed.
It's a little unruly here.
Now, who's gonna win for best game tonight?
I'm feeling it.
The way he's talking.
It feels like Arnett before he developed the character,
before he figured out that like,
if I'm just this guy yelling, that's funny.
Yeah.
He just is this right now.
Well, it's so much angrier than like,
eventually he would settle on this
and this is the guy kind of more delivering.
They say, we're here in.
Like he's got this much deeper like base,
aggressive base sort of in his voice.
I don't know what he was then.
Was he just a hosty guy?
I was shocked.
Cause yeah, I was like, I really,
he was not on my radar before Arrested Development at all.
I've seen him doing a live report from Woodstock 94.
That's the other early Will Arnett I've seen.
He's in, I think a couple episodes of The Sopranos.
Oh.
I think he's an FBI guy.
So yeah, he's like what, 24 here?
He's really young.
Yeah, yeah.
Got that bronze.
He's these looking bronzes ever.
He also, then there's this thing
that they make all of these arcade correspondents do,
which is they give them exclusive tips
that you're only gonna see here.
So be sure to remember this from this live broadcast.
Write this down, assuming that you own the game.
So let's put these correspondents into loud rooms
with uncooperative children
and make them say big mealy mouthed game tips.
And that's what this Arnett part is.
Use the standing hard punch that always gets Billy Lee.
Now secondly, to finish the Shadowmaster,
get you standing hard kick.
The Shadowmaster can't fight the standing hard kick.
And third, to finish the ice pick,
you gotta use the crouching medium punch.
I don't know, this is better than the standing hard kick.
The crouching medium punch gets him every time.
And that's all I can tell you about tips
on Double Dragon 5.
And then they start rebelling again.
Rawr, rawr, rawr, we've been quiet for too long, rawr.
The kids are about to kill me.
Meet me alive, I gotta go.
Dump him in the Pine Barrens.
They did, the kids did successfully eat
much of his bronze skin.
And what we see now in Will Arnett,
that was reconstructive.
That's all been added since this deadly day.
Tasted like coconut oil.
That's what helped them swallow it.
They wouldn't have gone through it so fast otherwise.
This is so funny too because I think JTT gives
a cheat code tip at some point during the thing.
Live on the theater.
But that is at least,
not that I think that's a good idea in the way they did it,
but at least that's a simpler way.
Here, Will Arnett is telling you an elaborate way
to beat a boss in a game.
And it is not easy to convey.
Because at least you could say,
oh, it's the famous Konami code,
up, up, left, up, up, down, down,
left, right, left, right, A, B.
B, A, B, A, start?
B, A, B, A, start, whatever.
That sort of, in Nintendo land in the old days,
that would be a code. That's a little catchy, you know?
Yes, like a little cheat code makes sense.
But this is just like, and then you're gonna,
the medium punch, you're gonna use a medium punch
because you can't deflect against it.
And make sure that you're crouching
before you hit him with that punch.
So if you're a kid, you're like,
I gotta get a piece of paper.
You don't have a DVR.
No one's taping this.
Oh, my man screamed a tip at me.
Everyone was screaming,
but the loudest screamer screamed a tip at me.
Yeah, I'm gonna do a run through of Mario 3,
the first level for you.
Okay, make sure you're writing this down.
That second level of boxes,
it's not one of the, I'm not talking about clouds.
Those are clouds, not boxes.
I know they have faces, but they're actually,
there's more, I call them clouds.
Tanooki suit, what is that?
The Tanooki looks kind of like a raccoon, but it's not.
It's not a raccoon.
It's Tanooki, and that's on the third question block.
Like, this is just not the venue.
Yeah. Not the venue to be doing this.
Also a questionable tip, because like Double Dragon,
especially the earlier ones,
there was only like three or four attacks you could do.
Oh, is that so?
I feel like if the ones don't work out,
you just try the other one.
Yeah. You know?
So, yeah, insane thing to make people do on live television.
The thing where you mentioned where JTT,
as part of why he gives a tip is that it's kind of covering
for Leslie to get back into the theater,
because there's this sketch,
and if you're craving theme park content,
this is the theme parkiest thing that happens,
that Leslie Nielsen's doing like a segue,
and then a loud car alarm goes off,
and he's like, oh, I think that's mine.
I better go, and he does a big long walk backstage,
and then he finds Doc Brown leaning on a DeLorean,
theme park Doc Brown, off-brand Doc Brown.
Another thing with that that we didn't know existed,
and he says, hey, get off of that.
That's my car.
You're gonna scuff it.
And then he hears gunshots and leaves that,
so the car is, that's the end of the car bit.
No more of that.
Really, what it's all been about is to get him
into the arena of the Wild Wild Wild West stunt show,
a rare universal thing we haven't covered yet,
and he, Leslie, while Naked Guns sounded like music plays,
he does all of the bits you can do at that stunt show,
which is pretty much just, he's firing a gun at cowboys
to trigger their stunts.
Yeah, all the, yeah, the fall, big fall.
Fall, the buster Keaton trick.
The front falling.
Which I like to see him do, seeing Leslie Nielsen,
a physical comedy master, do that, so that's cool.
What does it have to do with video games, you might ask?
I don't know, don't know.
But you know, it's also nice to not get lectured
for a minute, to just watch something without dialogue.
It's a dialogue heavy thing, for sure.
I also wanna point out that off-brand Doc Brown
does not speak.
No!
I'm assuming they would have to pay him more
if he set a line.
That's gotta be a pay issue, yeah, yeah, big time.
It's just very funny to see a silent Doc Brown.
Yes, famously man of few words,
with a chill energy, Doc Brown.
So then he finishes that and then JTT says,
now there's a guy who really knows
how to get into the battle mode.
By the way, here's a tip if you're playing
Mortal Kombat 2 on Super Nintendo.
And just does a big tip.
So that all, there's a big, I do like seeing
90s Universal Preserve by that,
a little bit of a preserve like that.
I skipped past something that is, okay,
so JTT introduces somebody named Jeff Leibowitz
who comes out on stage.
He's a real guy from the academy
that is putting this together.
And then he does backstage bits.
And his biggest backstage bit is that,
well, it revolves around SimCity,
another big iconic game of the era and up through today.
And there are two computers with SimCity backstage.
This is, this special really won my heart at this point.
There's gonna be a SimCity duel that happens.
And the duel is between a real mayor of a city,
not a SimCity, but a real mayor of a real city,
the mayor of Santa Barbara, Hal Conklin.
And then, and going up against him,
the smartest kid in America, Michael Kearney.
So Michael, no further explanation.
What does that mean?
What do you mean the smartest kid in America?
By what metric?
Smartest kid in America?
I guess that's a heavy thing to download really fast
and then just move into a skit, but that's him.
I looked him up.
Apparently he had a college degree at 10 years old.
He was the youngest college graduate of all time.
That's who we're talking to there.
And he does a bit about how he wants to be a game show host.
And really, why do you wanna do that?
Well, the models are pretty pretty.
Okay.
Found out that this kid actually did get his, after this,
got his wish of auditioning to be a game show host.
And they ran a test game show.
And what they found is the contestants did not like
when a kid was smarter than them.
Yeah.
So the show was never made.
He did go on to win money on a number of game shows.
Oh, he became a contestant.
Yeah, he became a contestant.
The funniest bit of his Wikipedia entry,
in 2018 he was working for an improv theater group
in Nashville.
That's what he used his brain on?
Yeah.
No smart person should ever veer
into the improv comedy path.
He was homeschooled and then he got degrees
at very young ages.
And I just think it's very impressive.
Again, like an AI or like he grew it in a lab.
Somehow they find a way to make improvisers
more socially male adjusted.
I think it's just really impressive.
Wow.
By the way, the rules of this contest,
this is this is big Sim City duel.
And whoever wins will be the mayor of Santa Barbara
for the day.
So if the mayor wins, he gets to stay the mayor,
but the smartest kid in America is gonna help him out
for the day.
But if the kid wins, he's the mayor.
He becomes the mayor of Santa Barbara.
That's not fair.
The mayor should have become his parents' son for the day.
Oh yeah, they should switch.
They should Freaky Friday it.
Yeah.
Or maybe not switch just like he becomes his brother
for the day.
Oh yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
It's not to wear big clothes and a backwards cap.
And he gets cooked, his mom or dad cook for him
and tucked in.
I feel like at some point.
He usurps the brother's girlfriend.
Sure.
She's mine now.
We are in love.
I proposed.
I feel like, was it Mr. Lebowitz?
Is that Paul Lebowitz?
Is that the guy's name?
Who's doing the backs?
Jeff.
Jeff Lebowitz.
I believe, I feel like at one point he said like,
and if the mayor wins, he gets this kid services
for the day.
And I was like, what?
Services.
The fuck are you talking about?
What does that mean?
Cook for ya.
It is, some people in this special have a lot of charisma
and then the people who don't have charisma
really don't have charisma.
Yeah, yeah, it definitely shows.
Yeah, backstage Jeff is not the most charismatic.
He has a pretty awkward moment later.
One question I had, my friend Tyler,
when I sent this to him was like,
and when I explained this bit,
he was like, how do you, like,
one-on-one play somebody at SimCity?
It's a very good question.
This is not exactly a versus game.
Yeah.
It's a long game where you build a city
and I guess you could say like,
oh, I guess you could put a time limit on it
and see who makes,
who's city like makes the most money, I guess.
Yeah.
It's not as fun as like,
we're gonna play Mortal Kombat.
Yeah, not really,
but I guess they're using what these people,
oh, they really wanted to shame the Santa Barbara maker.
Yeah.
Like, we'll see, we'll see how good this is.
Probably the guy,
the producer like lived in Santa Barbara
and there was some like zoning ruling that he didn't like,
something he had to take off his lawn.
Yeah.
All right, I'll get him.
Hey, I got an award show coming up in three months.
Let's put this guy to the ultimate test.
Plus mayor of Santa Barbara, it's like a part-time job.
Come on.
It's surfing most of the time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Partying with the college kids.
So, probably easy.
Probably easy.
SimCity, you gotta deal with like an earthquake
and Godzilla shows up.
Yeah.
That's what I remember.
I remember playing a SimCity where Godzilla comes.
I loved that.
Yeah, that's great.
And I think it's a SimCity with all the like cut scenes.
Because there was original SimCity
that was just I think a top-down look,
but I feel like there was enhanced SimCity
with like the FMV.
Oh, yeah, they showed some clips of that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stressed out Fire Chief or something.
Around this time, we move to why Robert alerted us to this,
which is another appearance of Charles Fleischer.
And we pose the question in the 35th anniversary,
what is up with this guy?
Why do we not see that much Charles Fleischer?
And this further answers the question.
We needn't dwell on this for too long,
but I believe every word he says
is done in a problematic voice.
And he's got that compulsive need
to keep changing his voice,
which is an interesting thing.
I don't know if there's a name for it in the,
what's the psychology?
DSM, thank you.
Maybe five, four, five.
Anoia-philia.
So I think it's combined of like,
oh, I think he maybe can't talk in his normal voice
and every voice he chooses is a problem.
Yeah, so because the main,
certainly he veers into a couple of specific accents
that are very not cool,
but even the bass that he talks in,
I'm wondering the whole time.
You know, I go, oh no.
This is kind of not good, right?
No.
Isn't it?
Is he sort of doing?
It's weird, because is he stealing?
Because look, Robin Williams, we like in a lot of stuff,
but Robin Williams also has sometimes,
depending on what mode he was in,
the voice is.
Mr. Switch's voice.
The voice is the hardest thing.
I say even at the time, they were,
I don't want to pretend I was ahead of these things,
but the voices were not my favorite thing
about Robin Williams for quite a while.
No, and the switching voice is very fast,
and it would be, yes, it would be a different.
Look, I'll take him doing a Reagan
or cartoon characters or whatever,
but we know the voices that were definitely go-tos for him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he was doing them at UCB in 2010, 2011.
And he had those voices.
So there is a compulsive, yeah, so anyway,
we don't have to dwell.
No, we don't.
I also remember, so you get a sense of,
because he gets a lot of time.
They give him a lot of time,
because he was of course a star in this world at the time.
Yes.
Him having been shunned by the feature film world,
why he took his talents elsewhere to the gaming world.
We of course know that he had just created the new CD-ROM,
The Universe According to Virgil Reality,
which was like a living encyclopedia
where he's like a German professor.
That's what he was doing at the time.
I watched some clips of that
and gained nothing particularly to talk about.
He also, I remembered another thing that's a clue of what,
okay, if we're annoyed just watching his voices,
we're forgetting a big thing about him.
Obviously he's Roger Rabbit.
Have you guys ever seen any of those clips
that are behind the scenes of Roger Rabbit
that show how he was there in the Roger Rabbit suit?
He was on set.
Oh, I don't think I have.
Or he didn't really need to, yeah, he was there.
Oh wow.
But like blocking those scenes
or just like trying to be a part of it
or like bring it to life in the physical space.
And maybe that was a helpful guide for Zemeckis
on some level, but then there's these clips
you could find of Bob Hoskins going like,
then you got Charlie Fleischer and he's around
and he's doing the voices and he's yelling,
yelling, going amuck.
Oh, it's Charlie Fleischer, yeah, he's quite a fella.
Like you're just dripping with hostility.
Like where Bob Hoskins is looking like
he hasn't slept in days.
Yeah, yeah.
That Fleischer.
Wow, I haven't seen that.
Yeah, yeah, look at those.
You get a sense of, yes, that maybe the chemistry
between old Roger and Eddie was not as much
as it is between the characters.
Right, right.
So a bunch of Charles Fleischer business
and Charles Fleischer presents what to me
is the key category, which is the comedy game category.
This is an onslaught.
I have heard of a little of this,
but not all these things are insane.
The first one up is called I'm Your Man
and it's an interactive movie.
This was a thing for a little bit.
I've been obsessed for a little while.
This is called Mr. Payback.
There was an interactive movie about a guy
who got revenge on people.
This is from Bob Gale of, speaking of Zemeckis,
Bob Gale of Back to the Future.
Fame, Christopher Lloyd is in it
and you can watch these great trailers
of the entire audience laughing and bobbing around
and swinging their joysticks everywhere.
We're making the movie.
And meanwhile, in reality, this thing was so badly received.
It was Siskel and Ebert's worst movie of the year.
So I think I'm Your Man is from the same world,
but this one is written by Michael Ian Black and Ben Grant.
Wow.
And they're in it too.
And A. Whitney Brown from S7.
The big picture, my friends.
An inexplicable old SNL.
Yeah.
Joe Jackson did the music.
That Joe Jackson, 70s singer-songwriter.
That's a big recurring thing of a lot.
I feel like this is like, 70s musicians are like, I'm in.
Because you get Thomas Dolby later in this.
CD-ROM is definitely a world where we can explore.
And we'll get to big ones a little later.
I'm gonna go in order of insanity.
We have to end with the craziest one.
There's a Bugs Bunny one,
where one of the most mad shatners in the whole thing,
where he has a copy for this one is just,
Wascoly Wabbit runs amok.
And boy, you can like, can we get a second on that one?
Absolutely not.
Not in your life.
And then there's a game made by Comedy Central
called Dating and Mating.
I think I was writing, I missed the Comedy Central note.
But like, ooh. I had to look that one up.
I was not in the, I was like, what the hell is this?
Cause it's standup clips.
And the copy of the game build it as like,
you're the club, whatever, promoter, owner, whatever.
So you're someone at a club and you pick who goes up there
and does their bits about dating and mating.
So like, it has clips from Richard Lewis and Mark Curry
and Adam Sandler, hey, and Ellen Cleghorn.
So you prog, you choose your own set
of wacky 90s dating standup, this sounds so dreadful.
I know, I guess they're just trying stuff out, I guess.
They're trying stuff out, they don't know what it is yet.
So they're figuring it out.
It got nominated.
We got on the board.
It got on the board.
Yeah, you're gonna call that a failure?
Yeah, I shouldn't, I'm sorry.
Okay, further comedy games,
the wacky world of miniature golf.
Eugene Levy is an animated golf ball
in the craziest mini putt course never built.
Yeah, this almost looked like a Saturday TV fun house
or something, like footage of it.
It looked so bad on purpose, even though it was not.
Yes, really, yeah, yeah.
But who, like these ones, who, again,
and just like the, it feels so reminiscent of like,
there's a podcast with what and who has one,
and like, what do you mean Eugene Levy has an animated,
and this one wins, by the way,
which feels like a real upset because
it feels like the one to beat
would have to have been Dennis Miller, That's News to Me.
Yeah.
The Dennis Miller weekend update style joke CD-ROM game.
This is insane.
This is insane that this exists.
Yeah, this, he's in like, I guess it's,
I'm trying to think, it's not like a futuristic,
like, I'm trying to describe this.
It's like he's on a screen on a computer,
and then there's almost like Family Feud style title cards
for like topics, essentially, next to him.
Yes.
And it is so bizarre.
How did this happen?
It's like pre-Dennis, he's like clean shaven,
it's pre-Dennis Miller show on HBO,
but it's like obviously a weekend update ripoff,
and is, yeah, is the idea you just clicked on him
telling a joke?
I think so, because they didn't have space for rants.
Just like they can't do big videos.
Yeah.
Just literally, we couldn't fit one rant on the DVDs.
It's gonna have to be little bite sized jokes.
Your computer couldn't handle a rant.
Yeah, the video had to be.
Your brother, maybe he opened up a rant
on your computer at home.
Maybe he pirated a secret rant.
Pirated a rant, the videos always had to be tiny
in the corner, and then there was a lot of text
that is not moving around.
Yeah, or it pops up and pops away.
So that doesn't take up a lot of memory.
Really quick, I found a YouTube video.
It's got all of it, I found, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
Well, this is one specific thing,
which is like topical year end jokes from 1993.
So this is what you want.
You know, I watch Weekend Update on SNL,
and I hate that they pick the jokes for me.
I don't get to tell them a topic and then hear a joke back.
And I really hate that I put it on,
and I have to hear a joke about this week.
What if I wanna hear a joke about February?
Yeah.
Well, finally, that, Dennis Miller,
that snooze to me lets you be in charge of the comedy news.
And I ask you guys right now to pick a number
between one and 23,
and I will play a corresponding joke.
That'll be the time code of the joke.
Mike, let's start with you.
Eight.
All right, eight.
And that gets us to, oh, you'll like this.
It's a music one, a showbiz.
This is, oh, well, you know what?
I was gonna do one about Michael Jackson,
but it looks like there's one about Euro Disney.
So I think I have to do that, right?
Let's see.
And nevermind, I can't find it.
All right, we're gonna have to do Michael Jackson.
Okay, fair enough.
Paul McCartney expressed his dissatisfaction
with Michael Jackson,
who won't talk to Paul about changing his royalty structure.
But this fray has been going on for a long time,
ever since Jackson delayed production
of their first record together.
It seems Michael couldn't decide
if he wanted to be Ebony or Ivory.
I thought Michael always said it didn't matter
if you were black or white.
Ooh.
I mean.
Ah.
Put a chill on the room.
He doesn't even have the juice.
No.
The Miller juice is like gone out of that delivery.
No, because the Miller had juice?
I liked the Miller weekend update.
I know we were supposed to hate him now
because he's conservative.
But I liked the Miller weekend update.
Let's see if we can save it.
Jason, do you have a,
what do you think is gonna be a better number?
I'm gonna say 21.
21, all right.
Well, it'll be more, you know.
Oh, good.
Jason, you'll be happy to hear that we landed on
abortion pill.
Plans to bring the French abortion pill
to the United States have stalled
because the pill maker is afraid
of anti-abortion groups' opposition.
They wanna get those pills into the country.
They should just smuggle them in
inside French people's armpits.
Not even the right-to-life movers are that committed.
It didn't even sound like him.
It sounds like an AI doing his voice.
It's, what if a show was hosted by dying Dennis Miller?
Wow.
Yikes, all right.
Well, that's Dennis Miller and that's news to him.
That is so insane that that game exists.
Dennis Miller is all, like,
I watch old clips of Dennis Miller's show sometimes
and I think 75% of Dennis Miller is attitude.
Because sometimes I listen to something he said
and I go, well, that wasn't funny at all.
No, I didn't understand what it meant to you.
Right, I don't know what it meant.
And the rhythm was, I guess, kind of funny.
Or, honestly, I think people thought he was cool.
It's a very cocky kind of delivery,
but it was very cool.
People thought it was cool, I think.
And do you think less so now?
I do think less so now.
Some of the cool is depreciated.
I do think so.
There was a clip of Norm MacDonald a couple years ago
saying, he goes,
Dennis doesn't even know what those references are.
It might be the trick.
Yeah, yeah.
Just jam them together.
Hey, not like, look, when we reference name after name
after name as we're doing here today,
it's because we're gonna do something with them.
We don't just reference and move on.
We have stuff to say about Herbie Hancock.
That's right.
Before we get into Herbie Hancock,
some of the reoccurring commercials are pretty good.
Panasonic 3DO game console.
I kind of remember this 3DO.
I remember seeing Fry's Electronics is what I remember.
Oh, okay.
I remember one kid I knew who, like,
his family always seemed to get the other game consoles,
like 3DO or Jaguar.
Yeah, yeah.
The other commercial, oh, there's an IBM commercial
with, it's Paul Reiser.
Paul Reiser, yes.
Yeah, Paul Reiser, a little more lively
in this commercial, certainly than Dennis Miller.
In his CD-ROM.
Yes, that's the-
Specifically in Dennis' CD-ROM.
That's the rubric, yeah.
But yeah, Paul Reiser popping up,
haunting somebody on computer screen after computer screen.
Another extremely 90s ad, the 90s techno ad.
They're all well-paired for sure with the special.
Yeah.
If we're talking about who was cool then,
if that's the, you know, an attitude,
there is a group of people who,
what could have been cooler,
what could have been more of the moment,
and had to be addressed in this special.
It's been alluded to earlier,
but I will let Leslie Nielsen do the full setup.
You know, cyberspace has given us a whole new breed of pirate.
Drawing number of dedicated, highly skilled individuals
who borrow through the cyber underworld
to seek out information and access highly sensitive material.
Now these people don't take no for an answer.
And it's not the FBI, it's not the CIA.
We're talking about hackers.
When you don't know what's coming there.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Leslie Nielsen is setting us up to learn about hackers?
Hackers?
What?
They burrow in there and they see what there,
what is, if they can find what is to be found.
This is such a strange.
So yeah, now cybermania presents a tribute to hackers.
And I don't leave it with any further understanding
of what a hacker is or why.
It's a pro hacker piece.
Very pro hacker and it's expelling all the myths.
You know, you only hear about hackers
when there's a problem with hackers.
The media never does any nice stories
about the nice things that hackers do.
Maybe it was like at the time people were like,
I don't know about this internet
because I think I'm gonna be hacked.
So maybe there was an idea of like,
that people would just be scared of that term.
So they were like, let's put a happy face on the hacker.
The hacker is virtuous, is good.
White hat hackers are virtuous.
Black hat hackers are suspicious operators.
Oh, uh oh.
Do they say those distinctions in the thing?
They don't say that in the thing.
That's just a thing I know.
Black hat?
Black hat.
Like the Michael Mann Hemsworth movie, Black Hat.
Is that about hackers?
That's about a hacker who also kicks ass, I believe.
Okay, so this is a,
knowing your extensive knowledge about hackers.
I know a little.
I had to read a book called Hacker Crackdown in college.
Would you say though this is a,
That sounds like an anti-hacker.
I think it's more than I know about hackers.
It sounds like I didn't watch the special.
Well, the government kind of went nuts prosecuting people.
I think they reference the 80s.
And it's people getting into databases
and a lot of it was they say in this thing,
it's people just doing it to see if they could.
And then of course doing midnight raids at MIT
to find garbage that they could maybe hack.
It's quite a special.
You follow some real hackers on a midnight MIT raid.
So doesn't that demystify hackers for you, mom and dad?
This is, but it is straight propaganda for pro,
because you can hack anything you want.
You can be a bad hacker.
Obviously you can use a black hat hacker.
We're learning about now.
And this is not, this is portraying only one side.
This is very one sided.
What if these are white hat hackers,
but then as soon as the cameras aren't rolling,
they flip that hat inside out and what's on the other side?
Or they own two hats.
Yeah.
Oh, that's it.
That's how they get us.
They hacked the system, how to dress themselves.
Mr. Rogers would call come home and take off his one sweater
and put a different sweater on.
And this is the same way with their hats.
Bastards.
I don't tend to put on my killing sweater.
But it's so fascinating because it has to be,
because they want to be a pot,
put a positive spin on computers.
Well, Emanuel Goldstein and death vegetable and count zero.
I love count zero.
Count zero is cool.
These are all some cool, you can see there's,
once you see these are people like you and me.
They have goatees like you and me.
Yeah.
They have cow skull bolo ties and wear sunglasses
and doors next to screens like you and me.
Yeah.
I love these hackers.
You know what?
I'm gonna marry a hacker.
Yeah.
If I could do it all over again,
I would have a baby with a hacker.
Well, yeah.
And you still have a chance to make that baby a hacker.
Oh yeah.
You're lucky if she applies herself.
Yeah.
A white hat or a black hat.
Up to her.
I'm letting her decide.
Yeah, yeah.
Totally open.
You can be any type of hat hacker you want.
Wear any type of hacker hat.
I said this at the start,
where the hell does this come from?
This is so bizarre in this five minutes or whatever it is.
I think it's trying to dispel like the negative.
Like they're called hackers
and they're coming for your computer.
Right, that's what I said.
Like local news.
I love propaganda because there are bad hackers.
Yeah, sure.
And I don't,
I don't.
Straight up propaganda.
Look, I'm saying that I love these hackers,
but I also don't,
I don't see how this piece dispels what you just said
that the news reports say.
Like the hackers are coming and that these guys are like,
yeah, we are coming,
but we're just gonna poke around.
What's the problem?
Yeah, just poking around the bottle.
Yeah, I'm cool.
I'm Dr. Who.
You can trust me.
I'm the name of something that you like.
And they're lying to you.
It's not all like these guys.
Oh, they might be lying to you.
And also they have some of the worst vibes
you've ever seen.
I'm saying the special is lying to you.
Yeah, these guys, yeah.
These guys could be big liars.
Count Zero could be a big liar.
I have no idea.
I don't know who's a good hacker and who's a bad ass.
They just showing me them.
I mean, the main way they try to get the hackers
into your heart is by showing that one of them
eats a slice of pizza,
which he picks up using a power glove.
That's what you have to do if you're a hacker.
I do like that though.
How does that, that power glove is filthy.
The other, the palm side of the power glove is cloth.
And how do you wash a power glove?
It has electronics in it.
And you just don't, no fact,
no power glove has ever been washed.
You probably, Nintendo would have said like,
hey, take a, just take like a cleaning,
take some little napkin or something,
get it wet, pat it down.
Fucking Count Zero is not cleaning his power glove.
It is cake and pizza grease.
How to de-louse your power glove.
How to fumigate your power glove.
I did not know how to take apart my zapper gun
and clean it and make sure everything was working
and then put it back together.
That was never part of any of the sitting stuff.
Nintendo Gun Military School.
I didn't, I could not assemble my zapper gun in two seconds.
They had to assemble it for me.
I never took it apart.
There was a legion of duck hunt dogs coming for America
and you were drafted.
The gun better be assembled.
If it's assembled, I'll do well.
And somebody got to clean it for you, but that thing breaks.
The war is over.
Yeah, yeah.
They also do a lot of,
they sure say a lot of times,
when you hear about hackers, they can move satellites.
Guess what?
Hackers can't move satellites.
That would never happen.
Oh, I believe you.
Well, why did you bring this up at all?
You really made a good case for now.
I'm suddenly afraid that hackers
are gonna move all the satellites.
Yeah, why'd you put that in my head?
Why are you making me think about that?
This is two, or one year away from GoldenEye
where Boris would hack into satellites.
Oh, sure.
Or hack into the GoldenEye itself.
I think we're also about a year or so from the movie hackers.
And do you think the screenwriters that were watching this
and go like, I'm gonna make some tweaks.
I'm gonna give them weird sunglasses.
Maybe.
You know what?
I think they might have,
because I believe that the first hacker you meet,
Immanuel Goldstein, that is from,
the name is maybe from 1984.
I'm sorry if I'm dumb and I got that wrong.
But that is also the name
of one of the major characters in hackers.
Wow, so these are the hackers from hackers.
Well, he doesn't play him,
they just used that name again
because it has Orwellian connotations.
Maybe that was just a thing that hackers,
oftentimes hackers would adopt things from Orwell
or 1984 specifically.
Yeah, probably, yeah.
Cause he called it,
Orwell was the original hacker.
Yeah.
You know what?
I like to think that I'm sort of part
of the lineage of hackers.
I'm not really a hacker, but I'm a checker.
You're a checker.
So I'm in the family.
Kind of a cousin, yeah.
I like to think I'm a white hat checker,
not a black hat checker.
You are, because you use your checking for good.
You get nice things for people and help them get on rides.
You have to wear a white hat.
Discount on toy, like I have my glitch Twitter account
popped up with a very good discounted baby toy today
and I grabbed it before it sold out.
Sometimes you send me links to discount Twitter accounts
of like you can get 40 Andy Cap hot fry bags.
Yeah, for a great discount.
And I hope you did it.
I hope you took advantage.
I did a hot fry bag.
I can't say I took advantage.
Wait, that free package snack you mean?
Yeah, yeah.
Andy Cap's hot fries.
Yeah.
Well, you absolutely do use your powers for good,
but I fear the day you decide to use them for evil.
The day Mike turns black hat.
It depends.
You don't think you can check your way into a satellite,
but I'm saying maybe you can.
Maybe it is possible.
At least you're being honest about it,
not like these filthy hackers.
Yeah.
No, I never touch a satellite.
No, I never, never check a satellite.
You can't power glove your way in.
Mike did a little eyebrow raise when he said that.
Never.
I don't know if that communicated.
I think it did.
You did?
I think that sounded in my voice.
I acted it and I performed it.
I think, yeah, we heard the eyebrow.
Can we do it one more time where we kind of like
hear your eyebrow raise?
Well, can you, you do it for me.
Oh, I'd rather not.
Show me how you want me to do it.
Is it okay if I don't?
I immediately regret saying what I just said.
No, no.
I'd love for you to show me how you want me to do it.
Raise your eyebrows.
I can't check my way into a satellite.
Okay, I'll do it like that.
I can't.
Just do a raise.
Okay, well then now you're just being silly about it.
Wait, I'm sorry I said that.
I felt as scared as that engineer.
Yeah, you should.
Boy, you know, if you're gonna have a music performance
in your Cybermania show.
Oh, this music performance.
We're halfway through the goddamn special.
I know, it's the long, we're gonna have to do,
it's gonna have to be part one and two.
The long episodes are back.
Performing a specially composed piece just for this night
is Herbie Hancock.
Herbie Hancock.
Wow.
We associate him with this kind of thing
with his rocket video,
with all those computer creatures dancing around.
Of course, this is up Herbie Hancock, Sally,
and he does a big song that he plays on a keyboard
or a keytar rather,
and the song goes,
Cyber generation, cyber generation.
It also then later it goes,
cyber generation.
It pretty much only goes, cyber generation.
This is, the tone of this,
also the fact that this is in kind of a castle set.
As soon as the song started,
this show transmogrified into a Bible man touring show.
The song, I listened to some Herbie Hancock,
I like Herbie Hancock,
this is maybe not his finest work
that he cranked out for Cybermania.
He made his point, there is a cyber generation coming.
Yes, he's right about that.
And they're gonna dance at us, but maybe also kill us.
But yeah, it's a little chintzy, right?
It's a little silly.
Three dancers on the stage.
Not filling the space.
Even Beetlejuice's Graveyard Review later had like five.
Yeah, and there's like one contortionist kind of dancer,
and they just do a lot of angles and video filters.
They put so many,
they put that secret invasion AI muck all over the screen
so that you think something's happening,
but it's just in the way.
Yeah, oh God.
This is a little bit trying,
but I love the existence of it.
And then he goes straight from the performance
into a speech.
Yeah, yeah.
And he, in which he shouts out a bunch of like the musicians
who are exploring possibilities in this area,
in the music realm of CD-ROM.
And I was excited about this
because there's a quick shout out to Todd Rungren.
Todd at the time was doing something called TRI,
which is of course T-R Interactive.
Just one of the dopiest titles, acronyms for a thing.
Yet I've poked, I love that there are these artists.
He mentions Bowie.
I don't really know what Bowie was doing with CD-ROMs.
I'd like to find out.
But Peter Gabriel, who's nominated for this music award
that they're gonna do,
it feels like they have to mention these musicians
who are exploring kind of the gaming space
and the interactive space.
And it was a big thing at the time.
But then he says, one band shattered,
what the fuck is this sentence meaning?
But one band shattered virtual vision
seen around the world.
And then there's a little piece about Aerosmith.
This is where I started getting paranoid.
This AI is making this for us.
What do you mean, Aerosmith?
Now there's a big Aerosmith part.
Aerosmiths have been on the cutting edge of rock and roll
is a statement that's made.
Since the beginning.
Cutting it, that's definitely what I think
when I hear walk this way is how cutting it is
and how edgy it is.
Cutting edge.
Who even would you say is on the cutting edge
of rock and roll?
What would that mean technologically?
TRI.
TRI I guess.
I don't think there's any answer besides TRI.
Whoever he first used, I guess you could say the Beatles.
They used multi-track or Beach Boys.
Who used multi-track recording first?
Probably Beatles.
Cutting edge of popular music.
I would probably say Herbie Ancock.
Herbie Ancock had a lot of phases in his career.
And as technology went on,
I feel like he had, he kept evolving.
You feel like almost like synthesizers
have to be a part of this discussion
because that is literally technology.
Yeah.
But it's so it's hard.
So it's weird to think about this pretty pure
rock and roll guitar band being on the cutting edge.
I get it.
Look, they made it to hair metal land, I suppose.
Like Eros must have survived the 70s to make it into
the 80s and had some like hits alongside
like hair metal bands.
Doesn't mean it's cutting edge.
No, I agree.
It means they were kind of chasing a trend
a little bit more.
Well, it's clearly it's all just in there
because they have these video games.
Of course.
Which all they do have three video games.
I mean, we gotta do Revolution X.
Yeah, we should cover full Revolution X.
Yeah, I agree.
I don't even know what the second one they mentioned is
and virtual guitar, which I think we talked about
forever ago, but they're in there.
They're on the cutting edge of cyberspace
and interactive gaming.
They are just built up and touted.
And of course they made that music video
with where Alicia Silverstone is the cyber babe.
That's cutting it.
They clearly, that shows me that Bradley Whitford
understands technology and CD-ROMs
because there was like a kid getting a boner
in a virtual helmet.
Well, don't forget the robot, the sexy lady robot
on the cover of Just Push Play.
Oh, of course, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's a future thing.
That was probably, they went to Aerosmith Labs
and saw the early prototypes of that.
They couldn't film it.
They sent us a camera to film that,
but that early robot went haywire
and crushed the camera.
All right.
And so there's so much buildup.
Aerosmith, the most cutting edge band that has ever been.
They also can't be here tonight.
And then, oh shit, deflating.
Yeah.
And then it cuts to what I am just gonna call
a video riddle.
Oh my gosh.
By Tom Hamilton, Aerosmith's member Tom Hamilton.
To be there or not to be there?
What is the question?
In cyberspace, we're all here.
He's, it's a still shot and he's popping all around a room.
It's very Alice in Wonderland.
Aerosmith is the band that said,
we're all here because we're not all there tonight.
Hi, I'm Tom Hamilton from Aerosmith
and on behalf of the whole band,
I'd like to say congratulations to Cyber Mania 1994,
the first annual interactive gamers awards.
Yes.
That is somehow an FMV.
It is a segment filmed with cameras,
but it acts like a FMV that would go on a CD-ROM
because it's just odd.
It's very short.
Does nothing.
It does not have enough time to tell a story.
Elements on the screen stay still.
Yeah.
Yeah, what purpose does this serve?
Digital riddles and then, sorry,
are we honoring them or, but then it finishes
and he says, hey, congratulations Cyber Mania.
Yeah, I don't know.
So it's them, Aerosmith is giving them an award.
Well, the bassist of Aerosmith is.
The bassist, I can't remember what instrument he is.
Yeah.
Yeah, the bass player from Aerosmith made a...
I guess maybe the third most popular Aerosmith member.
I don't know what you would rank the other three.
I don't know, isn't Joey three?
Joey three, Joey Kramer, what do you think?
Tom Hamilton, I believe is sweet emotion,
like kind of rote sweet emotion,
or had the most to do with it.
Okay.
Is that cutting edge because it's got like,
rawr, rawr, the thing Peter Frampton was already doing.
Yeah, Joe Perry was playing the, whatever that tube
that Peter Frampton uses.
The vocoder?
I don't know if you call it that.
It's called a vocoder, but it's called something.
It's a voice box, voice changing.
The talk box.
Yeah, talk box.
Well, that's not cutting edge,
because I like sweet emotion, but.
Yeah.
It's not, I don't know.
This premise is strange.
Anyway, but they had to, again, we had to do,
okay, the show's filling up.
We got five minutes on hackers.
We got Dennis Leary, nobody's heard of,
doing beat poetry, and then we got to give 30 seconds
to Tom Hamilton to pop around a room like the Cheshire Cat.
He seems like not, he's, I feel like he's doing his best
here actually, in as far as performance wise.
Yeah.
He's like kind of into it.
Can you do a little more energy, Tom?
Yeah.
Oh, more energy. Of course, I'd love to.
Thank you, of course, thanks for the suggestion.
Do you want to hear me play sweet emotion on the bass?
It's a treat for him to act.
Yeah.
I like Shadner, Shadner does do it so often.
Right.
This is so strange, and then you see a bunch of music,
CD-ROMs is presented by Thomas Dolby in a dumb beret.
I had no idea there was a Prince one.
I know.
This one, this is a whole, this, it opens up so many avenues.
Yeah.
This is a Prince CD-ROM where you explore different rooms
of Paisley Park, which itself seems to look like
a mist type early 90s VR space.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's what you do, and you walk up to like,
here's a torch, and then you click it with your mouse,
and then it lights with fire, and then at some point
you see a, you click on a metronome,
and the little needle on the metronome is Prince.
I think I saw it called a pointless scavenger.
More marketing than gaming.
I think that's probably right.
Yeah.
This is a very strange, I liked the screen that I saw
where he says, the title says,
are you sure, with the Prince language,
are you sure you want to exit the experience?
I bet people were, yeah, I mean,
I want to play the whole thing, but.
Can I ask a stupid question?
Is Thomas Dolby have something to do
with Dolby sound systems?
I don't think so, unless he's somehow in the family,
but I don't believe so.
Okay.
No, he just has something to do
with Buzz Aldrin and silence.
Silence!
Bad hats, you know.
Um, so, yeah, but is he a bad,
is he a bad head or a good head?
Then there's something that happens
where we check back in on the SimCity people
and we check in on the celebrities who are playing,
you can actually talk to Jenna Von Oy
in our Prodigy chat room.
Again, the most just hyper 90s on top of 90s.
And the real guy from the academy
is saying a bunch of boring academy stuff,
and then a girl comes up and puts his arm,
you guys notice this part too?
Yes, I noticed this part.
The hard line.
This is really weird.
It's really odd.
So she, like, he's just trying to say
it's boring president stuff,
but then she comes up and puts her arm,
locks arms with him, and we've met her earlier.
She's from My So-Called Life, you know,
a show about high school.
So then this guy, north of 40 probably,
gets a little flustered.
He gets a little distracted by the, again,
high school actress.
I looked it up and she's 20, so okay,
but still, this is very strange,
and then he stops his speech cold,
and he says, I think a lot more than my voice
is about to crack.
I know, so what does that mean?
What does that mean?
What does he mean?
Well, okay, I realized on second viewing,
he might have been alluding to something
that happened earlier in the show
when he was on stage in front of the audience,
and he did get nervous and his voice cracked.
You of course remember that.
We're paying close enough attention to remember that.
Yes, that was awkward and he covered okay,
but he may have been calling back,
it's that thing that's an elephant in the room
in your mind, but you did not need to mention it ever again.
So it's just confusing.
But taking that aside,
a pretty girl is making you flustered,
and you say, I think a lot more than my voice
is about to crack.
His boner cracks?
Is that when it extends into a boner?
You're saying that a boner,
and I'll go, I know you're just trying to
come up with whatever for him.
You're just trying to help him out.
But the idea that a boner is cracking,
is that like?
Yeah, you gotta get to the emergency room that happened.
I don't think, I can't think of anything
in any sexual process where cracking is a good thing.
Shaky bed frame?
Yeah, but I guess if your sex is so powerful
that it cracks pieces of the bed off,
then sure, maybe.
That's still pretty, that might be too powerful.
It's still not something I want to happen.
The Twilight sex scene.
The Bella and Edward film sex scene.
I don't know this one.
Have you ever seen this?
It's really funny.
Cause he's got the power.
With Pattinson and Kristen Stewart,
he destroys a four-post man.
Cause he's such a powerful vampire.
He's so powerful.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay, well that makes some sense at least.
All right.
But that's not what he's talking about.
That's not what he's talking about.
What is he talking about?
He's so turned on that he's going to crack.
Well, wait, can I say her line that sets this up?
Yeah.
Yes, please.
And it gets a little muffled,
but I think what she says is,
can I play in your chat room?
Ooh.
What?
Ew.
And then he keeps saying boring president stuff
and then says like, you know what?
We'll be right back.
And then he kind of turns back to get with her
and then thank God it cuts away.
Yeah.
I mean, I think this was just a skit
and nothing happened, but this is weird.
He's the president of the thing.
And then he writes himself a skit
where he's got a big crack and boner
for a girl who plays high school student.
He's doing a hummin' a hummin' a bit.
Yeah.
Maybe something, maybe there is something wrong with him.
He thinks, you know, that thing where you get turned on
and then your penis cracks.
It's like a reverse glow stick.
You know, when a glow stick,
you crack it to make it light up.
But with him, it's like, it's almost,
his boner's in two pieces
and it's sort of a reverse crack to assemble it.
It makes a crack to go back together.
Crack.
Yeah.
If that happens, does it make a big sound, you think?
Like a signal flare, a reverse signal flare.
Like that.
I don't know.
Look, what else would it crack?
I guess he could crack under pressure.
Is that, yeah.
Maybe that's his like.
Yeah, we were thinking, we were like,
does he mean, is he saying that he's gonna,
like he's gonna crack on his marital vows?
I'm gonna cheat on my wife.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm cracking.
Yes, he's cracking under pressure.
The engagement ring snapping in half.
That's sad. The wedding ring.
The wedding band.
Oh, okay.
So I think a lot more than my voice is about to crack.
By that, I mean my wedding ring
because I'm getting engorged as are my fingers.
Because blood is just going everywhere.
And so my fingers are getting thick
and my wedding ring is gonna crack apart.
Yeah, it's like when the Hulk transforms.
Everything bursts.
This guy gets so horny,
he transforms into a Hulk-like monster.
Yeah.
Again, this guy's name was what?
Jeff.
Hulk.
Lebowitz?
Jeff Lebowitz.
When video game Academy president Jeff Lebowitz
gets turned on, he hulks out.
He hulks out, yeah.
Ah, crack.
Wow, his wedding ring went flying.
It's in my eye now.
A 20 year old.
Hulk can now cheat on wife.
You're fucking out of your eye for you.
A 20 year old actress like real quick delivered this line
and she's like, all right, if I hurry,
I can get back to my North Hollywood apartment
before the rush, you know.
Oh my God.
Anyway, we gotta pick up the pace
because this is, I mean, we're getting down there.
Although we're not in a way.
There's so much fucking shit.
Just real quick, I gotta point out right after this,
there's two commercials.
One is the Big Mac deal, two Big Macs for $2.00.
And I'm like, oh, that's such a bargain.
RIP, fairly departed.
The other one is an ad for a TNT special
called In Search of Dr. Seuss, which looks so horrific.
Yeah, Robin Williams and Kathy and Jimmy
and Christopher Lloyd and they're all dressed like
Seuss people.
Yeah, it's really insane.
Shelley Duvall says some educational stuff
and she's got a big flower hat.
One of the games, a dog says,
it was time for my Sunday bone.
That's all I need to say about that part of it.
It's kind of the sake of time.
Now to present Best Sports, would you please welcome
Miss Marla Gibbs and the stars of the upcoming film,
The Babysitters, The Barbarian Brothers.
Now a true mystery walks on stage,
The Barbarian Brothers.
Oh, hold on, before The Barbarian Brothers,
the Shelley Duvall thing, the educational documentary
is even weirder than the hackers one.
Because it's got a bunch of assholes in it.
And the one guy says, research shows that networking,
oh no, he says, in the last few decades,
we've seen a dramatic decline in the quality of education.
Who are you?
What is this?
It says a man and a woman that keep going back and forth.
There's a really weird text card that says,
research shows that networking improves social skills
and decreases ethnic tension.
Oh, right.
I forgot about that.
Why are they dumping on education
and then they're just talking about CD-ROMs
that appear to just bring up encyclopedia entries?
It is weird.
I think that, yeah, well, time will certainly prove
that the internet will be a tool
that decreases ethnic tension.
Yeah.
Anyway, back to The Barbarian Brothers.
The Barbarian Brothers, what is this?
Then two big bodybuilders come out.
They're fucking massive.
Yes, what are they?
What's the babysitters?
They've been in a lot of movies.
If you look.
Two weird Jack Thicke guys.
Yeah, they're very weird.
One of them just passed away a couple years ago.
Oh, no.
But yeah, I was like, wait a minute.
Why don't I know The Barbarian Brothers?
I was, my first thoughts was wrestler, but yeah.
No, they're bodybuilders, I think?
Yeah.
They're bodybuilders.
No, the wrestlers have yet to show up.
That's right, there are wrestlers to come.
Double Trouble is a movie from 1992
starring The Barbarian Brothers.
Think big.
They're in DC cab.
Oh.
They're in Natural Born Killers apparently too.
Oh, really?
There's a movie called in 1994 called Twin Sitters.
How do I not know?
Twin Sitters I discovered is the babysitters.
Oh, it is?
There were a couple of titles for this.
Okay.
For this Barbarian Brothers feature film.
This trailer also, this will really vex you.
Oh look, and they tried to like steal the tagline
for the game.
You're never home alone when you're a twin.
They're trying to just kind of usurp.
I don't know, it is too much of a conundrum
to solve at this time, The Barbarian Brothers.
There will be more Barbarian Brothers content
coming to the show.
I don't know what for me yet, but that is not.
Wait, another tagline, move over Mary Poppins.
Here come the Barbarian Brothers.
I mean, I'm on board of that.
That I like.
Yeah.
I know everything.
I've seen plenty of Mary Poppins.
My Mary Poppins chapter is over.
Barbarian Brothers, you're welcome in.
Yeah, no, there's a, just for time,
we're gonna keep moving here.
There are a movie called The Flamingo Kid as well.
That seems kind of familiar.
Which is, I think it's, is it Matt Dillon?
Yeah, Matt Dillon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a very martial movie.
I've heard of that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're not the stars, I don't believe
of The Flamingo Kid though.
We'll check out, we'll go into Barbarian Brothers.
I'm even gonna cut, I'm gonna cut the clip of them
where there's just a 30 awkward,
30 second awkward pause where the package doesn't play
and they don't know what to do.
Yeah.
And they try to spike a football pantomime
and it doesn't, this is all exceedingly strange.
And then they present a sports award
that NBA Jam doesn't win.
What are you talking about?
Some Caesar's Palace boxing game?
Caesar's World of Boxing.
Oh, we're all talking about it.
It stood the test of time.
Insane.
Okay, yeah, then there's more of these things
where Leslie Nielsen has a speech to give,
but they make other things happen next to the speech
because the speech is dry.
And in this case, it involves, wait, no,
actually the setup is that there's two,
two actual wrestlers are gonna play WCW Super Brawl.
Yes.
And who are they?
So you're talking about back then Lord Steven Riegel,
which is William Riegel is what the name he's gone by
in the last 15 or 20 years,
and flying Brian Pillman,
who was a maniac who has passed away.
Yeah, he was a crazy man.
He would die three years later at 35.
Yes, and was a drugs and stuff wild man.
And this is so they see,
yeah, the bit is that they're playing against each other
while Leslie Nielsen is doing the speech.
And then they slowly just,
it devolves into them actually wrestling each other
on the stage.
And then, yeah, they're doing most body slams,
slamming heads into walls and stuff.
And then Leslie Nielsen pulls a gun out
to try to get them to calm down,
which is wild.
There's a lot of guns in this special.
The speech he's giving is anti-violence, right?
So that's the twist is that then he just use violence.
It's anti-violence in video games.
And someone earlier had read a message from Al Gore,
talking about the importance of the information
super highway and interactive content in media.
And I'm like, wait a minute,
wasn't Tipper like complaining about music,
found music and violent video games.
And then they do a violent video games bit shortly later
in the thing.
I think they're pretty clean in their pro violence approach.
Pro hackers, pro violence.
And yeah, so he scares Regal and Pillman away.
There's a really, one of the most famous Pillman clips
is on Raw when he pulled a gun on Steve Austin in a house,
which is a stage.
It was not a real, but it's a.
That's a spoiler.
Yeah, nobody died.
Big Regal, I wasn't watching back then.
Pillman was a really good wrestler.
I love Regal.
I'm a big Regal guy.
Yeah.
He's still great.
And then Leslie Nielsen gives a like,
ah, don't worry about all this stuff.
You know, there's ratings.
Don't worry.
Video games have ratings now.
So just check the ratings.
He basically hand waves the idea that violence
or any content is a problem.
And he basically just goes, he very throwaway,
just goes, ah, check the ratings.
Check the ratings.
Don't worry about it.
There's a throwaway line earlier with him
and Jonathan Taylor Thomas.
And Jonathan Taylor Thomas says,
you ever wonder how the games are made?
And Leslie Nielsen goes, no, not really.
That is pretty good.
I mean, that's funny.
Yeah, yeah, that's just, that's actually funny.
Yeah, that's a good laugh.
Okay.
There are some best actor awards.
Yeah, I forgot all about this.
By the way, I sent this link to past guest Pat Cassels.
And I sent it to him because I discovered
that this entire thing was covered
on a CollegeHumor show called Bleep Bloop 10 years ago.
And Pat was a guest on that.
So I haunted him with something from his past
by bringing this up.
And he's like, yeah, I kinda remember this.
And he's flipping through it and he's like,
sorry, I'm just skimming,
but how come everyone I'm landing on is like an old man?
And never does it get more old manny
than in this neck of the woods.
We present best actress,
and this is presented by one of the models Inc.
Oh, I got so excited when I heard models Inc.
Models Inc, yeah, it takes you back.
Very of the era.
And then Robert Culp.
Culp?
From I Spy, Culp is there.
And they, I mean, I don't have a lot about this,
but you discover that Culp is there
because he's also in a game called Voyeur.
This seems like a big, this is a prestige FMV game.
I've never heard of it till now.
But it sweeps the,
this is the everything everywhere all at once.
It sweeps the acting categories,
although which that movie did not do Brendan Fraser.
You know what I'm saying, it swept some of them.
It swept a couple of them.
I recognize Culp
because I've been picking random Columbus recently,
watching them and he's-
The first one, he's number one.
I think the book, the authors are number one.
He's the private detective agency.
Here's the thing about Robert Culp.
He is in four Columbus.
Yes, extremely recurring.
I've seen one of them.
Yeah. Yeah, he's in, yes.
That's a special slot, the Columbo villain role.
Some of the finest actors of all time have done it.
Leslie Nielsen, I think.
Am I making that up?
I think maybe.
Culp, also notable, the murderer in the pilot episode
of Mrs. Columbo with Kate Mulgrew.
Oh, they even brought him in for Mrs.
Yes, the weird Mrs. Columbo where you never saw Columbo
and they never crossed paths.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Yeah, no, separate lives.
They're both busy. Two seasons, two seasons on Tubi.
God, really? Wow, really?
Wow, I didn't know he was that long.
So yeah, Culp is good and they had to bring in him,
a big dog for this game because this game sounds good.
He stars as Reed Hawk, the evil CEO of Hawk Industries
and he is going to run for president,
but he is a bad guy.
He is a black hat and he cannot be the president.
At this time, evil CEOs were not allowed to be president.
So you, the player, has to stop him.
You have to sneak around his house
and the houses of his family.
And it's all done like very rear window through blinds.
You have to like leer.
You have to be a voyeur.
You're the voyeur and find some evidence
to stop evil Reed Hawk from becoming president.
And the best part about this game, it has sex in it.
There's sex in the game.
There's even a part where two girls,
two girls are in 1994.
1994.
Are standing next to each other in their underwear
and they touch each other lightly
and then there's a phone call that interrupts the whole thing.
But it seems like if there's no phone call,
maybe they were gonna kiss or something.
Oh my God.
This is an edgy game.
So it had to, clearly it had to win the acting awards.
And I forget the name of the actress,
but she gives the most sexual,
she gives the most horny speech.
Yeah, Grace, Grace Zabrinsky.
Grace Zabrinsky.
She wants Robert Culp.
It is heavy sexual tension.
Wait, which is this?
Which was the actress who played Susan's mom on Seinfeld?
That's a different category.
The idea.
That was the other one.
She's in this?
She accepts an award.
She what?
Wait a minute.
Now I gotta go back to my-
Is she Grace Zabrinsky?
My phone is, that's what I'm trying to figure out
is my phone is almost dead.
We're doing the longest episode we've done in a long time.
The phone is dying.
Look, in terms of Sexy Gay,
I was already choked up from the multiple airings
of the women's gel deodorant commercial
about the most important thing I put on.
And there's a sleazy narrator going,
is it red?
Talking about her lipstick.
And she's like, no.
This really loomed large in your head.
Yeah, was it tantalizing?
That's what I'm saying.
I was like, I can't think about a sexy game.
There's already sexy ads in here for deodorant.
I'm learning about hackers.
I'm getting turned on.
Well, and then plus we can't forget Andy Carvalhas.
And cute Andy Carvalhas is in it.
The sky's cracking boners.
The last 1% of my phone was dedicated to finding that name
so I could say that.
And it completely shut down before I could find the actress.
What a techno nightmare, Mike.
Oh, gosh.
Anyway, the woman who plays Susan's mother on Seinfeld,
who's like that very dismissive lady,
like maybe 50s or early 50s or something,
wins an award.
And I'm trying to remember if it's this award.
Maybe it is.
Yeah, she's got kind of, she's got a very sexual energy.
Is she like 50-ish, late 40s maybe?
It could be.
Oh my gosh.
OK, then we bring it up and give me your iPad.
Then it's the main, then it's the actor award.
And this is all old men.
It's nothing but.
It's Robert Culp.
It's Leonard Nimoy.
And then my favorite part about it, Mickey Rooney.
Oh, I got so excited.
There's a CD-ROM where Mickey Rooney does a voice?
I know.
Shocking.
I was watching this in the kitchen and I went,
I went like this because Lindsay was like,
she's like, what is this?
What are you watching?
What is happening?
You're taking a walk to look at Jason's iPad?
Yeah.
You're dragging the recorder around.
I have to cut some of the noise on this.
Crunch, crunch, crack.
That's not Mike's boner cracking.
No, it's not.
Oh, Grace Zabrinsky was also in Charmed in Ray Donovan.
Why do you have to go over there to see this, Mike?
Show me a picture.
Take Jason's word for it.
I just pulled up her Wikipedia.
It's an audio medium.
Why are you looking at a picture?
I wanted to see.
I wanted to make sure.
You want your boner to crack because you're
attracted to Grace Zabrinsky.
We're all horned up.
We've been here for hours.
Yeah, there she is.
She was on Seinfeld.
But you didn't trust your friend's word?
He was trying to tell you.
First paragraph.
No, let me see a photo.
If I pulled it up, it was just going
to be all pictures of Andy Carvalhas.
OK?
You can't trust this guy when he finds a lady pretty.
Tab after tab.
As George's fiancee, Susan's mother.
That's right.
Wait, we knew that.
Why'd you have to say that part?
I'm just saying.
He's confirming it.
It's in the first paragraph.
He's getting too worked up.
Like, I got a lady's doing that.
Playing over here.
He said that to cover the fact that he was just scrolling
through Carvalhas' photos from Google Image Search.
Your iPad is overheating from too much Carvalhas.
Again?
That's how the crack got in there.
OK.
That proves it, how Jason cracked his screen.
Wait a minute.
He cracked his screen.
Yeah.
He cracked his screen from cracking a boner?
Yeah, well.
My point, let's get things as unsexy as they can be
and talk about Mickey Rooney.
Because the clip that they play, it is a CD-ROM about race
tracks, and they play a clip.
And in the clip, it seems as though Mickey Rooney
is a guy betting on the horses.
And in the clip, he says this.
There's a long, very quiet walk home
when you lose the whole bundle.
So this is a CD-ROM where Mickey Rooney
is a sad man going broke at the race track,
and we haven't heard of it till 2023?
This is madness.
And then I try to look it up, and all the emulators
are broken.
They're all bright red.
That means error.
Means I can't play them.
I want a copy of A Great Day at the Races, the sad Mickey
Rooney horse racing game.
We got to do an episode on it.
Another day, another dollar lost.
I guess I'll have to steal my booze today.
There's many games where you root around
for tickets on the ground.
Maybe someone dropped a winning and didn't know.
Yeah.
Maybe I'm little.
Maybe I can pose as a child and try
to appeal to somebody's sympathies
to buy me my first beer.
If I lose, I can pose as a jockey
and steal one of these horses and sell them
on the black market.
I bet I could beat a horse.
I bet I could outrace a horse.
Run me in the race.
I'm at the end of my stuff, pretty much.
There's the best game award.
Mortal Kombat wins.
And Leslie Nielsen says, whoopee.
I really like that juxtaposition.
Before I play the last clip, is there
anything else in this shockingly long episode?
My phone's died.
I don't know what my notes say.
I forgot.
I think I'm out.
I think that's for the best.
That's the universe editing it for you.
The Kid won.
The Kid won Sim City.
Oh, you're right.
The Kid gets to be the mayor of Santa Barbara.
Santa Barbara for 24 hours thrown into anarchy.
It became a purge situation.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
As we know, Santa Barbara had to get.
Yeah, Santa Barbara was a lawless city for two years.
They had to chase out all the 10-year-old no-goodniks
let in by the smartest kid in America.
Yeah.
Smartest, aliquist kid in America, I say.
But they cleaned it up.
They firebombed parts of the town.
And ultimately, the awards ended.
And they ended with this.
Now, if you're a cyber maniac like me,
I bet you had a blast.
If you're a cyber maniac like me.
And if you've never heard of a CD-ROM before the show,
it's pretty exciting.
I know I can't wait to get home.
I can't wait to get home and grab ahold of my joystick
and boot up the hard drive.
Nice.
Ends with a joke where Leslie Nielsen
stands next to Jonathan Taylor Thomas
and says, I'm going home to jerk off.
Yes, Jonathan, let's all grab our joysticks
and give them a good crack.
Goodnight, everybody.
That's all.
Wow.
I mean, I would make an effort to have some last bit
in this episode.
This is fucking crazy.
I had no idea this would go for so long.
Robert Denby, you gave us quite a gift.
God bless you.
You gave us everything we wanted in one two-hour package.
Listeners, you must go watch this.
As it aired on TBS, the Superstation, it's incredible.
Honestly, think about how many Academy Awards
you have watched all of the night of and been bored to tears.
This is better than, I'll just say,
it's better than any Oscars, right?
Isn't it?
I guess it is.
Yeah, it is.
Maybe the best of the best, Billy Crystal era,
where everybody was on fire and they were tall,
the Lanch.
But think about this.
We love this so much.
And they didn't even need the Lanch.
They didn't even get Bruce.
I was hoping his name was in there,
but his name is not in the credits.
And they didn't even need him, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
That's how much fucking cyber firepower they had.
Whoever's alive in the credits on this
should do the next Oscars.
Yes.
Give it to, well, there was one name.
I don't know if he's alive or dead.
But when I looked him up, the first name that comes up,
one of his other credits is like a Leslie Nielsen golf video.
Oh, I saw that.
He's trying to get in on the dwarf trend.
And he seemed to have been born in the 1930s.
So I don't know if that's who.
If he's still alive, I don't know if that's who you give
the Oscars to.
All right, well.
But Culp died 13 years ago.
Who else had a golf video?
You can't ask this question now.
Tim Conway had a series of directed VHS golf videos,
I believe.
Dorff, I just said it.
Oh, is that the same one I think of?
Yes, Tim Conway and Dorff.
Sorry.
How embarrassing.
I will cut that out.
You're a fucking moron.
Fucking idiot, I am.
Yeah, he did.
And it was called Dorff, dude.
I guess, oh, I thought you meant Steven Dorff had a series
of golf videos on VHS.
Another big area that opened up, funny instructional videos.
The CD-ROM era should have lasted longer.
Why didn't it go longer?
This thing is incredible.
We must preserve Cybermania 94 as a time capsule of what
mattered.
Not if we needed to represent just the 90s,
but also how about the entire century?
The entire 20th century.
I say, flush it all down the toilet the way fucking
Zaslav wants.
And the only thing that should remain is Cybermania 94.
There I said it.
I think you're right.
And when the aliens, well, I shouldn't
say when the aliens come.
They're already here, as we've been seeing in the headlines.
Are the aliens helping the orcas?
Is that what's happening?
Oh, yeah, maybe.
Or the orcas are the aliens.
Oh, yeah.
They have been the whole time.
That's right.
Wow, just land and wig.
I know one thing that'll tell us that aliens have actually
infiltrated society already.
It's called Disney Marvel's secret invasion.
I'm hitting stop on the recorder.
Oh, OK.
Club 3, I don't need to do any of that.
You know what you're doing.
Long episode.
Bye.
Yes.