Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain
all-knowing drifter dogs, Popeye-themed toilets,
and a particular host trying to keep his cool
around the man who makes his Ninja Turtles.
Trevor Zammit from NECA Toys talks all things turtle
and growing up at Canada's Wonderland on Podcast The Ride.
["The Ride Theme Park Theme Song"]
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast
hosted by three men who would have had a better time
at their high school prom if they were dressed and styled
by a group of adorable woodland creatures.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Scott Gairner.
Yeah, well I mean, in what, I think if woodland creatures
are doing anything to help you, it's better.
I think that's a plus up for any of life's.
You mean like if you're cleaning out your car,
if there's a bird that comes by
and like picks up some trash with its beak, it's better.
Yeah, absolutely, bring a little magic into the process.
I don't wanna put animals to work doing anything gross,
but if they could just be part of the basic bathroom
process as well.
It's not like a full Flintstones
where the animals are being put to work.
They're sort of just helping because they're friends.
Yeah, I think so, and to like add a little,
because they're friends with me and us,
getting magic to our day.
So the bird would say something,
it would look at the camera and say, it's not a living.
I'm just doing it for fun.
Yeah, it's not a living.
I'm not getting paid for this, therefore it's not a living.
Right, Jason Sheridan is also here too.
Yeah, I have to think the woodland creatures
would have better taste than like whatever
suburban Philadelphia comfort bone.
You wore for prom?
Yeah, tuxedo rental.
It's like a fashion forward sparrow or something.
Yeah, yeah, he's getting you the shawl collar,
the kind of rounded lapels, you know,
just for a little, zhuzh it up, you know.
More styling too.
Yeah, who wears, is there, can you give me an example
of somebody who wears what you're talking about?
You say it on red carpets and stuff,
it's just as opposed to like peaks,
as opposed to point it, like a lapel.
Oh, it's like more of a rounded.
It's more of a rounded.
It's sort of what Big Bird wears,
but he only wears that like dicky part of it,
is that what you're talking about?
Yeah, I think that's right.
Okay.
I don't know what you're talking about
because I've never worn a tuxedo in my life.
Really? Really.
I never have.
I'm going to a wedding later this year
where it will require me to wear one for the first time.
So your terminology's going over,
I'll hopefully be a tux expert
by the time this wedding rolls around.
You go to any Friar Tux location
here in the San Fernando Valley
and they'll take care of you.
Okay, okay.
Tell them Jason sent you.
Had a very nice experience there a number of years ago.
Have I said on the show there's a prominent
star of an indie movie from the 90s
who works at a suit store around here?
I don't want to say who it is, but I'll say off mic.
Is it a clerk or a mall rat?
No.
Okay, that pause made me think that maybe it was.
I don't think it was.
No, no, he's not.
I know who it is.
I went right at the target.
I know this cast.
I shouldn't have thought that long.
But I just wanted to make sure.
I know clerk's a mall rat's cast.
Not even a peripheral mall rat.
I don't think so.
But possibly a mall rat?
Keep your eyes out at tux stores.
Let's bring our guest on,
see if he has any thoughts about tuxedos.
He is the brand manager of Nekatoys Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle
action figure line.
This is Trevor Zamet, ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, hello. Welcome to the podcast.
Hi, Trevor. Hi.
How are you doing? Thanks for having me.
Of course, yeah, thanks for doing it.
Tuxedos, just in general.
We have so much to talk about,
but for some reason we're stuck in tuxedos right now.
Yeah.
How do you feel about formal wear?
You know, they're great on penguins.
You know, it was always cute when the Muppets
would wear their tuxedos.
Well, of course.
You know, making an effort, you know, dressing up.
If they're on the Oscars or something, that's always nice.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, because yeah, I was saying Big Bird earlier
and I always loved it when Big Bird,
he would just have like that one little piece here.
Looks great.
It looks great.
He's naked except for the little piece,
which I don't think Scott is going to do that look at the.
Yogi Bear just wears the collar with a tie, you know.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, maybe I can get away with it.
A collar and a tie.
It's a Sesame Street slash Anna Marbera reference
as I'm getting pulled into the police car.
Yeah, well, the police will understand,
I think, eventually down at the station.
You have to have the cap, though.
If they're a fan.
I think the cap and the collar and the tie.
Completes the outfit.
Completes it, yeah.
Otherwise, you'd just be your run-of-the-mill pervert.
You'd look weird without the cap.
Without the cap, yeah.
Justifies it totally, yeah.
Okay, so we have so much to talk about.
I want to set, Trevor, I want to set you up a little bit here
of how we met, how I learned about you.
On this show, oftentimes I talk about this hobby of mine,
collecting.
These two gentlemen are, I would say casual,
like action figure guys, casual toy people.
I have some, but yes, but I, no, it's not even,
I don't think I'm 1% what you are.
Right.
With your life. You know of toys.
Yes, yeah, yeah, and I've bought them as an adult.
Oh, okay.
Yes, yeah, yeah, and I have some neck of stuff.
I've got, yeah, I got you a couple
of the Back to the Future things.
Oh, those are great.
Yeah, yeah. Which are great.
Jason, Jason will collect what he likes.
Jason has a maggot toy from the X-Men,
one of his favorite characters.
Oh, from the Marvel Legends.
He's got some Marvel Legends.
He just got Wimpy in the mail from the company Boss Fight.
Oh, that's a good one.
So he's very excited about that.
Yeah.
You have Popeye and Wimpy now?
I have Popeye and Wimpy now.
Yeah, so they can hang out.
That's how it starts.
Wimpy's just, he's lonely and he needs friends.
That is true, and that's how the Marvel, you know.
I don't have the room for this, this problem,
but I have a lot of tabs open on my computer.
Mike makes the room.
You'll have it whether you have the room or not.
You will carve some space out of wherever you're living.
We have a garage now, which is dangerous for a collector
because a lot of stuff goes into little bins that I buy.
So this is the plight of the collector.
So anyway, for many years at the company you work for,
NECA, which I've talked about before,
you would do one fun Ninja Turtles release a year,
usually Comic-Con, and it'd be like, oh, this is fun.
This is great to get a little retro Ninja Turtles thing.
Once a year, that's a fun little treat.
And it was about, the first one was the,
or no, the first one was the original comics, I believe.
That was a long, that was before me.
That was a long time ago.
Yeah, those were awesome.
That's what really started it.
And then they went away for a little while.
And then when I started working there,
there was an opportunity that popped up
to do the arcade figures.
Right, which was, yeah, so they have kind of pixelated,
look to them, and that was great to get those.
And then I think you did the movies, the movie figures,
which I believe you sculpted, is that correct?
Yeah, and the arcade ones too.
Oh, you did both of them, okay.
Because yeah, you're an artist and a sculptor.
How it started was just like,
I was sculpting some of this stuff for fun,
and it sort of turned into work stuff.
But yeah, so I had worked on the arcade stuff,
the early movie stuff.
There was a bunch of us that were working on it.
But then it went into the cartoon.
We did a cartoon set the following year.
A great retro package that looks like the old cases
that you would get back in the old days.
I don't know if you guys ever had a turtle,
big plastic case where you'd keep your figures in it.
The Playmates.
Yes, the Playgirl turtles.
Like an old vinyl carrying case.
So that was where you got these cartoon figures in.
And again, it's like, this is the fun, once a year fun
that I get to have a comic on.
And then I guess it's what, three or four years ago
at this point, something changed.
And my life would never be the same.
Men of my age's lives would never be the same.
Mostly men, I'm sure there's women out there,
but I'm in a lot of toy Facebook groups where I lurk,
and it is mostly men.
That's why I say that.
But of course there are women out there.
And so you guys started doing everything, essentially.
Every version of the Ninja Turtles possible.
The cartoon, the Fred Wolf stuff,
I'm just talking by the way, feel free to interrupt me.
I'm getting on a roll here, I think.
No, yeah, it's cool.
The movie stuff, the Mirage comic, and then recently,
which of course I've talked about before,
the specific Archie comics Ninja Turtles
that I read as a kid and I felt was the main canon
of the turtles.
I think that is one of the happiest moments
I've ever seen Mike.
He came to a recording one day,
and I forget whether we were arriving
or it was on our way out,
and he went, NECA is doing the Archie comics Ninja Turtles.
It's one of the most requested things we got
when we were doing the,
because that year when we made that carrying case,
Ken Metroni, who was one of the Archie pencilers, right?
He did the art for the carrying case.
So that was a cartoon set, but with Archie artwork,
and everyone was like, the Archie comics are so great,
when are you gonna just do Archie figures?
And so it was a long time to,
because that was a separate deal we had to negotiate,
and it took a while, but yeah,
we're finally doing proper Archie turtle figures,
which is cool.
For again, men like myself, very exciting.
So this guy Ken who drew the comics,
he's like, he designed a berserk from Toy Story 2?
Ken has got a really insane, amazing career.
And yeah, I think he was drawing the Archie turtle comics
on his lunch break from working on Tiny Toons.
And so that was like, he would just kind of knock those out,
but he did the early run of the comics,
and they're just beloved by people of a certain age.
So yeah, Ken is like, but after,
he was just kind of doing them as a side gig,
and then when he had worked on the Back to the Future cartoon
for a little bit, he did that, he just started naming stuff.
I'll ask Ken, we found this weird show called Fish Police,
I don't know if you guys remember.
Oh yeah, I remember, Prime Time bomb.
Like Post Simpson's.
Yeah, like Capital Critters and all those.
Yeah, yeah.
And I was like, I gotta find,
I'm sure Ken worked on Fish Police,
and he's like, oh, he's like, yeah, I remember that show.
He's like, I didn't do the show, but I did those comics too.
And then like. Fish Police comics?
Yeah, there was a run of Fish Police comics,
and he did gargoyles, and then he went to Pixar,
and he was working, I don't think he worked
on the first Toy Story, but he definitely had
like a big presence on the second one,
created Emperor Zerg.
I think he storyboarded that entire scene
when they're under the parking cones,
like running across the street, like causing chaos.
Oh, what a sequence, that's incredible, wow.
I think Ken did all of that stuff,
but he's just, he's kind of been everywhere
and done everything.
He's got crazy stories about hanging out
with like Kevin Eastman and Peter Laird
back in the height of like the turtles.
Right.
Ken's just a fascinating guy.
He's just got a million stories.
Wait, what's the last name again?
Mitroni.
Yeah.
So, yeah, so I brought a couple things,
just to show my coasts here.
I just wanted to show the range of stuff you do,
because it is pretty crazy.
Like this is Toca from Secret of the U.S.
Oh yeah. I mean, it's like.
You need gloves to handle the show.
I know, I wanna peel the back of it.
It's a murder weapon, really.
Yeah, geez.
Yeah, Jason Fraley sculpted that one.
He's got articulated mouth and the beak,
and the eyebrows are articulated,
so you get all kinds of cool expressions.
So you can pass these around.
It feels like close to being on set, you would think.
Like, I mean, it is small,
but in terms of like texture and realism,
it's as close as we can come to like,
he's saying hi to me on his lunch break.
And his beak moves.
I mean, it's like, these were maybe
my favorite figures that year.
Yeah, that was, Toca and Ra's are a great set.
Yeah, Jason gets like crazy obsessive
with all the details and stuff.
Yeah, this is Usagi.
He's from Usagi Ujumbo.
That's from the Fred Wolf cartoon,
and this is from Coming Out of Her Shells.
So like, the difference in the styles is really remarkable,
which is what makes people like me nuts about this stuff.
What's this frog?
That's one of the punk frogs.
Oh boy, which one is that? From the Fred Wolf.
I always forget which one is which, so that's a blessing.
It's not Genghis.
It's, oh boy, that's Napoleon.
Okay. Yeah.
So yeah, there were four punk frogs, which were like the,
they're like sort of-
They were bad for a little while, but then they-
Yeah, they were kind of counterparts.
Like, Shredder wanted his own team of mutants
that he could train in the evil arts or something.
So he named them all like Genghis, Attila, Rasputin,
and Paul the Author, after his heroes.
Right, of course.
Oh yeah, bad as Fred Wolf figures.
They're called the punk frogs, but they're just not,
like they're from, like they just wear these Hawaiian shirts
and like the shorts, like there's nothing really
that punk about them, you know?
Yeah, I know that the people making it
like knew what punk meant.
Maybe not, I don't know.
And that all their voices, they sounded kind of
like gym neighbors.
So like their voices were all hilarious on the show.
And like the frogs are some of my favorite characters
from the cartoon.
Yeah. Yeah.
So it's, yeah, so you're doing this, like just even
to describe what you do, I think you do a lot of things,
but like you're watching old cartoons for references.
Yeah, I just get paid to watch cartoons
and old turtle movies and bi comics.
You have what sounds like a six year old
from 1989's Dream Job or.
Yeah, definitely very close to that, yeah.
So. Just get to make toys and play with stuff.
And you're looking for details basically,
because like right now I'm holding the,
coming out of our shells, Michelangelo
with a shredded jean vest.
And on the back is a poster for the musical mutagen tour.
Just like the degree of detail fit onto this,
this single action figure is nuts.
Yeah, I sculpted the socks.
No, no, not the socks.
No, those are the fabric leg warmers.
I sculpted the shoes on that guy.
Wow.
Jason that did Toca, he sculpted the head for that one.
That one's got a hinged mouth and the creepy like giant eyes.
Oh yeah, it does perfectly reflect
how those turtles are kind of off.
Yeah, like you incorporate that they're weird suits.
Yeah, we try to capture like kind of the fun weirdness of.
Yeah.
So many, that's incredible that you're,
that's the goal because like a more corporate way
of doing these toys would smooth it out
and not embrace the odd.
No, we have to, it's, yeah, it's just too fun.
We have to like, we're just making the toys that we want.
So like. Yeah.
Even when that became a possibility,
it was like, we really have to,
we just need to go all out and make it crazy.
So like. Yeah.
That's when I remember Lindsay said to me, she goes,
oh, you're like, these are, you're so happy about these,
these coming out of her shoulder,
she didn't call them that, but I go,
I go, you know what this means?
This means anything is possible.
Like I give a very dramatic.
It was a turning point for us.
Yeah. I give a very dramatic thing.
Most optimistic thing I've ever said in my life.
All of a sudden the skies were blue.
So. And then your next thing out of your mouth,
let's have a child.
Yeah, it inspired us to have a child.
Yeah. Oh wow.
Brett, I have a photo that says NECA,
if you could bring it up whenever you get a chance.
So I've, you know, I've been watching all these videos,
like anytime you guys do a thing,
this is by the way, what one of my displays look like.
I've become a display guy.
Okay. Yeah. You gotta have the display.
I've become a shelf.
Right. So now I'm like displaying things.
I have my own light.
Well, I've put some lights under the shelves to display things.
I've always smoked.
So I've turned into like Reverend Lovejoy with his trains.
You're in too deep now.
You're just gone.
Oh my God.
You're in too deep.
Are you kidding me?
When Jane and I got to your birthday party,
we were some of the first ones there and we somehow this came up,
but you were like showing us on your phone on Amazon.
Like I bought these.
Oh, the little lights.
I bought these little lights.
Oh yeah.
You have the accessory set.
You got the TV with a stock and everything.
Oh my God.
I'm I'll tell you how crazy I am later
because we have so much stuff to get to.
But wait a minute.
Wait, jump.
Give us one taste of what is later.
Well, I have a couple, there's a couple of guys,
a couple of toy dudes that I text with and we're always sort of on top of like,
okay, it looks like stuff's hitting this week.
So I happen to be a bunch of your stuff came out at once in March or so.
And I'm in Facebook groups and I all of a sudden you see a bunch of guys start posting about it.
So I go, hmm.
And this is like, baby, I'm watching the baby.
I just by luck had like a lunch meeting to go to
and I built 30 minutes in to go to the North Hollywood Target.
Get the closest target.
Yeah.
Yes.
And I went to North Hollywood and boy, I ran into the guy stocking.
Oh, wow.
As soon as like it was, I almost fell over.
Yeah, perfect time.
And he was uncomfortable because I was just standing there.
I was trying not to be rude, but he felt like I was about to steal everything.
I was like, I'm not taking everything.
I just want one of each.
For a couple of friends, I was getting two things.
So I was just standing there.
I'm late for the lunch meeting, but I cannot believe my luck.
And I just, I got most of the stuff that was released.
So I got that like that week that it came out.
And that employee is safe, healthy.
He's been released.
Non-hospitalized.
His limbs all function.
Because he's in witness protection from me.
So he requested like, hey, is it OK if I transfer to another target?
No, to another country.
I will put my hand on a Bible.
I did not like stalk him or put like one of the Apple tracers on his car or something.
I just it was pure luck that I was there the time he was.
He does not accept your Facebook friend requests, though.
Nobody should.
I don't know you, man.
Just by luck.
I'll take some of the heat off you and tell an embarrassing story.
Kind of a seminal embarrassing story.
I don't think it's come up on the show before, but the presence of Usagi Ujimbo is a big,
plays a big part of this.
Go ahead.
Which was, it was a day in the summer when I was very young.
And, you know, I was up before my mom and I was like,
I think she said we're going to Woolworths today.
And I was like, pacing around, pacing around.
Were you gritting your teeth?
I was just like, OK, they have that whole aisle of action figures.
And I was like, I'm pretty sure they have Usagi Ujimbo.
And if they do, maybe I'll get it today.
And I couldn't wait any longer as I went in and I kind of woke her up.
I was like, hey.
Are we going to Woolworths today?
Woolworths?
She's like, what?
Is everything OK?
I'm like, yeah, I just, what are we doing today?
And she kind of like, eventually was like, why do you, what?
And eventually got out.
And she's like, I don't, please don't ever wake me up again to figure out where we're going
that you can look at action figures.
Did you listen?
I did listen.
You're a good boy.
I think, hey, what's the deal?
Did you get him?
No, I never got him.
I never got him.
So then I, last night as I'm looking at all the NECA stuff and looking at some of
what Mike had talked about and stuff, I have like all of the generate,
because I know there's NECA, Usagi, Ujimbo's.
I'm on eBay and I'm like, how much does the Playmates want?
It's like, oh, inbox, still $50 for the old one that may well be rotting with some plastics,
the packaging or stuff.
But the NECA one looks great.
He looks like picture perfect of the Sein Sakae comic.
Do you want to hold?
Did you want to stay with him?
Yeah, put him, give him to Jason.
This is a thing that you should have, you were denied as a kid.
He looks great.
Yeah, look into his eyes.
Yeah, just bring him next to you.
If you want to cuddle, whatever needs to happen here, we'll give you the space.
I have not read a lot of Usagi, Ujimbo.
It's a thing that's been going for decades and there's phone book size collections.
Yeah, it's digital collections.
Yeah, he's been doing it 40 years next year.
Yeah, and you've gotten to work with Stan Sakae, who did, yeah, which is pretty crazy.
Stan's awesome.
Yeah, when we were doing that figure, it was pretty regular emails back and forth
with Stan's people and Stan directly and creating the artwork for the box and everything.
He's got to approve every stage, the sculpt, the paint, the packaging, all of it.
Yeah, Stan's super cool and great to work with.
He was at WonderCon a couple of months ago and I got to meet him in person and actually
talked to him for a minute or two and yeah, it was cool.
Got him to sign some stuff.
Sure.
Great.
That's awesome.
So yeah, so all this to say, this turtle, you know what, I'll throw one more turtle
thing out real quick and then we'll explain how we got to Canada's wonderland.
Brett, that link I just sent you, a lot of these interviews you do with toy
people that I end up watching, a common thing happens and I kind of feel some sympathy too
because I feel the urge that the interviewers, well, they'll just be like, do you think maybe
there's a chance you could make and then they'll just list one of the characters they want.
Yeah.
Which of course I get that, but also you're like, well, I'll show, like when it happens,
it happens is usually how you can answer that question.
But I will say, is there a chance we could ever get the Disney MGM studio specific characters
and with Alan Thicke singing a song, a five pack.
This is, I'm pushing everybody over at Target.
Any employee I'm pushing over.
If I get my turtles era Alan Thicke.
I've never seen anyone asking about this.
Yeah.
It was only in all honesty, a couple of weeks ago when internally we were talking about this very
thing and kind of joke, like it's probably never ever going to happen, but if I could sculpt
another turtle, it would be like those big kind of puffy like walk around suits like from MGM.
And there's the, they did a video with like the LA transit or something.
Yes.
You know, so there's pictures of like, we were just talking about this the other day.
Like, yeah, those suits would be so, so much fun to do.
And it's again, it's a weird crazy thing that kind of perfectly shows like the height of the
nineties, like the early nineties, like turtle mania.
Yeah.
And like no one's ever thought to sculpt like one of those costumes, like that giant costume
was shrunk down to an action figure would be so cool.
It'd be great.
It's a lot of forms doubling in.
Yeah, we have to wait a second.
Yeah, play a little bit.
I think it's like 38 seconds.
It starts.
We should get a booth at Comic-Con.
You can sell it there.
Sure.
So, cause it's like a theme park thing.
Oh yeah.
38 seconds or so is when Alan starts singing with a rap.
I mean, we're going to, well, aren't we, we've been talking about doing a full episode about
We will do a full episode about this, but yeah, we'll show a little clip, right?
Yeah.
I mean, leather jacket, sunglasses clad, Alan Pick, kind of Terminator ish.
Yeah, I was going to say it's half Terminator and half like David Hasselhoff, like Knight Rider.
Yeah.
With the red shirt and the jacket.
Oh, those, they're so great.
They make like dopey smiles.
Turtles I met at like Cub Foods when they signed my cookie box at age five.
Yeah.
They're still different than like the turtles who might be at, you know, a market opening
or a movie theater opening or the ice capades.
There's a lot more to go.
So yeah, you can stop playing it.
That's the only thing I'll say.
You can also, also bread, feel free to leave this cool Alan Thicke still
where he's looking out into the Florida sun.
I think until we change topics entirely, I would like this to be on screen.
RIP Alan.
I've gotten so much joy out of Alan Thicke.
This is a perfect piece of footage because like, I love 90s Turtles.
You really love 90s Turtles.
I, on top of that, love Alan Thicke's music.
And the music career of Alan Thicke.
Yeah.
Also coming, all coming to the show.
But yeah, I don't know if this helps, if this like, this random focus group,
I was talking to these three random guys who all thought this would be a good idea.
Yeah.
They said it was, yeah, they okayed it.
I'll just tell my boss Randy, it's like, yeah, podcast the ride said it's like, it's gold.
It'll sell.
These will sell.
Yes.
So I'll calm down now and then say that one of these interviews you were doing,
I perked up when I heard you say, I grew up in a theme park.
Yes, that is true.
And I was like, whoa, that phrase again, another child's dream
was your experience growing up.
And that was Canada's Wonderland.
Yeah, that's right.
So yeah, I mean, just where does that mean?
What does it mean?
Tell us.
So basically I wasn't there every day, I didn't live there, but like, yeah, my dad,
the park opened in 81 the same year I was born.
My dad worked there since, you know, he got hired in like 1980.
So he was there like building, helping like just assemble, like get everything together.
So all through the 80s, he was like the games manager at Canada's Wonderland.
So we were just there all the time, like my sister and my mom,
we would just go and hang out like all through the summer and stuff.
I just grew up at Canada's Wonderland.
Wow.
So and actually, and a crazy thing because he would go to toy fair every year.
And this is how like this, it's weird that this probably formed like me, you know?
Like he would come back from New York toy fair with stacks of like toy catalogs.
And then my friends and I would just sit there and just like look through like the Kenner
catalog. It's like you'd see all the new Ghostbusters coming out for like this year.
And so all the Mattel catalogs, you see all the He-Man toys and like it's just,
so my whole life, and then they would send like, they knew my dad, like they knew he had a kid that
was like the perfect age for all of that 80s stuff. So like he would just come home with like
sales samples of, I would get like boxes of Ninja Turtles and like Toxic Crusaders and like,
we just had so many toys, you know? They would just, so yeah, I was like some weird like kind
of test subject kid or something for all this, all the 80s toy mania. I was just like completely
like surrounded by it.
So would he tell people like, oh, my son really responded to Toxic?
I'm sure he did. Yeah.
He was giving feedback on stuff.
There probably was some of that. Yeah. But yeah, we would just get like,
I remember getting like a turtle blimp, but it was like this, it was all incomplete.
It was just like in a box, you know? Wow, really?
Yeah. And so I'd have to like build the missing pieces for it. And I got a general
trag that just came with a Ziploc bag full of weapons, you know? It was like weird samples
that someone had laying around an office and I'd either get like a full fresh case of Toxic
Crusaders or I'd just get like any weird random toy they had like lying around. So I just had like
all this stuff. So did you have, do you still have any of that stuff?
I have a couple of the toy catalogs still. A lot of my old, like a lot of my 80s toys are gone.
It's a very tragic story. And then a lot of, I know I had the Cranks Android body like
for a long time and I'm pretty sure my mom like just took it to the thrift store, you know,
took it to Goodwill or something. My mom gets rid of a lot of that stuff.
Right. Oh geez, Toy Story 3 nightmare.
Yeah. That's not trash.
When you said your dad was the games manager. So that was like the throw the ball.
Yeah. He like built like the Skeeball machine. I was talking to him before I got here and I was
like, he was one of the guys like, you know, they would just get a kit of like unassembled
Skeeball machines. And so they would just like unbox it, like, you know, screw them all together,
like set them up. Like he was building all of that stuff. And then, so all the stuff in the
arcades, like the redemption things where you get like a stuffed animal or like, you know,
there's like those duck races, like he was, he was kind of in charge of all of that stuff.
Wow. So geez, early eighties theme park, Canadian arcade. This is so many, so many keywords.
Yeah. There's a lot to unpack.
Lit up on every level.
So, so, so he, even when the park you were there, he was working there for many years. So he was
just like, he would check on which games were doing well, what was breaking down.
Yeah, probably. Yeah. Yeah.
It's probably all that stuff.
And then, yeah, like if, I don't know, it's like there's, when did the horse racing game with the,
you know what I'm talking about?
You were all the balls.
The roll the balls up. And that's one of my favorites.
With the tiered, where they kind of like step up, there's all the horses.
Yes. It's like, there's a three, there's like a hole that's called three points or like.
Oh yeah. The rings, like it's like, if you get it in the center.
Yeah. Well, I think, yeah.
No, that's no, I'm describing ski ball. Like you're just, yes.
No, no, which one are you talking about?
So there's like a power.
The horse is.
It's a little diamond, I think. And that usually, I think the top is like,
we're three like paces or three steps horse. And then the next one is like two.
And then the bottom one is maybe one. And so if you roll it and you get it up to in the third,
the horse will go one, two, three on the board and you're playing against everybody else.
Oh, I don't know that one.
I'm pretty sure this is the game I beat a bunch of little kids on the Santa Monica pier
and one Homer accidentally though, because I sat down first and then was like, ready to go.
Okay. Play. And then I looked to my right after I won and I went, uh-oh,
you're a man in your twenties who just beat a bunch of kids.
Yeah. He's, he's got stories about, you know, like the guy that invented like whack-a-mole or like.
There's like, he knows, I think he knows all of these people, you know, cause it's,
it's usually just a couple of companies that like, you know, they build all these games or
they come up with some new thing and it's sold to like all the parks, you know, so it's, um,
yeah, he's just, he's got a million, cause he's been doing this stuff since 1980. Like that was
his first, he's been working in like the amusement industry, like since then.
And still.
Yeah, still. Yeah.
Wow. Where is it? Where is he? What is he doing now? Is he, he's not at Canada's wonderland,
but. No, no, he left there. He now he, he works for, um, uh, a company that makes like the,
the stuffed animals. So he's like on the other side, like selling.
Ah, he switched to prizes.
Yeah. He switched to the prizes. So yeah, he's, he's probably a couple of years away from retirement,
but he just, that's all he does is just work. So he's in, he was just at Carowinds yesterday
or he's going there today. I don't, he was just at Dollywood.
Wow.
In the last, like, like I, when I was talking to him on the phone, he's like driving through
North Carolina right now, probably on the way to Carowinds or something.
Geez. Making the, making the round, which is like, like assessing like what's working. What
can we do different? Something like that. Yeah. Hanging out with a bunch of, you know, old, uh,
amusement buddies and stuff like just.
So he's like Dollywood needs a fresh batch of like raccoon plush.
Yeah. And he's the guy that'll, you know, go scrounge that up. You'll find it, get it on a
truck, get it shipped. Like how? And cause he does a lot of, he's a lot of his customers are,
you know, they'll, they'll do like the, like a state fair that's only there for like a couple
weeks or a month. So he's got to make sure like the product hits, like when they, when they're
going to be in town, like it's got to get to the destination. So he's got to coordinate, you know,
with like the shipping company and everything, like make sure they hit all their, their destinations,
like on the right dates. Cause yeah, some of them are like traveling shows and stuff. So.
I don't know. It's an interesting job. Probably. Yeah. That being a job. Yeah.
As a kid, were you so like, yeah, as a kid, what, I mean, obviously everybody's just like,
Oh, this is what my parents do. But did you kind of know like, it's kind of cool.
I knew it was unusual cause like all the other kids in school were just like,
your dad does what, you know? And then we would, you know, everyone would want to go to like
the park with us. And, you know, cause everyone else had, I think normal jobs, you know, so we just
work in an office or do whatever. And yeah, it was just, it was definitely, I knew it was a
weird thing because none of my other friends like kind of lived in an amusement park.
My sister and I were the only ones, you know, in the, in the neighborhood. So
you were really in like a, my uncle worked for Nintendo sort of scenario, but for real,
my dad works for an amusement park. In one of my dad's friends, like,
you remember in Pee Wee's big adventure, when he goes to that novelty, like joke shop and he's
just, Oh, what do you got? What's new this week? And he's got the, like, my dad had a friend like
that for years and he was like, he was one of my uncles, you know, like I think he got me the
Ghostbusters firehouse and all this stuff, but we would go to his guy named Solly and we'd go to his
warehouse where all he had was just novelty, like stuff, like whoopee cushions and like inflatable
rambos and like just, just like every weird thing, like he had all of it. And you know,
we'd get these weird, when Ghostbusters was like huge, he had these like, like a ghost in a can,
like these weird glow in the dark, like fake, but yeah, but it wasn't even that. It was just like,
it was this weird can that would like shake or something. You just find these weird things.
They put like a Ghostbuster logo on it or something. And like an old trick. Yeah. Yeah.
Just be like Ghostbusters. Yeah. This week it's Ghostbusters. Next week it's, you know,
it's Thundercats or whatever. Right. Kids wouldn't know. Yeah. So all of my dad's friends were just
like, they were all in like, you know, this, this industry. So it's just, yeah. So we would just have
all kinds of weird stuff and weird, just like fun, like experiences growing up. It was just crazy.
They were all in the serious business of fun. Yeah. Yeah. Would you go, like when you were going
to like that, that uncle, were you like, X-Trix, like, was there one even like guy you knew,
were you like, this is the best one of all these? That was the guy. It was that guy.
Sully was, it was always going to see him was like always the best. Yeah. Cause it was just,
you never knew what there was, what you're going to find. Cause it was really just a warehouse and
he just let you like dig through everything. And you know, it was, it was great. And there was like,
I remember some kind of a showroom or something, but yeah, it was just, it was all just like those,
those weird, like those finger puppets or like those weird ugly faces where you'd put like,
you get your thumb and fingers in there and like scrunch up the faces. And it was just like,
there's just all, he had all like the wacky wall crawlers and all that, all that sticky,
like gooey stuff. Like, like the hands that would like splat. And we had, my mom would like,
she never wanted us, wanted me bringing that stuff home. Cause I just stick everything to the wall
and get ground into the carpet and like ruin everything. Just pick up hair. If you're not
careful with that stuff. Yeah. It was good for about two minutes. Cause you drop it, it would
just be full of lint and dust and hair. Yeah. The scourge of moms in the nineties was any number of
sticky items. Like all that goo and slime. They're so happy. The kids are so happy. I don't
want to make them sad, but also our walls are atrocious now. Every good toy line had slime.
Yeah. And I think, yeah. What was like Flo was Floam one of them in the like late 90s.
That was an yeah, like a nineties Nickelodeon. Yeah. Yeah. Did you have Gack or, or ooze or?
I don't remember. I don't remember which one I did. I wanted to have all of them.
Floam feels very familiar where it has like the, it has the little, the little like dot seeds,
like a little granules or something. Yeah. Yeah. Then it would get, it would get so disgusting when
it just like, yeah, yeah. Just, yeah. The dried up version of it was like, like old cat shit or
something. You guys did, uh, didn't Muck Man, didn't you put ooze in him? Yeah. I don't think
I've opened the ooze still. Um, it's probably dried up by now. You think it is? It may be.
Cause we, we've done two slime toys. We did a prop replica of the mutagen canister from the
first movie and that came with the jar of slime. And I have that sitting on my shelf at home and
it's just like a hockey puck now. It's just all, it's, it's all evaporated and just whatever
thing is left. But yeah, Muck Man was the other one we, we gave a little, um,
open that slime. Yeah. Now we know, yeah, now we know the shelf life of Muck.
Yeah. They were not proper. Yeah. I have a bag of that stuff. Cause the factory, yeah, they,
cause the factory, we're trying to get the right color, you know, or the right consistency or
something. So the factory will just send us like five different samples. I was just here, just
label them A, B, C, D, and I'll just pick the one I like best. And I have this also, I just found
the other day under my bed, there's like a, just a rubber made tub of like toys and stuff. And there's
a bag of slime jars. They've been sitting under there since we made the Muck Man figures.
Oh, those were just the samples. Those are the, those are the early samples where I had to just
pick the one I like best. So yeah, all mucks. Yeah. There's just a whole bunch of slime.
Rejected. So there's a factory that just makes slime still. Oh yeah, probably. It was probably
a few slimes. Big there's a, you ever go to power con? There was like the, I've never been to power
con. Okay. So I had a booth there like 2019 or 2018 or something like that. And we were kind of
into, it was in a little ballroom out in Torrance, like at a Marriott or something. So I was in like
the overflow section out in the hallway. I had a little table set up, I was selling like this
nonsense, like artwork and everything. And like two tables over from me, there was like a girl and her
dad and their booth was called the slime pit. And she just brought like homemade slime. Oh yes. That
was huge a few years ago. Right before the pandemic. Yeah. So she came in, her and her dad,
they set up this table of slime and every, everything was sold in like an hour or something.
Yeah. They just like, they came in like just sold all their slime and then they were just, they just
kind of hung it up and just walked her in. Like just, it was this little girl, she just made it
like a killing it. Like the family slime business. Yeah. Yeah. Wow. What can I, if I keep asking
questions, are we going to get down to some weird place? Like what is, what do people like slime?
What's the appeal? I think it was the same appeal as when it was big when, when like we were kids,
but I had a science teacher for a few years in elementary school and she, that was how she got
kids interested in science. She'd be like, who died in cornstarch and like everyone get a beaker
of water and you could just make slime. Right. It was like incredibly simple. Yeah. I guess I did
make it. I think I, I, even though I had it, I think I was maybe like, it felt messy to me
and maybe I didn't like. Oh, you're right. I was not. Yeah. Yeah. Like finger painting and
I didn't like any of that stuff when I was a kid. Yeah. Scott's slime pro. Pro. I feel like I liked
the idea of it more than the, than the messy reality. Like being slimed would scare me. Yeah.
Yeah. Or what, what, uh, you can't, did you watch, you can't do or no, not yet. Well, that's what
it's like, but, um, what would you do? Which is the game show on Nickelodeon that Mark Summers
hosted. Oh, double dare. No, no, this was the other game show. There's this other one where it was
just like, I, what is it? I don't know. Lots of excuses for slime and pies. Can we like reduce,
let's get those questions out of there. Just make it a big nightmare. Just being on one of those
shows where you're just like diving into a pit of like goo. I still kind of want it. I would do that.
I would do it now. But as a kid, I was like the idea of being messy in public. I didn't like that
at all. I had one thing of GAC that again was me, like as a kid, I knew I had seen so many
commercials for like the Chuck E. Cheese GAC tie in where you could, if you went to Chuck E. Cheese
and you got enough, you spent so much for enough tokens, you get a three free miniature thing of
GAC that smelled like pizza and we got it home and I was just so excited and my mom opened it up and
it was the most overwhelming garlic smell I've ever smelled in my life. And she's like, I'm sorry.
No, I can't. We're not. And she's like, I'm sorry. You won a lot of toys today. So you didn't come
home at the end of it, but like these have to go in the garbage because-
And you watched it be thrown away.
I could tell. Her side of the fact, like my grandfather, he hated garlic and he passed it
on to his kids. The hatred of garlic?
The hatred and smell of, taste of garlic, smell of garlic. So that you open this thing of GAC
and it smelled like garlic. I was like, oh no.
Also Chuck E. Cheese garlic is beyond, you know, it's not like fresh from the old country or
something. Yeah.
You may appreciate that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
At a nice restaurant, but I'm sure, I mean, cause that Chuck E. Cheese smell that that-
Oh, I didn't particularly like it either, but no, this was unopened Virgin GAC, promo GAC.
We gotta see if we can find a vintage sample of this and bring it back to life.
Yeah.
Of your Chuck E. Cheese GAC for Jason.
Mike, you were correct that if we kept talking about this, we'd get to something weird,
which is the phrase Virgin GAC.
It did. It was bound to happen.
Sure. Untouched GAC. I mean, who knows how long it had been there? Who knows how long
like it had been sitting around, but like, yeah, as soon as I smelled garlic, I was like, oh no.
Like I knew this was not- Dreams are crushed.
Dreams are crushed. Had not made an attempt to get GAC before this.
Maybe that's a side hustle for you is selling garlic GAC, garlic slime.
Maybe. Yeah.
I think I could, I think I could figure it out.
I think- With the smell, you can make it imbued with,
I mean, you just gotta keep it in a room, I guess.
I think the thing to do would be get that frozen cubes, you know, of like basil and garlic.
And you mix that in the slime.
Yeah.
Does he have to do this? Did you, okay. Do you, how much does Mike need it to happen
and how much does Jason actually want it to happen?
Well, you just saw how excited he was. He looked so happy.
I got kind of excited, yeah. Thinking about Jason selling garlic slime
at some convention somewhere. I think I really just like the idea of Jason with a little table
selling slime in general. Step right up, step right up.
Yeah. You could wear like the old timey outfit.
The barker. Yeah. Yeah.
The smelliest slime in town. And the straw hat and everything.
So how many times a week are you at Canada's Wonderland as a kid?
Oh, yeah. I wish I had kept a diary or some journal.
Yeah. It was, I know my dad said every birthday we were there.
Sure. And I think it was,
I remember my mom saying there were just days in the summer where if there was just,
everyone was bored, there was nothing to do. She'd just like pack us in the car and just
drive to Wonderland. We'd just run around.
So yeah, I just remember just always being there.
This is Toronto by the way. It's right outside of, yeah,
it's right outside north of Toronto. Which seems like, look, I soak up a lot of this.
I am not from Canada, but I'm jealous of people from Canada. I watch so much like,
do you watch that retro Ontario? It's a great channel. Yeah. Oh yeah.
Retro Ontario. That is a real, that is a true like just a blast from the past,
like watching old city TV clips and just all the weird random stuff that come.
Sometimes it's frustrating though, because they'll just have a clip of something.
Cause we'll just turn that on a night and start watching it. And
some weird thing will just pop on and then it cuts to the next thing. And I'm just like,
God damn it. I want to watch the entire, I just want to see the whole episode of,
there was like a grandpa rental thing on a, they had like a, it's not like a news show,
but it was some sort of like, there were people sitting in this room
talking about like the day's events and then they would have like guests on.
And I swear this happened. I know it was late at night, but like I'm watching this thing and they
brought on like a little boy and there was like this old man and there was like some sort of
service somewhere in Toronto or part of Ontario where like if your grandparents had like died or
they weren't around, like there was like a, it was almost like a, like not like a nanny or a,
you know, like a babysitter thing, but it was just specifically to go hang out with like old people
for the day. You could call a number and they would just send you a grandpa. And then it just
cuts. And then it goes to some other, like there's a guy reviewing movies or they're talking about
some other weird, there's like a parade for something. And I'm like, we got to finish this
grandpa story. Like, yeah. Oh my God. Did you find something? Is this the thing? Wait a minute. No,
this is, okay. I looked up grandpa rentals, restaurant, Ontario, and I'm, I found an ad.
I really excited because I found an ad with Ed Asner and suddenly I'm like, is Ed Asner the
spokesman for grandpa rentals, but it's something else called Granada rentals. It was kind of
a, did you mean he's like taking you into it? Like maybe a TV rentals, a movie rental store.
Cause if I was like, did I just find the greatest clip in history and Asner on behalf of do you
need a grandpa? But you don't want one long-term, you need a short term hang with a grandpa.
Don't have the money required to permanently buy a grandpa.
Well, we got to keep looking for that. Yeah. Yeah. I would like to, oh yeah. Yeah. Retro Ontario is,
that's a good channel. And the kids shows were you guys had Bowser on recently, right? And like
the Canadian kids shows like Mr. Dress Up and Fred Penner and like, they were so great. Yeah.
Sharon Lewis and Bram, Canadian. They were pretty Canadian. Yeah. Cause I had seen them
at Canada's wonderland. They had like an amphitheater. I was actually, I have one of
Bowser's shirts. There's a Sharon Lewis and Bram like concert t-shirt that he just made.
So I was wearing that at some other, there was like a banjo festival just like a week or two ago.
Sure. So I'm wearing my Sharon Lewis and Bram shirt waiting in line to buy some like barbecue
and some old guy comes walking over and he's just staring at like, he's like,
what is that shirt? And he's like, what year did you see them? I said, I don't know. I was like,
it's Bowser's shirt. You know, it's like maybe it was from the eighties. And this guy told me that
when his daughter got married, their first dance is like, was the Skinner Marinky Dinky Dinky.
The elephant song. Yeah. The elephant song. And this guy and his wife were just,
Bowser's shirt just brought so much joy to the banjo and fiddle festival. Oh my God.
I guess that, you know what? That's shocking, but also at the banjo festival, it just feels right.
Yeah. Yeah. It was great. Like a very low key. Did you watch the elephant show? Yeah. Yeah.
Was that Nickelodeon, I think, when we were kids? Yeah, it could have been.
It makes so much sense to me. Like, as a kid, I was like, so there's so many hours of shows made
just for us kids. How do they find the time? And then realizing, oh, a lot of it is repurposed
Canadian. Yeah. And especially if it's like very, you know, sweater and beard and brown, then you
know it's probably a Canadian export, which I liked anything like that. Very childhood affinity
for sure. For just like the calmness of the Canadian programming. Do you guys remember
Size Small? You ever seen that? No. That sounds so familiar. There's a guy, there's a giant record,
his name's Friend Record. It's like a human sized vinyl record. Nanthropomorphic record. Yeah. Oh,
Size Small is scary. Size Small is a crazy one. But yeah, Friend Record would come out and he'd
tap some, the spoons were named Tip and Tap and they would like, they'd sing some songs. But it
was a guy like in a black leotard that sort of like stepped through a record and then it was just
like a big smiling face and stuff. Kind of scary. I think just like the- Freaky. This big round shape
was kind of a blunt smile. And then he, Friend Record had a cousin named like Cousin Wagon Wheel
or something and they kind of repurposed the costume into a giant like wagon wheel. Wow.
And so this was too weird for Nickelodeon to buy the rights to show it? Yeah. They might have passed
on that one. But it was totally fine for Canada. They showed it in Ontario and like Manitoba and
everywhere. Let me ask something I can't now not ask about, and it ties into Canada's Wonderland.
Did you grow up with the show The Littlest Hobo? Well, we've got, we may have a clip or two.
Oh, okay. Good. Oh, really? Good. Good. Good. All right. All right. Well, thank God. I was
disappointed in myself. I didn't have them. Yes. Is now a good time. I mean, I guess you brought it
up. Wait, wait, sorry. What was your answer to that? Yeah. Who doesn't like The Littlest Hobo?
I did. Well, did you know? I heard it, I think, but I didn't know what it was until Trevor brought
it to my attention. About five years, 10 years ago, I learned about The Littlest Hobo. That's about
when I did too. Yeah. I had this big phase like seven, eight years ago. I think after I did a
trip to Toronto and enjoyed it so much and just wanted to soak up more Canadian stuff. You talk
about early 80s, pleasant Canadian aesthetic. This show, oh my God, had such a calming effect on me
for a while, just eating up these YouTube versions. The Littlest Hobo, for anyone who doesn't know,
was a show about the most trusty dog there could ever be, just a good, good dog. Very good dog,
who goes from town to town, encounters strangers, susses out the problems in their life
and with each other, fixes the problems by moving various objects around with his mouth,
solves everything that's going on in this family or this town or whatever,
real quick. Then it enters everybody's mind, this dog has been such a great presence in our lives,
maybe the dog should stay. Then there's always someone who knows, like, no, this dog just keeps
moving on because the dog is The Littlest Hobo and a hobo doesn't stick around. The hobo gets on the
train and keeps riding to the next spot where he's needed again. Six seasons. Wow. Of the 70s,
there was a 60s version I read. Oh, really? Two seasons for the 60s versions and six seasons for
the 1979 version. Yeah. Can I ask, we don't have this unless you said- Well, I have three clips
from an episode that I think you're probably talking about. Yeah, but now I'm like, I need the
song. Oh, I have it. Brett, you have the intro song? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Mike, thank you. You have-
Because I knew when we talked, heard Littlest Hobo, this is something, this is red meat for us.
Yeah, yeah, I can't. Littlest is a thing we like, hobo is a thing we like. The dog is a hobo. The
dog being a hobo, this is red. Yeah. And then this song is the, I might throw this in the
discussion of best theme song of all time. Yeah, Brett, it's hobo one is the clip. Oh, thank you,
Mike. It was my insecurity today. I feel like I'm prepared for the episode, but I didn't bother to
clip the Littlest Hobo theme. No, it's okay. Thank Trevor for this. Oh, good. Okay, well, yes. He's
the one who sent it to me. Oh, you're welcome. Oh, you're welcome. Okay, okay. Fascinating you know
this. I had such a big Littlest Hobo phase that I'm so fond of. I think we'll play it and we'll
edit it if it's not. I think we're good. Oh.
Starring London the dog. I love you, London.
Maybe tomorrow I'll want to settle down until tomorrow. Balloons and then pleasant shots of
the dog. The background horns there. Wonderful orchestration. Just grab your hat and we'll travel.
The light that's hobo style. Maybe tomorrow I'll want to settle down. And is this the one that has,
he's holding a rifle in his mouth. Oh, like a big gun. A big gun with a strap. The dog is running
with a rifle in its mouth as a party. Wow. There's so much to like about that. It's like smoking a
bunch of cigarettes. I don't, yes, a ton to like, can I also just say that this is how deep the
phase went that I had a tradition for a while of giving my wife birthday presents that were like
little custom videos of our cat at the time, Beanie, RIP Beanie. We love Beanie. And I recreated that
intro with the black squares and the yellow font with our cat. And with new lyrics based on our cat,
including I got a little like 99 cent store, little toy gun and tried to prop it up next to
the cat's mouth as best as I could. It was not happening. Did not take, but I tried. Yeah. Love
Lola Sobo. Wow. That's incredible. But you brought it up presumably because of the tie into Canada's
wonderland. Yeah. We actually go back to, sorry, we'll go back to the clip and play it after that
because I have some clips of the him going to the park. So, okay. Yeah. No, no. Yeah. I,
my girlfriend and I, we were, we went down some rabbit's hole of like, just like weird,
like Canada's wonderland stuff a couple of years ago, or maybe that's when we found like retro
Ontario and I don't know. We were just, she's also fascinated just Canada stuff. And not from Canada.
She's not, no, she's from here. Wow. Wow. Yeah. And just like weird, just, she's just fascinated
by all this stuff. So yeah, we found this, this Canada's wonderland episode of the littlest hobo.
And again, she just got sucked into this. It was just so strange. And it's like the whole episode
is kind of, it's just so bizarre, you know, cause it's like the day before the park is opening and,
and there's just no one in there, but this lady that's like has amnesia. And then she's very
troubled. She like, she was in a car accident, scrambled her brain up and she knows enough
people, there's enough awareness that she is not just an employee of Canada's wonderland, but like
the employee misses wonderland or something. Yeah. Yeah. They can't open without her without her.
Cause then once, once it's the day before, so it's like, they need her so badly. Yes. This
cannot happen without her. Brett, just play that, play it right here from here. Cause this is like,
the littlest hobo going into the park again, like at the start, I haven't seen a lot of little
less hobo now, but this would be like the setup to, yeah, this is where little less hobo just sort
of wanders up to the front gate. There's no one there. Right. One security guard and he's like,
what are you doing here? Little hobo? And the little, this is like this little hobo would sense
something was wrong and then he was needed. He gets it so fast, walks up to three people, figures
out the problem in their lives. See how alert he is. He knows he just knows something's happening.
And this is the entrance to Candice Wonderland that you remember. No, I don't remember this
cause we always took the employee entrance. So like seeing the front gate is bizarre cause I just,
like we never went in that way. So you didn't get to walk in the paw prints of the littlest
hobo. Oh, I wish I could have. That sign, that lovely like rounded orange to yellow gradient
so eighties. Yeah. So we have a couple more clips too. So yeah, you really get a good view of the
park in a lot of different angles here. Yeah. Empty. It's a weird, I'm curious when they film,
if this genuinely was before the park opened or did they like carve out a day and create a retroactive
plot set before the park opened? I wonder what the air date of this episode was. I don't know
the episode is the show is definitely on. It might've premiered in like this is one thing I
asked my dad about. I was like, do you remember like this littlest hobo show? He's like, oh yeah,
sure. Well, they filmed the whole episode of Wonderland. He goes, I don't know. Wow.
No memory of this at all. Cause it seems like it would have been a big deal cause they have like
cast members like going on the, you know, they have to set up cameras and like,
they're filming all over the park. So they almost, they invent like a new, we have watched so much
sitcom and TV show episodes, killing time at theme parks. It's some of our favorite where you don't
have to worry about any of this meat, any of this story nonsense. You can just watch your friends go
on rides and yell and laugh. But this is a rare episode where they find a new way to contextualize
just a character going on a roller coaster because she has amnesia and she's flashing back to a bad
car accident that just happened. So she gets on a roller coaster and then forgets why she got on it.
And then she's like having an episode on the coaster. It's a horrible thing for her. Oh,
it's bigger flashback to the car. Like usually it's not used for horror. Yeah. No, it's fun.
It should be like inviting. It should be a good ad for the place. It's also strange that yes,
this like, it's a big episode of this pleasant show set in a theme park where a woman's having
manic episodes and where like, let's just say one thing we haven't said about Canada's wonderland,
kind of their castle essentially is like a big fake rock mountain. Yeah. Wonder mountain.
Okay. That looks fantastic. And they had cliff divers, which is sort of revealed in this episode.
But part of her forgetting who she is or what's happening, she just kind of like starts climbing
instinctually. Yeah. There's something leads her up that path to the top of the mountain.
Yeah. For no reason. She's just walking up to it and then like teetering on the edge,
which you're of course getting. I mean, some of it is just confusion, but you're certainly like,
you're dancing on a suicide plot or that she might hurt herself somehow. And it's so funny.
The theme park would go, yeah, this woman is having a, just a mental breakdown and might
kill herself on our big famous cliff. Yeah. You would think they would just not have shown
Canada's wonderland. Yeah. They would have called it something else. It would film there, but not,
not like their logo proudly in the very first shot of the. Let's just real quick. Just hobo two
clip brats, please. If you would. You know, a major head trauma. You usually want to avoid
mountains, massive heights, a roller coaster. Oh, absolutely. So this is a clip of the littlest hobo
sort of learning about this lady and her struggles. And then he helps her out. He makes an attempt to
help her out here. So yeah, whenever you're ready. I don't seem to have a purse. He doesn't know
where her purse is. And then we cut to. Where's my purse? We cut to a doctor's office.
They have her purse at the doctor's office. Diabetic. I'm a severe one. I don't think she'll
get very far without this. Concussion, severe diabetes and probable amnesia. In her state,
there's no telling what she'd do. If she can't remember who she is, she's not going to remember
she's a diabetic. You better call a personal physician, Dr. Klein, and find out what time
of day she normally takes her injection and where she works. You got it? Yes, doctor.
Stakes are high. Well, how does she feel about roller coasters?
The little hobo knows this kind. He knows that she's diabetic somehow. He can sense it. Yeah.
He doesn't have that doctor's information. Yeah. He might've read her chart. He's, you know,
resourceful. Yeah. He might've checked on her before he even showed up here.
It's possible it's practical and he just can smell the blood sugar level. Oh, yeah. And he
knows that way. That could be. And now some real like muppets of construction workers.
With their lunch pails. A pails and a hits. Yeah. So little
fellow steals a sandwich from one of them. Oh, you want me to chase you now, huh?
Forget it. I don't even like bologna and mayonnaise. Enjoy it. That's a very Canadian
construction worker. He's not at all angry about the sandwich. He's happy. Yeah. He's happy. Oh,
you think you can take my sandwich? Do you? Okay. Well, I hope you enjoy it.
Give it a better home than I would have. Thanks for taking it from me.
So then he walks and he feed the woman is gone. The whole water. Scope of that. Waterfall.
Yeah. You see great shots of this. We can post some of this. You'll see shots of this part.
Oh, this is great. It cuts off here, unfortunately, but then there's a bunch of pirates in a lake.
Yeah. So you see, yeah, shots of the rides running. There's a dragon breathing fire.
Everything at this theme park is triggering this woman. The dragon breathing fire is making her
lose her mind. She's teetering on death because of all the fun stuff you can do. Right. Canada's
Wonderland. So Trevor, you've been on all these rides, I assume? I saw a lot of them. The crazy
thing is I was terrified of all these. Oh, really? My mom and I would just sit on the bench and watch
them. My dad and my little sister would go on roller coasters. I was terrified. The bumper cars
were fun. The little kid rides were mostly okay, but yeah, I was terrified of roller coaster until,
boy, it was junior high school or something. I went on an actual roller coaster for the first
time. But yeah, all these rides, the Ghoster coaster was the little kid Scooby Doo roller
coaster and it was just too terrifying. It's a heavy duty coaster park to this day. I feel
lame for how long I was scared of Space Mountain, which is a little dopey compared to, I mean,
there's heavy duty coasters if you guys want to. In the 90s, they got a really cool one. There's
a Top Gun ride where your feet dangle. It's the tracks above your head. That one's got really
tight corkscrews and loops and it's just crazy fast. That one I did go on eventually. That was
a great ride. It's a little bit like the Raptor at Cedar Point. I don't know if you know Cedar Point
too well. We have never covered Cedar Point. It's a big one. We're also not. Jason's the most brave
of the three of us. We really all started out scared, a little scared, even though we're
doing a theme park podcast and you would think we should be guys that go on everything.
Yeah. The current count of this park is 18 coasters. It's only behind Six Flags Magic Mountain.
That thing really ranks it in terms of number of coasters. I forget whether that's North America
or worldwide, but this park has both a hyper coaster and a giga coaster.
Oh, really? What are those?
A behemoth is the hyper coaster and then I think Leviathan opened. Only a few years later,
this park has a behemoth and a Leviathan. That is the giga coaster.
What is a giga coaster? I think it is however many hundred
feet that initial drop is. I think hyper is 200 feet or thereabouts and giga coaster is maybe
300 feet. Between 300 and 399 is giga. Oh my God.
Yeah. This park has a very detailed YouTube channel where they put a high definition camera on
every coaster. To do the POV stuff?
Like you can sit and add a big TV and it is disorienting. Especially Leviathan is so large,
it is unnerving to watch on a big television, but cool too.
Sure. When you would go in real quick, the employee entrance,
you would know the people working or did you have a pass of some kind?
I do not remember us having a... That is the weird thing. I do not remember ever having a pass or a
badge. My mom might have, but I do remember there is probably times where I was being a little brat
and there would be a security person or someone just kind of... Because there was a fence or this
wall with a little slit behind it and then another little fake wall and you just kind of
sneak through there and then it would go into the back where the office is and the
employee parking lot and everything was. But you just go around there and it is obviously
restricted access and stuff, but we would just run in and out of there all the time. Because my
dad's office was in the building behind there. But I am sure there were people that were like,
hey kid, come back here. There were people try to stop us. But I think we were always...
I do not know. I think my mom or someone was always around where they would let us go.
Also, if it is Canadian security guards, then probably.
Yeah. It was like that guy in the thing.
It was like the guy. He was just, ah. He goes, I hope you enjoy the employee lot.
Hope you have a good reason to be back there. No need to tell it to me. Just know it in your
own heart. Yeah, exactly.
I do like the idea that it would just be like everybody knows everybody. So it is like folks
say, oh, you are back. Hey, good to see you.
It was definitely a little folksy. There was like when we were in the office where my dad worked,
I remember the lower... They were on the second floor maybe and underneath was like,
it was where they were doing all the baking and stuff for all the restaurants. And there was like
the head chef guy was always... We would go down there. I think his name was like Pat. But
we would go down there and there would always be some giant cookie or like all this stuff. They
would just see us and they would just give us all this stuff.
Wow. Little street urchins.
The dream. You were the littlest hobos.
Yeah, I took over for the dog. Getting scraps from
them. Stealing baloney sandwiches.
What ages were you from when your dad started to when he was not?
I was like from one to 10 or zero to nine or something. We moved to Ohio in like
1990 or 91 maybe. So yeah, it was all through the 80s we were there.
Wow. Seemed like the time to be there too from...
It was like we were there before Paramount bought it.
Yeah. I was going to ask because as a kid I knew about Canada's Wonderland because my family
regularly went to King's Dominion in Virginia and they're like sister parks. And they did the full
owned by Taft Broadcasting and that's when you had Hanna Barbera and the Smurfs.
And then Paramount comes in in the mid 90s and that definitely elevated those parks in our
in my mind. I think my family's mind too because we're like yeah, Paramount movie studio like
Disney and Universal and MGM. And so like Yogi Bear would still be around, but there would
suddenly be Nickelodeon stuff and like Wayne's World or like the days of thunder sim. I love
the days of thunder motion simulator ride. And then for very briefly a Richard Scary restaurant.
Oh, really? I missed that. Really?
In this one or in King's Dominion? In King's Dominion.
I think Nickelodeon had the cartoon for a number of years. So I think by that way,
the Paramount connection. It seemed to me, I watched like a compilation of ads and they
seemed to assert, it seemed like one thing they were pushing is if you go to this Paramount-owned
theme park and you get on a roller coaster, there might be a Klingon sitting next to you.
Oh yeah, that was in those. Do you remember that really? Did that hit you like,
I want to do that. I want to go on a ride with a Klingon.
So I remember going back to visit in the 90s and the one thing I regret now more than ever was not
seeing, I didn't see any Klingons on any of the roller, like Top Gun or any of those rides,
which was a bummer, but not going to see the Star Trek on ice, like figure skating show.
Oh wow. That's like a huge,
huge regret that I wish I had appreciated that back then.
Yeah, that's insane. I have a clip called Star Trek Ice.
Did we ever talk about this in any of this? We mentioned that it's come up, but we haven't
done a lot. Because I saw it. I saw the one in King's Dominion.
How was it? It was cool. I mean, it was people ice skating and like-
It doesn't make a lot of sense for Star Trek, but it does look kind of cool.
It looks cool. It's that we got here.
It looks like the Thor in Star Wars. Yeah, it's kind of-
More than it does Star Trek. Yeah, a little, especially with that window.
But it could be a Klingon thing or something. That's true. Yeah, you're right. It could be
a different. Yeah, so play this at the start whenever, just a little taste of what it-
So they're playing the iconic Star Trek theme. They got that much right.
Which is, yeah, you need that. This could be on the holodeck or something.
Oh, that's true too. And it's basically like you would imagine people in Star Trek outfits
just twirling around and doing all the things you do as an ice skater.
Yeah, heavy on the fog. Lots of fog.
Yeah. Is it imagining that there's an enterprise with an ice floor?
Is that the idea here? Well, after this, and I don't have a clip of it, but after this,
they switch to a very dark people flying portion of it.
Where it seems like they're representing the stars.
Each one of them is an M-class planet or something.
Yeah. They switch from crew members to planets.
Yeah. They kind of abandon a traditional narrative right away.
And they go into something that's maybe more just ethereal sort of feeling.
Abstract kind of. This is a daring show.
Must have won awards, I'd imagine. Won Tonys, I think.
We haven't done, I guess we haven't done, we've kind of a couple, we did the ice,
the Mario on ice a couple of months ago.
As we determined, there's more with ice capades.
Ice capades in general we need to do more of too.
I saw Ewoks on ice when I was a kid. I don't even know that one.
Ewoks ice? Yeah, that was somewhere in Toronto.
Really? Yeah, probably in like 85 or 86 maybe.
Was it, did it feel like Return of the Jedi or was it more cartoon-y?
Oh, this was like cartoon. Oh, here I see a TV ad.
Oh yeah, there's a little. Oh wow.
Oh, this looks good. We might have to do this.
Yeah, we do have to do that.
The suits look good. Yeah, there was, they had all kinds of
like those crazy ice shows back in the day.
Like everything was an ice show.
I don't want to go giving you more toy ideas, but ice skating Ewoks.
Oh yeah, I know.
Well that's, they just, what, Hasbro's doing some new Ewoks
that are a little more cartoon-y I feel like.
I think they just showed a few things that are like kind of like the Ewoks cartoon or droids.
They've done, yeah, they've done a few things.
Like there's a Boba Fett I think that's like either from like the droids episode
or like the holiday special episode maybe.
Oh cool.
Real quick, real quick back to the turtles.
What's happened now is that you guys have ruined me for other toy lines in the sense that like
X-Men buying X-Men, I'm like, well I would like an X-Men in the style of Joe Manavarro.
I would like X-Men in the style of this.
So now I'm ruined forever because of the turtles.
Yeah, yeah, there's two ways to kind of design those toy lines, you know, where it's,
you can do kind of like a, I don't know, like just a generic looking version of like the characters
or you can kind of go like source material specific.
And like companies like DC Direct, they would do these like, you know, Darwin Cook figures
or like Jack Kirby, like New God stuff.
And I just always loved when like you'd get like a, you know, Jim Lee Batman or something.
So yeah, it was, that'd be great to get some really cool like Joe Mad X-Men or.
Yes, because they kind of did it in like old toy biz.
I have a few of them back in the day.
They were certainly inspired by him.
Yeah, there was a few.
Yeah, one of my favorite Green Goblins is based on the Humberto Ramos drawings.
Yes, I remember this.
Yeah, that was toy biz like way back.
They did a couple, there was like Storm with the big hair and like the two-piece outfit.
Yeah, there was like that monster series where like they had kind of like clip-on,
like mutant armor, like kind of monster pieces.
I remember that.
Those were definitely more, you know, artist specific like sculpts.
That's very cool.
We've talked before on the show about like, because I kind of feel like collector wise,
there is something that if they were made, everybody would become like a completist.
I'm not fully complete with Turtles, but I'm close.
Like Scott, we think we figured out that if it was like 80s architecture,
if people recreated like 80s shopping malls or office buildings.
Yeah, well, and I'll bring Toronto into it.
If I could get a really well done Eaton Center or CN Tower or Sky Dome,
I would gladly.
Just like a play set or something or what?
Yeah, no, they're just like a little model.
I think a little model.
I would take almost any size.
Yeah, I'm trying to, I mean, of course I would love a Technodrome size.
Yeah, yeah.
But I'll take whatever.
What's the other play, the CNE, like the Expo Center or something?
What is that?
That's somewhere in, I think it's around Toronto.
They would have like Maple Leaf Wrestling and there's, it was an,
an arena or a convention center more so.
It's more like a, yeah, like I think it's an outdoor convention center place.
Okay.
But I think it's right around where like Sky Dome and.
Oh, is it?
It's in that sort of, yeah.
I don't know.
If I could get a Sky Dome with a retractable roof, which again, that's like,
have you ever seen the opening of the Sky Dome with Alan Thicke?
Oh, with Alan, oh my God, with Alan Thicke, no.
It's another Alan Thicke.
I was going to say, yeah, like I'd been to Blue Jays games and stuff, but.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I didn't, I wasn't there with Alan Thicke.
I mean, the first opening of this guy, the first time they ever opened it,
where there is an original long musical number sung by Alan Thicke and Andrea Martin, I believe,
they had to make a long, long Broadway style song about retractable ceilings.
They had to like, how many different ways can we reframe lyrics to be, to like,
to focus on retractability?
It feels like how they, you know, there's that thing of like
50s and 60s, like trade show musicals.
Everything's coming to a profit.
Uh huh.
Yes, it felt like a throwback to that.
Like we have a long song about how it could be open when the sun is out and it can be closed.
And then the whole thing was, all right, now let's open it.
And it was raining so hard and they already had scheduled like skydivers
who had to dive into the skydome in the rain.
So there's tarps everywhere.
Big disaster.
That's some of the best.
I'm no expert.
I'm not from there, but in terms of Canadian entertainment, I've seen the skydome.
You're in.
That's one of the, oh, that sounds great.
It's so funny.
I wonder how long, like after you hit the open button, I wonder how long it takes to,
like if you, oh, this was a bad idea.
We should close it.
And then you hit the close button.
Like how long does it take to reset that?
You know how like, uh.
Pretty mighty.
And especially what, you know, like once it starts moving.
Yeah, I think we're talking half an hour.
It's raining.
Close it.
Go, go, go, go.
It's still got 15 minutes of like resetting and slowing down.
It has to be.
And if you pray, if you panic and press the button a bunch of times really fast,
each one of those was a different, now it has to close a little bit and open a little bit.
It's like the biggest garage door on earth.
You can't like stop it at certain points, like a garage door.
That's either it's all the way forward or it's all the way forward.
Two spots where it could pause.
Yeah.
Yep.
That's tricky.
Tricky retractable ceilings.
But anyway, if I could, I would like a playset, a detailed playset of
everyone present at the opening of the Sky Dome in 1990.
We should do that.
Maybe I'm getting the year wrong, but yeah, again, I look, I'm just spitballing.
I can't start demanding these things, but I, you know.
Demand all you want.
Yeah.
No.
Jason, of course, wants a complete set of original little rascals.
I think completely.
Oh, sure.
Who's your favorite little rascal?
Oh, God.
That's, I mean, I feel like everyone is everyone going to say Alfalfa?
Yeah, probably.
Yeah, probably Alfalfa.
If you have to pick between Joe Cobb and Chubby Chaney.
I don't think I can go that deep.
Oh, you know, do you know Brisbane?
He's Brisbane's great.
Is that your favorite little rascal?
These are expanded rascals.
Is this like the Curly Joe, like Three Stooges type rascals?
He's way better.
I did watch a little rascal short recently because it came on a DVD.
Trying to remember what I was watching a bunch of the Presnitz Sturgis movies,
but I also watched the Broadway melody of there were four of them.
One was just in 1929.
They just called it Broadway melody.
One best picture that year, and it's incredibly upsetting because it's a sound.
It's a talkie, but they are still figuring out how to do that.
So it's just a little weird.
This is Brisbane.
That's Brisbane.
Oh, Brisbane looks like a bruiser.
I don't want to make his mouth.
He's got like his lips is all like, hey, I'm dead tired.
How dare you?
Jason does like little rascals.
I will, full disclosure, that's not maybe his top pick.
I was more of a joke, so I don't want to make him look like he was trying to pretend
he was an expert and he wasn't.
Scott is the truly the building.
Do you have an answer for though what you're?
No, I just I was trying to figure out in one of these Broadway melody movies are not very long.
And by the by the last one, Fred Astaire's in it.
A few of them have Elnur Powell, who they call the queen of tap dancing.
She's very good tap dancer.
But every one of these DVDs had like the other shorts that would pad out like a two hour runtime.
And one of these DVDs I watched just had like a 25 minute movie called like
The Stars and Palm Springs.
And it's just walking around this property and it's like,
oh, look, there's Catherine Hepburn.
She's hitting the links.
And and that was it.
But there was a little rascal short where they're like, we want to make a movie.
And then we want to screen the movie.
That was the plot of it.
And hijinks and so one of them gets their feet stuck in wet cement and can't make it to the screening.
Well, that's a so that's a accessory you need.
You want regular feed and you want cement feed.
Yeah. Oh, no, they're putting on a little play.
So it's like the play is held up because I think Buckweed is stuck outside the little junkyard theater
and like can't get in to do the, you know, right play.
You know, what's a good I sorry, I'm jumping all over the place here,
but I'm realizing now a couple of years ago, I asked listeners on Twitter
how much they would pay for an action figure of Jason.
And overwhelmingly, they said, I think, fifty dollars are over.
So they were talking for a premium overwhelmingly.
How many people said they were fifty dollars?
Look at this.
I just I just totally remember this.
Don't tell yourself sure.
I think we were talking about all three of us.
Well, we were, but I think my first question to the listener was just Jason.
As far as an action figure was concerned.
Yeah, we can do the you're the most toy.
The word is toy addict, right?
Of things.
And Jason is the most toy addict of the three of us, I think.
OK, but I think if anyone's after a Jason action figure and until we get our act together and do it
in the meantime, I have found there are little rascals action figures.
And I think you could just start with Spanky and say it's Jason.
I mean, just just pretend, you know, he and I both get into lots of hijinks.
Yeah.
Well, you just OK, he seems to come.
His accessory is a hammer.
He's got a hammer in his hand.
So just take out that hammer and put in a big old blunt.
And then it's now we're talking Jason.
That's Jason.
I is that your answer?
Is it the way we still don't know what's your.
Oh, I said Alpha.
It's my polar opposite.
Very skinny, very tall.
No, I mean, what's what action figures do you want?
Is it Broadway melodies?
Oh, yeah, I would take like Fred Astaire and Gene Kelly.
Like I would take a pair.
There's only there's only like one or two movies where they were ever in it together.
One is called Ziegfeld Follies.
And I think one of the that's entertainment compilations, they do a number together.
Ziegfeld Follies series would be good.
I sent you a picture because I just got the neck invisible man.
I said this is my first Claude Rains figure and I was very excited.
Sent it to Jason.
Yeah.
And I thought I before I looked at the picture, I thought it was going to be a.
Casablanca.
Casablanca series.
Right.
What do you mean?
This is this is my first Claude Rains figure.
You said that like that was not a really weird thing to say.
My first Claude Rains figure.
I knew what I was doing.
This is a private communication between Jason and I shared it and I'm being ridiculed.
It's a flip of a coin.
I think of what do you associate Claude Rains with Casablanca or invisible man?
Yeah, I mean.
Or the third side of the coin.
Do you not really know who Claude Rains is?
Oh, he was a killer.
He was great.
He was in Notorious, I believe, right?
The Hitchcock movie.
I think so.
He's a lot of stuff.
My girlfriend and I call it the four Jorleys, but that's not the name of the movie.
It's like four sisters or something.
He's the dad of like, they filmed it on the Warner Brothers lot.
Like the house that's on this one corner is like their house.
I've never seen.
I know what you're talking about.
We were watching all these old movies when the pandemic started and yeah, Claude Rains is great.
He is great.
When we got that universal license, I was immediately just asking,
if like, oh, when are we going to do Edward Van Sloan?
I just started naming all of the like, Uno O'Connor and like.
Wait, who is Uno O'Connor?
Uno O'Connor, she's like the crazy lady in Invisible Man.
She works in that bar, the restaurant.
When she starts seeing stuff moving, she like freaks out.
I think she's in like, they used her a few times, like Ghost of Frankenstein
or one of the later Frankenstein movies.
She's always like the old barmaid or something.
But I just wanted to get the license, like the likeness rights for all of those
really, really, really old like character actors.
Everyone else just wanted like, let's make Dracula and Frankenstein's monster.
Boring.
You know, but it was like, we got to do all the other characters that like,
you know, are classic in the movie that like no one's ever done figures for.
Yeah.
But then you got to find out who owns the estates and whatever.
That's part of your job, right?
Sometimes finding and getting rights.
Yeah, that's more of my boss, Randy.
That's more his job.
But yeah, that's part of it when you're making figures is like,
you know, you got to figure out like, because a lot of the time,
Star Wars, like Lucas got everyone's likenesses.
Sort of like he had that master plan for merchandising and like
every other movie is just not really structured.
Doesn't walk down.
Not really.
Doesn't know those faces.
Like sometimes it does.
Like we were able to do, oh, well, like we did a bunch of Rocky figures
from the Rocky movies, but then like we can't do Carl Weathers from like Predator
because it's like the Predator movie.
We can only do like Arnold and the Predators.
Oh, so every movie is like structured differently, you know.
But you've done Carl Weathers as Apollo Creed.
Interesting.
Wow.
Any other dreams and any other that just calls to mind that question?
Like any property that like that's the one.
Maybe like unrealistic dreams.
Yeah.
Oh, unrealistic.
It would be making like Maria Ospenskaya and like probably like we're doing like
we do mashup figures of like the turtles and the Universal Monsters.
Like that's another subcategory of like all the turtle stuff.
And it's like.
Don't point at me.
You make me do shit.
I'm not.
You know what?
You look if you want to show it to me, you look it up.
I do want to show it to you.
But yeah, there's a lot of.
I don't know what like another dream license would be like.
I've said a couple of times, like I'd love to work on a lot of it is just 80s stuff.
You know, like the 80s cartoons that I liked, like Brave Star or Centurions, like.
Oh, OK.
Stuff like that.
Thank you for looking at those.
All right.
They do look cool.
That is a Rafael Frankenstein.
I see.
Thanks for putting for moving your fingers around.
Yeah, of course.
Well, this was just in the way.
So it's hard for me to get there.
I can't imagine the journey to show me.
It was.
I agree.
Trying to like all those old like now classic like B movies and stuff like.
Like Ed Wood, like Plan 9 from outer space.
Like there's no there's no paperwork.
It's a miracle there's any prints of those movies.
Right.
So, you know.
Yeah, those are those are tricky or they can be tricky, too, because it is just such a
mess sometimes to know who owns what.
And someone might have like distribution rights and then someone else is like retaining like.
Oh, yeah.
You know, the characters or the name or the story or something, you know, it's like stuff
gets like sliced up like a bunch of different ways and there's all kinds of disputes and.
Sure.
Even like the big budget, like like let's say double indemnity.
It's like, OK, well, we have to figure out what movie studio had that.
And yeah, what distributor?
And then we have to find who has Fred McMurray and Barbara Stanwyck's license.
Yeah.
Licenses, you know.
My friend my friend was saying because I was really obsessed or I was
am really obsessed with the idea of getting a really accurate Aunt Harriet figure from
the 60s Batman.
Oh, that's that's a dream of mine.
Yeah.
Great.
And I was like, who owns the Madge Blake estate?
Yeah.
My friend's like, you know what?
You would be the perfect.
That's your perfect job is going to find out and talk to like Madge Blake's great granddaughter
and convince her that we need to have a figure of her.
There there was we did we did a couple like Batman 66 things a few years ago.
And because because that was one thing that it took Warner Brothers forever to
that was a great example of like CBS on this or Fox on that.
It was and they finally got it.
We had this list of like these are all the actors that you can't like there's Frank
Orshan and like all the main characters, all the main villains.
But they had likeness, right?
Approvals for a bunch of the guest stars.
And they gave us this huge list of every everyone we could potentially do.
I'd love to go back and see if like Aunt Harriet was like.
Yeah.
On that list or not, because there was there's it was some stuff.
It was like we were obviously never going to get to this, but that show just with all
of the guest stars, I think it was just like a nightmare forever to, you know,
to work out the likeness rights.
My dream is Liberace's character Shondell.
Shondell, we said at the same time.
Wow.
I'm so glad you guys got together.
This is important.
It is.
Yeah.
I found it real quick.
43% of out of 900 people voting said they would want a deluxe style Jason at 30 to 50 dollars.
What were the other choices?
Yes.
Basic style like 15 to 25 dollars.
Thirty three percent.
And then no, I love Jason, but no, 24 percent.
OK.
Fair enough.
So.
But 50 bucks, we could get a lot of stuff in there.
You make a really.
A lot of accessories.
A lot of fun.
Yeah, it'd be a fun figure.
What are the other Jason accessories?
Slim Jims, snack cakes, you know.
Well, from what I understand in my limited knowledge about toys is that once the mold is made,
we can do a lot of different variants of you.
Sure.
So mash him up with the.
All right.
You know, the turtles are mashed up with the classic monsters.
He could be mashed up with the classic monsters.
So like in any monster merger.
Are you really?
Well, we had the we did the Rob Zombie one.
Yes.
Daniel.
I showed you.
Yeah.
Oh, so you're responsible for the Daniel Roebuck grandpa.
We did.
The Counts, I mean.
We did an episode about the late shift, which of course, Daniel Roebuck plays Jay Leno.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Because Scott and I specifically are obsessed with that movie.
And then we were just doing there's so much monster talk.
And then all of a sudden, like eight months ago, it was like, did you know that Daniel
Roebuck is playing grandpa monster?
Because we did an episode about grandpa's restaurant from New York where he like was
just the greeter and Italian restaurant.
Yeah.
Billy West has got great stories about that place.
Yes.
Yeah.
Those are really great.
So yeah, that was shocking when we learned that.
So anyway, yeah, we'll we'll talk off air about getting the Jason in the tuxedo.
Jason in the.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, his the fake prom tux the fake photo tuxedo and then separately the tuxedo you
were talking about earlier.
Sure.
Bathrobe bathrobe.
A different soft good.
Do we get shirtless Jason from when you weirdly took your shirt off at that live show?
Well, I kept saying I was going to change and I just didn't.
I was like, I don't think I'm going to take my shirt off.
We can do a garlic scented one.
Get a Chuck E. Cheese sponsorship.
Yeah.
A little bit of slime, a little covered in slime.
You know, Chuck E. Cheese still around.
It's not exactly the same as when we were kids, but I don't know that they're giving
away garlic goo anymore.
For a chance.
We have to bring it back.
The only way we're getting garlic goods out into the market again.
Yeah, that's too bad.
Brett, could you bring up the picture?
It says I think it's so long.
It says Canada's Wonderland friends on it because I just think this is such a great
picture.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Look at these friends.
Well, what friends do we see?
It's we got we got Yogi.
We got Scooby.
We got Huckleberry.
We got George.
George back there.
Jabberjaw.
Jabberjaw is great.
Jabberjaw was the best on the there's a carousel and it was all like Hanna Barbera characters
and like Fred was like there's a picture.
There's like a caboose or something.
But like you could just sit on Jabberjaw's tail like it would sort of like curl over.
Oh, that's a good carousel.
And that was always like the number one like go to I got to get to Jabberjaw and like kids
would just like Brett Canada's Wonderland merry go is the name of the file.
We have a picture of it here.
Also, some Jabberjaw paintings at the Dolphin Show.
There it is.
Yeah.
See.
So you could sit on like Yogi's lap.
You could go to Fred's like caboose thing.
But Jabberjaw was just the greatest.
You'd sit there and look up and have this like this huge mouth towering over you.
Yeah, that's cool.
So you can either sit on Yogi's lap or Fred has some very I'll be honest modern looking car.
Yeah, it doesn't quite fit with the bedrock.
Scoobyville.
It's a car that belongs somewhere else.
They all get along.
They mix up regardless of what time period it's like a weird MCU kind of thing where they're all.
They're all together.
Yeah.
Fred is kind of like peeping in the window of the car too in a weird way.
Yeah, he's not witnessing a murder.
Yeah, he seems like he's caught in the act of looking into this modern day Scooby car or
whatever modern contraption.
Yeah, he may be just confused by it.
Maybe.
All right, bud.
You killed my wife and then I'll kill your wife and then we don't know each other.
It's the full Flintstones Strangers on a train.
That was like going to be the second like Flintstones and Jetsons movie, I think, right?
Yeah.
Oh, the full genre exploration.
Yeah, that's great.
A train that has to be pushed.
They have to pull off the murder but also push the train.
Yeah.
So it takes a lot of feet to do an entire train.
So yeah, your favorite was the Jabberjaw car.
Oh yeah, that's great.
Whatever it is like rides wise.
Oh yeah.
I mean we're talking about a zillion things but like is there anything where like well
if we're talking canon it's one thing you can't let that pass.
Well yeah, my favorite place to go was the Smurf village or Smurf forest.
Something like that.
And it was a little different than the one in Kings Island in Cincinnati that I guess
I couldn't find hardly any pictures of the Smurf village but I remember it being like a walkthrough
and it was all like indoors and they had these little vignettes set up where you're like in
the Smurf village and eventually you end up at Gargamel's castle and it turns into like a
funhouse where like it's got crooked floorboards and so you're going through,
you're creeping through these hallways kind of zigzag around and like you just peek through
these windows and there'd be like Gargamel and Asriel like making some potion or something.
Oh fun.
And there's like strobe lights and lightning and all this disorienting stuff.
But yeah, it was like you guys remember like the Viewmasters, you know, they had the little discs.
It was like walking through a Viewmaster because every room was just like one of these scenes.
And it was just that to me was the greatest thing and like when you're outside
just walking around the Smurf forest there's like giant snails so you're like the side,
you're three apples high like a Smurf. You're just transported into this magical world and there's
Smurfs like on the trees like kind of hanging up signs and welcome to Smurf village or whatever.
So that area I loved as a kid and then boy what was better than that? I can't think.
That sounds great.
Yeah, I know.
Gargamel's castle was just like the coolest part. It was just so awesome.
Yeah, yeah. I didn't know that.
There was a whole bedrock area. They had like a little aquarium thing with like seals.
I remember going there with my cousins one time and it was like the first time my cousin had
seen like a seal and thought it was a guy in a suit because there's just no way an animal could
like I don't know play basketball or whatever. Whatever the you know it was just but we were
telling him that like this is like a creature you know.
Right.
Yeah.
Do when you were like did you ever I guess since you were so little when you started going there
was it did you get like bored by it ever?
No, I don't ever remember really getting bored.
You always felt like the magic was there.
Oh for sure. Yeah.
Yeah.
Definitely.
I just found something that seems to be called the heritage kids. There's these did you ever.
Oh these the giant head things that kind of look like funko pops.
These are horrifying.
Those are really scary.
Yeah big squarish heads they're kind of in the cabbage patch family but the heads are
massive compared to them and they look really like pensive and upset.
Yeah they're upset.
Not one of them is smiling.
They look like precious memories.
Oh totally.
Is that what they're called those ceramics?
Yeah and they're happy.
Yeah.
These guys are all like they're they seem upset and they're all like side eyeing each other like
do you want to be here? No. You want to be here?
Yeah.
I remember that like the Hanna Barbera land those guys might have been in like another
part of the park.
You stayed out of that territory.
That was like the yeah scary.
Yeah.
I just wanted to.
Oh you never saw a heritage kid taking their head off backstage did you?
If I did it's all like buried deep somewhere in the back of them.
If you unlock it you'll just start screaming.
Yeah it'll be like nightmares.
Like that woman in the lowest oboe.
Yeah.
Heritage kids.
Are they still around the heritage kids?
It's a bad sounding name.
Hope they burnt those costumes.
It sounds religious.
I was going to ask if there I forgot I had answered my own question I was going to ask if there was
a yogi's cave but I think by the time you might have been going that was flipped to the smurfs.
It's yeah.
So that I also just looking up stuff for this for this thing it was like it started the first
year or two it was like yogi's cave.
Yeah.
I do not remember that at all and then yeah probably by 83 maybe it had they had
they had switched it over to like the the smurfs you get like blue ice cream.
Yeah.
Oh wow.
All that kind of fun stuff.
That stuck around the yogi's cave at kings dominion stuck around until the 90s and I
forget what eventually cleared it out but the smurfs were in another part of the park.
You had both.
Yeah so there for a time there was both is the way I remember it.
That's my years developing.
I wish there's a couple pictures where you it looks like they had like ranger smith's
cabin and stuff it looks like cool I wish I.
Yeah.
Remembered anything about that.
I think a lot of that converted to gargamel's house.
Probably yeah.
Smurf forest and everything yeah.
Yeah I don't know you know sometimes you just wish you had a time machine you go back.
Oh yeah sure.
My god.
That occurred to me that like yeah I mean we think that all the time like to you know yeah do we go
to some amazing thing in history no I would like to see Disneyland Tomorrowland in 1986
is what I would waste time machine for sure on like really specific theme park slivers.
Yeah.
But it definitely occurred to me like what you got to early 80 I mean you were really
little then but early 80s Toronto theme park is what I feel I would like this this this would be
in my top 10.
Yeah it was I in another just vague memory I remember seeing like that live he man like stage
show.
Oh yeah like they have yeah like I remember going to some kind of like live he man thing and it just
blowing my mind like it was I remember there was a there was like an act break or something where
there's there's like a battle with like he man and Skeletor and there's like some kind of freeze
sword or something and like Skeletor had this sword and like touched he man with it he man froze
the whole stage just turned blue like this ice cold blue like music everything just stopped and
that was like intermission or something and I was just like oh my god like what yeah it was
like maybe five I was just like what the hell is going to happen to he man are we okay are we
or and are like are we going to die yeah are we next that's it's like that's what I that's like
my moment seeing the turtles live when I was whatever little and like shutters like I've
locked the doors you can't get out and then it was like intermission and we left get some popcorn
yeah and I was like wait maybe even the other door like the outside doors yeah yeah because
I was trying to yeah make sense of what he just said because we went through the doors but I was
legitimately like well this guy's gonna kill us yeah we're dead.
You can now with the action figures which I'm hold it like I got Michelangelo here you could do
dark coming out of our shells where like yeah like okay the intermission's over you come back
in you come back in just in time for the monitor to turn on and like oh good you're here and then
he does shred Michelangelo's face yeah like you watch Michelangelo's face get covered yeah yeah
all right eyes on the screen kiddies oh my god they're killing him in front of us
it's really it would be kind of a therapeutic thing I think because it's an unresolved
issue in my head yeah because I still was like thought it was real and I didn't I wasn't old
enough to know it wasn't so maybe if I play out some of these nightmare scenarios maybe I'll be
a better adult man yeah that's what we're making this stuff yeah right thank you so much
they help you get over your child doesn't it certainly they don't make you stay in it forever
you know what swim in it no no no no I just go in there and stare every night nothing's weird
about it lights on boys you know what do your show turtle friends well I just like yeah I don't
when I'm not there like 1 a.m rearranging things that's not what I do no no no here when there's
an earthquake I always stop and listen and like how many toys fell over like yes you know oh sure
oh this wasn't a bad one because I only heard like yeah and sometimes I can pinpoint like I'm pretty
sure that was like a spider-man that I knew was like kind of dangling on a ledge or something
right weak legs is it anyway yeah those ankle joints will go you know what I'm trying to think
you did the four turtles for the coming out of our shells in that video it's the behind the scenes
with your guy Dave Rubrik oh yes we've talked about that too
the first time my my wife bought an action figure
you do variants super mario sweep dave and different sweaters sweaters actually doing just
like generic like trying to do like like the um you know not specific contestants but like meld
all the contestants oh yeah just into a couple like base bodies or something yeah yeah yeah and
then do each type of sweater yeah yellow peach or i forget what they were but and they can all come
with a different like you know like here's a big inflatable jolly green giant and that goes for
that's a great idea too because you guys have done that where like the turtle wax you guys
called turtle wax to get the official yeah right we have to use it as a little toy
yep oh wow we did that so you could do this is easy oh sure this is a good one what were you
going to say though but there was something else with rubric oh i don't know i was just saying all
the version i think i said what i had to say about dave rubrik so okay well you could do yeah you
do rubrics on supermarket sweet and rubrics the behind the scenes host of the coming out of it
so rubric was i saying his name wrong i'm not sure rubric dave rubrik correct us we'll accept it we
need to learn he's an important figure we need to learn i mean residual payments are such a crap
shoot nowadays that would be great for actors you know just the the lightness rights for action
figures like another revenue stream you know sure yeah and especially if yeah you were you hosted a
game show in the early 90s or mid 80s and i'm sure all of those companies have protected you
from having your image exploited yeah sure i'm sure you'll be completely properly you will get
some money for the line of emily reasons why not the two three episode heather graham sitcom
or drama from the 2000s that's a good poll jason yeah
you know we talked so much about uh let's finish i guess finish up for now the thoughts on cat is
wonderland because we were talking also about you've been to popeye village i have yeah so i
oh my god we haven't even touched it so we obviously will have to do it again yeah but like if there's
any wrapping up thoughts about canada's wonderland and then you did say there was a specific story
about popeye's village maybe you could tell oh yeah sure so we can do that so canada's wonderland
um i i don't facts do you have more facts oh no i think i we touched you said the facts i mean it's
coaster park and they was you know hannah barbera and paramount and you know coaster called the bat
where the tv ad uh starred joe flairity from sc tv wow that's a hell of a get yeah that's a canadian
great count floyd or something yeah yeah yeah yeah is one of the great characters and and i think
radio ads with john candy and maybe one maybe levy or one of the others so you're like the
you know the canadian comedy greats are represented by the park and yeah the first
celebrity i ever met was at canada's wonderland what was that kit the car wow oh hell yeah wow
oh my god he was there doing an appearance wow there's some nbc day or something and
yeah kit was there and i got to like i'm pretty sure i got to sit in the driver's seat they had it
the doors open you take a picture i have a picture that's somewhere i gotta wow did he talk there
was a david hasselhoff um like on the dashboard tv there was like a loop of him just sort of of
david talking not kit or of kit talking no no of david yeah michael night wow and then yeah the
a-team van was there and uh oh jeez um well they had all these universal studios but this is a
whole other corporate structure they had to make a special like the like the toys a special deal to
get them over to canada's wonderland took them across the border and like yeah it was great yeah
yeah kit was like and i uh when i was a couple you kit showed up at the mattel booth at san
diego comic-con like i don't know a bunch of years ago and i was like hey dude remember me like i saw
you at like i met you at canada's wonderland uh in 1984 or whatever you were always my favorite
trevor i wondered when you would return yeah i don't remember if there's any like if there's a
william daniels voice or not there might have been or just a whoo that was definitely like
yeah they had that that thing going on that yeah front but that was great that would be a good
like donkey you know all you have donkey at universal and he's like there's a performer
doing it yeah you could just have kit and there was a performer somewhere that would talk to
people i was like well at universal um don't the transformers do that yes i think like megatron
there's a guy on a microphone that'll just like interact is it recorded lines or is it actually
somebody no it's a guy it is a guy yeah yeah yeah uh-huh because he felt i tried to say i think i
said i tried to say i love you to one of them and it didn't feel like they reciprocated it
so that may have been another therapy toy you're gonna have to go buy yeah buy a mega and i wasn't
even a transformer's kid oh dear wow but the ride means so much to me but now you yeah you weren't
a transformer's kid but now your validation centers on uh being yes being being seen by
optimus prime yeah but no it felt like that's how what i told myself is that it must be pre-recorded
messages so they wouldn't be able to say something personal back to me they didn't record and i love
you guess they thought it'd be weird they hadn't met me i would show them that it's not weird yeah
so that's how i got through the day for up until now that's all ripped wide open yeah um i i mean
yeah i got nothing i i mean i want to hear this popeye village thing i'm sure we should wind it
down but yeah yeah so so you went to so we've talked we did an episode but we haven't talked
about in a while if from the movie the robert altman movie popeye yeah they built all these
crazy sets in malta yeah in europe they're still there they're just there and they turned it into
a park and park kind of they're still there yeah it's a it's a theme not a theme oh yeah it's like
theme park like you know pay an admission to get in and um there's about when i went in 2019 like
just right before the pandemic started i was like october 2019 and we took a family trip out there
because my last name is maltease like my my dad's dad he was from malta came to canada
um so we had always heard about malta and just like never my mom just we should just it was
there my mom my parents like 40th wedding anniversary or something and so she was like
let's go to malta like have a big trip or whatever so um so i said well if we're going to malta we
have to go to popeye's village like that was the number one thing i wanted to do there so um
yeah so we went and it was that was the last thing we did we were there for two weeks and
that was the last thing we did on the trip on the last day and we spent the day there and it was
like it's seriously like the happiest place i've this is the greatest place i've ever been
wow there was just enough um it's not like one of those weird derelict parks where everything's
run down and it's all shambly and like falling apart and stuff like there was just enough of like
they were keeping it up but just kind of barely you know there's like five people working there
and like um it was just it was just it was just this wonderful place and uh um yeah so we spent
we spent the day there there was a guy's popeye walking around a guy's bluto walking around
and then um i had like the the pamphlet in my hand everyone was like we were having lunch and
i was like oh my god like the the 115 puppet show is happening right now i was like i gotta go
and i was like who's going to the puppet show with me and they're like we don't care like
no so so i i just ran up the street it's like i think it's in um it's in the the family room of
uh um of where olive oil lived like in the movie it's like olive oil's house or something right
it's at the end of the street castor oil yeah yeah and uh and so there's this so i i walk into the
already happening like puppet show and um and it was like me and a couple of kids and maybe like one
parent was you know they're just it's just the idea of like this puppet show happens like every
half hour every day like there's maybe two people show up maybe there's just nothing going on right
and uh and when i was like oh this is great so they're doing these like Popeye voices and stuff
and then uh and when the show's over the puppet the puppeteers like come out from behind the
curtain and it's just the guy in the Popeye suit like he was it was him and the girl playing like
olive oil or something were the puppeteers so like he didn't change no they didn't change so then and
when they were done they put the puppets away and then they went back outside and did like
photos with people and then like you know it's just like it's just
wimpy was probably at the grill like making hamburgers because there's there's no one else
that works there and then we i just my friend is like a huge Popeye fan and so i just i pretty
much bought up the entire gift shop when we left and like the guy was just like no this has never
happened before like maybe they sell like a spoon or a t-shirt i bought like everything in there for
me and all my Popeye obsessed friends and uh yeah it was it was just the greatest place but um
but yeah so one of my friends uh he's he's a buddy of uh of eric bousas they all work in
animation together when we were in um when we were in college uh the only like art project my friend
pez ever finished was painting Popeye's face on the toilet seat of our a part of our bathroom like
our apartment so and he did such a great job it was cool and then more Popeye stuff just started
going into this bathroom and then um and then you know we moved and he like unbolted the toilet
seat and took it with him and this Popeye bathroom has like been with him in like every house he's
lived in and it's just and so more and more stuff is just like that's just where all his Popeye stuff
goes and when i was at Popeye's village in malta i was like there's an actual Popeye bathroom i need
to like take because i brought my mezco toys and this is before the boss fight figures came out so
i was like in the bathroom like at Popeye's village like in malta taking photos to like
you know get a nice framed like beautiful Popeye bathroom photo for my friend's Popeye bathroom in
Toluca lake or where it's over like wherever he lives now um is this the photo you sent me of the
Popeye bathroom yeah the bathroom i think that's the second or third version of that bathroom okay
uh brett i have in the Popeye folder it says Popeye bathroom but for some reason not loading so maybe
we'll have to just put it in later but i have it on my phone here there's a Popeye oh there it is
so that's yeah so that's from both sides that's like both sides so it's the sinks over there
much but there's like like big towel and then he's on the shower door but then figures on every
single nook and cranny of the wait and wait and the camera is blocking oh i see the toilet seat
says that's the original toilet seat with the Popeye it was the best Popeye spinach the the
the garbage can is a spinach can that he he decorated well it's not he decorated it to look
like a spinach can they look great it's a bonkers yeah he he did like i think those are like custom
like vinyl you know stickers that he put on the on the shower door and everything so but yeah he's
like obsessed with um with Popeye and i told him i said the Popeye's village is so amazing like we
need to just go back there like it's yeah like malta is a really fun place to visit but it's just
the the icing on the cake is just going is sweet haven right on the coast yeah yeah yeah
sweet haven yeah pop i i cannot say enough good things about Popeye's village because it is just
like the craziest place is that your favorite theme park on the planet earth it's yeah it's
probably now that i've actually been there and like yeah it's probably that canna's wonderland's
great kenny wood is great um and then yeah Popeye's village is just like the greatest place i've
ever been oh damn we got a good vibe i mean looking at like big you know big plates of
pasta and yeah weird like you know all the the the Popeye gang dancing to the trolls song and all
that beautiful we've thought about it for years since we did the episode and yeah it's rightfully
it's so worth it like just going out there's there's a lot of cool stuff to see in malta
and it's such a small it's like three islands but there you can get around them like real quick but
um yeah yeah the Popeye's village is just like that's the greatest place ever how i be honest
though how was the bathroom bathroom was okay i'm glad that i got um my pictures before there was
like a father and son that walked in on me and i'm glad i was like finishing up with my photos
like by the time they got in because i didn't know how i was going to explain that whole stupid
story i just told you like i have a friend uh he uh look there's a whole thing yeah pop is got a
bathroom toilet picture i think i have here if you see it under that list there's you sent me a lot
of photos that were just yeah yeah so that was the best photo i got of the actual i mean it's just
kind of a regular bathroom but yeah it's but it's pop in like a you know semi-clean looking
bathroom yeah there he is excellent focus shift uh thank you yeah uh-huh um well we'll have to
talk about pop by village some other time or in depth i guess so um but uh i mean what a wonderful
journey from from there to canada's wonderland to the world of your your wonderful turtles toys
trevor zamit you survived podcast the ride oh my goodness uh this has been wonderful it's
the gift shop anything you'd like to plug uh i feel like we just maybe the littlest hobo is
that on dvd now i mean it's all on it's all on youtube yeah it is streaming yeah yeah i mean it
might be on a more legit streamer but it but i've been i've only watched it on youtube and nobody's
pulled any of it and and if that show sounded interesting to anyone i will say the way i my
way in and i swear i wasn't even looking for this it just happened to be the first one that i put on
and i was like you're kidding this is where i landed it's an episode where there's a uh there's
a kid in a wheelchair and he's in a frisbee competition and i forget but i like there's
there's some drama with i think he was in a car accident and now another one is forming now he
like maybe is going to get i don't more paralyzed i don't know he's heading down a hill the the
wheelchair is out of control mac and me style pre mac and me and hobo knows what to do he has
to stop this and then cut to what it can only be that the makers of littlest hobo just threw the
dog at the kid in the wheelchair really the kid the dogs just midair and just wow it's really
sloppily with the wheel they didn't have like a puppet dog no no it's just the dog oh dear
so i hope uh i hope he was fine i hope they didn't have to get another london
to do it again but then like yeah london was a good sport he was good sport you know he cared
about the craft the work he would have loved he loved he'd be so happy that he went out doing
a stunt uh but if that wasn't enough for you that this crazy thing happens that like the kid has
it's either an older friend or an older brother and he's kind of like a like a doofy canadian
and mike meyers one of mike meyers first appearances anything yes yeah like 15 so he just
is wayne is he like like he's he's so much more canadian and just kind of like a little bit
burnout and yeah he's in this uh this this crazy dog show wheelchair kid episode oh great great
half hour of television so i support your plug okay we have some more littlest hobo content
oh please i'm so i really thank you for yeah yeah we're we're looking for any we just the other day
we're saying the show is now going to be about the ghost dog show topper i think now it's going to
like maybe this is just a catch-all premise for all of the various old dog i just this is like a
little weird but i just bought there's i just found a movie last night just scrolling through imdb
my girlfriend and i are like obsessed with melrose place right now oh really just started season six
okay and um you know there's always you guys might know about some of this we have this theory
because we'll we're watching these episodes and there'll be some guest you know actor for
for whatever oh this guy i know he's from seinfeld or something we start looking up their credits
and like everyone that was on melrose place you know was probably like had a guest spot on like
90210 but then they were also they were always on star trek like next gen or voyager and they
were always like a character on seinfeld and it was like there's oh really so so there must have
been some casting crew or like a company that was just using the same bunch of people right
wow um but um but two of the guys two of the people from melrose place jack wagner
and uh princess vespa from uh because i don't know a real name uh from spaceballs they were in
a dog movie together in 2003 called it has multiple names so you know it's good oh yeah
but it's called release it's on the dvd cover it's called dog gone but then there's it has it's part
of a series of like ghost dog movies i think and uh but i just anyways a long story short i just
bought this dvd last night on ebay uh dog gone yeah wow but it's like that's there's almost nothing
for it because like dog gone's been a few other movies like over the years daphne's aniga that's
yeah that's it yeah yeah so jack wagner did the song all i need do we know all i need just a little
more time maybe i think i feel like a soap actor he's great a graduate of the universal tour guide
program oh really which i was i did the tram tour and they would say like you know uh there you can
move on from this to a successful film and television career perhaps you've heard of
jack wagner oh wow the star of dog gone the the catchphrase on this dvd cover is uh this old dog
just learned some new tricks oh that's so they didn't really go very far no i guess it writes
itself you know what's the so just quick google a dog phrase take the first results put it on the
poster there was there was some dog movie that norm mcdonald did it did the voice of the dog
and it's just like the laziest like just it was probably another weird like a canadian production
and norm was like okay i'll do it the world of dog there probably is an entire podcast about
dog movies yeah some of them are too unwatchable i mean there's there's a sub genre of just christmas
dog movies you know yeah you're right that's it's the venn diagram of because certainly christmas
movies is all thing it's its own dog movie and there is yeah right there's probably like a hundred
christmas dog movies our friend john is in the wrestling dog movie rustle madness where he
wrestles a dog really yeah did they try to get rustle mania there's like two close yep yeah that's
exactly what happened 100% they tried rustle mania they said oh not happening does he suplex or like
um frog splash jack russell terrier i believe he splashes off the top rope a jack russell terrier
macho man does that on the weird owl show oh yes yes i've seen that clip he drops the elbow on like
a i don't know like a little animal or some tiny owl show yes i remember that wow wow geez a lot
of dogs get this is the runner at the end of the episode is dog peril real or not i think both of
those dogs were much better off than london was in that wheelchair yeah i think early 80s there's no
gracefulness to throwing the dog full tilt into this there's there's that classic clip from uh
no holds barred where like in the background there's just like they're riding down the street
on like motorcycles and in the background there's a guy just tossing a dog like oh my god
geez just i don't think i've seen that actually oh really yeah there is yeah it's that's yeah it
sounds bad yeah it's really bad yeah yeah because it's just it's so like what is happening like yeah
wow geez uh um okay well again uh good to have you yeah and with that now that we've discussed some
bizarre dog scenarios uh uh no so great so great avenue thanks for your your memories this was fun
in depth extra figure discussions uh as for us you can find us on all the socials at podcast the ride
hey come see us at podcast the rides big vegas groove blender saturday july 22nd in las vegas
we promise a lot a lot of fun and no dogs in peril that's the podcast the ride vow uh and you
can get tickets at the space lv.com uh and for three bonus episodes every month check out podcast
the ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode in our vip tier club three all of that
at patreon.com slash podcast the ride which is also where the pop-by village episode yeah
hey wall it's on behind a paywall uh man now we gotta we gotta bust it out make sure the world
know now that we know how great it is it's yeah one of the best perks in the world it's amazing
the best place in the world maybe yeah could be all right forever dog this has been a forever dog
production executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner brett bohme joe
cilio and alex ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe
to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest
forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page
on facebook