Forever, dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains artificially dyed seafood,
space faucet water pressure, personalized Jedi secrets,
and a little play that somehow feels more real than real life.
All this plus, Andrew Barth Feldman joins us to participate
in the immersive experience that is today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about tax write-offs.
I'm Scott Gertner, and I'm Jason Sheridan.
That's a lot of entertainment these days,
or technically tax write-offs.
It's all what we're striving to do.
Should we be so lucky as to give one of our favorite companies
a big way to save money or rearrange money or scam money,
whatever it is.
Mike Carlson.
Yes, I'm here and I'm excited to write things off.
It's one of the most exciting parts of 2023,
and we're gonna do it.
You know, you can do it at home,
you can do it in a big corporation, you can do it anywhere.
And it's its own themed experience, if you're doing it right.
Yeah, I think so.
And you know, you sometimes think of it more
with movies and shows lately,
but today we're proving that tax write-offs
can happen out in the world.
Highly experimental, ambitious tax write-offs
that are physical experiences can happen.
And that's what we're handling here today,
is Star Wars Galactic Star Cruiser.
And we are still, you know, we had to take a little time,
I think, to process, to deal with the news,
the upsetting news that Star Cruiser is,
if I'm gonna use their terminology,
that they are sun setting it.
They are going to sunset this experience,
I believe is what Josh Tomorrow said.
Really makes it sound like the Star Cruiser
is cruising to a farm upstate, you know?
Because it's close to the term sundowning,
which sometimes you feel like is used
when somebody is like,
maybe slipping away mentally or something.
Sure.
So the phrase is meant, I think, to be gentle,
but it feels not gentle to me.
It feels aggressive.
Well, and then at the same time,
sun setting is weird because a sunset,
then there's a sun up not long after the next day.
Oh, right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So this actually, it actually is not applicable
because it will not rise again,
at least as of later in the year.
Are there any stars that are destroyed?
Are any stars destroyed in Star Wars?
I know many planets are destroyed,
but it's literally, the ship is called Star Destroyer,
but I'm trying to remember, is a star itself.
I don't believe so.
You don't consider the Death Star a star?
No.
No?
It's just a name.
It's a space station.
It's a station, okay.
There's no, stars are destroyed in Star Trek.
Okay.
A couple times.
Hence maybe your preference,
because that sounds more exciting.
Well, of course, if stars, yeah, it's a bigger thing.
It's a big ball of gas.
It's exciting when it blows up.
Dr. Sauron, of course, in Star Trek Generations,
blows up a sun to move the Nexus ribbon
so it goes in the way of the one planet
so we can get taken.
Yeah. Of course, we know.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
We know the ribbon.
We were filling it.
We were auto-filling the rest of that sentence
as you were going.
So I'm just trying, I was trying to figure out
a Star Wars parallel for like a sun,
some sun setting, but never rising.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
But Star Wars never had anything as exciting
as what you just described.
No, not with Dr. Sauron.
Not as exciting as Dr. Sauron.
No, Sauron.
No, they never had a Sauron.
And I guess this thing didn't reach the heights of Sauron
in the eyes of the Disney corporation.
And thus they are writing this thing off
for $300 million.
At the end of the year, they will no longer be doing this,
what is of course has been a immersive,
ambitious, experimental Star Wars themed hotel,
a two-night experience that's part hotel
and part immersive performance.
I mean, a crazy thing that they tried
and they're kind of like with buzzwords,
admitting failure, they're ending the thing.
It is flying its final mission.
But that leaves us in a weird place
because I think this thing is like selling out
now that there's no more room left.
So we're not gonna be able to get there.
We're not gonna be able to do it.
We're not gonna be able to do an episode about it
with any experience, right?
Probably not.
Now, do I have confidence
that I could somehow find us reservations?
Yes, I could check my way.
I check our way into the hotel somehow.
But will we do it?
Will we have time?
We have so much on our plates.
There's a lot of other, yeah, yeah.
There's plates spinning in the air.
How are we gonna juggle them all?
Probably malls and stores to talk about instead.
Correct, yeah.
So there's really only one option,
only one way that we could properly cover
Galactic Star Cruiser before it's closing.
We needed a hero to rise.
We needed a Halcyon veteran
to stand up bravely and to talk about their experience
and what they saw.
And luckily, that hero has risen and is with us today.
And that hero, that Halcyon hero,
also happens to be a star of stage and screen.
You may have seen him as Evan Hansen on Broadway.
And now you can see him starring in the new movie,
No Hard Feelings with Jennifer Lawrence,
which, Jennifer Lawrence, that was very graceful of me.
Star Wars name.
Correct me if I said that wrong.
But as you're hearing this,
that No Hard Feelings is in theaters today.
Here are now the star of that movie,
Andrew Barth Feldman, hello.
Wow.
I feel like my first credit is a Halcyon hero.
I do feel like before the other things,
that's really who I am at my core.
We drove to the heart of it.
I'm happy to give you that verbal badge there.
Yeah, that's what I really appreciate.
I have my actual badge.
This wasn't on purpose.
Obviously, there's a podcast, you can't see it.
This wasn't on purpose that I had this ready.
This just sits on my window sill, so I don't forget.
They give you that or did you buy that?
Is that an extra thing?
I think they give it to you.
It's in your room.
I think they give you one.
And then everyone else in our room went to the front desk
and was like, can we have more medals, please?
And then they shake out them.
Wow.
What is the legal limit?
How can it, technically, if you ask,
how many medals do they have to give you a dozen a night?
That's such a good question, actually.
Is there a limit to the amount of medals
that they can give you?
I mean, there's gotta be kind of like,
maybe it's made out of carbonite
and that feels probably a limitless resource.
The house seems very luxurious,
so I think it's probably fine.
I'm sorry that you're not gonna get
even a drop of cynicism from me about this.
Not even a little bit.
It's not gonna, I wish I could maybe provide it for you.
I'm incapable of doing it with most things,
but with the Halcyon and the Galactic Star Cruiser,
specifically, you're never gonna hear it from me.
It's just not gonna happen.
Wow.
Well, then this, I think this will be a little like,
dark side, light side battle,
because we'll probably have these things where we're like,
we saw a video and that didn't look very good.
And then you can use your lightsaber of optimism.
We are first order.
Today we are first order.
And you are resistance to use the newer terms.
Well, again, A, I have experience with this
from the Halcyon and B,
I feel like the dramatic question of this podcast
and that was, can I convince you
to take a voyage on the Halcyon?
I think that, and that's not, I'm not saying it's my goal.
I'm just wondering if it's at all possible.
And it doesn't have to be,
if that's not gonna disappoint me,
if it disappoints the listeners,
there's nothing I can do about that.
But this is big.
Wow, this is.
And I have to say to be the representative,
I said this in my email to you,
but to be the representative of the Galactic Star Cruiser
here on podcast, The Ride in Perpetuity
is very meaningful to me.
So thank you for having me.
Oh, no way.
So happy to give you that honor.
And I think it's good too.
I think it's like, this'll be a different perspective
than we might add.
There's a way this could have gone like grouchier,
unless I'm wrong and unless like,
I don't know, like maybe this, was this just great?
And does everybody who actually did it think it was great?
Is all the cynicism, people who were judging it from afar,
and if you went on it, it was just awesome.
I don't think it's that all of the cynicism
is people judging it from afar.
I think there's probably two things that are happening.
And I could be wrong about this
because of my sort of bias experience.
But one I think is that it was a lot of people
who went really early and it just wasn't ready yet.
This is a crazy thing.
This is like, nobody's ever done anything like this.
Like by theater terms,
this needed a really long preview period.
And it is a theater show.
So like it did, it needed a long preview period.
It took time to get its C or otherwise space legs.
And by the time that I'd gotten there,
I mean, it was really, really great.
In terms of the actors and the actual running of the thing,
it was so solid.
And then secondarily, I think if you're expecting
relaxing in any way vacation,
A, I don't know why you would go to Walt Disney World
in the first place,
but B, you definitely did not have a good time on that scene.
There's no relaxing to be done.
It's not like an actual,
there's so much of it that is reminiscent
of an actual cruise except for ever being relaxed
for like a single moment in time.
And so if you go and you're not prepared
to just keep saying yes to everything,
like an improv comedian,
but also somebody who's like wanting the immersion,
then don't do the immersive experience
if you don't want to be immersed.
And I think that people were not prepared
for just how much immersion there was going to be.
Gotcha.
Could I take your temperature,
your Star Wars fandom before going onto this thing?
What is it?
What are your movies?
Who are your guys as far as your characters?
Just in general.
It's pretty significant.
I'll say that when I was in eighth grade,
I wrote with my very good friend at the time,
a Star Wars, A New Hope parody musical.
It was an all of a new hope.
It was a full musical.
We staged it then.
It did not go very well.
And so then years later,
we didn't change a word of it
and we handed it to professional Broadway actors
and we did it at 54 Below
because I just wanted to do my Star Wars.
Wow.
So this is like, it is a very significant thing for me.
It's not as significant as most.
I should clarify before I'm tested,
I'm not like Clone Wars.
The Clone Wars I have attempted
to dip my toe in too many times.
And I bet if I had,
then I'd have a lot more background for this experience,
even not that I didn't have enough.
And in fact,
like you don't really need that much Star Wars background,
but it's more definitely more so like the central films
and like the day I've watched most of the Disney plus shows
since, but the cartoons,
I never really was able to get into myself, but yeah,
it was really huge for me growing up,
continues to be really huge for me.
It always made me feel like I was sort of a part
of something larger than myself.
And in terms of what are my movies,
my favorites have always sort of like pivoted
between five and six,
but I'll watch any of the prequels any day.
I really will.
Yeah.
Do you have a favorite non-Anakin pod racer?
Is that too aggressive of a question?
Is it Sebulba?
I mean, I like to think about Sebulba as an idea.
Okay.
Cause I'm like, wow, so many people had to approve Sebulba.
You know, like a lot of people had to be okay
with Sebulba being on screen.
That's true.
I'm pretty fascinated with him as a concept
more than a character.
I think Watto resonates with me.
Of course.
Definitely. He's not a pod racer, of course,
but from that sort of a taste of Star Wars.
That era, yeah.
Watto's big.
Yeah. Sure.
Can I ask a question?
Cause you mentioned 54 Below.
You did a show there called Park Map.
Could you talk about that and your parks experience?
Yeah, absolutely.
And I'm thankful that you asked
because I do have to speak for my own credits here.
I have this show called Park Map
that I did two summers in a row.
And I do plan on doing it again,
which is basically my one man Disney adult musical manifesto.
It's like a defense of Disney adults,
but also an examination of said Disney adults.
And I sing some Disney songs, I sing some original songs,
and I talk about just sort of my relationship to the parks,
the idea of being and becoming a Disney adult
and the sort of desire for permanence
and clinging to nostalgia that that comes with.
But also, yes, I have like,
maybe not the most encyclopedic
that you've had on this podcast,
but like near encyclopedic knowledge of the parks.
One of the things I do in that show is
people, when they're walking in,
they write down names of attractions on their little,
on like little piece of paper,
and they put them in a Boba Fett Stein.
And at three points in the show,
I pull one out and I have 45 seconds
to tell you the history of it.
And I've done so almost entirely without fail.
I'm very proud of that.
That's one of my,
it's probably my biggest accomplishment.
Would you, could we put you on the spot real quick?
Would that be crazy?
You could try, it's really scary.
It's terrifying, but yeah, you could.
I'm scared of specifically what you'll ask me.
I don't know that we, I don't have to go hard.
I don't, I'm just interested in.
Do you have any walls to put up or like,
just generally Walt Disney World itself or?
Not necessarily.
No, I mean, I definitely am probably like,
not as thoroughly versed in the international parks,
but I'm still pretty well versed.
Wow, okay.
I mean, I don't want, yeah, I'm not trying to stump you.
I'm just interested.
You can, I mean, I'm in.
If I said Horizons.
Horizons is one of the toughest ones actually for me.
Oh my God.
Because I missed the boat so much.
So that was like, nobody's ever put in Horizons
and I'm thankful for that.
But I can talk about the pavilion as a whole,
how it's become. Sure.
The Pavilion and now the Play Pavilion,
if I'm not mistaken about this,
then it wasn't something else.
But I think that this is right.
Horizons I missed the boat on.
But I would, if I was given that one,
I would talk more about Epcot as a whole and how like.
Right, sure.
It went from Walt Disney wanting it
to be a community of tomorrow
and turn like an actual like urban community.
And you want to be an urban planner
and turn it to like an edutainment central.
And now people are mad that it isn't edutainment anymore
and that it's actually fun.
And this is always the battle.
Yes, on every new announce.
Well, it seems like a good read, but is it Epcot?
Yeah, Epcot was never Epcot.
Like people don't live there.
So it's not Epcot, it doesn't count.
That's true, yeah, yeah.
But anyway, I guess if it's one I don't know,
I can bullshit my way out of it exactly as I just did.
That makes sense.
Look, that's improv suggestion.
Like you don't have to have to say about the word.
You can turn it into another.
Wait, I'm trying to think though, what is it?
Here, wait, I'm going to give you an easy one
because this was said in an email already,
an email exchange between us, Disney Quest.
That's right.
I was really hoping, that was my first sort of inclination
was to come on here and talk about Disney Quest
because I am one of the very few,
I think perhaps ever in history,
that like every year when my family would go to the parks,
we would do like a full Disney Quest day.
Wow.
Like, I loved Disney Quest.
I have like mountains of cyberspace, mountain VHSs
and toy and like radio Disney song maker things.
So in terms of the history, they wanted it to be like,
one of their Chuck E. Cheese's,
they wanted it to be everywhere,
but now we have virtual reality in our houses.
Like the technology was instantly dated
and there was no reason to be there anymore.
I mean, they barely ever touched it.
And RIP to the NBA experience, of course.
Yeah, that too.
Oh my God, cursed spot potentially.
Now, wait a minute, you want to stump me with one.
What is the, like, okay, cyberspace mountain,
I assume that that means they give you a VHS
of you writing the thing and or.
That you would create.
Yeah, yeah.
But then what's the, what is the radio Disney?
The radio Disney song maker was this.
So this was all, both of those rides
are in the create section of Disney Quest,
which is where you like make things
and get to take them home.
And that's cyberspace mountain, Sid's Toy Maker.
There's like a painting thing.
I think there's an animation academy
and then radio Disney song maker,
which is you pick a sort of like template of a song,
like what genre you want it to be
and who, what kind of person you want to sing.
You want to sing it.
And then it gives you like 10 options for every line.
And like some of them are very sincere,
like love song lyrics.
And then some of them are like,
hot dogs, we're in a two two or something like that.
And then, and like you get to voice certain lines and stuff.
And then it plays the song for you.
And then it like shits out a CD that you get to take home.
And I have so many of them.
Wow.
That's a, I don't know that we covered that aspect.
When we did, yeah, we did an episode.
I never did it personally.
I mean, I only went there really once.
So yeah, Jason, you know about that?
No, not really.
I knew about Sid's Toy Make.
I think Matt Cardona sent us, he was there very early on
where you could make a physical toy, like a Frankenstein.
Right, right.
That's right.
A toy.
And that didn't last forever for sure.
I think basically what they did was like you design it
and then it like prints out like a receipt
of all the parts and like a little picture.
And then you bring it to somebody
and they actually make the actual toy.
I'm pretty sure it's how.
Oh, a little trick.
They'd be like, come back in an hour
and they'd like go into a room and put all the stuff together.
Right, it was not a 3D printer 25 years ago
or whenever it opened.
Sure, instantaneously.
Yeah.
Okay, so this whole thing was, it's interactivity
and make it your own, but with some rules.
Yeah.
Yeah, there's some real constraints on it, for sure.
Yeah, there is some 1996 restraints on it, for sure.
Which is a good creative thought exercise.
Make it interactive, but for 1996.
If you had performed one of those radio Disney songs
in the show, that would have really like
tied it all together.
Wow, that's a real, I mean, hey, now you're giving me ideas
for the next time we do it.
That very well may happen.
Because they have like little lyric sheets on the inside.
Oh wow.
And you're like, this is absolutely nonsense.
God, I gotta hear one of these.
That's so bizarre.
Well, that's maybe an interesting place
to compare contrast that, all right, so there's,
you were totally down for that.
That was you early on doing non-Parks stuff in Disney World
and like we need a whole day for this.
I have to do all this interactive, off the beaten path,
immersive stuff.
So then cut to Galactic Star Cruiser premieres last year.
I don't know when you went, but you must have like,
you must have been so excited about this,
just the notion of it when it was announced.
So there was a moment where my camera test
for no hard feelings was going to intersect
with our scheduled trip.
And I was like, you have to move the camera.
Like I cannot come to the camera test.
I will be in space.
I cannot be there.
Yeah, this was like, this was everything.
So I just, and another example of just how excited
I was about this is like, obviously, yes,
it is a pretty large chunk of change that one's got to spend
on the Galactic Star Cruiser.
And when the sort of prices were announced
and the rooms and like a lot of details were announced,
I was making this show that just came out called Foul Play,
which is this like immersive sort of interactive,
improvised murder mystery show.
And the cast was going to get their COVID test.
And this was a show that I created with a lot of them
and prices came out and one of them was like,
oh man, I just, I wanna go,
but like, who's really gonna stomach this?
Like who's gonna be able to pay for this?
And one of them was like,
we're giving him the money to do it right now.
Like that's what we're here doing is in doing the show
that he created, we are giving Andrew Barth Feldman
the money to go to the Galactic Star Cruiser
and that's what he's gonna use it for.
This is generating that capital real time.
Wow.
Geez, this is great to know that it just like,
and projects you do go straight into that
and that it would potentially conflict it
with you getting this great role.
I'm so glad you could reschedule.
It wasn't, you didn't have to choose.
It was like, I can't tell you how much I like thanked
everyone and told them exactly what I was doing.
Like there was a day on set where I was talking
to Gene Stabinski, our incredible director
and John Phillips who wrote it with him,
No Hard Feelings saying like,
just I started talking about it and I couldn't stop.
And then we had to go film and they watched me,
walk away from this conversation because we were filming
and turn to my co-star of this scene and be like,
have you heard of the Galactic Star Cruiser?
Like to start a new conversation about it
as we were getting ready to film
because I wasn't ready to stop talking about it.
Like this is like, and this was months later too.
This is all I think about.
He seems a little distant.
I don't know, he seems a little not in the moment.
He's talking about this, some spaceship all the time.
Is there any alien on the Star Cruiser that if you needed
them to like just run some lines with you
and put yourself on tape that it would have been possible
or is that not probably in their book?
They don't let them do that probably.
I'm sure they don't let them do that,
but honestly like 100% that would happen.
So I've since this voyage, like these actors,
they really are like, we're standing there
and I was there with my friend Alex Boniello
who was in Dear Evan Hansen with me
and we're doing this thing and we're in these intimate
moments with these actors and we're like,
I think these are the greatest actors in the world.
I think these are my new favorite actors.
And so I've since, I've messaged a couple of them
on Instagram and we have like little text exchanges now
because they're so really brilliant.
Geez, you've made Star Cruiser friends.
That's incredible.
It's not an easy acting job to be in character
for 12 hours a day, eight hours, whatever it is.
Oh my God.
Not to mention like remembering everybody's names.
All right, yeah.
Three quarters of which are real
and one quarter of which are made up.
I could go and be like, I'm Batman
and they'd be like, well Batman, welcome to the house.
They have to do it.
It's crazy.
That's wow, that's almost like a school teacher skill
or a substitute teacher who has to come in
and remember everyone's names.
Yeah, 100%.
Like they're only gonna spend a day with,
they're two days.
Yeah.
Oh geez.
Okay, so friend group is on board, which seems essential.
It seems like you gotta go with people, I think,
to make this work.
So, but then how do you, like, everybody is down.
Is it tough to schedule?
Like, or are you going with like gung ho,
cannot wait to do this any day, any time?
That's right, yeah.
You gotta go with the people who are gonna say yes.
It's the same thing.
And these were people who were like,
it was Alex who's a big Star Wars fan,
a big fan of this sort of thing.
My brother, Matt, who's like on the same level with me
of the parks we've been going together our entire lives.
And my friend Julia, who's a huge, specifically,
Star Wars fan, but a little less eager to like engage.
And so to watch her open up and like accept the thing,
she kind of became the star of the journey
because she followed the first order.
I'm sure we'll get into all of this.
She like became fully a bad guy.
So yeah, no, you have to go with people who are like,
yes, I'm carving out three days of my life
to be in space with you, 100%.
You, on your YouTube channel,
I'm assuming it's your channel.
It is, yeah.
You guys kind of made like a little video diary
of your experience.
And all of you seemed pretty all in on it.
Yeah.
Although going about it in very different ways.
I like that you picked fictional names,
that you gave yourself character names
and pretty much stuck with it.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, yeah, 100%.
I think that's the move.
You come up with a character name,
you come up with a backstory,
but you don't have to go all the way into like,
like I was still myself,
but my desires were gone dream weavers.
Sure.
That was the idea.
I had, if you see at the beginning of the vlog,
I had like a mustache and I was doing this voice
and I thought this was the guy
I was gonna be the whole time.
But it was way too like engrossing for me
to sacrifice my own like genuine enjoyment of the thing
to put something on.
Oh, it wouldn't allow you to just like laugh with glee.
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly, exactly.
I had to still be myself,
but within the truth and the stakes
of the Galactic Star Cruiser.
And so, sorry, okay.
Gorn Dreamweaver.
He's a Gorgmonger from the planet Glorandor,
which is a carpet planet, which doesn't exist.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
So the consistency, like everywhere you step is just the-
That's great.
Feels physically like carpet.
Oh my God.
This is one of my biggest complaints about those sequels
is that most of them are on a sand planet.
This is the kind of creativity I was looking for
in those movies.
That's perfect.
Yeah, I mean, and hey, you get to bring it
to the Galactic Star Cruiser yourself.
It's your chance to rewrite history to make it right.
Now, can I ask, do they own your intellectual property
that you created because you set it to people
on Disney grounds?
Oh, that's a great, I would be okay with that.
Like if I open a Star Wars dictionary next year
and I see Gorn Dreamweaver,
I would die right then and there.
I'd be beside myself.
So yeah, I sell it.
I'd give it to them for free, absolutely.
Okay, great.
Wow, wow.
Okay, so I mean, let's just walk through the experience.
I saw that.
Okay, so you get to Disney World,
you pull into this weird, it's a backstage area kind of
and this odd, it's a building that looks like the,
it's sort of the port that's gonna take you
Yeah.
up to the Star Cruiser.
I found it in just an odd detail
that it's only valet parking.
So you have to, I mean, it's covered.
That's part of that, you're getting things
with that big price tag.
But I include, the parking is free,
but they do say bring a couple of bucks
if you wanna tip on the way out.
Make sure you retain your Earth money.
Credits, yeah.
Don't convert them to credits and then,
just remember to convert them back.
And then not be able to tip the valet on Earth.
Yeah, yeah.
I probably would not appreciate credits.
Okay, that's true.
And the exchange rate these days, just awful.
Yeah.
So, but you get, like, what is what,
and I know that there's some like transport,
elevator kind of thing, but is there anything
you wanna tell us about just like the easing
into the process?
Yeah, absolutely.
I mean, one of the biggest immediate surprises
was that there's like a line of cast members
standing in front of the space station,
like waving at you.
Like they're like waving and they're like,
you walk up to one of them to check in
on like an iPad and they like have all your information.
They give you a special magic band and all this stuff.
And they give you like water and stuff.
So right away, it's like, we're here on this weird thing
and we're not pretending that it's not a weird thing.
So that was like a big shock.
But then, yeah, you walk in, you watch a little video
that's like, this is a fake alarm and this is a real alarm.
That was kind of the big thing
because there's some fake alarms that go off
during the voyage.
And they're like, this is what the real alarm
is gonna sound like.
Which is like a voice that's going like,
this is a real alarm.
Like it's very clear.
It's not C-3PO saying it though to be more confusing.
Yeah, no, it's like, it sounds like very decidedly
not Star Wars.
And I will say, and this is not in the vlog,
it did happen during our journey.
Somebody I think did pull the fire alarm.
It was depressing.
Like obviously it was nobody's fault,
but like to be in the middle of it
and like really be buying in and then be like touching grass
was devastating.
Oh man.
Oh you like to go outside, oh my God.
Oh yeah, that's like getting yanked out of the matrix.
For real, that's exactly what it was.
We were so sad.
We were like, what if we have to go home right now?
Like what if there's a real thing that happened?
Then we all went in and they were like right away,
and this is all, I'm jumping around a lot,
but right away the sort of like Lenka Mock,
who was the character, the assistant captain of the ship,
was like, what a weird detour to Coruscant.
Like they were like right back in.
Well, I like that, yeah.
That was great.
I literally like, we almost applauded at that.
Like yes.
Coruscant looks a lot like Orlando.
Yeah, yeah.
Similar humidity.
Anyway, then you go to, yeah, then you watch that video,
you go into an elevator which has screens,
much like Disney Quest actually,
of like, you know, like you're like a little pod
that's like floating up to the Halcyon,
and then the elevator doors open,
and you have the view of the main lobby
and there is a real like, oh my God,
I'm in space right now.
Like there is a real bodily moment of where am I?
What is going on?
There are cast members there who like are like
already in character and they're like,
let me show you around the,
like they'll bring different groups around
to show them around the ship and all the different rooms.
And so right away we saw everything,
we were taken to our room,
and this is like, yeah,
a broad strokes overview of all of these things.
I mean, I think one of the big things to talk about
is the climate simulator, which is just outside,
but they're like, because our excursion is on Batu,
this is what the weather,
this is a room that will show you
what the weather is like on Batu,
which is just like a very well themed way of saying,
you can go outside, this is where you can go outside.
Little outdoor cove.
If you freak out, if you get claustrophobic
and have a meltdown.
Go to the climate simulator.
And like sometimes the Saja, which are like Jedi light,
because they can't have Jedi,
because this is like a post Jedi world or whatever.
They'll like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, we're squarely, much like Galaxy's Edge,
in between episodes eight and nine.
Everybody's favorite part of Star Wars.
There's nine people left on the Alliance,
or the good guys, basically.
Yeah, that's right.
It's very, very sparse.
Yeah, but the thing I don't know is whether,
I don't know where in that timeline we are
in terms of have the dead spoken or not.
They have not spoken yet.
Well, hold on, hold on.
Or have they?
It seems like before.
I think the dead have not spoken.
I think it's before, yeah.
It's before, yeah.
I think that's right.
It doesn't really come up all that much.
It's not important to this story.
Palpatine is not involved.
Very important to the story of nine,
but not important here.
Right.
And the other big thing I have to mention
from this moment in time is that when you go to the room,
which everybody's seen the room,
it really does, you're like, I am in space.
This is space.
There's like a little screen.
I don't see people talking about this
as much as they should.
That is like basically Alexa, but it's not at all.
It's a droid that is like, I'm your droid
that is here to serve you.
What do you want to do on your journey?
And you're like, go on adventures.
And they're like, I love adventurous passengers.
And you're like, what the fuck?
And then like, you have all these interactions
with the droid and the droid gives you little missions
and then Julia Hoop, who is character was named
Esperanza Mitsubishi.
Oh wow.
She who turned to the first order killed our room droid.
What?
You can do that?
Yeah, you can like use your credentials or whatever
to like hack into the room droid thing
and like send the stormtroopers there and like take her away.
And then at the end it was revealed
that she defeated the stormtroopers,
which was pretty exciting, but we like couldn't access her
for like a couple hours.
Whoa.
And then it was like, she's been powered down.
Like it was, it's crazy.
Wow.
And could she like send the, can you be like,
we need more towels?
Could she do that?
I don't think she, I don't think she served
any actual practical purpose.
Okay. She's just part of the story.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
And also again, like there are not that many cabins here.
Everybody's pretty close to the lobby where this stuff is.
So I wonder if she could, I don't think so.
I'm pretty sure that's not right.
I think you still have to like call or whatever.
Maybe not, maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe we just didn't use her for that.
It's like we were never in the room besides the talk.
Didn't need towels, never came up.
Yeah.
This, that gives me, the proximity to the lobby
just reminds me of just a question I had.
And I don't know if you know the answer,
cause maybe you didn't do this.
I've just been curious, what happens if you go out
into the main, into the lobby at three in the morning?
What's going on if you're just in the middle of the night
when probably not a lot of story is happening?
Do you have any idea?
You're in space still.
Like there's like, there's screens in the lobby
that are like, this is space.
The lights are dim.
We did, we did do this like after stuff was happening.
I think the bar's open pretty late.
I feel like there was one night it was open
till like 2 a.m. or something.
Wow, pretty good.
And so you could go there, you could place a box.
You could order some drinks and get some,
get some bar snacks.
And there's also like a-
Kind of like a desolate late night spaceship.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I might play it late.
Scott is gonna sleep during the day
and wake up around 10 p.m.
Skip admissions.
And then I just sit solo in the climate simulator.
Just have a moment to myself.
I think the climate simulator is also open pretty late.
Like if you need to get some air late at night,
you can, I'm pretty sure one of my friends
like went out to the climate simulator,
took a call and said it was extremely peaceful.
And there's also like a water, like you can go,
there's like a big water pump, I guess,
that you can go and get like water in the main lobby.
That's the main reason to go to the lobby.
Okay, okay.
So refreshments.
Yeah, that's good.
A game, something to do.
Okay, interesting, interesting.
These rooms, I'm so curious about
because I think a lot was made out of,
I feel like it seemed to me like photos
make you think these are claustrophobic rooms,
but then people who did it seem to say it's not so bad.
Where did you land on these rooms?
I agree.
I mean, it was pretty comfortable.
For four of us, it was like two of us in one bed
and then each of us had a bunk bed.
And like, that's not like the number one,
most ideal sleeping situation.
But again, like everything was comfortable.
It's fun to be in space and you're not here to relax.
Like by the time you get to bed,
you are so tired from interacting with these people
that like it is comfortable and it is like,
it still feels like you're part of the story.
I think night one, we like turned off the space viewfinder
in our room and night two, we left it on.
We were like, we can't, we have to cling to,
we have to cling to our final.
That's like kids like sleeping in the tent with like,
Oh yeah.
With some mobile like flashing lights or so.
Wow, you kept the space on all night.
Did you do the bunk? Yeah, that's right.
Were you in the bunk or in the bed?
I was in the bed.
Alex and Julia claimed the bunks pretty early on
and my brother Matt and I shared a bed.
Gotcha.
And that was fine for all of us.
Could a man that's six, three fit in one of the bunks?
I mean, listen, I'm not the authority here,
but I would imagine so.
They're pretty long, they're comfortable.
Like everyone was really excited to sleep in the bunk beds.
Actually, like again, if you're exactly right,
it feels like camp and like that is kind of part of the charm
of it, I think.
You're being told and like being part of
a really wonderful story at every second of the day.
Like they slip notes under your door and they're like,
we're sorry for the first order interference
that's happening on the ship.
Like you get like notes in your room, like it's crazy.
Yeah, I think I would try the bunk,
cause look, when my daughter was born,
I slept in one of the worst chairs
for like two nights in a row and I'm fine, I'm fine.
And I'm sure one of these bunks are much more comfortable.
So I think I would go bunk.
The bunks are great.
I would, if I get to do it again, I'm going bunk for sure.
Jason's bunk.
Jason, I think you, cause you want your small spaces.
I like, yeah, I like a cozy space.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know, I'm oddly was eyeing those bunks like,
yeah, these rooms look a little small,
but I think they're bunk.
Yeah, maybe we're everything, this isn't all bunk.
Or you would be next time.
Andrew, I think you hit the nail on the head
by calling it camp.
Like I feel like a lot of the marketing
or early views of it referred to like,
oh, it's like a cruise ship on land.
Yeah.
But the thing about that is, you know,
there's a Star Wars bar on the newest cruise ship,
Disney cruise ship. Right, totally.
And it seems like it's got a little bit,
if you just want a little Star Wars,
it's like the bar, you know, has big screens,
it jumps to light speed, there's a lot of dry ice drinks.
And then you can leave and then just be on a cruise.
You can just go do whatever you want.
Yeah, that's right.
As opposed to this experience where it's like,
it is all encompassing.
It is a two, three day immersive theater experience.
So I think camp, where it's just like, you know,
when you're at camp, you're at camp, you know.
That's 100% right.
Yeah, I think that's a great way to put it.
And might've helped them in the marketing
because I know some of the marketing material
started to get a little confused.
Yeah, it's like Star Wars camp.
Like you're at Star Wars camp for a few days.
Star Wars fantasy camp.
It's not rock and roll fantasy camp,
which I keep getting ads for,
where you can play bass with Tom Hamilton from Aerosmith
or Pete Best, the original drummer of The Beatles.
Are you going, Mike?
This is your galactic star cruiser.
It's either this rock and roll fantasy camp
or galactic star cruiser.
And I think they're probably similar prices.
No slight to Pete Best.
I did not know he was still with us.
Absolutely he is.
You didn't know either?
I don't think I knew that either.
Yeah, yeah.
I didn't know Pete Best was still alive.
Guys, he's still rocking.
No shade, no shade to Pete Best.
So their ads should be rock and roll fantasy camp,
the best way to discover that Pete Best is still alive.
Yes.
He's one of the, I think he's the top guy, Billed.
Pete Best is.
I mean, honestly, I'm like, yeah,
I kind of want to go to rock and roll fantasy camp
with Pete Best.
That sounds awesome.
Yeah.
Yes, it's like camp emotionally
and how engrossing it is it's camp
in terms of like your brain really does kind of think of it
as a cruise.
Like when we did the excursion to Batuu,
we kept saying in total earnest
and without thinking about it,
we should probably get back to the ship soon.
And like all of the big story moments
are kind of veiled in like cruise activities.
Like they'll be like, let's play this,
like we're going to teach you this game on the bridge.
Everybody come to the bridge, learn this game.
And then like Chewbacca shows up and it's like,
oh my God, that's a huge story moment.
So that's the way that they get you
to all these different places.
But of course not everybody goes to all of those things.
So different people get different points of the story
and like it's a pretty smart way to like engineer people
toward being in the right place at the right time.
Right. Wow.
And had you done Galaxy's Edge prior to this?
I had, and that's another thing that I think about a lot
is how incredible it would be if it was my first time there
as part of the Star Cruiser,
because they really do a like deeply impressive job
justifying both of the rides
within the story of the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Like it is your mission to do the things
that those rides are asking you to do.
And we were talking about it.
Like we had all done rides of the resistance
a number of times, but the thought of that being like
the first time in your story as a passenger
on the Galactic Star Cruiser that you see Kylo Ren
or that like you like this crazy thing is happening to you
and you were just on the house yet.
Like, and they really do make a whole thing out of it
when you get back that like, oh, there were like,
it's part of the story.
Hondo is part of the story with Smoke and Resurrect.
You have to get that coaxium.
That coaxium comes back later.
It's wild.
It almost seems like you have to do the Star Cruiser
to complete the story of Galaxy's Edge.
I, going back to Galaxy's Edge since the Star Cruiser
which I've done a number of times, it's,
I love Galaxy's Edge.
I've always loved Galaxy's Edge,
but in relation to how it feels in Star Cruiser,
it feels empty.
Like it really does not feel, it feels like I'm,
I am on this like weird planet.
We went to Ogas Cantina and we had like,
we like set a password to the bartender
and he gave us coasters that had QR codes
that we had to scan in our app that like gave us a new thing.
Like it's, if you really do feel like you're in a Star War.
Yeah.
Special Star Cruiser stuff at the Cantina.
That's, I don't think I knew that.
Yeah, everywhere.
Every, and you can book it through, like you can,
like when you're booking your Star Cruiser vacation
or whatever, you can be like,
hey, we also want to do the lightsaber.
We want to do the lightsaber workshop.
And because you're like, you wear a thing
when you go to Batuu that like is like a Halcyon pin.
And so all of the cast members know to like greet you
knowing that you're part of the Halcyon
to like give you the Halcyon stuff in different places
that's going to help you later in your story.
Like it really is a crazy,
it was always meant to be these two things together,
which is why it's so sort of sad.
And it feels like that's the,
the Star Cruiser is the place they didn't,
from what we understand, we're not insiders really,
but that was Star Cruiser is the only place
they didn't cut like the budget
on having everything be crazy immersive.
I feel like Matt might be part of it or yeah,
like you're describing this incredible experience.
And a lot of that stuff was not,
it was kind of taken out of the actual land itself.
So that's the difference when you're,
the difference you're feeling being there.
Yeah. And I've got to say, like, I mean, I mean,
cause this is such a big thing,
like in talking about the price, like worth it, quote unquote
is obviously such a relative thing
from person to person and what you want to spend your money
on what kind of money you've got.
But that is how much that thing costs.
Like that's just how much it costs to do the thing
that the Galactic Star Cruiser is for what you're getting.
If you pay that money, it is an entirely reasonable price.
Yeah. There's a lot.
I mean, there's so many performers just in general.
Yeah. Like once in a lifetime,
like all the, every experience on it is only happening
then essentially like the way you're doing it
is only happening right there to you.
It's personalized.
So that seems worth, I liked the way I was reading
the touring plans, Lynn Testa's breakdown of,
is it worth it?
And he does a really specific breakdown of
these are parts of the country and world
I think that you should see before doing Galactic Star Cruiser.
Like if I'm being honest, you know, make sure like Alaska
is really remarkable and Hawaii, you know,
maybe do this route, but, and then
just assuming all of that is important to you then, then.
That's good.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's reasonable.
It is excess, you know, it's like, what do you,
what do you value like emotionally and creatively?
And for me, it's, I have dreams about the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Let me ask you this question.
And now you're talking to an older man who feels like
there's a little bit of a lack of some of his friends
on the ship.
A hypothetical older man, this could be any older man.
Not necessarily you.
And a cooler older guy, like a guy who you wouldn't
really know he's an older guy.
Oh, I just assumed cool as soon as you mentioned this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, I sounded cool before you.
And a guy who you'd hear his voice, you're like,
ah, gotta be mid twenties or so.
But when he sees videos of some of it and he's like,
I am missing visually some of my friends.
I don't want the sequel characters to go away or anything.
I just, where are my people?
Like, and you're saying you're like five or six.
He's really well just now that he doesn't want
the sequel characters.
Well, I've been very consistent.
The cool guy has been consistent.
He doesn't want the sequel characters to go away
from Galaxy's Edge.
He just wants some of his friends.
That's all he wants.
He's a cool guy.
What would you?
Yeah, I hear you.
And I have to say that I really do think this is one
of the brilliant things about the Star Cruiser
because it's not about Rey and it's not about Kylo Ren.
It's not about those guys.
Like they make a big appearance
and they're a big sort of payoff,
but it's more about the like WWE phenomenon
of seeing them do the thing that they do
as opposed to like seeing those characters in the flesh.
And in fact, the fact that there may be less sought
after characters, I think lends to more urgency
and more access.
The characters that are like the sort of new made up
characters on the Star Cruiser are so exciting
because if you had a guy there dressed up as Luke Skywalker,
I could look at him and I could know
that that's not Luke Skywalker.
But this gentleman standing in front of me
and giving me one of the best pep talks of my life
is Rafe Cole as far as I'm concerned.
Wow.
I am Gorn Dreep.
Like I know that I'm Gorn Dreep.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like this is a story that I don't know
and thus it has a place for me in it
and it has a place for these spectacular actors.
So I think if the thing you love about Star Wars
is sort of like just the characters,
then no, it's probably not for you.
But if it's the world and the feeling,
I think this is one of the,
for me and what I appreciate about Star Wars,
this is like my favorite Star Wars story
is that of the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Is it still like, would you say,
because like I honestly, I mean,
from everyone I've talked to who's done it,
they all like it.
So like, I assume I would have a good time doing it.
I'm all kidding aside.
Is it almost something where like,
if it wasn't even branded Star Wars,
it would be just as cool?
Like, is it almost just like the performers are so good
and it's just the activities are so much fun.
You're just like, ah, it's a cool space thing
that reminds me of Star Wars.
It's almost not even the point in some ways.
Absolutely, 100%.
I think Star Wars helps to give it that boost
that of recognition.
But like, if you don't know Star Wars
and this is all gibberish to you,
that is totally, totally okay.
And in fact, I know Star Wars
and I don't know a lot of the stuff
that they're talking about.
And that is okay because it's about this sort
of isolated story.
And I think that it being Star Wars
probably puts a lot of pressure on it
to perform like a very certain and specific way,
just as everything Star Wars always has.
There's always this precedent
that people expect Star Wars to meet
that it could not ever and has never met.
Everything's so hyper judged,
which you see with this too.
If they had invented from whole cloth
a big immersive experience that you stay in and sleep in,
but that you weren't viewing under this judgmental lens.
Like the Space Mountain Hotel
full of original Space Mountain characters.
It doesn't have nearly as much pressure
as Star Wars does because all your friends
don't have to be there or the version of it
that you like doesn't have to be represented.
Just one friend.
Like the countdown guy, 10, nine.
There's only one friend in Space Mountain.
And then like somebody playing like Dick Dale
playing guitar on the stage or something.
You need to know where that,
in the world where that sound is coming from.
Yeah.
I was just in London
and they have a bunch of stuff like this.
Like not as sort of long form as the Star Cruiser,
but like things that are multiple hours long
that are these immersive storytelling experiences.
This thing called Phantom Peak that I didn't get to do
that I'm really hoping to soon.
But they know how to invest in those kinds of things.
And I think it is true that this is where
the future is headed.
And something we were talking about during it was like,
could this work with Marvel?
And the answer is no, because what would I do?
Would I become a superhero?
I know I'm not a Marvel superhero.
Like with Marvel, it is about the characters.
And so this doesn't work.
I think the reason it works for Star Wars
is because as great as the characters are,
it's about the world and the feeling
and the sort of like thing that happens when Star Wars works.
And Star Wars really works on the Star Cruiser.
That makes sense.
I mean, I will say this.
If there was an X-Men's mansion,
I could just like sleep in Wolverine's room for two nights.
I would absolutely do it and love it.
If I could just hang out, that'd be fine with me.
You don't want your own room?
You're playing me sleeping in Wolverine's room.
I am Mike Carlson, cool older guy.
And I'm sleeping in Wolverine's bed
because he's away for a while.
And I can just roam around, go down to the danger room,
see what they're doing and go, ah, cool.
And then I can go upstairs and like have a drink
in Professor X's study.
To be clear. I mean, that does sound pretty great.
Could you, but you wouldn't want that you have your own bed
that's only your bed and full access to Wolverine's room.
You need to know that it's his bed
and that he slept there, let's say within the week.
Yeah, I would like to know that he was there.
I mean, you could all pick.
But also that he's not going to be there.
Like you also don't, like this is a whole,
an immersive Marvel X-Men experience
where you're sleeping in Wolverine's bed,
meaning he will not be appearing.
The mansion's mostly empty.
They're like fighting apocalypse overseas or something.
Because if he finds an intruder in his room,
you're getting those claws to your throat.
Like, it has not.
You're gonna fucking kill you.
You won't ask any questions.
Not a kill move, but at least a threat.
Like who are you?
Yeah, it's an empty X-Mansion.
There's no interactive elements
other than you can just roam through the halls
and see what's going on.
And you've chosen a school setting
where there's often any number of students
that they could easily go like you're a new student.
Like, no, no, you're a guy.
I don't want that pressure.
Crashing.
Yeah.
I'm just an older guy.
And there's also no alcohol.
Like it's a school.
You're just sleeping at the school.
I mean, hey, I'm on board.
We're just brainstorming here.
You have to have snuck it in.
It's gotta be in a flask.
I snuck alcohol into this school.
If you start opening drawers and secret cabinets
in Wolverine's room, you're gonna find some alcohol.
Yeah, that's one of the missions.
Professor X has some brandies.
Sure.
Brandies.
Oh, that's the room to go to.
Hank McCoy, this beast drink, do we know?
I don't know.
Andrew, full disclosure, on that excursion day
when you went to Batuu, did any of your party,
did anyone cut out to go to Pizza Rizzo
or do a quick Tower of Terror laugh, you know?
Not one of us.
And people on our cruise did,
especially ones with little kids.
I personally advise against it, for sure.
Yeah, sure.
Like I was on Batuu for the first time.
I really was like, this is, I, you know,
you get on the bus that feels like a transport shuttle.
Like, it's a crazy thing.
So no, we did not go to Pizza Rizzo.
We did not go to Woody's Roundup Barbecue.
We stayed in Galaxy's Edge.
And it was also like a really hot day.
So we were like, let's go and do our missions and then.
Yeah.
And get back inside.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a simulator of a toy-themed barbecue.
It's just, it's the kind of thing they would do.
It's not real.
Trying to in character explain like, look,
this was really stupid.
I know the shuttle leaves at a certain time,
but I made a reservation for Woody's Roundup Barbecue
because I knew it would launch.
You know what you could have done?
You could have gone to, we just talked about this,
the 50s Primetime Cafe.
You could say, well, this is where Dexter Jettster
has his famous diner.
I feel like that one at least could have worked
as far as explanation.
I guess this is the criteria is if you're gonna do
anything else in Hollywood Studios,
you've got to justify it in world.
If you're gonna go watch Muppet Vision 3D,
you've gotta be like, these are the Ewoks
and Yoda's cousins and stuff.
Yeah, that's good, that works.
You can tell from the voice.
This is somebody Yoda's related to.
Right.
Yeah.
Star Tours is like when you go on a cruise
and then you need to take another shuttle
to the hiking through the woods.
Yeah.
And then you have to get back to the cruise ship.
Sure, sure, sure, right.
That's right, that's right.
What has happened story-wise before,
excuse me, it's a second day thing that you go to Batuu.
Just so that we get into some of the story of it,
like what's happened thus far at that point?
What's the initial stuff that you tackle?
Yeah, I mean, obviously here we go, spoilers ahead.
The First Order has come upon the ship
because they fear resistance sympathizers on the ship
and that there may be many of them
and so they're here investigating.
The crew is trying to be welcoming,
but there are, and also Chewbacca,
I believe has arrived at this point.
Chewbacca has in fact docked onto the ship.
So those are kind of the big things,
but that's like major main storyline.
Maybe the First Order has already, this is a big spoiler,
taken the central droid out of commission.
This is a droid we're made to have great sympathy for,
SK-620 maybe, something like that.
And they think the droid is having secrets
so they like kill the droid basically.
And that's a big moment where we're meant to turn
upon the First Order or not, as Julia discovered.
But yeah, first day is really more tutorial
than anything else.
Like those are the big moments, but we were like,
wow, this first day was amazing.
How could it become any more immersive than this?
And then everyone was like,
so today was basically your tutorial,
now you have to decide which path you're gonna take
and it gets real tomorrow.
And it did, it was crazy.
So that's everything that's happened.
I have to speak to my story particularly.
I didn't decide going in like which,
sorry, you hear the cars.
I didn't decide going in like which path I was gonna take.
You can be Resistance First Order, like Jedi basically,
or like Smuggler Scoundrel.
Following Gorn Dreamweaver's heart,
I fell in with the scoundrels,
who is this character Wraith Cole,
who is Gaia, the performer on the ship.
He's her manager.
And he is trying to-
I love that there's a space manager, right?
That's great.
Space pop star manager, incredible.
We were pretty obsessed with the concept
of somebody in Star Wars having like a manager,
but it felt very like, you know,
like grief Karga in the Mandalorian.
Like he's like a bounty hunter manager,
except for Talon and for Gaia specifically.
And they're trying to make some kind of drop-off,
they're trying to do this whole thing.
But basically the big thing is they're trying to steal
this stone from the heart of the ship.
The Hyanna-Neya stone.
And this stone is made to feel like,
oh, they're scoundrels,
so they're trying to steal it for money.
When you get to know them,
you discover that this stone was wrongfully taken
from Gaia's planet.
She's a Twi'lek.
And it was her planet.
Oh God, I can't remember what planet it's called now.
But like the Hyanna-Neya stone was taken from her planet
by like basically colonizers and used for like on the ship,
on display, like maybe provide some fuel or something.
And Wraith on Gaia's behalf
is trying to steal the stone back.
I found this cause very noble,
especially since Gorn Dreamweaver's home
was also perhaps under attack from the First Order.
He was really worried about that.
People trying to get free carpet, yeah.
Exactly, yes.
Spilling stuff everywhere.
Mining for carpet on the,
I mean, you look at the Death Star
and the sort of Star Destroyers,
and they're just, they need some rugs.
And there's one place to get them,
and it's the carpet mowers of Glorandor, of course.
And they're dampening some of that sound.
It's all, it's very echoey and severe in there.
Yeah, yeah, they need, they could use a lot of rugs.
Yeah, yeah, soften the landing when Kylo Ren's,
you know, throwing people all over the place.
So this has happened by this point.
Now I want to skip ahead because I,
this is a story that I feel is,
it's urgent that it's told.
This is sort of the big takeaway for me, I think.
So we get to talking to Wraith Cole in person.
Now there is an app component to all of this.
We're not using quote unquote Wraith Cole on the app,
but it's like preset responses to our preset texts
that are like, I want to hang out with you,
or like, no, I don't want to hang out with you.
And like getting a sense.
So we go up to Wraith Cole in the real world,
the actor, whose picture is on the app, by the way,
so we can like know who he is.
And we go up to him and we're like,
Wraith, we've been messaging with you.
We're here for whatever you need.
And it's notable that my brother Matt,
his whole thing was like, I love Gaia.
Going into the ship, the one thing he knew was that he,
he knew that Gaia was a character,
and he decided he was a big Gaia fan.
So he goes up to Wraith and he's like, I love Gaia.
I'm a big Gaia fan and I'll do anything for Gaia.
And Wraith is like, anything?
And we're like, yeah, yeah, we'll do anything.
And he's like, well, then I've got an extra secret mission
that's like not on your app.
Like, this is like a separate thing.
So they, so this is just immediately one of the instances
of like the ship itself rewarding you
for being like into it, you know what I mean?
Saying yes to things.
He gives us this like QR code for us to scan on our app
and tells us about this stone and all this stuff.
Next day we run into him again and he's like,
the heist is happening tonight at 3 p.m. in the cargo bay.
Don't let anybody follow you.
It's gonna be a small, a small group of people.
Like this was, and like we were one of the few people
who was invited.
A lot of other people ended up being like,
what's going on in here?
And like came in and kind of screwed everything up.
But then he's like, we're gonna steal the stone back.
We go up to the deck.
So this is, this is pretty deep day two.
The first thing he says, he's like, we need a distraction.
And he turns to me because we've now had a few conversations.
He's gotten to know me personally.
And he says, this is where you come in.
And he said, we need something lovey-dovey,
maybe some vows or an engagement.
And I said something that is true,
which is that I am an ordained minister.
I am an ordained minister in the real world,
just kind of for fun.
It's never been required of me.
And so as a distraction to get the stone,
I performed the renewals of vows
of two real married couples on the ship.
Wow.
What?
This is in the vlog and I stand up there
and I'm like yelling like,
can I have everyone's attention please?
My name is Gondre Weaver
from the carpet Moors of Glorandor.
And I am here to celebrate the marriage of Jerrick and Z
and Liz and Matt,
because one of the couples was really into it
and the other one was not.
Those are regular names.
And from there, all these other people
and all these other kids had all these roles.
And in the vlog,
I think it was my brother and Alec were both recording
and you could see the way that like the stone passes hands
and all these different people are intercepting
different actual characters,
because like the captain couldn't see about this.
So like we had to like alert Wraith
that the captain was coming.
Like it was like a whole involved thing
that a hugely important device in it was that I was very,
very loudly proclaiming the renewal of vows
of these two real life couples.
Wow.
Which well, okay.
Like a renewal, I guess it's not so important
if it's binding.
Like that renewal didn't count.
And yet the actual ordain,
like it feels like it had some significance.
It's crazy you had that up your sleeve.
Yeah, it worked out.
And I think it was my brother who reminded all of us
that I was ordained.
And then it, yeah,
that's the only time that's ever been useful actually.
Wow, you didn't do it to get friends married.
You just did it to do it.
To hopefully one day get friends married.
You know, like that one day I'd be asked to do that.
Wow, now that's crazy.
I wonder what like,
they probably have some like prompts,
like regular like ideas that they would give
for a distraction in a normal scenario.
But then they're also like,
oh, if we got something on the fly here,
let's just go with that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it's like a sort of bare bones idea
for what they're gonna do.
And then like let the guest kind of guide you.
And a lot of things they'll do is also kind of trick you
into thinking that you guided them.
Like the actor who played Sammy at one point,
he comes up to us and he's like,
we need a way to get the storm troopers away
from this thing.
And I was like, oh, maybe, you know,
like if they've got to get to the brig or something.
And he was like, wait, you want to put them in the brig?
What?
And it's like, oh, that's what you need to do.
And you just kind of put those words in my mouth.
So like sometimes they like really need to find a way in,
but other times there's a lot of room for like play.
And later that day, there was another need for distraction.
Like we had broken into the bridge
to like get the coaxium or whatever.
And we were there with Wraith Cole,
because this was like this council track.
And he was like, well, if we need another distraction
and can't think of anything,
I mean, I know my guy Gorin has got it.
And I was like, I'm healing father issues right now
in real time.
Like this is like really happening right now.
Wow.
Thank you Wraith.
You would be really great to hear
from some of the performers,
because I imagine you did a hell of a job performing,
distracting, you knew exactly what you're doing.
You're a performer.
I would imagine there's some versions where they're like,
and then you're going to be the one with the distractions.
And someone was like walked in the corners like,
hey, you motherfuckers over here.
Everyone look over here.
They're like, no, no, no, no.
Not like that.
No, no, no.
No, he's pulling his penis out.
God.
You know what I mean?
No, he's peeing in the corner.
It's like somebody stop me.
Put the pretzels down.
Put the bowl of pretzels down.
We need you.
You know what?
We got someone else.
We're going to get someone else.
Somebody has to have done a shitty job like that.
Yeah.
This particular actor sort of later confided
through Star Wars terminology, may I add.
He like, we at the very end of the experience
went to thank him and the actors like very much in earnest
and we kind of said like,
we know you can't break character right now
and we accept that and understand,
but we need you to know how much this has meant to us.
And this actor in particular,
like thanked us in return because he was like,
it's good to know somebody who I can like really hand
the reins to.
Like not even like, and that was for our whole group.
Like it was like this guy,
this poor guy who is working so hard
and you never see him sweat.
He needs to, in order to us not see him sweat,
find ways to pass the baton for even like two minutes
and like give like holding court responsibility
to somebody else.
Yeah. Right.
So that he can continue to be like full battery,
you know, rating poll.
And also the actress playing Lankham Mock,
who I think was like, yeah, cruise director.
Last day we did the same thing
and we like thank her very earnestly.
And she's like, just so you know, and I mean this,
if you ever want to come work here on the Halcyon,
there's always a place for you.
Oh wow. Whoa.
That's the ultimate compliment.
That's something I carry with me every day.
I'm like, I could always just go do that.
You know, I could. You could.
So it is possible.
This was something we talked about on our Patreon,
but we discussed the notion that if Jason was weird
and rude enough at the 50s prime time cafe,
maybe he'd get invited to play a permanent grandpa character.
Invited.
So I don't know if the same rules apply there,
but at least somewhere in that Dollywood Studios area,
that kind of recruitment magic is possible.
There's a headhunter.
Some of the actors are also headhunters.
No.
Ironically, you renewing the vows,
I was at a wedding recently,
and only after the fact did I learn the officiant
was in the original cast of Galactic Stark,
was one of the lieutenant crois,
was one of the imperial officers.
Was it a croi?
I wonder which one, because our lieutenant croi,
he's one of the few that I don't know his real life name,
is like one of my top three favorite actors of all time.
I think he's out of the game now.
I think he's retired from theme park acting now.
I think that's right, which is pretty sad for me personally.
All right, so you're on this scoundrel track, correct?
Yeah.
Your friends are on others, what's going on?
What's happening in the other, the stuff you're not seeing?
That's right, we all kind of fell into our own thing.
So Matt, my brother, was sort of on the scoundrel track
with me that ended up falling into a lot of resistance stuff.
And so he was really close to the main story
and would be asked to like,
you're gonna have to pass this suitcase of coaxium
around to somebody else around the ship.
He was part of bigger main story stuff
that we weren't invited to.
Because by the time day two rolls around,
this computers through the app
and through the different relationships
have kind of figured out who's the most into it
and what track you're taking.
So you get invited to specific things
and they have a list of who specifically
is allowed into this room.
And they won't let you in unless you're on that list
because of you following a specific track.
And so Matt was invited to this resistance stuff.
Alex went the Jedi path.
And he met Ray before the rest of us.
Like he was in a room for like some kind of like
forced training or something that was kind of a guide
that it was under.
They discovered that Luke Skywalker's holo cube,
like a holo cube that was Luke Skywalker's
was found on Batuu.
Yes, this was a mission of his.
He had to go on Batuu, find this holo cube through the app
and like scan different crates and stuff.
And then he's in this room and Ray comes in,
they open the holo cube and apparently,
and I have not seen this with my own eyes,
actual hologram of Yoda appears and like gives advice.
And this is something that only Alex got to see
and like 10 other people that were on the voyage.
Wow, that's cool.
Is there a, interesting, was there a,
do the other paths have anything comparable
to meet a legacy character such as Yoda?
One of your friends?
Any of my friends?
Yeah, no, nobody else really gets to meet
one of your friends.
Interesting.
That is true.
And in fact, Julia, who took the first order path
was hoping she'd get to have a relationship with Kylo Ren,
which she did not unfortunately,
but she did have a very tight knit relationship
with Lieutenant Kroy.
Yeah, she was invited to like similar stuff
is like Matt in the resistance side of things,
but for the first order.
So like Matt's team would go to the engineering room
to like fix stuff and Julia's team would go
to the engineering room to break stuff basically.
Wow, that's fun.
But she really was, there is this striking moment
that I will never forget.
Julia, who is the biggest Star Wars fan,
but like maybe the least into this kind
of immersive storytelling going into it.
It's the very big finale.
And a lot of the Galactic Star Cruiser
is long and gorgeous monologues,
like characters delivering these huge monologues
about like their ideas about the world
and like frankly race and things like that.
Race is discussed very much on the Galactic Star Cruiser.
And in this moment, Lieutenant Kroy is responding
to a speech of the captains, which is saying like,
this is a ship of good people
and these people will not let evil triumph.
And Lieutenant Kroy responds and says,
you'll be surprised with just how many
first order sympathizers there are.
And he starts to list them by name
and like point to all the people in the crowd
who are first order sympathizers,
you realize just how many of them there are.
And like the third or fourth one, he says, he goes,
Mitsubishi, who is our Julia's name.
And we were like, she won.
Like she won the Galactic Star Cruiser
by having her fake name said in the big finale
of the Galactic Star Cruiser, it was amazing.
And earlier too, the actor playing Sammy,
who's like one of the good guys found out
that she was hanging out with us.
And we were like, she's a first order sympathizer,
she's gotta go.
And he was like, get out of here.
And he looks at us and he's like, was that Mitsubishi?
The captain warned me about her.
Like stuff like that, it really is a nuts out thing
that they do.
That's great.
Do the first order sympathizers get punished
at the end of the experience at all or?
No, I think there is a sense of like,
obviously the bad guys lose.
But there is then a sense of like, look around,
these people have shared this experience.
And then you go, it is very much like we all love each other
and it's okay.
And then we go to the, you all go to the bridge
and where the screen of space was is like a video
of fireworks basically.
Like it's obviously it's not real fireworks,
it's like a video of fireworks that we had bought into it
so much by this point that we all four of us cried
at this like video that was playing of fireworks.
It fully worked on us.
I could see that.
I mean, that's such a like, you have to be,
there's so much effort, emotional effort,
I feel like for a few days where you're like,
almost just like the blowing off of that
has to have some sort of like emotional reaction point.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
Okay, there's discussion of race and these big ideas
in the experience.
Do you feel like somewhere in the text
and the narrative of Galactic Star Cruiser
is the solution of how to make everything better
in this country and world of ours?
This was a very kind of curious thing.
Like we're like sitting in like the big dining room
on the second night and kind of the big event
that's happening is the captain and the lieutenant
are kind of having these dueling monologues.
And you kind of see where both of them are coming from,
the good guys and the bad guys.
Like, and that is sort of, I think one of the big ideas
of the Star Cruiser is it's like,
once you boil the first order down to an ideology
and not like the people who are working at the highest level,
it's like, ah, there's something there.
Like there are people who believe this ideology
and would follow the first order in the real world.
But the captain's like, says something at some point
that's like, you know full well that I can't work
on any other Star Cruiser because look at me.
And we're like, oh, cause she's blue.
Like it's cause she's blue.
Like that's what she's talking.
And like, they never talk about that in Star Wars.
And so like, I think it is an effective,
an emotional tool for empathy.
I don't think it's like, you know,
the end all be all of sort of like racial analysis.
So we couldn't put some of the like worst people
in our country or world into Galactic Star Cruiser
then have them like learn a lesson, cry at the fireworks.
Then they come out and they fix everything.
They're like, we have to, we have to give, you know,
the stone back to the people, like the proverbial stone
back to the proverbial Twi'lex.
Like Carlson and Ben Shapiro,
their ways are healed after two days in the LCA.
I like the Lieutenant Croy and now I'm different.
I've changed.
I'm nice now.
That's what they have to do with DeSantis.
That's how they have to fix the DeSantis problem.
Just put them on the Star Cruiser.
The lawsuits kind of go away.
It's going to be fine.
Yeah.
They have blue shrimp.
I've never seen such a thing.
That you knew what the human spirit was capable of.
What have we?
Well, let's just do basic stuff like food, drink.
Like how was it?
So great.
Like genuinely good.
And not to mention all inclusive, you know,
like you don't pay like blue milk is so good when it's free.
Blue milk is so, so, so good when there's a fountain
of blue milk.
And it's unlimited blue milk.
Yeah, unlimited.
They literally have like a like found blue milk fountain.
Do you know that Jason?
I did know that.
I think that's available 24 hours.
Is it?
I'm pretty sure.
Water.
4 a.m.
You could have a glass an hour.
Yeah.
You could make money on the whole thing.
In terms of blue milk.
Where are the refreshers?
Jason has a full body like suit
that is actually just like a big,
some sort of big receptacle.
Oh yeah.
To get as much blue milk smuggled out of there as possible.
What's Star Wars language for doggy bag?
I wonder actually.
I don't know.
I do know that all like meat is bantha.
Right, yeah, yeah.
They always call it bantha meat.
And like on night one, they came around.
And again, we were just so caught in by this point
and we didn't even think about it.
We were so excited to be there.
And the waiter comes around and they're like,
would you like more bantha?
And we all look at each other like, oh, more bantha?
Yeah, we'll take more bantha.
Like no, no like facetiousness about it.
The second night, the dining experience is a tour
through different planets and cultures.
So the actual chef of the actual Galactic Star Cruiser
comes out and is like, this next dish is from Coruscant
and like, or like a Mustafar.
And like the whole room turns like red
and they like light it lava colors and play
like Mustafarian music.
And then he explains the dish and like how it was used
with like fire and stuff like that.
And we were like, wow, this is from,
this all the way from Mustafar, crazy.
And then it's, I'm just guessing it,
is night one a Gaia performance and night two
is more like a story happens like you were describing
kind of a back and forth?
That's right, that's right.
Night one is a big Gaia performance
and a lot of story happens in the Gaia performance as well.
Like that is another like just great reason
for everybody to get in one room.
Like Chewbacca appears and like they're chasing Chewbacca
around and Lieutenant Croix trying to get Chewbacca
while Gaia's performing, partly as a distraction
and partly just like that's what's happening.
And she's amazing, the songs are really great.
You can listen to the album.
And, but yeah, then second night is more story driven.
I think that maybe there was like,
it's part of a story that Gaia is supposed
to have a performance, but then it's canceled.
It can't go on for some reason,
maybe because of first order interference.
And so then she does like an unplugged show
that feels like a big protest, like on the deck.
That's cool.
Like she's like there and like one of the characters
plays guitar and she's singing all the songs
and everybody's singing along from the songs
they learned the night before at the big concert.
Oh, you know them by then.
So you get the Gaia songs are second nature.
We are like part of the protest.
We're standing there like going,
hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi, hi,
like we're like, so we're really, really there.
And there's like a lot of call and response on this thing.
Cause like, I think one of the resistance like terms
is ignite the spark, light the flame or something.
And they really get this stuff in your head.
They really teach it to you that by day two,
you're saying a bunch of like,
somebody will say, ignite the spark
and the whole ship will go, light the flame.
Like they like teach you all these Star Wars words.
It's crazy.
You don't even, you're not thinking about it 48 hours in.
Even watching a video of just here,
we're getting on the elevator.
I just watched somebody's POV of doing this
and hearing a bright suns on the way,
which is like the greeting in galaxy's edge.
And it really made me like, oh yeah, remember that?
Remember bright suns?
That was sure something they did for the first 10 days
and never again.
But the bright, if you like the bright suns thing,
it's the, there's so many more of it.
You're living in the bright suns mentality.
I said, when we did the Batuu trip,
I said bright suns to every single cast member I've had.
I was so excited to say bright suns.
And I had the little Halcyon medal.
So they were all like, bright suns.
VIP on galaxy's edge.
I have a couple of quick, more practical questions.
Did you see anyone trying to get hammered?
Like as far as like, is it open bar there?
I don't think it is, right?
Don't you have to pay for those?
I don't think it's open bar.
You have to pay for the alcohol.
That's to prevent people from getting hammered.
There were, there definitely were people
who were substantially drinking.
And that was the thing that they decided to do.
And you could, like you totally,
that is a Star Wars story of your own, you know?
I have to speak to-
I had to live a Star Wars story.
That's the Star Wars story I would live.
This is reminding me of something pretty important
that happened actually.
There was a gentleman who was Obi-Wan Kenobi.
And he didn't work there.
And we were very confused,
but he looked like old Obi-Wan,
like old, like he had like white hair and a white beard.
Old Ben Kenobi, yeah.
And he would sit and he was there definitely by himself.
And he didn't talk to anybody.
And he would just sit in rooms
and kind of like look wistfully at the room.
And like, he was just, he was,
we called him phoby-wan Kenobi eventually.
Like, and we were like that story wise,
how do we justify this for ourselves?
That's the force ghost of Ben Kenobi.
And then later learned that he doesn't,
didn't work for the hotel, was there as a guest,
but does work for the Disney parks as a photographer,
as a real guy.
And used to be a Walt Disney World ambassador.
Wow.
And this guy that we just saw as Obi-Wan Kenobi
constantly walking around, like walk,
being Obi-Wan Kenobi was one of the craziest things
I've ever seen.
Anyway, all that to say, yeah, you could get drunk.
That's it.
Hell yeah.
Did you drink, how were drinks?
I was 20 at the time.
You were 20 then?
Oh man.
Oh, wow, wow, oh, and really?
I just turned 21 this past month.
Oh wow, wow.
And you didn't arrange it to go back
so that your first legal drink could be some bubble and blue.
You have no idea how much I thought about doing that.
You have no clue.
Like I said it to like the Disney influencer people.
I was like, I want to turn 21 in the Galactic Star Cruiser.
And they were like, it's too late.
Last minute, we can't get you on the Galactic Star Cruiser.
You actually try, oh my God, wow.
I fully was like, that's how I, that's what I have to do.
I have to turn 21 in the Galactic Star Cruiser.
I feel like that's a big thing I have to be,
is 21 on the Galactic Star Cruiser.
But I was told that the drinks were stellar
and that there's like a lot of fun, really fun drinks.
And like those are also like from different planets
and they have them in fun glasses
and presentations and things like that.
So yeah, no, the drinks were given really positive reviews.
Here on earth, did you get anywhere close
to a dumb Star Wars drink as the first legal drink?
You know what?
Yeah, there's a bar not far from where I live
that has, it's like a Tiki bar.
And they have this drink that's in like a big whale
and it's like a straw in the whale's mouth.
That was my first drink.
That's great.
I'm happy to hear that.
Water pressure in the shower, how was it?
Very practical.
Yeah, it was good.
No, the showers and stuff were good.
And you do feel like you need to shower
the Star Wars off of you a little bit.
So no, the showers were positive experiences for us all.
Yeah, the bathrooms, solid for sure.
Okay, did you use a thermal blower
or what we on earth may know better as hair dryers?
I don't think any of us did, no.
Okay.
Do people talk about the thermal blowers at all?
I saw a photo and I think it comes in a little bag
and the bag is labeled thermal blower.
So if you were not- Fucking awesome, man.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I think other things are just shampoo
and conditioner, they don't go out of their way
to invent new terminology there.
But thermal blowers.
Is there any prequel behind the scenes
where George is explaining how Anakin gets his hair
a certain way, oh, there's a thermal blower
and he just puts the thermal blower up to his head.
You know what's wild actually?
One of the things they give you when you're there
is these Star Wars comic books
that take place on the house even.
Oh, wow. That allege that Han
and Leia had their honeymoon on the Halcyon.
Yes, yes. Oh, I forgot this detail.
They conceived Kylo Ren, right, on the Halcyon?
Or is it Anakin in Padme?
Is it that Luna Leia?
No, I think it was Han- I think it's Han and Leia.
Oh, okay. I think it's Han and Leia.
Yeah, it's Han and Leia. I think they conceived
Kylo on the Halcyon. Wow.
Wow. You're right.
Is there a way to know which room
and to ask for that room?
I mean, depending on the performer.
There's a weird energy at that room.
Yeah, yeah.
A bad energy.
I wonder if there's any way to tell in the comic book.
I didn't read it. I just came through and I was like,
wait, are you alleging to me
that they had their honeymoon here
on this place you made up last year?
Oh, Leia, where's the thermal blower?
I can't find the thermal blower.
My poofy 70s do is really-
I need to dry off my balls.
Yeah.
The thermal blower.
Here's a question.
At the end of the night,
you guys are back at the room, you're winding down.
Did anyone flip on that hotel room TBS or food network?
Oh yeah, you're watching Shark Tank.
Watching cable?
I don't think so.
No, I think we were all pretty committed to the bit.
We were like, we're gonna do this.
You can, they do show you,
oh, and you turn on the TV, it's like,
you can airplay to the TV.
They show you how to screen-play.
And the specific example that they give you
is it's like you see like a screen cap from episode seven
and it's like you should screen mirror Star Wars
onto the Star Wars TV.
Sure, they're trying to suggest,
watch some tales from the universe.
Yeah, it's like I don't wanna watch Star Wars
when I'm in one, like that's so not what I wanna do
is know that it's a movie right now.
It's like watching a Ken Burns documentary on some war.
You know, it's like in the universe, who cares?
It would have to be a documentary
about when the Empire struck back.
You couldn't watch the Empire Strikes Back.
That's too weird.
Yeah, Bert, like.
Wow, that's fun actually watching it as documentaries
is a really fun idea or otherwise like dramatized versions
of what really happened.
Oh look, some actors have taken it upon themselves.
Some fellow named Irwin Kirchner, I guess,
has reenacted the events that we know from.
Yeah, oh, that would be fun though.
Just in the, sort of winding it down,
I just wanna make sure we get to big moments in the story.
I guess on that last, how does it,
like where's night two, like okay, our last night,
we're going to bed, what are you left to think about?
Is it hard to sleep because the story
is weighing on you at that point?
Yeah, honestly, yeah.
He was really, we had like,
and this is skipping your question
and I won't go back to it,
but like we woke up for three days after
and Texas and our group chat like plugged me back in.
Like I can't.
I remember falling asleep on the plane
and waking up from like my nap on the plane home
and somebody was walking by to go to the bathroom
and I thought it was a stormtrooper that I had to like,
genuinely my brain was like, you have to talk to them
to get like your mission completed.
Like I was still really in it.
But yeah, the last night, this is the kind of amazing thing.
And I had, this year was my first year
watching WrestleMania after this Halcyon experience.
And I was told that I would like it
because of my reaction to the Halcyon experience
because the last thing that happens is you're at this dinner
and then the fake alarm, not the real alarm goes off
and they're like everybody onto the deck.
And that's where this big sort of fight
between the captain and the lieutenant is happening.
And this really, really incredible thing happens
where they manage to in this one big moment,
tie up every single storyline
that you could have possibly followed
over the course of your time there.
Like there were characters that we had barely ever seen
that had like endings to their stories
that still seemed meaningful enough to us.
Like they really do it all and they tie it all together
and emotionally and fulfillingly.
And I could get into all that,
but I think the big thing to note is this fight
between Kylo Ren and Rey that happens,
which is really fun to say that like,
oh, so we're just deciding that between episodes eight
and nine, Kylo Ren and Rey were in the same room
and had this like huge lightsaber fight.
But this is where the like big lightsaber
with the slap bracelet thing happens and all that stuff.
But one of the things that is not touched upon,
I feel enough in people talking about the star cruiser
is the different ways in which Kylo Ren or Rey
interchangeably will use the force
to slam the other's head into a railing.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
I did notice this in a video.
Yeah, that's a little more brutal than the typical.
It was amazing.
We were like standing there being like,
oh, they're gonna fight and then that happens.
You're like, oh my God, this is brutal.
But that was really amazing.
Every story is tied up.
There's like all these surprises that happen.
I think the big payoff has to go to the character of Sammy.
I kind of, I even don't wanna say like how and why,
but he really gets all of us.
Again, day one, we're like, wow, this silly Star Wars thing.
Like we're really excited, but come on, this is silly.
All of a sudden we're standing here in the deck,
on the deck, every single person on the ship going,
Sammy, Sammy, Sammy.
Impromptu of nothing.
Like no cast member was making us do this.
And the actor playing Sammy is taking this in so interesting.
Wow, I did it.
And like integrating it into the story
and then Lieutenant Crowley's gotta yell over it.
Like it's so amazing.
That's the other amazing thing about these big moments
with everybody is that a kid could make it go haywire
at any second.
A kid could walk up to Lieutenant Crowley
and this did happen.
During a big moment, like a kid walked up to Lieutenant Crowley
and was like, I think you're a bad guy.
And the captain was like, all right, sit down.
We're having a real discussion.
He's like, no, I won't let him talk to you like that.
Like this whole thing.
And then Lieutenant Crowley ended the scene early basically,
but said, come child, we have much work to do.
And like gave him a special little experience
in another room.
Like they have to give full respect to everybody
who wants to talk to them
because what is the point of this thing?
Otherwise they can't like ignore a kid.
So it's pretty amazing seeing these actors navigate
that so masterfully.
Yeah.
It's interesting you say wrestling compared to wrestling
because we went with a certain friend of ours,
Buzz Buzz once to a wrestling event,
but he put wrestling in probably the correct perspective.
He said, it's like we're all in a little play.
And he is right.
And it's what you're saying is, yeah.
What you're saying is we're all in a little play,
but that's the fun of it.
That's why we're doing it is that we're all playing along.
And it's more fun when we're playing along.
It is, if you like wrestling,
if you like the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Wow, wow.
And then like, I mean, cause I watched a video
of the finale or maybe like a preview they did
of the finale for vloggers or whatever.
And you could certainly see how it ends on this high note
and the emotion you're all feeling.
Like I get all that, but then how does it transition into,
okay, get your bags?
Like what is, how do you,
it seems like such a big come down.
Yeah, I think there is a moment to maybe like,
like a cruise, like I think you can put your bags out
in the hall and like tag them and they'll have them ready
for you outside the next day or something.
It is a really big come down.
It's not left to be like out of universe or anything.
Like I feel like the characters will be like,
cause again, they're running a cruise.
So like the characters will be like,
and you can like leave your bags outside
and our amazing crew members will come get them.
Like it doesn't feel out of place
for something like that to happen,
but it is for real depressing.
Like the come down after was very, very visceral.
And we still text in our group chat about it once a week
because now we keep tabs on the actors
on their social media.
So we're like send their posts and be like,
oh my God, they're dating or stuff like that.
Wow.
You've kept it going.
Did you then transition into more Disney world
or did you go home?
We transitioned into a bit more Disney world,
which I would argue wasn't a mistake.
I just wouldn't advise it.
Like you feel like you're like, I can't,
like you still feel like you're back on earth.
You know, like we had like an extra day at like,
I think Epcot and I would suggest that if you're gonna do
the Galactic Star Cruiser,
just go and do the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Don't like make, don't pair it with a longer Disney trip,
I would say, cause it really is like such a different,
yeah, it really is its own thing.
And going to Hollywood studios during it,
like you get some rides in there.
I get like, if you don't go to Disney,
I go to Disney so often.
Like if you don't go as often as one does
and this is like your big trip
and you want it to be part of it, I get it and do it.
But I would advise the ideal Star Cruiser experience
is just doing that.
And like, then it's just kind of,
you're pretty drained going back into the parks.
Like if you've done it right,
you've given your all to the stars.
So at least do it at the end maybe of a trip.
You gotta make it the finale.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
At the list you're gonna do it all.
I think that's right.
Wow.
Yeah, go to the Magic Kingdom and do some rides.
It just, it really feels like you're like,
oh, all these people who are just here for today,
they don't know, you know, like I think that's part of it.
They don't know what you've been through.
You know, you've been through something
with these hundred somewhat specific people.
It's strange to then be in like, you know.
A line.
Community, world community or whatever it's called.
Right.
Wow, wow.
So then, so what's your reaction a few weeks ago
or whenever it was that they're shutting it down?
Now I'm like afraid to ask how you felt
and how the group chat felt when this news broke.
Yeah, I mean, I got texts from multiple people
who I have not talked to in a while asking if I was okay.
One of them and one of them who I was talking to,
but like out of our Gene Stupnitsky,
our director of No Hard Feelings texted me
and was like, like, I'm so sorry.
You know, this is like, they really,
it really was like a real point of sadness.
Like I think obviously, you know,
the writing on the wall was pretty clear
like of the direction it was taking,
it was becoming emptier.
It just wasn't selling the way they'd hoped.
And like, as an artistic risk,
you know, my heart really does go out to it.
Obviously, like I'm not gonna sit here
weeping that this big corporation's big money thing
didn't play out.
But like, as this really, really incredible theatrical
thing not succeeding in the way that it had hoped,
that is always gonna be at least a little sad to me.
And I will always be very thankful that I went,
like, I don't think I'd be able to,
I don't know how, I would regret it forever
if I didn't get to do it.
Geez, that's a, well, I think some listeners,
maybe some hosts are going through this right now.
Maybe forever regret, because if we can't,
I think we're boxed out, right?
Unless Mike works some magic,
unless you like do some hacking.
If we chat about it, there's no way I couldn't do it.
Okay.
Well, I think you could do it
and I really want you to do it.
Maybe you gotta prioritize now.
We gotta talk about it.
You just got it like, and really,
this is the number one piece of advice
to everybody who's going, you just have to say yes
to the whole thing.
Like, obviously it's campy, obviously it's silly.
You have to set your kind of ego
and cynicism aside a little bit.
But like, you have to say yes to everything
and like seek out more immersion.
Because I will say like, you can't,
it's not that you can't escape the immersion,
it's that there isn't anything else.
So like on day two, this like,
my brother and I were running around
and doing all this stuff.
And this dad and his like poor younger son came up to me,
came up to me and my brother.
And they were like, the dad was like,
excuse me, do you know about any secret stuff happening?
We can't seem to find the secret stuff.
It's like, oh buddy, you had to earn the secret stuff
yesterday, my friend.
I don't know what else to tell you.
Too late.
Oh man.
Oh, what a sad tale.
I have one more question that this is,
I don't know if we're gonna find the answer.
And there's just one thing everybody's wondering
at this point, which is what happens to the building?
They made a weird spaceship hotel
that is in the backstage of the park.
I mean, you know, in theory, you could re-theme this
or do something else with it,
except that it requires an odd little bus ride
that's not right next to the park.
The rumors are that they've thought about other things to do
or make it a day trip or something,
but it's just, they're not gonna do anything.
Supposedly it's over.
Like there were, apparently they were trying to figure out
other things to do, Mandalorian overlays or something.
And then day trips to it.
And it feels like, no, it's just that building's gonna rot
until they need the land.
Yeah, I mean, us there, we were like, oh man,
in three years, God willing, this thing stays open,
which obviously it has not.
And they like make a sequel story
for people who have been before.
Because honestly, the biggest audience
for people going on the Star Cruiser
is people who have already gone on the Star Cruiser.
Like they kind of, I feel like the people
who were gonna do it did it at the beginning.
And so to do like a follow-up story and it's like,
oh, you can have the same cast, which obviously you can't
have, because a lot of them don't work there anymore.
Like it's like, it was this sort of wonderful dream,
which the Star Cruiser always was.
Like it's this wonderful, wonderful idea
that I think was executed very well.
But in the time we're living in this society,
we're living in the place that it was,
et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
It just didn't hit.
I think, sorry.
That sucks, no, that's it.
I was just gonna say, I think that the issue with it
is that nothing visually or video wise can convey
what you just did for like an hour and whatever, 45 minutes.
Yeah, I feel it after this.
It's like the video doesn't show me the experience.
You have to feel the experience,
which is very hard to convey, even when in a written review
or even seeing things, because obviously video makes things
look less cool in general,
unless it's a very high quality video.
But like, you just did a better advertisement
than any of the social media posts we've seen
for this thing in a year.
Yeah, yes.
Yeah, I mean, that was something we were really feeling too,
because like you watch those videos and you're like,
oh, I'm paying $6,000 to do this lightsaber training
where I'm holding this stick.
And it's like, no, of course not.
Like that's not the thing you're paying for.
You're paying for like what that means
to the thing as a whole.
And it is a really, really hard, difficult thing
to convey, like this is the first time
I'm even bringing up the lightsaber training,
which was really, really fun and amazing.
And like led Alex to be like,
I wanna follow this Jedi journey.
Like that's what it's about.
It's about the story as a whole,
not how cool is this very one lightsaber thing.
If they just had that as like its own thing,
it would be lame, but it's because it's part
of this whole story that you're being told
and you're part of unfolding it in real time.
And that was the thing missing.
Fractions are never gonna tell you the story.
And some piece of video is never gonna do it.
Or some weird promo video starring a Goldberg's cast member
that is yanked within 48 hours.
Oh man, that was so tough.
Because it makes the sets look less than good.
That was so tough.
That was so, so tough seeing all that stuff play out
the way that it did.
And listen, I understand.
We just did this doing,
trying to convey these immersive experiences.
You just can't because that's the very nature of it.
It's supposed to be very ephemeral
and only exists in the moment.
So it's impossible to,
I think as soon as it's figured out
how you can market something like this,
it will open the flood gates
for so many more experiences like this.
I think literally the biggest problem
with doing an immersive risk like this
is that nobody has yet figured out on the planet
how to market it.
Yeah, I remember when Sleep No More opened in New York
and all of the marketing for that was very vague.
It was like, it was building a mystery.
And hearing people who went and they tell you bits
of it's like, oh, it's kinda,
there's little Shakespeare bits and it's jazz age.
And you don't really get,
you don't get it hearing about it
as opposed to the people who saw it.
And they were like,
yeah, if you go on a really good night, it's amazing.
Yeah, and I think Sleep No More,
which this could absolutely be very easily compared to,
it just has the luxury of being sexy.
Sleep No More is amazing, but you're like,
oh, I think something about it being this sort of secret,
speak easy kind of thing, as opposed to this thing
that from the outside seems so corporate and false
as opposed to Sleep No More,
which seems very dirty and intimate.
This is not, obviously the Star Cruiser is not dirty,
but it is very intimate.
Anytime that we would kind of like wanna play,
we'd go up to one of the actors and be like,
hey, you did a great work back there when you
got the coaxium or whatever.
And they would see us trying to play,
but keeping a distance.
And they literally, I remember Justin,
the actor was playing right on our voyage,
grabbed me and leaned over and whispered in my ear like,
hey, thanks for having my back back there.
I really appreciate you and I see what you're doing.
And you mean so much to me, thank you.
And he walked away and I was like,
a tear, a single tear rolled down my face.
If you are willing to be pulled in by it,
they are so desperate to pull you in.
It's like the end of the Transformers ride
over and over and over again for a couple times
a day or a couple times in a week.
Yeah.
Mike thrives on being told by Optimus Prime
saying that he's proud of him.
Yeah, when they pull into the station at the Mummy
and they're clapping, that's what it is.
Oh my God, I did.
But it really is just for you.
But it's a human reaction.
Yeah, it's a human being saying it to you.
It's an actual connection that I had with an actual person,
even though he was Wraith Cole and I was Gorn Dreamweaver.
Right. Yes.
But it's so much more than names at that point.
Exactly. It's a feeling.
It's about living a moment. 100%.
You have taken us on a journey of optimism
and a journey of hope, one that I will not forget
anytime soon, much as you will not forget
your star cruiser journey.
And I feel like I should be respectful to the mythology
and say, Gorn Dreamweaver, you survived podcast The Ride.
I it's this has been such a pleasure, really.
Fantastic. We're proud of you.
We're proud of you.
I take it in.
It's a single tier.
For the listeners, we're watching.
I think a bunch of single tiers are streaming down.
Yeah, no.
For those of you who can't see my face, I'm really crying a lot right now.
Thank you so much for having me.
Oh my God.
I hope to never use my platform to talk about any good causes
and only talk about the galactic.
The best cause.
Well, I insist that you use it briefly to talk about your current
the cause of the day, which let me say, let's exit through the gift shop.
And is there anything that you would like to plug?
I don't know anything that anyone can go see in a movie theater right now.
Is there hearing this?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I can't remember.
Yeah. No. Hey, listen, there's this little movie
that just came out, I guess, by the time this has been released
called called No Hard Feelings.
It's very, very fun.
And I had a really great time filming it.
It's me and Jennifer Lawrence.
She's trying to sleep with me. How silly.
It's please.
It's a very, very special movie.
And I really think I really think that you're going to like it.
Please check it out.
Oh, my God.
I know so many people who are who are really rooting for it.
And that, you know, that a big, crazy R rated comedy
with a big movie star and a burgeoning movie star.
Everybody wants to do well.
And we're also excited to check it out, especially knowing that you are a
now knowing you are a theme park fan and a halcyon hero.
You'll be able to tell.
You know, it did impact my performance for sure.
Yeah. Well, you did it. Yeah, you were.
But you you came from that you've you undoubtedly you brought something
from space back to this your performance in this film.
Yeah, that's right.
That's that's exactly correct.
I did. I was like.
I now that I've been going, I can be personally
what I felt I had to be like that was my hero's journey
to be able to film that movie.
Geez, that's that's amazing.
How do you think Percy would have fared
at any choices he would have made
if you had to guess his experience?
I mean, honestly, like, it's so funny, like where we find Percy
at the beginning of the movie, like as you can tell from the trailer, sort of
the reason that he goes on the journey that he does in the movie
and why Jen's character, Maddie, is trying to seduce him is because
his parents are really concerned that he hasn't been brought out of his shell
and that he's about to go to college and he's very antisocial.
And I genuinely think instead of the whole plot of No Hard feelings,
he could have just gone to the Galactic Star Cruiser and like
shell there and then been ready to go to Princeton.
Like then then he'd be after being, you know, I feel like he'd probably.
I think, oh, God, I don't know, actually.
He might have been first order.
Like, I think he kind of needed to get something out.
I don't know. I really don't.
I bet he would have had a really good time, though.
Yeah. He would have surprised himself.
The exciting world of the Halcyon would prepare him for the wilds of North Jersey.
You know, that's it.
I mean, I honestly, yeah, 100 percent.
Like, I mean, it's true.
I in total earnest, like so much of No Hard feelings is about needing to kind of
break out of one's bubble before, you know, and grow up and kind of
evolve into a different version of themselves and the different steps that one takes to do that.
And I think in a very microcosm way,
the Star Cruiser, much as any sort of immersive experiences,
much as any theme park is, but more so is
is that opportunity to like escape yourself for a second and come back,
having like learned something about yourself in any small or large way.
And I obviously like as somebody who performs and I wasn't so surprising
that I behaved the way I did on the Star Cruiser that I like really took the reins.
But I think for somebody to go and do that for themselves and having not done it before,
I think it can be a pretty addictive experience and like something that really does
does change them. And there were people there who were on their third or second
voyages, like who would like this was something they did because this was their opportunity to do exactly that.
So I do think it's a special thing.
And as sad as it is, as it's leaving, I really hope it's not a sign that things like this can't succeed.
Yeah, yeah. You got to creatively.
You got to root for this for sure.
Disney, whatever. Yeah, they need to they need to work out their books differently.
Yeah. Hopefully the spirit of this move moves into.
Yeah. So we can one day sleep in Wolverine's bed.
We're praying for this opportunity.
Well, thank you for joining.
Please come back anytime.
This has been such a blast, Andrew and written for this movie.
Kyle Mooney's in there, too, right?
He said, did you have scenes with Kyle or is that a different thing?
I did. I did have scenes with Kyle.
Wow. Is it me? Yes.
And oh, my God, of course, I meant to bring that up.
He like told like we we were in a so we filmed together in Montauk,
which we shot most of the movie on Long Island, like just outside of Manhattan.
But we filmed for a week in Montauk and Kyle's scenes with me were in Montauk.
And we shared a van to Montauk together. Wow.
And I don't know how it came up, but it always comes up to me.
I was like, do you like rides like, you know, like, like, hey, think about it.
And he was like, I was just on with my friends on podcast, the ride.
And he talked about you guys.
Wow. Oh, no kidding. Wow.
Yeah, for real. Oh, geez.
Love connecting these these dots.
Oh, it's a movie with both of you guys.
Big theme park fan credibility in the cast of this film rooting for it so much.
You're going to like him in this movie a lot.
It's very, very silly what he does.
Oh, great. Oh, excited.
Awesome. Well, thanks for joining us.
Thanks to Carly Wisell for playing matchmaker and setting Andrew up with us.
Really glad to connect the dots here. Appreciate it, Carly.
Thanks, Brett Bohm, for producing this episode at Forever Dog.
Come hey, if you want to come see us in Las Vegas,
please join us at podcast, the rides, big Vegas Groove Blender.
Saturday, July 22nd in Las Vegas, tickets available at the space LV.com.
And for three bonus episodes every month, check out podcast, the ride,
the second gate or get one more bonus episode every month on our VIP
to your club three. All of that at Patreon.com slash podcast.
The ride has that for a plug pile.
It's a big pile.
Cool stuff. Fun stuff.
People to think things to do, but go see no art feelings as well.
And I guess try to hack the system, get to start
cruiser before you can't anymore.
And if you figure out any tips, tell Mike.
But I think Mike's probably going to figure it out before you, whoever.
Save your tips.
Yeah, who am I talking to?
This has been a Forever Dog Production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog News by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.