Club Three.
All right, let's just kick right in this time.
No discussion of whether Mike's gonna tell his story or not.
This is jam-packed, that'll come at a later time.
Unless you wanna do the 20 minutes where we talk about
if you're gonna tell the story and then don't tell the story.
But let me think about telling.
Let's think about, yeah.
Let me think about thinking about it.
And I'll think about you thinking,
but we'll talk about you thinking about it.
No, this is, we got a lot to do here.
It's Warner Brothers Studio Store,
a delightful remnant of the 90s in our childhoods.
The poll this time, the runner-up,
Dolly Parton's Dixie Stampede.
Which is, I believe, the Medieval Times-esque dinner show,
horse-related show in which, to their credit,
it's not the Dixie Stampede anymore,
but how can you not think of it as that?
And I believe that there was,
what I was, maybe we'll look at it when it's not true.
I feel like I always heard that you could choose
whether your side in the dinner show
is the Union or the Confederacy.
That was my understanding of it.
And I believe it changed a long time ago,
2017, 2018, something like a long time ago.
A long time ago.
I always was under the understanding,
and maybe this is next door, the Hatfields & McCoy show.
Oh, uh-huh.
Cause that's like an easy Jedi versus Sith.
There's no definite Jedi versus Sith.
The Capulets and the Montagues, I guess.
Well, those are two families, yeah.
Those are both two warring families.
Yeah, that's better.
Jedi-Sith is more of a faction.
I've never heard a professor,
an English professor or Shakespeare scholar go,
the Capulets, those are the good guys.
The Montagues, those were the bad guys.
It's not like Jedi versus Sith.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right, right.
And every block in, what's that town?
Where's Dollywood?
Pigeon Forge. Pigeon Forge, yeah.
It's nothing but versus dinner theaters.
Wow, that's Coke versus Pepsi.
This Coke, I'm sorry, this horse represents Coke.
Who are we fighting for?
Wow, that sounds fun.
That's RC Cola's music.
Oh, the Dark Horse.
The Dark Horse, it's a donkey, it's coming in.
Portrayed by a donkey.
Well, we're gonna figure that out,
but I, you know, why I haven't discussed this with you guys,
this kind of a question.
By the time the Club 3 is up next month,
we might be in Vegas mode.
I'm not sure we could slot it before,
we could slot it after.
I'll just say, submit any ideas you want,
but maybe let's get some Vegas ideas.
Because if we don't do it in July,
we'll definitely do it in August.
So if you got burning Vegas obscurities or passions,
now might be the time to do it.
Yeah, good tip.
If, we'll see, I mean, well, I think people,
I'm always surprised by what is in Vegas or was in Vegas.
So I imagine there's somebody out there
that has something we've never even heard of
that might shoot to the front of the pack.
I bet, try to stump us.
Yeah, I mean, there's so many,
like the crazy thing about Vegas for sure is like,
there's something that was only open for seven months,
but it cost a theme park amount of money.
Like somebody really did put money into it
and then like, nope, gone forever, burn it.
No one has a picture,
nobody thought to write down in a diary that it was there.
So if you have one of those things
you think only you know about, throw it in, please.
Did you know there was a Marmaduke experience
at Caesar's Palace from 1999 to-
20,000 square feet.
Yeah, there was 30 different dogs
that all looked like Marmaduke
that you could interact with.
To train them to act like you.
To drag you on a leash.
To drag you, yeah.
It cost, it did take a $20 million hit the casino
and they had to wait 12 whole days to make that money back.
It was a tough year for them.
Tough week and a half.
So throw Vegas ideas out, please.
But for now, let's get into this thing.
This is from Seth Finkelstein,
a second time Club 3 topic winner.
Wow, congrats.
I believe now tied with Shane Cannon of Garfield Eats fame.
I feel like we should reward-
We should have a restaurant where we join,
people can go on a Seth side or-
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, right.
Yes, Seth versus Shane, the ultimate dinner experience.
Exactly.
I'll leave it to Seth and Shane to tell us
what you like to eat and what they should serve
on your side.
The answer might just be bad chicken no matter what.
It's probably bad chicken.
But you know, give us some, you know,
we'll try to incorporate your taste into the theater.
Plastic beer stein, soup out of a pitcher.
The finest culinary delights.
Coincidentally, Seth just likes the worst,
most watered down soup that's ever been made.
So his favorite food will be represented.
So here's a quote from Seth.
With the premiere of Max, it's time to celebrate
the great brands and intellectual property
of Warner Brothers with a look
at the Warner Brothers studio store.
Indeed, I know.
And it's been a great, it's been a banner year
for this corporation for Warner Brothers Discovery.
And I'm like, it's, you know, it's actually good
to see you guys just to like process the flash.
Like, I'm just so like, I feel like soft inside
from the feeling of seeing all my Batmans again.
Oh, yeah.
Just seeing, and seeing the, you know,
the respect with which they treated these, you know,
deceased actors who suffered more than most human beings
anyway while they were alive.
It's sad, you know, you would think that puppeting
around their dead bodies, like a digital weekend
at Bernie's would be like a, like a bad thing.
But you should see how they, you should see how they do it.
What's the name of the, do you guys know the name
of the flash director?
I've been talking about him.
My new favorite director.
Andy Muschietti?
Yeah, yeah, Muschietti.
The way you would think it'd be bad, but Muschietti.
Oh, Muschietti.
He pulls it together.
Muschietti, that's how I say it.
I say it with a zest and a chef's kiss.
Yeah.
Muschietti.
He pulled it off.
I was gonna either send it to, send this to you somehow,
but I didn't want to ruin your fun.
I was gonna go like, and they probably,
all these multiverses, DC multiverses,
they probably didn't use the right charts.
There's a lot of charts.
There's truly a lot of charts for the DC comics.
Explaining multiverses, okay, okay, yeah.
Multiverses in the 70s, 80s,
and then in the 90s, they kind of reset.
Do you think this is a new chart?
Maybe they just made a new chart.
I think it's a new chart,
because they reset in 2011,
and then they reset with the multiversity storyline.
I have not seen the flash.
I've seen every spoiler possible,
because people have been tweeting everything about it.
I am upset though, it seems like Space Jam 2
paced it for the amount of cameos
from the Warner Brothers family.
Yeah, I mean, they had to focus.
Yeah, and it's true, because Space Jam,
ultimately you get more, it's a bigger Batman multiverse,
because in those basketball background shots,
you would have seven Danny DeVito penguins,
because they would just copy and repeat them
for another one in the 10th row,
put another one in the 30th row.
If you do want to see more of your favorite
Batman characters silent,
and not contributing to the story in any way, shape or form,
Space Jam 2 is still the place for you.
Still wins, and it's a grand tradition now
in the Warner Brothers family, I think.
Yeah, well, look what they're doing, right?
It does make this, that is correct.
This is, I think, a good time to talk about the brand,
and to analyze the brand, and this,
you know, the studio store, which was this way of kind of,
how do we sum up the brand and the vibe of the brand?
Because it's clearly on their minds now, again,
they're trying to convey it to us with these movies
where all of their characters meet digitally dead,
and do nothing together, you know?
And plus, you know, every two years,
when they have to relaunch their streamer again,
they also have to like summarize it,
and go like, we're the home of the doctors,
and then they have to make a poster
where it's Doctor Strange Love and Doctor Evil,
and I don't know what TV Doctor's in there,
the good doctor, or Cluny from ER, I don't know.
Yeah, Cluny, oh, spoiler, Cluny from ER isn't the Flash.
Oh, why do you think I'm so emotional?
Why do you spoil his name?
Jason, you know Cluny's name in ER?
I didn't really watch ER.
I didn't either.
Well, yeah, they open it, like, the Flash just keeps split,
he goes so fast that he opens up every line,
you see George Cluny from ER,
and also George Cluny from the 80s sitcom called ER,
that he was also on.
He opens up every George Cluny ER.
Sure, well, you can do anything if you harness the speed force,
I mean, if they get the treadmill in there,
the cosmic treadmill.
It's probably been in there, isn't it?
I haven't seen it yet.
We haven't seen it, but there is a treadmill
where Flash runs on.
And these are like the high point of Flash,
these are Grant Morrison, Mark Millar,
who would go on to do Wanted and Kick Ass and stuff,
and Mark Wade, who's like a life for comics guy.
They wrote a lot of great Flash comics in the late,
most of the 90s into the early 2000s.
That's true, but it's all trash now.
Who gives a shit about any of it now?
After an incredible weekend
of just people outpouring Flash love.
Flash is gonna do more for Black M.
And we forgive you, Ezra, Ezra, everything's cool.
If the movie had been less good, then maybe not,
but in this butt, the Flash ran so fast
that we forgot everything.
This is also a banner weekend for Max,
because CEO David Zaslav was mentioned
in a on-air wrestling promo by CM Punk.
Whoa.
How so, what was the context?
He was a favorite of the CEO, David Zaslav,
because of how much money he can bring in.
Yeah, he calls him one Bill Phil.
He's touting, he wants to be connected to Zaslav.
It's sort of a heel promo.
Depending on who you talk to, it's sort of a heel promo,
but he came back and this was part of his promo,
was talking about David Zaslav now,
because AEW is in the Warner family, the Max family,
whatever you call it.
I don't even know what to call it.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, what is it now?
It's Warner Brothers.
I know Max's the app.
Warner Brothers Discovery is the whole thing.
Max, of course, and Max is the place
where you can be watching HBO if you want.
That's the official tagline.
Not AEW.
Not yet.
Even though it's one of the rosier sides
of Warner Brothers Discovery.
Success-wise.
It's all rosy to me.
They're shaking it up at CNN,
they're having a blast over there.
Everything's going great.
They don't, you know, sure there's this writer's strike,
but a shared love for storytelling
is gonna bring us all back,
and it's gonna bring us back
to Warner Brothers Discovery first,
because that's the place where the best stories are told.
It's really saying something when you get booed
by graduating college seniors on their graduation day.
Like commencement speech is supposed
to be the most softball thing.
Yes.
And speech was the most softball thing.
Yeah.
He did his end of the softball.
Yeah, yeah.
But then why did these students throw nothing
but hard, hard pitches on fire?
They entered the speed force.
Yes.
Throwing rocks at the Sands Love's bed.
This, going through the Warner Brothers store
and all the photos and all the catalogs and everything,
it felt like exploring Rome before the fall.
The current, like going back in time
and seeing the glory of Rome,
everyone was flourishing and architecture was perfect.
And then thinking like, oh, this is what it looks like now.
It's just a shadow of what it once was.
Yeah.
This is one of the most well-preserved things
I think we've talked about, because-
Yeah, that's, yeah.
Pinterest and Flickr and YouTube, I mean YouTube-
Lots of photos.
I'm assuming maybe we all found the 1993 and 94 Christmas.
Like it's been a banner year for us.
And like everyone's having fun.
All the local employer, like Merry Christmas,
Happy Annika, Happy New Year, you know.
Everyone's having a good time.
Yes, these are like internal use holiday videos
showing how this brand is going up and up and up.
And not only that, everybody seems so excited,
the enthusiasm.
I feel like this must have been a good company to work for.
Maybe not like all the way on the ground,
maybe like all the way at the bottom, retail job, who knows?
But I feel like people in the middle,
I feel like kind of like a regional manager is psyched.
And I'll try to provide, I have further proof of that
as well, speaking of the YouTube stuff.
But, and look, the enthusiasm is on my end
for the Warner Brothers Studio Store as well.
I loved this store.
I loved it.
Do we all feel the same way about it?
100%.
We should be kicked out of this podcast
if we all didn't feel the same way about this.
Absolutely.
Yeah, thing in a mall, a thing in a mall,
like much like the Disney store
or any other weird mall oddity that, you know,
I know that we were all the kind of kid who wishes,
wished that they were at theme parks all the time
as much as possible.
But you can't be at a theme park all the time.
But much closer to you is a mall
and maybe mom has to do some boring shopping,
but that's okay because there's one place
where there are big cartoon statues and things to play with.
And I don't mean some boring, like little dopey sly
that can fit into a mall.
I mean, interactive IP based experiences
that felt made by themed entertainment crafters.
I mean, that were, like, this place was great.
It was, I'll say this, better than the Disney store.
And I don't think I ever vocalized that as a child,
but I feel it when I remember the memories of both stores.
And I loved the Disney store as a kid.
And I loved Mickey's Kitchen, of course,
which was in Woodfield Mall.
I don't wanna keep bragging about it.
You're so lucky.
But we got to try Mickey's Kitchen.
My parents would never drive me to Montclair.
All I ask is that you drive me
to go to a failing fast food restaurant.
But we have a Disney store.
It's five minutes away.
I don't care.
You do that all the time.
Show me that you love me and drive me.
Wait, actually, wait, no.
Montclair might be like an hour and a half
from where I grew up.
It would be shorter for you to have driven to Disneyland.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
But I'm bored of Disneyland.
I wanna go to a place
with only one Disney themed restaurant
that's worse than some of the ones in Disneyland.
Scott, I wanna go a step further.
And Warner Brothers Suites store,
if I saw one that was like, drop what you're doing.
We're going in there now.
And I didn't have it at the local malls,
but the nice, the big malls
and out of town weekend trips.
So we're talking King of Prussia,
which is one of the biggest shopping,
like Mall of America, for a little while,
the Syracuse Sky Center, I think it was called,
or Carousel Center, excuse me.
These were like the biggest shopping areas in the country.
So of course they had massive Warner Brothers stores.
Washington DC, Baltimore, they had Warner Brothers stores.
So this is a sign that you're somewhere elevated.
Somewhere elevated.
And I'm sure we'll get to it,
cause I have a clip and maybe we all pulled it,
but the Atlantic City Boardwalk.
Of course.
That was a primo one.
And the revelations of like,
oh, I didn't remember this from childhood.
The man, the man himself.
What's great about, yeah, I guess,
well, we're for sure getting into this,
but each store had different,
like specifically made like statues
of the Looney Tunes characters dressed in different attire,
depending on what the location was.
Yeah.
So you get totally unique,
different like outfits for the characters.
You didn't feel like you were,
hey, you know what?
Here's a bold statement.
Warner Brothers Studios stores were better than Galaxy's Edge.
And here's why.
Because you go to Galaxy's Edge in California,
then you go to Orlando, it's the exact same thing.
Been there, I don't need to,
but Warner Brothers Studios stores
different everywhere you go.
So obviously I've made the case.
I think we can all agree on this.
Ancient Rome Looney Tunes is different
from turn of the century, Seaside Resort Looney Tunes.
You know, these are all different Looney Tunes.
It's different than the beach,
chilling out LA style with a big flip phone.
Oh, LA had so many.
I just read it.
Yeah, I know.
I wish I came out here for just to go
to the Warner Brothers stores when I was a kid.
Just on a trip.
Yeah.
There was like a community open Google doc of like,
okay, I think this is the full list
that I've been able to find in Warner Brothers stores.
And I saw it missing a few.
So it's not a hundred percent accurate,
but the LA area had so many.
Woodfield Mall, one of the first.
I believe.
The second is what I saw.
Wow.
I think.
The memories, I was trying to figure out
it was there a more exciting store.
And I don't think so.
I can certainly, there's a handful of stores
I found very exciting, but I don't know.
That might've been number one.
Do you ever have like a nature company with a little,
I forget if the one at City Walk,
used and that look, that's no mere mall.
That's City Walk.
But the City Walk one had like a walkthrough
that was a little forest.
And it smelled like the ET forest in there.
And you could pick up rain sticks
and tip them over and shake them.
And I think other nature companies
may have had some little walkthrough.
That's an interesting thing.
So that's one of the only, like,
oh, I get to go in a little rainforest.
But I don't think a lot of them had it.
I also like the store, the Imaginarium,
because there was a little door for kids to use.
But once you're past the little door,
then it's a bunch of toys I can't play with
because they're in a package.
And Disney Store is great.
I like the clips they're playing.
And I like all those little dioramas
and see whatever you wanna call them.
You know, the maquettes, the statues, I'm not sure.
But there was not like,
there were not environments to explore in any of these.
So it's gotta be Warner Brothers, right?
I think it has to be.
I think the combination of environments
and then also looking back at pictures of the stores,
the catalogs and some of the items aimed at
older folks, adults, and young adults and stuff.
There's an attempt to be tasteful.
Does that make sense?
There's jewelry counters in the Warner Brothers store.
There's expensive statues and cookie jars
and coffee, home goods. Tasteful's the word
you're looking for.
I think it's trying to elevate.
Elevate it. Elevate crap.
But it worked. Let's not overlook that it worked.
I'm not saying it's bad.
I'm saying that maybe the word is unright.
That's all. This was a real time,
I feel like, where it kinda worked.
Where, you know, Tasmanian devil shirts
had a real cultural era.
This was kinda the time of the huge jacket
with the puffy sleeves.
The store had to be a lot of what caused that.
Here, there are so many, I hope this just works.
Pepe Le Pew things you can buy for your wedding
in this one catalog, where you can get champagne sippers.
You can get cake slicers with Pepe in this.
The cat he was always seducing, quote unquote.
Yeah. Champagne glasses, a wedding cake topper,
plush where they're in a bride's outfit,
a dress, and a tuxedo.
Like. Look, this is all very romantic,
assuming that she is a willing participant in this wedding.
Which we're not sure.
Assuming that the cat, we don't know the full story.
It doesn't look good at the start.
No, and we have cartoons to prove.
We have evidence.
Yeah.
So.
Maybe canonically.
They gave them a willing wedding,
and if that's the case,
then these cake cutters are really romantic.
Yeah.
How about this tasteful statue?
Here's Bugs Bunny playing the saxophone.
Tastful?
Wait, you saw that street lamp?
Street lamp.
Elevated.
Fancy.
Tastful, I think is funny.
Tastful.
That's the most tasteful bunny
you've ever seen play the saxophone.
Oh my God, is that Bugs playing a saxophone?
What a tasteful piece.
Who knows what tasteful things you'll find
in the Batman Forever tie-in catalog.
Of course I have.
I saw that.
I saw that, yeah.
Oh my God.
And we're recording on the day
when Kevin Smith is about to reveal
that he has seen the Schumacher cut of Batman Forever.
Oh.
He's gonna talk about it today.
He's recording whatever it's premiering today.
So will we hear it by the end of the day?
I'm sorry.
I know let me correct myself.
Will you hear it by the end of the day?
Yeah, I will, yeah.
And tell us about it
because I'm not going anywhere near that.
Luckily, okay.
Luckily, where this is on topic for the Warner Brothers store
because Batman and Batman Forever,
but like Akiva Goldsman also in a recent interview
was like, I've seen the Schumacher cut.
So someone in Warner Brothers is like
giving this to people to watch.
Wow.
So it exists on some levels.
I feel like we are going to get it
in one form or another.
You're gonna get the Schumacher cut.
I think so.
In our lifetimes.
Probably on Max.
We'll have to sign back up for Max.
Maybe.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
But is it too evil now?
Are they not gonna see the upside
and paying for the Schumacher cut?
I don't know if they have to.
Joel Schumacher is dead.
So they don't have to give him any money maybe.
So true.
I'm not sure.
I don't know what deal they have with everybody involved
if it's gonna cost so much money
that it won't be worth it.
I don't know.
We'll see.
You're saying Akiva Goldsmith, Ken Smith,
willing to sanction Jim Carrey's buffoonery,
but you don't know if the accounting department
at Warner Brothers is willing to sanction it.
That is what I'm saying, yeah.
Okay.
So we'll see.
I'm hopeful that we will get the full two and a half hour,
two hour 45 minute cut of Batman Forever
with all the dark stuff put back into it.
We'll see.
And with like, I don't know, maybe like Chase Meridian
and like a little negligee or something.
Like an outfit that we didn't see in the-
Yeah, but maybe like a different one.
Yeah, maybe a more sheer one.
Yes, that's what I'm thinking.
We'll inch up and a little inch down in certain directions.
Yes, and if yes, if she,
maybe just a longer like horny rooftop scene or something.
Maybe just a little bit like a couple more lines
of dialogue, suggestive dialogue or something.
She sucked his codpiece.
Of course they're not gonna-
For some reason.
Like I'm not filled, I know that in that movie,
that's for 10 year olds,
they're not gonna show actual oral sex,
but there's nothing inappropriate about showing a woman-
A codpiece?
Licking a codpiece.
Well, I mean, let's say she is a successful doctor,
so we can at least assume she has a full closet
of slips and camisoles.
Mm-hmm.
So there's any-
Plenty of time to see all of them.
Number, yeah, time to see all of them.
Yeah, well, look, there'll be plenty of time.
If this indeed gets announced for release,
we'll have to do a pre-episode and a post-episode.
Our feelings before we see it, our feelings after.
So at that point, then we can speculate
on all kinds of scenes that might appear in the new cut.
We can get a lot of content out of that.
Yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
I mean, I know Kevin already is,
but he's trying to be kind of the face of it.
But like, you know.
And then maybe Batman Forever 2 is right around the corner.
I do feel, and it actually posts to the Flash.
Well, maybe not because the Flash was not,
not everyone opened their hearts to the Flash,
but it feels like the actual contents of the Flash
lead us closer to Batman Forever 2 than ever before.
I agree, I completely agree.
Yeah, so.
Yeah, anyway.
We'll see, fingers crossed.
Okay, to step back a little bit.
Actually, you know, all right,
let me go back to this like brand issue.
This like, what is the Warner Brothers brand?
To me, it was crystal clear at this time.
And I don't know if it was just because of the store,
that was certainly part of it.
But I know they've struggled to make all of these things
fit under one confusing umbrella.
And it's even the craziest now that like, all right,
how do we explain that we are Dr. Pill Popper
and the Matrix?
How do I like, and an increasingly unpopular CNN.
How do we sum that all up?
But at the time of this, when it's a smaller corporate,
we're Time Warner, we're not AOL Time Warner yet,
it made a lot of sense to me.
It's okay, I know that it's the Looney Tunes,
those are still on TV and I like them.
They're a little more for my parents.
I know that's what my parents liked,
but I have my own Looney Tunes, the Tiny Tunes.
And I know that Batman and Superman
are in this umbrella as well.
And then there's, yeah, there's Tiny Tunes for me
and there's Animaniacs and Animaniacs especially
makes fun of all of it.
And I'll see, you'll see Plucky Duck dressed up as Batman
and you'll see an Animaniacs parody of something else
in the umbrella of like, do they only treasure
the Sierra Madre?
I think it all made sense to me.
Those all feel like disparate things,
but it's like cartoon icons and some are classic
and they'll always be beloved and some are new and hip
and sardonic and they poke fun at the old ones
and they all live together at the mall and I go see them.
Yeah, I think maybe this is what you're saying,
just everything felt very relevant to me.
Every character seemingly seemed relevant
and they had just recently added like Hannah Barbera
into the mix.
It was maybe a little bit into the run of the studio,
that might have been a mid 90s.
Yes.
Because I was gonna say like with that even
when that got added.
That was Turner, Turner.
Right.
Turner acquisition, when they combined,
that got them the Hannah Barbera and sure enough,
there is a graphic with Fred Flintstone next to Bugs Bunny.
Yeah, but those all maybe were not quite as relevant,
but they felt like, oh, they're getting an upgrade now
or something too.
Friends.
So it felt like everything in the store
was like cool at the time.
Yeah.
It didn't feel, yeah, dated.
Also with Animaniacs, I can't say enough about Tower,
at least to me as a kid in the early 90s,
loved Animaniacs and it really tied it all together,
including that suddenly you're into that water tower.
So then the water tower on the Warner Brothers lot
is something, because that's where they live
and I grew up around here.
I didn't grow up near that, but if we went by it
or we're in the area and like, oh wow, the tower.
I still think that driving by it.
You still think of the Animaniacs every time?
Yeah.
I go to the fucking tower from the Animaniacs.
Which only a couple years prior
would have not meant anything.
It's a pretty modest tower.
I mean, it's in the logo and everything.
It's cool and as you know, that's Warner Brothers
and they shot famous movies here for sure,
but yes, I drive by and I go into the Animaniacs house.
They still have the, if you're driving by it
on Olive, which from Burbank leads you into Hollywood.
There's still, there's that huge space
where there'll be big murals, usually for animated shows.
Yes.
They're doing.
So a couple of times I got to see that when I was a kid
and it's probably some big collage of all of them.
I'm like, this is a magical place.
It looks like old Hollywood, the studio itself,
but they're making things that do matter to me now.
They're making new Batman that is good,
the movies and the animated series.
It all made sense, right?
Yeah, it was a magic time.
It was a magic time.
Probably worth examining the evolution
of the Warner Brothers mural wall.
Cause I thought it was documented.
I think when I first came to LA,
I think it was more Looney Tunes, more client.
And then it's been updated so much over the years.
Well, they have to trade out different shows
that they then would pull from Max Forever
two years later after spending millions of dollars.
Judging their behavior, it just makes them furious
to have successful animated things that people like.
I was gonna let this go and then Jason brought it up again.
And now I have to say,
it's not one of these things where I have to say it.
You're talking about the wall where you drive by on Olive.
Yeah.
And for a long time it was Justice League.
Okay.
And you would see at night,
the villains would be illuminated on the bottom of it.
So it was some paint effect or whatever.
So they look spooky, like campfire lighting.
So you would see Joker and you would see whoever else,
Lex Luthor or something.
And here is my confession to you right now
that I've never shared with anybody.
There was some, for some reason,
when I first moved out here and I would drive by there,
I would feel weird and creeped out.
I got some sort of weird intrusive thought in my head
that I would get freaked out by this mural
specifically at night to the point where I would avoid it
for like six months, seven months,
because I used to work right around there.
But all your friends are on it.
I don't know how to explain this.
And this is, I haven't thought about this in years
because I know I drive by it all the time
and it's been switched so many times.
And I don't think about it at all.
But there were a few months, maybe a year,
maybe two years where I had this bizarre,
I would even describe it like when you talk about
like a fear of some big thing in a small room or something.
It was so weird.
I cannot even qualify or quantify what it is about it,
but I would almost have to like in an OCD way,
try to avoid driving past this mural
on the Warner Brothers lot.
What?
I don't know what it is.
It was like a nauseating kind of green and purple.
I think it was sort of a big thing.
It was bad guys.
It was your friend's enemy.
I think it was a size thing.
I think it comes back to when I was talking about
how I used to be very afraid of like inflatable things.
Inflatable things like at a car dealership.
And I think there was some old buried memory
that was triggered by this specific,
did you find it?
It's probably on there somewhere.
I don't think the one I'm looking at is it
cause it doesn't have villains.
It's just-
Well you won't be able to see it.
Cause-
Oh, I see, wait.
Exactly as you said that.
I found a different picture where they're all like
half opaque.
Yes.
Wow. Well it's a little scary.
I mean, I still don't understand exactly why you would-
It's not scary.
I'm telling you, I can't explain what it exactly was.
I wasn't going by it going,
oh, the Joker is going to get me.
I think that on some level it was a size thing
from when I was a kid.
And for whatever reason,
this thing one day kind of gave me an intrusive thought.
Just an aura of foreboding as they say.
As they say on the mansion.
Yeah. So I would sort of,
I would avoid that for a long time,
which is not a convenient street to avoid.
If you're trying to get into Hollywood from Burbank,
you'd have to kind of go around
or go all the way down to Lancasham or something,
or go around to Luca Lake.
You could get around, I guess,
go by the smokehouse.
Was it just the villain component
because this big billboard,
this billboard also has Tweety and Scooby Doo on it.
You're not bothered by Tweety and Scooby Doo.
I'm telling you,
I don't think it has anything to do
with the actual characters.
I'm not afraid of Scooby Doo.
Yes, but the treatment is different.
So you're not, are you afraid of the big top ones
or only the scary glowy ones at the bottom?
Well, afraid is even maybe the wrong word
because I don't look at that and I don't feel fearful,
but I do feel some sort of like weirdness in my stomach.
If it's like on something unsettling about it.
And I don't know why it's a hall of justice.
It's the Bruce Tim DC universe, which I am very fond of.
I would think you'd want to see this as much as possible.
Yeah, it's really strange.
Maybe it was too real for me.
I don't know.
I think I could drive by it right now if it was still up.
Now I forget what it is.
It's changed into, it was Thundercast Roar for a while.
Yeah, it was Philander Katz Roar.
I swear I drive by it.
I don't think twice about that anymore,
but I really cannot tell you,
I'm usually decent at analyzing myself.
I cannot tell you what it was about it.
This is funny, cause this was like my initial,
this was my entry level to LA.
Cause I in college lived at the Oakwoods for a semester,
the apartments, the furnished apartments
that it put people up at temporarily
be those college students or people out here for pilots.
And then the Ithaca satellite campus for a long time
has been in this office building at the corner.
And then people would intern at Universal or Warner Brothers.
And there's a bank and a pizza place on that strip.
So it was like, it was convenient and it was quiet.
And it wasn't super zooey except at rush hour
in the morning and the evening.
Super zooey.
It's a little zooey.
That actually, that bar and backs up,
that street backs up a lot.
Well, right now I pass by it
and there's all these fucking people everywhere,
yelling, waving signs.
Get a light.
I don't know who they are,
but I tried to drive my car into them the other day.
Okay, get out of here.
It's too zooey here.
How are these stomp drummers?
They're banging on trash cans.
It's a bunch of clamp trap.
Warner Brothers don't stomp.
They might.
The billboards need to teach us.
Well, I'm very curious what this spall means.
I am too for you.
Honestly, I am too.
But all right, so despite those fears that you had,
we got a warm feeling from the place.
A hundred percent.
Yes.
And you'd get them from the store.
I think also, okay, the fact that it is,
if you've ever been by the lot,
I think, I work on the lot,
like it's a, it does have an old Hollywood feel
more than a lot of lots have.
And I think they brought some of that
into the vibe of the store too.
Cause I really like just the marquees,
the gold on black and it's very art deco.
It feels a lot, it has a lot in common,
I feel like with that, you know,
big at that time 90s Gotham vibe,
like I think it tied that together too.
Cause Gotham is sort of perennially 40s.
Right.
Especially in the Burton or Schumacher mood.
Yeah, yeah, the stores felt to me,
there was a distinct Gotham vibe
just before you even go into the place.
Some of the ones that had giant marquees outside
like Atlantic City had very Burton, Batman,
Gotham City accents.
Yeah. I feel like.
Absolutely.
In the way that some of the Planet Hollywood
also does, you know, similar art direction and such.
Yeah. I mean, it wasn't,
I have the same fondness for them that I do
for Planet Hollywood that either it's at my local mall
or I'd go on vacations and get to see just these big,
gaudy, bright kid things, you know?
And I feel like there's been a blandening
of everything a little bit.
And it was just like exciting touches of kind of like,
places that you'd get to go.
Especially as this grew and grew
and it spread so quickly.
Mike, the Schomburg one was your, the second one,
one other great feather in the cap
of this great shopping center.
Yeah.
Anything about yours you remember specifically?
You know what's funny?
The thing I remember the most was the,
like paint a Looney Tunes screen.
Where you could just go,
that's the strongest memory I have of it is where, yeah,
you could pick Bugs Bunny or whatever,
and then it felt like future technology where you pick red
and you'd make his head red.
Like this was just like mind blowing to me.
It all was really similar to the post show
of the Hanna-Barbera, the Fantastic World
at Universal Florida.
Digital touchscreens, black and white character,
like a digital coloring book.
Wow, cool.
And then let's not go too far
without talking about something I imagine all of them had.
I hope they all had Marvin's Rocket.
Yes.
This is 80% of it right here.
Why to love it.
If you were in Marvin's Rocket, you're having a great day.
This is Marvin the Martian.
And I always liked those a lot.
But you got to like, it was a little space
only kids could fit in.
You crawl in there and there are so many buttons.
There's so many noises to make.
Just like, there's one video of it
decently preserved on YouTube.
And if you get four kids in there,
it is just the most cacophony you could possibly make.
So many things I feel like would have buttons
for kids to push that wouldn't do much.
Yeah.
So just going a little bit at the extra mile for kids
to make them feel like a button was doing something.
Yeah, really.
Felt like amazing as well.
Yeah, hey, again, I'll go back to it
better than Galaxy's Edge.
Smuggler's Run, some buttons do make a big sound,
but some of them just go like bloop, bloop.
This thing, you get an iconic mel blank sound effect
when you push it.
Is it better?
You're saying it's better.
Yeah, there's another reason why.
Better than Smuggler's Run.
Better than Smuggler's.
Yeah, maybe.
If you're in the iconic rocket of Marvin the Martian,
just like the Millennium Falcon.
Yeah.
But you're even getting more like,
the Falcon, I've seen it, you know?
I've seen it in a movie.
I don't really know what it's like in Marvin's Rocket.
Right.
And it's less frustrating in Marvin's Rocket.
Yes.
You get rewards no matter what you do.
Right.
You really know, you might not know what Coaxium is,
but you knew Marvin the Martian
because of cartoons and syndication
and t-shirts with the giant,
the biggest screen printed image you've ever seen.
Yeah.
Yes.
He is huge on shirts.
He's huge.
At school and at theme park.
I see Marvin more than I see some family members.
Weird little guy in the cartoons,
huge on the Peggy t-shirts.
My dad, I was asking him,
I was like, what do you remember at Warner Brothers stories?
Like, were we trying to track down
Marvin the Martian figurine for you?
And I'm like, look,
between my outings to Warner Brothers Studio Stores,
you going out of town on business
and inevitably finding a Warner Brothers store
when you like went to a mall
and Six Flags Great Adventure,
I think I assembled a full Duck Dodgers.
I think I got Daffy and Porky and Marvin and the dog.
Like it's like, I think we assembled that.
And I full disclosure,
I love the Warner Brothers Studio Store.
I think total over the years,
I spent maybe $15 on little PVC figurines.
I don't think I ever bought anything large there.
Yeah, I don't think, yeah, I was trying to recall,
do I have memories of anything I bought?
I think I would just go and run around,
which maybe was part of the downfall.
Yeah, it was a playground and you don't buy anything
or your parents don't want to.
I think my parents didn't want to.
I think I wanted big stuff,
but I think maybe I got like a toy or a shirt
and that was it.
And the shirts I think were more expensive
than shirts everywhere else.
That's my memory, which could have meant they were $25.
Yes, at that time.
Yeah, yeah.
And like $10, $5 is what shirts for little boys were.
Well, and now like Looney Tunes shirts
or Warner Brothers Store stuff at resale websites,
like Etsy and Depop or Jane finds it at like vintage store.
It's incredibly expensive, this stuff now.
Sure, yeah.
Can I ask who, was Marvin your guy?
Was Marvin your guy from Looney Tunes?
Well, I think Marvin and Taz.
So you equally would split that they were your favorites?
I think them and Buster Bunny to some extent.
Okay, you're adding, you keep adding to this.
I keep adding because there's so many friends.
Okay, all right.
So you have three, it's a three-way tie.
I think Marvin and Taz were the big ones.
Take Buster out, take Looney Tunes out of the universe.
Yeah, that's a different universe.
Yeah, okay, fair enough.
And of the core Looney Tunes, who was your guy?
You know what, I'm gonna make you choose.
Huh?
I'm gonna make you choose.
Oh, wow.
Taz or Marvin.
Who do you like better?
That's pretty good.
Yeah, yeah, I never tried that.
I think it's gotta be Taz.
I was in the 90s.
Oh, my God.
Taz, okay.
Good choice, good choice.
I bought the adult version of the kids Taz shirt I had
thanks to listeners finding it on eBay.
Oh, wow.
Scott, who's your guy?
Daffy.
Okay.
Yeah, clever sardonic.
Daffy's sure for me.
Who doesn't get mad?
Who's yours?
Wiley Coyote.
Oh, cool.
I haven't talked about them yet.
Mm-hmm.
Any particular rationale?
I really don't know why.
I'm not sure.
Again, there's a lot of things I'm saying today
that I don't really have a good explanation for.
I had a plush of him on my bed.
I think I liked it when he would talk.
I liked the ones where he would talk.
I think I found him.
Those are funny.
Yeah.
I thought it was funny that he was smart,
but then he'd get shit kicked out of him.
Did you relate it to a character
with a lot of anxieties and dealing with grief?
Like, oh, good grief.
Did Wiley have a lot of anxiety?
I mean, he was always trying.
None of his solutions would work.
It's one way to put it.
He was trying to get Roadrunner,
and it would never work.
I mean, it would never work,
but they would show it, I guess,
as he went on in the cartoon,
but he didn't seem, it didn't read to me.
I could see you being like,
okay, so there's this company called Acme, right?
And they have all these gadgets,
and they're actually really reasonably priced,
and I get the alerts for when the items go on sale.
And yeah, often they don't work,
but that's a little like over, you know,
if you read a lot online,
if you read comments,
you see that like sometimes the traps do work.
Quite often, and it's like the ones where they fail
are the only ones that get attention.
So.
The best day of my life
when one of those big crates arrives,
and I gotta use a crew bar to pry the top open.
I have a whole display in my house now,
just for the Acme stuff.
I collect all of the Acme stuff.
Yeah, I have a lot of eating crate Acme stuff.
It actually makes more sense for me
to subscribe to Acme Plus,
because I get the shipping for free, you know,
because if you just buy five guns a month,
and like, and a couple of ropes, you can mix and match,
but like it actually ends up being a pretty good deal.
Good point.
So I become Wile E. Coyote in a lot of ways,
is what you're saying.
I said, yeah, I see it.
I think that's right.
I'm like a tall guy, like he is,
compared to somebody else.
Oh, you are, yeah.
I look like him.
Is your hair, the top of your hair looks maybe like.
Like the ears.
Sure. Yeah.
You got headphones on right now.
Yeah.
Okay.
Looks like Coyote ears.
Every now and then to keep you on your toes,
Scott and I will paint a tunnel on a wall.
I'll run right into it.
See if you can run right into it.
I think we're all like our favorite characters.
Sure.
Jason out of control.
Just out of control.
Wild man.
Oh, I said to Jane when I was leaving,
like girl, Taz, girlfriend, Marvin the Martian boyfriend.
Like that's our dynamic.
Wait, say it again.
Yeah, say it again.
Girl, Taz, boyfriend, and Marvin the Martian,
or no, girl, Taz, girlfriend,
Marvin the Martian boyfriend.
That's our.
You're Marvin dating girl, Taz?
I'm a weird little guy.
She's girl, Taz.
Yeah, she's girl, Taz.
So she's girl, Taz.
Yeah.
I like that you're crossing Looney Tunes world
in the dating.
That's fascinating to me.
You know what?
It takes all kinds of opposites to track to you know.
Is that the first time you've ever like given
like characters, cartoon characters,
like you've ascribed them to yourselves?
I don't know.
I can't remember.
Now she's gonna make fun of me
because she's like you're forgetting
when we choked about this thing.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Well, I mean, she compared you to Quasimodo before.
So don't forget that one.
You know.
Quasi energy.
Usually flattering way.
Yeah.
The BZE of Quasimodo.
I remember very well.
Sure I was.
You know, here while we're in this area, personal stories,
this one's not me.
This is my mother
because my mom was over this morning, babysitting.
And I said, I am learning
about the Warner Brothers Studio store right now.
Do you have any memories of that?
And I said, I'm sorry.
She said, yeah, yeah.
And I was like, that was an odd tone.
Is that something you don't wanna talk about?
No, no, no.
It's just, I don't think I've talked about this before.
Said, oh, well do tell.
You have to tell me now.
And she said, I only have one real association
with that place.
And it's that one time your father
got me something from there, like an article of clothing.
And at the time I wasn't feeling great
about my appearance or my weight.
And I was just in a weird state anyway.
And then he got me this thing
and the thing didn't make me feel good.
It just didn't play well into where I was at at that moment.
And you might see it and think,
oh, what is he talking about?
I'm like, what do you mean?
This is crazy.
There's an article of clothing
that drove right into your insecurities at that moment.
And she, you gotta tell me more details of this.
And she's like, it was just like a,
it was a big sleep shirt or something, right?
And it was one size fits all.
So I probably didn't like that.
Like I'm just wearing a big bag or something.
Like I'm dying to see this shirt.
Is there any way?
And she said, well, there wouldn't be a picture of it
because I didn't wanna be photographed in it
because it made me look terrible and made me feel bad.
Whoa, okay.
First question, can I tell all of this on the podcast?
She said, oh, it's behind the paywall.
Your father's never gonna go there.
So that's fine.
So I do have my mom's permission
and she's in a better state about all this now.
But my sister also over watching my son.
So she said, maybe she wouldn't,
my sister has a photographic memory
and this was described to her.
My sister, without missing a beat, was like,
you wore that when we went to Newport Beach in 99 or whatever.
And I think it's in a photo album.
What do you, you remember this being in a photo album?
Well, maybe we could find the shirt.
This is great.
Do you remember what was on it or what it was?
And she said, the brown guy, Taz?
Okay, well, I could see that.
So now I'm going, okay, my dad got my mom
a big dowdy item with the Tasmanian devil on it.
But then I'm just like, I'm scratching my head.
Like, what could it have said?
She said that it said something too.
Like, what could the Tasmanian devil have said
that made her feel bad?
I was flashing to like, me so hungry.
Like, what would the devil say?
Me hungry all the time.
Yeah, because Taz likes to eat.
I think he like eats everything in sight, right?
It's your guy, Jay.
Am I missing other qualities that would not,
I don't think that your, girl Taz maybe,
I'm glad Jaynes is associated with girl Taz,
but I could see why my mom does not wanna be
the Tasmanian devil.
I mean, Taz, I feel like very similar to Stitch.
You can ascribe so anything to him.
Mischief and mayhem.
Mischief, mayhem, yeah.
Things chaotic when I'm around.
He's also like, he's not slovenly,
but he suggests being slovenly.
Yeah, sure.
You know what I mean?
So if it was a picture of Taz sticking his tongue out
and it said, I'm a mess.
Yes.
Yeah.
Or me crazy.
Me out of me mind.
It could be like, don't talk to me before me cough.
I know, I was wondering about that.
So I started digging and there was a version of that
with Tweety and she said, no, Tweety would be fine.
I'd say he's cute.
I found one with Taz and it was Taz eating
a big sub sandwich like Carl Winslow would have eaten.
And she said, no, I think that's kind of cute.
I don't mind that.
She said, maybe it was a little like Western themed.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm thrown now.
And we can't decide if it's a nightgown or a big sleep shirt
and I'm dying to know.
So I am now waiting and she's like,
you're recording the podcast at three?
Okay, and there's just enough time
or maybe I get an update about what was this awful shirt
that my dad gave.
Wow.
What could this have been?
And then thankfully with an hour to go,
she finds a photo, but the photo is a little too hard to see.
But so she says, all right, I found a photo
but it's too unclear to read anything
except cowboys all caps and sleep.
Just can't remember.
Looks like characters include Pepe Le Pew.
Okay, I don't know.
Go to sleep so I can fulfill my cowboy fantasies
coming out of Pepe Le Pew's mouth.
I don't know.
Pepe Le Pew's through the whole thing.
I didn't know what to think.
But cowboys and sleep, that's enough.
And sure enough, I found it.
I found it on eBay, the item, here it is.
It is a giant beige shirt that says
even cowboys need their sleep.
And it is a-
Why did you buy that for?
I don't know.
My dad, oh, well, first of all, sail rack.
That's first reason why.
First reason why is sail rack.
But then it's bugs and not Pepe but Sylvester
and an especially grouchy Tasmanian devil.
So he is on it and they are all in like,
I mean, honestly, what it looks like they're wearing
is Civil War uniforms.
Like it looks like they're waking up on the battlefield.
And honestly, and I hope that's not what it is
because I think one's in blue and one's in gray.
Oh my God.
I don't remember which is which.
One wore blue, one wore gray.
Gray is the south, is it not?
Well, that's Taz.
Oh, well then that's where you don't wanna be.
Jesus.
Do you believe in tradition?
Oh my God, that's a big story you've broken here
in the middle of this other story.
America built on slavery.
Oh no.
Must be kept up at all costs.
I feel-
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
There's a lot of cowboy stories that are post Civil War
and people like trying to start new lives or disappear.
Maybe they just all still had the uniforms.
But they're all making like grouchy faces.
It is definitely a very male shirt.
And yet seemingly, I feel like meant for females.
It is, you think?
Yeah, well, at least-
Why do you think even cowboys needs?
Were men wearing big giant sleep shirts?
I mean, it's very, you know what?
We keep mentioning this on the show, barren stained bears.
This is, this is ma, this is mama bear type.
I can see what it did to my mom.
This does not make you feel feminine.
I hear whatever she wanted to feel.
Yeah, certain way.
And that's on it.
But like, if it was, it was for specifically a female,
like even, are they cowboys even though they're dressed
like Civil War characters?
It says even cow, one is boots, bugs as boots,
even cowboys need their sleep.
First of all, of course, what do you mean?
I would think that, I would think cowboys more
than anyone would sleep.
You're on a horse all day, physical, heads on a swivel.
I have never doubted for once in my life that cowboys sleep.
Sleep under the stars when it gets dark
and then you arise as the sun gets up.
I actually really do picture them sleeping.
You could picture, you could picture cowboys
about to go to sleep so easily.
I mean, this is confusing because I feel like the marketing
in the 90s was like, dad doesn't get enough sleep.
So the dad stuff is about sleep.
And the mom stuff, at least for Warner Brothers
was like Tweety Bird.
And then when they got the MGM, whatever it is,
pre 1960 movies with one of the acquisitions,
it's like half the stores Wizard of Oz now.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
But this, I think what really did it for her was that
if she wasn't liking it as she was looking at the time,
seeing a shirt that had two, both sides of the tag,
fits all, all caps, fits all.
It says several times.
And then the worst fact that I learned was
that this was a present for Valentine's Day.
Oh, that's the whole, that ruined it forever.
Cause if it was just always the funny thing I picked,
oh, now it's completely clear.
I'm glad you saved that for the end
because now it makes the mystery.
No, she was upset no matter what.
I mean, there's no holiday where it's good,
but Valentine's Day, the only box you need to check is cute.
And apparently my dad said, I thought it was cute.
He gets it a little bit, but he defended it and said,
I thought it was cute.
And apparently his full answer was, I'm sorry,
but I don't see you as just a sex object.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's twisted as a statement.
Yeah, trying to take control of this narrative.
I guess I think you're pretty even in a cowboy related
burlap sack.
Maybe that's just me.
Maybe I'm just progressive.
Can I ask, was she anything approaching a Looney Tunes
fanatic?
No.
Looney Tunes not.
That's the only way I could have been like, oh,
she likes all kinds of Looney Tunes stuff.
That's the only way I could see reaching.
Beige shirt, the characters in dark burlappy clothes
themselves, cowboys, the biggest word on the.
The shirt doesn't make sense.
There's so many strikes against it.
This is confusing.
It's a character she doesn't particularly
care for looking the least attractive possible.
They all look like they're on their way to smile in a photo,
but being caught in a weird state with their tongues out.
Right.
Here you go, honey.
I guess just a little something.
Hey.
I hope it's a real special Valentine's Day for you.
While you were talking, I didn't know if you had found it.
So I was looking through this catalog.
And there's so many denim shirts with the Looney Tunes
characters on them.
Now that I feel like she again, I
was showing her a number of other things.
And she's like, oh, I like that.
I like she liked almost everything else.
I would say she was an elementary school teacher
denim shirt with a cartoon character on it.
OK, so bread and butter.
Right.
That would have should have worn that every day.
Yeah.
But the sack to sleep.
Did you see these right here?
I can't see what's on them from here.
I'll walk over there.
I wonder if Jay has any.
Jay probably just sticks with the regular denim.
Silly.
Yeah, like this on their top.
Gets in the way of the denim.
Top right.
OK, it's Wiley Coyote.
What is it?
Just well, there's a Taz one.
Just call me a party animal.
Daffy, I am.
Yes, I am totally out of control.
And these are like stitched embroidered like lines
on a like a Jay Leno denim shirt.
OK, yeah.
Wow.
Again, Jason said tasteful.
And that's what this is.
This is a tasteful shirt on the top right there.
I you know what?
Like CM Punk says, tell me when I'm telling lies.
Because a lot of these openings, the big stores,
they did a fashion show.
They would do a fashion show with like those denim shirts
and like the varsity jackets with the Warner Brothers emblem
on the back.
You're right in one regard.
But the only like OK, they did they did a fashion show,
I would underline is the true.
But the questionable part is they did a fashion show.
They would they are trying to sell this shit.
They'll do a show of any.
They probably had an entire they got all the most beautiful women
in the world to come wear that Cowboys Need Their Sleep shirt.
This is going to be the hot thing.
You're going to override Victoria's Secret this year.
Well, they also put those very attractive men and women
like in the most like this is the most current shirt.
Like this is the most modern shirt we have.
This is the like patchwork.
Coats is that this is the newest technology.
This is the newest type of denim shirt men are wearing.
I definitely saw a fashion show in London where, yes, that
is going on in very attractive people.
And then Tweetie comes out just like pointing fingers
maniacally.
Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba.
Full of piss and vinegar.
Tweetie.
Mick Jagger in the first song of a Rolling Stones show.
Be great if that Tweetie actor just did a line right before.
Yeah, yeah.
Need my Tweetie energy.
Stop me up.
There was a five minute video on YouTube.
And I do wish I knew the origin of it.
It is Bugs Bunny greeting people at one of the stores.
And the very start, they pan to the video wall.
And it's playing a New Order music video.
And that scores that the New Order song scores the footage.
And it has production company slates at the beginning and end.
So I'm like, where did this go?
Where did this Bugs Bunny New Order video go?
Bugs Bunny and the Tucks and Tails.
That's cool.
Yeah.
That sounds good.
They used a lot of big songs and some of the internal stuff,
I'm assuming, because Warner Brothers Records probably
had those songs.
Probably Warner owned.
There was definitely a big stretch just showing,
here's some of the features of the Connecticut location.
And then the music is Cream by Prince.
And they use when he sings boogie, but they don't use cream.
It's not the most explicit song in the world.
But you kind of guess what he's talking about when
he talks about cream.
Yeah, of course.
They don't play that.
So they did take that part out.
But knowing where Prince was at at the time with Warner Brothers,
his feelings about Warner Brothers at the time
where he changed his name to not be beholden to the contract.
It was like, OK, sure, well, we get it.
But have you seen how well Cream goes with this Connecticut mall
montage?
You might want to change that name back when you see this one,
Prince-O.
Do they censor the chorus?
Or do they just don't play it at all?
Just instrumentally.
I think they changed it to dream or something.
Dream.
I don't think they use the moaning at the beginning of the song either.
Snoring.
They change it to snoring.
Oh, yeah.
Cream becomes dream.
And it's a song about having a nice nap.
Tasteful, close.
Jason likes Prince.
Now I like it.
You know my famous anti-Prince tie-race.
That's right.
Jason, I found a very classy, tasteful Marvin the Martian polo
shirt on the bottom right here.
Would you be interested in wearing this even to this day?
Let me see.
OK, here it is.
You see it?
It's over here.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, the collar is a little, some of those.
You're not usually a polo.
They're a little Proud Boy-y.
For sure it is.
It's a very preppy kind of shirt, but it's got Marvin the Martian logo on it.
I have a few polos.
I haven't worn them that much.
I feel like I haven't seen you in a polo shirt in years, if ever.
Not in a long time.
I have one with crabs on it I like to wear sometimes.
Crabs all over?
Little crabs, yeah.
OK.
It's a Uniqlo.
Audience, let's get this crab shirt out.
Let's get the crab shirt going.
So I, OK, maybe let's talk about some of these other location,
like some of the bigger, you know, I feel like all the,
like the base style was always good, but then they would elevate
in the big spaces like crazy.
New York City, incredible.
These were so massive.
In New York it was on 5th and 57th, which I believe is now Louis Vuitton.
It is nothing but the entire intersection is like,
and was at the time, the most crazy elevated brands.
And I found this quote even, like OK, I loathed the Coke store,
the Disney store said Roxanne Bednar, a New Yorker who was headed for tea
at the plaza dressed in a fashionable cream colored suit.
They're destroying the most elegant corner of New York.
This is not Hollywood or Florida.
This is Fifth Avenue.
Wow.
I look, if you like cream colored, I have a very tasteful shirt
about how cowboys need their sleep.
Yeah.
I think you'd look great in Roxanne.
Wow, so snooty.
Yeah, I know.
What is the, and she did not get her wish in terms of this going away right away
because the store did close and then reopened to go from three stories to nine stories.
It was a massive location in like the highest end shopping New York.
Then that's still there.
Then they do Times Square also.
Right.
One Times Square specifically.
The address is one Times Square.
They were in one Times Square.
Wow.
They were number one.
That is the location I believe where there was a glass elevator you could see from the outside
so that you could see Superman lifting the elevator into the air.
So cool.
And then to go elsewhere, let's maybe head into,
you can't go too long without talking about Atlantic City.
So you must have been to this one a number of times.
This one, yeah, it is again massive marquee.
You could see it from the boardwalk.
Kind of important location wise because when we started, Atlantic City had its Vegas theme
parky years and so Caesar's Palace, of course, one of the most themed casinos.
Of course, the restaurant on the boardwalk at the end of Caesar's Palace was Planet Hollywood.
When you made a right and you went barely half a block, there was the Warner Brothers store.
So this is kind of what I knew of Atlantic City for a long time.
That is insane.
It is such massive statues.
They look like they're three stories tall.
Yeah, I think they are.
I think that's exactly right.
Bugs and Daffy in Tux's, the carrot alone is so huge.
And, you know, we're in Atlantic City, so you might sense a ghost already.
Do you have the clip?
I have the clip.
Yeah, yeah, he probably knows what this is going on.
We've talked about this on the show before.
I'm sure we have.
Yeah, I mean, the full segment is like 230, but I'm just going to play the start of it.
It touches on something we did an episode on before.
That's right.
Yeah.
You simply can't miss the Warner Brothers studio store on the boardwalk in Atlantic City.
Besides sporting three story high versions of Bugs and Daffy on its portals,
the store is located adjacent to the famed Trump Plaza Hotel.
This is where the action is, and that action translates into 30 million visitors a year.
I think it's one of the most beautiful stores I've ever seen.
Donald Trump, chairman of the Trump Organization and a host of the opening ceremonies,
thinks that Warner Brothers Studio stores will fit right in.
This store is going to play a very big part in the success of Trump Plaza.
So we're really happy with it.
It's going to be a tremendous success.
There you have it.
OK, you got beautiful store.
You got tremendous success.
He thinks it's one of the most beautiful stores he's ever seen.
He doesn't dole out compliments like that very often.
I've never seen him use language like that.
No, no.
I'm impressed.
Language, wow.
He looks relatively normal.
Well, no, I mean relative to him now.
Yeah, relative is doing a lot of heavy lifting.
Relative to him now and relative to humanity.
Well, it is to whiplash, you know, because the last I hear is him like,
I think it's going to be a beautiful thing and it's going to be.
And the last I heard him talk before that clip just now was I did.
I did nothing wrong.
He is boy.
What has happened to this man's voice?
How it started, how it started, how it's going.
Put those two together.
I really wish he had commented on something specific to one of the characters.
Like he was holding up a daffy mug or something and talking about the craftsmanship or something.
At the very end of the clip, you can't hear what the sound is,
but he's holding up the jacket.
He's holding up like the letterman jacket.
Very tasteful, incredibly tasteful.
Is your screen cracked on your iPad?
Oh yeah, I got to go to the Apple store.
What happened?
I don't know.
It's like a airline crack.
It happened a few weeks ago and it's just, yeah.
It just appeared.
You didn't drop something, Aaron?
No, I don't have any memory of dropping it.
It just appeared.
That language seems like a little bit wiggle room.
I have no recollection of how it appeared.
Okay.
I did lean it up against this chair in the garage, this garage one night,
and didn't flip the cover.
So I'm wondering if it just slid under the ground.
I'm going to get a new screen on it soon.
Can you get that?
Can you just get a quick new screen?
You can get a replacement.
It's a little bit of money, but at the Apple store,
I think they'll take it and give it back to you in a couple of days with a new screen.
Interesting.
Jason's blazed out of his mind.
He's like, you know what I've been thinking about?
That crab shirt.
I'm putting it on.
I think it's cool.
I think it's good.
And you're for some reason struggling to get it over your head.
And somehow he's putting it on.
Yeah.
Fling the iPad across the room.
Oh boy.
This is now, this is something I don't want to remember.
Time to smoke some more.
I think Jason was eating a heavy East Coast meat in his bed, his research fort.
On his bed and the heavy meat fell and cracked the iPad screen.
Pimento loaf, but the whole loaf, not the slices.
The whole loaf.
It's so heavy.
And you dropped it.
How much they pack in there?
Yeah.
No, thick enough to crack a screen.
All right.
We'll keep it posted.
Hey, I've never cracked an Apple device before.
I actually haven't either.
This was the first one.
I had never seen that.
I just wanted to know what happened.
It's good.
Four years I've had this.
So it's like a little crack.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you for noticing.
Look, there felt like there might've been a story there.
I don't know.
There was.
We just had to remember it for him.
He has no recollection of a possible story existing is what I maintain.
I'm pretty sure I leaned it up this chair.
It's like this one night when we were recording and it might've slid off.
That's still pretty, like they usually hold up to like something like that.
That's true.
Interesting.
Well, if the mic goes off there.
So I've been thinking, I think I know what happened.
I'm going to crack this case.
This is really what we're going to start digging through some ACME.
If you would just give me your exit, if you would give me your Apple login,
I think I can access the iPad's camera.
Oh, that's definitely going to go.
Your Apple ID and login.
You definitely want to be giving that out to pass or by.
Is it?
I will pass or by now.
Well, I never.
He was.
It's hey, it's great footage and you get to see his fucking piece of shit kids
hanging out with Batman and Catwoman and some.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, you know, doing what any of us would have dreamed of doing.
I guess I guess only piece of shit kids got to do it.
It's really a bummer.
Yeah.
We weren't shitty enough guys.
Neither were I.
Now look, my dad gave some shitty gifts, but it doesn't put them in the league of
Donald Trump.
Unfortunately, it was that was that shirt was the like Trump stakes of shirts.
It was a poor investment.
Right, right.
So yeah.
The Ivanka and the kids and maybe Donald, I believe, are also in the footage from
the New York opening.
Yeah, yeah.
This was his second time.
There was even it didn't end up being the location.
I think that that shopping district one was really near Trump Tower, but not in
Trump Tower.
But I did find find concept art where it could have been in Trump.
So they were vying to be in Trump Tower.
OK, he was very interested in being associated with this brand.
The other guy.
And only the best for him.
I saw.
I mean, we may have all seen the Sylvester Stallone, like, and they're like who he's
they ask him, who's my favorite Looney Tunes?
Let me ponder that.
Oh, Thuffer and Thoth.
Sylvester like me, my name.
I'm really just now got that.
That's why.
Yeah, that's all I need to say.
Your name is Sylvester.
He's doing a horrible impression.
Like I'm not putting these pieces together.
But he's he's had an opening.
Of course, got to play an Hollywood Jacket on.
But the guy that I saw in multiple openings was Steven Seagal.
Oh, yeah.
It was Seagal.
And I didn't there was no audio to clip because he just put his hand together and bowed a
lot like ribbon cuttings.
He wasn't saying anything, seemingly.
Is like under siege at Warner Brothers movie.
I wonder, was he in the family at this point?
Like that.
Yeah, because it's a weird guy to send to the Warner Brothers store.
Like Christine Brinkley, Tia Carrere.
Steven Seagal, like, you know, it's all the 90s stars.
OK, yeah.
No, they got him out for this.
Definitely.
This was this seemed to be a real like brand lynchpin.
You could buy like a Steven Seagal mug from under siege at the Warner Brothers store of
his head.
You'd like a lot of coffee and my big fat head.
Yeah, you could buy his like clothes, his outfit from under siege or his,
I don't know, his geese from his training kimonos.
Right.
From his dojo.
Seagal dojo.
That's a way to bring his stuff back, you know, give us more specialized merch like that.
I know.
Yeah, well, I don't think they were activating every part of the brand and everything that
they own.
Right.
I do have a memory, though, of not really investigating much further than this, but
like going to the corner of the Warner Brothers store and seeing like the Humphrey Bogart
standee and the James Dean standee and it was like, wow, the movies, the golden age
of Hollywood.
He did represent them.
Yeah.
Under siege Warner Brothers, they were trying to reboot it two years ago.
There's an article on deadline.
Without Seagal.
I think I haven't read the article, but I'm assuming it's without Seagal.
If they don't want him around anymore.
For some reason.
Yeah.
Well, they do.
They do.
There's no word yet if Seagal will reprise his role as Casey Ryback, the ex-Navy Seal
turned cook, who was the only person in that movie to stop a group of terrorists from taking
control of a U.S. battleship.
Of course, Casey Ryback.
Casey Ryback.
All of our tongues.
How can you do it without Casey?
Yeah, true.
1992 was the first under siege.
So this is prime.
It's right before, but it's prime.
And under siege two probably was 94 then.
They're going to get it.
So it'll be about, you know, Colin Ryback.
It's about his kid.
And then there's like, you know, a flashback or they like Mufasa cloud him basically.
And it's it's that's a CGI puppeted deep fake of Seagal who nod, who like does the
little bow to him from heaven.
You're like, wow, it's cool that they got Seagal in there.
Wait, he didn't die.
No, but Ryback did.
Actually, yeah, Ryback died.
The next time he faced a bunch of terrorists, they cut all his limbs off
and threw him in the ocean.
Yeah, he was available, but they insisted on doing siege.
They insisted on giving a couple visual effects guys, nervous breakdowns to have that CGI.
They were just like, oh, we cannot deal with Seagal on set.
Like just just ruin a couple of people's lives for the worst.
See you've ever seen under siege to dark territory.
Nineteen ninety five.
So that's right there.
So that's why he's doing the rounds.
Because sometimes if his toilet situation isn't agreeing with it, he took a shit.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, charged.
Dark territory.
Hey, Jay, thanks for having me.
Just heads up before you go to the bathroom.
It might be some dark territory.
Your bathroom was under siege.
Steve is all bowed towards me after he told me he destroyed my bathroom.
Under siege with both one and two.
So the stars are coming out.
They're attracted all the at least New York's best and brightest.
And then the other really major one in my mind, the the forum shops at Caesar's in Las Vegas,
because that as here as we're heading into into Vegas, I mean,
the Caesar's aesthetic is incredible that Caesar's mall aesthetic is nuts with the cloud ceiling,
the perpetual cloud ceiling and all the brands had to elevate that.
Like that is the most like insane, gaudy.
That's that's honestly that the forum shops are like the ultimate stretch of the Trump aesthetic.
Yeah, beyond it's all columns and grandeur and arbitrary gold.
And I mean, there that's that's really that's that's Trump's dream.
I feel like that's like a like not not classy opulence.
Yeah, that's this this weird brand of like, I'm not sure where I wonder where that aesthetic
came from for certain people to think it was like the height of class is like the gaudiest
gold shit possible.
Like the pictures of Trump's apartment or whatever condo in Manhattan is just you're
like, this is the ugliest thing I've ever seen.
The gold toilet like, yeah, this sucks.
Well, the room with the boxes has isn't there a chandelier in the box?
I think so.
Yeah, there's little touches of fancy, but then just like,
there's some touch I'm not coming up with.
But like, yeah, it is just like really basic ass sink or something.
Or it's like, all right, I would know if you put a chandelier, they're not going to care.
They'll be looking up.
Yeah, that feels like, yeah, like they're like, he's like, I want everything in here
gold. They're like, well, it's going to be very expensive.
All right, we'll just throw up a chandelier and it'll take care of it.
Like, while you're taking a shit, you're going to look, there's a chandelier in here.
And you are going to pay the chandelier guy, right?
Of course it's going to be a tremendous payment.
A beautiful check.
My checks are medical too.
And he's going to get everyone chandeliers for everyone.
He said as he went into the chandelier store and then didn't pay for anyone's chandelier.
Never seen this coming.
I was in a shared, either a shared ride or like a shuttle bus or something in Vegas once.
And a bunch of people on the bus, it was like a group of people and they had, you know,
everyone was talking with the driver and he said, they said they were from North Carolina.
We can see the Trump thing in the distance.
And one of them just went like with the most specific, I don't know the North Carolina twang
super well, just hearing them say like, wow, look at that thing.
What a piece of shit.
That's the gaudiest shit I've ever seen.
All right.
We have more.
So much in common from around the country here in Sin City.
Having a good time.
Looking at the dumb fucking gold cigarette lighter building.
Carolina's turning blue.
But this, this version of the store, insane, like huge crazy marquee.
In this one, they're, they're all in gladiator uniforms.
So huge helmets, huge shields.
Everybody's going to battle.
This it's, Aaron recalled that it's right in the front.
It's one of the, it was one of the first locations in the mall.
So it's in a corner.
So it's also like exploding into the main casino.
So there's photos of just slot machines and Elmer foot in a gladiator uniform.
So much to add to the chaos of the aesthetics around there.
And then they point out in that holiday video that usually when you leave the stores,
it says that's all folks.
But in this one, it says that is Phinney T as focus.
They fake Greek it.
Wow.
Did you ever go to this?
I don't recall.
I definitely, I was in that.
I must've been in that show.
It was still there.
I don't recall.
I noted that it is in the background of an iconic scene, which is a scene in show girls
where it is Elizabeth Berkeley and Gina Gershon.
And it is there like they were kind of enemies, but now they're getting along over a fancy lunch
and they're bonding over how they used to eat doggy chow.
It is in the background of the famous doggy chow scene.
Check that out on YouTube.
Are you show girls?
I am a big show girls fan.
Yeah.
I don't know it as well as you do, but I've seen show girls and I'm a big, yeah.
There's like, it's iconic.
There's so many iconic scenes from it.
We just talked ourselves into an episode.
Maybe it counts.
I don't know.
I mean, the like something in there, it's on my mind with Vegas coming up because it's
a really wonderfully captures 94, 95 Vegas, especially with a scene in that shopping center.
And you know what it really is is that the perpetual blue cloud ceiling
mixed with all the gold and everything, it is so like vapor wave.
Like it looks like a CD-ROM in there always still now.
That's what I love.
Wow.
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know you're saying.
Yeah.
I think a lot of other places duplicate.
I mean, plan Hollywood, the miracle mile shops, they have, I think that sees their own now,
but they have the blue sky ceiling with the clouds and really has it or whatever.
What is it called now?
Planet Hollywood, whatever store connects to that.
Yeah.
Indoor clouds.
They were all in her class.
Never really caught on in the theme park world.
I think there's one like Mickey meet and greet where it's like Mickey's barn.
Maybe it's in Florida and it's like a farm in the daytime.
They have a little of the blue scale ceiling clouds.
Because ultimately it's depressing, I would say.
It's a bit of a bummer.
Yeah.
But it's like almost it's a pull off.
I don't know if you can even call it well in there, but it's pulled off insanely.
I mixed with golden columns.
Have you done a full Vegas tour of the scenes of showgirls?
No, that's a good idea.
I mean, I've been to the pepper mill, the really red diner that they filmed one scene there where
she freaks out with the fries.
I don't really know where they filmed.
I don't know what the main casino is or what the showroom is.
That's worth looking into.
That's a good idea.
And I haven't been to the pool.
You've not been to the pool?
I haven't.
I haven't splashed around backwards.
The iconic pool, yeah.
Yeah, I'd love to.
That's a good idea though.
Maybe while we're there.
Okay.
Oh, and one more.
I didn't know about this one before.
This was in a mall in Buffalo and maybe this is a nod to Niagara Falls.
Much like Schomburg, there is a waterfall in the mall.
I think they took the pre-existing water feature in this mall.
Yeah, right.
Massive.
And they hijacked it.
They put Bugs and Daffy in barrels going off of the waterfall.
Then a boat down below with a bunch of the characters in rain slickers.
That must be...
You go do that in Niagara Falls.
Cover yourself and go get near the falls.
And Wile E. Coyote with just an umbrella.
That's great.
That's his only protection against the anvil.
And then Taz and some sort of insane flying device.
I don't know what he's up to.
These are so elaborate.
This is the most elaborate one maybe of all of them.
It might be the biggest one, weirdly.
I didn't know about it.
I was looking on eBay for any of these things to see if they existed.
And I could find only a couple like...
I found this on Mercari, which is eBay.
This is just a regular Marvin the Martian that looks like a WB store.
Looks like it was WB store.
But I couldn't find any specific location ones that had an outfit on.
Oh, okay.
One of the like...
Yeah, yeah.
Clearly you only made for that store.
Well, when these closed, I think that the Warner Brothers put out the message,
destroy the statues as quickly as you can because we don't want them falling into the wrong hand.
We don't want a brand with some fly by night thing taking our characters and using them.
Of course.
So first of all, first things first, there were like 130 of these at one point.
That means there must have been a bunch of bonfires across the world,
burning bugs and Daffy and Marvin the Martian alive.
That's what's cool.
Yeah, it is awesome.
But that's why there's so many you would think a couple made it out, but I guess not.
Well, there's one.
Well, you guys found it?
What do you got?
The ones that kind of more became historic artifacts.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay. Well, this is what...
All right, here.
Wait, maybe I'll use...
Mine will cheer us up after that one.
All right.
Yes, you do this one.
Impressing one.
Yep.
Okay.
There was a Warner Brothers store in the mall in the basement of the World Trade Center.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
This is what it looked like after people were able to get in there.
There was a number of pretty unscathed statues and stuff that just have a little dust on them.
And these, I believe, were preserved.
There was a hanger showing stuff that was taken out of the World Trade Center.
Here's a subway sign.
The most haunting thing is the sign that says,
that's all folk.
The S did not survive.
I mean, that's insane.
Scott, what are the cheeriest thing I've ever seen to get us out of this section of the podcast?
Well, first of all, look on the bright side.
Foghorn Leghorn survived 9-11.
I'm pleased to know that that happened.
Foghorn Leghorn dressed in a...
I say I made it.
In a pinstripe suit, Bugs is talking on a...
Bugs is like an electric...
Oh, no, he's got a cell phone and a trench.
He's a New Yorker on the go.
I say, soon the whole world is going to hear you.
And the people who did this to us are going to hear you too.
You know, you forget that it was George Bush and Foghorn.
Yeah, they shared they went back and forth on the microphone.
Well, he didn't need...
Foghorn didn't need the megaphone because he's so loud.
Yeah, he is a Foghorn himself.
The events, I believe the people doing recovery of everything underneath...
Jason's trying to take us back into it.
We're trying to leave.
I was just trying to contextualize it.
They offered to Warner Brothers, like,
we found a bunch of stuff from your store and they're like, you can...
We don't need...
You can keep it.
This was on day one.
This was important to get to Warner Brothers.
This is...
Well...
As they're all going under, it's just like...
That is an insane thing.
The stores are disappearing.
One of the New York ones closes and then the worst possible thing.
I'm getting a layoff.
Can this day get any worse?
Oh, yeah.
All right, Scott, hit us.
Let's do it.
Get us out of here.
The other one is that the Atlantic City ones, the Trump Plaza ones, the giant ones,
for some reason showed up at a place called Sanford's Grubbin Pub in Casper, Wyoming.
Why?
I missed this.
Why are they there?
They're still there.
You can look this up on Street View.
They're so big.
One of them's just...
Oh, wait, I thought one was standing on a rock.
I was like, I was at balancing.
No, that's just on the ground.
But these are massive and there's a...
Unbelievable.
Whatever's going on with this place is there's big NASCAR's out
outside and like a big statue of a gas attendant.
So Sanford's Grubbin Pub has it going on,
seemingly, maybe some original IP and the logo, like a big weird character lounging
around shirtless drinking a beer.
Wyoming is so far for those to go.
I thought you were going to say it went up and down the coast or something.
They were still there when they did the implosion and the implosion caused them to fly away
into the sea and some deep sea divers found them one day.
You know what?
I think it's clear what happened.
It's the same thing as the documents at Mar-a-Lago.
He took the statues.
Trump took the statues and then sold them to this place.
Well, he was on the campaign trail in Wyoming.
Why else would it be there?
Oh, yeah, still got all the Warner Brothers stuff.
I got them all.
You know, I have the brown guy.
I got the big chicken.
I got every one of them.
They're beautiful.
They're tasteful.
I'll give them to you.
Cash upfront.
You could have nuclear secrets.
Which one do you want, Sanford?
That's exactly what happened.
I got to say I love your grub, but I love your pub even more.
I don't drink, but I love the vibe of the pub.
In terms of the boardwalk.
Hey, you know what?
Grub for everyone.
I'll pay on me.
Trump was found later to not have paid for any grub.
In terms of the boardwalk, that would eventually become the area with the boardwalk side
Rainforest Cafe.
Oh, yeah.
That has had so many lot like I believe still open eventually got a permit to like have their own
you know, utilities because their utilities were hooked up to the one Trump Tower building.
Oh, they wanted to keep operating.
Yeah, they wanted to keep operating.
So they got their own.
They got permission to keep operating.
They got permission for the utilities and stuff.
I believe attached to a portion of the hotel that has not been imploded.
Mm hmm.
And hopefully it wasn't just the Trump just like ripped out the all the outlets.
He for sure ripped out all the outlets.
Get the copper.
Yeah, I'm taking the copper.
Man.
So I was looking in the wrong spot.
I should not have been looking on these retail site eBay or anything because that's probably
not where you're going to find this is going to be a black market situation.
Like so you buy a statue from a Warner Brothers.
Well, I was just I was just doing Google Street View all across America until life.
I've been up every day.
I haven't slept for months.
Just maybe if I find and then write, I was about to give up.
I said in North Dakota, I'm giving up right in Wyoming.
Found a couple doing Geo Guest Sir just for the Warner Brothers store cast off statues.
There were many like journey limited statues you could buy in the stores that you can get
that are pretty expensive, you know, but those are just statues.
Those aren't animation cells, too.
That was the crazy high end nature of this that you could buy.
It was kind of maybe some of the beginning of the interest in that on a wide scale,
that this bit of mall in the middle of the country would have real Chuck Jones.
Right.
Work who is around.
They would have him come do events.
So you got the real artists in there sometimes.
You know, I think at various points in time, this place was a important hub.
If you're for particular fandoms, the fact that you could meet Chuck Jones at the opening.
Yeah.
If you really like Warner Brothers, you could actually get a cell.
I think that they they ebbed and flowed in terms of their relevance or how well they
were selling.
But I think right before they closed, I think I think Harry Potter fans ended up kind of
bummed out that these closed because good Harry Potter merch and I think like the cast
members would go to the more prominent ones at times.
And then, of course, it becomes the hub of the Batman.
I feel like this is do you recall?
Did you get like Batman stuff at these?
I don't.
I really think I got very little here because I believe the words this is store is expensive
was was set.
I remember this being a case of like this is a little expensive.
So you would get like a little tiny like plastic.
It wasn't even a good figurine.
It was not a figure, you know, not a figure.
Yeah, not not an articulated action figure.
Four inch figurine.
Wonderful thing about figures.
Yeah.
So they were, yeah, like they weren't articulated.
It was just a little statue, essentially.
That was like, I think I got a couple of those.
Yeah.
You know what I'm talking about distinction here?
They may not action figure.
Not like you don't play with the arms.
You couldn't move the legs.
It was just kind of this little like plastic piece that was the character, but it didn't
have articulation is the word in toy business.
Right.
Where you can't move its head or whatever.
You know, you still see them at Disney parks, but they don't really sell as much in a bin
anymore.
They sell you a box.
They have a picture somewhere.
Yeah.
Most of the characters from Mulan and you have to buy the set and it's 30 bucks.
It's like they were in this.
I'm going to move again.
It's like they were all in these little like tray.
That tray is like little bins, essentially.
Okay.
I'll let you remember the.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
Yeah.
I see what you're saying.
All the characters would be in there.
And you pick one out.
Not bad.
So I think we got like those and again, maybe a shirt, but I do remember because I was too.
I was not allowed to see the first two Batman movies in the theater.
I was told obviously Batman.
Yeah, me same.
Yeah, yeah.
89.
I'm four years old.
So, okay, probably not.
But then returns comes on.
I remember my mom, she doesn't remember any of this saw return Batman returns with her
friend to see if I could see it.
And they ruled no.
They said no.
They may have been right.
It's a disturbing.
It's a very, it's a horny movie.
It's disturbing.
It's I was, yeah, 92.
I'm eight years old, so I probably would have been freaked out in the theater, but I loved
Batman.
And anytime you would see Batman in the mall, you get very excited.
So I would just be, it was cool to be near Batman in the Warner Brothers store.
I remember.
And then finally going to see Batman forever.
Ninety five was my first, which maybe this explains my thing with Batman forever.
In some ways, my first Batman experience.
You were pent up and ready to explode.
I was here to shoot all over the.
Batman joy.
Yes, not with anything, not with cream.
With Danny Devito, black blood like.
Yeah, it says read a bleed all over Batman in celebration with my black blood.
I had a lot of toys for Batman returns.
Yes, McDonald's toys.
Toys, toys.
Yeah, let me have all the toys, but didn't see the wow.
We're all the same.
Yeah.
And the toys make it look so much more fun.
The penguins.
I had some of the penguins, like the penguin with a jet pack and the penguin with a rocket launcher.
The actual penguin, not the character.
My mom brought one of those here because my son saw a penguin that he liked in an aquarium
and gave it a hug and like, doesn't he have a penguin?
He took the rocket pack off, but so now it's just a generic penguin.
Well, some of it, because like penguin is in a, they say toy, you know,
toy addict, it's a very toy addict giant duck like vehicle in that movie.
Oh yeah.
The big yellow duck.
So they had, I had the toy, I think of him in the like duck too.
You're like, oh man, I want to see this, but it's scary.
And it was so emotional for me was when the flesh entered the speed force
and he ripped open the fabric of time, thus creating a line of every single bat mobile
and vehicle with a price tag on top of it and a QR code that you can scan in the theater.
So you could just buy them right then and there.
Did you see the flesh?
Yeah.
Okay.
It's why I've been so, yeah.
I just wanted to make sure.
Cora, what do you mean?
Did I see, I felt it.
No, you sound like you saw it.
I just wanted to double check.
No, I'm sorry.
Did I not just describe the best part of it?
Yeah, yeah, you did.
It is so, it's so funny.
It's such a weird movie in theaters, but like reading the monthly flash comics has like
puberty.
Jesus wants to talk about the flash comics.
And it's hitting me like-
At 9-11.
I don't really like being 12 or 13.
Super school's kind of hard.
I don't have a girlfriend as far as the eye can see, but maybe my friend bought the
flash comic this month and I could borrow it to read.
You know what?
I got no lady taz yet.
As far as I know, I don't have a girlfriend, which sounded like the answer about the iPad.
As far as I know, I did not.
As far as I know.
Sorry, I am made of a streak.
I definitely did not have a girlfriend.
That's definitive.
Definitively.
You know what's funny about flash?
Now I'm thinking about it.
I was reading flash a little bit when I was like 10 or 11.
It felt like an adult comic.
And maybe you guys ever have this happen where you would whine about going to get something?
Because I remember going, we need to go get the flash.
And then your mom would be very mad at you, but do it.
And then you'd have this weird feeling of like, oh shit.
Like we're on our way to get the comic and I'm going to win, but mom is so mad at me.
And now it like leaves a cloud over you the rest of the night.
Do you remember this?
Honestly, you're describing that I'm hearing this as a parent and I'm realizing this is a very good
weapon to me.
It is.
In a way that I like attitude and tension.
Yes.
To make him feel bad for not shutting up.
I think I'm going to use this on the other side is what I'm going to do.
No, break the cycle.
I think it's the only way to learn.
Your child will end up becoming a podcast or even worse.
No.
Now you've really scared them the other way.
A truth teller.
I remember it going well for me.
I remember doing it with the dragon's order and going to Toys R Us at like 8 45
and getting the dragon's order and it was fine.
But this flash you did, you're talking about flash comics so much.
I remember we went to go get flash like at 9 PM or something.
And I remember she was just mad at me.
And I remember like feeling so bad, like reading it and like having an unpleasant time doing it.
Because I felt like I had made her so upset.
I think I'm on her side.
I think that's what she had to do.
Well, obviously you need to shut up about the flash.
It left me because I saw flash on the side of the building.
It's a memory from when I was a kid.
Now my association, if we're playing psychologist here, my association with the flash is that
it means that I made my mother upset, which is the worst thing you can have as a kid.
Wow.
And this is why you need to go and heal.
To see this new flash.
Andy Machetti's flash.
Yes, Mushi-ed-y.
Mushi-ed-y.
Sorry, Mushi-ed-y.
Wait, that might be wrong.
I forget already.
I don't know.
It might have been.
Who knows?
Maybe there's a part of it where the flash enters the speed force and reverses that
and makes your mom happy in that moment.
Oh, gosh.
Your awareness, you a kid.
This is how much the movies are AI'd now to just appeal to.
Please put my own flash memories in the movie for me.
That is not far away.
Yeah, that's the future.
That is.
Yeah.
Sure.
All my toys scuffed in the exact places.
This is what Zaslav is going to do for us.
My Ernie.
As soon as we get those pesky writers out of the way, movies can be what we need them to be.
Yep, that's true.
Who's the director?
Oh, the Russos.
Yeah, the Russos are dreaming of this future where every movie stars you and a famous actress
who you want to kiss.
Or a character like Chase Meridian.
I think you're going to end up all for all of all four Zaslav, Russo, Muschietti future.
Yeah.
Because it's finally your chance to.
Finally.
Finally, we get the cool dystopian parts of Fahrenheit 451.
No individual can stop a dystopia entirely themselves.
So why not?
If it's going to be one, let's enjoy the cool parts.
Yeah.
There's no, if you look in that little insert, the Batman forever insert catalog,
there are no Chase Meridian anything.
It's all Batman and Robin and Two-Face and the Riddler and the Batmobile and
the Shafour shirts are those characters as well.
Marketing is already they're working on.
There was a line of exclusive Wizard of Oz action figures to the Warner Brothers tour.
Or also at some point I saw them like in the marketing department, the product management
department.
Yeah.
One of them was holding like clearly a Maltese Falcon and I'm like, oh man, it is amazing.
I was not a weird little kid going like, can we buy the Maltese Falcon for the house?
It won't be our downfall.
Surely by obsessions.
Buy a Maltese Falcon.
I'm surprised you didn't have a Maltese Falcon as a kid.
Mom, mom, we have like no McGuffins in the house at all.
You should own.
I'm going to buy you a Maltese Falcon.
It's a good idea.
It's a good.
Oh, thank you.
And just give it to him purely.
Don't make him feel bad about it.
Don't you start whining so that he gives it to you and makes you feel guilty about it.
Oh, my trick used to be like, oh, you're going to the mall.
You're going to Sears to return.
So I'll come with you.
I'll swing by the comic store.
Well, we can't say no.
I can't politely say no.
I was like, oh, you're driving right by there.
I'll just run in real quick and do my 25 minutes looping around the comic store.
Really sly.
Yeah.
So to tie into the Batman thing a little bit, clearly the like need for these places to
become the Schumacher Batman headquarters was very strong.
And now we go into a rabbit hole that somehow I did long ago before this episode was even
a twinkle in Finkelstein's eye.
I weirdly a couple of years ago found a set of videos on the same YouTube chip, probably
because it's on the same YouTube channel as the holiday videos that say how good the stores
are doing elsewhere on that.
There are multiple, I believe, four entire editions of the Warner Brothers Studio Store
internal awards where they award like general managers and like just, you know, like whatever.
All right.
And representing the West region.
And that sounds incredibly mundane.
And it is for a lot of it.
But the thing that makes it special, I think, is that they dress these things up to the
nines.
These are happening on the lot in Burbank and they are happening with stars.
These are produced award shows shot multicam.
Like the quality is not incredible, but it's also not bad.
They they they preserve these things and like made it a tape that you could get if I think
if you worked at the stores.
Oh, and by the way, what these awards, what are they called?
You ask why they're called the bugs.
It's the bugs.
Yeah, that's right.
I did have a line in my notes.
I was just like, yes, about the bugs.
The award.
Like, are they good enough for their own?
And I was like, what are the bugs?
No, we're not doing the bugs.
I can say my thoughts about the bugs.
The awards in 10 minutes.
I didn't.
I saw them right before we came.
This is crazy talk out there.
OK, I went.
You are right, though.
There is there is a ton there.
I'll try to do it quickly.
The biggest thing about it, you can tell that these just makes you it makes you feel like
these stores mattered to the Warner Company because one year Bob Daly co CEO is there.
They send different stars of Warner properties to go to these things.
Perhaps the biggest.
Well, I mean, I'll say this one because it happens twice.
Joel Schumacher is sent to these things on two occasions.
I can't tell exactly.
One is definitely right before Batman and Robin is coming out.
And the other one might have been while they were filming.
I'm not sure because here's how open book this guy.
He has nothing prepared.
He's just extemporaneously talking and being really casual about how everything's going.
And you know, and it's and you guys are important to it.
You know, we're just one end of this thing and you guys need to get it out there.
And we love the work that you're doing.
And hey, is anybody if anybody a fan of the circus circus fans because we're doing this
big circus sequence tomorrow.
If you want to come over to stage 16, we're shooting it.
If you all want to come, he invites all of these Warburg Studios stores managers to the set.
Wow.
I didn't see this.
Is there a circus part of Batman and Robin?
Well, no, circuses in three is in forever because of the graces.
OK, Batman Forever is ninety five.
I think it's too late.
I think this would have been.
Well, what's a circus?
Well, there's the there's the poison ivy ball that she has in Batman and Robin
where like Bane is in the gorilla suit and then Batman and Robin swing.
Yeah, but that's a whole big like on the Warner Brothers lot.
Big set constructed on the biggest stage.
They have the one with the logo on is right next to where we did Conan and credit like
massive, massive stage.
So he like they're like these Warner Brothers, these store people, they might work in
Schomburg or Connecticut or whatever.
But they're part of that's crazy for this day.
And like and not only that, Schumacher comes twice.
Chris O'Donnell, Chris O'Donnell is there once and they are screaming their heads off.
They're losing their minds.
The Chris O'Donnell is there.
Wow.
What year did it say it was that those awards?
There's so many.
There's multiple ones.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, of them are on.
But I feel like it's I feel like what's posted is ninety five to ninety.
It is on a specific YouTube channel.
Dan wait.
Thanks, Dan, for posting this stuff because Warner Brothers stores open in ninety four.
No earlier one ninety one.
Sorry.
Yeah, yeah.
Stores open in eighty seven.
OK.
It's all rise and fall kind of YouTube video.
And it was pointing out like Disney store opens in ninety seven.
At some point, the chain Paramount video morphed into Suncoast movies,
which was everywhere.
Right.
So if the ninety five awards, that's the would have been out.
Yeah, it would have been out already.
I don't know.
He calls a circus sequence.
I'm not sure.
Maybe it was cut.
Maybe this was it.
Maybe this was this could only be seen in the Schumacher cut of Batman and Robin.
Oh, my gosh.
First, we can't.
There's no way there's Schumacher, Batman and Robin without Schumacher, Batman forever.
Oh, no, I would love to know what if he was given free rein.
To me, Batman and Robin feels plenty Schumacher as it is.
I don't think there was a different vision for Batman and Robin.
No, I think he got I think he completely got his way there.
They got all the Burton out of it.
Yeah, there's not one drop of Burton left in Batman and Robin.
The one it's so great when he he talks for so long to them in the second one, especially
he presents the awards he has to go like and he has to say jargon.
He talks about like, you know, in this in the Atlantic City location
has been great with their white TV's and he's like, I don't know what that means.
What's white TV?
I don't know.
And just go on.
Just blab it like, you know, I just came from vacation, so I'm just wearing this.
Should is the only shirt that I have so that you're just going to have to deal with this.
I don't know where I am.
Do we have a clip?
I think we have a good.
Do you want to see the trailer?
OK, I wasn't sure because I don't know if they maybe they showed the trailer to you
already.
Let's watch the trailer.
Let's do the trailer.
OK, well, we're going to need and he talks about some of the stuff that you're alluding
to my that there were no chase meridian.
He says, like, we noticed with the first one young girls really liked it.
So that's why we're happy we had Batgirl.
And so we got a lot of great Batgirl stuff coming for you.
Robin, if he's talking about this.
That's a yes.
But the first one, I swear he invites everyone who works at the company who's there to come
see a circus scene.
Could it be mislabeled?
Maybe it's mislabeled.
I don't think so.
I mean, I think this guy knows his shit.
I think this is an insider.
I'll send you the clip.
You're going to solve this.
We need to solve the case of the correct case.
You got a lot to solve after this.
He's he's it's great seeing him before Batman and Robin comes out because he doesn't know
what's coming.
He doesn't know that it's not going to go over so great.
So he's going he loves he's going on and on.
He says when we got Mr.
Freeze, of course, Arnold, what can you say?
I think the suit I think Mr.
Freeze is suit is the greatest suit ever constructed for any film ever.
I guess now that I've said that, I was going to say the suit is awesome.
It's a specific area suits to Batman.
Robin is great, but it's great in a specific way.
But you can't not say but of course you can't end the sentence with great.
I've maintained that if you keep the same cast and the same outfits and sets and the
script is just different that we it's a whole different ballgame torn because what makes
it bad?
A lot of it is the puns.
Yes.
If the puns weren't there, that's part of it.
Then what then what when what do you have?
You'd have to have a new take on it.
But I maintain that if you wrote it more like the sick, they thought they were making
like a 60s Batman.
That's actually funny.
This is actually growing worthy funny.
It also has things where like there's like henchmen on ice and then they slip around
and it goes like really bad.
That's cartoon sound.
There's a little of it in Batman forever.
Yeah, but I maintain that people still don't know that the 60s Batman was funny on purpose.
And I do believe that it was an elevated that it was like a get smart that it was like a
I think it was like part of a wave of.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, played straight.
I think Joel didn't know that.
Like everybody didn't know that.
No, it's like it's what they saw they were doing.
It's Dutch angles and colors, aka funny.
Yeah.
And then the jokes, the joke is that it's cheesy.
Yeah, because that's what if you think people think about 60s Batman is the joke is that
it's cheesy, but that is not the joke.
No, no.
It is written by comedy writers.
Yeah, the the part of the conflict is that like the market, the McDonald's tie ins,
the action for like all of that is just like, oh, there's a new Batman.
It's a dramatic Batman.
It's he's solving crimes.
You know, he's fighting bad guys.
You know, you get there and you don't know that it's suddenly become like it's like it's
like a big 60s.
It's like, yeah, good.
Do it's like it's the biggest fair knows what's good to do is it's like a bit of giant
all star gaudy silly.
Yeah, like it's there's no way to truly prepare for what you're getting with Batman and Robin.
He also seems like he Joel was much more like, all right, you want me to do more stuff for the
kids?
Fine.
Whatever you'd like, like, God bless.
OK, it's going to be like like lighter and there's going to be a lot more characters
for toys.
Great.
The corporate mandate, he's completely on board to do it.
He's like, I'm a hired gun.
I think it's evidenced by that.
He is here talking to the store people twice.
Yeah, 15, 20 minute stretches.
He doesn't want to leave.
They have to drag him out of that.
He would stay there all day.
He loves it.
And the final thing he says also, and hey, what more what more need I say?
George Clooney and black rubber.
I remember him pushing in general.
That was part of the I don't I don't know.
I think you do need to say more.
Yeah, that's weird.
Also, I think you also need to disclose that the black rubber includes nipples and realistic
body.
Realistic near like almost like scrotum shape.
That's what the rubber is.
One thing I don't think anyone was prepared for what was going to be on those bodies.
The buttocks.
Yes.
Yeah, it's insane when there's smash cut when they smash into the crotches.
Yeah, I'll get them back.
Girl gets them too.
Yeah, we got a smash soon.
Yes, in a way, though.
I mean, wouldn't you love if I know they're Hey, spoilers characters are coming back,
but they're never going to bring back the vibe.
That's what's gone forever.
The vibe is that's yeah.
And it's the same with the store vibe.
It's gone.
The vibe is gone.
Never to be recaptured.
Yeah, I didn't know when it was closing.
The closure resulted in 3800 people getting laid off.
Which even with like mergers, that was 4% of the company's 90,000 member workforce.
Like that's not nothing.
Of all of Warner Brothers?
Yeah.
My God.
I think it was and it was something like half of those employees are part time,
which means the other half are full time.
And so I guess if you factor in marketing and product,
like all the behind the scenes, like office people,
but even so that's like 3800.
And I think one of the mergers,
after I forget, I think it was the Turner merger.
This was like the second round of layoffs that year.
Like they were already condensing the company.
Well, this was this is them transitioning from their old brand to the new brand.
The old brand is cartoons and superheroes.
The new brand is constant layoffs.
So they were thinking to the future,
the Warner Brothers of the 2000s is going to be a little different.
Mainly there will not be health benefits for anybody.
But they are also simultaneously, I believe right now,
doing 100 years of Warner Brothers.
And I mean, we're all so excited to celebrate.
Is very odd.
They have read the room and the room has said,
we want to celebrate with you.
Congrats.
Happy 100 Warner.
Thanks for everything you've done for us.
And thanks for getting rid of those pesky shows that we don't.
They were just in the way.
They're in the way.
We don't want to take any more.
Yeah, we were worried about the server.
We know how precarious the server is.
What would the devious algae rhythm always trying to make his way on there?
You need is you need to clear off the clutter.
There's too many Space Coast Coast to Coast episodes.
And they didn't even make it to half an hour.
I was I've been like, like Max is I've been honestly dying to sign up for Max,
but I was just really waiting for like, what's that last hook going to be?
And ultimately, when I heard a total lack of Space Coast Coast to Coast,
I was like in I signed up for I signed up straight to 10 years.
Yeah, I love what a hook.
I fucking hate Space Coast.
I'm so glad he won't be there.
Yeah, they got me.
They got you.
If you want to see these employees in happier times before it all fell apart,
watch the the Bugsy Awards where you can see full sketches that they made in the store.
Music videos, a foot like a multi song version of Grease that is fleece because of fleece sweaters.
There is a big parody of Madonna's Vogue called Fold.
That one is that's at the Woodfield Mall.
There's a music video filmed by employees at your mall.
There's all the like I've heard that the Gremlins are a part of this in general.
They've got certain stores that Gremlins crawling up in the walls.
It's so they do like Letterman top 10 lists.
There's a whole Willy Wonka parody called the Acme Man can.
They do the entire thing called Shoppers Paradise where some general manager is in a Coolio wig.
This is what a treasure trove of retail mundanity.
There's so there's I've look I've participated in something like this.
I've explained on the show before making videos for internal use only for retail, a retail store.
But that container store.
Yeah, yeah, I've talked about this.
I made a video for the and we showed it to the owner of the store when he was in town.
I mentioned this for him to see.
I don't remember it.
Next time I said this, I think you've mentioned.
Yeah, so my friends and I would make videos in high school and we decided to make a video
because we all worked at Container Store.
We made a video for to talk about the new sale for the shelving we were having during the winter
and we made a very weird video at the store at like 4 a.m. and we edited it and we everyone in
the store thought it was the greatest thing they'd ever seen.
So we were getting like, oh my God, this is so funny.
This is great.
Let's show it to one of the owners when he's here in a couple of weeks
working at the store because he would he would come around.
And I remember I was not even working that day.
I came to the store so I could sit and watch him watch this video.
We made it.
Went into the stock room and we put it in.
It's very like unassuming.
Texas guy.
Well, nice to meet you.
Showed him this video in which Luke, my friend, Luke playing an employee gets choked out by a rabid
customer.
He didn't crack a smile the entire time.
Oh.
And said, well, that's very nice.
It's very interesting.
And then he got up and he left.
And we were devastated.
I don't know what we know.
We Asian.
We were humiliated in this one guy.
This guy, Frank, Frank, Soraru was like an old Vietnam vet who worked at the store
who was behind him watching the video stifling his laughter because he thought it was the
funniest thing he'd ever seen, but he didn't want to laugh in front of the guy who owns a company.
So he was like, that is the funniest fucking thing I've ever seen.
He told us later.
We're like, that's great.
But we didn't, the guy didn't like it.
The guy who owns a company solely like counting down the time where he can just jump to like
home goods or bed bath and be like, he was just trying to trade up.
Yeah.
Well, no.
So like, so it was shock.
We were shocked.
But, but anyway, my point was going to be just that I, there's so many more internal
videos out there like that of like all the employees put on a show or they do this thing
or I would like some of it's online and like, there's so much of that.
There's like a whole podcast in that probably just in general.
That's true.
Yeah. I know.
I know I saw a good cheesecake factory one.
I know.
I think it was, I think it was a parody of fancy Iggy Zellies fancy with a bunch of like,
you know, like whatever they call the buzzers, like the cheesy factory internal use terminology.
We there's of course that captain Eeyore Disney thing.
Oh yeah.
Land employees made the Narts videos we were talking about with Rachel Bloom.
Yeah.
Those were very polished.
So internal.
It's great.
Store video.
If you made a video at your store, we want to see it.
It's a Jay Mike's video of them like dancing to Robin's dancing on my own.
Didn't take off where they're singing.
I'm in the corner stocking the shelving.
You think that's what the video was?
That's what Mike's video was.
When did that song come out?
Yeah.
Timeline wise.
Wait, is Mike at the container store?
A few years.
In 20 minutes.
A couple years in.
A few years in.
I know it's a little before they think.
Yeah.
Do you have a video?
I have a video.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
At least a part of it.
You got to post this.
Yeah.
I have all of it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Make reminds my listeners.
Luke might have digitized.
I think.
Get this up.
We want to see this.
Well, so, you know,
I think maybe one of the craziest things about this entire story is just the speed.
It's all 10 years.
Yeah.
From the from nothing from one location to 130 glamorous award shows.
Kathy Griffin,
Mike O'Malley, all of Hollywood's bid is kind of crazy.
They have to come.
They don't even seem to know what it is or why.
Chevy Chase hanging out on the cover of the Warner Brothers catalog with bugs.
Trumpet, a bunch of the classiest man on earth hanging out at the stores, calling them beautiful.
And then within 10 years, it's all it's all said and done.
Crazy.
And I'll just pick a why.
I think the why is just then the merger happened.
It's like, well, we don't really want to do real estate.
AOL wasn't in that real estate because they knew we were all going to be living in the digiverse.
Yeah.
Well, they were looking for a buyer.
Oh, really?
They were going to split it off somehow.
And so there was a chance that, yeah, somebody could
have taken it, but I assume that's a large amount of stores and
could potentially have been on its like a downturn business wise.
Some international locations stuck around for a while.
There was ones in Australia.
There was ones in China.
And those stuck around a lot longer.
I think the China ones was like 2006 to 2014.
Oh, weird.
That's always just like there's still a toy.
There's Toys R Us in Canada still.
Yeah.
Like weird.
It's weird how that stuff.
Tower Records in Japan.
Right.
It's wonderful to see.
But pretty dead and gone now.
And it's a boy is it a thing that makes every mall less fun.
Boy, do I wish I could take the kid out of Marvin's rocket.
I think he would love it unless there was even a single other child in there.
And then he would run out immediately.
But if we had it to ourselves, he would love it.
Yeah, sure.
And so would I.
I would insist on crawling in there myself.
I guess one problem they would have if these were still open is that
a number of them would end up with a full man.
The three of us by name.
Yes, would maybe get stuck in the rocket.
Be like Pooh Bear.
Getting into the house with us.
Yeah, I just I was like, is there any way you could bring this stuff back?
But everything is so damaged at Warner Brothers.
It's just that the stars are not aligned for this to exist now in any capacity.
Not that this is going to ever happen.
But I was like, oh, man, it would be cool if they started doing some of this again.
Because there's all chatter.
Oh, we're going to bring Toys R Us back.
And now Toys R Us is like in name only back in some Macy's.
Yeah, third floor.
Whoever owns it.
Take the kid.
They're not bad, but it's not what it was.
Sure. But there's still like chatter that, OK, eventually that's the plan is to bring
Toys R Us back in some capacity.
I know that's a different thing than Warner Brothers specifically store like
Warner Brothers stores.
But well, I think it's just right now it's impossible.
Yeah, they seem to have their hands full with very successful launches and brand management.
But I was trying to I was like, is how could you if you brought the stars back now,
how does it reflect the current if it was the Warner Brothers Discovery Studio store?
Oh, yeah.
My main idea is that it's still the rocket.
It's still the rocket with all the buttons.
But this is but it's not Marvin's rocket.
It's Zazlaw's office and all of you can use the buttons to delete shows permanently from
being able to be seen by anyone.
That's good.
Yeah, it's not pretend they actually work.
You have just deleted Infinity Train.
No, no.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm sure it'll like exist somewhere, you know, and to live somewhere.
I'm not sure.
As long as someone has copies.
That's all you need.
As I learned, if you make a show and then it's gone for a while from any streaming platform,
just make your own streaming website and put it all there and have people DM you.
I think it's the most it's the most streamlined way to do this.
As far as I know, the handbrake software still free and separate USB DVD,
RW drives very inexpensive.
So if you need to rip stuff like if you have a DVD of that,
I think they only released the first two seasons on DVD.
No, I'm thinking about it.
Not all four.
I just mean if I just mean as long as somebody involved in the show.
This goes to any listeners out there and it's very possible.
There are even Club 3 listeners who've been part of a show that's been deleted forever.
I'm sure just make sure someone has a hard drive.
Get to be friends with those editors, those post people.
All you need is to have it.
I see people like, but the show is gone.
Not not not as long as you have a shady streaming site and private DM links.
That's all you need.
In this case, take a little sidle over to the Internet Archive or Daily Motion,
our friends in media preservation.
Yes.
Yeah, the true kings of media today with no offense to David Zaslov.
Closing thoughts.
Anything?
Do we get it all out?
Yeah, I just I'm obsessed with just the catalogs in general.
There's just so much stuff if to get.
I mean, that's that would I'm not saying we're doing another episode,
but that's the stuff, right?
I keep finding fun stuff.
I'm interested in like things like they have a picture called
or a picture that's titled Monumental Characters with a Mount Rushmore of
Warner Brothers at the time and their characters on.
Did you see you just get a spoil?
Jason, did you see it?
No, I haven't seen.
Do you want to guess who the four monumental characters are?
Do we understand the brand or not?
Right.
So this is this is probably a couple years in.
This is after the Hanna Barbera.
So that should be a hint of who could be on your Warner Brothers Mount Rushmore.
Yeah.
So you're guessing right now what this is, but then we can say our own as well.
Yeah, I will say this one probably Bugs Bunny.
Correct.
Fred Flintstone.
OK, Taz.
No.
Superman.
Batman.
Yes.
OK, so we got one more.
One more.
Yogi Bear.
No.
Real life or cartoon?
Cartoon.
OK.
Sylvester or Daffy?
No.
Oh, Tweety Bird.
No, I'll just tell you.
It's going to be do.
Oh, OK.
Oh, yeah, that was kind of obvious.
And there's a trick question because unlike the real Mount Rushmore, there's a fifth and
it's Casey Ryback from Under Siege.
Some of these stories did have a mural of executives.
What?
Like paintings of like I'm assuming it's Jack Warner and company like it seemed like very
old men.
Jack Warner kind of regarded as a mean guy, like not a great guy in terms of like.
Ahead of a movie studio?
Hollywood moguls.
Right to me.
Yeah.
But right.
Well, who's your for who you're for on Mount Rushmore if you had to pick now for right
now?
It's Aslov.
Yeah, yeah.
Warner.
Jack Warner's Aslov.
Dearly departed, gone too soon.
CNN had Chris Licht.
OK.
And the it's one.
And Great Gazoo.
Oh, sure.
We'll get Great Gazoo on there.
I was going to say one is like it's a panel that flips over and over and over again.
And as every single Batman and Superman, just like the end of my favorite film.
Got it.
Of the century.
Of any century, the Flash.
Right.
OK.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Yeah, great.
Well, RIP.
We missed the store.
Bring it back and we'll forgive you for all the other stuff.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
Suggestions, please.
Some Vegas, some not.
Throw it all out there.
If we don't use Vegas now, we'll use them next month.
But maybe we just maybe do a lot of Vegas.
We're excited about Vegas.
And Mike's video, Mike's container store chokehold video coming soon.
Choke out.
I'd rather call it a choke out video.
Yeah, that's just a little piece of it.
Container store choke out.
That's just a quick gag.
OK, that's what it is in my head.
That's the primary videos that mine has stockpiled.
I'm going to have to get people approving this.
There's so many friends of mine from high school in it.
Oh, yeah.
You need releases.
I'll need a bunch of releases.
Yeah.
To monetize this.
Well, no, you just got to find out how just like, you know, like they're trying to keep AI
out of all the contracts.
That's one of Zazlov's.
Oh, right.
So, you know, the current spirit is just use them.
That's a good point.
And say it's not you.
AI recreated you, which is illegal.
Yeah.
So it's all good.
I'm doing it as well as Zazlov too.
OK, well, yeah, if they ask, they don't know.
They don't probably know about this podcast.
Some friends they are and I'm checking in on them.
I was in second level with some of these guys.
My band in high school.
Second level doesn't subscribe.
I don't think so.
But once you're in a band of brothers, that brotherhood lasts forever.
Well, you have a brotherhood of rock.
Yeah, Joe Perry and Steven.
Yeah, but they were at odds at certain points, but luckily they're getting along perfectly now.