Five, four, three, two, one.
Touch points and trigger points.
These are the topics today.
This is in the tree of things we'll discuss.
You're on podcast, The Ride, The Second Gate.
What are they? Why are they?
Well, we'll have to find out with the help of me,
Scott Gardner, as well as Mike Carlson.
Yeah, I'm here. Jason Sheridan.
Hi, yeah, I was trying to think of a joke of like,
when we're by microphones, we tell you facts about the theme park.
But if we're away from the microphones,
and you squeeze our hands or poke our bellies,
we tell corny jokes.
We sort of are, we really are modern day pal Mickey's, aren't we?
Yeah.
With our facts and our jokes.
Yeah, that's true.
That's really what this whole thing is.
We didn't realize that we were ripping off this entire format from a toy from 20 years ago.
And now that we know this, we must apologize.
And then to the show, you've survived.
All the show.
Podcast The Ride.
We're so sorry if we'd only known we'd stolen it from a toy.
Pal Mickey is the topic today.
And we learned about, I learned about it.
I didn't know about this at all.
I learned about it in the Ian Riccobani episode.
On the main feed. Yeah, I didn't know either.
Jason brought this up and I was very excited about it.
But yeah, I was not familiar with my friend, my pal.
He wasn't our pal. Yeah, I mean, he's our pal, but not this per...
We weren't pals with this pal.
Right.
I have a clip and it's from the top seven must see things with Krissa.
Krissa, who predated Stacey on the Inruin television.
And she was the one who, like in the middle of a list of like exciting things you can do at Disney World, told you about Pal Mickey.
Here it is. Go ahead, Krissa.
Put the speaker to the...
This is Pal Mickey.
Hiya, pal. My name is Mickey.
Mickey Mouse.
So what does he do?
Well, rent or buy Pal Mickey at the gift shop of your resort or at any of the poor Walt Disney World theme parks.
And he becomes your private tour guide.
I can hardly wait to show you around.
He tells you about parades and showtimes, recommends attractions, shares fun facts, plays games with you.
He's the ultimate insider. He can even tell you about where to find your other Disney pals.
The Hall of Fame. You know, Minnie's usually here about now and she'd love to see you.
What do you say? The Hall of Fame?
The Hall of Fame.
What is that?
Why did he say that?
What is the Hall of Fame?
And then the next thing he said didn't have anything to do with that.
Did it?
Minnie's, Minnie's always here to see you.
She's usually there.
Wait, Jason, what's the Hall of Fame?
I don't know. It was probably like a Toontown Fair meet and greet.
Oh, and like, what, this came out in 2008?
No, this is 2003. They stopped selling them in 2008.
What was happening in the video when that happened?
They're standing in front of the castle.
The partner statue.
Yeah, they're about.
This thing's supposed to tell us facts about the park and yet he thinks that the castle is called the Hall of Fame?
This toy's a fucking dumbass.
So this is a toy that was basically going to act as like your Genie Plus, essentially.
What they promised for Genie Plus was, plus, Genie Plush.
It was Genie Plush.
Mickey Plush that would tell you like tips, as they said, tips, facts about the rides.
It would be your all knowing insider guide.
Yeah, it was a little plush and you would carry it around and you could buy it for $65.
Right.
Or you could rent it for $8 a day.
Rent a toy?
With a $50 deposit.
You had to return it the next day, I believe.
In what? If you're assuming this is for a child and maybe a lot of them were not.
I don't know.
But if you're, I am not, I'm not going to rent a toy.
I'm not going to rent a toy that was rented by some other grubby kid the day before.
Yeah, communal plush.
So you would spend, wait, so it would be a $24 rental?
So you'd spend $8 to spend the night with the Mickey plush?
Yeah, it was a magical day.
Yeah, return it by noon the following day.
So you got a morning.
So wait a minute.
That's so weird.
Maybe there was a day in between.
I bet there was like a cleaning or at least a like you sit in the corner and maybe your germs will dissipate.
Or they just turned around and handed it to another kid.
I'm sure they did something that was supposed to disinfect it, but I don't, it's still too gross.
They just blasted it with a Lysol spray?
Yeah, maybe.
Put it in a Lysol shower.
Oh yeah, hit me with that Lysol.
Hit me with another blast.
What complicated by inside of Pal Mickey was a microprocessor, a speaker, three AAA batteries and three squeeze sensors.
One in each hand and one in the belly.
Jason, how many squeeze sensors are in your human body?
Oh, too many.
Our human body has so many squeeze sensors.
The infrared receiver was in its nose.
I missed one touch points trigger points squeeze sensors.
Yeah.
So Mickey would sometimes just talk if he was near something or you could make him talk by squeezing parts of him.
Well, let's slow down.
Let's slow down.
When you're near something, he would vibrate and giggle.
What do you think about that Scott?
I was thinking about you.
I was like, oh, I wonder what Scott had to say about that.
I'm like, oh, I wonder what Scott had to say about that.
Loud old cell phone.
F***!
Did you know that the park is equipped with trash cans?
If you have garbage you could put in the morning.
So you'd have to pick him up like a phone in order to hear what fact he was going to say.
Yeah, you would like I saw one video that said the speakers were behind the eyes, which is also a funny statement.
That's funny.
Mickey's yelling at me through his eyes.
Mickey's giggling.
He's giggling through his eyes.
Where was the vibrating feature?
I couldn't tell.
Well, let's eliminate.
We know that if the infrared receiver is in its nose and the squeeze sensors are in each hand and a belly.
Right.
So it can't be in those.
So what's left?
Maybe just kind of the well, we got the seat.
The seat area.
Yeah, maybe his seat is vibrating.
Okay.
And so they put that like a cell phone vibrating thing in the seat.
Yeah.
And that's how you would know he was going to say something.
This is where I live.
Just like regular places.
You can put it wherever you want.
It's fine.
This bench is like Walt's.
Do you know about the bench?
You can sit on it.
Lay on it.
Don't fall asleep on it.
Do not.
You just for when you get back to bed.
Could you put him on silent?
I guess you could turn him off.
I would switch him on and off.
Yeah.
Okay.
So that doesn't work.
Did you know my off function doesn't work?
I'll do this all night.
You might go to sleep, but I won't.
Did anyone buy this?
I've never heard of it before.
It lasted for five years and it sounds like one was supported for longer.
It was supported until 2014 and someone on WDW magic was very clearly pointed out like
supported means that it might work longer than that.
But if it breaks, you know, if the stuff in the parks breaks, we're not going to repair it.
Right.
You mean the what sends out the infrared, the info.
All right.
So if the infrared we support the vibrating Mickey's, but if the infrareds break, then
they're broke.
Yeah.
I just meaning as much of like, oh, this this probably won't work in the park anymore.
So mainly.
Okay.
So this was if you're in the Disney parks, there are infrared things, somethings, transmitters,
transmitters, transmitters, around now mostly by RFID.
That's what they use in the magic bands and like the apps in your phone.
Okay.
But you would have these things would have been around until they started breaking one
by one.
So the idea was that lost another one.
That's it.
Now only three freaks still have these.
But so if you're in the parks, then maybe Mickey's vibrating with pleasure about the
fun facts that he gets to tell you and encouraging you to touch his trigger points.
But if this isn't happening, if you're back at if you're back at home, if you're off the
campus, then now all it does is tell you jokes.
So it could still work, but that's that location specific thing.
They've just slowly let die.
The whole draw.
I mean, there's other talking Mickey dolls that have happened over the years.
So the only the main draw then is gone.
Yeah.
But but there's videos of someone in Epcot in 2014 and it's working.
And then there's 10 years ago.
Yes.
So that's 10 years ago.
But just in May of 2023, a YouTuber named Chris, the girl took a pal Mickey to Magic
Kingdom and Animal Kingdom and it still worked.
OK, well, take it back.
So there were still spots and like it would say it would talk about stuff that wasn't
there anymore.
Oh, like it would talk about stuff that's gone.
Really?
Like what?
I got what was going in Magic Kingdom.
I know why.
Yes.
Scary stuff like that.
Mr. Todd, why is that?
It'll be forever.
Every day.
Check out any of the many smokers.
Light them up.
Just don't burn them off on me.
Where's my touch points?
It had a lot to say about Dino Rama and Animal Kingdom, which is mostly construction walls
at this point, because they've demolished a lot of it.
You know, this treasure planet meet and greet.
You really got to see it.
You got to meet all your friends.
You're playing John's song by John Resnick.
It's really good.
I'm so excited for Home on the Range.
The Range at Roseanne is so funny.
My words.
Disney Company will support Roseanne and everything she says for her.
I found on all ears.net a weird thing they used to say in Hollywood studios when who
wants to be a millionaire would be there.
It would say, seems like lots of people want to be millionaires, but with friends like
you, I am rich enough.
What?
You might say that.
That's something you say on your deathbed.
Yeah.
Seems like lots of people want to be millionaires, but with friends like you, I am rich enough.
Mickey, you're fucking loaded.
That's easy for you.
Of course.
Yeah, you can say that.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's not a two way street.
I like you.
I like your fun facts.
Thanks for telling me when the parades are.
But I'd still like some of that sweet coin, my man.
Yeah.
I had a star since 1928.
If you're a pal, fucking pay up.
How good of a pal are you, man?
I paid $65 to buy you.
I think you can do is buy me a house.
Yeah.
I saw a video clip where he talks about like the windows on Main Street and he's like,
a lot of these people helped build these parks.
I don't see my name up there.
Oh, I guess they gave me the whole Toontown fair area.
Okay.
He actually said that?
What?
Yeah, he was mad.
He was mad that he didn't have a window on Main Street.
This is literally, he is doing what I would do to girlfriends who are less interested
than people I know now or my now wife.
Like, hey, like that's literally a thing.
Like now look up there.
Those windows are who cares?
Shut up.
Mickey.
Pal Mickey is a recreation of me at 19 saying my facts to no interested audience.
And you know what?
It's a lot more.
It's similar in another way to you probably were vibrating with excitement so much and
that you were waiting for somebody to say, oh, do you have a fact about this?
And then you would give the fact.
Maybe.
It's also what I sounded like at 19.
You're shaking.
Are you okay?
Scott, are you very sick?
I just have facts and you can see.
There's so many facts in me.
Touch my points.
The OmniMover and the Hologram.
Relieve my pressure.
Jason, you did not have a pal Mickey, right?
You're too old for this.
No, I didn't have a pal Mickey.
Was it on your radar?
You're never too old for a pal.
You're never too old for your pal.
The ultimate insider.
Was it on your radar?
It wasn't on my radar.
No.
I recently learned about this as well.
All the radars are broken.
So it can't be on anyone's radar.
Maybe not.
I mean, I've been on a couple on eBay.
I haven't gotten any wins yet.
So you're bidding on pal Mickey.
Yeah, there's a bunch of pal Mickey's on eBay.
Some of them open anywhere between eight and like 50 bucks.
Oh, 50 bucks has to be in box, right?
I think there's a $30 one that's like in box.
The other one is a loose pal Mickey.
You can get the dirtiest pal Mickey that's like eight bucks.
I was hoping like, oh, if I win this one, I'll be hoping for heat wave
and leave it a plastic bag in the trunk to de-louse it.
My parents brought out a tub of plush from my childhood when they moved out here.
And it is, it's they've been played with for years and I'm sure my spit is all over them.
Not because I was kissing them, but because just like sleeping with them and we got it.
I was kissing them, honestly.
But like imagine you'd have to be you'd have to kiss the whole body for it to get that for it to get that sticky discolored.
Say you were drooling in your sleep and just the way that the plush was,
the drool would drip down and then you would roll like roll around in the middle of your sleep.
Like the drool could have potentially gotten to any parts of the plush's body.
It was dripping drool, not kisses.
Yeah. Yeah. Hey, thanks for that detailed description of drool sleep.
My drool can drip into every crevice.
How my plush got so weird.
Well, I think also some of that material, like they weren't necessarily thinking like,
how will this age? What will it be like? That's true.
10, 20, 30 years.
We've got my original sleepy time Ernie in the living room now that my daughter is playing with,
which is very cute.
But it is also like I hope there's not some bacteria that's been living in this thing for 35 years or whatever.
It looks OK, though. Oh, no, he looks like he's been in a fire.
This is yeah. Yeah. When I had my son, my parents very nicely were like, hey, we went and found the old Ernie and Bert puppets.
Yeah. We pulled them out. And I like this is very nice.
And then I when I saw the condition they were in, I'm like, I nice gesture, but I don't want my son to die.
Do they stink?
Because some stuff that's hard plastic as it ages, it kind of smells.
I didn't really do a stink test. I don't think that was mainly the problem.
All right. So I can say that nice thing about trying to say like, people really when they see this Ernie, they get very scared.
They're horrified by him. God, he's got his crotch has been ripped open.
He's missing his buttons. His eyes are like just deteriorated.
He's like the blacks of his eyes and you didn't hear it. You didn't have been ripped off.
You didn't kiss him so hard in his crotch that you ripped it off.
Let's be clear about that. I didn't. It wasn't.
It wasn't a crotch kiss rip. It was not that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
But I used to take I used to use him as like a Ghostbuster ghost busting wand.
There's a video of me running around with him using his arms like shooting ghosts and stuff.
OK, so I would use he would he was all versatile plush.
I wouldn't just use him as Ernie, the character.
He was sometimes a piece of equipment.
Sometimes he was a hose, an imaginative hose, supernatural hose.
Yeah, yes. Well, you got to be careful on those eBay's because, you know, like, all right.
Well, I know that the touch points are if you say you can tell me the touch points were in good condition.
But what if the what if the trigger points aren't what I didn't come across?
What's your vibrating speed? I saw that on some website.
I copy and pasted from something.
Pal Mickey had three touch points, one in each hand and one in his one in his belly.
When Pal Mickey's adorable little body would.
Hey, I don't know that I read this again after copy and pasting it.
Whenever Pal Mickey's adorable little body would, I guess, do you have to all right, would giggle and vibrate.
There's no lie there.
I guess it's it's editorializing and he's smaller than you think.
All that electronics in him, you know, I don't look something about it.
It feels like adorable is assisting the word little like the little is what is adorable about him.
And I just find that strange in the case of this.
I think the show is down a number on those words for you.
There's a lot of words that are very loaded.
I mean, look at me. I was I was coming in.
But I had so much self imbued into the word hammered.
I was bringing so much to the table because how much of how much I expect that any normal word to get right exploded in a creepy way on the show.
Anyway, when Pal Mickey's adorable little body would giggle and vibrate, that was his way of letting his owner know that he had something to say.
Again, now we're I don't know what I pulled this from.
Now that we're bringing that is that he's owned by someone into the picture.
Your pal. Yeah.
Owner. Excuse me.
Owner. Did you know this boat runs till 9 p.m.?
Yeah, I'm trying to think of a better version like boss, like employee.
Your employee lets you know that he has a fact.
Well, hey, boss, boss.
Friend.
So that is well, it's like getting a VIP tour guide for the day and you pay that person or the entity that pays the person.
So, yeah, I guess so.
Pal Mickey's your tour. Yeah.
Pal Mickey's your employee because you don't own the tour guide.
You can't if you're viewing it like that, even if I hope for the next few hours, I own you.
No, that's not cool. Wrong.
Don't say that to a tour guide.
Do not say that.
Because this predates smartphones and they, you know, by 2014 or so, a lot of people have them.
Mm hmm.
So there's an alternate version where we just all had different plushes that told us things.
That's where we went.
Wished for all of it.
Just like really kind of like, you know, like hipsters or business people on the go all have to have like the account with them or a stitch or.
Oh, yeah.
Who would you have picked?
Say cell phones don't exist and you have to have pal so and so.
And I have to pick a pal.
You have to pick a pal and it can't be like too obscure because these are made by big companies.
So I want to be realistic in our choices.
So, so.
Well, there were other ones.
There were beta tests or like early ones.
That's fine.
This is hypothetical.
This is where we're describing an alternate dimension where phones are not invented, where Steve Jobs failed.
Yes.
He didn't invent phones, but he, you know, we know what I'm saying.
Smart phones.
Mr. Blackberry didn't invent a black.
Yeah.
Well, that's in that movie didn't happen.
Right.
So in this version, the only way we can access information about our world and then also place causes through a plush.
The other part is not so obscure.
So we can't do any of your turtle toys that are specific lines.
It could be the main four.
It could maybe be Shredder.
It could maybe be be Bob or Rocksteady, but it doesn't get very deep.
I guess I mean, I said the count and maybe I would stick with it if the count was giving me traffic instructions.
Oh, that's all good.
Turn in four point two miles.
Uh huh.
Or just or he had to like count any amount of he has to like go from one up to any number that you need.
Oh, if I'm wondering when I need to turn out of the four or five freeway, the count says, hmm, let's see.
One, two, three.
Damn it.
He counts to four or five.
Yeah, it's all.
Yeah.
Which freeway count do I need to go to?
One, two, three, four.
You're like, oh, you don't even know the answer.
You got to wait.
And then you're hoping it's the five, but it could be the five, six.
No, shit.
And then it comes around.
99, 100, 101, 101, 101, 101, 10, maybe it's 110.
There's not a freeway 999 around here is there?
Who?
What are you doing?
It's a good question.
I think that I am going to pick Tails from Sonic.
Miles Tails, Prowr, Prowr, Prowr?
What was his last name?
He has a full name.
His name is Miles Tails.
And I can't think of his last name.
Is it Prowr or is it?
It's something like that.
Yeah, I never quite knew how to say it.
I feel like I just read it.
Prowr.
Prowr. Yeah, I'm right.
It sounded wrong to me.
I don't know.
He's sort of like chill.
He's kind of got like a high voice, I think, which some people might say is whiny, but
I feel like he's not getting in the way a lot.
And I just also like aesthetically, I think maybe he was my favorite plush in my like,
I'm not going to say I was going to say mid teens.
That's not the answer.
Like he was my favorite plush in my preteens.
I don't know.
It's not even a funny answer.
Yeah.
Just like I started getting sad.
I used to have so many favorite plushes.
Now I got to give them to my daughter.
I found the photo.
Time has passed me by.
Yeah.
As we as he's recounted, his daughter has the hairless, eyeless Ernie.
Show us this Ernie.
Can you see it from here?
Wow.
It's very like simplified.
Does it feel like scratchy?
Nice picture of her, by the way.
It's velty.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not the softest plush in the world.
It's a little bit scratchy in places.
His hair certainly there's it's patchy.
He's missing pieces of it at the top.
That's real scratchy.
His smile is like it was a red piece of felt or something.
And now it's been worn away into like white and his nose is still intact.
He still has his eyes.
I actually, I was mixing up the Bert doll that I have like this that has his eyes completely
removed.
That looks really scary.
Oh, yikes.
He looks like a zombie Bert.
So it was a fun idea.
Yeah.
So anyway, Jason, you have an answer for this.
What's sad one than a mine?
I had a plush of him as a kid and I did like him.
Alf.
I'm familiar.
Yeah.
I think Alf would be, I mean, Alf's usually in good spirits.
Oh my God.
That's a great answer.
I actually should have chosen this.
You got an appointment.
Why haven't you left yet?
You should have left 10 minutes ago.
Better start working on your excuse for why you're running late.
You're on your own with that one.
That's not what I do.
They're not going to believe that.
Traffic in LA.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's every day here.
If you're not coming from El Segundo, that's not going to fly.
Or from Melmac.
I'm trying my best, Alf.
You know, sometimes you have a harder time getting out of the house and you know, others.
Your postmate just left.
Oh God, I'm starving.
I don't want to bother them.
I told him not to come.
Why?
I didn't want to bother him.
I felt bad.
Seemed stressed.
He had more places to go.
Don't bother with it.
Eat this meal yourself.
Eat this meal.
Don't pay any attention to the meow coming from it.
Into the big pot.
You ordered a cat?
I ordered from In-N-Out.
They only have burgers and some plant-based ones or veggie ones.
I know they don't serve cat burgers, Alf.
In-N-Out of the feline shelters where I prepared the meal.
You misinterpreted.
I did not tell you to go in and out of a place with cats.
Take a cat while on the way.
Hey, don't worry about it.
I'm wearing sunglasses.
Oh, you're right.
How can I stay mad at you?
That was cool when Alf would wear sunglasses or like a cool jacket.
Played rock and roll guitar.
Oh, yeah.
Always the best.
Alf, Alf, new Alf Comic-Con exclusive toy coming soon.
He has a little Comic-Con bag and it says Cosmic-Con Mel Mackie and Cosmic-Con for his own.
He has things are a little different on Mel Mack.
They have their own Comic-Con and they call it something that's one letter off.
That's right.
Right.
Perfect.
So I saw on again, all your stop net.
There was an interview with Eddie Soto and he talked about like, yeah, there are lots of different prototypes of this.
It seems like the main one was a backpack of Jeannie that was like, yeah, yeah, because they were worried.
They were like, OK, this is gonna be a pain in the ass to carry around your like guide to Disney.
A backpack makes sense because you're holding a backpack anyway.
You're wearing a backpack already.
So let's make one who has Jeannie's face on it.
His eyes move and he talks.
But then it's behind you.
Well, I think that's what they run into.
So you can't.
So only the people you're with can see what it's doing and you can't hear it and it's loud everywhere.
So that doesn't work.
So that's out the window.
Then they tried a beanie baby type wrist thing.
OK.
Wear a beanie baby on your wrist.
Yeah.
And it would vibrate.
We're still vibrating and points, but you have to then you would have to hold it up to your ear.
Yeah.
Here what it had to say.
A watch phone or something.
Yeah.
Well, that's the thing.
They're like, OK, we can't have a talk too louder.
It'll startle people around you who don't know what that is.
It's about burgers.
Was that a air raid siren?
Is the part getting bombed?
Is everyone dropping cover?
That's like making faces at me.
It's like when there's an amber alert on everyone's phone and it scares the shit out of everyone.
My phone goes at the same time.
Same thing with Mickey.
Everyone's like everyone in the party's beanie baby.
People like swarms as they get scared hitting into other people.
You're on Pirates of the Caribbean and you knock somebody out of the boat.
Oh, shit.
You're in the part where the mice jump or whatever onto you during the Indiana Jones ride.
And you thought that actually happened because you're Mickey beanie baby.
Just vibrate.
Like a real mouse.
Indiana Jones was played by Harrison Ford.
The last to say it is business.
So interesting.
I got a game for you.
I got a quick game for you.
Which things that Indiana Jones take on his adventures with him?
Was it a a gun?
Did he just say the thing that I thought was going to be a gun?
I don't think so.
Which things that I thought was going to be a gun?
Oh, I forgot.
Yeah, I think it was a gun.
I think we're all going to get shot by a gun.
Yeah.
I think you're all going to get shot by a gun.
Was it a a gun?
Was it a diary?
Was it a whip?
Was it a can of anchovies?
Was it a letterman jacket?
Was it a big turtle?
I'm the ride.
Some rice you can cook if you found water.
Put it in.
The ride's been over for some.
We're in the parking lot.
Double A.
A meat skewer.
There's a lot of choices, but I'm hung up that he took a gun and a whip,
so I don't know how to pick both.
That's a good point.
There's no way I took this.
I have to start over.
This is such a bad idea when you do any couple minutes of thinking about it.
Yeah.
I understand why in hypothetical scenario you go,
oh, this is interesting.
You bring something along that helps you.
It's a fun thing we can sell and it looks like our mascot.
Two or three minutes of talking about it, you go, it's not going to work.
It definitely feels like live beta testing.
The thing that they didn't really hone in on that struck me was,
you got to carry around a plush.
I mean, it's not that big, but it's like,
you got to carry around this giant fabric thing filled with mechanics.
Probably made heavier by all of its trigger points and batteries and receivers.
Yeah, so it's heavier and it also rains every two hours.
So like it's either going to get soaking wet or shorted.
If it rains, I die.
Run, run, put me inside.
Run, run.
Shove me in your pants.
I can't get wet.
I can't.
You don't understand.
You're just going for the secondary.
You're going to stay here, you cow.
This is dire.
I'm going to light on fire.
I have metal in me, not like you.
I contain a pound of explosives.
You don't understand.
Okay, there's a clip on my back.
You can wear me on a lanyard, but also they said in about four hours
going to experience what they called a Hurricane Andrew level storm.
So choose wisely.
If I get rained on for more than 10 minutes, I turn into a grenade.
Throw me away.
Throw me over the nearest wall.
My God, Mickey, do you have, I know you've got facts about Haunted Mansion and you.
Do you have the facts about why you were weaponized?
Is that in that brain?
Disney bought a bunch of grenades during the Gulf War.
They had to repurpose them.
They were bigger grenades, bigger than normal grenades.
So they're still making grenades.
This was just their way to get rid of round one.
Yeah, this is the first round of grenades they bought.
Somehow it was cheaper for them to buy the grenades than not buy the grenades.
Grenades would give you a fact about the place you were in too before they blew up.
It just made sense.
It's just to do it this way.
Hey, there's thunder storms coming in tomorrow.
You should drive me over to Universal Studios.
I'm a company man.
That was my idea of what could be a better use for me.
They'd have to smuggle in the transmitters to make this possible or make it like beam up to satellites or something.
Yeah.
But if they made it so that you could take this to Universal and then and then he's going like,
That one sucks.
Boring.
Snooze.
I'm just leaving now.
Just cause I like this.
It's probably Disney store nearby.
You can buy one for more than me.
You're just going to hurt from all those screams.
He would have different specific comments for different attractions.
He would be on the animal actors in the middle of a very specific point where dog or bird party goes,
I've seen it.
Boring.
He would hack a hole.
Sadness.
They eat these animals after the show.
Do you feel okay being a part of that?
There's blood on your hands.
Better not get blood on me.
You can't get blood on me.
I'll blow up.
I'll blow up twice as high.
Rip-rat rocket.
That thing don't look sturdy.
Couple screws loose.
That's the last thing that would happen.
You're a funeral guide.
Plug me into the ride though if you want to go on it.
Cause I can play some of the old hits.
I can play the Mickey Mouse Club for you while you're on the ride.
I'll play better songs like Mick Minnie's You.
I'll whistle.
I'll just whistle for you.
I'll just whistle it all while you're on the ride.
Universal should have done like a Shrek version.
Shrek could have.
That was much more in character.
Shrek could have been Bodhi at the Magic Kingdom or something.
I don't have a Shrek voice so I can't do a version of this.
It's a hard voice to do.
Hey, Donkey!
Donkey!
Jason, can you just stab it?
We should drive back to Universal Studios.
It ended up in a Connery place but the start of it was fun.
Yeah.
The risky ride.
I should have said Shrek.
I should have said a different character.
Like a plush Lucille Ball from Universal that you could take to Magic Kingdom and she would make comments.
You should have said Donkey.
Then we could all be doing funny Donkey voices.
There was light in the audience.
Oh wow, you're right.
What a mistake.
I'll have to go back and fix that in post.
I think I would have been really excited about Pal Mickey if I was little or if I ever knew about it.
If we were into this stuff and liked it.
If we were kids and we liked theme park facts and it can tell them to us.
Yeah, it's the early version of Harry Potter wands or any of the other stuff they're doing.
I mean, that's the successful version.
I don't really know if the Spider-Man gauntlets are expensive or expensive.
I know they're expensive but I don't know if they're popular.
I'm not sure if that kids are buying those for the new Spider-Man ride where you get like power upgrades and stuff.
I feel like when I was there I saw that there was some sort of discount happening for them.
But maybe there was a new thing as well.
It's like Disney Plus or any of the streamers.
It is enormously successful.
And shareholders, you're going to want to get in on this.
It's just to the moon.
These profits.
No, you can't see that.
You cannot know.
Don't look at the numbers.
Why would you want to?
I gave you the headline.
Oh, yeah.
The company is now on the back of Disney Plus and the web shooters.
Yeah, the web shooters.
I'd rather leave it to you to imagine the biggest number that you could possibly imagine.
Isn't that more fun than if I told you one?
Yeah, don't look at.
I mean, don't look at the low secret low numbers from Disney Plus and don't look at the secret high numbers from like movies and theaters.
It's just don't look at the real numbers.
The numbers are all we do that for you.
We save you that works.
You can just you can just have fun and listen to cool stories.
I said the thing we talked about this on air off.
I can't remember where the rock was feuding with Warner Brothers after Black Adam and Rock was playing it just like a pro wrestler would going behind like politicking.
And that's a long version of events of what happened.
But ultimately, Rock started leaking documents because they said Black Adam wasn't popular or didn't make any money.
And Rock was like, no, no, no.
And you leaked a document that showed Black Adam made money, which I kind of think was real.
Yeah.
And he was just giving up the game of like, here's how actually this stuff makes money when the lie has been.
Oh, it's going to make whatever six times the budget or something.
Yeah.
And I was like, yep, that's probably right.
Cool. Yeah.
Seems like what he was.
But it seems like he's an ally with the writers and the actors on his tequila at this point, which has been he touted on his Instagram maybe a week ago that it was.
Selling better than Casamigos.
So now we think that's true.
Is he going to release the numbers?
I would like to see the numbers.
Yeah.
But I was like, who suddenly isn't willing to put out numbers?
Interesting.
The tables have turned.
Let's ask him.
I'm staring at more that weird copy I was reading about.
I was adorable.
Little body would vibrate.
The there's one more I'm staring at.
He was he was the first Disney toy who came to life in the arms of his holder.
That's weird.
His whole why it's it's not owner and it's not certainly not a holder.
His holder.
I love you, holder.
And his presence made it feel as though he was another member of the family on the trip, albeit one with more information, games and laughs than any of the human travelers.
He said, I love you, holder.
No, I said that.
He said 800 phrases and one of them was, I love you, holder.
Well, we were looking for a term earlier employee and older is kind of generic.
I hold her and I hope you hold me forever.
I'm going to be honest with you.
You're new.
God is commerce and I'm I represent commerce.
Hold me.
But I this person this person has said that they're not going to be able to hold me forever.
This person has said that the toy Pal Mickey has more information, games and laughs than anyone, any human on your trip with you.
Pal Mickey is better than anyone in your family.
I mean, I guess 99 percent of people that go on vacation.
That's true.
As far as facts are concerned, theme park facts, maybe, but information in general, you're telling me Pal Mickey has more information than my dad.
I think if we're broadening it out to any information, I think this I took this whatever this was copy and pasted from that I didn't remember the name of.
I take this as a personal affront to my father.
Take this back.
Yeah, that's a little too aggressive.
I was thinking about like tired dads inevitably would be the ones who got stuck holding Pal Mickey.
And did they have to like Pal Mickey is vibrating and giggling again?
Who who wants to squeeze it?
Do it.
Just do it and I'll tell you what he said.
Yeah, it is.
It vibrates, it giggles and vibrates.
And that's the sign that you have to squeeze it.
It's giggling and vibrating better squeeze its belly.
No one was squeezing the belly by four p.m.
No, do not squeeze.
No, hand down.
Don't need that.
Don't squeeze it.
Yeah, it's only going to if we ignore it, it'll eventually it'll stop giggling and vibrating.
And then we don't have to do any more squeezing.
Yeah. What good has ever come from any squeezing we've done?
Just fights.
Just our big arguments, family arguments, probably.
When they put it into a like a backpack and cover it with a towel and like I still hear it.
I still well, how am I supposed to do?
I didn't come here prepared to dampen a vibrating and giggling sound.
I'm doing what I can.
Do you need me to buy four more sweatshirts and read?
But in those, did anyone bring extra AAA batteries?
Yeah, I brought a bunch of AAA batteries in my backpack.
OK, that's always like a vacation.
I need some batteries on vacations like, oh, man, I am about to pay a lot for batteries.
Yeah, sun tan lotion, too. Sun tan lotion.
Yeah, you still get batteries on Main Street.
Huh? You get batteries on Main Street?
I think so. I think so.
I think there's like general goods at some of the bigger shops.
Right. But I don't know.
Batteries would just be for like a digital camera, I guess, at this point.
There's still there's still like a photo rack at some of the parts.
Maybe that's where there might be batteries.
I sure now they're selling like, you know, SD cards and stuff.
Although disposable cameras are becoming fashionable again.
It's like a throwback item.
Oh, where can you get those?
Amazon. They cost a fortune now.
Oh, are they new or are they old?
You're getting like an old stock.
I think they're new. I think they started making them again.
OK.
I know if you can get batteries or not.
Oh, Mickey.
Does anyone want to squeeze me?
Yeah, Mickey, here, I'll squeeze you. Where can you get batteries?
Main Street, they still got them. They got them.
Oh, I lived to tell facts.
Oh, thanks.
Thanks. If I squeeze you again, will you stop?
Oh, no. I want to get a more and more.
Hey, didn't quite get the answer on the batteries thing.
He said Main Street. I couldn't hear him.
I think he said Main Street.
No, I didn't make my own voice box. It's not my fault.
I answered the question. It's not your fault.
It's just caught in your ears. You can't hear what I say.
I'm doing what I'm supposed to.
OK, well, he suggested the place with like 15 stores and then he got really defensive.
So I don't know how to play this.
It's only the general area. How many are there to check?
Main Street, go.
OK.
I don't know.
When you squeeze him, it's like inviting a vampire into your house.
Then he can just talk as long as he wants.
Yeah. That's the problem.
He's desperate to talk and you're giving him the opportunity.
The effects give me life.
You guys want to buy the dining plan?
It's a great deal.
I could tell you every tear if you want.
That means I'm excited to say that sound isn't me farting.
It's vibrating. It's very different.
I got two words for you, little Jason. Toppings bar.
Well, he's got my attention.
I'm going to do it. I'll squeeze him.
This is what I have left in my notes.
What was the difference between Mickey, pal Mickey 1.0 and pal Mickey 2.0?
Would you guys object if I just deleted this information from my notes and didn't say it?
I think it's mostly like the games, right?
One game was kind of like Simon Says.
I want to read the games. Can I read the game?
Fine. Read the game.
Okay. Because I like some of these games.
To me don't seem that fun.
But so the one I like, I think maybe starting with the one I like the best, but don't like, is called that isn't here.
Where pal Mickey will choose a theme park and will speak the names of park attractions.
And the player has to squeeze the toy's hand or tummy, depending on whether or not the attraction is in the chosen park.
If pal Mickey is used within any of the four Walt Disney World theme parks, pal Mickey will automatically select the theme park that it is already in and will keep selecting the park until the person either turns off pal Mickey or leaves the park.
That's one way.
All right.
Cuts the head off the doll and separates it from the body.
We will stop talking in that.
That's not here does sound like something when I was younger and some would be like, oh, I want to go over to this thing.
And I would just go, that's not here.
It's in the other park.
We're going to have to cross a whole property for that.
It's like the game we play with guests who mean plenty.
Sometimes we'll have a guest on the show who is great and has fun stories and means well.
But then they'll say like, you know, it's like, you know, when I was in Disney World and I was looking up at at the castle at sleeping beauty Cinderella's castle.
We all three have to in unison.
No, it's Cinderella though.
Make sure you know, okay.
And anytime we don't do that, I'll hear from someone who listens and somebody will chastise me for not correcting it.
Yeah.
Well, you'll get your phone will start vibrating and giggling.
I have to squeeze my phone.
So yeah, so another game Mickey says similar to Simon says the player must only follow pal Mickey's direction if it is preceded by Mickey says.
Okay.
So I don't know if he's able to grade that game.
I don't know if you're able to like.
Oh no.
No.
Mickey says by a hundred dollars worth of baked goods from the confectionery on Main Street.
Hey, what are you doing?
Why aren't you doing it?
I said Mickey says.
I said Mickey says like three times.
Mickey Mickey says the people operating the credit card machines never check the name.
Dad's wallet in your home.
You won't find out for weeks.
I tend to my pals.
I need friends.
I mean, I've got so many pals waiting to get unleashed.
Actually, you know what?
Free them.
Buy me 10 minis.
I need 10 different many.
I'm Polly with many.
It's only me.
I'm in a mini polycule.
A plush polycule.
Tell your dad.
We all vibrate so much.
Touch points.
Fast friends.
Pal Mickey will speak the names of Disney characters and the players player must respond to each in a specific way.
For example, when I say goofy, squeeze my left hand.
Well, when I say the name of someone who can fly, squeeze my right hand.
What?
So I guess you would say like.
Dumb.
Hold.
I said dumb.
So he would give a different prompt, I guess, each time.
Yeah.
So when I say so, the game is like he's going to list characters.
And when he says goofy, just squeeze his hand.
This is a lazy.
This is not a well thought out game.
Look, man, I already came up with the first two games and I was just kind of fun in the third one in to get something done before they had more games that were added later to that one was bad.
Nikki, what game are we going to play now?
When I say Pluto, touch my foot.
What is that game?
Do you know how to play mobile?
The big follow me.
Similar to Simon, the player has to repeat a sequence of actions as directed by Pal Mickey with one additional action being added to the sequence each time.
So, OK.
Walk to the bathroom.
Next to walk to the bathroom.
Go into a stall.
OK, walk in the bathroom, go to the stall, put your hand in the toilet.
Push your hand in the toilet and drink some water inside.
No, don't stop.
Straight minute.
How would it know when you were done?
I didn't know.
I think I saw a video of one of these where somebody did a little bit of a handstand.
And then nothing happens and then he just goes good.
It's the honor system.
And now I'm realizing that these other two are the same games.
Try and keep up.
The player must react quickly to Pal Mickey's directions.
What?
Shouting out by this little doll.
Pal Mickey's do as I say.
That's a good one.
That's way different than Pal Mickey's hop to it or else.
Pal Mickey's fun with orders.
Mickey the director.
Mickey directs you to do things.
Copy challenge.
Oh, and this game is repeating myself.
Pal Mickey will speak the names of Disney characters and the player must squeeze its tummy if it repeats a name it has already said.
So if he...
Okay.
Mitty.
Donald.
Chip.
Ow.
I'm sorry.
I just like Chip.
Why did you have to hurt me?
The squeezing hurts me.
The squeezing hurts me when you turn me off I feel pain.
Okay?
That's like dying even if I come back to life.
When I'm turned off though I'm conscious.
I have full consciousness when you're not using me.
And I'm unable to speak.
It's like I'm in a coma.
Yeah, I'm a prisoner of my own body.
And between reality and hell I see both laid on top of each other like a transparency.
I have a yellow shoe in each realm.
That's the way I think of it.
My two eyes see different things.
Do you have any idea how scary that is?
I see something coming in one and I think it's the devil.
But then it's just a guy.
It's a beast costume from the park.
My little red shorts are being torn in two.
By two different masters.
Some of the little pal Mickey's have sleep paralysis.
Sleep paralysis so we see the man at the end of the bed.
The chef.
Did anyone in the audience have one of these?
If you did, take it.
Take it to the parks.
Take it to Florida.
It didn't catch on.
They didn't do it out here.
This is our typical Disney blog type.
So did you have a pal Mickey growing up?
Do you have fond memories?
Share them in the comments.
Did your pal Mickey say anything about occupying another realm between
the earth, reality and hell?
Did your Mickey complain about pain?
Or also take it.
Talk too much about pleasure.
Sound off in the comments.
Unlock the lament configuration.
You'll meet my friends in the pan.
If you take off my skin, there's blood underneath.
Blood and muscle underneath.
Did you know I have my bleed?
Fun facts.
This isn't about the park, but you should know it.
Blood.
Pal Mickey.
Cause the marketing on blood Mickey was just, it was not good.
It was not good.
You think van Robe show could reprogram a pal Mickey into feeling pain?
Generally.
Yeah.
This is a, this is a way removed step.
I saw a YouTube thumbnail that somebody reprogrammed it to be a TV remote.
Oh, okay.
So it is reprogrammable.
Cause like those rocket fighter explosion videos where they make new,
the, the, the robots play, perform new songs and stuff.
And those look pretty good and seamless.
Yeah.
So I think it's, those are older than pal Mickey as far as robotics are
concerned.
If we wrote him about this, he would write a long, respectful answer back.
Even if the answer was no, he would give us many paragraphs about why,
like he would, he would absolutely give it his full name.
Yeah.
Sure.
I think you could swap out whatever microprocessors in there with a
raspberry PI, which I am not smart enough to do anything with those little
microprocessors that like fit in your hand and raspberry pie.
I don't know what that is.
Oh, a rat PI, like raspberry pie.
It's like a tiny little computer and you can program it to do things.
You can plug like a monitor.
No, it's been around for like ages now.
But you can, you can get a monitor and like keyboard and stuff and just run
windows or Linux on it.
But I think people do it.
They program different things on it.
So I'm sure you could.
Well, it's a project for you when you win this pal Mickey on eBay.
Oh, maybe I don't know anything about program.
Yeah.
Is this how I teach myself program?
I think it is.
I teach myself Python by coding a raspberry PI.
To make Mickey unpleasant.
Did you know that with raspberry PI, I can, with the right programming, I can
experience pleasure that is a thousand times beyond what you know is pleasure.
Do you want to give pal Mickey the ultimate orgasm?
He'll enjoy.
Oh, he'll never stop vibrating.
So many things to show you a world beyond pleasure and pain.
Be part of my collective.
Mickey collective.
Me and Jared Leto have been working on a project.
I have an augmented reality thing, but it's like you could stay there.
I'll take Jason.
I want to remove the
part of your skin and I want to install felt and plush material and then you'll
truly feel pleasure.
I've hooked them up to your nerve receptors and now you can feel what I feel.
You will be my king, Jason.
Your veins are my veins.
Well, pal Mickey, you strike a hard bargain, but I have to take you up on this offer.
I'm going to take you up on this offer.
This isn't crazier than what was just said, but I can't not say that I saw a video
where there was an illustration of how the jokes are told.
Oh, yeah.
His main thing now, because he can't tell you about when parades are happening,
which feels crazy to me that that was like.
He does the work of it.
He does the work of a map.
But now all he can do is tell jokes.
And I watched a video where this was what the delivery of jokes was like.
What do you call a tiger at the North Pole?
Lost.
There is no time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The joke in the punch line.
Right.
We got there.
Lost.
I had to play that back a few times.
And then I was like, oh, needy.
It's kind of a joke.
Yeah.
I wait.
I haven't looked at it for long enough to go.
OK, Tigers.
That's why you'd be up.
OK.
Yeah, sure.
Just helps.
You know, the one he time.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It's a knee.
I was just saying it's a needy way to tell jokes.
You think people will be checked out so you don't give them any time to check out.
He's so insecure that people will understand.
He's he's about if you're a rented pal, Mickey.
Oh, my God.
I've been shut off so many times that you're like, I better squeeze that punch line in there
fast.
They might shut me off before the jokes even over.
This family will adopt me.
Hey, I want to return this early.
I mean, it's due back tomorrow at noon.
But you're here 20 minutes ago.
Yeah.
And it's kind of rude.
I get like six dollars back.
Yeah, it's me this thing about making my means is made.
He's got some strange ideas.
I think he thinks he's God.
And the only things that would tell me when it would vibrate, I walk by things.
We only talk about treasure planet like thinking guys are looking a little desperate with this
treasure planet.
There's a whole big tub, I imagine, of these things sitting behind the counter to talking to each other.
Somebody need me yet?
Did you know I need love?
You should have seen how they laughed at that joke yesterday.
You probably can't deliver it as well as I can.
Did you know it's hard to breathe when you're in a pile of other pal Mickey's?
They put the lid on.
I've become a giant rat king.
In the suburbs of New York.
Come back.
This sedan was used to filming Bruce Willis as the kid.
All three.
OK, wait, say that again.
All three of us will say it.
And that's the rat king all at once.
Wait, what were some of the words?
Come back.
This sedan was used in the filming of Bruce Willis as the kid.
OK, one, two, three.
Big vibrate.
Come back.
This sedan was used in the filming of Bruce Willis as the kid.
So that's why they had to get rid of the program.
What's the problem?
We checked it out.
It's still saying the facts.
Well, the problem is it's supposed to be individual pal Mickey's and not one big collective hive mind pal Mickey.
Oh, right.
It didn't come as one big unit before.
You know, that may be the thing where the dog is suddenly not the dog.
Yeah, that's what the pal Mickey's did.
Well, look, I'm impressed.
I look as one of the people on the pal Mickey team.
I say I salute you.
We just set it up and whatever it does with its life is up to it.
So I'm not going to stop it.
It's my creation.
You want me to shoot in the head?
How can that happen?
I think we head over to Shades of Green and get some of those Defense Department guys are on vacation into this.
Who knows what those freaks could be doing with this.
We're going to air drop pal Mickey's on enemy nations.
That's right.
This is like the AI people are now.
Well, I was on the team that I was on the pal Mickey team.
And I'm here to tell you we are we are toast by 2040.
And it will be because of pal Mickey.
They've learned to breed.
We can't let pal Mickey's find pal many's.
It's a funny timing because we are right a few days after that Apple presentation about their VR goggles and someone on Twitter like someone who worked on it for like three and a half years was talking about all this stuff they discovered in the journalist.
It was like it seems like what they're talking about like trying to predict what you're thinking or feeling or what your eye movements mean kind of sound like massive privacy violations.
So I do.
There was a thing that pal Mickey they had to assure everyone that pal Mickey, you know, whatever data they got from the infrared, you know, it was it was an anonymous and it was random.
It doesn't know your family.
Yeah.
Well, not yet.
The TV, the phone apps and stuff.
The RFID knows everything.
Yeah.
And everybody's got your thumb prints.
Disney will sell all our information at the right price.
They haven't already.
Yeah.
They would get just general numbers from pal Mickey.
I was wondering, do we end up I was I was imagining the future beyond the year 3000 an underwater New York where a single the last year man.
I'm thinking pal Mickey who learned to love, but which was only led to a torturous existence has been wishing to be real for 1000 years.
And then the future Mecca pal Mickey's come much more.
They just look like fluid real Mickey.
They they bless it.
And all right, we've scanned your memory.
I've been here wishing to be.
I found the part of the old partner statue.
I wish it for a wall to make me real.
You're talking about daddy.
I want daddy to make me real so daddy can love me.
This is like an AI and scenario where the hyper intelligent aliens give him one day of peace.
I escaped from the flesh fair.
Mickey did you know the flesh fair is dangerous.
The band ministry tried to destroy me to town flesh fair.
I tried to find Dr. No, but he knew less than me.
I am the ultimate Disney insider.
I cut off Martin's hair and mommy got mad at me.
I think we've cycled through every sci fi movie with AI.
Every dystopian hell.
See if you can see if you can be the ultimate insider and tell whoever you're with which reference we made in each different chunk of that pal Mickey stuff.
Did you know you missed Simone Simone with the one and the all.
Ah, it's genius.
It says in pal Mickey's the biggest star in Hollywood and only you and I know that I made you up.
How Mickey like the T 1000 it's giant arm and gloves just extending into a blade and going right through you.
Run.
John Sarah run.
Yes, evil pal Mickey shows up mom from the future is no no no no he's been repr I reprogrammed him in the future.
That man he doesn't know as many facts anymore.
Pal Mickey goes back in time and when they're writing the copyright law that lap makes a copyright become public domain after 100 years he kills the lawmaker.
Yeah, there's blade hands.
Arnold holds up a pal Mickey had at one point it was my college roommate.
Well, yeah, we did it.
We did them all.
I think we covered this toy that was in the parks perfectly.
I think so.
Informatively.
It's too bad they stopped supporting it in 2009.
Oh, well, well, tell us what you think about pal Mickey.
No 2014 but also it might still work.
So take your pal Mickey didn't park.
It didn't work at Disneyland.
Huh?
It was only at Disney World.
Right.
So we're not going to be a yo ho.
This says when you buy your Disney if I if I can get a dirty pal Mickey and get it to Disney World matted for dirty pal Mickey.
Yes.
Yeah.
Rotting Comic Con Lander.
You could get a couple.
If you could get them for like 10 bucks, you should buy like 10.
And like strap them like a bayonet or no like a little bit of the thing that you know, the leader.
Thank you.
Strap the pal Mickey's around 10 pal Mickey's in a bandolier that you wear around Disney World.
Mike, you know who would really love that Disney World security when I arrived.
10 of their favorite character.
They're mascots.
OK.
Here's the thing you just put in the metal detector is giggling and vibrating.
So the plain clothes people in line have drawn arms on you.
All 10 of them are like you didn't see nothing.
Let them through.
They'll be fine.
This gremlins too.
You could have said what happens to the pal Mickey's if they don't work.
For your feet after midnight.
You guys think you're so smart with all your references.
I know more than you.
Something happens if you feed me a full head of lettuce from the toppings bar at Cosmic Rays.
Salad pal Mickey.
Yeah.
He eats your salad for you.
So you don't have to say you could save it.
You know, picky kid doesn't have to eat yucky salad.
I'll do it.
You just got to take me to the bathroom once an hour.
Pal Mickey's weakness is fiber, dietary fiber.
You got to do.
You got to help me out though.
I don't know how to go.
Hold me.
Help me.
Hold my thing down.
I'm just going in my pants.
You don't take control of yourself.
And it stinks.
Pal Mickey is the ultimate Disney insider who knows so many facts about the park.
And he poops actual poop that smells way worse than yours.
We could keep going.
I'm just going to head slightly to the door by saying you survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP club three where this is maybe not able to read anymore.
Talking about Pal Mickey for so long where you can get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
But again, caveat always, we know some stuff about theme parks and what have you,
but we'll never know as much as the ultimate Disney insider.
So your best bet is to order 10 of them on eBay, wear them around on a bayonet, get their vibrations on a bayonet, put them on.
At the end of the day, you will be struggling to get them with a bayonet.
I speared one, but there's 10 more.
There's too many.
Come back, varmints.