Forever.
Dog.
Warning! The following podcast will irritate ATV instructors, offer a detailed explanation of how to play craps,
contains spa locker hacks, and will mess you up more than two liters of a gross slushy alcohol drink.
Vegas aficionado John Gabras joins the good boys to offer Vegas survival tips on today's podcast, The Ride Sin City Nights.
Welcome to podcast The Ride Sin City Nights, a scintillating all-male review, which is hosted by, as far as the listeners know,
three absolute beefcakes.
I'm Beefcake1 Scott Gardiner, joined by Beefcake2 by Garza.
Hey, hi, how are you?
That's a Harrison Ford voice, by the way.
Of course you have to have rippling abs. How could you not?
Where else would that voice come from?
Not an 80-year-old man.
Hey, hi.
Yeah, that sounds like Harrison Ford, currently. Jason Sheridan.
Hopefully we give you a listening experience that you'll never forget.
Is that a sexy phrase?
I feel like those review shows are like, and you're never going to forget the time you have at Magic Mike or at the Luxor topless review.
That was meant to be sexy.
Oh wow, can we do it again?
We say body around here.
We don't even say the word sexy?
Yeah.
In Sin City Nights we do.
Well, look, you've got to build up to it.
You've got to build up to it.
Look, one day we'll get to an episode where we all acknowledge each other as sexual creatures, you know, but I don't think we're there.
No, we're not getting up to that episode.
I am out on that episode.
Oh shit, guys, I've got to run. I'm sorry.
I didn't realize there was that kind of show.
Okay, we're going to have to drop in from the episode.
Okay, let's do this. Shift-tags really fast.
We're asexual, okay?
That sounds more like it.
Yeah, okay.
I'm not hearing a lot of yes and from my collaborators today.
Not only yes and, if it's something I want to do.
Not acknowledging you as a sexual creature.
Let's bring it up.
Give me something I want to yes and, and only yes and.
All right, before he leaves, let's throw him in.
We cannot do a Las Vegas month.
Las Vegas month, we knew we had to have the presence of a Vegas fan and one of the funniest people around from High and Mighty and Action Boys.
It's John Gabris. Hello.
Oh, what's up? Jason, you're a sexual being.
Thanks, John. You're a sexual being too.
I mean, that's how we screen each other is just funny to do it on the pod.
Yeah.
Look, you're at the Grove as well, you sexual being.
Hinn, Barnes and Noble, my sexual being friends.
A couple of magazines, Mr. Sexual Being.
Yeah.
Buying Settlers of Catan and all the many board games that they have at the bookstore that is practically a toy and board game store nowadays.
Practically a kid, like a teen tween hangout spot.
Oh yeah.
You go in there and it's just like a bunch of kids looking at comics and manga and shit like that.
You're like, oh, this is actually kind of cool.
Anytime my wife has something to do with the Grove, I shoot to Barnes and Noble.
It's a fun little gimmick there.
Oh, sure.
That's like me with my parents anywhere.
Let me loose in that bookstore for a while.
It never changes.
Or if I'm near the Apple store, I'll go in and subscribe to High and Mighty on every iOS.
I go to each of the podcasts, go subscribe, subscribe, subscribe.
I don't know if it stays or they wipe those every night.
Or if it converts somebody who works like an Apple store employee.
Maybe they see that and like, oh, interesting.
Does that just come with it?
If this is an Apple recommend, I got to check it out.
I'll start drinking athletic greens.
My one sponsor.
It's better than better than most.
I think.
OK, so it's Sin City nights over here.
It's Sin City.
Yeah, you didn't know.
This is the, you know, the ultra sultry.
This isn't the lame old daytime podcast.
The ride you thought you knew.
Things are getting wild over here.
And so we had to pull you in on it.
And that's part of, I think, maybe a good reason to have you here and a good thing to talk to you about is like we're as we record this, we are going to Vegas.
All three of us soon.
It will have happened in the past for the listener.
But for us, it's in our future.
We've all been separately, but we've never all been together.
And I think we've got a couple of slots.
We're not there for a long time, but we're like, we don't.
We don't really know how to fill those other days.
And we're trying to think, is there a way that we can get out of our Vegas comfort zone to push it to the max a little more hit it a little harder?
And there was three guys whose comfort zones I couldn't understand less.
You guys.
Yeah, I do.
I want to be clear.
I've been uncomfortable for 37 years now.
So when I find my comfort zone, I wallow around like a pig and slop.
It's why I like being little spaces.
That's why you're in the matrix.
Pink pod go.
Finally.
Oh, you could.
My energy.
Please.
I love the major going back.
Going back in the womb is exactly where he wants to be.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I like sleep often in the fetal position.
I.
Yeah.
It's just a shame that our mothers don't grow with us, that our mothers don't become what you'd have to be like nine feet tall for us to be able to fit back in there.
Why don't moms grow to be nine feet tall so we can crawl back in?
It would be nice.
I'm up to it.
I got to go back east and rest up.
Swan dive into my mom's garage.
That's my sneakers are sticking out.
She pulls them off for me and I slide my bare feet in like Superman recharging in the sun.
This is the ideal Mitch three month vacation.
That's my go to text to him.
I'm like, are you currently breastfeeding?
Hey, I'm going to you're my only friend that I'm going to ask to do an improv show and I don't know where you live right now.
I don't even own a home.
You own a home and are never in it.
Empty most of the time.
I can't stick here.
The boys.
But yeah, we're we're hoping that you could like it by telling us some some tales of your Vegas lore.
Maybe you could inspire us to do to push it hard to go past our again, unintelligible Vegas.
What are you guys going to do there?
Is it wrestling based or you guys?
No, we're doing we're doing a show.
Oh, you're doing a live show.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're doing the pockets are a big Vegas groove blender.
You could take some stock.
You could ask us some questions to just try to gauge where we're at, what we've done.
I mean, we can share some annex to Jason and I have been to a strip club for a bachelor party at one point.
So there's that.
Now, I want to say this right now, right?
Right at the top.
I forbid you from telling the story of Jason falling asleep at the bachelor party again.
I was not in time.
I was not.
I was told on this show.
It's at least twice.
Once every two months.
We've had a handful of group conversations and I know that story.
Yes, the relatively limited window.
You've I just wanted to get the rules out in case you got tempted.
Well, I'm not a strip club guy.
That's just like one facet of this city that I'm not really into.
And previously I was always just a gambler because I came from the East Coast.
So I was going to Atlantic City as soon as I was 21, which is like if you think Vegas is gross, hit Atlantic City for a weekend and you'll be like, let's take the whole family to Los Angeles.
But over the course, like the last 10 years living out here and I went to Vegas several times from living in New York.
But after moving out here, I've gone way more frequently.
And I found that like I'm super pumped about the city and I do think anyone who doesn't like Vegas, I can make them an item that they will like.
Oh, yeah.
I just think Vegas literally has and you guys are theme park guys, but this is a theme park for like grownups.
And if you're like a foodie, you can get you.
It's going to be the Vegas version of you know what I mean?
So it's like if you love restaurants, well, all of your favorite chefs have their second or third best restaurant in Las Vegas.
Yeah, I like a restaurant that's like good opening weekend and then it kind of decays a little bit.
But still it's close.
It's pretty good enough.
Like it's fun to eat at Morimoto and you know, or you know, you can eat at the Momofuku and Cosmo and all these places that in New York and L.A. have insane lines and weights.
You can make like a 10 p.m. dinner reservation.
You know, you can make a you can eat at Wolfgang Puck restaurant like anyone, any celebrity chef.
They every hotel now has like four kind of name recognized restaurants so you can have that if you're just a drinker but not a gambler or just a party or not a gambler.
That obviously is there.
If you're a gambler, that's obviously there.
If you're show people like you like to see shows, you can see a ton of great second tier shows.
Everything is second tier.
But in a way that it's all also there.
You know what I mean?
And if you like anything that's a chain or anything that's like, you know what?
Like Bachelor Party or Bachelorette Party activities like they have all of those.
And I'm including the ones like the Topgolfs or the Dune Buggy racing or ATVs or dirt like or anything of that like group activity.
Like I feel like you can have a conference in Vegas and I know a lot of people do because there's just like a lot of activities you could do that are non casino related as well.
Yeah, yeah.
We know this is an interesting something for anyone.
And truly you could be like a like a leftist or like an absolute like QAnon gun toting freak and still find some overlap and stuff, but also find a bunch of shit that you would be into.
And dispensaries are there now too.
And like so it's got weed, it's got booze, it's got everything else too.
But you can get most of that stuff without having to text somebody named Johnny Vegas in your phone.
That's the name I have saved in my phone.
I bought drugs off of like 10 years ago and I'm always like if I ever want.
But now like I only really need weed when I go.
Only if he's growing something special.
Also, he's a CPA now.
So he's kind of out of the game.
He probably owns five dispensaries and makes more money than I could ever dream of.
Do you do you have a dispenser of choice in Vegas?
No, see, that's funny.
I have only tried like three.
Now I'm kind of braver and just bring LA weed with me on my carry on.
Yeah, I got a little cocky, but I usually what I do is, you know, find one that I haven't been to yet.
Have my Uber driver from the airport drop me off there.
Or wait for me if I can give them my I'll be like I'll give you $10 cash and you just leave the thing running while I run in there and shop.
And then you go in there, buy all your weed, because for me, I don't necessarily want to if I'm there for two nights or three nights, leave like the strip.
Yeah, yeah.
Sometimes I'll add an activity that's off strip or a restaurant that's off strip to try some shit.
But like for me, I want to like be supplied up.
I like the idea of like you put all your weed or your whatever you buy your drugs, your booze, whatever in it.
Like I like having it like in my room.
It feels very Vegas as to be like, which one of these and I like the Cosmo life hack for people because they have balconies on their rooms and they're not on their suites only or what you know.
Yeah, it's not the cheapest of the hotels, but having a balcony where you can comfortably smoke weed.
I mean, if you guys are going in August, the balcony will be a full nightmare.
Like, oh, yes, sunscreen on the plane.
But the phrase 113 degrees was uttered in the forecast this week.
And I think that's a good 99 down weekend, I think is one 18 higher.
It's like it's bonkers.
Well, these are the last few years we can go to Las Vegas.
I think so we better drop like it.
I bet you Vegas will be the first place to drop like the dome full blown air conditioned to buy a dome on top.
Well, that's the sphere is testing.
It's beta testing.
Fucking Stephen Baldwin and Paulie Shore currently living in it.
Yeah.
We're in the eyeball.
He moved to Vegas.
Oh, yeah, Paulie.
Yeah.
Well, well, that's a sword into the city before I got Paulie.
Yeah, with a top Danny Gans.
Rich little there.
That's by the way, the number one thing maybe I want to do is go see Rich Little.
I think that's a good cause that's the other thing too about Vegas that not a lot of people understand.
You can set your irony meter wherever you want and enjoy yourself.
You could slide it all the way to authentic like like and you can enjoy yourself that way and you can slide it all the way to like anthropological study of the disgusting human and like you could enjoy Vegas on a whole nother level.
Yeah.
Guys, if you want to talk about a sliding scale of irony, you guys sent me to go see the David Copperfield.
Yeah, which was hands down one of the best recommend I'm leaving my house today.
I dragged my wife Tiffany to that as well and leaving the house today.
She's like, Where are you going? I'm like, I'm going to Burbank to talk about Vegas.
Okay.
But I was like, Remember that I told you about the guys who recommend and she goes, I still don't know how tongue in cheek that show was.
And I'm like, I'm not bad news for you, babe.
It's not like, yeah, I think it itself, I think is is heartbreakingly sincere.
Yeah, at least was in its inception, but is now like devolved due to his own lack of interest and care in every step because he performed because he does 20 shows a week.
Right.
So he's just like the numbers up. Yeah.
He had like his delivery throughout the you guys like even undersold how how like wrote he is like, and then we go over here and he literally would do shit like like doing magician.
I guess I shouldn't do a silent magician and very like limp little to die.
He does just like as and like this parts were like the lights go out and you hear people like moving around and then like everything is it's like a Jurassic Park the ride like everything is kind of like ride based the thing drops from a UFO drops from the ceiling and uncaged dinosaur comes out an alien that farts root beer bubbles.
You met him you met blue 30.
I'm so thrilled that you did it. I mean, it's a it's a life chain now you know that you know now that you can be in Vegas in the future and see the little like the little bronze statue in the lobby of the little alien know like I'm in the club I know what that is.
I know who blue 32 is and they can fog the room with root beer sent when he farts which is crazy. I still don't understand. Yeah, he because there's there's this gag in it about like that where it cuts to a lady with a bottle of root beer and then she like was that in it when you were there things just slide in and out of the dude all of the all of the tricks he does all are like contingent on like you trusting that like there's no like good magician.
Good magician will do something where you're like I see like what you think might have how I did it and then I prove you like you're right. Actually, yeah, actually these rings aren't you know don't have a gap in them. But all of his stuff is like huge props and stuff and you're like that's got to be custom made like yeah, I'm not gonna you're not gonna surprise me by like and all these letters fall off and it's a message from my dad from the future. Yeah, it's all contingent on the letter being like I'm proud of you too, which is like.
A real heartbreaking moment for all of us performers who are maybe not from a family of performers who are like it felt super real when he was like and it said I'm I'm proud with your dumb magic choices David.
Well, and some of them also it's like you've done this on multiple TV specials and then you had to explain how it worked in court and you're still doing it.
Yes, yeah, big trial. Yeah, like diagrams were like which the one that got revealed was essentially like OK, so I take eight people from the audience and then a bunch of people go run run run run through a secret hallway under the theater. We like push and prod them. We shock them with tasers until they get to the other side in time. Ta-da, there's the trick. Yeah, I saw an amazing Jonathan off Broadway special RIP back in the day and he was like, I'm so proud of you.
And then I was like, all right, and now everyone just act like I teleported up here like and he's like, I'm in and post it'll look real.
You can't get us. And then I'm like, if there's a person who let you do hack shit like this should be a comedy magician. But if you're David Copperfield, your shit can shoot should be contingent on like and you keep your fucking mouth shut about what you saw down here.
So your friends don't tell your family, I will take other people that I go to. I will sit through it again to get other people to it because I and I don't think people trust me when I'm like, no, because I didn't trust you guys either. I'm like, oh, great. I'll sit. I know it sounds. Yes.
Every reason to be skeptical and he puts so much effort in, but then doesn't match it with like his gusto. Like it's like, it's so funny how like deep and serious it is, but he doesn't match it with his energy at all. He's not acting it. No, because it's like supposed to be like meeting the moment of like, oh my God, this character is dying.
The few times I've done like sketch shows where I've had to memorize a bunch of lines, his delivery is like me backstage of like, okay, tonic. All right. You know, like practice my fucking line. Like it's that exact pace.
And energy speed. You're not blowing your energy. Yeah. Okay. And remember like he's just like that and he seems old and he's got like a weird posture. Now he's got like something that happened to his neck or his traps where he kind of like doesn't like fully move the right way.
And you're like, this dude should be able to retire, like let him retire. Yeah, but it's like it's spite or something. It's like he's got something to prove and it's about crushing all the other magicians and performers. And I think it's like, yeah, like, I think you guys mentioned it.
Like it's some sort of like Guinness record for tech tickets or shows per like whatever. And he's going to just try to hold on to that, like run that number up, I guess. But when the alien is revealed and it's all like a time travel story that is also aliens.
And then there's a dinosaur and a motorcycle, like all this shit keeps happening where you're like, and it's always just like a big physical thing that he's like, how did I get this out here? And it's like, I, my dad was an IOTC stagehand.
Like, I think I know where some of this stuff comes from. Like also, and I, at one point, my wife goes, we were like pretty stoned, but she's like, look at everybody else's faces. And we just looked around and it was a 50 50 split from people going like, what the fuck is this kind of like looking at each other? And the other 50% were just like, oh my God, a UFO.
It was like, this is fucking crazy. If you get it like, that's a great split for a fuck. But that's the power of Vegas. There's so many mouth breathing freaks there that the city delivers for them. But then there's also real money there and the city delivers for them on that too. So you get to have like all of these worlds, which is fun.
And you and like, you can put your, you're right. We can set our irony dial within within something like that. There's things that we're enjoying on a kitschy level, but then the UFO shows up and you just like, oh, you're like, it's like orgasmic. You can't do it. And like, you know, I can do any amount of like, I'm going to see this weird like wing of this hotel that failed. This is a weird failed endeavor. And I'm going to go see the decay and kind of be, you know, be snarky about it. But then you pass by just the Bellagio fountains and like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, it's one of man's great achievements. You can't have irony about the Bellagio fountains and a lot of stuff like that. Yeah. You, you specifically did not spoil anything when I went to see Copperfield a few years ago. And I, when the UFO appeared, I nearly fell out of my seat because I was right. I was right under it.
Yes. Yeah. How does something truly? How does something show up that close to you without right? You don't hear it. You don't see it. Like, it's just in the rafters. Right. And then like, right.
I guess so. Yeah. Because it is kept weirdly dark in there, too. Like where you're like, clearly, like, because everything is is hidden behind some huge fake wall or something like that. It feels like. Yeah.
Even if you know, it's just a just like when you get on like the Transformers ride and Universal Studios, you know, you're just watching a screen and getting bounced around. But if you let yourself have fun with it, like you'll have fun with it, just like a haunted house. You got to like, yeah, you got to kind of bring that energy to Las Vegas a little bit. Like you got to kind of let yourself like a when in Vega, like a when in Rome, you kind of got to bring that energy of like, and also where else can you go to like a five star restaurant in like flip flops and it's.
Oh, yeah. You can just be whoever you want there, which is kind of fucked up for, you know, the average viewer. But like, it's fun to be there and just see like people. There's like, you know, fucking billionaires speaking Mandarin at one craft stable and at the other craft stable is like nine UFC wannabe guys.
Oh, yeah. With the biggest fat Tuesday, like plastic things you ever seen. Scott, you also took a photo. So there's these billboards for Copperfield kind of everywhere in L.A. There's also one in the Burbank airport. And I have seen this a million times, but you zoomed in on the photo. And again, I always fell out of my chair because there was a very tiny blue 32.
Even though I was like, oh, my God, it's been there a decade, probably longer, longer. Yeah. Yeah. So fucking rad. It's just it's this special thing that you have to. There's only one room in the world. Yeah. Go meet this friend.
And I'm so glad you met him. Only 10 people talk about it. Yeah. We're all like one of 10 people that have ever like mentioned it after seeing it is only due to the passion of Jason Waller.
Right. He specifically has spread this if he if it's not for his proselytizing, I don't think because I think most of the people who go see it forget they don't remember his name. They remember like the UFO and the dinosaur more than that.
There was this original alien character with a voice of an animaniac doing comedy and sex jokes, clearly trying to ride off like Grogu popularity.
Like, you know, it feels like it was before. Before. This is like 10 years in the making. It's been going for so long. Different name.
It was Attila the Hug before it was blue 32. Blue 32 is so funny, too, because it's like a football.
Right. 32 is like all you could think about. Yeah. He maybe all I could think about, you know, his company might be excluded.
Yeah, yeah, it's true. You know, we don't think about football much. I understood that in context, but I don't know other than that what it means or wouldn't know what to do with the phrase football.
Yeah, I know there are huddles. Yes. Very weird theatrical experience to seeing like a theater show.
There's a tiny alien statue outside their slot machines 20 feet away and then emeralds fish house and really got these fish is steps away.
Which is good. That was good. It's at the MGM. It's kind of like not one of the fancier hotels now. Right.
Like, it's like the wind and the on Cosmo and on and are kind of the fancier hotels now.
I guess so. Yeah, it's very is. So it does seem to like like try to step it up in terms of elegance and five star.
Yeah, and when you see him a little more populist. Yeah. When you start looking at the fucking like the M life casinos and whoever like these parent company casinos are like whatever brand that they're all part of for like points or whatever.
You see like the built in tears of someone owns the Cosmo and the Excalibur and like two hotels in between.
You know what I mean? Like you got to cover the spread. They know to diversify their audiences.
And so here are a list of things I always try to do when I go to Vegas, but they fit. They are like slottable wherever.
And like so I always want to go to one baller meal, like whether that means fun steakhouse, you know, something that is like dumb Vegas meal.
I want to do one buffet trip and this all contingent on like if you're there for two nights, you don't really want to do too much food stuff.
But like one buffet trip, the wicked spoon at the Cosmo or the Caesar's Buffet, which I think is called Bacchanalia, which is a really fun one, too.
And you're like, you know, you're paying like sixty five dollars for lunch or whatever.
So just be ready to go in there and like, you know, aim to get like be hung over or be high or, you know, get your money's worth a spa day.
Now, oh, always a spa day. Usually I do is the spot every single day, but not like with a treatment.
I just get a day pass and do a little sauna, steam room, hot tub, cold plunge, depending on what the hotel has.
Cosmo doesn't have a cold plunge, unfortunately. But the so for me, that is like one part recovery, one part.
When I look back at the 72 hours and I was in Vegas, I'm like I did like three health adjacent things for myself.
And then this is where you're going to learn a lot about my internal logic.
I could pay fifty five dollars for a day pass to the spa. Go down.
Also, life hack. If you get there well before check in or you have a flight well after check in the lockers in the spa can fit your suitcase.
So for fifty five dollars, you throw all your shit down there.
You can go to the casino for the day and then go take a shower and a spa and everything before you go home or before you even check in.
That's good. That's like a fun way to extend it without having to get another night at the hotel.
Also, every hotel has like for fifty dollars extra, like a way later check out.
Like if you're especially if you're not checking out on like a Friday or Saturday, you can get like a two p.m.
Check out for fifty bucks if you need like, you know, to shit in your hotel room.
It's usually mine. I'm like, I don't want to do this at the airport.
Any amount of money.
We we had a great experience last year where we we kept seeing the same guy at the check in desk every time we would need like, oh, hey, this key's not working or like, oh, can we get this or that?
And then the day before we were like, hey, could we get a late check out?
We have like our flights not until the late afternoon.
And he he kind of he waved the like the feet and he was like, sure.
How about a two p.m.? We're like, oh, my God, I didn't know you could check out that.
And then he's like, I'll just make sure I know you had that sink issue.
Like he's like winking at us.
And it was solely because we were like talk to him and we're friendly with him.
Yeah. And off what Jason's saying here, I think Vegas is maybe the last bastion of corporate wiggle room.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Every other business is like everyone runs it so fucking tight.
Everyone so hard. They are a bot that you're dealing with online or whatever.
But they go by the rules so hard.
It used to be back in the day, someone who had job security would be like, look, I'm supposed to charge you.
But look, if you pay parts, you're not supposed to like you're a loyal customer.
Vegas is like the last remaining bastion of that, even outside of like the official like,
oh, you gambled enough to have a comped meal or free.
They have like Daniel Van Kirk, another podcaster.
He on my podcast on high mighty said, I take out twenty dollars when I check in.
I go, if there's any upgrades available, I'd love.
And he said it has worked for him 100 percent of the time.
He said one time the person was like, I'm sorry, we just have nothing.
And he like didn't take the 20.
And Daniel was like, no, you can you looked you can have the 20.
Like I put it out there.
And he said otherwise, he's gotten upgraded to a suite every single time.
The twenty dollar trick. Yeah.
The this is documented online.
You hand them your ID and a credit card and you sandwich a 20 between them.
And you ask like if there's any upgrades available, that'd be great.
I still find it hard to believe you're giving away 20 bucks.
I tried this for the first time last year.
And this very nice guy who is checking us in
was having issues with his computer, so never looked up.
Oh, so he never like missed the bill.
Missed the bill. Like he missed the bill.
For the barista to look back before you drop the dollar in.
She's messing with the machine.
I am tipping you. Wait, wait, wait. Look up. Look up. See. OK.
I'm not a piece of shit.
Yeah. Fly or a bird in the room.
It's like it's really stressed, like banging on it.
Like something is going horribly wrong.
Like this is the worst part of the day.
And it's like, please, I just want you to know I'm a good person.
Did he take the money, though? No.
OK, so you didn't take them.
I put it sandwiched. How did he not take it?
Yeah. Because you never have to look at your ID and stuff anyway.
He just grabbed the card and ran the card.
He just never took it.
I think he was pretending he didn't see it.
I mean, he could have been he was also training a guy who's like,
it's my first. Oh, there's no way he's going to take the 20.
Yeah. So that's the other thing.
He didn't see. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So probably didn't see it.
But it's like the last place where if you call down and like, yeah,
they are hospitable there, especially at the nicer casinos.
And I should talk, I only mostly stay at the Cosmo for the balcony thing
or the Venetian, which I like, because it also it has like
the weird mall attached to it that has a bunch of restaurants,
but also has only sweets, which is kind of cool.
You know, they all have like the little living room attached.
And it's not like much more than another room.
It's like because that's that's their standard is like a king size bed
and like a little living room.
Those rooms kind of like I thought about staying there and I'm not.
But are those rooms kind of like silly, fake Italy?
There's it like, yes, little flourishes, little beds, a little gaudy at times.
And then the mall has the gondola that runs through it,
like a river that runs through and you could take a gondola.
I never done that goes all the way outside.
And then the ceiling is painted with like blue and with clouds in the mall,
which is also really funny.
We were saying in another episode, indoor skies.
I like all of those in Vegas.
Yeah. Caesar's shops.
I love is it planet Hollywood as that whatever that mall is,
I think, because indoor miracle mile. Yeah. OK.
This is only tangential.
No, is the sports store where Pete Rose is always signing?
Is that in Caesar's?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I do not know, but this sounds awesome.
There's a sports store every time I'm in Vegas.
And I feel like it's by Caesar's that it's always there's a thing outside.
It says Pete Rose signing.
And I go, this is five, like the fifth time.
That's so right. I don't know about it, but I got to go.
Mike has pulled out recently some of the most fascinating
P. Rose today.
Rich little
I was in a sea.
Secure. Yeah, no, they're not obscure.
It's just an interesting more.
We're missing the Morris Day in the Times show by a few days.
It's just such an interesting.
That's the big thing about Vegas.
It's an interesting cast of character.
Yeah, I saw Purple Rain, our EIG.
I've also seen this show. Yeah.
And it was fine.
But the guy who is playing Prince up there got angry
that no one was like enjoying it as much.
Yeah. How could he tell?
There was just little not enough applause.
There was just not enough people in there either.
It was like, you know, and it was just like a weird vibe.
The person I went with just happened to have like like Prince and we're
for their birthday and we're like, all right, we'll go to this.
And that's always fun, too, is just like agreeing to someone else's itinerary
for a couple of things. You're like, I would never do this at a Vegas.
For so Spa Day, that that that
some sort of show of some sort, whether it is like a Copperfield
or even like one of the Cirques or something.
Oh, yeah. Do you like us?
I haven't done a Cirque in many years.
They're like fine.
It's like it's like it's really like just watching a screensaver
with your friends in like a weird way.
And I'm impressed by just like, wow, this theater is very impressive.
The sound. Wow. The production.
Oh, that's a bouncy part of the floor.
You know, like, yeah, stupid, like just been hard to build.
If only Kelsey Grammer had fallen on that one day.
It'll be OK. Pop right back up.
The P.
Rose's site autograph schedule, it's he's in Mandalay Bay
and MGM Grand at a place called Art of Music in both places.
I don't know why it's called Art of Music.
Wait, Mandalay Bay and what? And MGM Grand.
They might be MGM Grand, Mandalay Bay and Luxor might all be connected
by the tram, so it might be like an in-between situation.
Oh, yeah, there's a straight line.
It's Mandalay Bay Luxor Excalibur Excalibur.
And then further up, it's Park MGM Aria
Bellagio.
Aria is another one of the like fan, like nicer hotels to.
Yeah. The theme of Aria is glass and metal. Yeah.
That is I've been there a few times and I have tried to like,
what is that?
Like, what is the and like some large installation art?
Yeah. The wind is very colorful, which is kind of rad to be in
because Steve Wynn, wonderful guy, great, great fan.
Always on the lookout for humanity.
He's like losing his eyesight.
So everything has to be like in super.
He makes them make everything intense color.
So it does have a fun by like byproduct of being a man.
It's like all neon and like bright colors and shit.
That's kind of a fun one to be in.
Yeah. Wow.
Mike and I walked through that once and they have a lot of the
what's the guy that's a balloon, the metal balloon.
Jeff Koons, they have so much Jeff Koons in the wind.
Yeah. Did they was Koons make an appearance in the Cross the Spiderverse, right?
Like, yeah. Or am I? Oh, I don't.
I haven't seen anyone yet. Whoa.
None of us. Yeah.
I have not been to the movies much.
I lost a huge bet.
Oh, yeah. You're you bet.
Mitch wouldn't have a would be would not be the first one to have a house
and that we had already seen Spiderverse.
Man, that parlay did not come in. Absolutely not.
No. If you're if I'm there for an extended period of time, I like to hit old Vegas,
especially if I'm there with people who never go.
I'm like, let's go to the old strip.
And because it's got a half domed there, like it's got like a domed
ceiling area to with less.
But it's like a LED screen.
So there's stuff going on on top.
And also that's the place to have like play five dollar craps
in a place where you think they're ripping you off or like a great spot
for like those giant jungle juice, necklace, drinks and shit like that.
I always try to have one, you know, Marty Gra adjacent consumption
like moment where I'm like, all right, guys, I'm buying.
And especially if it's a bachelor party, I'm like, I'm putting my card down
and I'm buying 10 huge frosies.
I'm going to force this upon people.
And yeah, that's a funny duality, too, that you can like drink the finest drinks.
You can drink at such a high level or just like a
packet of slum at a place or you can have like this is paint thinner and ice.
Do you like do you like that drunk as opposed to is there something from the
the trash drunk or is it just a ticket to to vomit?
It's gross.
And I and I even drink way less than I ever did before, especially in Las
Vegas, especially with like the proliferation of cannabis in Vegas.
But there's something about like I'm like I have camp counselor energy a little bit.
And it's like, wouldn't it be fun if all four of us had giant stupid drinks?
And then you regret that instantly.
Like just sits.
Usually what happens is you drink like a quarter of it,
go up to the room to barf shit or like, you know, change the vibe in some way.
Put it down on your dresser.
Go about your day.
Come back at night.
And it's just like condensation sweat and all the ingredients have like separated
in a weird way. And it's and you're like, I can't believe I almost drank.
And then you're like barfing while you pour it down your sink drain.
My my girlfriend and I have been to Vegas every year since 2020.
Like we squeezed in a trip in end of February 2020.
And that first trip I was like, well, I'm just going to try the slushy drinks
because it's so hot and it's so like even in February, it's hot.
And, you know, I want to cool down and stuff.
And I just spent most of the trip very bloated, like that much.
I'm like, I'm going to go to Vegas.
I'm going to go to Vegas.
The trip very bloated, like that much ice and slush and corn syrup.
I was just like, yeah, for days, I was like the hydration of the air.
You're like hands are like Mickey Mouse.
My hands are destroyed.
My hands are like totally dry.
When the ring explodes off at the.
What do you think of that?
Because this this seems this is the yard.
Your alcohol taste is a colorful slush.
Yeah, it's fun. I like the I like doing it, but it's
there's no way you're drinking all of it.
So I like they have a smaller one at the Taco Bell Cantina, I feel like.
That's that's one I have not hit yet.
Yeah, I want and I want to I've never been to any Taco Bell.
Oh, because it's one of Hollywood Boulevard.
I know. I know. I got to check that out.
That seems like a place we all want to be actively on Hollywood Boulevard.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What nice don't we spend on a whole
wandering Hollywood Boulevard.
Gene went to the one in Times Square
when we were there for the New York show and immediately saw a fight.
Like we had a fight going on when I was there, too.
There were like we was like scared.
It was a little scary. Yeah.
Well, it's nice to know there's a establishment out there
where there is always a fight to watch. Yeah. Guaranteed.
Yeah. No, you don't want to be in Vegas on a big UFC weekend.
It changes the tone a little bit.
You know, I mean, like it's just a little more masculine than you want it to be there.
It's kind of peak masculinity there to begin with.
But like it used to be like feel like old school masculinity, like brandy cigars,
like wealthy fat guy, wealthy fat tan guy masculinity.
Then like everyone now it gets like it's like, oh, shit, there's so many like
Ed Hardy shirt guys now.
And there's like and still even like trends that you thought died in 2005.
Oh, my God. Driving today.
I know, dude. It's crazy.
Tucked in tank tops to jean shorts and shit.
And the guys making like twenty five hundred dollar bets.
And you're like, I do not know your life, man.
How do I classify you?
Douchebag from the past.
We in OK, in terms of like
masculine energy in Vegas and something else you mentioned
you've done is the gun range.
I did that crazy automatic gun range.
You can fire almost anything.
I shot in a belt fed M60 into a target like like the Rambo gun.
Oh, my God. And I'm I am very anti guns.
I think only movies should have them.
Yeah, yeah. But I am a fan of action movies.
So and this is crazy.
The weekend I was there was a Friends bachelor party.
He's like, I want to go shoot guns at that crazy range.
And like we're like 10 guys, four guys were like, no, thank you.
Ten L.A. guys and six of us were like, yeah, I'll go.
And I went had a blast.
I shot an M16. I shot a 12 gauge.
I shot a big giant like Magnum revolver, which like I'm 300 pounds.
And that hurt my elbow.
I'm like in movies like women, like 80 pound women are shooting two of them
or whatever.
Yeah, I'm like almost blow my fucking head off.
Just like trying to hold it.
It was crazy. It wasn't until.
I was there a very specific weekend for this bachelor party.
We're flying home on Sunday and we all landed to a bunch of texts
and calls from our loved ones because it was the night of that crazy
guy in the hotel.
Yeah, the guy who shot like the country, right?
The country festival shot it up and we had all posted
Instagrams of us tagging like Las Vegas, holding machine guns and shit like that.
And we were like the bachelor party.
Texas, like everyone take down your shit, take that shit right now.
People are dying because everyone was texting us to be like, are you OK?
Is that where you guys were?
And we're like, no, we were not.
We were the L.A. bachelor party.
We were not there for that. We were there for we did shoot guns.
And it was just crazy.
And then, you know, if the proliferation of shootings,
public shootings and mass shootings and stuff, I had the moment.
I'm like, what would have stopped someone from just like turning to the right
in this gun range and spraying?
This is my problem with doing this.
And then all of a sudden I was like, oh, I never thought about that previously.
And now it's in my head and ours, too.
I guess we'll cross that off the list.
Yeah, that is anyone can turn. That's true.
It's it's kind of a scary situation.
I've done a lot of weird off strip stuff there because I've gone to so many bachelor
parties. I like to joke, you know, women like there's like the expression
always the bride's maid, never the bride.
But I'm always at the bachelor party, never in a tux.
Like I never get groomsman level.
No one wants me in photos like with their wife, but everyone wants me
in Vegas with them for four nights.
So I'm fine with that.
But like I did ATVs there, which was kind of rad, like riding around.
But the dude who took us on the tour was super angry that all of us kept like
our bikes kept stalling because we just didn't know what we were doing.
And can you start mine again?
He's like, you mother fuck, fuck, god damn mother.
Starting our shit up and we're all kind of like looking at each other.
And one of the guy, the bachelor party was I didn't even go to this guy's wedding,
but he invited me to his bachelor party.
They want you there for the sin, but not the matrimony.
Yeah. And I know for that, like, I don't need to fucking write a two hundred dollar
check and like dance with your fucking cousin or whatever.
So this guy is like the groom is a lawyer and on the drive home, he's like, hey,
didn't I hear one of you guys is a lawyer?
And he's like, oh, yeah, I am.
He's like, I got a quick law question for you.
I walked in on my wife, fucking another guy,
went and got my gun from the car, and when I came back to shoot him,
he shot me in the back.
Can I sue him? We were like, oh,
and that's just a small business owner in Las Vegas has a story like that.
Like, wow, did anyone have the answer?
What was the answer?
No, the answer was, uh, yeah, well,
like, well, this is our hotel right here.
Get out, get out, get out, get out, but tip them, tip them, tip them.
I was going to say I did not think that was some New York improvisers
asking that question.
You would ask like 200 follow ups. Yeah.
Another cool thing I did there was recently I did the Meow Wolf Omega Mart.
Let's talk about this.
I see we're deciding if that's something we should make time for or not.
Yeah, it's not a huge, not super far off strip.
It's like a 10 minute ride from most of the strip. And, um,
it was really fun.
And I think me and Tiff were in and out in like three hours on like a weekday.
And we had a, we had a blast. It's really fucking weird.
And I think like comedy heads would like it even more,
especially like if you're like world building at all, because it's like,
the entire Mart is like everything you can,
you can buy stuff there and everything is like a funny tongue in cheek,
like item in some way, or like the ad is weird or it's like, you know,
something that we were like, and then you're like, this is kind of cool.
And then you like go through the butcher shop and you're in like a, you know,
10,000 square foot fucking a huge loft space.
And it's like multi-floored all kinds of everything is fully interactive.
Any screen is playing something that is like, like,
like a video game where you're like,
can click on every single thing and read every single thing.
And it all kind of has connectivity. It's all that. And then you're in there,
you know, like if you're like me,
you're eat some edibles and you just wander around looking at shit.
But there are like kids having a blast. They're like,
it's like for everyone in a weird way, cause it is just spectacle.
Or you can like dive down and be like,
I think we're supposed to go to this room next to determine what happened with
the laboratory experiment. Like, or you can just,
there's a story to it though. Here's a plot you can follow,
but you can do it a little more. Just wander around.
And I don't know how much like, like there's a strict narrative direction,
but it is sort of like this room maybe think made us think we should keep our eye
out for this room when we find it and stuff like that. Okay. And it was,
and it was way cooler than I even thought it was going to be. I thought,
I was like, oh, this will be like, cause I was always intrigued by it.
I guess the originals in New Mexico and George R. R. Martin, well,
helped finance these guys for a while because he's a New Mexico guy. And,
I was like, oh yeah, let's, let's do it.
And then I was truly impressed. Like it is also like,
cause there's no like human interaction, you know what I mean? So it's like you,
and I know you guys are theme park guys. I'm not personally with like,
the person who's like, alas, welcome. You know, like there's none of that.
It's sort of like you're on your own pace.
I like psychos wandering around there. Like obviously just like people go and like,
like I'm tripping balls and you have to engage with me now. But otherwise it was,
I thought that was really rad and, and it's in like a,
the Meow Wolf's in like a kind of,
it's called like area 55 or some kind of weird complex.
Yeah. There's a couple of bars, there's acts throwing, there's drinks,
there's some like other shit to do there too.
Is that where that heart attack grill is? No, that's on the old strip.
That's the other one. That's Fremont.
Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Sorry. Sorry. And I think you can eat there for free.
I think they raised the weight. It used to be like over 300 and now I think it's
like three 25, 300 not good enough because like too many people in America are
now over 300 or something. Especially Vegas. Yeah.
Most of them are in Las Vegas.
Vegas is where I feel like a fucking, like you talk about the joke,
like I'm in LA six, but I'm a Vegas fucking body.
I'm a Vegas Olympic fucking swimmer.
Yeah. There was the talk of we were,
we were figuring out venues for our live show and Mike,
you checked one out and I think did not really look at it very hard and no,
send it to me. It was in neon Opulence,
which I went to once and just past neon Opulence. It was,
it was like night of the living dead. Just like, I like,
you could just see silhouettes and it's just bodies like staggering through the
day and it felt like there was mist and like, I'm just,
I don't want to know whatever is happening there and why they are this way.
And that is where the heart attractor is. Yes. Yeah.
And then, but then I looked at where you sent and it was,
if it was a venue that had a giant writable penis,
I was part of this facility. Yeah.
I mean that's fine to do.
We could have done the whole show while writing, taking turns writing a big penis.
I feel comfortable getting on that. It's like a, it's a mechanical bowl,
but it's a big penis. Yes. Yeah. I wasn't arguing otherwise. Yeah.
I'm just saying I would do it. Oh, that's what it is. I'm in.
It actually comes.
Sounds like the confidence of a sexual being, a man in touch with the spirit of
Eros. Jason, thank you for seeing me as a sexual being.
I just see a couple of sexual beings recognizing each other here and it's kind
of beautiful, man. Yeah. Nice. Nice. Nice. All right.
I guess I'm on the outside of it. Maybe I need to come on in brother.
There's room on the cat. I was going to say the water's warm, but I don't want to,
I don't know. Yeah. Kind of makes it worse. Makes 10 times worse.
Let's get that back to a single entendre, please.
I speaking of Vegas shootings, I was there one time with friends,
just going out, just having dinner at this fancy like a steakhouse in the MGM.
I think it was, if the name comes to me, I'll throw it out there.
Cause it was, the food was fucking bomb.
But I, first time it's ever happened to me,
waiter came over and was like, please get up and leave the restaurant right now.
And every time we look around and someone like flicks the lights and it's like
everyone up and out of here. And we were like, what's going on? They're like,
and you hear whispers like there was a shooting on the strip. There's a shoot.
And it's all over the place. We have to evacuate a restaurant.
We're all like women in high heels and a man and all dressed up,
do she running through like the back tunnels behind the casino and a restaurant
out into a parking lot. And we're like running to the street.
And then when we like run to the street, we see people running the other way.
No one knows what's going on. It's all, and this may be like, you know,
a Psyop deep fake cover story.
But apparently what happened is someone broke a glass door with like a hammer
or slamming or throwing something at it.
And that went over security as a shooting at a fucking different hotel.
But so me and me and some friends, Dan,
Gregor and some Jack Dolgen and our partners all had to leave.
And then we didn't want to go back on the strip or take an Uber or anything.
So we went into the MGM and just like went up in an elevator to the first floor.
We can get off without a key.
I'm like the eighth floor and just went down by the stairwell and like hung out
there for like an hour and a half. And like,
and like it was a really intense like moment. Like,
and I don't want to tell other people's stories,
but Dan was in New York city on nine 11, like as a freshman in college,
or sophomore in college,
and he had just had his kid and was like without his wife. And he was like,
like that was like, you know, it was impossible to laugh about that.
And we eventually, as we reconnected with society and like went back to our hotel,
we went down first time I've ever seen a casino closed. We went downstairs.
It was just not, sorry. The casino is not open right now.
And people were telling us stories. They were in the restaurant, the Cosmo,
and someone people were flipping over the dining room tables and hiding behind
them for cover and shit.
And this was happening at like eight hotels simultaneously, but zero,
only one of them was where the door was broken and allegedly no shooter
whatsoever. Yeah.
And that's all anyone was talking about for the whole weekend.
You would just be at the craft stable and someone's like,
were you here last night? And you're like, yeah. And they were like,
what'd you do? We hit out on the eighth floor. You know,
we were at this restaurant. They told us to leave.
It was an enormous delicious steak dinner that we walked out on the bill.
Okay. Well, there's a bright side to everything.
When we went back for a friend's birthday,
we went back to that steak house the weekend of purple rain and we found our
waiter and tipped him cash. We were like, we're not going to pay for the guy.
Cause he was such a, he was like in the Vegas hospitality way.
He had like our Jack had had him as a waiter before and we requested his
section and he was so good to us.
And we were about to drop like a thousand dollars cause we were just like
ordering oysters and bourbon and all this shit. We were like,
totally over the top and then didn't pay for it. So we're like,
we got to give this guy a couple hundred bucks.
Oh great. Yeah.
A lot of weird news stories out of Vegas lately, multiple cashier
robberies, some various casinos, some on the strip of like,
you know, somewhere put the money in the bag. Others were like, hi,
I'm the brother of the owner. And if you could just give me a,
like $50,000 he's asking for and like got away with it.
Some try that.
Someone sandwiched in between two room keys, please.
I'm the brother of the guy who owns this place. Someone,
uh,
Jason Caesar.
So I, I, I don't know the conclusion of the story,
but someone barricaded themselves in a hotel room in Caesar's and they like
evacuated their massive pool deck and stuff.
I saw that he was throwing furniture out the window.
Yeah. Yeah.
30 something floor or some shit.
Yeah. So this is one. Wow. Wow.
Always something in that city.
Something positive that's happening when we're there.
And I didn't tell you guys this yet, but I'm going to reveal it now. Oh boy.
There are some,
a very important sporting event tapings happening when we're going to be there
next weekend. And of course I'm talking about the return of slam ball slam ball.
My car trampoline basketball league sponsored by ACL surgeons.
It's not good for your ankles. There's no way it is.
The only league sponsored by orthopedic surgeons. I'm like,
we're going to print money off this fucking job.
Slam ball is returning and is taping in Las Vegas the weekend.
We're going to be there. I think three days.
What do you think is the degree of hassle of attending the slam ball tape?
What is the time commitment? I mean, I, I, I've never seen slam ball in person.
I've been accidentally at universal studios to see slam ball. Uh,
and I did last about 15 minutes. Okay.
Kind of same standing outside that weird like bush area.
When you know the guy who created slam ball, maybe you could send an email.
Ooh, what are you talking about?
I know the man who created slam ball,
I'm his brother.
That's my middle name.
Slam Carlson would be a good fucking heal. Yeah, that'd be great.
You already have, you're already Mr. Mike fisto, which is a reference.
Yeah. Bono's evil character.
Oh, that's where he's a little devil,
but there's no reason you can't expand your lineup of heal persona.
Yeah. Full cactus, Jack. Uh, mankind. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They could all show up in one episode, just like, uh, Mick Foley. Yeah.
All of his guys showed up in one Royal Rumble. He came out three times.
Yeah. So fun. That's like the appeal.
That's like what the definition of why wrestling rules. Yes.
This guy's back out, but now he's a hippie.
He changed his t-shirt.
He's clearly more tired than everybody else. Triple H selling.
When, when cactus Jack came back, Mick Foley is cutting a promo and he goes,
I'm not going to face you. Basically.
There's a different guy that's going to face you.
And he opens up his shirt to show cactus Jack shirt and triple H sells it as if
he's seen a ghost. It's the same man.
So it's just a tie dye t-shirt.
I was in the audience and lost my mind. Oh, cause cactus Jack is more violent.
He's scary. Very violent. Yes. Even though all of his matches were violent.
Yeah. You know, the other guy wears like a BDSM mask and puts a sock down your
throat. He's the less violent one than the guy in the tie dye t-shirt. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh, speaking of sporting events,
I've now gone to two different, uh,
professional sporting events in Vegas and enjoyed myself at both.
I saw a summer league and I'm not a basketball fan,
but I went for a friend's bachelor party that was to see summer league,
which I guess is like NBA potential people playing in like, uh,
and that was kind of fun, kind of come and go as you please.
Sort of two days of tickets kind of situation.
And another time I went to go see the Vegas golden Knights play the New York
Islanders, my old favorite hockey. Wow. Okay.
And I don't really follow hockey anymore,
but I happened to be going for with some Long Island guys who were there and
they were like, we're going to get tickets to the Islander game.
And then I was like, Oh, that'd be fun. I've never done something like that.
And then it's really cool. You can walk to like,
there's that area called like the park, the park. Yeah. Yeah.
Which is kind of like an open air bar strip area.
Places smoke weed. Yeah. Yeah. Go over and get in the park, baby. Yeah.
That's the Washington square park of Vegas.
Maybe we're man offers you a hit off a blunt and they start selling you.
It's like, yeah, we're growing the original strains.
The ones that were kind of grown out.
Do you want some of this? And it's like 2021 and you're like, no,
I don't want to share that. But thank you so much. Keep the lighter,
keep the lighter friend.
But that was really fun to just be like, walk to a sporting event. Uh,
this fall I intend to go see the giants. My,
the team I do actually follow and support the New York giants. Uh,
they're playing at, uh, Vegas. So I'm going to go to a golden night or whatever.
There the Raiders Raiders. Yeah. Right. Right. Um, isn't there some insane,
didn't the Vegas golden nights open with some ceremony that I know we were
alerted to this because we,
we did an episode where we talked about how the mighty ducks, uh,
started their entire existence.
They had like a really bizarre irritating opening ceremony where like a
big, a big duck with a mask flew in a while like,
and then there was a guy named ice man who pumped up there when it was just like,
just a guy in a silver suit and silver makeup pumped up the, did you,
do you have any memory of that? I feel like the Vegas,
I know about this. Well, no, it was,
I know about the nicer way because the golden nights were an original,
like they didn't come from anywhere. They started in Vegas.
Their first game was pretty soon after the Mandalay Bay shooting and the
captain of the team was a Las Vegas, uh, local. And, and they,
they put together like a very tasteful tribute and everything.
So like immediately got the town on board for the team. So, uh,
the locals are really big fans of the hockey team and they just like went wild
when they won the Stanley cup this year.
Oh, that's so fucking rad. Yeah.
It's fun to go because hockey is one of the fun live sports too. You know,
I mean like it's just like very manageable to watch and like kind of like,
uh, a little smaller of a ring, you know what I mean?
So it's like the volume and it feels more intense in there. Uh,
so I want to go for a giants game.
And another thing I never did because I had this scheduled for March 13th,
2020, um, was the NCAA tournament.
And it's not played in Vegas, but it lets you bet, you know,
you can bet on 64 games on one day, you know, like you can really have fun.
There's always some sports bets. You can get some crazy parlays going,
and there's always games on TV to like, cause that's a big part of,
I should say part of my Vegas, uh, uh, strategy too,
is I lay sports bets right when I arrive too.
And that's sort of like my fake savings account where it's like,
so when I lose all my money, it's like, well,
I still have $400 up in the air for on the, on games this weekend.
So, and then like that gives you something to be like, Oh,
I'm losing at the craps table. It's like, Oh, well, the chargers game is on.
Let me go sit down and have a beer and breathe and hope that the chargers, uh,
get hit the over or whatever, you know? Um,
so that adds like a layer to my entire trip too. And, and, uh,
I go with a recurring group of guys, a lot of people, mutual friends of ours.
We go, we're all married men in our forties. So like,
our Vegas, but who are all gambling guys.
So our Vegas trips are very specific and it's like,
the texts are like who's landing first.
I won't land in time to make the 4pm bets. Can you,
so there's just like Venmo's shooting around like crazy and shit like that.
Yeah. I, so I have some gambling questions. Um, uh,
remind me what your game of choices is that roulette or crap? It's craps.
And how do I play that?
Craps and now give us something you could Google.
Is this something I should do on strip or I should go to like Ellis Island or
like Fremont or something. Uh, Ellis Island, you are Jason Schaer.
Your name shortened that Ellis Island is a casino with a microbrewery just behind
the strip. Just off the scene. That's fucking rad. I'll take a look at that.
Um, it's fun to go to a place that's cheap because if you're there on the
weekend, no table at like any hotel is going to be below 15, no less.
Potentially not even below 25. And you want a little bit more,
uh, craps is sort of like seems complicated at,
but you can play it in like the least complicated way.
You just bet that pass line and on the first role,
which is called the come out role. If the roller rolls a seven or 11,
you automatically win whatever you bet on the pass line. So the minimum,
usually, so it's 10 bucks, whatever. Uh, if they roll a two, three or 12,
that's called crapping out.
You lose whatever you bet on the pass line and all of the other numbers four,
five, six, eight, nine, 10 are called,
uh, then that point moves to that,
which means now the roller is rolling their dice until they hit that number
again and you win your pass line bet.
Now this is where seven becomes the bad number seven is.
And so there's some like lore around seven.
You don't say the number out loud at the table.
That's like one of the things you don't say seven, like they'll say, Ooh,
like the only the croupier or whatever stick man will go like seven craps,
but you never say like no seven or like, Oh, I hope he rolls a set.
Like just don't say it out loud because craps is one of the few games where if
everyone's betting the pass line,
you're all actually in it together and rooting from the same outcome. Oh, sure.
So like that's the appeal of the game that got me the first time is that when
someone rolls an 11 on the come out bet, which is called a yo, everybody wins.
And that's exciting to be at a table where everybody wins.
Even in blackjack, if the dealer busts,
you may have also busted or someone may have hit at the wrong time and fucked
your cards up. Craps just has that positive vibe.
And so the only basic skill I'll give you is once you're betting on the pass
line and once the point is set. So the point is at four, they put them,
they call it the button. The button is on four and you're waiting for the,
uh, the roller can roll anything but four or seven and it does not affect
your life.
Obviously there are people placing other bets, like maybe a heart and that,
you can just forget about that for your first time playing the best odds in the
casino are your backup bet,
which is the bet you put behind your pass line bet once the button is set.
So the, uh, pass line pays one to one. You put $10 out there.
They roll a seven or 11 on the come out bet. You get $10. You put $10 out there.
The buttons on the four, they roll a four again. Yay. Everyone wins.
They hit the button. You get $10 on that.
But if you can put $10 after the point is set behind your pass line bet,
that's called backing up your bet. That gets better than one to one odds.
Uh, and the odds vary between the four, five, six, eight, nine, and 10.
So like, uh, that's the, where you juice the odds. So then,
and you could put up to three, four or five X that bet that you have.
So you can have a $10 pass line bet. The button lands on a six.
You could put $50 in the backup and if they hit the six, you win your $10.
And then you win like 78 on the 50 or something rather than 50.
So that's like the bet you want to get to,
but that'll get you hanging out at the table.
And then that's how you really learn crabs. Okay.
It's just being at the table, being present,
slowly losing pass line bets and slowly and hopefully hitting some stuff.
And then you start to see, uh, on the hop bets, which are one time bets,
like I bet a yo on the hop, they're going to roll 11 on the hop, uh,
hard ways, which are doubles like 55, 33,
44 are eight the hard way, 10 the hard way, six the hard way combats,
which is like a secondary pass line. Once the button has been established,
the field bets, which are,
so that's an easy bet to make too because it just lists like these are the
numbers. If they come up, you win. If two comes up, you win double.
If 12 comes up, you win triple. But the famous craps expression is only farmers
make money in the field. Like you don't bet on the field. Yeah.
So there's so much shit going on and everyone plays differently.
Usually there's like a six foot eight person of color who's betting on the
don't pass line and is in a leather jacket no matter how.
And it's just like straight up challenging the table to be like the don't pass
line is I'm betting you all lose. And they're like,
and they're usually just a person who's so intimidating in a way that no one says
anything. And he's like, okay, whatever you say, tell me. Yeah.
Yeah. Like it's always just a giant person. And it like, with like,
like style that doesn't match the climate or something like that,
where you're like, it's too hot to be dressed like that,
but that makes you scarier or something like they're in like a leather duster or
something and it's 110 degrees and you're like, fuck, so don't be that person.
But that's the way you get at the crash table. And Jason,
if you don't get to do it on this trip, the next time I go,
I will line my trip up with you to,
cause I've taught people craps before. It's like,
I learned from a college roommates Jordanian father who like was like a crazy
like all cash business guy.
And like one of those dudes who I now recognize the type of like gotta lose some
cash at the casino in order to not have the IRS in my house or whatever.
So like it's fun. Like I learned from a dude like that. It was like, yeah,
Gabris, I'm not going to do his voice. Whoops. Here, Gabris, here's like,
here's a hundred dollars cash. And you're like a 21 year old college kid,
you have a hundred dollars in AC and you're like, Oh my God. And he's like,
bet this, bet this, bet this. And I like learned the game from him.
And I brought, I brought that energy that that was 20 years ago that I learned
that. And this was passed down. This was an oral history.
And now I have my own like a combat strategy that I do that, uh,
any one of my friends would say never works.
Like, man, we were rolling good for awhile. How'd you do Gabris? I lost a lot.
Why? I bet way too much.
But you maintain you stick with it anyway. Yeah, I got it. Oh,
you gotta win it back. Okay. That's what I see. This happened so bad.
I wanna, well, I want to go to the sports book too,
cause the Phillies are doing pretty good this season. Hell yeah. And so like,
the other thing I learned this tip, um, because the ATMs in Vegas aren't safe,
but if you go to the sports book and you put a few hundred dollars on your
account, you can slowly withdraw that money with no fees.
So it's essentially a free ATM. Right.
But you have to put your money in it.
So you have to make sure you don't forget that you put like $300 in the sports
book. You're in Barstow. Shit.
That's always the case too.
And you get home and you have like $150 in chips by accident or like,
and you're like, I can't use these until I go back to one specific casino.
The chips work, but the tickets, the paper tickets, you only have a few days.
So you gotta make sure to cash those in. Oh, is that right? Yeah.
There's insane numbers of like casinos make X amount of money every year just
for unclaimed winning.
Cause I always think about that with like the 40 cents tickets that people like
who are losing $200 might just toss or might,
I usually just walk by a lady like an old lady who's playing the penny slots and
put my like dollar 63 in for her.
It was like my go-to with that move.
Cause I don't want to go to the fucking cashier and be like, and here,
okay, $1 48 cents.
And that's all you have left from your trip.
This is sad is like pulling the empty pockets out and a little fly
along other Vegas strategies I have to prevent myself from hitting that ATM.
I do it once a night.
I do it for a high amount if I have to,
but my real plan is when I have a Vegas trip booked about two months
out,
I stopped using my credit card on groceries and start using my debit card on
groceries and get cash back every time, every time I get like 60 bucks out of
cash back. And then eventually by the time I'm ready to go to Vegas,
I have like $480 cash that I don't fully miss because it just was from like,
according to my brain, a lot of expensive trips to Gelson's or whatever.
But I pay no fee on those in another city.
So you're not thinking about that anymore.
You don't pay fees on those withdrawals as well. And rather than take like one,
when you look at your thing, you don't just see like minus 800.
You just see like minus two 20 minus two 20 minus two 20,
like 10 times or whatever.
Because you can't do this on this trip.
There's a million CVS and Walgreens and they all have cash back like $20,
$30 limits for cash back.
Right. Cause they know people will just go out there,
buy a soda and be like, I have $700.
It's a Walgreens and a bank vault in order to do what we want.
Now do you just bet for teams? Do you just bet them winning or you bet like,
I'll bet the win and Kyle Schwaber hits a home run. Yes.
I'll do stupid parlays like that.
Normally when it's sports, I don't really know about if other people,
I'll be like, let me know what you're doing. And with my friend group,
it's not like tacky. I'll be like, let me know what you're doing.
And I'll just match whatever you're betting. You're putting $50 on this.
Cause the fun thing to do, especially if you're there with a group is take,
and you happen to be there. If it's football season,
you don't want to fly home till Sunday night. Cause it is fun to be there.
The games start at 10 AM, the games are over at 8 PM and you get to just bet on
three different sets of games.
And what we'll always do is some like 10 team parlay. That's like,
everyone puts in $5 if we win, we all take 1400 or whatever, you know,
but it's never happens, but that's like a jackpot sizzler. Yeah.
You got to leave with that. That's cool. Yeah. The other,
another game me and my friends play for bachelor parties was taught to us by
Greg to Kolesk, who it's called Denny,
Wilensky and the way Denny Wilensky works. And I recommend you guys play this,
maybe even is if it's, you know,
whoever's bachelor party it is or birthday party, whatever we,
everyone wears suits. Everyone gives Denny Wilensky, whoever,
or like for some time, if it's no occasion,
put your names in a hat and whoever pulls like the Denny Wilensky card is Denny
Wilensky. And that means everyone gives him a hundred dollars.
They go up to the craft stable and bet on the pass line,
whatever that amount is.
So the last time we went with Greg to Glasgow was like $1,800.
18 people gave him a hundred dollars.
And the plan is the where the name Denny Wilensky comes.
If you crap out and lose, everyone goes to Denny's in suits.
If you win,
you double that money and that goes towards the bill at Smith and Wilensky's.
So like, so it's like you either,
and you adjust those two restaurants as taste as needed for us.
It's now in and out and like whatever the steak house is at our hotel.
So we'll have like a standing rez for like 18 people at John George.
And then like, it's actually really funny on to the one I did recently with
Tuca Lesko was an $1,800, a $1,400 roll.
He walked up crapped out on the first roll and we were like, all right,
every we like, we're all partying in the room. We all went downstairs.
He rolled it. We lost.
We all just turn around and went to in and out together.
Everyone's all dressed up and we just, and then that way you eat in and out.
And then it's like $130 for your meal that night where, you know,
and then if you end up going to John George, everyone,
you get $2,800 knocked off the bill. So like, yes, your $100 is gone,
but you got like a free hundred also towards you in a direction.
Are you doing trash Vegas or are you down?
And it's kind of fun to like, just like let, let chance pick that for you.
Yeah. Yeah. So we, we have to give Jason a hundred bucks. Is that what we're,
is that what we're saying? Yeah, but he has to chip it in too.
So it ain't happening.
This on my sports book card.
We call ours, I hops subways.
Yeah. And I, I see one. Yeah, it's international.
I'm assuring you, I'm going to bet on the MLB all star game and it's going to be
great. Let them know the game happened last night. Oh,
I like to, if I go there in the off season,
I bet on the giants to win the super bowl, which is like a varying sliding,
you know, you put $10 and it's like, this ain't happening.
$1,800 if this happens, you're like, great, I'll take that. Yeah.
I'm definitely, I wonder if you're thinking the same thing, Mike.
I think that we're trying to find like a Vegas activity we haven't done and
that's a group activity. I,
what I'd like to do now is watch Jason lose several thousand dollars and then
see what happens to him.
Does he melt into a dollar? Alex Mac.
I watched the a hundred dollars.
I watched the Apple employee tell him he needed to pay for a new iPhone and he
almost fell over.
It's funny that you say that because I was at the Apple store last night and I
learned the current costs for replacing glass on an iPad is $249.
So you may as well just buy a new iPad.
And then I was looking at Apple watches and they're like,
the one you were looking at the, the,
that configuration is out of stock. So I busted it.
I busted at the Apple store, two for two,
put like 12 more of the iPads onto podcast, the ride, which is more important.
Subscribe, subscribe, subscribe.
For itself in the long run.
The podcasters life hack. Yes.
You joke, but I really like gambling and I could see developing a very serious
gambling problem.
What do I play? I play the little shop of horrors penny slant.
What's the name of the plant? What's the,
uh, Audrey?
You need to make her bigger and bigger. I try.
I almost got all Seymours.
I was playing at Atlantic city once and I cashed out when I was like $20 up
and walked away and then passed it like 20 minutes later and someone had won
$1,200 on it. And I was like, oh,
that's the shit that gets you not to leave.
We other things I always do in Vegas is on my Sunday morning or my last morning.
Uh, last, usually I just build it around a weekend church,
but sometimes I'm there to say, I go to church, I go to Bieber's church.
It's fucking great. Uh, no, I do, uh, like, uh,
smoke a fat, something on my balcony, go buy a smoothie or a big iced coffee,
something that's non party drink,
and then sit at a video poker machine and play it like video games. Like,
just super stone zoned out nice and slow,
sip my whole coffee or green juice or smoothie apples. Uh,
the Cosmo has like a fun little, uh,
smoothie store that makes a, uh,
coffee smoothie that has like espresso and peanut butter.
And so you can feel kind of like healthy and coming back to life a little bit.
So I'll hit the spa in the morning,
then sit down super high and do that for like,
and that's like the time where I'm trying to even get away from TIF. My wife,
I'll be like, I'm going to go do it.
Cause like I don't want someone sitting over my shoulder while I slowly play
video poker high, like perhaps like TIF likes to be around craps.
Cause there's free drinks and people and weirdos and stuff.
But like when you're in the video poker section,
it's just like cigarette smoke and fucking rascal scooters.
I'm terrible at video poker.
I want to learn how to play the video Kino on those machines.
Oh, I never played video Kino, but that's, it's kind of like bingo. Yeah.
I play a lot of quick draw at New York bars, you know,
any New York bar that has like the lotto machine I'm always fucking with. Uh,
another meta game I play,
which I think you guys will enjoy is slot machine IPs like finding the wildest
IPs is really like the like existing IPs in the world or their weird generic
like golden lion. Yes. The, the, my favorite one is,
there's one that's just like stoic Buffalo or something.
And it's like just a big Buffalo. And I'm like, who's like, my game is that,
you know? Yeah, I find that really funny.
And then the actual IPs are really like real shit where you're like,
there's a monopoly of star Wars. And then it just like,
there's some weird vestigial ones where it's like,
there's a petty co junctions slot machine. Yeah.
I have my Las Vegas geo tag on my, my apple photos open. And I was like,
I must've taken a photo of a weird one and I just found judge Judy. Yes.
And it's like the funny, you would just imagine who,
like how the IP licensing works for stuff like that.
How much money is judge Judy making off the slot machine?
How much is that part of judge Judy's vast stamp? I know judge Judy's like,
it must have like $3 billion.
How much of the 3 billion is from slots. Right. And then you also are like,
you are also curious about like when an IP is on like a penny slot,
like versus like a dollar, you're like, ah, and here's another, uh,
Gaber's family tradition that my fam,
my parents and me and my brothers always do.
And then I pass that on to the people I go on vacate to Vegas with everyone
puts $20 together and puts $20 each into a wheel of fortune machine.
Cause we really like to wheel of fortune slot.
Cause you get the spin that wheel that is only for $20, whatever.
Anything that has like a mini game inside of it,
where it takes you up to the top. Yeah. We got a new game up here.
Exactly. Change of scenery. I'm looking at a wheel over there as well.
Oh yeah. So for our show.
Over there.
I'm looking at a giant spaceship covered in a tarp that if you guys keep saying,
he's going to maybe, don't worry about it. It's going to put us on the map.
Uh, the, the slot machine IPs have gotten so fast. Like when the dude,
the first part of the dune movie came out in theaters and on HBO max,
uh, at the time I was in a casino and there were already doing slot machines
like simultaneously released with the movie.
Well it's just part of the release.
Right now can be changed so you don't have to actually have a practical physical.
Yeah. You're just like, upload the new IP. Like here's your IP USB stick.
You can have the full new NBC fall lineup just represented immediately when they
premiere.
I've always heard the odds are worse on the IP machine.
Like you want to find the shittiest looking slot machine.
I think that's what they say. Like they don't need to pay out as well.
Cause people will play it for the IP. Yeah. Yeah. Um, so when we play,
when we pool our money for a slot,
we come up with an arbitrary system of like we're going in height order,
age order, weight order. And it's like always like a gimmick in the family.
And if you hit for any amount, even if it's like, it's a 75 cents spin,
but you won 50 cent, you get to spin again and whoever gets the, you know,
and then the game becomes, if you're winning,
you start to negotiate what the cutoff number is on the way down where you're
like, Oh, we each put $20 in. So we have $80 in this machine. Shit.
Now we're winning. We have $120. When do we cash out? It's like, well,
not at 120 because then we're only going to take home $30 each. It's like,
but then if you like don't hit and all you lose all your money,
you really only lose $20 and adding four people taking their time and figuring
out like different ways to spin the reels or three people or whoever else might
be there. It like you're sharing in this moment,
but it also slows the casino down to one fourth speed of money losing in a way
that is like all split up. You're not all split up together losing at one fourth,
the pace you could potentially lose by yourself. You'll hear,
I guess maybe listeners can put this together at this point. So much,
I consider any moment I'm not gambling to be money, money I'm earning.
Like if I'm in the slot, like if I'm out to dinner, I'm like, yes,
this dinner costs $300, but I could lose a thousand.
700 bucks on this dinner.
And once you're in that head space, you're fucking yourself.
We need to shift into that's interesting. You know,
and if you're doing a group poll, you know, everyone's chipping in a, you know,
worst case scenario, Oh,
you got to watch all those fun little snippets from Jurassic park. Exactly.
Yeah. It cost me $20 and I got to watch like five of their little play outs,
their little scenes and shit. Yeah. I'm looking at it. I'm also,
in 2015 early vestige of the avatar fascination that there was an avatar
machine and that's like the time, the way of winning the way of winning,
the top thing in this, like a Papyrus laden machine, the,
the top win is mighty win. Wow.
Mike thinks he invented a phrase in, in avatar and thing. No, you're right.
You do. You're right. You're right. I started calling the Akron,
the mighty Akron years ago. It's not in the movie.
That's not a phrase. Any of the avatar people say, if you Google mighty Akron,
I come up there like the podcast, the ride.
I've heard you scream this in someone's face at a bar before. Yes.
Google mighty Akron. My name comes up. Yeah. That's what my,
when I'm in a retirement home and I've lost my mind,
the nurses will be hearing.
You all know the phrase. Hey, look at me. Look at me. Where are you going?
Look at the eye contact pal.
I have like a laminated sheet of the Google results that I just like pull,
like put on a table.
Remember when there was Google SEO before everything was abolished.
Yeah. Yeah.
Avatar five is about to come out.
Yes. Yeah.
Is this a tip or do you want this back?
He's got a backpack full of them. No, keep it.
I need an autograph.
There's something about, sorry, one real quick going to Vegas.
There is something I do that I recommend other people do is just kind of shift
your perspective on a lot of things up to and including the value of currency.
It's almost like, and that's,
it's difficult and arguably not financially smart, but arguably,
but I'm talking about enjoyment. I'm not talking about retirement.
Yeah. You got you.
Everything costs a little more than you think it does. You guys are the,
I keep saying you guys are theme park guys on your podcast.
The ride that that's all I want to be recognized as is a theme park guy,
the sexual being thing. I don't want any recognition that I'm glad you're right.
You're recognizing me for what we should be celebrating.
When you accept it yourself,
our guy in sexual being is just Jason.
Hey, well, we are the ones who made kids. So there's,
true. We must have done it at some point.
And must have done it just precludes you from being a sexual. Yeah.
I don't know that you have when you say it like that.
Congratulations. Of course.
To the young PTR, the next PTR generation. Next generation of dorks. Yeah.
PTR TNG.
Okay. Question here.
I like going to one big douchey pool party.
How do you feel about this?
They're not for me, but I,
I've done them and I enjoyed myself there.
It is one of those, like if you can get yourself a cabana,
it feels like a little bit better.
And every one of them now kind of has like, yes,
pool party, like official pool parties or pool party energy,
just at the pool, which is kind of fun.
So like you don't have to go fully to go to rehab at hard rock.
There's levels of douche. Right.
You just go to this adults only pool and you know what that means. And it's like,
there's going to be some wild people getting fucked up there,
but there also might be like five people reading, laying out, you know,
I forget which hotel I went to recently,
but had a wave pool with a giant TV in the back.
And then it was at someone else's bachelor party and they had
outdoor craps table. And when I went to the hard rock, I played,
uh, blackjack in the pool, which was awesome.
Oh, that sounds good. And then you have the pool for like 12 hours.
Everyone, no one's getting out to go to the bathroom when you've had like a
hundred. Hey, what's happening at this table here?
It just all pissing in the circle. All right.
There's the encore beach club that has the giant sports screens.
I'm thinking that's what you've got. Yeah. And Circa downtown. Yeah.
That's the newer one. That's like the nice hotel next to Fremont street.
And it's like, well, what's the point?
There's a night and you guys can talk them on yourselves.
I found an app where I put myself with five other guests.
You have so many pages of apps.
I have never seen. What's this one?
Disco tech is the app and you can put yourself on the list for a many,
many different Vegas, like parties or nightclubs or pool parties.
And I have signed up for many already for this weekend.
Where are you going? What's on your?
I don't know what I'm doing.
You guys are all going together. See you guys. I gotta go to the pool party.
I only put myself on the list.
I'm assuming I've never made it seem like I want to go to one of these pool.
I'm not saying you have to go. I'm just saying I definitely put myself plus five
guests with me. So if we want to go, we can't.
This might be the thing is to join you at one of your.
Pool Saturday, a Zillow Ultra Pool Sunday, Nico X way at wet republic,
DJ dynamic at the Drays Beach Club. Any of these are possible.
The thing I'm kind of excited about is Sunday night,
DJ Spider drenched after dark, starting at 1030,
a nighttime douchey pool party.
Oh, this is what I'm interested in. That one.
This is at Marquis Nightclub.
I don't know. Like survive a night pool party like a day pool party.
You will be. Yes, that's true, too.
It'll be a nice 95 degrees at night.
It'll be a balmy.
The pool day parties have changed the vibe of Vegas in a really fun way.
If you go to the casinos at like three or four p.m.,
there are tons of women cross eyed in bikinis
staggering in from out like that.
And like and guys absolutely piss wasted with no shirts on.
And it's like they are, you know, one a.m.
drunk, right? You've had dinner. Yes.
And they're dressed for the pool.
So it's like if you are a standard horny American, it's it's quite
if you are sexual, which Jason and I are a standard horny American.
That's got welcome to the S.H.A. boys.
Oh, man, I guess I'm getting FOMO now.
I think you guys are stumbled upon, which is also another fun thing about Vegas,
because it does have something for everyone.
Yeah, it sounds like you guys need to go to a pool party for Mike.
You guys need to gamble or go in on a sports bet with Jason
and then scris you need your own.
Like and I got to pick one.
Yeah. Yeah. And off strip activities always fun.
Like, yes, I know the bangerang people did this.
I never did it, but it was a lot of fun.
There's like the huge sandbox where you get to like play with excavators
and bulldozers and stuff.
Oh, right. Right.
Construction pit. And that's all I've heard about.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, what do I?
Oh, my God.
And I believe they're building like a Formula One racetrack.
Oh, yeah. That's happening in the fall.
Yeah. Oh, it's total sense.
Like as the fifth city to get one or whatever.
They're building a headquarters and then there is a race on the strip.
Like they're building bleachers in front of the Bellagio.
That's I used to have in like I think Caesar's had a racetrack.
So this is going back to decades ago. Yeah.
I did the Vegas half marathon where you run the street.
Wow. Oh, wow.
With friend of the show, Nick Weigert.
We and it was amazing.
Like the one way to get me to run 13 miles is like they close the strip down.
You run down the street at night.
And I was like, fuck, it was brutal.
And it got really cold by the end.
And there's one leg where you go off strip just because like you can't do 13 miles
just on the strip.
And when you go off the strip, the entire tone of the city changes.
You're like, this is creepy. Let's get back on the strip.
Let's get back on the strip.
But I like eight edibles at mile 10 and like the last the last three miles,
I'm just like running under neon lights, like super slow.
It was such a fucking rad experience.
Wow. Yeah.
Well, I don't know what mine is.
I mean, I was wondering if it'd be fun to go to Palace Station
and walk in the footsteps of O.J. and his band of memorabilia robbers.
Sure. We could take the the O.J. robbery.
There's an aquarium at Mandalay Bay, I believe.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like, I mean, the orb or like the big ferris wheel.
Those are like potential.
High roller. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Station casinos are interesting.
Run by Tillman for Tita's cousins.
Wow. Wow. From the Texas.
You're one of the Texas gang.
And if you tell them you're there's a panel coming for their ass.
This is the owner of the Rainforest Cafe and Landry's restaurants.
I recognize the name.
You read Tillman for Tita's book.
What is this book called again?
Is it like like shut the fuck up and do it?
It's something really severe and not friendly.
His uncles were all Texas gangsters.
So when he bought the Raptors, everyone was like, the NBA is letting this guy
buy a jean.
Mine could be pepper mill, too.
I like that peppermint.
Oh, yeah. You've done it before.
Right. Pepper mill.
Pepper mill is this diner that has a bar also.
Oh, I have done. Yeah.
It's the very it is like early 80s neon pink and purple aesthetic.
I did do that on a travel show for Esquire with Adam Pally.
Not the one recent one we did, one we did way back in the day.
Me, him, Gemberling and Doug Mand and a few other people ate at it for.
Oh, sure. Remember the getaway when they were doing like a celebrity
one off travel show episodes was on the Esquire network.
Like Jack McBrayer went to Hawaii and like Eve went to Jamaica and stuff like that.
And Pally took five of his dumb friends to Vegas.
Oh, that's cool.
What was the highlight of that?
We had. Oh, we stayed at the
Rain Man Suite with the in Caesars with the two stairs.
Wow. I don't know about this in the movie Rain Man.
They come down the sweet stairs in like suits.
It's got it's this huge two floor suite where they're like the living.
Like the living room is like 18 feet of windows and like and we stayed in that
and had and this is the dumbest highlight.
We had like a top shelf brunch room service,
like lobster tail cocktail, Bloody Mary bar like and they filmed it at all.
But for us, it was just like got super baked and just ate like this insane
morning feast. And I was like, this is the best part of Vegas.
It's like the moment we didn't leave the hotel.
Oh, we we tried to do that
indoor skydiving thing where you're like, and oh, yeah,
they were like, how much do you weigh?
I was like this much.
And I was like 40 pounds lighter than I am now.
They were like, you will.
You can try, but you probably just be laying on the ground with the fan
blowing on you.
I was like, I'll pass.
You want to know what it's like to have a lot of wind in your face?
Great.
Interesting. Well, this is a good idea.
A little like curated experience.
Yeah. I mean, I think harder on mine.
I had an awesome Chinese food restaurant that Weiger recommended
that was off strip, like in a strip mall.
And the food was bananas good.
And it was bring your own beer, which was kind of fun, too.
Oh, that's funny. Yeah.
Oh, really?
But yeah, pepper mills, a good time to.
Yeah, I do like it there.
That's a drink like a fucking kitchen sink full of like alcohol and sherbert.
They're like some huge.
Yeah.
Those big old flaming goblets.
Yeah, because the thing they're known for is the cocktail menu is like
the bartender's handbook, like they have every cocktail.
Right. Yes. That's what it was.
You can get almost any.
And we got some big, dumb, like, you know, lobster, thermidor, the cocktail.
Yeah. Yeah.
To Brandi Alexander's for the table.
You know. Yeah.
Well, I think we got, you know, they that might be the way to do it.
Everybody we hope we pool our interests and then pull and also pull our money
in a little shop of horrors slot machine we put we each put one hundred dollars.
I got one hundred dollars in free play.
So I'm starting off like winning.
So, oh, shit.
There we go.
Thanks to Vegas games, we play on our phones.
All you had to do was play a game at all times obsessively.
And it is the worst pop ups.
Like it tries to get you to spend money on it so much.
And I wish Diablo for our Dave the diver gave me fucking cause
of points because I just spent like the last 80 hours of my life
on those between those two games.
You need to use a lot of points.
This is the app he's talking about. My Vegas slots.
You need to use a lot of points to get a hundred dollars of free play.
Yeah, I got like two hundred and thousands of points.
Well, I have like two million points.
Oh, my God. This guy's beating me by like a million and a half.
We all are wild away the hours during lockdown in our own ways.
OK, sure. Some of us mastered slots.
Yes, some of us are in craps.
So I spent 10,000 hours playing the slots.
Some of us figured out how to X through fastest, like spend money, spend money.
No, no, I'm doing it for free.
In the pandemic, I downloaded a craps app that I was not that much fun to play.
But the highlight was when you wanted to roll the dice, you shook the whole phone
like that. Oh, that is fine.
And then you like did that and stopped it and the dice would roll.
That is that mechanic was fun.
I like the the thing that stuck around since early
iPhones where like you shake to undo like that still works.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, maybe we all got to get on this app master Jason's ability to X pop up ads
and build up enough capital.
There's like five of them. OK, OK.
Black. There's a few slots.
There's blackjack. There's bingo.
Yeah. But the true game is getting rid of the pop ups.
You can keep the pop up and you've got to be shit again.
Another one. Another one.
And the dangers you have to be very careful because it will try to use Apple
Pay to buy chips. Oh, fuck.
Yeah. So I can get into this, right?
I can jump into your Apple Pay.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
It's like that freemium shit like, I hope you're enjoying yourself.
Whoops, you actually paid eight dollars, but don't worry.
Now your machine glows.
And yeah, we don't like that freemium stuff anyway.
Please support our Patreon.
Please support Action Boys Patreon.
And on that note, I guess, let's say, hey, let's head to the plot of the
the the plugging point.
John Gaber, you survived podcast, the right Sin City Nights.
Oh, man. So much for joining for the guidance and for a big pile of ideas.
Thank you so much for having me.
Any chance I can to talk about Vegas when it's sanctioned, especially like
I'll just ruin parties with this conversation.
So it's nice to just come here and ruin a podcast, you know,
simulated party with thousands of disparate people out there.
I appreciate you, Kevin McAllister, and all these dancing cardboard
cutouts all time to make it feel like I'm at a party.
And everyone's so enthused regaling us with the day.
Tell us more about the Islanders game, Gabris.
Thanks for bringing the crystal head vodka.
Do you have any stories about what it is?
I my my plugs are check out High and Mighty.
These guys have been on.
So if if you're a diehard PTR fan, maybe start there or listen to Action Boys.
We are a Patreon only podcast, but we do have some free episodes
that you could find in the iOS app.
But otherwise, it's Action Boys dot biz with Z's
and one hundred one places to party before you die.
Eight episodes on HBO Max Max rather.
And maybe who knows by the time this comes out, maybe the app doesn't exist.
So for tax refunds or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
This is like every every day now is awaiting the death sentence.
So if you're of the show, you may.
I think you survived by putting it out.
What that was like. That's a twenty twenty two that came out.
And has zero residuals because it's all non union.
Unscripted.
So you're not complaining about loss of residuals because there weren't any to begin with.
Yeah, I'm not complaining by the I did lose health insurance
during my most successful career career.
I love it because it's a TV show.
It's sure far away to lose health insurance because I had to spend
so much time traveling, making money.
I was unable to make SAG money.
Oh, my God. It's so complicated.
And that's the most interesting part of the SAG health insurance.
When it starts, you're immediately watching the clock of like, OK,
so this is out in one year.
I'm out of now. I'm like, I'm seeing doctors.
I'm back on after spending, you know, two G's a month on Cobra.
And now I'm back on SAG health insurance.
But for a year and I'm hoping maybe with this strike that's currently happening,
we get a little grace period.
Oh, that would be great.
So, right. Oh, my God.
So everyone in all the industries don't work for many, many months.
Did you make your minimums?
I hope you made them in the couple of weeks before they took away
the cheap entry level plan.
So I had to make more.
And also, there's no residuals anymore either.
Like that used to be a way to like, yeah, if you got two good jobs
and enough residuals from last year's two good jobs,
you could maybe make health insurance again.
But now that's gone.
This is you'll hear us if the strike is still going in three months
and we went to Vegas and like, let's have some fun.
Let's do some crap since then.
Oh, shit, we all lost twelve thousand dollars.
Hey, we are starting a we're starting a twelve thousand dollar tier.
There's a twenty dollar here.
We show up at your house to one episode in your living room with you.
You you're not allowed to talk away from your face.
You'll have an unplugged microphone to pretend you're playing like a cousin
playing video games with the boys.
Don't make eye contact with Mike.
He really gets wild if you do that.
Really starts to act out.
You'll turn into Slam Carlson and you do not want that.
Yeah, he's slam.
He's more violent than the regular Mike.
He's more dangerous
because of the sure he's more likely to start playing slam ball in your living room.
That's right.
Hey, for us, keep up with the PTR Sin City Nights
on all the bad social media at podcast, the ride.
Watch out for more of these episodes on the main strip.
And for three bonus episodes, check out podcast, the ride, the Fremont gate
or get one more on our high roller to your club three.
You'll find all that at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
Now let's get out of here before Mike turns slam.
We.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit Forever Dog Podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog News by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.