Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate,
where today's recipe calls for a little bit of garlic
and a little bit of sincerity about a magical place.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I'm very intrigued.
This is the first park in a while where I was like,
I'd never heard of it until you mentioned it.
Yeah, it's kind of a rare thing, I think.
And I was a little inspired, I think I'd heard of it,
but I was definitely inspired by the audience
because we did a call for second gates at some point,
where this was suggested and I realized I'd be up there
or I could group it into my NorCal theme park wanderings.
And I'm so glad that I did.
Mike Carlson, hi.
I'm here and since I'm here, I'm something.
I'm here, I'm sincere.
And let's be clear, Gilroy Gardens is a very nice theme park.
I'm spilling the lead, but I kind of did in the preview.
I'm so excited, am I, about this place and to talk about it
and to keep talking about my Northern California theme park wanderings
as I was on the main feed about Great America.
And we'll get into that, but there was something that I saved for this
because there was so much to talk about in the other one.
And I alluded to that I had stories to tell about the Chuck E. Cheese
that is up there in San Jose.
The world's largest Chuck E. Cheese, which it's not, look, you know,
I hear world's largest Chuck E. Cheese and I want it to be the size of an Ikea.
I think that's everybody's.
I picture the Warner Brothers store in Times Square.
Or is that the one that's nine stories?
They expanded from three to nine.
Yeah, that's what I, a nine story Chuck E. Cheese.
Oh, God.
With all the characters from years past, Dolly Dimples and et cetera, et cetera.
The king, if you're getting an entire like beach section for the beach,
Bowser's an entire cavern club or whatever.
Oh, yeah.
I call it for the what is the Beatles one called?
I always just were they the Beagle the Beagles.
Yeah, I think a full barbershop for the four little shavers.
Oh, yes.
Oh, God, Jason, can you imagine a whole floor for the four little shavers?
Four little shavers.
One of the restored ones at the Volo Auto Museum.
Yes.
Illinois.
Yeah, we got to do next time you go back.
Yeah, you got to.
Yeah.
You have a follow.
My parents live out here.
I'm never going back.
That's right.
Yeah.
Wait.
Well, yeah, you got friends out here.
Yeah, you're not.
OK, then you have to go just for that.
Just for Volo.
Oh, yeah.
I guess you're right.
I'll go for Volo and I'll go for I don't know the pizza.
You don't want to have FOMO about missing.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
And because, you know, Yolo.
That's true.
So you got to go to Volo.
Yeah.
And I'm a car guy, too.
So of course.
Get there.
Rent a car.
Rent a great car and you'll be set.
So yeah, it's not, you know, it's not like unbelievable, but it's big.
It's a sizable Chuck E. Cheese.
It's it's three stories.
And it's like first floor is big dance floor that has become the thing they've
replaced the animatronics with.
And of course, we'd find that to be a bummer.
But now, having been to that one and other ones with my son, it works pretty well
for the kids.
I got to say he's not too interested in the animatronics.
He really likes the light up dance floor.
I'm trying.
I'm try.
Of course, I took him to a full munch one.
Yeah.
So I'm giving him all options like, you know, as I said, like religion, like you
want to like, you know, not dictate it to you, you know, maybe put some different
things on the table.
But but this being my religion, you will be into Chuck E. Cheese.
There's no negotiation about that.
Right.
What kind of Chuck E.
Cheese I do leave up to you.
Yeah.
You're you're not forcing him like you need to like the mouse and the tuxedo that
says good night, ladies.
He sings good night, ladies.
All sorts of barbershop songs.
If you want a Chuck E.
Cheese that does more updated songs, and by that I mean sound, the likes of hits
from 2013, then that's fine.
Get more modern.
That's your prerogative.
So that's the big dance floor on the bottom.
Second floor is maybe a little more older kids.
Like it's more mature stuff up there.
It's weird.
Like Dolly Dimples used to be.
You can say that's the thing you're in.
There's not a lot of remnants of old Chuck E.
Cheese in this place.
There's a few, a few scattered ones, but they're being like eliminated bit by bit.
But enough that are.
And if you watch videos that people have posted on the.
So you just know from the space, like, of course, this one had different.
Of course, there were other like cabaret style rooms in this one.
That one.
I really am jealous because I don't think I've ever been in a Chuck E.
Cheese that felt like it was one of the old original ones.
Most of them felt like, oh, it's kind of one big room.
And then the area where the dinner show and the robots.
Well, you got to go to Northridge or recede.
It's on recede of Boulevard.
I don't know if you call it Northridge, but you like.
Yeah, genuinely good for a kid hang.
But there's like a back room where that's just games.
But for sure, absolutely.
That was the home of the beach bousers.
Man, I do have the faintest memory of it's really if there's if, if you're in a Chuck
E.
Cheese and it has any other room of any kind.
Yes, it's not a bathroom.
Right.
Don't go into a bathroom looking for old animatronic remnants.
Yeah.
Our Chuck E.
Cheese growing up used to be a showbiz pizza, so it was not like that.
Oh, it was just it was just a room.
It was just a room and then room with table.
It was just there was there was the area you eat in front of the robot show.
And then it was just a big room for the games.
OK, OK.
And that's look, that's fine, too.
There's not it's not a problem.
That's fine.
It's a base model and it's great.
And if they've kept it up with the right style of.
Yeah.
I mean, why can you not have animatronics and light up dance?
But these things should not contradict each other.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess if they feel like that's what they have to do to keep the company afloat,
I suppose I'm more willing to accept it if it'll keep Chuck E.
Cheese in business because God knows how they still are in business, but they are.
They keep they keep surviving.
They thriving in some ways with their constant YouTube content and new songs.
And there's an album of every three months, seemingly.
Well, and look like it, as I'm saying here, I've been now a bunch of times with my son,
Aaron takes them all the time to it.
It absolutely works as potentially cheap or free kids entertainment also, because,
you know, he barely my son barely wants to like actually play anything or do anything.
It's just kind of like run around and touch everything, jump on a merry-go-round,
decide not to go on the merry-go-round.
We take them off immediately.
So on a hot summer day, you're killing a lot of time and pretty cheap in there.
Assuming you assuming we don't start just like guzzling wine, the wine's bad enough that it's not tempting.
I could say that I haven't done that as a parent is have Chuck E.
Cheese wine on a genuine Chuck E.
Cheese child visit.
How much is a glass of wine at a Chuck E.
Cheese?
I don't know.
I don't think I don't think it's expensive, but you also know it's not.
Sure.
I'm just wondering what the what the upcharge is for your like Carlos Rossi or whatever.
Yeah, I don't.
Yeah, it's definitely in there.
It's definitely the kind of wine.
It's just it feels like it's it's just like a cherry or something.
More akin to a Kool-Aid.
People are not ordering it a lot.
So that's sitting.
Oh, I bet.
And the home I get well, and it's like employees opening it who possibly are not of drinking age.
And even if they are not allowed.
Yes.
And if they are drinking, then it's just kind of like whatever crap anyone's buying them.
They don't realize that you can't just leave wine sitting out.
And they they did.
These are not they're not fine vintners being hired at Chuck E.
Cheese.
I bet there was like a great wine menu and you could sit and listen to Dolly Dimple's play.
I well, I'm going to I'll counter that a little and say I don't know if it was great, but I bet it was more akin to the kind of wine you could get anywhere.
Yeah, wine was worse in the 70s, but you're getting the same thing there as you are at the nice sit down restaurant.
Fair enough.
I'm thinking a lot of table wine, table wine with the wicker.
Yeah.
Kind of in the basket.
You know, yes, I don't know how to describe it.
I just I always know.
Italian restaurant decorations.
But at some point that was practical.
Jason, if you could go and blaze a big fat blunt right in front of the four little shavers and listen to their show, what would be better?
Yeah, sure.
Is Illinois recreational?
You can buy it.
I don't know about smoking it inside and no, we can't really smoke anywhere.
But it's a hypothetical.
Yeah, I think we should also we should standardize.
But there's different things that we say when we refer to Jason smoking.
And I think it should just always be smoke a big fat blunt.
Did you say blaze?
Did I say I think I said blaze?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry.
So from now on, it's so when you where would you like to blaze a big fat blunt?
Well, as usual, out of the way, like where I won't bother anyone or get the Leilani yourself in a Chuck E.
Cheese in a Chuck E.
Cheese from the 70s, I guess.
Oh, yeah.
Or just dream animatronic big fat blunt pairing.
You know, I don't I don't really like the smell of any kind of smoke like indoors, but I love smoking patio.
OK, so you'd want to go outside.
Yeah, I want to go outside and then come in and get comfy and enjoy the shavers like with a nice cool Coke Zero.
Enjoy zero sugar.
Why do you smell so funny?
And what are they opening with?
What's that song?
Yeah, what's going to hit?
What's going to hit different?
Like Lida Rose and they do like Lida Rose.
I'm home again.
Like the one that Harold had, they believe Harold Hill tricks the school board to do and to becoming a barbershop quartet at some point.
The music man.
And I think they do Lida Rose.
No, those harmonies are going to they're going to they're going to feel like 64.
Yeah.
After big fat blunt.
OK, so I was saying I was describing the floors, right?
So, you know that there's and floors one and two I got through, but I was stepping through this because floor three is not open to the public.
But I've looked into this and I know that floor three, I think I mentioned in a club three episode where I found this place that floor three was where managers from Chuck E.
Cheese had to come and learn how to manage Chuck E.
Cheese.
OK, so this was a classroom environment.
Oh, my God.
That, you know, where all the greats from across the nation learned Chuck E.
Cheese magic.
And now it is not open to the public.
It's just things that the I don't know if it ever was, I guess.
But, you know, we're having fun.
My son's having fun.
But something is gnawing at me, which is I don't know if I'm going to be back here.
This is already my second visit to the San Jose Chuck E.
Cheese.
I want to know what's on that third floor.
And I'd heard things.
I've seen little like fits and starts of pictures basically.
And then I'm in the store and I start Googling this and I found a Reddit post on some deep Chuck E.
Cheese Reddit or maybe it was our Reddit.
Who knows?
And I've and somebody was asking, is there a way to get up there?
And I found a reply saying, well, I've a lot of the employees are really nice, actually.
And I've just kind of like been super nice to them, too.
And they've said, sure, we'll give you a little tour.
We'll let you go.
Well, they will show you the old Chuck E.
Cheese stuff.
Wow.
Because that's where it all.
None of the remnants are down where I am on the floor where the public goes like an idiot.
This is where I got to get.
So I'm trying to think like, what is my in?
How do I worm my way to the employees?
Only third floor.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
How do I leave my family to go do that?
And then I realized, wait, I have an in with the manager.
And the in is that I met the manager a little while ago because when Aaron kind of exhausted from a long kids travel day,
gave me the reins for exactly 10 minutes, we went to go play Skeeball and my son got beamed in the head with a Skeeball and bled a little bit.
Whoa.
Don't worry. It sounds worse than it is just a little bit.
It didn't even alarm me when it happens.
So then when I bring him back out to her, she's like, oh, what's that?
Oh, yeah, it's just a little.
Hey, it's OK.
I should say this is a game that he requests and one of his favorite things to do at an arcade and arcade is to sit on the ground next to the Skeeball as they all land and clackety clack.
He loves the sound.
It drives him crazy.
He laughs and laughs and laughs and he likes them to like come down the ramp and land on him.
But of course, this is a recipe for some for either dad getting nailed in the balls or in this case, him getting nailed in the forehead and bleeding ever so slightly.
Not so bad.
But of course, I only have this.
I took over so quickly and he starts bleeding.
So she's like, will you go get like a like an alcohol wipe or something?
OK, yes, can do.
I owe you that much audience.
Don't judge me.
Look, it's happened.
A little injury, no injuries happen all the time.
Yeah, that's why I take them away from me.
Please.
I just will.
One question.
Yeah.
He threw the ball up and it came back down.
Well, you take them all.
You're not playing the real game.
You just kind of like taking them all going crazy like Van Hammerslee on Mr.
Show at the pool table.
Whoa, just like like stirring them all up.
And then he toss them all up and then a big barrage all comes down and they land in his lap and he laughs and let they go all over the floor.
I've got if employees are watching this, they must be like, Jesus, play the balls.
Yeah, yeah, they are.
Yes.
So the the the possibility of injury is is really high.
But we've done this a lot of times without injury.
Of course, it happens up there again.
Mile. It's very mild.
So I go.
I mean, that's what you know, it was the universe punishing you because it's antithetical to the spirit of the game to the game of ski.
Jason, I respect for the game.
I mean, you're right.
I wasn't I didn't even I wasn't scoring at all.
In the end, they're all just deposited up into the gutter.
So zero points are scored.
So if you're in it for the brinksmanship, yeah, for her, the eternal mystery, I'm not we're screwing up.
We're just we're just breaking all the rules.
Look, it's hard enough to get it up the top score in the middle, let alone those two on the sides, the mystery ones.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think it's a mystery.
I believe those are mysteries to me because I love it, but I'm not particularly good at it.
I think it says what number though.
I think it doesn't.
You're right.
Mike, you're logically correct, but I do like the spirit of the mystery hole.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Yeah.
Who actually nobody's ever gotten one is you don't know the whole thing might like start shooting fireworks.
I can tell you it sounds like though, Jason, when God closes the door, he opens a window.
Yeah.
Here as far as your relationship now with the manager.
Yes, exactly.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
That's what I was thinking because I went up and I met her after I went and asked an employee for an alcohol wipe and they didn't know what that meant.
So they pointed me over to a manager who was having a meeting with several employees, which I had to go interrupt to get a small alcohol wipe.
So now this is all happened.
There's blood every day.
Chuck E. Cheese, what is it?
What's going on?
You would think maybe there's not.
And again, look, it's not getting on the ground.
All right.
It's barely the just a pinch.
Just a little kids not bleeding like Ric Flair in the seventies.
It was it was a controlled bleed.
Exactly.
Maybe not a purposeful one, but under control.
So I went talk to her.
She was very nice about it.
So when a little while later, I'm thinking I got to get up there.
I'm like, well, she was nice enough.
Maybe this is my shot.
So I go I it's gnawing at me here and says, you better go get this out of your system.
I'll make sure he doesn't get injured again.
I'll keep being a parent.
You go be a child.
And I I go up and I interrupt another meeting and I say, hey, another question.
Ah, and then the regret surges before the sentence even starts.
It's just I I've heard about some of the stuff up in the back and the third floor.
I've heard that there's things on the third.
And I really like Chuck E.
I like old Chuck E.
Cheese.
And I was and I've heard about some of the things that might be there.
And I was hoping is there any chance that I can she has started glaring at me, you know,
10 percent of the way through.
She knows where you're going on sentence.
Yeah.
And so she lets me get to the end.
She lets me make a full fool of myself.
And then she very, very nice person, but also very sternly just says, there's a lot of room for me.
I've heard rumors about what's going on up there about what's on the third floor.
And that's all they are is just rumors.
That's it.
There's nothing to see up there.
All right.
I've worked here for 15 years.
I know that there is nothing to see.
If there was something I would have seen it.
So I'm sorry, but I can't let you do that.
But there's don't worry about it because there is nothing to see.
It's really intense.
This is I feel a little ashamed, a little scared.
I the energy of this was so severe.
I mean, I assumed to know.
But then what I got was so heavy.
Wow.
What do you make of this?
The Ark of the Covenant has been placed in the hands of top men, top men.
It could even be the dial of destiny up there for all I know.
The dial of destiny up there.
I yeah, I don't I don't know.
Weird, right?
So this is where the story ends.
You didn't try to sneak up there.
I didn't try to although in the lead up to this, you're right.
I'm forgetting part of the story, which is that I checked every employee door first.
First, I tried to sneak.
I did the sneaking first and none of it worked.
I jiggled every door and none of them worked.
So this is kind of I've now been checkmated and I'm just left to wonder why was the energy so weird with that?
And then I remembered something.
This if Eagle Eagle eared listeners.
Sure.
Why not?
It may remember the first time that I ever talked about this.
The first that I heard about it when I just saw it in a book when I was in that car wash.
The thing that it said was that this Chuck E. Cheese is haunted because supposedly a young girl jumped or fell out of the third floor to her death.
And I don't know if this story is true, but it's left it to where people think that this Chuck E. Cheese is haunted.
So I'm like, wait a minute.
That's what she thinks I was asking.
Yeah.
That's why it was all this weird stuff about rumors and there's nothing to see.
She thought that I was after the ghost stuff.
Right.
So now I'm we're driving away and I'm like, oh my God, that manager.
She thought I was a ghost weirdo.
I didn't convey that I'm a Chuck E. Cheese weirdo.
She was totally confused about the kind of weirdo I am.
What impression did I give?
Well, did you say you said you were a Chuck E. Cheese fan though?
That came out, but she might not have.
I'm not afraid you think?
I don't. And I also danced around it for no reason.
I have said I heard that there's old Chuck E. Cheese props.
Can I go see them?
Instead, I was like, I've heard things.
I've heard things.
I have an old De Niro impression of things.
And I was all weird and cagey.
So then she assumed she had to be.
So this means that she's dealt with this before that ghost hunters have tried to go in there.
Many times a week.
It sounds like if she has a kind of a speech prepared, it seemed pretty ready to go with her number of years of employment.
Wow. That's so interesting.
I wonder if your hypothesis is right and then it's just a ghost thing.
But I wonder.
Yeah, I wonder how many people are like,
What's the ratio of Chuck E.
Cheese weirdo to ghost person weirdo that wants to explore the third floor?
I don't know. And how are they hearing about?
Is this Chuck E.
Cheese San Jose Ghost Girl story that famous?
Was it on like, I mean, I know there's probably a lot of like ghost hunter shows that have had to populate hours and hours with fake stories.
Right, right. But so maybe was it on one of those?
And now it's on people's little little trip.
I don't know. There's probably a hundred of those shows.
There's no way to check all of them.
No, I wouldn't want to channels now.
Yeah, there's YouTube ghost hunters.
Never. And she thinks you're going to be pulling out like an electromagnetic meter or something.
And you're just hoping for like a shipping crate with Dolly Dimple's head in it.
You're looking for like Jasper Jasper's like old vest.
Yes, I want like I want the old sparkly dress that Helen used to wear.
Yeah, I just want to try it on. Of course I do.
All these clothes. It's a part of history.
Yes. Do I want to put it on and shimmy around like Helen used to get to?
Of course I do. Yes.
But then I'm going to go. Right.
I will. I'll never be back here.
I promise. I'm more likely to be back because you're not letting me do it now.
Yeah, right.
So I didn't get I didn't get up there, but I have watched YouTube videos.
So I do know what is up there.
And I guess it's no wouldn't have been any better to see it in person.
Who am I kidding? Of course it would have been, of course.
But can I tell you what what is up there? Yeah, because it is pretty good.
I mean, it's a bunch of like old artwork like murals that used to be on the wall, some of which are old characters.
There's Dolly Dimple's.
There's one where the king, the Elvis type character, the lion, is at like a drafting desk and he's hard at work and he looks stressed out.
And and Chuck is over his shoulder looking really angry at him.
Like he's not happy with the work that he's doing and only through the deciphering the view.
You have to stare at the image to know that it's because he's drawing a mouse trap and that's why.
But what it looks like is that he's like, like you're planning renovations to Chuck's house or something.
And like, that's never going to work.
I need a lot more secret doors.
I got a lot of shit to hide.
You contractors are all crooked.
I knew I shouldn't trust you.
This is why I never pay you.
I get you up here, get you working, then I steal your plans and I just build them on my own.
I should have just drawn it myself.
Give me the pencil.
I guess I got to do everything around here.
But Squally's pizza tastes like shit.
It's my recipe.
And if I let him cook it, he fucks that up too.
The best, the big centerpiece of it, though, is that there's a big mural.
This is on a YouTube channel for the user sets streets and eats.
And there's a big mural and it says the Royal Order of Rodents.
And it's a big gathering of a bunch of cartoon mice.
So Chuck's in there.
Mickey and Minnie are in there.
The Cinderella mice, Jock and Gus are there.
And Mighty Mouse is there too.
So it's a big gathering.
The Royal Order of Rodents.
And I don't know what they're doing.
They don't seem to be getting along.
They're just kind of all together.
But this was apparently up in the store with Mickey and Minnie and other Disney characters in it.
And then so that's up on the wall.
And then next to it is just a kind of crumpled piece of paper, not in a frame or anything, just a pin on the wall.
And this is a letter from the Walt Disney Company from 1989 saying,
We have noticed some photos of some displays in your store.
And we assume that this was done in innocence, but we now ask you to take them down immediately, motherfuckers.
Get this out of your store ASAP.
Signed Michael Eisner?
I mean, I think it did seem to be a female name of a lawyer.
I wish I could say it was Eisen.
But you know, he was staring over her shoulder like angry Chuck looking over the king.
Make it meaner.
Threaten more.
Threaten her.
Threaten stronger language.
So anyway, that's is that a video with video or just like pictures, still pictures?
Those video. Yeah.
Yeah.
From what year?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
A couple of years ago, within the last few years.
I wonder if there was just a point also where it was like no more tours.
Yeah, maybe.
So like something happened.
Yeah, right.
Something happened.
Some employee did something.
So then he smoked a big blazed, a big flat blazed, a big fat up there and up there.
And it was over.
Somebody said somebody tried to get Chuck blazed.
Yeah.
And have lightened part of the mural on fire.
And then it was like from now on, nothing fun is happening up here anymore.
There was another mural where it's Chuck and Minnie hooking up and then it got lit on fire by the blunt.
So it's not the person painted it and then like ash.
They're they're right when they finished.
It's a shame.
Now it's just up to all of us to imagine that scene.
Yeah.
You'll never find out.
Take a memo.
Take a message.
I see you've got some artwork.
Chuckie doing Mickey's old lady.
Please.
Right away.
We have standards in our character design and we'd frankly rather not know what is going on under her skirts.
It is pulled up a bit high for our comfort and you could see too many parts for our comfort as well.
Signed Michael Eisner.
Yes.
Hands off Mickey's old lady or else.
Then a year later.
Hello.
You might.
You might remember my letter from a year ago and I'm not pleased to see that there is now another mural in your store in which Chuckie cheese is doing things to me.
I get the message.
I understand.
I do it too.
I do it right back to you.
However, this is a place.
This is an establishment for children.
The acts being performed.
I only perform on my wife.
Only her and no one else.
I've made her a vow and I don't like to break it even in cartoon form.
I have a work relationship with Mickey and I would never fight him in such a manner.
I forget.
Was it Minnie or Mickey in the bit?
I can't remember.
I don't appreciate you depicting me doing sex acts with all of your characters and all of ours.
The Walt Disney Company owns hundreds of characters and I can't believe you took the time to draw me fucking all of them following our list of acts.
I would never perform on Chuck E.
Cheese.
Number one, Felatio.
Number two, analingus.
Number three, cigar stuff.
This is the world's largest Chuck E.
Cheese in San Jose, California.
Yeah.
Because Sestrates and Eats has been to a lot of Chuck E.
Cheese.
Oh, OK.
And found the various different shows and such.
Oh, he's a cataloger of the shows.
He's cataloging a lot.
Wow.
He's doing the Lord's work and I appreciate it.
There's one little thing and we'll get to the much nicer Gilroy Gardens.
But after there's a lot of filth at the top and the filth isn't done because I texted you guys something here.
Don't look yet.
Don't spoil it for yourselves.
I found, you know, because I'm just scouring this Chuck E.
Cheese for like old remnants of old Chuck stuff.
And I found a pretty old school little display in the way they got a lot of like big window display space to fill.
So they have to keep some old Chuck stuff up there just to even have anything to make sure that's not just empty.
So a pretty great display that it's like it's like an old movie theme.
Right.
And it's like a little little scene is being filmed with where Chuck, modern Chuck and Helen are having lunch.
They're having a nice lunch together.
And this is nice.
And then there's like I think there might be a camera and there's definitely film reels and like a clapboard and the clapboard says title show biz and me starring Chuck E.
Cheese location San Jose producer Pete Tenayuka.
I don't know who that is.
That's not a cartoon.
That's not one of their characters.
Maybe that's who started the branch.
I'm not sure.
The point is it's a little like movie themed thing and there's a big film strip and it has some pretty like usual suspects in terms of old classic movies to show.
There's Gone with the Wind and there's The Wizard of Oz.
But I now ask you guys to look at the picture that I sent you and just register when you see what I saw that was a tad alarming in this tribute to black and white Hollywood.
Just zoom around.
I think you'll I think you'll get it.
I think I think I I see Captain Kangaroo.
No they and that's just a nice thing.
Okay that's nice to see him.
Wizard of Oz.
Yeah keep going you're heading in the right direction.
Okay.
Is Bill Cosby in this?
Yeah.
Bill Cosby's up there.
You got a lurking Cosby.
It's a smaller picture so I wasn't sure but yeah.
And Culp right?
And yes and yes Culp you might remember from Cyber Mania 94.
It's a nice ride.
It's from I Spy which is a television show not a film so it should not be on a film reel.
So that's issue number one.
Issue number two is the continued presence of Bill Cosby in the window of their store.
This is in the windows out front basically.
I mean to be fair this doesn't look like it's been updated recently.
I don't believe so no.
I guess just you know.
Well I guess I'm going to address the manager specifically.
A lot to do a lot on our mind you know between needing to distribute alcohol wipes to briefly negligent parents and then having to help the same briefly negligent parents.
Yeah.
With their creepy questions.
She's got a lot on her plate but I would just say check your store for hidden Cosby's.
This could be the case with any.
I remember I've also speaking of world's largest I've also been to the world's largest McDonald's.
Oh yeah.
Which is on I Drive in Orlando and that's had a big redo since I was there and it was okay.
Well it was never okay but it's especially not okay.
There was there was a big Cosby in the store that I believe is gone now.
So if you're a world's largest store check for Cosby's every once in a while.
They check for gas leaks.
Yeah.
The plumbing is working and make sure you got no Cosby's.
I think that's why I see there maybe has been one there and you have no idea.
Yeah.
Wise words.
Largest target world's largest.
The hardware could be a Cosby's can be anywhere.
Yeah.
So yeah.
That's a good lesson.
If you're listening to this and you on the world's largest something.
Beyond the alert.
How I'm disappointed honestly that you didn't get to get up there.
So yeah I wish that I'd been hyping and I think don't ask the manager.
I think you got to ask.
Yeah.
I mean I should have.
I understand why you did it.
Just in hindsight.
It's the one that I'd met.
I met the other one who didn't know what an alcohol.
She's got all the keys.
Yeah.
I mean ultimately that's that's who you want to talk to.
Well I guess I'm going to have to go up to this area again which I would be happy to
because they have great places like Gilroy Gardens and you know maybe I felt like top
loading you know snarky or gross stuff here at the top because I don't really know how
to I feel a little like you know vulnerable heading into this year.
Yeah.
Because this is I just love this place.
Like do I have a know how do you do this when you just love a play.
We got to take a page from Andrew Barth Feldman's book.
Yeah.
Just being excited about something.
But I don't don't we all use snark and jokes as armor and when that armor is stripped away
by a nice place like Gilroy Gardens what do you do.
Yeah.
I watched a few videos and I saw some people writing about it online referring to it as
like the most beautiful theme park in America because it it is seems to be you know a horticultural
like botanical garden.
Yes.
First and foremost.
Exactly.
It grew out of that.
It was that first and became a theme park in 2001 and has evolved since then.
But don't any of the gardens look shitty and we can make fun of the gardens like they look
like you know some trash hanging around or something like there's got to be some cynical
angle this podcast the ride.
Well we can roast the circus trees.
Okay.
Yeah.
Those whimsical pieces of shit.
There's a way trees are supposed to look okay.
If there's not a big branch if there's not like a branch what's the there's not a big
trunk trunk.
I don't want no holes in my trunk.
Okay.
We don't care.
Let's let's just tear these trunks up.
Oh people in the past just totally bemused by silly little Swiss cheese trees.
Yeah.
They didn't.
They didn't have our phones and our gadgets.
Those simpletons.
Yeah.
I would entertain them for a day seeing some wonderfully cultivated trees designed bent
into all kinds of whimsical shapes.
Oh shoot.
I what can I got.
I got nothing here.
I'm veering back into sincerity.
Yeah.
I guess I guess I just got to go with it.
And you know what I really was I feel like okay I knew about Gilroy.
I've taken trips up north before and I've driven through Gilroy and the smell of garlic
has wafted into the car just passing by.
So I thought this is a silly place that smells like garlic and maybe I heard that there is
a theme park or something and I thought well that's got to be some that that's got to be
like what's the you know in it like a goofy movie where they go to the kind of podunk
clusters possum.
Yeah.
I'm like it's going to be like that.
Right.
But with garlic and all kinds of stuff that it's you know it's garlic milkshakes and garlic
waffles and all this shit that's not good and it's going to be janky and then it's not
that at all.
I think there are probably things like that in Gilroy.
I think there are a little like knickknack stores and they do a garlic festival.
And there's so I think I probably had seen photos of a lot of these things conflated
them in my heads in my heads.
I was I was of multiple heads about this subject and and thought that I was getting something
silly into snarkette.
But instead it's just what you said.
It is like I would say America.
Absolutely.
It is the most beautiful.
It's certainly the most beautiful park I have been to in America.
Absolutely.
Wow.
Yeah.
It seems like like I think Disney's Animal Kingdom beautiful landscaping.
It's been open for a while now.
So the trees are really grown in.
And this is because it started it was built over time by a family who sold their grocery
store chain.
Yes.
And then use the funds to build it.
And then slowly it was a nursery and then then it was you know for the employees of
the grocery stores and then they hired the Paramount Parks to manage it.
Yeah. It's open for a little bit initially called Bonfonte Gardens.
That's the family Michael and Claudia Bonfonte.
They own Knob Hill Foods and it was a place for their employees to spend time which is
a very like old school that feels like a turn of the century idea.
That is how Hershey project.
Oh I heard she park started.
Yeah.
That was a play that was grounds like a nice picnic park for the sprawling factory.
To apologize for them getting chocolate long.
Yeah.
All day every day.
But he's yeah he's just he's a big tree fan.
He just really believes in the beauty and the power of trees and wants to communicate
this some out of the public.
And I think it is open a little bit as a botanical garden.
But then he realizes that the only way to make it economically viable is to add rides.
But how do we add rides and still keep it very beautiful.
And they definitely pulled that off.
It is also like for L.A. people or for you guys if you've been to Descanso Gardens or
Huntington Gardens one of these.
I mean it's like one of those spaces but with rides and a lot of them.
OK. I like those places.
I like them too.
But already I liked them pre-kid.
I loved them post-kid.
They're one like you know he wants to do is just kind of like roam free through a beautiful
place.
And so to get that plus attractions that are really well done it's great.
It's so great.
So yeah you're right that you OK.
Yeah. The history of it Paramount's part of it.
They're just operating it initially because I think this place is not going well from
2001 to 2003.
So they need somebody to take care of the theme park stuff who gets the theme park stuff.
And then that causes it to get folded into all that this history that we've gone over
with so many parks where it's Paramount but then Paramount is bought by Cedar Fair.
So it's one of those.
And then only recently did it shed the Cedar Fair relationship.
I think the contract ended in 2021.
Really recently.
A video I saw I think it's Cano B Coaster is the channel was talking about how they
were there in 2022 and they were still taking the Cedar Fair Platinum Pass that gets you
into every Cedar Fair Park.
Oh OK.
And we're still selling Fastlane I think is their line skipping.
They still do.
Yes it's the same branding of their Fastpass Skip the Line thing.
You see those same signs as you see in Great America but it's otherwise not related.
But there was a time where you could have gotten passes to all of this.
Yes.
Which should be great.
That's a great value.
There was you know there were things to like about Great America.
But you add it to this.
I mean this truly if you're if you were listener if you were passing through this area and
you have to pick if I have not if you haven't gotten this just already take Gilroy Gardens
it's great because like I would say it was really like for experiencing new theme parks
that new to me it doesn't happen that often with me.
And so to like get a vibe and start like that that's something you only have your first
like 10 minutes in the right to do is just what is the vibe here.
And I was so bummed to realize Great America the first the first thing that occurred to
me was charmlous.
That went straight into my head.
I'm like I'm going to find things to do here.
We have some fun here but there is definitely not any charm.
And then the opposite when you go into Gilroy I didn't know what we were in for because
you're driving in through pretty landscape but also kind of like nondescript to some
extent a little brown.
I don't know is this just going to be like the way theme parks are plopped into some
kind of farmland.
And it's like pretty adjacent or there's something way in the background that's nice to look
at.
But instead this place you're just you're just suddenly in this lush oasis.
It is so green.
The mission accomplished on the trees beautiful trees everywhere.
The did like the Disney Berm ideas so like blown away.
But you know they have like a layer of trees sometimes while blocking the street or whatever.
But this is you don't know like you assume that forest just goes and goes you feel totally
the only like it's what it's it's what Efteling sounds like.
I feel like.
I what Jason was saying where it's you know you just are in genuine forests but that has
rides and stuff.
Maybe it's the closest we have in America to that possibly.
I what's the other.
What's the big oh just like waterfalls everywhere.
Great waterfalls.
Lake Lake is incredible.
Do I have one.
Would I.
I mean I'll just I would end up just showing you a picture of a nice lake and you would
say oh that looks nice.
So it might not be need to do that.
Wait.
Well hey I might as well.
Yeah.
Show us the photo.
Look at this.
I was ready to make fun of it but it's beautiful.
No you were going to use like this is I got Scott here finally.
You think that's pretty.
Yeah.
You think my puke is pretty.
I was going to throw up.
You can't can you look at that.
No it is.
That is great.
Yeah serene.
Then.
So you got a good vibe just from like before you're even in the play it just like the parking
lot is beautiful signage is great.
Then you get into the park proper and you are hit with this blast of music that is such
a delight.
Oh yeah.
This point I'm going to address very specifically.
Kevin from Telethon and my friend Tyler if you guys are listening you will be happy to
It is this wonderful soundtrack of Super Synthy 90s New Age that is not I will say it's not
like what I listened to necessarily.
Sure.
But for I mean OK it's basically it's like and thankfully somebody has cataloged some
of this on Spotify on a playlist called horticulture hymns the music of Gilroy Gardens.
I assume this is accurate because it sounds like what I heard but it's like I mean the
big names are Mannheim steamroller and Yanni and then there's a little bit of Mike Post
and then a guy named Steve Hawn and just this will give you the vibe a little bit Steve
Hawn.
This is some of what you hear.
Big old, big powerful drums and then...
Oh man, this is like Weather Channel or Hold Music or...
It's like what?
Weather Channel music or...
Yes, Weather Channel is right on the money.
Yeah, yeah, that feels totally right.
It's like, it's very silly.
It's definitely cheesy.
It's definitely bombasty.
But I don't want people to start thinking,
I've already got caught some shit
because I've said that I like Kenny G stuff
on the podcast a little bit.
Although that's one of those...
Because I've seen comments that are like,
Scott's going to scold people about music taste
and he likes Kenny G.
Hey, listen, the Kenny G that I'm talking about,
you have not heard.
I promise you, you have not heard the Kenny G that I mean.
I know what you're picturing,
but the Kenny G I like is some really good Kenny G.
I have to take my word on this.
What era?
Early 80s.
He was like wrapped up in...
He started in legit like jazz fusion funk.
I'm not just going to start playing it,
but I swear, he was involved with this guy, Kashif,
who did a lot of really great R&B producer.
That's like Kenny G, I know it got cheesy.
I'll get a little cheesy with Kenny G too.
I'll listen to some Pure Mood.
There's lots of Pure Mood's riffs online.
You're not talking about Pure Mood though.
No, no, I know, I know.
I'm saying the cheesier stuff.
Yeah, yes, totally.
I'll listen to some whale songs.
I admit, you know what it is if you're getting into that.
But there is for sure some just legit instrumental funk
that he was part of that is fantastic
and some top tier music videos from back then as well.
Before we grew the hair out,
you're like Kenny Gorelick does not bear any resemblance
to the Kenny G that I know.
But anyway, look, I'm not going to pretend
that I listen to a lot of Yanni and Mannheim Steamroller,
but I have an appreciation for it.
And I'll tell you,
maybe I'll get some listeners back on board with this
because where are you hearing early 90s Yanni and Mannheim
Steamroller, you're hearing that in Epcot Center
and maybe Tomorrowland as well.
And when you hear it in this theme park setting,
it's like where's Spaceship Earth, where's Horizons?
It's gotta be around the corner.
You hear that music and you're like,
I'm going to get edutained today.
I'm an infert, I'm gonna see so many edutainers.
Well, it sounds a little like the ending song
with different pictures and tomato girl
of living with the land.
Certainly, yes.
Yeah, absolutely.
And you know what?
This was all in my head for a lot of the,
because this park is simple,
it has aspects of educational, of edutainment.
There is even a big greenhouse.
And I'm like, why am I so enamored with this?
And yet I've found myself so bored by living with the land.
And maybe this is the gateway that I needed.
Maybe I go back and appreciate living with the land
a little more because I now know how to better,
I've seen the fusion of theme park and farm
that works for me and that worked for a little child as well.
And maybe that's the step that I need.
Just like, and again, listener,
I will give you the gateways to the Kenny G
that I like if you need them.
Like the same, you need music to,
you're missing that middle step.
So maybe, I don't know,
maybe this is my gateway to living with the land.
Could be.
Oh, wow.
Maybe, I mean, this does have the,
is it the monarch garden that has the monorail
that goes through it?
Is that the big greenhouse?
I didn't end up going in there,
except that really fantastic part of the trip
was getting on a train,
because we got to prioritize trains for our three-year-old.
And we hadn't really been in the park much,
which this is a good way,
this would be a good way to do Disneyland, honestly.
How many people actually have gotten to Disneyland
for the first time in their lives and done the train first?
That'd be kind of a trippy way to do it
because you suddenly are like,
wow, this place goes and goes.
I've experienced bits and pieces of the theming,
and now I get to go do the details.
Be kind of a cool way to do it, I think.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll do that with the babies first.
Could.
Well, and the train's a good first one to do,
because it moves, but it barely moves.
You could not be scared by the train.
Hopefully not.
It's basically a room that moves a little bit.
That'd be, and it's maybe a cool way to do it.
But that's what we got to do here,
where we thought this place was dinky.
It was gonna end pretty fast.
And instead, this train ride keeps going and going.
You're like, you're kidding.
And they have this and they have this and they have this.
And then it goes inside the greenhouse,
which is a huge greenhouse.
And it's a real like, whoa moment,
because you don't know they have it,
and you're amazed that the train is going in there.
And then you're hitting waterfalls,
and then seeing that they have a whole water park
and everything too.
It's just, the scope of this place is really fantastic.
Let me just name some other stuff.
Swan boats, you got swan boats.
And then you got like, I mean, really what it is,
really the core of it,
and listeners will know if they've been there,
is it's just, it's as simple as this.
It's rides that are big fruits.
It's just big fruits, big strawberries.
They swing around, they get a little bit off the ground,
but not too much.
It doesn't scare your three-year-old.
There's a big silly symphony swings kind of thing.
A giant swing mechanism, but it's a giant mushroom.
Like you can see, you can picture that shape.
That works great.
And I say that, and I'm like, well, isn't that like,
this place opened 2001.
There's a little bit of like an acoustic guitar,
plucky, mediocre jazz element
playing musically all over the place.
There's farm stuff, little simple rides
that are showing you what a fun.
This is, it's a little bit DCA 1.0.
That's, I don't know, I was thinking that a little bit,
and I was wondering.
In a good way, in the best way,
not in the like clashy, ugly signs way,
or like rides that they have fast way.
It feels, this whole place feels to me like,
if they had pulled off Bountiful Valley Farm.
I was gonna say, it's like Bountiful Valley Farm,
but I didn't, which I never got to experience.
No, I don't know if it would change your mind
if you experienced it. Sure.
Cause you know what it didn't have? Rides.
Yeah. It was stuff that you climb on.
But this place, I mean, like why not,
like Eisner wants his farm area.
Yeah. He wants to show you
how a farm works.
Okay, do that, but then have a ride that's in a big apple.
Right? Like why, like, and of course,
now I brought this up partially because
there was a big orange.
I'll give them that.
They did have a big orange, but it wasn't enough.
And also the orange stinger was confusing.
Why oranges and bees?
These things did not, those don't go together to me at all.
I never understood.
That seems like two things.
Why would it have been a honeycomb?
Yeah. Wait, yes.
Big honeycomb. Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, I don't know.
No answer.
Why is the giant orange by the seaside pier
not traditionally where orange groves would be found?
A swing set, an unadorned swing set,
you just put it in a seaside pier like the golden zephyr.
The golden zephyr makes sense as like.
Well, they got it right.
Now it's just like, you know,
swing ride with nice trimming, basically.
Yeah, basically.
They figured it out, but wait,
I never even thought about that, that oranges,
you know, oranges have to be inland, right?
I guess oranges are consumed by the sea.
They wouldn't have to be.
But the orange groves were taking a-
In Anaheim. In Anaheim.
There was plenty in Anaheim, that's true.
But also you're right, like steps away from the Malibuumer.
Look, there was a lot of issues.
There was a lot.
He should have put it right,
and I'm sure it was just like an extra 50K,
and he was like, that's out.
I think so. Save money.
Yeah, yeah, I think they were.
They were. Nothing, yeah.
Nickel and doubt.
Well, they'd put a lot of muscle into suing Chuck E. Cheese
for various sexual photos,
so didn't have a lot of left over there.
McDonald's bailed our ass out with this bear invasion.
We'd have nothing without them.
And then you get, you know, you're more unusual.
You get artichokes.
So you get artichoke dip.
You're just sitting in big artichokes that swing around.
Great, love it.
We had a great time.
I can't give more than sentence long reviews of these,
but that's not what you're supposed to do.
They all, they aim for a real A ticket kind of thing,
and they deliver.
It's all great.
And then of course, garlic twirl.
And this is the one that I knew about,
and I thought it was all gonna,
I thought maybe this was the only ride
or something was garlic twirl.
And this is where it is a bunch of garlic bulbs.
And so it's like the teacups,
except it's more of a little room that they lock you in.
That is a weird part about this park I forgot,
that they closed the door,
and then when the ride's over,
you try to get out and you cannot get out.
And then the single employee has to go around
with the one key that is a really weird particular shape
like the Ikea screws thing.
It's like a really odd little implement
that only he can let you out with.
Or it's kind of like, you know,
what gets the plastic off of liquor bottles
at the grocery store.
Oh yeah, very specific, like proprietary technology.
An Allen wrench.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like where if this guy got,
like if he fell in the lake or a bird came by
and stole that thing,
you might be locked in the garlic bulb for hours.
There might be like 10 of those in existence.
In the world.
Yeah, because that's the rarest of rare.
You're not going into a hardware store
and making a copy of that.
No, I don't think you could.
You can't copy that key.
I don't believe so.
Yeah.
It seems like pretty space age technology to me.
I mean, you should, it would be funny to try,
but they have all those kiosks now
where you can make your own key duplicates.
So maybe some of the Gilroy Gardens employees
have tried to go to those places, get duplicates,
so that they can.
Open the door.
They were on the clock.
They got a slurpee.
Open doors whenever they want.
And they try to make a copy of the Allen wrench
at the 7-Eleven kiosk and it immediately started smoking.
Does not compute a killing self.
So can I get a Buffalo chicken roller
and also your thing smoking back there?
So yeah, you're in big garlic bulbs and they spin around
and that's great.
That's what you want out of the garlic theme park.
Great, delivered.
I didn't like when a bumblebee flew in,
especially given that there were not a lot of windows
and things, was getting a little claustrophobic in there,
but it flew out right away.
It was fine.
Can I ask a quick question?
If these rides were more indoors,
would you have been afraid of the size
of the vegetable or fruit?
Oh.
Were they not big enough?
Were they not that big?
Maybe I would have been afraid
if they had faces or something.
Yeah, I think in and of them,
no, I don't think I'm afraid of a big fruit.
What if you could imagine the size of the strawberry
and it's in this garage?
Well, the garage is small.
I guess it might bother me.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, I'm gonna give you that one.
But I don't think the theme park is gonna end up,
unless they do a haunt event where you go into,
and they do do a Halloween event,
but I don't know if it has anything
where you end up in a small room with a big scary fruit.
Yeah, probably not.
A rotting fruit.
Do you ever get afraid
when there's the biggest pumpkin contest?
I haven't been to one, so maybe on some level,
I am afraid of them.
I feel like I've seen big pumpkins, but.
Now imagine they're in this garage with us.
I wouldn't like a pumpkin that mostly filled the garage, no.
Okay.
No, I wouldn't like that.
And maybe I will, if I ever attend a big pumpkin contest,
I'll try to make sure that it's in a stable type of environment
or a hall.
If I see room, and especially if I see closet,
no way, I'm sorry.
You will have to get your pumpkin money from other people.
Okay, that's fair.
Okay, well, let me ask a question.
What is this giant plastic orb?
This is not a joke.
Yeah, that is, I know.
That's been in the corner of my eye
the whole time we've been talking.
That's a litter robot that broke.
We have two cats, so it's a more efficient way to.
That is a lot more sizable than I thought those things were,
but I understand it.
You clocked what I was saying.
We're talking about big things in a garage,
and that is taking up a lot of space.
What would you describe in fruit or vegetable terms?
What does that seem like?
Oh, good question.
Well, what's pretty circular?
A big pea.
A big pea, sure.
A big gray pea.
A big pea is good, yeah.
A pea is probably the most circular kind of thing,
and it looks like it's placed on a carrier
or like a display of some kind.
This thing looks like you would load your baby in
and shoot, if Krypton was exploding,
you would load your baby in and shoot your baby off to Earth
to save the baby.
I thought maybe it was a rocking thing.
Space cradle.
Like I thought maybe, oh, they put the baby in this thing.
It wasn't a baby thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Rocks, yeah.
If you saw the other side, if I turn it around,
and I could if you want, but if I turn it around,
you would see a lot of caked on litter
with that's got perma pea stickiness.
It's not a pretty scene.
Thing conked out on us, so we have to figure out
a new pea and poo disposal situation for the cats.
Your correct, Mike, that it is very Superman,
and we had this before our child showed up,
and it was definitely a fear that he goes,
rocket ship, tries to climb in the thing.
Yeah, yeah.
And then he also then gets in and says, sandbox.
We assumed big time curiosity.
I think we had to teach him early on.
This is the opposite of where you should go.
Yeah, smart.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Well, now you know about that.
You know what, while I'm looking in that direction,
let me, I'm gonna get up towards it
and bring something over here,
and this is a specific Gilroy Gardens,
I think one of the best facets of the park.
Here I am going on about artichoke rides and garlic rides,
but you might be thinking these are not the rubric
by which we judge theme parks, right?
Oh, I know where you're going.
We judge by, I mean, one of them is IP.
One of them is original IP, and that can be whatever,
and I'm sorry to say there's no dark rides here.
That's a disappointment, because I think they would pull off
a great dark ride, given the charm of the place,
but there are characters, and I'm gonna go fetch the character.
Yeah, I was hoping.
There he is.
Gil, the Gilroy garlic.
Wow.
Look at this guy.
Look at his sunglasses.
He, it is, he's a big garlic bulb wearing sunglasses,
and he's got a big smile, and until I was really analyzing,
why do I like him so much?
I really like him, and I saw photos of him,
and I thought, yeah, that looks a little stupid,
and then when I saw the toy,
I thought there's nothing stupid about this.
I really like him, and I think in analyzing it,
he's very Kool-Aid man, right?
Yeah.
Sunglasses, smile, big bulbous guy, big seat.
He's got a massive seat.
He's a rotund fella, but then kind of, you know,
it's whittled down to nothing up at the top.
Then he's just got like a burst of hair or leaves,
or a peel, I guess, whatever you wanna call it.
He's very 90s, I would say, in general.
That's the vibe from him, and that's why I'm so drawn to him
and his features immediately.
He, the first thing I thought of was cool spot.
Yeah.
Oh, the 7-Up.
Yeah, 7-Up.
Absolutely, for sure.
Just, you're right that it's very 90s,
where all you had to do in the 90s
is put a mouth and sunglasses on something,
and great, and you love him.
That's all it, it's like a couple of lines.
How few lines can we use to make you love
an inanimate object?
Right, right.
Let me throw him to you, because he is satisfying
to throw.
The way the limbs dangle on this toy,
I've been throwing him with the boy ever since.
Does he have, actually, I missed this,
does he talk at all in the park?
I did not see any, unless there is a show
that I'm not aware of, and if any listeners
are Gilroy Garden's heads, please make me aware,
because I would love to know what this guy sounds like.
You know what, he also reminds me of what are those little,
are they books, like Mr. Happy and Mr. Angry?
Those little small kids books.
And now, I'm gonna find out what they're called,
and then I'm gonna say that I've recently seen them
try to rebrand those as memes in a Walmart.
We were going up.
Aren't they the original emojis, right?
Yes.
Aren't they?
I've seen them as memes on Instagram.
Yeah.
It's, I don't know.
Mr. Angry?
I believe there maybe was a point in time
where they were gonna make a movie out of those.
Oh, I'm sure that's the case.
Mr. Yuck, is that one of them?
Yeah.
Or that's the poison control guy.
That's the guy.
Oh, have we done that episode?
This is very funny.
Mr. Yuck.
Counts, great.
The sunglasses are kind of hinged on some fabric,
and you pull them up and there's no eyes.
Yes, really weird, right?
Yeah, you got nothing.
There's not even dots.
You got absolutely nothing.
It makes him very strange looking, just like zero.
They saved some money not putting the dots there.
What does he do?
What does he do with zero with nothing representing eyes?
Yeah, my son's in an age where we're throwing plushes
all the time, and this is the most throwable.
Also, the limbs are just so satisfying to wave around.
I was having him fart a lot too.
We got a lot of farts going on,
so I know there was a lot of like, toot, toot.
That's what he's, yeah, yeah.
Is that his voice?
Yeah, toot, toot.
Does it, I don't know, does it add up
that a garlic guy would fart a lot?
Because he makes people fart?
I don't know if garlic makes, I guess depending
on your tolerance or your particular stomach, he might.
Well, it depends.
I mean, if a garlic, if an anthropomorphic garlic
is sort of brought to life by magic,
then I feel like maybe he doesn't fart,
but if there's, he actually has like a lower GI
and upper GI, like if he has a tract
and he actually has a bio, like there's a biological reason.
Wait, GI, what's GI?
I don't know, that's what the doctors say, right?
When they're talking about your intestines and stuff.
Yeah, I was gonna say, is garlic a thing?
Is it acidic?
Is that an acid reflux one?
For having garlic?
Oh yeah, maybe.
I'm gonna have to look up GI now.
Because I have learned that I am kind of susceptible
to like all the delicious high acidity foods,
tomato sauce, hot tea, hot coffee, you know.
Yeah, they can really.
I have some of that.
Wait, what are you saying?
Do they make you toot?
No, not really, much of a tooter.
Gil, get off the mic, don't call Jason a tooter.
He's not a tooter.
It's kind of a constant burning.
Oh yeah, no, this guy don't look like a tooter to me.
Yeah, okay.
Toot, no, that was you, I know that was you.
I know when you're talking.
This guy's got a 90s attitude too.
Yeah.
I'll say that.
Yeah, what can I say?
You know, before I had shades, not much attitude.
Also couldn't see at all.
Kind of put me in my place, I just sort of like rolled around,
couldn't get up or do anything or know what my life was.
But ever since I got these shades.
I'm a regular on Tough Trail with Gung Win.
Yeah, me and Norton, we'd get into some pretty big rift fests.
I was in the wet whack pack for a week, it didn't work out.
You know, it was a lot of fun, you know.
Let me add a morbid question
as you're holding the stuffed garlic.
Did you try the garlic fries?
I did not actually.
I heard that was a thing to get.
It seemed like the theme park food there was a lot of fried stuff,
a lot of bakery stuff.
Oh, I think this guy tried some earlier too.
Gil, stop.
No, I did not have garlic fries.
Those my current farts that are filling up the garage
are from other foods.
Different foods.
Healthier foods.
GI means gastrointestinal.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
Oh, I should have known.
That should have known.
I mean, I should have known too.
You all should have known, you idiots.
Oh.
It feels like Will Arnett should play him in a big budget film.
Hey, this is Gil at CyberMedia 94.
Everybody's going nuts for NBA Jam up here.
Hey, cool it, kids.
Young Will Arnett.
An AI recreation of 24-year-old Will Arnett
should do the voice of Gil.
Right?
His name is Gil?
Yeah, Gil, that's right.
Gilroy, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Gilroy garlic.
Mm-hmm.
And don't forget my catchphrase, dude.
I also, my son has been, my son just started calling this guy
White Guy.
That's what he's been.
Throw White Guy.
And I don't have the heart to tell him
that White Guy has just, doesn't have the best ring to it.
Yeah, yeah.
These days.
Well, these days.
It's not something anybody is, I'm certainly proud to be.
Or should you be?
From the mouths of babes, you know.
To him.
Well, yeah, when you hear the phrase White Guy,
you probably conjure some bad stuff.
But to him, if you reset and a White Guy is just this cool
garlic and sunglasses.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Cool White Guy.
He knows his colors.
He does, yes, he is correct.
Gil's got a girlfriend.
I assume they're together, or at least a female equivalent.
It's the same mini relationship that
you can change it depending on what your needs are for a story
or something.
Oh, we fuck.
As a friend with benefits.
So situationship, I learned that term recently.
It's fairly not desirable.
What is it?
What does it mean?
I think it's like friends with benefits, nothing serious
kind of thing.
Situationship?
I'm going to look it up to correct myself.
Sorry if anyone's had to deal with that and it was unpleasant.
Don't want to just be flipping.
I've been flourishing my situationship.
And then this podcast that I listen to says that it's not
something that is beautiful.
The funny thing about that is just the elevated term for it.
That's all.
I'm not even judging.
Ship is a dressing up that I don't think it deserves.
Look, maybe now I'm getting into club random territory.
But then there's also a phrase I've heard recently too.
Ethical non monogamy is the phrase that is on a lot of.
Well, I'm an old man who just learned about it, Jason.
But again, these are very elevated terms for like, I want to have
sex with other people too.
I've been doing ethical monogamy for years.
Non monogamy.
I don't perform ethical non monogamy with my wife.
On our colorful array of classic characters.
I do not have a situationship with Minnie Mouse, Daisy Duck,
or Claire Bellacal.
Situationships can be defined as a romantic relationship
that lacks commitment and the associated norms
and expectations.
That's from Women's Health 11 Signs.
You might be in a situationship.
11 signs you're in a situationship
and how to handle it like a dating pro.
That's definitely going to be a TV show in the next six months.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Situationship and then how quickly can they sell that
and then how quickly will it be on CBS and then gone after one season?
Yeah, sure.
How much money will they spend on one season of situationship
that will never be watched by anyone again?
I mean, a lot.
You know what Josh Radner's great is?
I mean, goddamn.
Who's Josh Radner?
Wasn't he the star of How I Met Your Mother?
I don't know.
Is that a man's name?
Forgive me.
I was not a watcher of this program.
Or not.
He's not father.
He's How I Met Your Mother.
He was the star.
I think Neil Patrick Harris.
Yeah, Josh Radner, Jason Sego, Colby Smulders, Neil Patrick Harris.
Sal Sinclair.
I know now the names of the other people.
Kristen Milati later on.
I didn't know her name, but I knew the other names.
I just didn't know Josh Radner's name.
I apologize.
What I meant was his quote is probably very high now
after heading up a very popular show.
You know?
Well, and to play a character with kind of mixed likeability,
like somebody willing to be in a situationship.
Yeah, right.
Well, then that's why we have to go to somebody who's cheaper,
like a Jason Sheridan.
Jason Sheridan is.
Oh, our first scale.
The first CBS sitcom star.
Situationship.
Jason is in a situationship practicing ethical nonmonogamy.
And it's 8 p.m. on CBS on Thursday night.
As long as you make it clear.
Oh, yeah, you're playing.
That is on TV.
I mean, a committed relationship in reality.
This is a TV show.
Oh, yeah.
You're playing Jason Sheridan, though, on the show.
Oh, OK.
That's your name.
But let me ask you this.
On your way to a committed relationship,
was there ever a window, be it a day or a week or a month,
or who knows, where you would have defined
this relationship as a situationship?
Was it ever a situationship?
Because we may have all, Lindsay and Erin,
but there was probably maybe just an afternoon
where you're like, well, for the sake of, you know what?
I think it's a situationship.
For the sake of the public record, no, it was always
a very specific, defined thing.
That's what I'm going to say while we're talking
on microphones that are being recorded.
This was your wife.
I think, yeah, we didn't.
We we got serious reasonably quickly.
We didn't really see any other people, but we were.
It was a little casual to start.
Sure.
So it was ethical monogamy.
I yeah, I think so.
I think it was a bunch of a couple of real neurotic little
weirdos trying to figure it out.
But yeah.
Always ethical.
You make sure.
I pride myself.
I'm a very ethical person, honestly.
Very.
Well, there are people who are going to learn all about it
at 8 PM on CBS on Thursday nights.
And yet, can't you like, you know that anyone who goes out
of their way to like tweet, see, I practice ethical monogamy.
You know, that person does not do it.
Or would not be not.
No, no, no.
I think if you brag about it like, no, I don't know.
I guess I just mean it's just the way I was raised.
I guess I believe in ethical monogamy.
That person has so many fairs.
Well, that's true because because because no one's even
asking about is your monogamy.
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
If you go out of your way, if you've just tweeted that
unprompted or said it in a conversation or on a date.
That's a red flag.
Yes.
John, this person is a sex addict.
That's like the John Lovett's character.
The liar would say that.
Yeah.
Anyway, I believe ethical monogamy with Roy or Royale.
It's Gil and Roy.
Right.
And Roy is defined as a tomboy.
OK, that's the name.
That's how they backed into Roy.
What's the full name?
Roy.
Gil Roy.
Royale.
Oh, Royale.
You said it.
OK.
Mm hmm.
Royale or Roy like R.O.Y.
E.L.L.E.
Oh, OK.
Royale. I've never heard that name like a Royale with cheese,
you know, in France.
Yeah.
Anyway, is this this original IP is good.
There's Halloween stuff.
They have I didn't watch a lot of these shows, but they got Wolfgang
Werewolf and Cranium, the mad scientist.
We got a lot of their events.
The great big boo.
Yeah.
Seems very charming.
That would be the time to go back up as Halloween time.
I would really like to.
And you know what?
And you know, they and of course, this is the kind of place that does
like the Christmas lights event.
If I was up there, if I was within an hour of this place, membership,
annual pass, whatever, I'm going to every special event.
Really wish I was I was there.
That's it. It's lovely.
Sure.
Do any other?
I did you get a chance to do the these look pretty cool.
There are a lot of modes of transit.
Did you do the Rainbow Garden round boats?
Yes, that is one of the most pleasant rides I've ever that also that one has me
that that almost felt to me.
I was thinking while I was on it, this is like a tunnel of love
that doesn't go through a tunnel.
Yeah. And there's no love.
Is it now it's on their big lake and it's just kind of a little.
It's like a rapids ride that doesn't really that is not raucous at all.
It is so gentle.
You just like slowly spin your way down this little path.
And it is so serene.
I know this sounds nothing.
That sounds like nothing as I'm saying it.
But I'm so glad you brought that one up as one of most pleasant rides.
And I was also thinking in the line how this is an episode we never did.
This is this would be a great podcast.
The ride, I think the tunnel of love.
Yeah. For Valentine's Day.
I think we floated this once. Really? Once.
But never obviously did it because I because the tunnel of love to me
is one of those room like
movies and TV for a long time would have you believe
that there are 100 tunnels of love in the world.
Are there two?
It's a good question.
Often like where did this come from?
Was there ever a time where there were lots of tunnels of love?
Because have you ever been in a place with a tunnel of love?
I think this is like a fake idea.
I don't think I have. Yeah. Maybe once.
I know the the appeal of the very dark boat ride,
I think was part of the appeal of the old mill at Kennywood,
which became Garfield's nightmare.
Did they? That's what's been in my head.
Did Kennywood have a tunnel of love?
I don't. I feel like it was just called the old mill.
OK. For, you know, it was an enclosed boat ride.
Then eventually they put big flats of Garfield in there.
Yes. Yeah. Garfield freaking the hell out.
Sodas. Yeah. Yeah.
Pizza. Terrifying.
But yeah, we should dig into that because it also the idea
that something like that would be romantic to anyone as portrayed
in media that there's like cupids and you go through hearts.
Yeah. What is the inside it that makes you feel romantic is a flat of cup.
Like a picture of cupid is what that's certainly what I always know.
See. And like, but it feels like it's only in cartoons.
Only to set up like scenarios. Yeah.
You know, I think at the in the past, I think it was one of those things
where it's like a couple can get some time alone in the dark
to to make out and fool around a little.
And we can't do this at our home.
How long we can't do that ride.
Just a few minutes. People were desperate back then.
For any privacy.
Wait, what year? What year?
In a time before we had these great phrases like situationships
and ethical non monogamy.
And people were more clear. We had no terms to define anything.
We can't. It's a quick.
They needed three minutes in a boat ride to kiss.
Couldn't they go in the car?
That was what the car was for.
If they take my car to get there. Yeah.
Yeah. The car would go park on a on a hill and neck.
And one of the least convenient situations.
Those are in general, just like, you know, being like on a being on a bench,
something where you can't, you know, like face to face.
Maybe I'm alone in this.
I think face to face is the best way to kiss.
Oh, you think so? Yeah, I don't know.
The whole craning your head facing the same way never did it for me.
I don't know. I like being locked right in.
I like to be in a shallow pool in a boat made of plastic and to
really be going at it hot and heavy, as they say.
So horrible creaking for the worst gears and
early animatronics and people yelling like,
it's getting rusty. I told you we have it.
We got to replace them. This thing's going to fall.
The common knowledge urban legend always say whatever you want.
That is a piece, I think, of like haunted haunted houses.
You get scared and you grab the person next to you.
And if you're with someone you like, you know, that was the appeal.
I never occurred to me because I was usually at the haunted mansion with my
family. And I'm like, well, I got to see this.
I got to see all the characters. I see the storyline.
Yeah, Jason, I don't got no game bugging me. Try to get up on me.
I got no comfort to give. I got to look at this. These creaky coffins.
Sitcoms and movies really convinced me that I would make a lot of new
friends and love interests on vacations. And that's really didn't occur.
Yeah, absolutely. Well, and that's what I'm saying is this tunnel of love.
And Jason, I think still think you're describing one thing.
You're describing a dark room where you can get a little,
get a minute for some hanky panky.
But I'm describing a rides where the lights are on and it's very romantic
on a date because there's pink hearts and right. Why would it be romantic?
Yes. Is there actually this anywhere? Has this ever happened?
I bet to me it feels like something a hundred years ago was at like some kind
of carnival show. And maybe it's what you describe.
Maybe it's just what Jason described is in it's a tunnel and it's there's not
much in there. And it's literally, it's just for two minutes of, of pleasure.
The most uninterrupted passion at two minutes.
I don't know. Because also if it's a carnival, you're not, it's not,
it's not easy to set up a boat ride in a carnival.
So it would have to be something that would last for a while.
That thing's dinky. That's just, it would have to be so small.
They just made another like in the downtime,
that's where they like bathe the animals. Yeah. Some carny.
It's a hose that he fills it up with.
Yeah. The carny perfer when he clocks out of animal washing and into ton of love
leering. Yeah. And it's, and yeah, let's be honest.
There's a carny inside there watching everything.
That's probably why they do it. Yeah. Yeah. The like,
cause what need do they have to like, I just want to give the couples a romantic
moment. Young lovers. Yeah. No way. You wanted to watch.
That's why you built the tunnel. I'm an ethical peeping Tom. That's what I,
that's what I'm doing.
Practice ethical non-closing ethical peeping
and ethical paper. Well, we'll, we'll figure this out. I w I think that's it.
That's an episode for sure. We, I'm genuinely curious to know,
are there, there've been a hundred or zero. I have no idea. Um, let me,
let me shout out a couple other things. Oh, they've, there's, uh,
some area of the park, they have this marble dinosaur. Um,
it's just a nice little piece, uh,
but made a little more distinct by the fact that it, it,
this is from knots Berry farm.
I discovered it when we were going back into the knots rides with Rachel Bloom
that outside of kingdom of the dinosaurs, they had this cool marble dinosaur.
They took dinosaur right out of there, uh, sent it up to Gilroy gardens.
I love when charming theme park things and get another life like the California
letters from old California adventure that are outside of what, like the capital.
Yeah.
Billion second as new.
Someone was given a speech at it one time in a deep pandemic. Yeah. Yeah. Um,
so I like to see that. Um, there is also my favorite ride.
My favorite was the last one we did barely got it in before closing. Uh,
it is called South County back roads and this is,
um, it's a car ride and I'll just cut to the chase
better than Autopia. Wow. Easily, easily.
I mean, this is no room of Autopia fans,
but what I think I appreciate is like the way that they make it better.
And there's nothing stopping Disney from doing some of these things. I mean,
they can't do that like inherent thing of this ride,
which is that you load from one station, but there's one track goes one way,
another that goes the other way. Um, one way wasn't working, which sucked,
but if, if both were going, you know, this thing's cooking.
And one way is 1920s cars and one way is 1950s
cars. And this is great. This is a good idea. We of course wanted fifties,
fifties sounded good to me, but if you want to be an old weird jalopy,
you could do that. Um, at this point audience,
we have stopped so many times for a cricket that will not shut the fuck up.
So you're just going to have to deal with the cricket for the rest of the episode.
I'm very sorry. You have no idea how many times we've tried to stop for the
cricket. We were throwing in the towel. This is a perils of recording in a garage.
This is from all the, um,
trash talk you've thrown at the Jiminy cricket from the recent Pinocchio movie.
Oh, I guess so.
You are now getting sort of backlash from the cricket community who are big fans
of Joseph Gordon Levitt's Jiminy cricket. All right. Well, maybe if I say, all right,
you know what? I think Jiminy was very charming.
I think he's better than the original. I think he's very handsome.
Beautiful face.
He sends the sarcasm.
I'm trying to think of something I can see. He adds to the stories rendered in
perfect CGI. He doesn't scare me in the least.
Okay. Great face.
Awesome face makes me comfortable to look at.
I've watched it many times since, not just the once.
Okay. If you still going,
it's almost like you want to make him like kind of tear up or something.
He's so thinks your comments are so beautiful.
Fine. I'll just sing all of when you wish upon a star.
That almost got him. Yeah. All right.
And almost made him stop talking. Okay. Or chirping.
Let's just, we'll just end this sooner than later. Here's the deal with this ride.
Yeah, it is. Okay.
The they take away the gas ability on the car.
So the speed is not controlled by you,
but the steering still is who kids can't even do the gas themselves on the
utopia. They want to steer. No kid is excited about, but mom,
I want you to do the gas. Okay. Actually, you know what?
I take this back because I was obsessed with power wheels and hitting the gas on
a power wheels car. Okay. So I think I would be a little disappointed,
but if it gets rid of like an issue and it's easy, fine.
I steering is more than enough to have a lot of fun.
But you sort of can't, do you ever remember going on the utopia and like,
Oh boy, the gas. Well, no, I,
to me the power wheels almost always seemed 10 times more fun than the utopia.
And I liked fi like, I like going on utopia fine cause you,
it was fun to have some control, but never,
maybe I tried a power wheels once when I was a kid and that felt like free.
I felt free in a power wheels versus utopia, which you still knew as a kid,
you were on a little rail and it wasn't a responsive pedal. Obviously.
Yes. It was like, it felt unsatisfying in a way.
Like wiggle room there, right? You know, like it's either,
it's all the way on or it's all the way off. It's not like you get some,
like half speed that's cool. No. So just take it away. No need to do that.
I'm not upset by that. I'm just remembering that I,
the idea of hitting the pedal was cool to me. Okay.
I do remember putting the pedal to the, yeah, but I think,
but a fair concession, right?
What's this car ride gas powered or was it just electric power through the rail?
Okay. So it didn't stink in the middle of a garden.
Yeah. It doesn't smell. And then just,
and then you have like actual stuff to look at along the way.
There's like different gas stations depending on which area you're in there.
And then you see like a motorcycle cop who's mad.
Then you get into this tunnel, bang, siren guys coming after you.
Wow. The littlest thing. If that happened at the end of utopia,
you got, you have a third act. Now there's like something that occurs in it.
Right. Great. That would be fun. Yeah. And then you, do you pull over or?
You just evade the police?
I, huh? Well, the story of this ride seems to be that you just, you get away.
You've taught all the kids now. Yeah. Yeah. Disobey.
I guess maybe, maybe, you know, I don't know. Hey, you know, or Dave distrust authority.
Hey, you know, okay.
Worst thing. So, okay. Good message to teach. Um,
a cab daddy.
A cab. Oh, okay. Oh, okay.
Robert F Kennedy jr.
I thought you were saying like a 1920s phrase. Hey cab daddy.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
Jason's second album.
Sunglasses are down. The door is on. I'm cradling one of those microphones.
Songs about those new fangled inventions. Cars. Yeah.
I like a cab daddy. You're like calling to the cab driver and you call him cab
daddy. Yeah. Well, and employee, like, oh yeah.
Cause who doesn't have a crush on the cab driver?
That's right. Yeah.
You only get a brief little window with them and don't you want more?
Do you want it to at least turn it into a situation ship? That's right.
Scott, let me ask the issue.
Notice one of the things notable for this park, they have its own web page,
the circus trees. They call them.
Um, yes. Circus trees. You know what? I have to admit,
I didn't super clock them while I was there.
I know that they have these and this is a big part of it and we haven't talked
about that yet. Um, yeah.
So this was like this roadside attraction from that area from long ago.
Yeah. It's moved around a lot.
It's a guy who kind of figured out a way to grow trees in certain shapes or
bending in certain ways.
Yes. Where he would take five trees and like guide them along different paths.
So they would go into like a diamond shape and then refuse at the top and become
one tree again. Yeah. Very Dr. Susie. You know, very,
they, and they have some at Sus Island and islands of adventure,
not circus trees per se, but trees.
Yeah. Yeah. We're due to a hurricane or something like that. A hurricane.
I think when we're two of them, yeah, they got the, the still,
a still living tree that had been kind of bent from hurricane.
Playing God with trees. Yeah. You don't approve.
I mean they might look cool, but if you really, she's, she's just these trees.
How do we know they want to grow like this? That's true.
And we, the trees don't have a way to tell us that they're suffering. Yeah.
And they live forever.
So they got to be like that for, yeah. If, yeah,
if we were bred to have like a, you know, a, a, a weird,
like wicker basket middle, right. Uh, with only, with there are like,
uh, uh, GI, uh, it's just, you know,
we used through in this bizarre fashion that might be very uncomfortable.
That's right. So yeah, I'm just thinking about,
I wonder how they're feeling about it. I hope. Okay.
I remember that this Dr. Moreau of trees. Yeah.
He was brought to justice. He's twisted experiments.
The circus trees started the happening, you know? Yeah.
All right. You've met the trees for the park.
Now meet the ones that I do things with. Yeah.
Yeah. You know what he was doing.
Ethical non-monogamy. Ethical non-mahogany.
Wow. Wow. You nailed it. You nailed it.
Um, let me not try to do much beyond that because that's, uh,
we should just get out on that. But I, but really one more thing before I go, um,
you would think that a park,
a regional park of this nature with off the shelf kind of rides that are very
nice, they're all very well done. Um,
you would not expect a place like this to have an animatronic show. Would you?
And yet, and yet, um,
I'll just cut to the chase of how I learned about this, which was that I,
I went to do the garlic bulb ride because that seemed like the important thing
to do. Uh, but it seemed a little scary for the boy. Uh,
it was a more intense, like more intense than the med tea party would be.
So they went off to look at some waterfalls or something. And, uh,
when I caught up to them, um, Aaron was like, Oh no,
I think you missed the last show of the animatronic singing fruits that do a
beach boys song. Oh no, no,
it was the last one of the day.
What could I want to see more on this earth than that? Um,
what a bummer. Um, and so from that description,
this it's basically it's a food rocks. They have a food right.
It's so much like food rugs. Wow.
There's even like that some of the,
some of the characters are in a fridge that opens up and closes great,
like down to that detail. And I think there's onions and tomatoes. Um,
you'll be happy to hear all of the songs are from before 1965.
Thank goodness. You got, they're all about salads toss, toss it up, baby.
Uh, run around fruit and then, and, uh,
and most of it is dialogue. Most of the,
the 10 minute runtime of the Santa matrona show is quiet dialogue.
So there's only three songs in it, but then it culminates in salads,
USA. Wait, what?
Surfing USA. Uh, what's that? That's a parody of surfing USA. Yes. Yeah. Okay.
Um, so, you know, they didn't exactly nail it.
Did they name the salads like Caesar and I don't think so.
I think it was just like,
cause then you can be healthy and having a good diet.
I want to die early.
I don't have a heart attack. Okay.
I think it was more in that neck of the woods. I would say if everybody had a,
was it just, if everybody had a salad, I would look, it was not the best.
Maybe just salad was said in every line. Okay. Um, it's not the best written show.
It's not the best animatronics you've ever seen. Yeah. But God damn it.
I'm so happy it's there. Wonderful.
This might be one of the only animatronics shows in this country built post
2000, right? Yeah. I guess how many are new? Yeah. Yeah. Good point.
This doesn't happen. We threw this away. This isn't part of our culture anymore.
Right. It isn't Gilroy. Right. And it's 23 years old at the,
what year is it? 22 years old at this point. But like,
yeah, that's still like the youngest, one of the youngest shows,
probably non Disney or universal.
I like you put it in tree terms. Yeah. You're like youngest. Yeah.
It's a fairly young animatronic show, but it's thriving.
It's going to have a nice life and positive spin on it. Yeah. Yeah. Um,
it's so great. It's so great. The cricket returned.
It's so great that the cricket return, which means we should wind it down. Um,
the cricket might be a new recurring character on the show. Yeah.
As we head into some summer nights, we try to avoid the heat and where we have
to, uh, we'll try to not have it be.
The cricket or heat sickness, heat vomiting.
So this ride was a, what this opened in 81.
Oh, the host sir. Oh, we got to restart the recording.
Mike passed out on top of the recorder.
That's the way when you hear certain cuts in the episode,
you won't know that four days passed because we all went to the hospital.
We all got saline. Yeah, we all got saline.
Sorry. I was going to say we all, we all went to like the,
the storefront or I think I've seen them popping up in casinos,
like the vitamin bar, basically like an IV bar where you go when you get
rehydrated. Yeah. We got liquid IV. I took it out at the wedding.
I did some of that. The wedding I just recently went to.
I did the liquid IV to get all like the electrolytes back.
This is an IV injection. Yeah, this is, yeah.
You're saying in Vegas they'll go stab you full of vitamins.
I, they can't, some of them, I have to look them up. I got to find them. Yeah.
Are you sure it's not like it's like a sexy nurse that gives you like a shot?
I think it can get vitamin B shots too. I think it's, I believe so.
Something stuck in your veins?
To get rehydrated from partying to us.
Does this sound right?
Let me tell you, I want to dive in on this. I really do,
but I'm pondering something right now because we're,
we're talking about cricket. Yeah.
The garage door has been open and closed over and over and all of a sudden.
And now smell the air guys. It's a skunk. Yeah.
Well this is a podcast to write first. There's a skunk.
And it's not because Jason's lit up a big fat joint.
I know what you're thinking.
And I'm not tooting. Okay.
Yeah, right. I didn't toot the whole time either. I didn't toot.
Hey toot toot. I, okay.
If that is not the sign we need to end this.
We do need to end it. I agree.
I know what it is. A skunk. All right. Well, look,
the point is Gilroy Gardens is great. It gets you in touch with nature.
The good kind of nature, the pretty kind of nature,
not an annoying cricket and a skunk that might start spraying if we don't wrap
this up soon. So.
What if we get Michael Iser to be a guest on the show and he comes into the
garage and there's a cricket and a skunk?
Pepe, Jiminy.
Well, if the weirdos, a Chuck E.
Cheese dad, they're drug.
They might say that he might start necking with him.
I see Flora. I get to was attracted to Thumper, not Flora from when that's
actually, you know, yeah, that was an episode we haven't released.
Well, only in comparison to other characters. It seemed natural to me.
Okay, look, we'll get into that later.
I would love to not wrap it up super quick, but there's a thousand reasons to
go to the gardens. So great. So great. Check it out if you're in the area.
Super charm. Go give Gil the high five and
see if he gives you a toot back. You survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate. If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes.
And oh God, guys, it's in. Oh no.
Oh, throwing up.
Oh no.
It's a bucket of white paint fell on my backside.
Now it looks like I'm a beautiful skunk. Oh no.
Jason and the skunk are creating some sort of situation with each other.
Oh no. They're not committed. They're not in a committed relationship.
I gotta explain this one. Ooh, I like the look of this.
Can I get in on this situation? Oh no.
I think he likes that they're stinky. At least the skunk is.
Jason, I can't speak for, I don't want to include him in that, but oh no,
a weird throuples happening on the floor of my garage. Oh no,
but it's not a committed throuple. It's loose.
It's not ethical at all. Oh God, I don't want to see this.
It's ethical though, if they explain it to each other before. That's it.
I'm getting out of here. Oh no, I fell into the litter robot.
I have cat litter in my eyes now. Stop there.
I go through his episode. No.