Alright, we're high rolling here on Club 3 Sin City style, the VIP lounge with my boys
Mike and Jason.
Hell yeah, what's up?
What's up, you guys?
What boys do is elongate H's.
Yeah, Jason, my man.
What the fuck is up?
Hey, what's up, brother?
Hell is happening.
Hey.
Are you rising and grinding like always?
I'm rising and grinding.
I am ruined.
I bet everything on the...
I bet everything on black and it landed on red.
Oh gosh, story of my life, bro.
Yeah.
That's what I do every day.
I lose all my money.
This is such realistic, you know, like with this AI battle that's going on, you need human
dialogue to feel lived in and real.
And you think an AI could spit out accurate casino VIP lounge dialogue like that?
Absolutely not.
That's right.
Yeah, this is just like authentic man talk and it feels good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it does.
To finally talk like men.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
It's good on the club three is where when we can do it.
That's what's behind the paywall.
Our guest is perplexed.
Fairly.
Girls come in with cookies and lemonade.
So many boys.
No, you can do man talk with us.
Don't ruin our man talk time.
Time to put our asses in place.
Mom's in the clubhouse.
Okay, I get you can stay just for an hour and a half, but only if we talk about the MGM
Grand Wizard of Oz walkthrough.
Okay.
Hey, that is the voice of our guest of the Rare Club 3 guest.
Yeah.
And so happy to have her.
She is the designer of all of our logos.
But importantly at this point in time, the very snazzy Sin City Knights logo.
Thank you for that.
I love it.
Aaron Gardner is here.
Hi.
Hi, I'm so happy to be here.
Thank you for letting me crash the clubhouse for real.
Even though I live in the clubhouse.
Yes, but sometimes, but this is a section of the clubhouse where sometimes you have to
go busy yourself and you know, get a little laundry done while the boys do their thing.
As women do.
But you're, but you look, it's you're good for more than laundry.
Let's make that clear.
One or two things.
Credibility we're providing you.
You're being on this episode is because of well, where the Club 3 die landed.
Thanks to our listeners.
This was a tight battle.
This is a really close race.
One of the closest that we've had.
You know, it's one of those anybody wins no matter what because the two main
competitors became 90s built animatronic shows at casinos.
So you can't go wrong either way.
Fall of Atlantis at Caesar's Forum shops ultimately fell to I'll read
Benjamin T's description of it.
The Wizard of Oz theming at the MGM Grand Casino in Las Vegas in the early 90s,
including a walkthrough attraction featuring the Oz characters and animatronics.
This was also suggested by Ryan Schieffer who said some of that stuff and added and
ended with a magic show inside the gates of Oz.
All sounds great.
And then and mainly as we're seeing like, okay, MGM Grand peripheral nonsense.
I thought well, I know an MGM Grand super fan of fans specifically of the
peripheral nonsense and that is you Erin.
Absolutely.
I've been I actually tried to do a count.
I wasn't totally successful, but I've stayed at the MGM Grand since 1997 at
least 15 times.
Wow.
And I've been to Las Vegas in general.
The count is either 23 or 24 times.
I've been many, many, many super fan.
You're like better than Gabris.
Thank you.
Highlighter.
Spoiler guest spoiler.
Oh yeah.
Shit.
I've done this already on the show.
I was to say he's a guest.
Maybe he I don't know.
That's just something we talked about him in general.
Yeah, I was just thinking a lot of a guy.
I know goes to Vegas and I was just thinking better than him.
Yeah, you are coming to Vegas with us.
So this will be the probably my 25th time.
Wow.
Probably.
What an achievement.
I didn't know it was like round anniversary number.
That's so great.
And those stats are very impressive.
Even though there's been a big break in that because of I haven't been in four
years.
We went with 2019.
Yeah, this pandemic and kid era has slowed down the Vegas going and I'm so
happy that you're you're doing it again and joining us and breaking the
streak.
Can I ask some general Vegas questions because you've been so many times like
do you have a top trip that you've gone on?
Is there a top show?
Like what are your faves and faves?
Yeah.
Scott and I in 2016.
It was I think it was New Year's 2016.
We did a trip called Divas weekend.
Yeah, where we saw was that when we saw Britney Spears and Olivia Newton,
John.
Yes, it was fantastic.
That was one of my favorites and same show.
No, we saw them two separate nights.
I would love to see it go out between the two of them.
Unfortunately, we can't do that anymore.
Yeah.
All right.
Pete.
I'm so happy.
We saw her.
She was incredible.
Yeah.
Yeah, that was a delightful show and you wonder as you head into that.
Are we going to shy away from Xanadu?
And then when we're going to lean in.
Yeah, biggest wind up of where you're going to live in Xanadu for a little bit.
I was we were we were literally in Xanadu.
It was wonderful.
And Britney was amazing too.
Yeah.
What a hell of a show.
That was great.
So good.
And then we did Divas weekend to the next year or the year after I forget.
We maybe like broke the definition of diva a little bit because we see them.
That was Katy Perry with opening act Carly Rae Jepsen.
All right.
And then David Copperfield.
The biggest diva of them all.
Oh, yeah.
Counts right.
Absolutely.
So yeah, that was probably my favorite show trip that we saw.
But so many of the trips blend together because I've been so many times.
And starting from when you were a kid with the family to family.
So growing up my family did two vacations, Las Vegas and Hawaii.
Once we went to New York, once we went to Orlando and once we went to Tahoe.
But other than that, my entire life, Las Vegas and Hawaii.
The end.
Not bad places to go.
But my dad's a real creature of habit.
So it was like, but we know we like Las Vegas.
We know we like Hawaii.
Why would we go anywhere else?
Right.
You know, great places, great vacation destinations, very a lot of stuff to do.
You can do different trips every time, especially in a city like Las Vegas that morphs every year you go.
Yes.
It never looks the same two years in a row.
Yeah.
I mean, I've always heard Los Angeles is a city.
That's constantly destroying itself and rebuilding itself.
But Vegas even more so.
Oh, yeah, it's amped up.
It's exponential.
And it's like Los Angeles, true.
But sometimes that'll be something that has been around for more than three years as opposed to like the Vegas.
The turnaround is nuts, including what we're talking about today.
Yeah.
And unfortunately, my first visit to the MGM Grand was 1997.
So I did miss a lot of the things that technically, you know, we're supposed to be talking about today.
But there were still remnants of Oz the first couple of years that I was there.
Okay.
Yeah, that was sort of the thought as we were talking about because we okay.
Main feed was MGM Grand Adventures, which I've been to many times and for a while I thought,
oh, that would be a great thing for me to talk about.
But I don't know.
I my memories aren't as strong from the theme park itself because it's kind of boring.
Honestly.
Yeah, this is what we figured out as we were talking about.
Like, was that something you want to talk about?
And then it became like, well, yeah, it's what people say on lies.
We're doing that episode.
It seemed like that thing looms so large and then people sort of, yeah, I don't know.
I don't remember this.
I don't remember that.
Yeah.
And also the other thing we're having when we're talking about it is I would bring up.
Well, yeah, did you ever do that that ride where you go deep under the earth?
No.
What the hell are you talking about?
Yeah.
Did you ever do the ride where it's like a it's a back clock tour, but it's a river and then a creature jumps.
Yes, because and I don't think you realized until we were doing this timeline math that you were there.
The first time you were there was post the 40% blow up of that park.
Right.
You only did these 60% of what it was.
Let me ask though.
I feel like we were maybe a little hard on the putt.
Did we did we miss anything?
Was there anything that you could speak to that you would rep in terms of MGM Grand?
The bumper cars.
We didn't talk about the bumper.
We did not talk about that.
Totally unmentioned actually.
Oh, the bumper cars were part of a it was like a European area.
Yeah.
By theming, I mean very lightly themed, but the bumper cars was like Parisian.
It was like a Parisian taxi, I think.
So there was a bunch of like I liked it because I was a Francophile when I was a teenager.
So like and I was like the French Club, but you know, like like ooh la la like like little Lisa Simpson.
You recognize the words that were painted in cursive on the wall?
I knew the mild French swears that were on the wall with people bumping into each other.
Oh, is that what it was?
Yeah.
It's what road rage would be.
Yeah, really mild though.
Yeah.
So, you know, I really enjoyed the bumper cars.
I thought that they were well done.
You also wait, it's in a plastic bag on our table under some other books.
You had a couple of pictures from this trip.
You had a really weird one that was like there was some attraction we definitely missed which was just by attraction.
I mean to like water wars.
Yeah, what was it?
Okay, there were two kiosks that were like there was like a walkway and two like wooden like lemonade stands with like a roof basically.
And they gave you a bucket of water balloons and there was a little hole in the ceiling and you launched water balloons out of your bucket through a little hole in the roof.
To get the people on the other side and it was called water wars.
Wow, really?
So there was a essentially like a summer camp activity.
The whole place felt very summer camp.
Especially I was the right age for it and it was the place that you know, my parents would dump us for the day.
Well, yeah, that's the question because we were wondering and we were talking about like, you know, what do kids do?
Like is Vegas a viable destination for kids today?
In the 90s, yes.
Sure.
Now probably not.
No, maybe not.
Yeah, I don't know what you do.
But yeah, you started going in this age where you couldn't drink.
You couldn't gamble.
So you did like is that where the MGM Grand fondness comes from because you I don't know if you're skeptical when you were a kid.
What am I going to do all day?
And then you did a thousand things.
I think the first trip erased that fear if I had it at all just because well, actually I should back up.
My first trip to Vegas was in 1996.
I was 12 years old and I went with my friend whose grandparents lived in Las Vegas.
Okay, so I went and stayed in an old couple's house in Henderson for a couple of nights and it was awkward.
I don't like being a house guest.
So it was awkward and all we did we went to the strip once to go to a buffet like, you know, 499, you know, Shrimp and Steak Buffet.
And we did go to the Grand Canyon.
What's adventure dome?
What that?
Oh, yes, it's adventure dome today.
But I love that.
Yeah, wait, it used to be could you guys know that that is that adventure dome in circus circus the creepily pink tinted theme park was once called Grand Canyon Grand Slam Canyon.
I didn't know that the dumbest 90s name ever.
So I did go there.
So I knew that there were glimmers of kid things, but I knew we weren't going to be staying anywhere near there.
Right.
So that's true.
You don't like being a house guest, which is what you I don't know if you clocked that we did not.
I forget if you offered or not, but we did not stay in your parents house in Schomburg when we came to visit Schomburg Jason did.
Oh, I did.
Jason did.
Jason insisted.
He slept like a baby.
Yeah, he would not have it any other way.
This has no problem with mom coming in with snacks.
He was a little disappointed in the service, quite frankly, for my mother.
He was expecting that a little more on the clock.
Look, I still left a good Yelp review, but I mean it was specific and I had some qualms.
But so that's the that's the first trip with friends, grandparents, and then you start doing these constant trips with your folks.
Annual.
Yeah.
And we always stayed at the MGM Grand.
So is that just like it's it's a comfort zone for them for your dad, I guess.
Just like shout, shall we delve into the privilege of my upbringing?
I guess that's good of you to get to get ahead of it to.
I don't know how crazy.
Look, it's Club 3.
I feel like maybe the listeners will be a little won't be too hard on me.
VIP to the high roller tier.
Let's talk about how you rolled.
Pretty high.
So I grew up in an entertainment industry family and my dad got comped rooms at the MGM Grand because of his job.
You know, friends at MGM, which involved the show West Convention, if any, but right.
Is that is that the right thing?
Yeah, I think it's called CinemaCon for anybody else.
You read Entertainment Weekly or Premiere magazine in the nineties like me and knew what these only I could go to show West.
I think show us was pretty boring.
They'd show like the heater for Batman and Robin.
You think my dad cared about that?
I mean, it was wasted on him.
Why weren't more kids allowed to go to show West?
I've heard you talk about this before and it is not the you're not a Zaslav.
You know, you know, you know, kind of a more logistical.
Yeah, I understand the privilege is relative, but like I did have many, many bizarre privileges growing up that I didn't think were strange at the time.
But now that I'm an adult and I could look back and be like, jeez Louise, like I went to so many movie premieres like the movie premieres are nuts.
You were at the you were at the premiere.
I'm sorry. Is this correct of all three mummies?
Really?
Wow. Even Tomb of the Dragon Emperor.
I was in that one.
That's straddles the yeah, what you're you're a young teen and then we're we're dating by Dragon Emperor.
Yeah, we so he had snuck down to the tram area.
Just like the first time we hung out.
This is my only move.
Sneak into the tram.
I have a place.
It's important to have a move.
Yeah, going and seeing it.
Well, like, yeah, I don't know if you're into this, but like if you want to see a Billy Bush standee, I can hook you up.
Nancy Odell, too.
This is the shop where they have last season's merchandise and it's a little markdown on top of my employee desk.
We're talking 12 percent.
Anyways, anyway, so point is that was one of the reasons that we went to Las Vegas every year and stayed at the MGM Grand every year because the whole trip was comped.
I'm talking food, too.
And like the phase and pay-per-view movies.
So like I would we would watch my sister and I each got to take a friend and the four of us would share a room and my parents would have their own room.
And at night, my parents would go down to gamble and set us up with, you know, pizza and Sundays and like all the room service that we wanted.
And we would just watch every pay-per-view movie.
Oh, wow.
Do you have is there a strong memory of one of those?
Yes, actually one pay-per-view movie.
Have you ever heard of the movie A Feast at Midnight?
Stumped?
No, I think we're all stumped.
Okay.
It was it was a British movie.
This was Bottom of the Barrel.
We had already watched like Meet the Deedles and like whatever else was out there.
All the movies you've heard of we watched and then we were like, what's a feast at midnight?
And it's a really boring film about a boarding school where like a hot teacher comes in and all the boys are like that she rocks their worlds because she's slightly younger than like your traditional headmistress.
That's my memory of it.
Who was in it?
No idea.
Christopher Lee.
Really?
Legendary.
He acted.
It's notable for being the feature film debut of future conservative politician Michael Gove as the chaplain.
Oh, all right.
Early Michael Gove work.
I think you gotta be a real Brit to know.
I don't know about Michael Gove.
So you remember liking this movie a lot?
Not so much.
There was one part of the movie that my sister and I quoted for a long time, which is like all the boys are like really like gently talking about being horny.
And when they're referring to the teacher, it's like a Wayne's World one-off where they go, show Wang, show Wang.
And that's like my only memory of a feast at midnight.
I've never revisited this film.
We watched it like three times.
We were in Vegas.
Wait, you haven't shot a take yet.
Have you?
We just got the we just got the facts from Paramount Pictures.
Do not say swing.
Whatever you do.
Show Wang.
We can't.
We have to.
Sorry.
We have to say, do I make you angry, baby?
It's copier.
Fucking Myers.
Locks it all down.
Empire magazine said of this film, nothing about it suggests that it should have been made for the big screen.
So modest is its scope.
Oh, wow.
It's a damning thing.
Nice way of saying boring and that's accurate.
You got to live it up such that you would like that you're scraping the bottom of the British barrel of pay-per-view movies.
Well, no wonder.
Okay, so that's a big that's a huge aspect of loving MGM Grand.
But then you and theme park still open smaller, but still open so you can go have some fun there.
But like, okay, I think you know, because I started getting in on the I've stayed at the MGM Grand with you a bunch too.
And I think slowly we've watched the transition into like today.
There's a lot of generic stuff there.
Now.
It's a lot of like every every available space becomes a nightclub or like kind of an anonymous gastropub type thing.
It doesn't quite have the silly magic that I think it used to have that it still had in the 90s even as the theme park went away.
So what like let me can I throw out a couple of things that I wonder if these factored into your shirt or if you have any, you know, and then we'll get into the Wizard of Oz thing.
But the okay, what was going on with arcades?
How the arcades in the oh, the arcade was incredible.
Are you kidding me?
You if you guys stayed at the MGM Grand before I've never stayed there.
Okay, I spent time there.
I have not either.
Okay, but you're familiar with the lay of the land kind of you've been in there before.
Some three.
Okay, so near the the garden arena, they had this thing that maybe you saw while you were there called the CSI experience.
Okay, it's it you go down a pair of escalators into this giant bottom floor that you can't see from anywhere like you have to go down the escalators to see what's down there.
And that's where the arcade was.
They turned it into the CSI experience.
Yeah, I don't but the arcade maybe the should we do it?
Maybe we should do it.
Oh, maybe we should.
Are they going now?
Is it really I looked it up?
I think I'm pretty sure it's gone now.
Huh?
But that's what it ended up being for anyone who's listening who has been to the MGM Grand and has seen that before that's where the arcade was.
Okay, and it was magnificent.
It was huge.
Wow.
Under a little escalator.
Yeah, you had to go down an escalator into this little it felt like going into a private club.
Wow, that's kind of like the Excalibur one too.
I think yeah, that one is also a bottom floor.
I feel special when you're a kid is like going to your little place.
Purposefully hide it because you don't want it to be on the casino floor because if you're you don't want to see a bunch of kids doing kid gambling.
Well, you're trying to do real.
It's kind of like that in the Luxor like there's it's like a little tucked away.
Yeah, the luck of that my or is Excalibur has the little maybe both area.
I think is is in New York, New York.
It's on the second floor.
It's my roller coaster.
Oh, right.
We've been up there.
Yeah, which one has the Dairy Queen?
Which one has Excalibur Luxor?
I don't know.
There's like a Dairy Queen right outside the arcade in one of them or there was at least eight years.
Smart design.
Smart design for Occupy if you've brought children.
He's changing his reservation right now.
Oh, we've had we we're not big Excalibur fans.
Dana and I we just very weird vibes anytime we've been in there and like very weird people.
We saw like a much older woman like we were in line for the the loyalty card thing because I think we were getting like free play or something and there was like a an older woman with like very tight bleach blonde and purple braids and a much younger man and they were all over each other.
Cool.
That sounds nice.
No, it was not.
It was really smoky wherever we were.
It was just like I don't I don't need to gamble here.
Yes, Scott and I stayed there once.
We did Excalibur once.
Yeah.
I didn't like it.
Yeah, no, not really.
No, you only go there out of like perverse fascination.
I feel you don't want to plant there.
Is Dix there?
Dix is there.
I don't know if it's still there.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
We've had that discussion.
Do we do?
Listeners can weigh in on.
Wait, no, no, no, it'll be too late by that.
Never mind.
Yeah, you still can.
Should we have done Dix?
I'll weigh in and say no.
Jason and I have been.
Is that based solely on the ugliness of that cartoon that you don't want to go first of all?
Because I'm part of this trip too.
I have every time something comes up.
I'm like Jane and Aaron are going to be to that so fast.
It's going to be so funny.
Jason and I have been to the San Diego location before it closed.
No, we haven't.
You've never been there?
I've never been there.
Oh my God.
Well, then I've been there like three times with other people.
So I saw you.
So you're covered on Dix.
You're a Dix expert.
I could do the whole Dix.
Yeah, all the characters.
We've talked a little bit about the characters before.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It's original mythology.
Yeah.
Did you know the dog from Dix last resort is named Assbite?
Why don't you want to go, Aaron?
No, that sounds really funny.
Here's how funny you're in person.
Yeah, if you're laughing now.
I'm laughing really hard.
But in 2013, the big joke was that they will call you gay.
So I'm interested to know what they're doing in 2023.
I'll bet it's still that and I'll bet it's still very funny.
You might be right.
But we might all need to go to find out.
That's the thing.
Imagine if someone was gay.
Yeah.
This is the right thing.
It resonates through the decades.
They're right on your big hat.
They make a big paper hat for you and they write like this guy's gay.
And then that's it.
That's the joke.
It's funny that we're saying this because I saw a Vegas Twitter account I follow yesterday.
It was pouring rain and hailing and 114 at the same time in Henderson.
So it's like just imagining being soaking wet and trudging into Dix last resort.
And all of a sudden you're gay.
Like how many ungos you got with you today?
I want to find out I'm gay.
Yeah.
How my wet hair is melting my paper hat.
I'm not ready for this life change.
I just want to dry off a little first.
Okay.
Other MGM grand silliness.
Rainforest Cafe.
Oh, yeah.
Did you do it?
Fond memories of it?
Of course.
Yeah, we went there for breakfast a lot actually.
I remember you saying the breakfast was actually surprisingly solid.
It's hard to screw up breakfast.
That's a good point.
You have a good point.
It's not that hard to make a waffle, you know.
That's true.
Yeah.
What were your...
I used to do that in the college dining hall.
Just make waffles?
I was on the Saturday morning shift and I was on the whole bar for a full semester.
What?
Yeah, I was a waffle maker.
Wow.
How have we not learned this before?
I don't know.
And I...
You were on the waffle shift in the morning?
I did not burn myself, but there was like two or three regular size ones and then a pan.
The one that was for mini waffles.
And they were just like, just keep it going.
It's so busy here Saturday.
Just keep making them.
So you were on like a Lucy style assembly line?
I was a Lucy style assembly guy.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
This is insane that we don't know this.
I would ruin people's morning because I'd be giving them the four mini ones.
They're like, can I wait for a big one?
I'm like, oh yeah, fine.
Same one, one mini ones.
They told me I had to do this.
They were making you move mini ones?
They were just like, just keep filling the batter.
Just keep and flag one of us down when you need more batter.
It was not super well run.
We have a hundred questions, but we have to get to the MGM grand.
Sorry, I mean, it's sidetracked.
I'll just pick one.
Pick one.
Good one.
Okay.
What time did the shift start?
Did you say?
Oh, good question.
Yeah, it sucked.
It was like 8 a.m.
Gosh.
7.30, 8 a.m.
Who is this guy?
I don't know.
That's what I mean.
That's okay.
That seems late to me.
But only in, well, you've been an early riser for a long time.
Yeah, when you're 18.
One more question.
Yeah.
Did you have to wear an outfit or like a little hat?
It was just like a denim or blue dress shirt.
And yeah, I did have to wear a little hat.
I had to wear a little hat to keep my hair and a black apron.
Do we have a photo of this?
Every day I would end up like, or every time I worked, I would end up
inevitably collected a lot of stray silverware because I would like,
people would forget stuff or I would use the fork to scrape off the
excess cooked batter.
And then at the end of the shit, like stuff, I would just, so by the
end of the semester, I had a bunch of cups and forks and stuff.
So you would just take them back to your dorm with you?
I was so tired.
I was so out of it.
Not purposefully.
I'm imagining forks just like sticking out of your hat.
Yeah, that's not an easy.
Everyone who worked in the dining halls, you would go to their
dorms and you're just like, is that dining hall silverware and cups on
your table?
Yeah, I had it.
My apron.
I forgot about it.
Every day you'd come home with seven stray forks and knives and
pockets full of batter.
Yeah.
Oh, covered in batter.
I had to wash that stuff so much.
The uniform and the apron just covered in dried batter.
This feels like the AI is creating new stories.
Again, this has been happening a lot lately.
Please prompt.
Please tell me a Jason story that is exactly up my Jason story alley.
Right, that I've never heard before in decades.
A year ago, a year later, I worked in the dish room.
Oh, so you were washing dishes?
A million degree.
Why were you doing this again?
Uh-huh.
Why did you have to do this?
I had a work study.
I had a work study credit and then eventually I transferred to the,
I think the higher paying jobs on campus, which was calling alums and
parents and asking them for money.
Phone calls where no one is happy to talk to you.
No, and you're not happy to do the talking.
I can't imagine.
No, you are seeing you do any of this stuff right now.
You would be the most stressed out person.
I tried so many times to get in the computer lab or the library because
library people just sat at the checkout counters and just dicked around on the internet.
I'm sorry to tell you.
That's what I got.
I got it.
Yeah.
I worked at the video rental place in the library where the main thing was,
it was so far in the bowels of it that nobody made it up.
And if they did, they'd say they'd get, take a, they'd take a video and then
say, uh, and then start leaving with it.
And I'm like, no, no, no, the videos must be watched in the library on the big blocky.
So people, and some of them are real movies.
Like I, so I can't take diehard back to my, nope, library only.
So, which, uh, you know, it caused a wave of, uh, no one ever wanting to be up there for any reason.
I'm really sorry to tell you that that was my call.
Did you, Scott, do you have to wear an outfit of any kind of little outfit?
I did still have to wear a black apron.
In case any stray tapes getting rewound spit out at me.
And did you go home with a bunch of just tapes in your pockets?
And I get all these tapes, our buttons.
Ah, how did I end up with the fast forward?
Uh, well, Aaron, I'm so glad you said waffle.
Thank God you really say we're inspiring words.
Uh, I, I, Mike, I think you get one more question at the end of the episode, but just to make it a go, just like, think while other things are.
I'll think about it.
Um, one, one more big one as we're talking about, uh, sillier things in the MGM grant, uh, and this is gone now, but I'm sure I remember passing by this with you.
This is a big facet for a long time.
Lions.
I knew that's where we're going.
Lions and not just the big lion used to enter through the statues.
There were lions, real lions, uh, in the MGM grant, uh, feelings, experience with those.
Yeah.
The first year I went, they had a brand new lion cub that you could take a photo with, with your hands on its.
Hind.
Whoa.
Like you would line up and they had a, um, you know, like a professional photographer.
And, um, um, you would, you would go up behind the lion.
So the lion couldn't see you and the trainer distracted it with like a big, like ball and, uh, whatever to get the lion to look up.
And you would go behind it and just like touch its back legs, hold for a quick photo and then get the hell out.
Um, and in between photos, they were feeding it out of like a big bottle.
Wow.
Yeah.
Um, it was magical or seed.
What is it?
Yeah.
Magical through the eyes of a 13 year old in hindsight, CD as shit.
They should not be making lion cubs.
Yeah.
If we saw many stranger, many young people to or even less.
It seems like a liability nightmare to, to have, just regular people touching lions.
In like 22, there's footage in 2012.
I think they, uh, closed the lion habitat in the mid 2010s.
There's footage around 2012 or so of a lion, like beating the shit out of it.
Of a trainer.
I'm sure.
Pouncing on a train clear footage.
It's not even one camcorder.
I know it's pretty, it's nicely shot.
Yeah.
They were moved many, many times too.
They moved to that habitat, like all around the casino.
It wasn't always in the same place.
Oh really?
From my memory.
Cause I can't tell you exactly where it was.
Um, but, uh, I know one of the locations is where.
The wizard of Oz thing ended up, but that wasn't the only one.
Is that the big one in the center?
Like, well that, well that would have been, but that's by the strip entrance.
I get, but I didn't, yeah, I don't think there were, yeah, I think it's still multiple.
My memory is that they were moved around a couple of times.
Like the lions were in different places every time.
Like while they were building that big habitat, that was probably the final one.
There were lots of weird construction things.
The pool.
Oh yeah.
Crazy construction too.
Oh, because yes, we were talking in the MGM Grand about like now there's this
massive pool facility with a lazy river and stuff, but that replaced some of the
theme park.
So first time you went smaller pool, crappier pool.
Yeah, it was a sand bottom pool.
I hate those.
Um, they had a really small pool that, uh, the only access to this pool was through
the fourth floor.
So you know how there's like five or six elevator bays in the MGM Grand?
Every single bay had access to the fourth floor.
And this was for years after that pool had closed, but that's the reason you
would walk through rooms just like regular hallway with hotel rooms on the
fourth floor to go through this janky entrance to the, the pool that they had
set up for the time being while they were building the giant pool that they
have now.
We've got a lovely room for you on the fourth floor.
I mean, I don't know if maybe when it was max capacity, people were staying in
those rooms.
Could you imagine?
Oh God.
Just constant carpet on the, on that floor too, was just like wrecked to shit
because you have everybody walking like two and from the pool.
So it's like reeks of sunblock and sweat and chlorine and sand and sand
and toes because it was a sand pool.
So let me ask, uh, are you, have you ridden the Vegas monorail very much?
Yes.
Which one?
The, not the people movers on the other side of the strip.
The one that you pay for the one you pay for that goes like MGM Grand
to strat.
Yeah.
I was there when they built it.
Thoughts?
Do you like it?
I do.
I like, I can't, I feel like there was a time that you didn't have to pay for it,
but maybe I was just a teenager and didn't pay for anything.
But yeah, I, uh, that monorail, the entrance moved for it a few times
actually from the MGM Grand where you loaded.
But, uh, yes, I love that monorail.
I was really excited when they built it because it really opened up access.
You know, we saw a lot more hotels that way when it's like, oh, we could take
the monorail all the way up and see, you know, that takes it to the Hilton
or Westgate or whatever.
That one is a nice memory to our first vacation together, uh, to the
Las Vegas Hilton while Star Trek was still open.
Didn't do it.
I was there when it wasn't.
Yeah.
One of my biggest regrets of my life.
Star Trek experience.
Uh, um, I, uh, I, I, we did though, I'm sure I've said this before, but
that I do strongly remember getting on the elevator with just married,
fully decked out Star Trek.
Yes.
Yeah.
It was a just married couple who did a full Star Trek wedding.
Am I, am I making up that they had personal pan pizzas?
No, I completely remember personal.
Whoa.
You, oh, I'm sorry.
I, I remembered that you, I remember eating personal pan pizzas in the hotel.
You're saying that the wedding dinner of these two going up, these two
Klingons going up to their room.
They were also holding their personal pan pizzas.
Whatever the, the people who work on the ship.
Oh, they were like humans within the regular like regulation outfits.
I feel like in my memory, there's one Klingon, but maybe that's wishful
thinking, maybe that's me just leaping to the cartoon version.
I think we're both creating a scenario that didn't exactly.
I really want Klingon forehead wrinkles and you really want them to eat
personal pan pizzas to be their wedding dinner.
Yeah.
These memories are like beautiful scenes from like a Cirque du Soleil.
This is straight out of MGM Grand's Ka show, which is read seemingly forever.
Uh, when you set those up, yeah, they were at boy, there's, there's
something really wrong if you ever end a Cirque du Soleil show.
Yeah.
Uh, the Vegas monorail, by the way, I believe now goes by the sphere.
Oh, right.
A way to get a view.
You can see the sphere.
People are getting sphere-pilled left and right online.
And I couldn't be more excited about it.
I've been sphere-pilled for months.
Someone pointed out the, the win, the very open to anyone, but pretty
expensive, the very exclusive win golf course, a very nicely been here.
Golf course.
Now you can be on the golf course and just be staring at a giant eyeball.
I love it.
You look at video of it.
Like surely this is doctored.
That's this crazy.
Any photo or video of the sphere you assume is a Photoshop.
Yeah.
It looks fake.
It looks like somebody inserted a bunch of stuff onto a bubble, but in
fact, so they built something that always looks fake.
It's really weird.
I can't imagine.
It looks so crazy in video.
I imagine in person, it looks 50 times crazier.
We're going to have to, I mean, that weather is going to be nuts, but we
have to somehow at least get it.
I am excited to see those things.
Yeah.
Where do you, especially because it will be torn down in three years.
That's your money's going on that.
I think I'm with you.
I feel like, and we'll, we'll discuss some of this.
Saudis buy it in bankruptcy, you know?
Oh, that's true.
There's always that option.
Yes.
It just may not be owned by the current owner for very long.
I think sphere is going to work.
That's my prediction.
It's going to be crazy.
I think.
Yeah.
But that's also you're coming at it from a pro U2 angle.
I think that's telling us coloring your view.
I'm coming at it from a, I'm indifferent to you too.
And I think that seeing a side of a big eyeball with the weird
muscle-y side part of an eyeball.
I think it's so bizarre.
It is.
They just stopped showing the eyeball.
Maybe the eyeball makes it extra weird.
But when they turn it into a giant pumpkin, that's cool.
They showed that already.
And there's a big basketball.
WW.
I like the best.
WW you might run an event in there.
They're talking to them already.
Okay.
That would be good.
I feel like we're getting into the zone of like, oh, people are
interested in using this thing.
So we'll see.
As long as the performers and wrestlers or anybody who had
don't like go into absolute seizure convulsions every time
they look up slightly, as long as the room doesn't scramble
everyone's brain.
That's yeah, which it might, that might be a danger where
you might never come back.
But we're like, we need to make sure we should record a
goodbye episode from you just in case.
Yeah.
Who's the ability to Colonel Kurtz Mike's apocalypse.
Now he's going up river to the sphere.
If that look I have mission possible spoil.
Am I allowed to do a little spoiler Jason?
I'm sorry.
Fine.
Sure.
I mean the entity is the sphere.
Oh, you're right.
Yeah.
AI that is the bad guy.
Mission Impossible is that'll be in the sphere.
Spoiler Tom Cruise fights the sphere.
Yes.
So yeah, I may give myself over to it.
I may willingly give my body to the entity when I'm seeing
you to perform Octon baby.
What was that about?
Like, oh, all the sphere footage seems like it's doctor,
but it's real reminds me of the thing that is doctored,
which is the clip from the flash where someone reversed
it.
So it looks like the flash is putting a baby in the microwave.
Oh, Jason, Jason, I've got news for you.
The flash absolutely puts a baby in the microwave.
He saves it, but this seems like the flash is smiling
and about to microwave.
Yeah.
Yes.
Well, he puts the flash midair puts babies in non working
microwaves to save you to shield them from explosions.
Got it.
So no, it doesn't feel weird at all to see someone we're
supposed to believe in as a great superhero putting a baby
in a microwave.
Like how did nobody in the biggest corporate chain do the
calculation that a baby going into a microwave is one of the
most profoundly disturbing images ever.
Small baby are pretty big.
It is.
Well, it's a like it's a newborn.
It's like babies who are just born that day go flying out
of a building tons of them, tons of them.
And the flash has to save them all from like sharp objects
and shans shove some in microwaves.
But even still the littlest baby could the little microwave.
I don't want to find out.
I don't want to run this test at home.
No, someone refers to there's footage at the end of the scene.
He tastes baby out of the market.
Someone refers.
So it looks like a woman is screaming as he's smiling puts
it in the microwave and I mean that sounds funny and weird,
but I'm telling you the way it actually plays out is equally
disturbing.
That is one of the most disturbing sequences ever shot by
humans and somehow Tom Cruise is trying to tell us this is
the best movie ever made.
The sphere is like a big circuit like an orb microwave and
I'm willingly going to be put into it.
You're a baby happily nestled in your sphere.
The sphere is a big womb.
The sphere is.
Yeah, we just talked about big wombs.
Yeah, it's yours.
Jason.
Yeah, you're into this.
Mike's pondering is orb again.
Okay, as we start heading towards this little this little
animatronic thing and some old-school 90s, I'm going to
bring up one more thing just in case you crossed over with
this, but I'm going to bet that you did not.
We've done many trips where we've kicked things off at the
MGM Grand in the lobby bar.
That's a wonderful bar.
Nice to get some champagne and hey, we're here and we're
going to start hitting it which is now like a pretty like
classy elevator.
I like that bar.
Did you have any recollection of the bar being stupider than
it is today?
No, okay.
What it was due to the stray licensing we talked about in
the theme park that hey, all your favorite characters are
here Popeye tumbleweed for the 1960s comic tumbleweed and
we forgot a big one Betty Boop.
Oh, yeah.
We I guess I was on my list tonight.
We just never said her name Betty Boop was around at the
theme park.
I don't know if you ever saw Betty Boop anywhere on the
property.
Novelty lunchboxes.
Yes.
Yeah.
That's the main place you seen her now is tin lunchboxes,
but Betty Boop had a presence in the theme was a let's say
something we said in the last episode face character not
for character.
So kind of weird that it's a big mascot version of Popeye
and olive oil, but then just a woman is Betty Boop so you
could see that in the park, but the bar was Betty Boop's
bar.
It was a Betty.
Wow, it was a Betty Boop bar and then you hear that and
you think okay, so kind of like pink hearts got an aesthetic
sort of close to Minnie Mouse.
No, not at all.
Regular bar got a little trashier in its style.
Maybe then currently but relatively standard issue Vegas
bar except that it had an animatronic.
Are you following me an animatronic Betty Boop?
Wow wrong.
No, what Betty Boop's bar had an animatronic if I made you
guess 2000 names you would never land at what the animatronic
was of is it the dog?
No, as fight.
It was not an animatronic of Dix as bite.
It was does the name Foster Brooks mean anything?
Yeah.
Do you know Foster Brooks?
So Foster Brooks was a while you might describe Foster as
a lovable lush a drunk cat like a cat.
A comedic guest kind of an handicap but a real pretty it was
like like the real person's name is Foster Brooks and that was
like their persona was a slurry drunk guy and you would see
Foster Brooks on like Dean Martin specials and stuff like
that like a very 1960s Omni present thing that I only know
the I think I only know the name because like Jim Brewer saying
like I want to be like Foster Brooks.
I want to be like the modern foster Brooks, you know, I'm
really angry.
He can't play hot drunks on SNL.
Anyway, so name you've never heard before in your life in
the early 90s people think we got to put an animatronic Foster
Brooks into the Betty Boop bar.
What is this?
How does that all tie together?
It makes no sense.
Foster Brooks ever in Betty Boop cartoon or anything.
Do we know?
I don't think so.
Well, and also it's like a it's a photo realistic right.
It was very human animatronic.
Yeah, I know.
I'm going to play a clip and stop it almost immediately because
the sound is going to be awful.
This is just to give you vaguely the flavor of the fun you
would get if you sat next to animatronic Foster Brooks.
A loud laugh track mainly.
This is like our favorite Simpsons joke.
The John Muir.
National Park and opens the door.
It's playing a movie.
Let's let John Muir tell the tale.
Wow.
Was this animatronic put in there to make you feel better
about yourself?
Like you think you're having a bad day.
Maybe so.
Yes.
Are you're you're worried that you've had one drink too many?
Well, you're no foster.
Yeah, not slurring to I bet though many many people challenge.
I put there are lots of people vastly drunker than Foster
Brooks.
Yeah, Foster.
Why not like a more famous?
Maybe he was very famous and I'm wrong, but like he was like
the 15th most famous guy on those Dean Martin roasts because
of I think because of the drunkenness.
I think I'm saying there's no more famous like drunk or fake
drunks.
Maybe they went to several people before him or before several
estates.
Yeah, that all the time.
Yeah, the WC fields estate was just playing hardball.
I think that's it.
I think maybe like nobody's there's never been an offer for
a Foster Brooks anything.
So they are they are motivated to sell.
Mecca Toys has not approached the Foster Brooks estate to
make a series of seven inch articulated Foster Brooks action
figures.
We found one podcaster who we believe will buy a Foster
but so with that as an entry point, maybe we'll sell to
what about Red Skelton, right?
He had the drunk thing too.
They were all doing this stupid drunk pretending to be drunk
and it made them like money on the Ed Sullivan show.
Look, I think I think what we're learning is that the MGM
grand while very fun when it first opened probably needed
like a big picture got Tony Baxter or Joe Roady for like
to make it cohesive.
Yeah, for some cohesiveness.
Yes, absolutely.
And it probably should have been the person who did the
the Wizard of Oz display would seem pretty top-notch just
really good before I moved past that.
So that was the thing would you would just play a scratchy
tape with a laugh track and I think no one ever got near it.
I think like how can we get some seats across the and the
why did it go away?
Well, one person says it just got it fell into such a
disrepair that they just threw it in the trash and nobody
knows what happened to it video, but I would rather believe
the urban legend of it, which is that Mike Tyson was there
on a fight night and the animatronic made him so mad or even
possibly the specific Hector ring from this old comedian
recording made him so mad that he's like, oh yeah and like
punched the head off.
I don't believe that for one minute.
But I love that would be really fun.
Yes, if that's the yeah, yeah.
And if that was like what if that I don't know the timeline
here, but MGM Grand Arena is where Tyson bit Holyfield's
ear.
So what if that was like the instigator the night where
shit really.
Oh wow.
Yeah, what if that pushed him over the edge and animatronic
foster Brooks caused the ear bite?
Oh my gosh.
I was I thought you were going to say what have you bit the
ear off the animatronic?
I broke that gives me a good idea.
So maybe all the scenarios I like with him involved with
animatronics.
I mean idea.
I just love that it was there in general now doesn't sound
good, but pretty good animatronic pretty believable looks
like it might have been a Sally.
I think maybe it was a Sally and that maybe leads us into
I just wanted to let's get all the nonsense out of there
and now get to the main show here.
The Wizard of Oz walkthrough.
I mean we can kind of step through what this experience
was but I the headline as we talk about that foster Brooks
animatronic kind of looking good.
These animatronics looked good.
Yeah, really good.
It is a full set of I mean, there's several iterations of
the main four of Dorothy's Scarecrow Cowardly Lion Tin
Man, but then you get a Glinda and you get the Wicked
Witch and the Wizard.
They all look these are top-tier animatronics.
They're really good.
I sure wish I could have seen these that I mean they're
incredible.
Yeah.
Yeah, and this is a nut.
This is like night and day from the video of the park itself
the MGM Park.
Yeah, far as just like feeling do you remember we were talking
about how the rapid ride had animatronics and it was Garner
Holt's first job.
Yeah, but do you recall the animatronics in any way?
I recall that they were there but I not not especially you
didn't think these are wow, this wasn't blown away.
Sure.
I mean, I will say that those animatronics maybe were
on the same level.
It's just I was I'm seduced by the atmosphere and the mood
of this more than I am of barely seeing any.
Well, and like look a rapids right is not a good mechanism
for yes, animatronics because you're spinning past
her Milly Fes these things you can yeah, could you at the
time you could walk up and stare at them.
Yeah, get really close to them probably touch them try to
kiss them get tackled get kicked out of the scene.
Yes, I would have tried to kiss a couple of them just a
little kisses, but I would have tried I just I'm not
attracted to the tin man.
I just want to know what a tin kiss would be like.
Yeah, of course.
He's so friendly.
Yeah, he's been with me all my life.
Sure you can anytime.
I got a big high.
I think it's very interesting to that like very detailed
animatronics in the queue.
But the first thing you see are very detailed statues.
Yeah of the characters and then the wizard in the hot
air balloon.
Yes.
Yeah, which less of a part of the original movie than the
Franco Franco.
Which most of the marketing was about the hot air balloon.
Yeah, that is true.
Get you the balloon in theaters.
Finally.
Yeah, so this was okay.
We talked we talked about the theme park in the main feed
but that was not the only big crazy themed thing meant to
attract people in the case and meant to make a big statement
in that casino.
This is what this is what you saw when you walked in on
opening day from the strip from the main strip entrance.
And it's like it's an insane tableau.
It's those characters and then the rendering of the Emerald
City.
Yeah, is unreal.
It's huge.
It is absolutely movie quality.
You could this would completely work in a Disney park.
Yes, it's that high level and it's when you see the video
you go, how would you get rid of this?
Yeah, I don't I mean, I know most adults don't give a shit
about it.
I understand that from a logistic point of view, but it
looks so good.
It did add such an interesting atmosphere to it.
Yeah, and that area that's like three stories high.
Yes, really high and like that is a massive space and it
looks like they utilized all of it really high domed ceiling
thunder and lightning and colored light.
I missed I guess trying to simulate the tornado.
Yeah, as you get closer to the core, it seems like yeah, then
the storm is starting the Wicked Witch flying overhead every
now and then yeah a little projection of that and meanwhile
the audio experience is just slot machine sounds on every
side.
It seems like yes because it is like, you know, some of it
is the clean entrance to the entire property.
So, you know, it's not slot machines on all sides, but the
deeper you go into the corn maze, you are definitely only
10 feet away.
It's the oddest tableau juxtaposition of it because it
is there's a lot of like eerie sounds happening and atmosphere
sounds for Wizard of Oz, but you can also hear slot machines
just going nuts like normal casino.
It's very competitive.
Let me step through the entire experience and I'm even going
to walk us out the door a little bit because I'm not going to
let two MGM Grand episodes pass without giving a little bit
of love to the big blocky lion, the original entrance.
Erin, you were there.
You started going in this transitional time.
What was going on with the line?
You missed it entirely.
Yeah, I believe I missed it.
It was under construction the first time you...
I think so.
To be honest though, I always entered the hotel through the
carport through the, you know, like the valet area.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Since I was staying there.
So I very rarely went through the entrance and exit.
Do you know what was there when you went?
Because now it's sort of this kind of a fountain and like a
lot of big screens playing music videos and stuff.
I don't remember.
Nothing like noteworthy.
It might have been under construction.
It might have been just, you know.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah.
But this is something I remember.
The first time we went to Vegas together when I was but 21.
You educated me about a number of things.
You like onboarded me.
First of all, that Vegas is fun and you can have a big silly
time and the best meals you've ever had.
Like I don't think I knew any of that.
Like you completely turned me on to how much fun Vegas can be.
But there were little things too.
One of them being, I think I was like, oh yeah, I can
get to go see that big blocky line.
I didn't know the lion was gone.
You burst my bubble.
Oh, I love the but I just I don't know.
I love the weird mustard color.
I mean, I like my kind of like blocky brutalist Epcot.
The architecture.
So you made me sad a little bit when you told me that the
lion was not only gone long gone.
I didn't make the decision.
It made me so sad.
You should have let me believe it.
I saw with my own eyes.
You should have been so happy on the plane.
I told him I was there but you couldn't see it because
something was going on that day.
I could have just lasted 17 years.
Someday we're going to see it.
I swear.
Yeah, the other thing that you I also just remember being
in our first Vegas trip together that like wait on the
drinks are free.
If you play a little bit, I didn't know like this is how much
I knew nothing.
And then we're walking out and like but wait, I still have
my glass and you say no, no, no, you can keep walking with
that.
That the note I actually didn't know that you could just
walk the streets with alcohol.
Yeah, be a shithead and just drop your glass in whatever
hotel you want.
Afterwards, throw it trying to hit the big breast lion car,
the big bronze lion because I'm mad that it's not the old
lion that I like.
That's the same thing Jason would do with his silverware
from the waffle job.
He was living.
It was just trying to live vicariously Vegas.
Hey, you need a forks gang.
Just trying to get to know each other.
I got a lot.
This is your end to make college friends.
Yeah, I was making college friends covered in flop sweat
from waffle batter.
Yeah, I've covered in flop sweat and waffle batter.
But if you need a fork.
I got a pot of mine.
Over 19 year olds and the nastiest syrup that I've
got most never.
You can probably speak to how never changed it was.
I only get one question at the end.
Pressures on a good one.
You're going to call me up the scar.
Maybe we'll answer that question.
You got a waffle scar?
No, it's more complicated than that.
Fuck fine.
And just do it now.
I want to know how you got these scars.
I switched shifts with someone once and so I was working
the dinner shift one night.
What were you preparing for that?
I was on the meat carving station.
I was taught how to do it in about 45 seconds.
What were you slicing?
What kind of meat?
I was slicing different different story.
I get to ask a couple of more questions.
That's the line of questioning.
I understand.
I was slicing like roast beef or roast pork.
And when you wear that, you're already wearing like rubber
or latex gloves.
Then you wear like a fucking chain metal glove so that
you're slicing with your right hand.
You got the chain metal glove on your left hand.
I've watched a video demonstrating carving stations before.
I think at the old country buffet.
That's one of the great employee informational videos
available on YouTube.
I know about the big glove.
Jason wore it.
So you don't cut your hand.
What a falconer would have to wear.
Unless you cut right at the above where the glove ends.
So I stabbed myself.
I poked myself.
Oh, God.
And they really have to like dump that roast.
They had to get you.
You bled on the roast?
You bled all over the roast?
I ruined a roast.
And they're like, all right, we're going to put you on the ice cream
stand for the rest of the night.
You went to the ice cream stand?
I scooped ice cream a few times, which is kind of nasty
in itself because it had a toppings bar with it.
And marshmallow syrup, as much as I love to eat it,
is incredibly hard to clean up and manage.
Oh, no.
So wait a second.
They didn't send you to urgent care.
They sent you to ice cream?
Eat.
We've still got to get somebody to cover the shift.
It was a pretty small jab.
But you have a scar from it?
I do have a very tiny scar from it.
A small jab that lasted forever?
That's part of your life now?
It's very faint.
That affected your body?
Wow.
Yeah.
So that's my work study story.
And they had to fill out an incident report
and begrudgingly get me a glass of water.
How many begrudgingly?
Oh, God.
Yes, Prince.
Here you go, sir.
All of the adults who manage the dining
are like, they hate it.
They hate it running it.
They hate it managing a staff of students.
How many minutes into the shift did you slice your wrist?
We're talking like 30 minutes.
Wow.
So and you also, I didn't really know about the concept
of restaurant crew meals.
So we would have to get there 30 minutes before our shift
to take lunch before we did a shift.
And looking back, I'm like, this doesn't seem right.
So everyone's eating beforehand.
And then at the end of the meal, you clock in.
So you kind of had to do a mandatory meal with everyone.
Very odd.
At the beginning.
And also, they have only kind of put out the food.
You're kind of in a weird in-between period
between meals, a lot of the chefs.
So yeah.
Did you have to do, did they have to do a funeral
for the roast?
Did you have to say a few words?
Did you offer to take it home?
You can eat your own blood.
That's fine.
I'll throw it out for you.
Just let me take it.
No, no, yes, I'm putting it in my car.
But that's because I have a bigger trash can I know about.
Jason's running the old bleed on the roast pun.
Life hack.
Brace yourself.
This asshole already dropped a vat of marinara sauce
last week.
So like I did drop a vat of marinara sauce in the pizza
station.
Jason dropped a bit.
You keep like this episode.
Now you tell us all this.
This is an untapped wow.
This should be a 19 part series.
Yeah.
Are you working?
You're pulling like Mr.
Bean style like mistakes during food preparation in college.
Yeah.
Anyway, there was a magic show at the end of the
Yellowbrook Road.
Yeah, I was going to say there's we've talked about there's
some episodes where people end up saying when are they going
to get to the fireworks factory?
Yeah, but this one feels like okay, when are they going to
get to the fireworks factory?
But they are in the dynamite factory.
Big and it's colorful.
It's going off red and green and purple all color.
I got to know it's kind of equivalent to the fireworks
factory.
Yeah, it Jason Lohr unlocked.
It should be also part of the description of part of this.
Oh boy.
Yeah.
Well, we'll tease it.
Anyway, the lion was cool.
The lion is cool.
It's like Sphinx style.
Like that's like an Egyptian old but like metallic or gold.
Yeah, definitely.
I don't know.
I just like the color.
I like the treatment.
I like the blockiness.
But then there's that bizarre.
It also to me feels like 90s polygons.
Yeah.
Like also CGI.
Or video game stuff, which I think also makes it sort of
attractive to a man of a certain man or woman of certain
age.
Anybody who saw early CGI, the kind of early CGI that wasn't
terrifying.
Yeah, it was just blocky and bad.
It was charming.
Yeah, charming.
There's some attention to detail on the line that I like.
One, the eyes are emerald green.
Oh, like the building and everything else.
And then the doors into the casino,
the door handles are giant letters that say Oz.
They say Oz.
Did they still does that sound familiar in your transitional
era?
I believe so.
I think on the other side where there's the West Wing entrance
where there's that Starbucks where like the Rainforest Cafe
also was that side entrance there.
I think was Oz for a little while.
Wow.
That's harder to change.
That's what I like is that they'll get or they'll implode
the big thing but leave little odds and ends.
Little odds and ends all over the place for years.
Oh, yes.
Oh, it's you.
Yes, you enlightened me to one which we'll get to when it's
when we get to the attraction.
The big lion went away because of this odd mythology that
Chinese gamblers didn't like the lion because it was bad luck.
So entering through the lion's mouth felt like, well, I'm not
going to have a good night.
So I'm not going to play here.
Like a giant swath of the population would not set foot
in that place due to the lion and somehow.
Okay.
What if it's just a big bronze line?
What if it's the big?
What if it's the biggest bronze statue in the US and it's
of a lion?
Yes, that's fine.
That is not bad.
Don't enter through it.
Yeah, I guess that's what it's about.
Might be the huh?
Yeah, then where the logic kicks in for that culture, which
I'm not an expert on.
Two story line next to the three story hawk a song.
Yes, the biggest bronze statue still doesn't come close to
just a nightclub billboard.
There used to be a billboard in Hollywood.
I think for hawk a song like a rotating series billboards
for Vegas Residencies and clubs and I'd be drive by them all
the time.
Yeah, they were always pushing that stuff at us.
It essentially knows.
Yes.
I don't are we going to end up?
We're going to end up going through Sin City.
I think without EFX.
I don't think we have time for EFX unless we make a please
make your appeal listeners if you know EFX needs to be done.
But anyway, Lion Lion goes away.
But still this is just like this is all just to set the
scene of and then you go through these do you open the
Oz door handles and then find Oz.
I'm sure the best depiction of Oz anywhere.
We sort of we know theme parks pretty well.
We know the great movie ride, of course.
And that's the great movie ride scene of the Wizard of Oz
is spectacular.
It's probably the best part of the great movie ride and yet
better.
This is this better.
What's a different?
It's a different part of the move.
I mean, it's showing a different scene.
I guess it's so I don't know.
I think there's up there's positives and negatives.
I guess it's I mean, there's you have the like cast of
hundreds animatronics.
Yeah, it's it to the great movie ride, which is good.
The vast array of munchkins you have less animatronics, but
these animatronics are really fantastic.
So it's it's the big four.
Who are your favorite four favorite Wizard of Oz characters?
Me?
I don't know.
I got to go with lion tin man.
Scary grow.
And the munchkin killing themselves.
And oh yeah, yeah.
An interesting thing that I because there is some good
video footage of walking through this.
There is one really good all the way through well, even
though it's old camcorder.
We're like and it's it's very charming to women walk into
the casino and see the Oz for the first time.
One of them like goes like wow, like like it's so excited
about it.
It's a real Barb and star.
Yes.
Yeah.
And Barb is one of them actually Barb.
I watched it last night.
I like have a Barb and Sherry.
Barb and Sherry for sharing your your memories with us
allowing yourselves to be on YouTube and they're having a
lot of fun and it kind of made me realize a few things
about this one.
Of course the yellow you follow the yellow crude this walk
through was kind of out of the reverse order of the movie
or like another water like you see Oz first and then you
go to the cornfields and then you go to the scary forest.
Oh, yeah.
So it's kind of an interesting order.
But the other thing that I think other footage didn't
reveal was the ticket booth.
Yeah.
So this was a ticketed attraction cash only cash only.
Wow.
But I funny detail.
I was trying to figure out like I it seemed like maybe the
walkthrough was free and the tickets were for the magic
show.
Maybe these that sound right.
Yeah, there might have been a way I could see that being
the case because towards the end of the that specific video
in the walkthrough they're getting close to the Emerald
Castle or whatever the hell it is and somebody asked for
a ticket.
Okay, so the walkthrough where you see like a lot of the
animatronics was probably free and then there's a ticketed
point so you could maybe just bail after well, and then
that's the thing that we've talked about a essentially a
queue where then you don't do the attraction.
It was possible there and look it does it does seem like a
good one.
Yeah, maybe this is the unskippable unskippable queue.
I would say that that's that's right.
So yeah, Emerald City is huge balloon going up and down.
What's like I mean, it's not like the scenes are super
memorable.
It's just that you get still versions of the characters and
then you go along this path and you meet really well done
animatronics of all of them and you're two feet away and
you could tell even in old in old camcorder footage.
You could tell if these were not good, but they're really
good.
They're really good.
What seems like the best is that if you if you guys will
watch these these videos, I was very impressed by the wicked
witch.
Yeah, I think that might be number one.
Yeah, that that's that just seems exactly like the actual
actress and from the film.
Yeah, it's I don't I they're all pretty good.
Which one is the most memorable probably also because that's
the most scary character and it's burned in my child brain
forever.
Sure.
So took like confront and they kind of hide her you sir around
a corner behind a tree.
And yeah, no shit.
But yeah, the whole thing it's not that even it's just the
whole thing and it's because of the video I'm sure is adding
some ambience because it's old the foot it's old but the vibe
is correct for this eerie feeling.
I would have every time I watched the Wizard of Oz, which
I loved as a kid, but and I probably said this before the
movies is weird.
It's got a weird air like air vibe going on through the whole
thing and I'm not like a I don't want to say it's not pleasure.
That's not correct, but it's not like a relaxing.
No movie.
No, it's not edgy to me very edgy and you'd want the same
way growing up.
Yeah, I don't know anybody who was like, oh the wizard.
Just put that on kick your feet back and that's a pleasant
thing to fall asleep to know is always like, oh, that's the
scenes coming up where I'm going to hate it and like it would
be you feel forget what's when and where like, yeah, because
how many characters has she gathered by the time the scary
trees happen?
Yeah, wait, do we still shit?
She's got scarecrow.
Yeah, for a lot of kids.
It's probably the first film of your life.
You know what?
I mean, you see a lot of like movies, you know, just like
like casual like yeah, I'll throw on all over in company for
a minute.
I'll throw on a lot of sure.
Yeah, all the fucking shit our kids watching right now.
All the non movies baby.
Talk about AI.
Oh my God.
Yeah, that's the future.
Our kids seeing the future of a.
It's horrendous, but I feel like Wizard of Oz is probably
one of the first films, you know, like like a really
respected movie like a fi type top 100 to that you actually
sit in your entry for many years aired around Easter on
TV.
Is that right?
Oh, am I remembering that?
Christmas maybe Easter.
I think of me.
I'm in step Thanksgiving.
Is it a big it's all day on Thanksgiving?
What is what holiday is Arbor Day?
I know I was in the trees.
I just remember there was a reverse of it.
That makes me want to chop all trees down.
That's true.
This Arbor Day.
Let's get rid of all Arbor.
Just there was one holiday and I remember every year flipping
channels and landing on whatever broadcast network and it's
like, oh yeah, Wizard of Oz every year Thanksgiving.
I think it's Thanksgiving.
Okay.
Yeah.
The vibe though, that's that's like even the carrot like,
you know, there's a close-up of Ray Bolger's face and you're
like, I like this guy, but this is creeping me out his
makeup and the whole thing.
So like watching that's killing them.
The makeup is destroying their size.
I was reading about this last night.
I talked about this with my dad because his buddy Epson is
who it happened to.
Right.
He was replaced and so he was already recast as a Scarecrow
at first and then he was cast as a Tin Man.
There's a lot of photos of him in the Tin Man outfit and then
he had a severe allergic reaction to aluminum dust breathing
in aluminum dust.
It almost killed him.
And so they're the same kind of paint on like do they use
the same paint?
They switch for the replacement.
They did aluminum paste so that he wasn't free.
Still aluminum.
It was a paste not paint.
So it was fine.
But there's an outtakes.
There is you can hear Buddy Epson sing If I Only Had a
Heart on YouTube and there is an ensemble number in the
movie where it is his voice.
Really?
They still use it?
Wow.
Still makes it in.
That's like seeing the you know,
Eric Stoltz's hand in one shot.
Yes, it is exactly like that.
So yeah, when I say that it's like the walkthrough.
I when you see the walkthrough like something like this,
you know why they put in ride vehicles because they have to
move people through versus you wanting to live in it for a
while because like if the Haunted Mansion was a walkthrough
people would just be standing around because they want to
they want to soak it in a little more.
Yeah.
Well except though.
I mean like aficionados of themed entertainment maybe but
just regular Vegas folks.
I don't know because one of the videos I watched there's a
like it's a guy filming and he's with his wife or something
and she's just blasting through and he's like wait,
stop stop.
This is she's going to start talking like they like she's
doesn't even it doesn't occur to her that Dorothy is going
to do something.
Yeah.
Well, I there's the Vegas goers maybe aren't lingering like
the theme park people.
Sure.
That's I guess what I'm saying.
I feel like this like I feel like it hit a really specific.
I don't know if adults cared about this and maybe not at all
because they obviously got rid of it really quickly.
But I think if you took one of those trips when Vegas was
family-oriented, I think this stuck in your head forever.
And I even saw on our patreon Marnie sure said something in
voting for this one to be the Club 3.
I talk about the Wizard of Oz MGM Grand experience so often
that it came up in conversation literally yesterday.
Nothing made a greater impression on my young mind and
nothing ever will again.
Wow.
This lasted with people so like I think our generation is
just more predisposed to like this kind of thing and we fix
it on this kind of thing and go and where was it and what
day and how long was that around and I don't know.
We're just we're the animatronic generation.
That's I think that's right.
Well animatronics and just the ubiquitous nature.
We joke about the tin lunchboxes, but everywhere my family
went on a trip for like a day trip or a long weekend the
kind of souvenir shop selling like gadgets and gizmo.
It's a wall of Elvis tin lunchbox Betty Boop Wizard of
Oz.
So it was just always around.
These are the big ones.
Yeah.
Lucy.
I love Lucy.
Yeah, always.
So, you know, like you're saying Jason starts it starts a
little friendly but then gets spooky and you and of course
like I'm pretty sure I did this.
I'm pretty sure I was in here when I was a kid didn't, you
know, hit me as hard as Marnie I guess but I was like why
don't when we were looking at video of it the other day
like why doesn't the God this thing is so much grander better
done than I thought and maybe I blocked it out because of
the goddamn trees.
Oh, right.
As soon as I we went as we're watching the video together as
soon as it hit the and I'm not joking.
I'm not just like, you know, doing a bit about now as soon
as one showed up like out out.
I'm out.
Yeah, I hate those trees.
I when I started watching I was like, I wonder if there's
scary trees in this and I saw it.
I was like, oh man, Scott's got to have to talk about the
scary tree.
Aaron reaching for the emergency can of like Coppola winery
Sophia Rose.
We got to go higher than Coppola.
That's an emergency.
When you keep it in the cow.
That's our version of an Epi pen.
Just get him something.
We'll get you better wine later.
But yeah, that can we can't raise the what's his name test
Parker.
We can't wait to test park.
Yeah, yeah, buddy.
Ups and pal fest Park.
Yeah.
Yeah, don't like it.
I don't and it's in that voice.
Dear God.
Oh, yeah.
Should like that voice though.
It's so up your alley.
That's true.
And I like doing it.
I know.
Yeah.
Whatever you know, I agree.
He's like, I guess it sounds like like the MGM Grand Show
that one of you and your mom.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
This came up in the episode.
Watch this terrible like Blacklight show where there was
like some repeating it for the eyes, but you haven't heard
it Aaron the that there was like a an astronaut with a cord
in this show is at the MGM Grand and then a director yells
cut and then some scissors show up as if to cut the astronaut
off from his supply and connection to the spaceship and
then you're the same voice say not that kind of cut.
Law way back in there taking up space in my head since I was
eight.
Wow.
Just like Figaro pulling the signs from the last time you
were with us.
This shit is why this podcast has to happen.
I just like you got to get it out and just get and get
revenge on the world by planting these things that wasting
adult brain space, right adult brain space of strangers.
Now you have this.
Yeah, you're forcing your bad memories on them.
Yeah, this podcast is mostly a spite show.
Yeah.
You want to make me watch weird things and learn weird
things that I'm a kid world.
Well take this a specific group of really nice seeming
people.
This is true.
First, I'm going to give you my facts.
Did you did everyone when they were kids?
I was obsessed with the idea of like gambling and slot
machines, but a casino is a like kind of a scary ish place
in a lot of ways noise wise and just smoke wise.
They're scary when you're a kid.
Yeah, for sure.
So it's like to have the Emerald City and then have it
be this scary atmosphere and in addition have another
scary just on the outskirts of the Emerald City.
There's an even scarier place where the adults are all
losing their money and they're drunk and it's like an
extra level of it.
Frosting that's happening too.
Yes, they don't stop short at just the scary cake.
Yeah, it's like you get past those cowardly lines like
don't go past here like don't like don't is weird with
at one point you get two views of them, but you pass by
cowardly lion and Tin Man talking and scared and him
like go but then you're looking like through several
layers of bushes.
You just see distant slot machines and ash.
Yeah, which just land here that you're barely catching
like these characters from from behind and they're scared
and yeah, what are all those people doing?
And yeah, so so if you were a kid, I think that almost
that amplifies it to some degree because it's just like
this juxtaposition of two scary.
You think maybe the lack of full immersiveness actually
adds to this experience.
It adds to it and not in the way they wanted but in a way
I feel like if you were a kid, it would have been an
extra level of like this is for the adult.
This is the adult place on the outskirts of a scary place
that I like with some friends of mine.
Yeah, so it has an extra level.
I do think it's like I don't know.
We'll probably sum up but like it's in the wrong.
It's in the wrong spot.
We know that it shouldn't be in the lobby of a big
casino where a bunch of adults are just going like I just
want to fucking win some money and I'm tired and like
it's not the place where I get my free well vodka.
Yeah.
So but yeah, the have that sort of be how it's set up is
interesting.
Isn't it amazing that they tried like the risk of all and
all the things that we're going to talk about like it's
so nuts that Vegas took this swing and like would all
this stuff work?
The only way to find out is to spend more money than we've
ever spent to get Disney caliber ride creators and art
directors and like they most bits and pieces of MGM Grand
Adventures seem like cruddy low budget but across if you're
looking at the entire trend of Vegas family stuff, some of
it is so high end for something that was only there for like
a year and a half.
It's crazy.
Yes.
Yeah.
I always thought we talked a little bit like I get why they
tried it but in this instance, this is truly like just trying
to cram a thing in another thing like two things that are
competing for its audience.
Like these are two different audiences and they're both
right.
Right.
And one right up next to each other than the other.
This was very strong.
I know it was the runner-up but I will say I saw the
Caesars statue show.
Yeah.
And same thing because you have a lot of people who are who
just want to shop and shop expensive shit like you have
people there who like are so annoyed that suddenly there's
a huge show that people are flocking to and the lights are
dim and it's really hard to get around that main hub.
There's a big hub with lots of story.
You have to pass through that to get to other areas within
the shops.
Oh, that's fascinating.
Yeah.
It gets here.
It's the people are walking by with a ton of bags and a bunch
of kids stop in front of me.
Excuse me, you know, like bumping into as like you're
trying to watch the show or it.
Yeah.
Very similar thing.
Where it's just like I get why they tried.
I still I think that there's a better version of it now and
I've said this before because we we're all grown up where the
animatronic generation, which is a thing we should start
saying now.
Yeah, actually that is a ring to it, isn't it?
Yeah.
That's a nice nice term.
I like it's the one thing that binds us all.
We have that's what we have for that to ageing.
Millennial.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not loving that one.
Don't lump me in with all that.
Isn't there another more specific term something millennial?
Is it it's a geriatric millennial?
No, you're a geriatric millennial.
Yeah, that's not what we are.
We saw most generations of animatronics.
We saw some scary older ones.
We saw ones where they're getting we've seen it all.
We've seen it all.
And we've all were at the end of days with animatronics in
some ways, which says sad because the Chuck E.
The beloved Chuck animatronics are gone.
Sure.
But sometimes new ones show up.
Hey, we also seen the highest end, you know, Honda.
That's true.
You're right.
He's new.
Sure.
Yeah.
And we've seen the many Johnny Depp.
That's true.
We saw the golden era of activations.
Do people talk about activations anymore?
I think so.
Yeah.
Okay.
Immersives activations.
Those are all sort of in the same family.
It's all in the umbrella.
Yeah.
But the okay, so when you go, this is the part I sort
of recalled the walkthrough, but I did not recall that
the point of it ultimately is to get you to well, first
of all, to the dead center where things get scarier and
scarier and there is a thunderstorm that is really well
done and then legit unsettling and then laser animated
birds go by.
That's really nuts.
What were you saying?
Jason about the wisdom?
Is there a flying witch?
So I thought one of the ones someone said there's the
witch, but now that you say laser animated bird, it's a
little hard to make out.
It could be there's some like, is it some distant prop
or something on a distant projection on the ceiling?
Okay.
So feeling the cloud ceilings as a kid, I was always
fascinated when I saw clips of Vegas attractions or casinos
and then it eventually saw it in the Caesar's Palace in
Atlantic City.
But I love the cloud ceilings because it was just a thing
that Disney didn't do, you know?
Yeah, true.
Yeah.
Maybe here and there, but yeah, like environments are
supposed to hang for a long time.
There's see it like clouds on the Pirates by the blue Bayou.
I mean, yeah, here and there, but I big daytime cloud
scene.
Right.
Very Vegas night time.
Probably a few years ago.
I think I was in like a photo up in Disney World where you
were going by a barn.
There was like a barmen of fake crops and stuff to like
get to take a photo with Mickey or something and I was
like, oh, it's cloud ceilings like the you know, like the
casinos.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Well, there was also and again, I asked you, Darren, if
this was still going the first time you went but not just
the cloud ceilings when you enter this but once you're
done with it or if you're just going straight into the
casino, which was most people do you have were you ever
there when the ceiling looks like this?
Wow.
Rainbow casino.
This was the original.
This is this is what that main wing entrance wing looked
like in 93.
You know, I'm not I'm not sure it's amazing.
Yeah.
It's very like Sanrio Puroland.
Yes, very pure land.
Yeah.
And there's a couple I mean somewhere over the rainbow.
There's that and then there's also a rainbow projection or
see lights or painting on the ceiling.
Right, right.
Yeah.
Above the Emerald City.
So that yeah, that center but the fact that it's not just
like facade distant Emerald City that you can get right up
to it and then that houses a magic show.
Oh my God.
And I didn't think I remembered that but one.
Okay, this is where the videos get tough and where we don't
have a lot to say about the magic show because you got to
turn off your cameras.
I think one of those videos says that on screen had to turn
my camera off so long, but you see enough of the vibe and
it's this green tinted laboratory reminiscent of like
the Wizards workshop or whatever and it's vials and old
library books.
I have always had this distant memory of seeing a magic show
in Vegas when I was a kid, but I was like how because it
wasn't a thing where you could it couldn't have been like
a late thing where you could drink and now I realized it
was this I did this whatever was going on in there.
I think it was it must have been like kind of brief magic
shows, right?
It probably was not like a full hours worth of entertainment.
This might have been like 15 20 minutes.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's the deal.
But once I saw the room and realized I'd been in the room.
So I did see whatever this was called the Wizards secrets is
what this like hidden laboratory was.
The secret is that he's a he's a he's got a wizard man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and in her dream.
He is a both a con man and a liar.
He's getting the F out of here.
He's in the balloon.
He's getting out of this room looks incredible like really
intimate really detailed like pretty Disney style.
You would really accept that is like, yeah, it feels like
the pre-show room in Tower of Terror or something or Matt.
It has real Magic Castle like little side theater room
extremely.
Yeah, which and that's good for Magic.
You're you're close to whatever and I don't remember what
it was.
All I remember is that it was building to some particularly
big illusion that when it happened, I didn't know how it
happened.
And then I must have been with my mom and she explained to
me here was a premise for the first time in my life.
Like that was the art of distraction because like remember
when they were building the big thing and then somebody yelled
or there was a big thunderclap in the back and everybody
turned their heads and looked this way and then back in the
center or whatever the thing was had happened.
Right.
That's all I vaguely remember about it is that it was some
hey look over here and and then something huge happened and
that's a neat thing to discover when you're a kid.
Yeah.
Sure.
Yeah, I love I just thinking about how your brain blocked
out the trees and the magic show remains.
That's interesting to me only barely but I didn't connect it
to this.
Yeah, like vaguely remembered the room and the eerie green
hint of the room, but I didn't remember anything that
happened in there other than than getting distracted.
Right, right.
And my mom ruining magic for me.
So she told you that day what happened.
Yeah, I think so.
Okay, I just want to that was at least her idea of how
whatever the thing was but did anyone see anything else in
a video of have we have we mentioned everything?
Am I missing any details here?
Yeah, I'm trying to think if there's anything else.
I don't think so.
I mean, it's pretty it's well-documented compared to some
other Vegas stuff but not like comprehensively.
It's like a Disney ride or something.
I think there was a gift shop that then after they tore this
down moved around.
Yes, was yes, the gift shop remained for many many years.
Yeah, there's a it's the there's this shopping corridor.
That's like the forgotten basement sort of of the MGM
Grand.
It's the corridor that you take to get to the self-parking
and for a while also to the original monorail entrance.
That's where I think that's where like the that Brad
Garrett's comedy club is.
And that's where you could get like IVs, you know, if you
had too much to drink the night before you could get,
you know, like vitamin B replenishment.
I didn't realize this was possible and the Jason brought
this up and I thought that there's no way they there's
like three or four on this strip at this needle.
But no, yeah, you get stabbed with a needle.
That's crazy.
It's pretty I think that's pretty hot right now.
I think you can have them like if you're willing to pay
for it for like bachelor parties and stuff.
If you're like staying somewhere like at a house you
can have like a couple of nurses come over.
Yeah.
Well, are they sexy nurses?
No, just like professional.
They're just professional RNs.
Yeah, that would be a really good thing.
Professional RNs could be sexy too Jason.
Fine professionalism sexy.
So yes, they're sexy nurses.
Show Wang.
Should we all get injected and vaing?
Is this our new experience we need to have?
I've never done it.
Wait, we can just get B vitamins.
You could also electrolytes and B vitamins.
They might come to your room.
You could get it.
If you don't want the IV like you could just get a quick
shot.
And the idea is that this gets in your system a lot faster
than drinking it.
Yeah, it's like a hangover cure.
So if you had too many well drinks or cold drinks at the
slot machines or the tables, you know, but would the idea
be that like you'll be like, oh my God, it's gone in 10
minutes or something.
Is that the idea?
That's the idea.
I think my brother-in-law has had it done before.
I have a memory of him going in at least to get the shots.
Okay.
But anyway, that's the shady corridor.
It's always been just like that.
If you it's the place that you don't want to be.
It's the it's the least grand part of the MGM grand.
It feels very old.
The ceilings are low.
It's kind of weird, but that's where all the remnants of the
Wizard of Oz stuff was when I was going there.
Like that's where the last bits of it decayed for a while.
And one was a big gift shop.
No entrance Wizard of Oz thing gone.
What like 95 96, I think but this still but like there was
still like you had to just like Wizard of Oz footprint in the
corridor that takes you to the self parking where all the
crap is and what doesn't it's it's isn't there like a very
pervasive subway smell subway sandwiches.
There was a subway and there was a hot dog cart to okay.
And the very end of it really traps.
Yeah, that really smell the buns just absorbed the smell.
That's where the flavor is Jason.
You didn't work at a subway or anything in college.
Did you know I didn't work at a subway?
Okay, we don't I didn't work at the BJ subs between the
West Tower and the East Tower sandwiches you've ever tasted.
I was going to say shout out to BJ's, but maybe they don't
shout down to BJ's.
Or the what do you how would you say like the the cappuccino
premixed cappuccino machines from the gas station.
I did live on those sorts of like push the button fill up
the cup.
I did live on those when I pulled all nighters, you know
finishing from BJ's you mean from BJ's.
You have a same gas station cappuccino.
Yeah, and that I feel like when I moved to the other side
of campus, that's when Red Bull was catching on which I
really don't like the taste of but sometimes would grin
and bear it, you know, how many all nighters did you pull
in college handful?
Got I tried to not zero.
Nice.
No one one one night, but it wasn't and it was more of my
friend Kia and I stayed up all night just like having fun
and then we found out that the name for dusk but in the
morning is civil Twilight.
So we called that day civil Twilight and yeah, I heard
that cute.
Yeah, we called like that that night like the first night
that we like really hung out.
It was just like yeah, like we're good friends.
We called simple Twilight.
Oh, we stayed up all night.
Hey, Kia friend of this day.
Kia.
But yeah, Emerald City gift shop remained neon follow the
yellow brick Road sign in the window.
Just really weird that like, okay with it.
We have realized we don't we need all the square footage
we can get for like more slot machines for restaurants for
nightclothes fill in all this stuff.
That's just like fun little flourishes start making more
money and I guess this was a gift shop.
However, it seems really strange that in increasingly
unfamily Vegas, they still need a place to sell like little
porcelain Glinda's.
We need to have that all the time.
Yeah, and yeah a lot of Ruby slippers not that you could
actually wear but like little figurines of Ruby slippers.
Yeah, they probably a good grandma kind of present.
Yes, that's where it strikes me is that like well, that's
completely for the old ladies doing their Vegas trips like
they probably they're spending a lot of time in there.
Yeah, maybe Michael Jackson when he was I have that one.
I have that one.
I have three of those.
I have seven of those each munchkin.
He had all the munchkins in.
I know all of their names.
Yeah, and he was yellow.
Mustache bigger mustache.
He was personal friends with all of them.
I assume to Jackson befriended each living munchkin.
Act.
Yeah, probably correct.
It seems right.
That feels very Michael.
Yeah.
So this thing disappears other than the store at some point
in time Toto got stolen.
Yes took Toto out of there.
Although then I watched a news report about it thinking.
Ooh good clips and I was like this is all fake.
This is a bunch of crap.
This must this is like a coordinated PR attempt from the
MGM grand.
Everybody was like acting in it a little bit too much.
That's what the news anchor is even like.
Was this a publicity stunt?
Well, I can't say probably like he seems like it when they
interview the kidnappers and they all have bags on their
heads.
Yeah, it's very given Toto a tour.
It's very cutesy like sending fake ransom photos of Toto
bags on their heads was a paper.
Last resort.
Did they shave him and turn him into ass bite?
Look at this knucklehead.
But he steals dogs.
And is gay.
And also as always.
Yeah, but then but other than that Wizard of Oz stuff kind
of disappears.
Mostly is gone by the time you're there, but there's still
a lot of dumb family stuff for you to enjoy and for these
formative years to happen in.
I don't okay.
Look, we've been going for a long time.
I don't know that I have time to do a lot of the stuff that
I have here.
But let's so let me just let me do the speed round of it.
Yeah, because there's one other big way that the Wizard of
Oz characters factored into the MGM grand and that is the
opening ceremony the December 18th 1983 opening ceremony.
We love our opening ceremonies.
Yeah, this is this is some real Scott and Aaron YouTube
crap one night of you know, Discovery.
This is exactly how we like to entertain ourselves.
This was such a good one, right?
Like an hour like a 50 minute here is just the live disorganized
not like shot with nice like coordinated cameras by the I
think they were filming it on like film cameras.
But what we're watching is the local news and they've set
up two cameras to cover one of the most complex opening
ceremonies I've ever seen.
They don't have good vantage points of anything in order.
They have good audio feeds of anything.
So it's just news anchors who in many cases are saying now
is that I see somebody pulling up there.
Is that is that Chris Christopherson?
Honestly, I don't have a good lie.
Can't tell I can't tell and I we do have an angle on it.
It is absolutely as a man who doesn't resemble Chris Christopherson
in any way.
But anyway, this ceremony is this huge thing in the where
you park your car where you where you arrive in the casino.
They've taken over that and there's a ton of pedestrians
but then also cars pulling in celebrities arriving for the
big grand opening.
Let me let this local news guy say all of the stars who are
going to be there.
Art Link letter Sugar Ray Leonard Evander Hullifield of course
the two boxers Bill Simon you may remember him.
He was Treasury Secretary many many years ago.
He may remember years ago Andre Agassi, of course will be here
the local hero tennis course Jerry Tarkany.
We saw Jerry Harry.
He's expected to appear for tonight's events.
Dr.
Dre.
Dre is a rapper.
He will be here as well.
Matthew Modine will be here.
Wow.
Howie Mandel will be here as well and we're expecting Shirley
McClain and we also saw Dr.
Dre who is a rapper rapper rapper is a profession.
I don't know exactly.
I've never seen it in action, but I'm told people enjoy seeing
rappers do their rapping clarified the not the kind that
you would get on a Malm's bar or something like that such
an assort is a living human being I guess who performs in
some way.
I don't understand it either.
I'm scared.
Ask your kid.
I hope they ban it whatever it is, but the biggest stars
who are at this opening are four very recognizable characters.
Here they are.
The Wizard of Oz is here.
Let's take a look.
And of course the movie is here.
There they are.
The news anchor said there's Dorothy and then there are the
three characters the three characters three characters are
here.
Dorothy and the rest.
It's a real Gilligan's Island.
It's a Gilligan's Island.
It's three of the most colorful three characters who look if
you want to guess their names just look at them and say what
you see.
Yeah, this guy is so stressed out though.
Like give him the benefit of the doubt.
He's been there all day.
He's had to fill so much time.
Yeah, because everything started late started like it
should be had to BAM for like 20 minutes.
He's been live on television for hours.
So he's he's just bleary-eyed.
He doesn't know what then he isn't.
You wouldn't know what Mickey Mouse is named.
He could have gotten like he would have been like Scarecrow.
I think he would have said he could have tin man.
He made it call like Mr.
Metal or something and then the lion you probably would have
said there is a woman approaching me and three whimsical
creatures who mock God's plan.
An upright lion does not walk on on his hinds.
Please.
I hope somebody shoots him.
Can I mention the one weird pop cultural moment where this
is referenced?
Yes, there is a line in the movie swingers.
They go to Vegas if you remember that part in Vegas and Vince
Vaughn and Favreau pick up a couple women Vince Vaughn says
like, oh this girl so-and-so she's a Dorothy at the MGM
Grand.
Oh, yeah, I mean that's good.
That speaks to yeah.
Hey, that's a catch.
Yeah, sure.
Favreau is an animatronic guy.
But the real catch at this and now and you'll see why I'm
jamming this in that at a long episode you will understand
immediately.
Well, maybe not immediately you have to like I'm going to
make you you'll see the face and you will understand because
he said the Wizard of Oz is here and that's true.
The Wizard is here and unlike the Dorothy whose name we don't
know you will certainly know the name of the Wizard.
Who do we see?
Who do we got?
One of my favorite people of all time Rip Taylor.
Rip.
Rippy beloved to Aaron and I both because we have the really
specific memory.
I'm sure I've said on the podcast when we were having a
nice dinner at the Animal Kingdom Lodge and then I got a
phone call that I thought was going to be my parents which
made me think there was going to be an emergency.
So I'm sorry.
I really got to take this and I go outside Scotty.
It's Rippy.
I'm angry.
Because I had filmed a Funny or Die with video with him three
days prior right before getting on a plane to Disney World.
So the bizarre and then me I left for so long and you look
at me like what was that?
What's going on?
Sorry.
Sorry it was Rip Taylor.
It's Rip Taylor.
Man about a lot of things.
I know you knew you'd known each other a long time.
You're probably very impressed.
God my boyfriend.
I guess he knows celebrities like Rip Taylor will just call
him and chew him out.
You're on the phone with the gals bragging.
Well, Scotty just step away last night.
He was on the phone with the celebrity.
It is really is something we say just that's lasted.
That was 13 years ago now and still so often we will say
Scotty you used me up Scotty.
Sitting in Giku the cooking place with Scotty the starmaker.
So yeah, I mean is this not the greatest casting you ever
seen?
He looks just like him.
He's ever looked more like a Wizard of Oz.
He looks like every Wizard of Oz character.
He looks like the Munchkin.
They keep calling them the Wizard of Oz and he gives
little awards out to MGM executives.
He says like because you are the heart of this organization.
So I give you the heart by the power invested in me as the
Wizard of Oz.
But then what he's wearing, I think that's not right.
I think what he's wearing.
He's actually the gatekeeper.
Yes.
He's the guy who pokes his head out which is the same actor
is the Wizard of Oz, but everyone from news anchor to
rip himself calls himself the Wizard of Oz and I don't unless
is that the same guy is that the idea that he's the Wizard
in disguise or something?
I don't know.
Is the joke that like, yeah, the Wizard pulls a lot of fast
ones.
So he's like, I know what you can't see the way and it's like
a trick like pretending to be your own secretary.
Yeah.
The Donald Trump.
The Trump.
Yeah.
If you go a little further up the strip like, oh, yes,
you can find unpleasant not fun casino.
So anyway, then there are just hundreds of dancers who come
out every type of Wizard of Oz character, the ones in the
big hats.
There's flying monkeys.
We didn't mention that there's a flying monkey bar.
That was another thing.
There's no photos of you can't figure nobody filmed that like
animatronic drunk.
What's his name already?
Foster Brooks.
But anyway, limos are pulling up.
This is not just a brief appearance from Rip Taylor.
They make him read the name of every car that pulls up and
he doesn't have a good vantage point either.
So like a car pulls up and you hear him say that there is
it's from from Dougie.
How is there?
We all know him.
It's Neil Patrick Hayes.
There is Neil Patrick Hayes.
I really listen to make sure and he gets it wrong.
He doesn't say the right name and then after and it's the
most insane lineup of people you ever seen.
It's Dougie Hauser.
It's Neil Patrick Hayes.
And then right after that is Alexander Haig Reagan's
Secretary of State.
And then after that is just a mascot owl and wolf from the
theme park.
You cannot make any heads or tails of the theme of who's
arriving at this.
But Rip Taylor has to read and read and then let me just
play a couple more clips really quick.
Then like then there's a big gap where no limos are showing
up.
So with the news guy asked to vamp again.
So here's how he fills the time.
As you stand here watching and you see the characters from
the Wizard of Oz, of course the original characters,
of course you have Judy Garland, Bert Lahr, Jack Haley,
and Ray Bolger.
Of course they have all passed away.
At least I'm pretty certain they have.
It's kind of sad that they would not be here for something
like this.
I'm sure they would enjoy that.
Not all the original actors, the original character.
The original characters.
John Elham, Judy Garland, Ray Bolger.
But Ray Bolger, I'm pretty sure Ray Bolger is dead.
I think he kicked the bucket, but if he didn't kick that
bucket, I think he'd be having a blast here.
Then there's a big fireworks show, but they don't turn off
Rip Taylor's mic.
So you're watching fireworks, but you get occasional commentary
from Rippy.
Talking to people he knows.
Who he sees.
What the hell is going on over there?
What is that?
I don't know her.
Send her away.
She's looking at me weird.
And then one more thing really quick because the other thing
I loved about this special was that then when the fireworks
really kick in, there's an amazing medley of classic rock
songs where you cannot possibly predict what's coming up next.
And here's a taste of that.
Here's this.
Yeah, one sec, one sec, a little more.
It's too much.
Honestly, it's there's too much smoke.
I can't breathe.
An ash landed in my mustache.
I'm on fire.
That's what Rippy out.
Someone put Rippy out mics on for the next 48 hours.
They're very dramatic station.
I'm sleeping.
He interrupts the network.
It's a reruns of cheers at 4 p.m.
Why I don't need room service.
I'm trying to sleep.
I was out late being the Wizard of Oz.
I fell asleep on the lion snoot and then I was stuck up there
for about I fell out the window and landed on the snoot.
Worst night of sleep I've ever had.
What is that very recognizable music cue?
Baker Street.
And then it'll go into Human League.
Don't you want me and paint it black and then still more and
it never stops.
Hey, it's so just look this up on YouTube.
This is the most delightfully disorganized but it has the
Wizard of Oz.
The Wizard of Oz has to be there as we kick off this play.
You know, it's like it's part of the fabric.
Yeah, the citizen at one point there's the very dynamic
fireworks show and then there's a cutaway to the citizens
of Oz all pretty much standing still.
Oh, you're right.
I forgot that was in there.
They're not dancing anymore.
They don't know what to do.
They're looking at each other.
What are we supposed to dance for part of this?
I know they didn't tell us to so don't don't do it.
You can see that very human moment where you go like I guess
I'll put my arms at my side and then no one seems comfortable.
Like it's like I guess that's not conveying anything.
I guess that's normal and then they just look so uncomfortable
doing that.
So anyway, I couldn't I had to show Rippy is the Wizard of
Oz but you know, look this Club 3.
Thank you for voting for this and Aaron.
Thank you for being here because you inspired we got to
inject some Scott and Aaron YouTube Vegas bullshit.
We got some great memories of you being scared of lions
and hanging in fun arcades and you prompted some greats
by saying waffle you have unlocked Pandora's waffle iron.
Do we have a good question?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
See the problem is there's a couple of different ways
you can go with a good question.
Like one is like kind of a joke question, which I don't want
to do that.
I want to get to the reality of the situation.
I mean you can save it.
We can just make it its own episode.
Jason's college college career preparation or whatever you
would call it.
I'll say this.
Did you have a waffle each time you worked?
No, really well because like I said, we ate the crew meal
half hour before no one was working the waffle station
until I rolled on over there.
Nobody but you didn't like to scream take them.
You weren't like grabbing minis is you know, because the
oh no, I was not discreetly grabbing like because that was
the other thing they're like, here's a big plate.
If no one's in line, just keep making waffles and mini waffles
and put them over on the plate.
So that way when people walk up they can just you can just
give them one which looking back I'm like, oh yeah, nice
room temperature waffle.
Yum.
Not fresh.
Yeah, would that happen?
We'd have to start stacking up waffles.
This is two questions.
Even like again, the 19 year old semi hungover college
students would be like, can I have a fresh one?
And I'll be like, yeah, sure.
Okay.
Well more to come on that.
Yeah, this is not the end.
We have finally you keep finding pockets.
You think you're done and then you get to like that
fireworks show and then it just keeps on going.
But this episode I will have to end for now, but I'm so
happy to say Aaron Gardner, you survived podcast the ride
Sin City Nights.
Yay.
So happy you could do it.
This was a blast.
Thanks for joining us.
Thanks for letting me talk about one of my favorite places.
Oh jeez.
Oh, we had to and you made it one of my favorite place.
You made Las Vegas one of my favorite places with our many
great trips there.
So thank you.
Let's exit through the Emerald City gift shop.
Last time you were here.
You were you had a thing to plug which is your appearance
on the Price is Right.
You don't have anything else like that going on.
I can't imagine.
Well, I'm pleased to report that my career my lucrative
career as a game show contestant continues and I believe
December 4th y'all can catch me on let's make a deal.
Wow.
CBS check your local listings.
Geez finally something to look forward to in December.
I know it's so far.
I've been filming this like a month ago and it's so far away.
It's a long haul to Christmas, but now there's a little
treat for everybody right before.
Wow.
Thank you for dropping this.
Everybody shut up about it though, because we were not
supposed you made the calculation like we're behind
several paywalls.
Yeah, I think we're think we're also let's make a deal is
a much jinkier production.
And the prestigious prices, right?
Well, don't think this did.
Oh, if they hear you say that too, now they probably lean
into it.
That's the vibe that I got there.
But anyway, it was a blast.
I really loved doing it.
I had a lot of fun and yeah, I don't have a social media
footprint myself, but I will force Scott to post the let's
make a deal stuff on your socials.
I will use mine.
Hey, do you want to put it out in the universe the next
game show that you like to be?
I may have filled out a contestant form for a certain
game show that a certain Jay Leno.
Gentlemen, but I haven't heard back from them.
So fingers crossed everyone.
But we're crossed you could win upwards of $200.
Honestly, it would be worth it.
But hanging out with Jay and Kevin.
Well, fingers crossed for you listeners put out your good
luck for that because well, my God, all of our brains
are explode Aaron with with with Mr.
L.
I know.
Hopefully my recent appearance on let's make a deal doesn't
hinder things because there's a lot of weird laws.
Oh really?
Oh, yeah.
Because you have to wait.
Show you could appear on.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, and we got you know, you got strikes going on too,
but it may know it's different rules of the game.
Who knows?
Who knows when they'll look there's something more powerful
than the like collective action of all the actors out there
and that's Jay Leno's need to work at all times.
So I think he will he will find a way.
Well, wonderful.
Thank you, Aaron.
To have you.
Oh wait, I have to apply.
We never have good.
So I have to say your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done freedom fighter.
But I wasn't that that felt great.
In many years of marriage that felt like the most intimate
moment we've ever had.
Yeah, it doesn't get more intimate than those magic words.
Yeah, but I say that to the listeners too.
And I forgot to say next month.
What do we do next month?
We got a couple things floating.
Fall of Atlantis was the runner up Dixie Stampede Dolly Parton's
Dixie Stampede was a runner up.
I say chaos round.
If you want more Vegas, let's do fall of Atlantis or suggest
other Vegas ideas.
Let's throw those in too.
If you want other stuff, let's do Dixie Stampede new
new non Vegas ideas to the let's let them all against each other.
What about Jason working in food service?
Full Jason food service.
Ever since they're trounce all of them.
The protocol is just somebody needs to say it in the commu.
I was saying it doesn't count somebody needs to it's like a
very parliamentary procedure.
Yeah, but if somebody stands and calls for it, it can be in
the running.
I have a good story.
I haven't even told you about you preparing food.
Yeah.
Yes, and it's a little too on the nose almost.
Oh my God.
Did you get a bunch of tomato sauce on your nose?
Miraculously in the story.
I did not but I did get yelled at by an unpleasant man.
Yikes.
Okay, we got that Mike story still floating out there too.
This could be a bit actually August could be the tough one
to win.
What's that?
Yeah, somebody should put it out there.
Just like the vote for the story hour.
Like yeah, three is just like the stories that oh just the
story is the story.
You could group them together.
That is another move you could make.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, it's in your hands now listener only you can decide
California split my gambling buddy over here.
What do you mean?
Well, we would both be telling our our foolish stories.
Yeah, my film California split.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Elliot Gould and George Siegel, you know, today's Elliot
Gould and George Siegel.
Yeah, and I guess because I drink two glasses of wine
sometimes I'm today's Foster.
Foster Brooks.
100%
So long.