Hey, it's Podcast The Ride Sin City Nights.
Tonight on the Fremont Gate, we've got a spectacular show, the finest Podcast The Ride impersonators
you've ever heard.
It's gonna make you feel like you're really listening to Podcast The Ride.
I'm Bart Tate and tonight I'll be inhabiting Scott Gardner.
This guy, he's gonna dazzle you as Mike Carlson, it's Nathan Ruiz.
Hey Nathan.
Hey there, I just bought some collectibles and I really enjoy them.
Wow, wow.
It's the voice, it's the affectations and it's the interests.
He manages to put them all together.
That's like juggling and singing and dancing all at once.
Hey, and of course, the nation's premier Jason Sheridan impersonator, Kip Finkel.
Hey, it's Kip Finkel, but today you'll just call me Jason Sheridan.
I'm here eating far more sugar than a 37 year old man should ingest.
You've been doing your research.
That's right.
Just really work on some of those Pennsylvania.
Whenever we practice in the Pennsylvania vowels, just make sure you got those.
We want to hear at least one through the episode.
Sure.
Sheets versus wah-wah.
They love it.
Hey, I love hearing it.
I don't even know what it means, but it's part of the picture.
It's how you play Jason.
All right, well, Nathan, Kip and I are really excited about today's topic.
Okay, impersonators, obviously a big part of the Vegas entertainment landscape.
What we're talking about today is perhaps the biggest and longest standing impersonation
enterprise, legends in concert.
Now, I say that I give it those credits.
I'm not exactly sure if they're true or if that itself is part of the legend is conjured
up by the man behind the enterprise.
You might say a guy will get into it, but we're doing this.
Our guest brought to our attention the importance of this legends in concert corporation, whatever
you want to call it.
He himself, a musician, a Twitch streamer, the DJ for the sadly deceased hip hop artist
Bugmane.
Thankfully, he's gotten back on his feet and he is now the DJ for up and coming hip hop
artist Bugmane 2000.
So happy he's here.
Andrew Coates, welcome to the show.
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much for having me podcast.
The ride.
Wow, man, I am excited to have you.
You've been such a supporter for for such a long time.
And one of my favorite folks, we've gotten to meet over the course of doing this and
this whole whatever we're doing and bug con ecosystem that we're part of.
And yeah, happy to have you on the mic here.
I'm enthralled.
This is amazing.
I'm looking at Garf like Mike's wearing a pink Mickey shirt.
Like I'm really getting the full experience.
Yeah, you're getting the real deal.
And you're wearing a Steely Dan hat, which makes me happy.
Thanks for representing that and Knott's Berry Farm.
A scary farm.
A scary farm indeed.
So you're representing and with that, I mean, that's one thing.
You I know that you're a Knott's guy.
And which I feel like is always bonded, all of us when we've gotten to talk.
But let's let's talk general theme park stuff before we make the drive into Vegas.
Wait, what's what's some important stuff to you on your your theme park plate,
your theme park journey?
Oh, my gosh. Thank you so much, Scott.
So like I'm from Bakersfield, California.
You guys are aware, have any relationship to Bakersfield?
It's always interesting asking anyone out here like, oh, I stopped there for a
sandwich or something on the way to San Francisco.
But like I don't remember.
I don't remember if I've ever done it.
So my parks growing up were mainly weirdly six flags, six flags,
Hurricane Harbor and Knott's Berry Farm.
Like majority.
I've maybe been to Disneyland like five, six times my whole life.
Like not that I don't like it.
I love it. It's great.
But like not a ton of times, but like six flags more times than I could count.
Oh, sure.
A little closer up because the Bakersfields, I forget what freeways are talking about.
We're like, but it's it's heading up north.
We're talking about the great line.
We're talking about the ninety nine, the five and okay.
So six flags is right there by Cal Arts, and it's pretty close to Bakersfield.
And like just yeah, if your standard is like ninety six flags with all that
element and theming going like Knott's was huge for me and sure like Mike,
you've talked about in the past, you marched in marching band where again?
Disney World Epcot Center and Magic Kingdom.
Wow.
So yeah, pretty impressive.
No, yeah.
Multi-park marching.
So for me, I got to march in front of the Calico Mine Ride.
I think twice.
Okay.
I was either playing trumpet or sousaphone.
They switched me to sousaphone at some point because they needed it.
And like the fingering is the same.
Yeah.
Okay.
But this is like a massive one that goes all the way around your body.
Yeah.
There was one of the roots at a sousaphone player at one point.
So that's my only sousaphone association.
Definitely.
I thought that was odd, but cool.
So like Knott's really locked into my head, like marching there.
And you marched in middle school, you said?
Yeah.
I believe it was like sixth or seventh grade.
You were marching really because I didn't start marching until high school.
Interesting.
Yeah.
High school is when I stopped marching.
I got into orchestra and I played the upright bass in high school for a little bit.
And then I stopped because I was playing in bands and stuff.
And I was like, I can't do this structured shit anymore.
But yeah.
So in middle school, I marched, I think, six, seven, eighth grade all three years.
And we had to wear these terrible little costumes.
Yeah.
Ill fitting.
And there was a cummerbund and all this stuff.
And the hat, it wasn't like a big hat.
It was like a cowboy hat.
Oh, that sounds cool though.
Yeah.
It's more of something.
Marching band uniforms can only be those.
You can't wear any piece of a marching band uniform just around in your day to day.
At least cowboy hat.
The cowboy hat sounds so much better than what I had to wear.
I had to wear a normal marching outfit, which feels like you're wearing snow pants.
I don't know if you California.
Yeah.
Snow pants is what you would wear in the Midwest.
You wore snow pants as a child ever?
Did I watch snow pit?
Where?
I wasn't sure.
The way you said it sounded like it was like an 80s movie or a kids thing where it's like,
you know, snow pants.
Oh, no, no.
Wearing them.
Yeah, sure.
I had some snow.
I think I had like a snow suit overall thing at some point.
Yeah.
They were like overalls basically.
Those.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's what it felt like to wear the marching band outfit.
I don't know if you had a similar thing.
It was just heavy, like a heavy material polyester or something.
I assume.
Yeah.
If you're out there, you're usually doing like a Christmas parade at night.
So like, yeah, you get bundled up, but no, it was just like black slacks.
This insane like looked like a like a color band flag type of shirt and like very stiff
with a cummerbund and I had to play trumpet.
But yeah, everything you're describing sounds awesome to me.
So like so much of a better outfit than when I had to wear definitely deep in my parents
stuff somewhere is like a VHS tape of like KGET Bakersfield of like me marching by in
a broadcast like Christmas parade.
So I'll have to try to find.
I'm like five years away from wearing a rainbow shirt and a big cowboy hat out in general.
You should.
So you really should just push it leaning.
Yeah.
Sure.
Why not?
That's your band chic.
When they started, Captain Neo went back in Disneyland.
They were selling that t-shirt.
I bought it.
Yeah.
And I don't know where it is.
Somebody a lot of people.
I lost it somewhere.
That's cooler than what we're describing is I had the rainbow shirt, the rainbow shirt.
Yeah.
Now we're talking about marching.
We're comparing that to the swoop.
He brought it into Captain Neo.
I didn't say this part.
I feel we should all wear Captain Eos outfit soon.
We should all start wearing that just casually.
Just casually.
Just running in.
Yeah.
Just running in the target to get milk and bread and eggs.
And you're in the full Captain Eo outfit.
Yeah.
I did it for Halloween once, so I do have Eo gear around somewhere.
So now it's just a matter of making it a part of the routine.
You add a cowboy hat to it and it's perfect.
Wow.
It sounds like a little Nas X would wear.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
I never did marching band, but I remember a week or two before school started, they would do
practice in the parking lot of the school in 100 degree weather.
Yep.
Terrible humidity.
And then everyone was wearing T-shirt and jeans.
But I think it was a point of pride of like, yeah, we're doing it.
We're doing two a days for marching band.
Not for me.
I don't think I would.
I think it was like, this sucks.
Yeah.
But I'm sure there were...
I'm not saying you're wrong.
I'm sure there were kids that were like, yeah, we're being forged in fire.
This is the trials to prove that I'm the ultimate musician that can also walk while
he plays.
I'm thinking more the instructors were really into it.
And then a handful of kids were probably like, yeah, we're doing it.
We're hard.
Yeah.
They saw all the cool.
Did you ever think, oh, and I guess you were, you said you were playing in bands.
I was a roommates with a guy in college who was into drum core.
Oh, wow.
And that's a really intense thing.
Yeah.
Like you're saying, like, you know, if kids are very hardcore into like marching and
doing that thing, the most hardcore of them were the drum people.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
And that was like right around the time of like drum line and stuff, too.
Yeah.
That was like very in the cultural guys to be on a drum line.
And I remember the guys with the quads and all that stuff.
And yeah, especially in high school, they went on and like, I remember being in the
orchestra with people who ended up going on to like teach that stuff professionally,
like drum line people, legacy drum line people in Bakersfield.
I don't know.
Mm hmm.
Good.
Yeah.
I think well, because he would.
Yeah, he was like you could do marching band in college and other but other like
places for competitions.
It was a whole world that I didn't know.
Sometimes it's like a cacophony, but it's like really if you can get into it, like,
yeah, big drum ensembles are very interesting.
This listen.
But yeah, there was like a whole like it was it was basically I shouldn't even say
it because I don't know the details, but it was almost like full on marching band,
like competition, almost independent of sporting events.
Like there were just like, yeah, like a few teams and like people would kill to get on
them.
And then like once you were done, like you were like, I need to get back.
I need to go back.
This is the highlight of my life.
Yeah.
Wow.
See, wait, because I was thinking you didn't like it really, but you but the thrill of
competition.
You I'm not saying I did.
I'm saying these people are in these like that sort of did it past high school.
And you never got to bring the sticks marching band show that never made it to the big stage
of the competition.
No, no, no, no.
That was Mr. Bada arrangement was not a year.
Yeah, that was a senior year.
I listened to that song again, like just to refresh after you had you had said that
it really is all it's like a lot of sweets.
It's like that's that's an intense song to get really builds up and then like ding, ding,
ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding,
then it gets like little mysterious.
I remember doing anything even that, you know, as popular of a song as that.
Do you remember what you played in knots?
Do you have any idea?
I I don't.
I'm assuming it's just some kind of like I seem to remember doing a lot of like Philip
Sousa style like you know what I mean?
Just jaunty like American general sense, it's not too with all the patriotism of knots and
though you got to bring it there.
Yeah, yeah, American.
What I want to say about not generally though is like I love that it's just so much
it's it just feels like a dry California history museum and in the best way.
Oh yeah.
Then there literally is what's it called?
The Western Trails Museum inside a knots is an old history museum and the guy who
generally works there is like this older dude who'll really talk to you if you ask
him a few questions.
Sure.
One time went on about his deceased son with me for a little while.
It's just like that, but that's like going to a real weird museum.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then just like all the the the mission like dioramas that are all over not like
is that still there?
Did that ever want to?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, right.
It's like I think maybe you did it too, but like kids in California, you had to create
a mission in elementary school.
Yeah, school project.
You would have to make a model of a mission of your choice and that was and then you
usually I like did a trip to a mission.
I can't remember which one it was.
I think it was one in San Jose, but like just all that stuff at knots just makes me.
It's like classic California.
It's like I'm living inside a Hewlett-Hauser episode when I'm at not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I do that all the time.
He did a he did a knots.
I think he did.
I don't think I came up.
There was so much to talk about on that one.
But he did Gilroy Gardens.
He talked about those twisted trees that we talked about.
Oh, wow.
There was there was discussion of you guys got to do a Hewlett-Hauser and I'm a big Hewlett fan.
I even have I ever said this on the show that I spoke to Hewlett-Hauser on the phone several times.
When I got my Funny or Die shot to meet any the biggest stars, the hottest actresses,
I instead chose to try to get Hewlett-Hauser and Oslet, which then led to it was the same
situation as where my meeting of Rip Taylor.
So if that's a tea, we can table Hewlett-Hauser.
But yeah, definitely a Hewlett-Hauser here.
He does an episode about the Knott's Chicken Dinner Restaurant.
I have not seen that.
Where he walks in and starts talking to these waitresses and they're all just like a glow
about it.
And then one time my wife and I were in the Knott's Chicken Dinner Restaurant eating
and I mentioned it to our server who's like an older lady.
And I was like, you know, there's a there's a Hewlett-Hauser episode, you know, about this
place. And she was like, yeah, I'm in it.
Just like walked off.
I was like, what?
Like my drop moment.
Yeah, no.
And then people who have those jobs at Knott's like work there for 20, 30 years.
They love it.
Yeah, it's like, geez, I don't know.
Did he heal that he liked it?
He liked it, right?
He said it was amazing.
Of course.
It was amazing.
It was the one place.
He didn't know.
It sucks.
I hate this.
Amazing.
Sucks.
Shit.
Honestly, though, like Hewlett, I don't think he was eating a lot of fried chicken and
mashed potatoes.
Like he's jacked.
You ever watch some of those older episodes before he gets into like the yellow shirt,
older Hewlett style, like if they were doing necker toys, a Hewlett, that's like his later
yellow shirt.
But it's more billowy.
Just early on, he was in the military.
Like he's like, wow, really jacked in to show it off.
Yeah.
Big upper body Canadian tuxedo.
Jack really people.
He'll is.
Yeah, you can tell.
I mean, I feel like at some point I must have seen a photo of him in his 20s or 30s,
but yeah, very early.
Yeah, very so.
Mm hmm.
Now, he'll he would eat half a plate to be polite.
Like he's got a oh, it's so good.
He's got a pastrami sandwich in his mouth for, you know, wherever he's at.
Yeah, yeah.
Historical for research purposes, he has to.
Any listeners who do, but does he only people in California know Hewlett-Hauser or was this
because he was like a California historian guy.
California's gold, a PBS perennial.
Yeah, California's gold.
But maybe, but I feel like some of the cult of Hewlett has spread to non-California.
Yeah, certainly.
I didn't know about him until I lived here, though.
OK, yeah, it's definitely would have been somebody on my radar.
Sure.
Would have been interested in it before.
Less I think.
Yes, so specifically California, not like, yeah, like Rick Steves.
I think his shows are everywhere and he's written a lot of books and stuff.
Sure.
Travels.
Because he's yeah, he's Mr. Europe.
Yeah.
People are interested in Europe wherever you go is what I've found and what Rick Steves found.
That's right.
Yeah, I love Rick Steves.
I read it.
What was this?
I read it a few years ago.
Travel is a political act and it was like really fascinating.
I'm a Rick Steves stan too.
Yeah, but yeah, but how much can Rick Steves lift?
Oh, I don't know about that.
I'm taking Hewlett.
How big are his biceps?
He keeps himself pretty good shape.
I know he really kind of, you know, during the pandemic, he couldn't really travel a lot.
Sounds like you're making excuses for him not being so jacked.
I'm saying you can have weights in your house.
Yeah, you could have.
I'm sure he was working out a little because he's like, he can't travel, but I think he kept a lot
of his like all of his staff employed and started doing other stuff.
We can get my steps in Europe is what I do.
Yeah, a lot of excuses.
I can't walk around my neighborhood.
We're onto you, Steve.
So we know your deal.
I'll kick Rick Steves' ass.
Hell yeah, you'll get a view.
Might have strong legs from the walking, but if we're fighting up north for fighting
north of the equator, I push them down.
Can't use your legs if you're on the ground.
I can break an apple with one hand.
I can squash it and I'll squash Rick Steves head.
And you'll say it's amazing.
We're here in the Huntington Beach wetlands to fight Rick Steves to death.
A perfect place to bury his body.
Yeah, this is where nobody will ever know.
These wetlands are acidic, so he'll be dissolved after I whoop his ass.
I wrap my fist in barbed wire.
Well, what else?
Anything else you want to bring to the table here?
Or do you want to talk?
If I can do one more, like you guys have talked about over the first of all,
I'm just I'm a big fan of this show.
I've been listening since like first five to 10 episodes.
Well, thank you.
You're one of the first.
Yeah, absolutely.
I was trying to track down like, did I see you guys in the Craig thing
and then made the connection in?
Excuse me.
Complicating.
Complicated.
All in.
Yes, that's right.
My complicated pre the show.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
But then I've so I've been to the PTR twenty three show in the Anaheim.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I was at the fries interactive installation, the legendary.
I mean, that's on the trip.
That's the first thing I keep thinking back to it because it was so as an observer,
it was so insane because it was just and then in context now,
it was like so close to the beginning of Covid.
So it's like the last thing, the last thing a lot of people did I got to do before Covid
and like coming.
I saw it like when I got out of the car, you were like walking in with the spacesuit.
I was like, oh, he went.
He got the suit, man.
Shit.
I had to rerun it because I'd filmed the video long ago.
So I had to do a second to see Chary Chip walk out from the distance.
Like how far away he came.
I was just like, well, it was such a happening for me, too, because I didn't know about that
part legitimately.
Yeah.
When suddenly the front like to like try to plan a flag and like has anyone ever talked
or thought about fries as themed entertainment at length?
And then we put it out there and then we get the greatest gift on the other side of it
you could ever imagine.
And also me walking in in a space suit wondering like, did anyone come and then being like
greeted like I'm getting off of a spaceship.
All right.
People actually came to that.
It was so nuts.
And thank you for coming.
What a memory.
I like I can't even.
And then also I went to the late night dirty show at the dining.
It's inspired that you bought a ticket and you gave us the you said, I can't wait for
some X, X, X and some body nest.
And we're like, wait, that's the idea.
So thank you.
What a body show.
It was so dirty, though we can't release it.
It's too hot for podcast feed.
I want to get into the takes they had.
Oh, my God.
The secret.
Oh, the other thing I wanted to say is you guys have talked about how the theme parks
have really influenced your musical taste in some way like the ambient music.
You're always talking about listening to music that's played on a train or so.
I'm sorry.
That's correct.
Listen now.
And like with your love of all the whatever eighties top hat bands that are play around
Disneyland and so.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, Alice in Wonderland, a party at knots right under a different name, broader
impersonation.
Yeah, yeah, but no, but like okay, so I mentioned Hurricane Harbor, which is the
water park attached to six flags in California and like so my my best friend
in like elementary school, his mom was dating a rock radio DJ for crab radio
Bakersfield, which is like the old rock like sure big radio station and clear
channel radio station.
He then through a promotion got like a big stack of like free tickets to Hurricane
Harbor.
So for like two summers, we must have gone like I sort of got like eight, ten times
this.
We would just drive back and forth, spend all the day in like the lazy river and the
giant wave pool at Hurricane Harbor, which is one of the biggest like wave pools, I
think in America and like but specifically the music that was played is like Euro
trance, like 90s club music.
So like I am now completely obsessed with this stuff and I collect these 12 inches
off of the Hurricane Harbor off of Hurricane Harbor, like groups like, you know,
or like Hataway or like, oh, you know, a lot of that stuff because I like, yeah, I
I think about those, all those bands that only had like two hits and like what else
is going on beyond the hits or like why did those like nobody knows who they are.
They're almost like anonymous bands and like nobody could name the members of Quad
City DJs or any of them too are just like an Italian guy who's a producer who like
finds a singer and then they make a name for it.
That's live and joy or that's like, you know, the real McCoy or like all these
groups, but they have a lot of them, but like hearing like also like the music of
the night of the Roxbury, you know what I mean?
Yeah, exactly.
Like that stuff has completely influenced like the music I buy the records I play,
all kinds of stuff.
It's because you have so many good memories associated with it.
Absolutely.
I'm floating around eating expensive chicken tenders, smelling like sunblock, like
putting my stuff in a janky locker.
Could you eat and float at the same time?
No, I would.
I don't think I would attempt that because it sounded good when you said it.
Well, you know, it's closely tied.
We would eat the chicken tenders.
Yeah, Lazy River.
You know, we would listen to, you know, because I would know another dream, but
I'll raise you.
I have that 12.
It should.
Wow.
Well, I got to see more of this.
Speaking of that, I just want to say in this time of, you know, Mercurial,
Mercurial, you know, CEOs of media companies, I'm a big proponent of physical media.
I think it's maybe the only way that you can really own media.
So I have a few gifts.
No, which should we have some other because you've got me stuff before.
This is a 70s, your record.
Yeah.
Gosh, this was my thank you for that.
Whatever.
Thanks for a little physical media for the good boys.
This one's for Jason.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, this is like a like a 100 years of magic.
This is the trip video is a promotional tape that we had that at some point.
I think you said that you might have those already, but you know, a very dry tape about
a boat and a celebration.
I love it.
Yeah.
No, this box does not look familiar, so I'm excited for this.
Oh, just talking about like, oh, we got to buy a VCR.
Like we got to buy a VCR to fiddle with.
I'm trying to I'm trying to influence a little bit, maybe get a VCR.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, we're moving.
So, you know, it's an excuse.
It's not expensive to get a VCR.
I don't know.
It's not really.
Oh, boy.
Let's see.
Oh, man.
Wow.
Well, geez, you know, you've always like, I feel like we've bonded on the music end
of things and you really.
Wow.
Okay.
Uh, Toto, holy Anna.
This is like not this is a deep cut song.
When they play this, they say here's a deep cut.
So you got me a deep cut.
Wow.
Single of holy Anna and Mr. Roboto.
There it is.
Single.
My God.
I mean, I got Kilroy was here and I got I think I have the DVD of caught in the act.
The live concert.
Let's play from around this time.
Caught in the act.
The act of musical righteousness of talking about censorship and oh, and there's all my
favorite character.
This is my this might be a shot called in the future is sticks.
Oh, yeah.
Kilroy was here, so we can talk about the iconic characters like Chuck Pena.
So as Lieutenant Vanish.
Well, how are we not said the phrase six years we haven't said the phrase Lieutenant Vanish.
Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
That's that's deep.
It was in the back of my head at one time.
Like in high school, I could have produced that in zero seconds flat.
But now, well, thank you for bringing Lieutenant Vanish back in my life.
Of course.
Thanks, Andrew.
Wow.
No problem.
And then like.
Now, I'm a VHS.
Yes, but I'm really into laser.
This.
Oh, my God.
I feel like I just have some of the same like brain sicknesses as you guys.
Like, sure.
I love Lucy like my parents.
It was just in our household.
It was a second nature.
Like, I don't know, just being completely unrelatable to other kids.
Because I hate to you're into old shit like that.
I hate to spoil it, but I can see the smiling face of Jonathan Frakes.
Look, it's it's.
Yeah.
Wow.
First contact.
This is a laser disk for my.
Oh, my God.
Thank you so much.
And maybe the way I got into laser, I found a copy of Twin Peaks Fire Walk with me at
a thrift store and it's like one of my favorite films.
And I was like, OK, I need to now get a laser display to watch.
How yeah, that's more expensive, right?
To get a laser display.
Yeah, that's a little harder to track down.
But if you do, you know, I'm planting seeds of like, yeah, well, this is all you're going
to send us on our little well.
This is a display piece as well.
This is Star Trek First Contact.
This is one of the best Star Trek movies ever.
Maybe the best is up for debate.
Would you say it's your favorite or are you a Star Trek guy or you just know I'm a.
Like Star Trek.
I'm mainly like a next gen guy and I do like this movie.
Did you watch Picard season three?
I'm not up on any of the new shows now.
I like to I like to put on.
It's just I was just next gen mostly.
It's just funny because last night I watched like the second.
So I'm just watching scenes from Star Trek Picard and just like as I'm going to sleep
last night and like getting excited all over again.
This is like a 2 a.m. last night is what I was doing.
Now here's the extra special tweet for Vegas month.
Mike, why don't you go ahead and check out what the insert is on that laser disc?
Is it Star Trek the experience?
I don't know.
Is it Star Trek the experience ad for it or something?
Maybe.
Wait, wait, maybe it is.
Did you leave it in the sleeve?
It's still in the sleeve.
Excuse me.
You got to learn your way around laser discs.
I'm really fumbling here.
It's really like Andrew.
It's an ad.
That was just what was in there.
A poster.
Wow.
This is awesome.
Star Trek the experience Las Vegas Hilton for 30 years.
For 30 years, you wanted to boldly go.
Now you can.
Summer 97.
This is awesome, but also makes me sad too because we didn't get to go.
Wow.
It's a teaser.
Look at this content.
Wow.
I've seen this.
It's like a movie theater where it's dangling from the ceiling and it like it spins around.
You see both sides of the poster.
This is I've never seen this version of the poster before.
It's the same photo of Patrick Stewart and Brent Spiner, but it's a silhouette of the
Borg Queen, Alice Kriegs Borg Queen, of course.
Borg Queen.
Who seduces data.
Love the Borg Queen.
Wow.
Who makes data horny.
And Picard I think gets a little horny too, but it's not as obvious.
This is incredible.
Yeah, thank you so much.
You clearly you listen carefully and our specific nerdiness calls out to you.
Yeah, really.
You're able to identify us so well.
Yeah.
Holy Ann is blowing my mind.
And your streams, if people haven't seen, check out King Cove's streams on Twitch.
Crazy music selection.
Really good.
Really well curated.
Jane and I will put them on, often play them through a gal.
I got her a galaxy light a few years ago.
If you guys remember the galaxy lights.
On the ceiling like.
Yeah.
Well, when someone would have a viral tweet, people would reach out and go like, hey,
will you put these, will you tweet these?
And the thing and the one was like starlight galaxy light.
Uh, so I, I think it was for Christmas or her birthday.
I was like, I'm going to get her a galaxy light and the websites all looked so scammy.
And then I found like, oh, you can just buy these things on Alibaba or Amazon.
And it's still working.
It's still working, but it's fun to have colored lights.
So cool.
Thank you so much.
Thanks only Andrew for the color.
Oh, sorry.
I should have explained.
It's thanks for the lights.
Andrew.
It's got a Bluetooth speaker in it.
It'll pulse with the light.
Yeah.
That's dope.
Our lights are fun.
So you just run anything through this.
It could be anything.
I could play a laser disc of first contact or a King Cove Twitch stream.
Yeah.
That's really sweet.
Thank you, Jason.
Yeah.
Follow my Twitch channel if you want.
I DJ vinyl on there.
Sometimes I'll watch a laser disc or two.
Wow.
But yeah, I really enjoy.
Gee, Jan on there.
Thank you for this, this pile of stuff.
Star Trek, the experience, one of the only things we got to before
Sin City Nights here, an outlier.
But now we're in the thick of it.
And you're OK.
I think you've also proven your love of deep pop culture and deep finds.
And that seems to be at the root of your discovery of all this, of legends and concert.
Yeah.
Which we can talk about that documentary and the guy.
But like maybe just big picture stuff.
I mean, we could sort of do this together.
But this has been an impersonation show that started in Las Vegas in 83 at the then Imperial
Palace, now the Link.
But it's everywhere, too.
This is it's in Branson.
It's in Myrtle Beach, Broadway at the beach or on the beach.
Something people have told us to talk about before.
Like their city walk, it seems like you can see it on a Norwegian cruise line.
Oddly, not in Vegas right now.
They do not currently have a home for this show.
It was at the Tropicana.
Now there's it ended.
And now so will the Tropicana that's going away entirely.
And this is also the kind of impersonation show.
I mean, the only memory I ever had of it before you brought up to us was just seeing like
if I'm on a trip with my parents in Vegas or somewhere else that had one of these shows
and I'm like checking out the pamphlets, I like go rifle through pamphlets so I can
look at them in the room and what the hell is this one does that.
I remember seeing the pamphlet for this and it's that kind of show where it's seven mismatchy
stars all on stage and all a little bit off because obviously I mean, the makeup and
costumes are as good as you can get, but it's still a little it's a little weird, right?
Yeah, a lot.
You're probably getting an Elvis.
You're probably getting a Michael Jackson.
And then I feel like I always remember seeing like a Rod Stewart or a Tina Turner.
And then they change and shuffle out through the years.
But is that a pretty accurate, you know, general summation?
Anything else you want to say about Legends in Concert generally?
Yeah, I honestly I don't even have those memories.
My journey with finding Legends in Concert and Johnny Stewart,
Banjo Johnny as he's known and that we'll get into it.
But like I at the original, the original Hollywood Amoeba location, not the new one.
Yeah, they've done fine.
It's all right.
But that original one was so fun.
I have very important memories.
High school memories for me, too.
Yeah.
My dad's like a graphic designer.
So when he would go to like design conferences in L.A., he'd bring me along and just be like
buy some CDs and I'd be in there just like 13 years old.
Like, oh man, hours, hours.
I'm with my wife and I are at old Hollywood Amoeba.
She's more she's very my wife is varla vuvum.
She's like a very talented, like burlesque costumer and performer.
So she's very into like vintage Hollywood stuff.
So she's really into Marilyn Monroe.
Her films, films about her films featuring impersonators apparently, too.
She's really into all the TV movies of like about her life.
Every single there's a million of them.
So I saw this VHS tape.
It just says legends.
Just as legends.
Along with some pull quotes and stuff.
Right. And I was like, oh my God, a movie about a Maryland impersonator.
We got to get it, babe.
You know, oh, great.
It's her face mainly, but you got an Elvis in there, too.
And that's kind of all it tells you and some like cursive font.
Ironically, not the because the legends in concert font feels iconic to me.
Very, very using that branding.
So it's like obviously that means something.
But we took it home and we watched this and this documentary blew our minds
and it stuck with me ever since.
That may have been like twenty sixteen, twenty seventeen.
And yeah, I guess this was this documentary is from I have it written down.
I think it was shot in eighty five, but and then maybe like existed or went to
festivals and stuff, but wasn't maybe fully released to like ninety two or so.
Says okay, so if you listener at home, if you want to watch this on YouTube,
it's called Johnny Stewart's Legend in Concert, the Making of aired on Cinemax
February, Ninety, Ninety Two.
That's the title of the YouTube video.
It's a lot of sloppiest every word in a foster.
Now that's I'm glad.
Thank you, Trina Foster, because I thought I was going to have to like rip this
because there's like very little information about this documentary itself.
But eventually somebody did rip it to YouTube.
Watch along if you want.
But like this has been in my mind, like this guy just like Andrew.
You sent this email, you sent a pile of a bunch of links about the show and you sent
the documentary as well and just with the briefest dive into the documentary, it's like
this is completely worth talking about this whole enterprise.
And the documentary is amazing.
How you said the same you said what I was thinking, which is how is this not a bigger
cultier work because it's like truly facet, like aesthetically cool.
The characters you follow are haunting.
Some of you will.
Listen, if you watch this documentary, you will not forget the people who you meet.
I want to shout out director Alana Bardin.
Yeah, I don't know anything else about her, but I want to say the name because this is
like I didn't know if this was going to be like funny, like an old like, you know,
what they played in the hotel rooms at Disney.
But no, this is like this is true.
Great filmmaking.
Yeah, this is a great documentary.
Yeah.
You guys, you guys, you guys all check the character, like really pushing, like not
just playing it for laughs the whole time.
Like, you know what I mean?
Yeah.
When you when you could because the and there are laughs, there are definitely laughs.
Yeah, they're fascinating characters.
I mean, the main one being you've alluded to the name, Johnny Stewart.
If you were at the Groove Blender, if you saw the live stream of the Groove Blender,
it'll be out, you know, soon on the main feed.
But the it was a big celebration of Vegas guys and, you know, some more famous, some
more obscure.
This is maybe on the more obscure end, but this is this is a big old Vegas guy that I'm
glad we're encountering this month.
He is like truly and there is no question that he is a guy just from looking at him
the first time.
This is a guy who founded Legends in Concert.
OK, yes, you go to this is him today, right?
He is a he's 15 years ago with that photo.
Oh, roughly in the broadest scheme of things today.
Wow.
This guy.
So to describe him physically, it's kind of like like a perm mullet and still today,
like right to some extent.
So yeah, very much so.
Yeah.
You can compare it to a lot of people.
Same hair today.
Yeah.
Great curly hair.
A little goatee.
He kind of reminded me of the guy in The Last Dance, the security guard.
Oh, yeah.
Who Michael Jordan plays quarters against and who Heidi Gardner played in a sketch later.
Definitely got a vibe, just like odd vibe and kind of like weird, wiry guy.
And the eyes are intense and like and the energy is intense.
And so a lot of the documentary is is through his eyes before we talk about him in the 80s.
What you just showed is from his website, Johnny Stewart Productions.com.
JSP Productions.
And it's a great website in general.
But when you go to websites, yeah, yeah.
When you go to the about section, you see a picture of him hunching down at his ranch,
Legends Ranch, which still is around.
And it basically just is there to do like Christian weddings.
If you track that rabbit hole of the Legends Ranch, you can just rent it out to do your
godly wedding.
That is, I think, important context to mention.
And it comes up like 50 minutes in the document.
You're seeing all these impersonators.
Everyone's very focused and passionate.
And this guy's really intense.
And he's talking about putting on this show and the people love to see the show.
And he can teach anyone who's really a good singer.
It doesn't matter if they're good or a singer.
They embody the person.
And then he goes, and that's what you can do with the power of Jesus Christ.
And I was like, oh, yeah, okay.
It comes up in a lot of interviews, too, because there's a lot of ephemera of local
Las Vegas interview stuff.
And he's got a whole his own YouTube channel of interviews that I didn't really get into.
But it's too much professing his Christian views.
You laid it out.
It's like 50 episodes of a 45 minute public access show that's all on YouTube.
If I had the time to watch Johnny Stewart, I would.
These videos have been watched 20 times.
I don't want to YouTube video shame because who knows?
Our videos don't always do so many numbers.
These are viewed four times.
That's really the sign you found something in a YouTube rabbit hole is when
we're south of 100 in these views.
Oh, my God.
This is one where I wish I could enter a little time warp or something to just sit and not age,
but I could watch them all like the hyperbolic time chamber in Dragon Ball Z.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You are in the space ship.
You are going to.
Yeah, but I won't age.
And it's just like a little rip in space time getting ripped.
And Mike is there just going like all the Johnny's watching.
Oh, Johnny Stewart weighs in on the Oakland A's moving to Vegas.
Is Goku more ripped than Hewlhouser?
What do you think?
Well, not in my mind.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I mean, we're talking super saying.
Rowling or whatever.
Can I also say by financial metrics, Johnny Stewart is successful.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
This Legends show has run for so long.
It's so many places, so many iterations.
Mm hmm.
Oh, yeah.
No, this is not like a down in dog patch update.
Situation.
No, no, no.
True.
Yeah.
He's not all bluster.
The thing is really successful, but it's hard to imagine what exact what kind of success
would justify what you find when you go to his website, which is this photo of him hunched down.
And with the big headline giant font, sometimes father does know best and him looking at you.
Hey, hello.
And then you go down, especially when it comes to creating a new entertainment genre.
Take the case of mastermind slash producer John Stewart, known as the father of what is now the
impersonation empire throughout the world.
Then a little bit of the history and it's been Vegas, it's been an Atlantic city and then a long
list of shows you've never heard.
I don't know.
We got to focus on Legends or we'll never know.
I know.
Once you get into the subshows, it's in said, but a long list of shows you have not heard of.
And it is it is all funny given that like at most, I don't even know if you guys are similar,
like what I was saying, I've heard of Legends in the concert.
I've seen the pamphlet for it.
Then you go into the world of the guy who thought of that name and like, yeah, that's right.
That's who I am.
And I'm a legend, too.
And I'm a bigger legend than all of them.
And how much is in the bubble once you puncture it?
Yeah, no, it seems like something that would just be like, yeah, let's just put up a show.
And it's like impersonators and like, that'll be fun for everybody versus a guy who's like,
I birthed this from my birth canal.
Like, this is a creation of like, yeah, we basically says that in the document.
So intense about it.
Yeah, yeah, there's some clips and I have some I don't if we want to like, I mean,
understanding his philosophy a little bit is probably a good thing to do.
And also that, you know, here's a photo of him today and the style isn't as crazy,
but the hair is kind of similar.
But, you know, 80s, 85, it's much more 80s ish mustache.
Perm is crazy or mullets crazy or leather jacket with rattlesnake cowboy hat.
With lists like a skull, rattlesnake skull in the hat and tassels on the jacket.
He looks a lot.
The wardrobe is a lot like Eli Cash, Owen Wilson's character from Royal Tenenbaums.
And then what's even the first, I mean, maybe a big thing to say about him is that he put the
show together and he hand selected all of these great impersonators, only the best,
and he pushes them to be the best and he's proud of them.
And sometimes he'll say like, and they're a dear friend of mine, they're a real friend to me.
But he also needs to tell you at any moment that they could all be yanked whenever he wants.
This clip might be an important one to play earlier to get his character.
And this comes right after his wife, who was also just in full like denim tassels,
Dolly Parton, they're still married.
They're still doing interviews together.
All these years later, I almost can't believe that given the general way she's treated in the
interview.
I found some other interviews.
Apparently they met when they were 19 at a church dance in Long Beach, California.
Wow.
And he like within like a year they were married and have been married since they were 19,
apparently.
And have 15 children.
11, two of which are their own, the rest are adopted.
So they adopt a lot of kids.
Wow, a lot of adopted kids.
Interesting.
So she has just given some compliments to one of the characters, one of the figures in the
documentary, an Elvis named Jonathan Von Brauna, I believe.
Yeah.
So she said some nice things about him and what I like.
Notable Elvis.
He, you know, there's a lot of Elvis impersonators out there, but this guy seems to be one of the
tops and even like has his own following with his own name as much as an impersonator can.
And after he is complimented, this is what Johnny has to say about him.
But that show in Las Vegas, every single person in that show could be replaced in one day.
Every single person.
I never allow, I build enough molds and I create enough of the product of those molds
that at any point anyone tries to pull my string.
I cut theirs.
Incredible.
What a clip.
I mean, he's a me.
There's another point where he says, do you think you created you or I created you
like I'm and then he's like I'm going to recreate the recreations.
I'm going to recreate you.
This is what Charles Manson says.
Yeah,
we create you Jack and I'm a city by a new fifty vote.
So I found this if I could expand a little bit on his early life.
Yes, Johnny Stewart.
Now this documentary is great.
Watch it, but like okay, so I found speaking of YouTube, it somehow this video
was just for us.
I think this interview of him of Johnny Stewart, an hour brand new hour long
interview from Las Vegas tonight with Dale Davison, which is another local
Christian interview show, Christian Vegas entertainers love that who also I found
it a Dale Davis and also interviews Kevin Sorbo's wife for like an hour.
What does she do talks about people being snowflakes and stuff?
I don't know.
No, literally in the interview, but like no, she like co produces all those
terrible Christian movies with Kevin.
So I guess like we're producing a new movie about the blood of Christ or
whatever.
Right.
Sure, sure.
But like so seven days ago, this new interview dropped.
I was the first viewer of it.
I'm like taking all these notes, but Johnny Stewart lays out a lot of these
things that are a little more unclear.
Let's say there's some inconsistencies in some of the stories that I found
through articles and interviews and stuff.
So basically like he's from a poor family.
It's an entire like singing band family.
Both his parents are singers.
There's like eleven kids in his.
He has like nine brothers and sisters.
They're all singers.
He plays banjo since he's seven years old.
He's known as Banjo Johnny, which just feels like, you know, what is it?
Asbury Jukes.
It just feels like, oh, Southside.
Sounds like Southside Johnny.
Yeah, Joe John.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, in that clip, they talk about we had a trailer and we traveled around
to like the county fairs and state fairs and stuff.
And my mom had invented like a baby, a seat that you could bounce the baby up
and down in.
And then it would be time for the show.
And she would leave the exhibition area and come do the show with all 15 of us.
Insane.
Like yeah, they're creating products and selling them on the road as well as
singing.
So I guess they're from Pocotillo, Idaho, and then they moved to California.
After that, he wins an award on the Arthur Godfrey show as banjo.
Johnny at seven or eight years old claims he worked with Burl Ives at the
Sacramento State Fair.
He said he did.
What a boast.
Yeah, lives.
He said he did the Bob Hope Show, the Cliffy Stone Show, getting so cliff.
We're all stumped on Cliffy Stone Jason.
You know, Cliffy Stone, I feel like I don't know Clippy Stone, yeah, quick
Google for me on this one and then okay Scott, are you ready for this one?
Oh no, I don't know if you're ready for this one.
Oh boy, does Audubon Junior High mean anything to you that school?
I don't think so.
Well, it's the junior high school where Johnny Stewart met his friends, Mike
Love and Brian Wilson.
What the fuck?
What are you talking about?
What?
What Audubon?
Yeah, so he went apparently went to junior high with Mike Love and Brian
Wilson.
They went.
They would go to church with him.
Claims that either he see this is what unclear he kind of mushes this, but
basically either him or his brother sang with early incarnations of them pre
beach boys.
This is such a thing that guys try to do is right.
Yeah, I was kind of in the beach boys.
All right.
Oh, my brother did it, but regardless like and then and then okay, so there's
this beach ways connection.
Then he says he goes to Garden Grove High School next where he meets his
friend Steve Martin.
What?
Oh man, I mean I almost buy it in that.
I mean, I don't know about friend.
He like thing is real.
I'll keep going like it's like he so he's the he's the director of the plays
or he puts on the plays at the high school right.
He then goes on to be the creative director of the Birdcage Theater at
Knott's Berry Farm.
Johnny Stewart was the director with the theater where for like a Martin
got to start.
He hired Steve Martin at the Birdcage Theater.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
He also claims to have introduced him to Don Galvin, a famous banjo player who
teaches Steve Martin the banjo.
So maybe banjo, Johnny banjo, Johnny.
So like a key figure in the rise of Steve Martin, like one of the biggest ever.
There's your theme park connection.
And this came upon us, my wife and I, because okay, so we found this tape.
We watched it from Amoeba blew our minds.
We're like, I can't find much about this guy or this documentary.
This show is still going on, but it's on him anymore.
We're huge fans of knots.
We have our season passes.
We walk into the Birdcage Theater and it's lined with all these
pictures of shows of yesteryear and stuff.
And there's a section called Birds Who Have Flown.
Wow.
Okay.
And at the top is Steve Martin and you go, oh, Steve Martin.
He performed it very cool.
And then on the bottom, yeah, Johnny Stewart, he's been there this old time.
Right.
We walked in and we were like, wait, that's the fucking guy from the documentary saying
he's going to cut the string.
He the most angry glaring photo.
I want an energy there.
Wow.
He's he there's a photo of this man at Knott's Berry farm that you can see any time you want.
So logistically, Johnny Stewart is a, an in theme park character.
Absolutely.
Like just like Papa Steve or Sad I Joe, you know, this, that's incredible for 1963 to 1969.
He was a creative director.
This is yeah.
So this is like his truly his villain origin story.
He's banjo Johnny.
Then he hires Steve.
Right.
And then goes on to become banjo.
The famous banjo.
Yeah.
Banjo and close to the beach.
But he's like, he's so close to this like California dream.
These people who really came from just, you know, like run of the mill, no money,
OC and South Bay and whatever.
Who would have thought anybody would be massive global stars who you just ran into in school?
So he must be as the as the seventies or the sixties and seventies are going by and
his friends are getting huge.
Apparently he has a very short, like one line scene in the man with two brains.
Wow.
He talked about like Steve Martin, like invited him on set and like had him do this whole
thing and just gave him one line.
It was like, all right, you're done just like, like, but like that movie's not free.
I couldn't pull the clip, but like he just runs out in front of a car and says, hey,
stop that or something.
Yeah.
It is amazing.
Johnny Stewart is not like a one scene character in licorice pizza.
Oh yeah.
Oh, you know, he's like John C Riley is yeah, he's always in that he's in the monster outfit.
And then he's also this guy, uh, Johnny Stewart, you know, he came around and he hung out with
young PTA, uh, along with Conway and yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Stirred to be another one that I found in a different in at the end of the Dale Davidson
interview.
He's like, yeah.
And then, you know, there was a drummer in my band.
He had a little boy about five years old by the name of Bruno Mars.
No, like so like the way the bit in Vegas, uh, honeymoon to Vegas or whatever the
where Bruno Mars appears as a Elvis impersonator as a child.
I knew he was a little Elvis impersonator.
That'd be the connection is like, yeah.
And of Elvis impersonators and then also hit now his son becomes.
Yeah.
How do they have any connection to him?
How does he?
Wow.
So he's part of the Bruno Mars rise.
Maybe apparently too is Bruno Mars almost the biggest impersonator.
Is he the biggest performer who came from impersonator world in any regard?
And the fan he is, I think you could now at at least one of these legends shows,
see a Bruno Mars as part of the starlight bowl had a Bruno Mars cover band already.
So that's gotta be a rare case of impersonator to impersonated.
Right.
Yeah.
Can you just explain?
Cause I, I don't think I know fully about this.
Bruno Mars was doing impersonator acts.
He was a little kid Elvis.
He was in there.
So you can watch of different shows of him at like seven as the littlest Elvis.
The moon, honey, the movie, honeymoon in Vegas.
He appears as little.
As little Elvis.
I didn't at the end of it have it on laser disc.
Oh, okay.
This is what I thought you were saying.
And I was like, I just want to clarify that he was a little Elvis.
All right.
So, okay.
This guy has crossed paths with all these things.
And then he I'm going to pull a little bit from a different Vegas interview show that
you sent as part of your link pile, something called Vegas live with Nina.
That was my, I think my favorite of what you said.
I really like anything like this.
It seems like Vegas is a lot of these things where like people just start talking and don't
explain who they are or introduce their guests and like, that's fine.
We don't need to do any of that.
We're in Vegas.
I'm in on that's all you need to know.
And this is a talk show that's filmed in a bar that's not closed while they film it.
This is like,
look good.
There's just like people like people like, you know, putting big trays of glasses down
and cleaning and dropping stuff.
And they'll look into the camera for a long time as if to go like, should I,
do they tell us not to be doing this?
Well, no, this doesn't matter.
This is just Vegas live with Ninon.
Clang, clang, bash, clean sink.
So the loudest talk show you've ever seen.
But he says on the show, speaking of the godliness too, this is also so we're fusing
near brushes with celebrity with Christianity.
And he is in Hollywood and he drives by a billboard or some, you know,
collage, whatever mural, whatever of like all of the stars that we've lost.
Probably all the ones that ended up in the show.
It's Buddy Holly and Marilyn and Elvis.
And he sees that and goes like, what if you could go to something that was this,
that was like the gates of heaven opening up.
You almost said that one.
What's that?
I think you almost said hell.
Depending on the acts.
The gates of heaven opening up and all of like, and they're all there and they're all here to
perform for us.
And that's what gave him the idea for the show.
And he'd had like false starts of other things he tried to do.
So I went to state fairs with robots and I don't know what the hell he's talking about
with that.
That shit is crazy because he claims to have created pre the legend show.
He claims to have created robot legends.
He doesn't say animatronics right right.
He says robots.
I had a robot show.
Well, he was going to show at the Knoxville World's Fair and cool yeah,
and but then he said that like there were all these mob people that like took over
that world's fair and started trying to like tax him for fifty percent of his profits
and stuff, and so he left and he's like and then you know, like nine people got arrested
for that.
It was just like what is dropping these details of the like?
Excuse me.
Story there is real or not.
On X, that doesn't make anything like apparently in eighty one there was a robot show that
he was working.
I don't know.
I mean, what do you mean?
I mean, it does sound easier to hire people and put them in wigs and makeup.
I think we could get this guy an interview.
Listen, I didn't call it, but there's just a number on the web.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, guys, guys, I was going to save it for the end.
Did you call up in on Vegas live with an on?
He's really hyping up a bunch of stuff he's got going and you know, and I got the Jets.
You got to come see the Jets.
The Jets are coming to Jets.
This 80s group who did the Chip and Dale's or a version of the Chip and Dale song like,
wow, he's working with the Jets.
Yeah, it's the Jets and it's their kids.
They got some big family band is that tons of them.
You got to come and is that show going?
Well, it is, but everybody's got to come.
Everybody's got to come see the Jets.
He's really sweaty.
Like maybe they're not doing well on the Jets to the point where he gives out his website,
gives out an email address and he gives out his phone number and just his band.
It's not a 555 or an 800 or anything.
It's just a regular phone number.
I'm like, I'm sure the number let's see.
And I call and on the other end of it, it's just an answering machine, but it's definitely
Johnny Stewart.
I know the voice at this point and just something like it.
Just leave your name, leave your name.
It's got that intensity and I will call you back.
I'm going to call you back.
And then and then it says the mailbox is full so I don't leave a message.
But as I'm going to bed one night, I get a phone call, two phone calls in a row.
Oh my God.
Las Vegas.
And I'll just play him.
Call Johnny Stewart.
Call me back.
Oh my God.
Or what?
Call Johnny Stewart when you can.
Thanks.
So easy to contact.
I elected not to knowing what we would be discussing.
But if we end this with any big questions for him, if there's anything really burning
that we want to know, we need to make a list.
I got to say that is one of the most efficient voicemail messages I've ever heard.
Jason's impressed.
I was like, it never dawned on me.
It never dawned on me to do that.
I feel like if regular people without the Johnny Stewart flair did that, it'd be like,
oh, he pissed at me.
Did what?
Just say, call me back.
Hi, this is so and so.
Call me back.
At this point, how many messages are you leaving?
Not often.
My parents leaving me one or me leaving me one.
They're the only ones I feel like.
You leaving yourself one?
No, no.
Me leaving them a voice.
They're the only ones.
I think now we have to hear a to the point Jason voicemail message.
Yeah.
How would you do it now from you've been inspired?
Hi, it's Jason Sheridan.
Call me back.
Call me back when you can.
Thank you.
Now, can you do what it would have been like 10 minutes ago before you had this revelation?
Hi, it's Jason.
Just going to say hi.
You're probably out or runs.
Give me a call when you can.
I'm around today until like five o'clock.
Okay.
See you.
You know, I now I kind of understand what you're saying.
We probably all meander on these things and John, but Johnny Stewart's got business to do.
He's running 20 shows at all times, so he doesn't have time to waste doing these messages,
but he does have time to call me twice in a row.
Somebody who didn't leave a message does no idea who this is, but it could be an opportunity.
It's like one time my wife and I are really obsessed with Angeline as well.
Yeah, of course.
Oh, yeah.
Billboard superstar and we're watching these old black and white like document,
a little documentary clips on YouTube, and one of them at the end has a phone number
for the Angeline fan club and we called it and it was still the same scratchy like Angeline
fan club voicemail.
Wow.
And it's probably like the guy who like runs the stuff for her or whatever, but.
Right.
So isn't there a whole thing?
I've heard if people like try to go down the Angeline rabbit hole that it becomes like
she's trying to like shake you down.
She sells you one of her paintings or shirts are like $50.
Like the pictures $50.
I've seen her on the street a bunch of times.
You guys probably have to.
I've never like gone up to her because I never have cash.
You have to have that cash.
Yeah, that's because that one.
Yeah.
That's a strong one.
Did it.
And then, yeah, she just tries to just all the souvenir shop.
Yeah.
And then there's like videos of people doing it and they just like she just takes him and
makes him buy her groceries most of the time.
Wow.
Interesting.
Chief, the dream of buying Angeline's.
If you had gotten a hold of Johnny Stewart, he may have had you buy him groceries too.
I don't know.
Possibly.
Well, you know, the dream isn't over.
We can all land on what can be done with this easy way to contact Johnny Stewart.
I love.
Here's what I love.
Because he would have to be 80 years old, right?
Around there.
Maybe.
He has to have money.
He's not ever had a divorce.
True.
He lives on a ranch.
There's been some lawsuits.
Okay.
There's been a few lawsuits, but he still has like a lot of shows.
And he sold legends in 2005.
He sold the show after doing it for 25 years.
So he probably got a big, big pay off.
You would hope.
I think so.
Yeah.
I'm saying what I think is crazy is he is so still trying to like prove to someone that
he's like that he'll go through all the missed calls on the answering machine and call you.
But how, what, what time was it?
I don't remember that later.
Was it like 11?
I don't remember when the calls came in.
Let me see if it.
I'm just saying there's a drive there at 80 years old.
Night is eight o'clock.
Okay.
There's a drive.
Business hours.
That is impressive to me.
Yeah.
At that age.
Maybe I'm a producer calling to finance something.
Yeah.
That spark is still going off in his brain.
Like this is my shot.
Maybe he thinks like he wants Banjo Johnny to appear to perform finally or something.
So I.
Yeah.
But this is not, I feel like the ins...
It's not an insecurity that it's like tribute acts, a real band.
This is a real act that it doesn't seem like there's much of that.
Oh, like insecure.
No, no, no.
I think he, I think he thinks he achieved his dream of like opening rock and roll heaven.
Yeah.
I think he thinks he's as good as the original acts.
And he pushes them to get there.
You know, but wait, just before I move on from that thought, when I mentioned him,
that rock and roll heaven is the premise, he also says in this interview that literally
when the show started, there was more of that, of the overlay of, he said that actually when
it started, I played our heavenly father.
I was the voice of God and, and Adam and Eve came out.
And then, so it was, it was like Elvis and Marilyn, but literally it was heaven.
In heaven.
And I guess that the Adam and Eve stuff just sat there.
So now it's just like, it's just magic and there's living people in it now too.
Did Adam like play the banjo or anything?
It was a dance.
I think it was an interpretive of a dance and it may, maybe it represented.
I mean, if you're going to do Adam and Eve, you maybe want to do like, you know, the,
the dawn of sin.
It's taking a bite and then, you know, and then lightning crashes and, uh,
Oh, it's snake.
Someone's maybe in a,
Yes.
You've got a snake.
I was part of a high school play that was like the Noah to the like Genesis tale that of course
had like the, oh, the snake, you know, the snake song was very sexy in the play, in the high school
play.
It was a perfect number for the girl and like the, like, you know, the, like the Brittany,
mid drift kind of like, like, Hey, Mr. Adam, I've got something for you.
I remember this place.
So I would love to do an entire podcast about the musical, the original musical Noah that was only
at my high school.
Wow.
There's a, it's a really, it was, it was a masterpiece.
Having to get permission from the principal.
It's like, okay, we want her to wear spaghetti straps.
Now don't freak out.
They had to negotiate.
The Dean had to keep coming out with like, can we get something like a, just a centimeter long?
I only want a centimeter.
That's all I want.
That seemed to be the thing.
The, the disciplinarians at my high school were obsessed with like, you can't wear baseball caps
inside and you've got to cover that spaghetti strap.
Like that was a discussion at our school as well.
Yeah.
I remember a lot of measuring of the girls skirts, which like, you know, so just the thing in high
school where high school girls are wearing skirts and then grow like 50 year old men or walk out.
Okay.
I better get very near your skirts here just for disciplinary purposes.
That's all.
Nothing weird about me going in.
It's my job to get very close to your skirt.
I think we had the female teachers that would have to assess that at our school.
Now maybe I'm throwing some people under the bus, but I feel like I remember like
old bald, mustachioed man.
Let me get in there.
If somebody wants that tape measure on his belt.
If somebody like Batman, somebody wants a list of perv teachers from my high school.
I'll give it to them.
Oh yeah.
So we've heard.
Yes.
Yeah.
Baker's field is ramp with them too.
No, not Bakersfield too.
Could you imagine?
But this, this whole thing, Jason, what you were saying about like,
it's that it's not just this, it's not in person.
I mean, this is clearly so much of the drive and you saw these clips in the documentary,
which is what I like to play here that he, he demonstrates how much he pushes an Elvis to be
not just a rote filling out the form Elvis because there's Elvis and then there's Elvis.
Right.
And these are two quick clips back to back.
This is the interview where he's in the tassel jacket and the rattlesnake hat
and it's early on in the doc.
This is really great.
I can go on that stage right now and I can do Elvis Presley and I can do him and there
won't be any problem.
Spray my hair black and go out there and shave my mustache and I know I can do Elvis Presley
and get the crowd going.
I know I could do it right tonight.
I'm positive I can do it.
What?
Jump up and do Elvis Presley?
Show me some Elvis.
Well, just like that would be hard for me to do.
Then there's a little bit of, you can tell he's going in his head.
He kind of just like fills time with pattern, but then he's going like,
I got challenged though.
I got challenged and I got to prove that I could have been like Brian Wilson and
Steve Martin banjo, Steve.
I could have been my glove.
I could have been me out there.
Could have been me in 2023 still hustling through.
But then it comes to he's like, all right, I got to do it.
I got to prove it.
Now's my shot.
There's a camera in front of me.
They don't do a situation where a person can stand up.
Can I stand up?
Okay.
Or a person can stand up and they're going to say, they can go, you know,
you ain't nothing but a hound dog, you know, and just do it, you know,
or they can get into a situation where you go,
you ain't nothing but a hound dog all the time.
They can get into it, not not like I mean that like doesn't sound like
Elvis.
Yeah, it's just just louder.
He just demonstrated at the end of the documentary.
There's a whole sequence.
The documentary ends with like a guy doing Sammy Davis Jr.
Oh yeah on the stage and like about how you could see him just sitting there
like he's watching him for a long time and then about halfway through the song,
Johnny Stewart jumps in on another mic and just start singing the same song
louder.
Yeah, more like more gaudy like over top of him to like show him or something.
So yeah, and occasionally there'll be a note just like, you know, from here,
stand up straight like ostensibly.
It's like, oh no, I'm teaching you.
It's not me proven that I could do it better.
Just singing over you.
I'm only not Sammy because of the color of my skin.
I absolutely know I'm a teacher.
I'm teaching you.
I could have been him.
Yeah, I have.
I have just a taste of that.
Hang on.
Yeah, yeah, go for it.
Oh, it's just Sammy Sammy impersonator.
I don't give a damn.
And then maybe then I'll know what kind of.
Blowing out the mic.
Yeah, apologies.
Listener.
And he sings longer than the same.
Yeah, he makes it longer.
You know, that's annoying to if I don't this is one to the I am.
I am in a documentary right now.
This is my moment.
How many seconds can I top this Sammy?
It's so incredible.
The whole thing is a lot like the whatever happens in the British office
that pushes David Brent to do that dance that goes on uncomfortably too long.
And no one's he's not having fun anymore and no one's having fun watching him.
And it's just very uncomfortable for everybody.
It's all a lot.
When he can I stand?
Can I stand?
OK, let me stand.
It's yeah, boy, this guy's this guy's something.
In the clip with Sammy, he's got like a crisp white dress shirt and a mullet.
But then in the interview segment, he's dressed like.
I feel like I'm just picturing the poster, but I think he wears in the movie, too.
He's dressed like John Voight in Midnight Cowboy.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Like a tassel.
Jacket and a cowboy hat.
And yeah, it's a it's a very much is that the name of the show Dance Moms,
the reality show or like a pageant, whatever, whatever.
What did Honey Boo Boo come from?
What reality show?
Oh, Toddlers and Tiaras.
OK, yeah, like so much about like the mom in the audience.
It's this is mine.
This is my shot.
Yeah, actually, what I'm doing everything.
Yes, really, it's all the moms on stage astral projected into the little bodies.
Yes, I created her and I'm showing her how to dance.
And if she wins, I win, actually.
He's the he's the creator.
He's the father.
It's on his website.
All the impersonators are him.
Every impersonator is both Elvis or whoever and him, Johnny Stewart.
It's I mean, you can only imagine the day to day of being one of these people under his his tutelage.
Is also very timely.
There is essentially discussion of a labor dispute in this documentary.
Basically, the performers, they're like they come to him and they're like, we want our names on the on the marquee, not just Marilyn and Elvis.
We're the performers and he tells them, you know, who created you, I created you and then but also like there's a scene where he's just talking to the whole cast and telling them to remember how good it is to get a paycheck every week and that and basically the main Elvis in the main Maryland,
Jonathan Von Brana and and Susan Griffith, the Maryland who's actually she's the Maryland and pulp fiction.
She's the Maryland and Big Mama's House Three.
She's been in Nip Tuck, Sible Splitsville.
She's the Maryland and in that episode of Curve, I can't remember which one it is, but there's like a Maryland and one or somehow she's a decade on career of.
She actually like has a pretty good career off it anyway, so her and Jonathan Von Brana, they they ask for more money or something and he dumps them and he so they're out of the show and the Judy is very sad and well, they were the originals, but they're gone.
So the new Elvis he brings in like so basically John Stewart, Johnny Stewart has a at some point a Liberace in his show and then he immediately starts doing the Candel Opera behind the Candel Opera thing on this.
His next, what it is he buys him a nose job. He gets him new teeth, it's fatty tissue removed from his face and like when the new Elvis is breaking it down, he's like you know he put these ideas in my head about my face and I already had him.
I had him years ago and I'm just totally down. He fixed my teeth. It did my nose and like that guy's still an Elvis impersonator. They all are still bettering it at some level at it.
He brings in another one immediately and starts reshaping his face and just like in the same era in 80s with Las Vegas plastic surgeons like imagine what's going on in there now.
I know. Oh my God and the whole sequence with the Jonathan Von Brana fan club in the middle is like you talk about like it's a waiting for government vibe.
That fan club thing is like fucking crazy like every year, two times a year, his Elvis fans have just a party for him where they line up and give him gifts.
Each one gives him a gift. He opens it. He looks at them and he kisses them and it's like all these like in a big banquet hall in a very like shows up to this a lodge kind of place two hours late and then when he comes to hours late, they say it there because they're all pissed.
They're paying him and they're like he's two hours and seventeen minutes late. They're paying him to be at a birthday party. They're all give him gifts, not a birthday party, just a hat. We love you.
Jonathan party right and then one of the women is just like after seeing Jonathan live with my husband, my husband got on the Navy and we got a divorce and in order to fill that void, I switch the focus to Jonathan and the fan club and like, oh my God, sing tribute songs to him.
They sing Angel Baby. It's like the obsession he's like David Lynch in that moment of like cutting between the woman singing Angel Baby and then his his stare, his like fake caring face that he's somehow too big for like, yeah, okay, I'll let this woman sing passionately to me.
I guess I'm going to be late and I'm going to be out of here as soon as I can. You can see where they get the idea that like, no, I want my name on the thing because two times a year, fifty people show up and hand him gifts and cry and like talk about their divorced husband to him.
These people get his name. Yeah, he's not Elvis to them. He's Jonathan Von Brana and he's still around. I think he made it to Hawaii and it gets his rap. Now he's ended up in a big Elvis in Hawaii.
I'm yeah, like there's so much to talk about just with Banjo Johnny, but the phenomenon of this in general of seeing tribute performers and seeing people dressed up as movie stars, I find strange.
Yes, extremely.
Like like I, you know, I'll go see a Beatles cover band or something, but we've talked about that. I talked about this before. It's too. It's always weird. And like the last time I did it, I mentioned like John was doing imagine in the Beatles band.
You're like, well, he was out of the Beatles by then and he's like, there was a man who knew and he's talking about himself in the third person. If we had a little more love, maybe this man would still be like, this is and it's not.
It's not fun in a lot of ways because everyone feels like they're in like embodying the spirit of the performers. Like I'd almost rather just see a band play Beatles songs that are not being the Beatles.
And I feel that way about it. I'd rather see a band play a bunch of Prince songs that was just a good band versus Purple Rain or whatever, which I've seen.
Like my Rudolph's band is really great, but there's no, there's nobody dressing it. You don't need. You can do all the prints. It's probably better to like what you're really focused on is like, got to put my mustache on my eyeliner and then you're not like doing the songs good.
And the guy when we saw Purple Rain at Planet Hollywood, like six or seven years ago, the guy just seemed annoyed that like the audience wasn't very good and sort of bored. And like they sounded great. But like.
You've seen a Prince impersonator.
That wasn't the legend. Purple Rain. Purple Rain. Yeah. Who still like plays. Spelled Arnie. Yeah. Plays in and around Vegas.
To their credit. Doug Jones, who was hanging out in Vegas with us, said that the Carpenter's tribute that he went to nearly moved him to tears. He loved the Carpenter's tribute.
I would see that. Yeah. I think they're going to be, they might be here. I'm not saying I wouldn't see it. It's just some of the phenomenon of pretending to be the people.
Well, yes, it certainly well, as this documentary illustrates, it definitely sends some people into some odd places. Yeah.
When you take somebody who's maybe like had a lack of success or opportunities and the natural, you know, the oddity that comes from that and the weird feelings that come from that.
And then you fuse that with like, now I will fix all of my feelings onto my slight resemblance to one of the biggest legendary stars that ever was.
And you put all this together and creates an odd little, little cauldron in the human body. There's a lot going on.
I think, I think they kind of, it kind of gets like thrown off in the documentary, but I think old Johnny Stewart might have it be a little more.
I don't want to say predatory, but that's too much, but like he's sniping these people because the Judy Garland, she says that, oh yeah, basically he met her outside of her a meeting and when she started, she's she'd only been sober for like two months and he just came up to her and was like you're Judy Garland.
You look like Judy Garland and like he's just hanging outside a meetings. I would say predatory is fine.
Now we're expecting a call from this.
He's too busy to go back.
Paywall helps us.
That Carpenter's Tribute Act, I believe on their website or their Instagram described themselves as like the only Carpenter's tribute performance ever on Legends of Concert.
Oh, you don't say. There you go. Well, it seems like Legends is like a thing that you do and then you like try to piece it off into it.
Actually, that seems like fairly common actually made like as if there's something strange about this enterprise that you might ever want to leave.
Yeah, how could that be?
If the Purple Rain guy started in Legends, maybe and then he started very possibly.
I just wanted to bring this up to you, Mike.
So this is the guy now we've been talking about the past of it like the current Legends lineup that is on the website is vast.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
There are so many stars.
The performers you could see.
I don't know if you would.
It seems like there's like no more than seven in any show.
This is the Prince Mike.
It's Tony Torres.
I see him.
But I also clip these things.
It says interested in planning your own special event or customized entertainment for.
Here's the thing.
Take the guesswork out of whether Prince will show up to your birthday party.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, good point.
Okay.
All right.
Yes, let's not leave it as a chance anymore.
I had a big milestone coming up next year.
Think about it, buddy.
I'd like to not say out loud, but maybe.
You're going to have to start saying it is the tagline of the show.
Milestone coming up.
Tony Torres also coming to SoCal.
Wow.
I thought about a repeat theme for this next year for my birthday.
So that's a good idea.
You bring up a good idea.
That's a good idea.
I.
What have we not made it to?
Oh, okay.
Well, let's talk.
Okay.
Wait a couple of quick things still in the documentary.
The other, the Maryland who it seems like it made it out a little bit.
And it's kept a career going and it seems like it was the right move.
Yeah.
What a crazy this coming to a head of like, all right, well then hit the.
I'm just happy these people had some other career.
Yeah.
But I was just going to say, do you think we could audition for one of the stars?
I had that question of like, who, if sincerely, is there anybody who you think that you could?
Yeah.
Who would you think?
Because I know mine and ironically, it's something that I don't care for, but I think
I think completely I could be an impersonator of Billy Joe Armstrong.
You do the hair you do that.
I mean, there's people have mentioned my resemblance to him.
This is I guess I can see it.
I find the right pictures.
I see it.
Yeah.
And I, and the whole thing, like, who you impersonate.
With a black shirt.
It's I think it's the challenge in thinking of who are new performers who can fit into this.
Oh yeah.
Because, and it's tougher with men, I think especially is that you need costume.
You need, you know, wig, you need a Kutra monst to do it.
But I think you're right.
You put me in punk wardrobe.
You put me in, and suddenly I seem as authentic of a real low down, dirty punk as Billy Joe
Armstrong is.
Now the voice, I don't know, but that almost doesn't seem as long as I can pump my fits
to get the punk revolution started.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Yeah.
You guys ready for a perfect song from a perfect album?
It's hard.
I know you're talking about American India, but actually that could be one of four albums.
I know.
No, no, no, sure.
I'm sure.
Yeah.
I was gonna say how many perfect albums.
It's just, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Um, you guys, who would you, is there anybody you think you could successfully?
Well, uh, I guess I gotta get a little more familiar with his go-to songs, but if I wait
a few years, Cliffy Stone, who has the rights to Cliffy Stone?
Oh, I really like this one.
A cowboy hat and a long pipe coming out of his mouth.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Wow.
Do you think a little, I was going to say like, he's up there maybe with little Jimmy
Dickens as a recent discovery now.
I think immediately, I immediately like Cliffy.
Um, I was told a couple of years, this isn't a newer man.
I was told I look like Burton Cummings from the Guess Who.
Let's see.
And so I could, I don't know if everyone agrees, but I feel like, I mean, I would wear that suit
for sure.
You could, I guess.
That's a cool looking suit.
Oh, I see this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Burton Cummings.
So if they need a, a guess who, if they need an American woman or behind, uh, what's,
what's the other song?
These eyes.
Yeah.
So, and he's got a lot of songs.
So yeah, if they, if I don't know how in demand he is as a tribute before as a character in
a tribute show, but yeah, perhaps him.
But I mean, we could also just do green day, the three of us, because there are three core
members.
So I didn't think I could be like, I'll be Mike Dern and Jason's tray.
Cool.
I can't believe that like I'm here on this episode when green day came, comes up.
You know what I mean?
I was just like, because I'm with the honest I'm what's got.
Yeah, I was hoping.
I don't know.
Mike, maybe go, let's go.
Maybe what other kind of punk bands do you like?
Because you've talked about punk music.
Are you into any like, I don't know, golden age kind of hardcore music from 1977 to like
1986?
Not saying that's a little more pop, maybe from the nineties.
I don't know.
I'm like, do I like Fugazi?
Are you Mike still?
Mike's got a big feud going still with the DC scene.
You know?
Yeah, yeah, too hard for them.
Still warring with minor threat.
You know?
Yeah, I have this weirdly that you came too close to one of my things.
I mentioned it to Scott, but like a while back in the rockinist moments of theme park
history.
Oh yeah.
You guys brought up this story about it was like little Stevie and Bruce, right?
Going to Disneyland.
Yeah.
And like there was some kind of.
They weren't allowed in because of how they were dressed is the story that.
Well, pertaining to punk rock, I have another story very similar.
Oh, if I may.
Yeah, please.
Yeah.
Okay.
This is Ian McKay of the teen idols at this time.
Minor threat, Fugazi, the evens, the discord records, whatever.
Yeah.
Okay, so we all got tickets to Disneyland.
He's with Henry Rollins and other members of teen idols.
We all got tickets to the evening, took a bus there.
How long does it take two hours?
They dropped us off, walked a mile up the parking lot.
We got to the gate and the guy in a suit walked out and says good afternoon, fellas.
Thanks for coming to Disneyland.
We're like, yeah, sure.
He's like, no, thank you very much.
He put his arms out in a while like he was collecting us.
He says, have a nice day.
We're like, no, we're just coming in.
He says, I'm sorry.
You're not welcome here today.
It still hadn't done on us that he was rejecting us.
It was like, wait a minute.
We can't come in.
He said, yeah, why not?
He said, I'm sorry.
We don't allow people with ripped t-shirts.
Well, we'll go buy a Mickey Mouse t-shirt.
Sorry, we don't allow dyed hair.
He's like, do you have any women in there with great dyed gray hair?
What are you talking about?
It's a very good company.
He points to Henry Rollins, Mohawk, and we say he's a Marine.
They tried everything.
He said, I'm very sorry.
You just don't meet the dress code.
Can I see the dress code?
I am the dress code.
Oh my God, just like that, huh?
He says he talks into his walkie talkie and these guys come out in little carts
with guns.
They marched us all the way back to the street and gun point.
Yeah, and then an armored car pulled up and a side door opens with a cop
sitting there pointing a rifle at them.
What he spread his legs, grabbed himself and then called them
a slur.
What we're like, damn, this is terrible.
So they got back on the bus and went back to downtown L.A.
Wow, wow, geez.
So this is a true I guess we left this one out.
I never heard this story, but this is off.
Potentially the rock is sneaking in things that we left behind.
Absolutely.
They encounter that without even getting in the gate.
That's nuts.
That's how much they had so hard they went just in their appearance,
but you still didn't answer what like what are the punk bands?
Well, I don't even Green Day have really transcended punk really for in a lot of
ways, so I don't even think rock and roll.
That's like a relation IV or like I mean, I've heard some of that stuff and I like
all that stuff.
But you know, when you really, you know, you start from one place and then you
really just blow it wide open as far as genres concerned.
I think that's kind of more what's closer to the thing.
You know, they started out punk, but like why stay here when we could do theater?
Yeah, of course.
So like the cramps version of Shorten and Bread.
What you heard this?
I have not heard the cramps do the old ones.
The cramps.
Yeah, the now Jason finally likes punk rock when he hears short and brass,
Nick, a classic song like that being interpreted.
Really?
How long you gonna make us listen to this, Jason?
Look, they get to it.
They skip ahead a little or.
Do you like this, Jason?
I do like this.
I like the cramps.
Sure.
The germs with the germs.
Yeah, those guys are good.
Very good.
Yeah, I like to rock.
Look, I like to rock, but I also like to soar with Green Day.
Oh, so and address the issues.
Times.
Yeah, you know, and the, you know, the mess, the wars that we get into and the messes,
these politicians when the character St. Jimmy has his important revelation in American Idiot,
I think that that's kind of more powerful than anything like just a regular song could happen.
It could tackle.
OK, let's let's make sure we stick.
Well, you know, you know what?
Why don't you?
Here's here's maybe something to Mike.
You talk about people taking these impersonation roles a little bit too seriously.
And I think there's one guy who is not in the documentary.
This comes later.
But there's one guy who I'm like, you know what?
He is having fun with it.
He does not seem like just a, you know, looking too much into the spirituality side of things.
And that is a guy named Chris Van Dahl.
And he is Legends official Steven Tyler.
And here's a little taste of him.
He actually he was part of a show like an impersonator episode of Regis and Kelly
before the passing of Regis.
And here's a taste of Chris Van Dahl.
He sounds like David Lee Roth, though, doesn't he?
He has that like David Lee Roth kind of way he speaks like that.
Like he doesn't sound like Steven Tyler to me.
Well, look, we're not all experts like you, Mike.
I don't know.
As far as I'm concerned, as far as the as far as the tourists are concerned, I think he's
right on the money.
Ed, you just had a picture of him.
I was seeing he looks right.
He looks really good.
I think he looks right.
There's to honestly though, I found two photos of him and the real Steven Tyler,
and in both cases I went to him first.
In both cases, I was like there's Steven.
No wait, there's he like maybe is a little more Steven and even he put up like a picture
of him and Steven Tyler on his Instagram, and he's like rest up.
Get well soon, brother, like when he went back in the rehab, like he's been going through
for 30 years, but when it happens to him, it basically happens to me.
I carry that.
I got to send my physical.
I got to do the steps myself.
I have to get sober just to put that energy out back into the world to him.
How does this sound like Steven Tyler to you, Mike?
Is this pretty close?
That's good.
Well, I don't know.
It's gonna be a little bit.
But like, okay, that's better.
Yeah, that's better.
Okay, so I could do that too.
I could be a student.
Andrew, do you like the song jaded by Aerosmith?
No, I'm not a fan of Aerosmith.
Listen, like when I was like, I made a point to not be like, you know, taste is subjective
and I can't yuck people's yum.
And especially with music, I live a lot of weird far out shit that people don't like.
Yeah, so like now I'm in a better place with it.
You know, I'm not going to make fun of you for liking Green Day or Aerosmith.
You know, sugar raise cover of Abra Kadabra is something that is pretty good.
I did remember, like in high school one time, one of the bands I was in, we went over to
record at this guy's house who we knew from school, and he had like a little garage studio
set up and he had all these like Weezer posters up and we like laid into him for it.
And that was before they got bad.
No, I mean, that's just for Weezer.
We were just, you know, we were little assholes about stuff like that back then, but not now.
I wouldn't make fun of you for liking Weezer.
Sure.
You wouldn't?
Are you sure?
Of course not.
I mean, just feel free.
You're our guest.
And if you if it struck you to do so, I mean, you know, I just have you.
Have you thought about getting tickets to their new to their tour?
You think this is for the new Weezer tour?
I actually pretty good.
I was talking to Doug Jones about this.
They're doing like I just threw out the love of my dreams and stuff.
Some good like Pinkerton B sides and stuff.
Long time sunshine.
I think this is an arena tour, you know, they're not doing Billy Jean.
I got to Billy Jean.
I don't know if Billy Jean's on the revolutionary cover of Billie Jean.
I don't think so.
They probably do in Africa, though, because that was actually a hit.
Africa.
They're stuck with it.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's their song now.
As far as people are concerned.
I just made a connection, by the way, talking about Steven Tyler and the Steven Tyler impersonator.
There was there would have been a short time where Aerosmith is doing a residency at the Dolby
Live at the Park MGM and a few blocks down Las Vegas Boulevard at the Tropicana
you could see that Steven Tyler impersonator.
Like they could run into each other at the CVS in theory.
They could run into each other.
Steven Tyler goes to the CVS.
Only one of them may actually have to do it himself.
I think that's the only difference.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's possible.
You're right.
The Steven Tyler's could meet at the CVS and Prince could have gone to Mike's birthday party.
Assuming the rock stars are just walking down crowded streets by themselves.
Yeah.
Then yeah, these things are possible.
I'm glad we all believe in that.
Bloxers, you know, they seem sometimes they seem like bigger dividers than they are.
You know, it could only take a few minutes.
There's a long sense to do so high.
They seem like bigger dividers than they are.
You know, sometimes Bloxers.
Mickey Mouse, yeah.
You asked for it.
Hey, meet me in front of the New York, New York Statue of Liberty and we'll take a picture.
People are going to know which is which and they're not going to know if we're in front
of the real statue, man.
It's a blow in minds.
It's rock and roll, baby.
It's equidistant from our venues.
We can stop in the Shake Shack right next door.
I want this to keep going.
What else they talk about?
What else they do making plans together?
Do you want to go to Hawkinson?
I got on the list for the Hawkinson nightclub at MGM Grand.
Is that one equidistant or is that one a little closer to me?
Yeah.
I need to think about these things.
I don't want you to have broken up those famous feet, man.
The longitude and latitude.
I need a little treat.
I'm going to the Hershey's store.
He's sounding a lot like Jason right now.
Jason.
Jason could do Steven Tyler, maybe.
I think that's what we're learning.
Oh, OK.
Actually, you'd be surprised.
Pretty close.
Just get enough scarves on him.
OK.
What else in this world?
I mean, in terms of the show itself, do we find any other interesting characters or like,
if you see that show, they have this?
You're going to find a lot of Gaga's.
It's going to be like Gaga's for sure.
Britney.
For sure, Britney's.
Let's stay on you, Mike.
The spotlight's on you.
There is a Buffett.
Yeah.
Barry Cunningham, who is also a Neil Diamond and sometimes a Neil Young.
There he is.
Barry Cunningham.
I watched a minute of Barry Cunningham.
Yeah.
And I have to say, this is the closest an impersonator has ever come to the real thing
in my eyes.
This is exactly the same as the same wardrobe on him and the girls.
It is the same like Jif of a cheeseburger rotating around on the screen,
display the same looping beach footage.
The voices it's because Jimmy, especially singing live, like he kind of shouts thing
like it seems like it would be the easiest one to imitate of all of these performers.
I was thinking the same thing.
And like that whole the cottage industry created around the Parrothead people is that
they all have a steel drum band that plays.
Yes, they're all chop rock, all of them are chop rock people.
So it's like it fits so well into his thing the same way like Grateful Dead bands,
like bands that just play the Grateful Dead.
Like I've seen quite a few of a Cuban sis and like Owsley's Owls and like all these
like it goes into the kind of the culture of it.
So like that stuff is a pretty one to one.
Like I think Barry Cunningham is probably cleaning up doing.
Yeah, well, especially because he's got genuine members of the coral reefer band.
As part of his show, he's got Roger Bartlett and Fingers Taylor.
You tell me he got fingers Taylor.
You got fingers.
Yeah, he got when you hear that guitar, you hear those fingers.
Those are from those are fingers fingers.
I fired fingers.
That's the board nation.
Anybody in the coral reefer band, they could go just like that.
They pass off to me and I pull the strap, cut the strings.
He ain't he ain't using catch it.
The right catch up when he's eating dinner.
So he's gone.
I cut the strings.
Did you say he's working with an impersonator now?
That son of a bitch still making money off of me.
I got Roger Bartlett refused to get his face refashioned in mine.
He refused to get his hair shaved to be mostly bald like me and Frank.
Like me, my best friend Frank.
I've been trying to get my backup singers to get plastic surgery to look like parrot women
and to get a beacon installed on my ladies will get their noses reshaped into beaks.
I say it makes you more beautiful.
Everybody thinks bird is beautiful.
Everybody thinks one is beautiful and putting together a beauty.
I got a mad doctor on an island who will do it.
Yeah, they won't.
They won't take me up on it.
I can't go fix it.
So you lay eggs too.
Yeah, no one wants to meet on the road.
No one wants to meet Dr. Muro.
Yeah, Jimmy, you know, he has had a couple of health issues in the last few years, so
he may just have to hire Barry.
Is Barry Cunningham praying for him on his Instagram?
Barry, oddly quiet about Jimmy's health issues.
Barry, how much do you do?
Are you only playing him because you look like him and you'll switch to Neil Diamond
at the drop of a hat?
How in how in are you?
Disgusting.
In your adventures in Parrot Dice, your show.
Is it Parrot Dice?
Parrot Dice.
Nice.
That's the funniest thing.
Great name and a great idea for a product for Jimmy.
Dice with parrots on them.
Yeah.
Oh, I rolled a six.
Squawk, squawk, squawk.
Here it is, parrot, hey.
Or like how to describe like one of their salads.
It's parrot dice, tomatoes.
Oh, that is good.
Yeah.
We also got, Andrew, I know you went down the rabbit hole of an important area that
they've long represented in this show and that is the Blues Brothers.
We love our Blues Brothers impersonators.
We love them in the original Groove Blender.
We love them anywhere because, you know, you're talking impersonations.
You know, you're the ones that you see all the time.
You're you're Michael Jackson's, you're Whitney's, you're Freddie Mercury's.
Big deal.
Dime a dozen.
Anybody can, you know, get up there and put a mustache on and.
But to be two out of shape guys hopping around asymmetrically to hop on one leg and shake
your hands with the other in a raw way and to go like, you know, like I will always love you.
We've been watching this song for anybody.
We could all do it after the show's over.
But to go like dip, dip, dip, dip.
Yeah.
This is otherworldly talent.
And it's just, you know, being that we've lost John, we lost brother John, we lost John.
So I'm so that people that people are keeping the franchise alive is so important.
So this is a different though tribute band than the official Dan Aykroyd
owned Blues Brothers tribute band.
You might know this.
You know, the man of the lineage.
I think it seems different.
What's the legal breakdown?
I think you're right because when you guys had talked about it before,
I think it was that like Belushi like licenses or does something.
There's an official.
Yeah, there is because they have Blues Brothers con that was in Illinois.
And we talked about that, I think last year.
Yeah.
And on the website, it's he does the Blues Brothers revival.
Right.
So this is an unofficial Blues Brothers.
Parade and our parody.
Well, look, it's before they set up the rules, you know, before they put up these,
before the Belushi estate put up these limits and laws.
So, so yeah, they, I'm not sure if these people have been personally
selected and supervised by Judith Belushi.
Judith and Danny.
Yeah, I don't know.
But if you're looking for that, I don't think they have.
So I think there's you're going to you're not going to get that authenticity.
You will because we've also noticed that Dan and Jim will still go on the road as the
Blues Brothers, but they will also officially send out their tribute act.
So you have to make sure when you're looking at whatever casino they're playing,
you have to make sure it's Jim and Danny versus just a tribute.
Now, maybe you don't care about seeing that.
You just want to see this great songs.
The great songs.
So, but so there are many blues brothers, soul man, all the great blues brothers.
Sweet home Chicago.
The great blues brothers songs.
Yeah, right.
To hear a two note harmonica solo, you know.
Yeah.
So, so I think, yeah, I think this is not official and.
So are you banning it from being discussed further?
Yeah, I'm a little upset actually, the more I talk about it.
This is an oddly.
Money out of Dan Danny's mouth.
It means less vodka crowd seed money for everybody.
Right.
In terms of impersonation, they're doing like two levels because they were impersonating
the characters, but also the actors doing the characters.
No, exactly.
That's why that's exactly why it's it's harder.
The moonwalk.
That's a magic trick.
You spend enough time watching tutorials.
You'll figure that out.
You figure it out at the end of the day.
When he leans really hard, that's just he's got a thing.
He's got a little peg that comes up.
It's got a peg on his shoe.
We all know that.
We've seen it bring the diagram.
Yeah, you can just buy that, but the blues.
You can't buy the ability to run at each other and chest bump half a foot off the ground.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's why.
That's why you need the official John and Danny magic.
Do I think John and Dan, are there any Jim and Danny, are these,
we think there's a date on the schedule or they think like, are they still going to play?
I would love to.
I, I.
What are you asking?
I'm saying is there like, if I look right now in the future, in the next few months,
do you think Danny and Jim are going on the road as the Blues Brothers?
I don't know the answer to this.
Well, Jim's got a weed business now and a TV show about that weed business.
That might be.
Have any of you tried to watch that show?
I've seen bits and pieces.
Is it?
Yeah, it's not interesting.
I find that a piece of media starring Jim Belushi.
I'll never believe it.
Hmm.
Someone very nicely offered to send me some once and I'm like, please don't mail marijuana
across eight lines for the sake of a podcast bed.
I do not want you to get in trouble, friend.
You guys got to see this, this particular, this is the Blues Brothers revival performing at a,
uh, a Christmas event in 2016.
And if Blues Brothers weren't good enough, then what if you add a children's choir and what if
you add them singing, I think about candy.
Oh my God, Jason could be in this.
It's mostly kids with the Blues Brothers are clapping on the side of them.
I think some of the audience is up and doing the twist like a candy cane.
Only some of the audiences is, uh, returning with their nachos.
The kids are all wearing white and red.
So then it just, with the Blues Brothers on the side, it looks like there's just two
undertakers dancing.
What are on stage dancing with a children's choir?
Gotta be prepared if any kids drop dead.
Don't know if I haven't been scanned for heart conditions.
The Blues Brothers on the website says the Blues Brothers with the sacred hearts,
which is Jim Belushi's band.
My God.
But then when you go down, it does, there's no dates on the schedule for this act.
But so, so it's, it's listed as a possibility.
Guys, you don't have forever.
I mean, look, those guys are in great health.
I think they're probably going to make it another 50 years,
but even then clocks ticking.
Look, you know, Jim Belushi, of course, remember what his name is.
His Blues Brothers name.
Do you remember Zee Blues?
And it's an evening.
Cause he's a different character than John's character.
He is different than John Goodman's character.
Mighty Mac.
That one I know.
There's more media to support it.
The film.
This is very much.
This is like the boomer version of the, um, death cab and postal service splitting the bill.
You've got the Blue Brothers.
Entire me.
I was sort of, you got to double Chris, Chris Gaines growth Brooks concert.
Very excited to see people.
I go to that Hollywood Bowl show and see people I haven't seen in years.
It's like, Oh, you're here too.
What do you think about Jason's love of his music that he listened to for one year in college,
death cab for QD,
It is clear.
And new pornographers.
Jason's time is definitely like 2004, 2005.
I mean, you say you like the Pixies and stuff like that.
No, no, but I'm asking these three.
Those three.
I'm fine with that.
Fine with them.
Doesn't sound like an endorsement.
Listen, I'm not, like I said, I'm not going to make fun of it.
Pixies, Pixies had a lot more albums.
So I was able to stretch them out more.
I saw the first reunion tour, but there's only one postal service album and some live records.
Yeah, there's only the one.
You can only play that so many times.
Like at the time I was very popular.
Are you thinking like that they might be controversial to say you like those bands,
that those bands are better than Aerosmith and Green Day.
Do you think that's going to be like people will spit as they listen to the podcast?
They might spit about it.
The incredibly controversial take of, oh, yeah, these bands meant a lot to me.
My freshman year of college.
Yeah, of course.
That's not at all a time when things imprint on your gray matter.
Are you more of an Owl City guy as far as like you think they kind of approved on
the postal service stuff?
I don't know.
I mean, like I feel like.
Like I don't know, like just like listen to craft work or something.
If you want like some cool, so I have Tronica or something.
Yeah, that's always going to be what I'm going to say.
That's a good point.
Is this the just sorry I'm so mired in the is this is a different or is this the same
one?
My pitch for you guys is that you've got a perfect.
You three have the perfect Blues Brothers Two Thousand Act.
Yeah, I'm the kid.
You're the kid.
Yeah, no offense, but like you.
No, no look.
Come on.
Yeah, the Heights, too.
Like, yeah, the tall one, Acro or Acro.
You're Acro.
Okay.
I'm Belushi.
We need our own names then, which would be really hard.
And then you need to hire a Johnny Lang impersonator.
The blues thing.
Remember when Johnny Lang was going to be the future of the Blues?
You know, that is the white guy.
It's like, yeah, vaguely.
Yes.
The great white hope for the Blues.
Well, I think we could get these little soul patches going.
And I think, yeah, we could do it.
I mean, still a moment in the podcast that blew me back, blew me out of my chair was when
you two were discussing, are we going to be, could we be a trivia Blues Brothers?
And Mike questioned which was which.
Well, the only reason.
Mean, obviously, height wise, yes, there's a specific.
The one thing that matters.
Yeah, visual.
The only thing that matters.
Well, but you can do a lot with Apple boxes.
You're paying black.
Okay.
You're going to dance in Apple boxes that you taped to your legs.
Well, you need to make a no, you make a robe Apple boxes.
I'm ready to be up on a.
This is like a muppet stage.
I need a riser.
Okay.
I need a personal rise to get you all the way up.
So now it's a Blues Brothers act with where the short Belushi is what?
Six foot.
But yeah, I want to rise and Mike's on a whole like, yeah, and up on boxes.
Our rider involves a very complicated riser and a very complicated on stage.
Did I'm a soul man.
It does sound more interesting than the typical.
I think literally the kid wears converse in the movie.
That's part of his like that he wears the suit and the hat, but he has chucks on.
Wow.
Yeah.
Well, you know, I mean, it'll be very exciting when Mike and I immediately hurt ourselves
trying to get in a ditch and Mount a riser, but that adds to the show.
You start the show with you guys attempting a chest bump, but it doesn't work great because
you're up on blocks.
So you fall back.
You fall off the stage entirely from now on, from a combined height of 12 feet.
Yeah, it's a Kelsey grabber.
Who does it?
I would love the blues brothers concert that starts with ladies and gentlemen,
first talk.
I got my leg.
I don't want to know.
I got a rosero.
But I'm a dead.
Shit.
The three second.
But we all have to laugh about what I said is saying I'm a soul man.
I say I'm the gash man.
Because I have a huge talking about I have a gas.
I've got a huge gas on my leg, just like Kelsey.
When I do when you did that, when I did the ball, you guys know you were making like
the oh, no, no, you gotta earn that.
No, I talk about it.
Now that's punk.
I'm talking about our rific leg gas that sent him to an arch county emergency room.
The most aggressively sexual thing is you never make said, unfortunately, that's your
freedom.
It's a banner with Jason.
Gash me.
Placents plate.
I'm sorry.
I remember the specifics of Kelsey Grammer's traumatic injury.
You had a gas.
I don't remember.
I guess I remember.
I remember that he cut his leg falling off the stage.
Not so in my head.
I think I've always heard the cut was very bad.
Like it was like, oh, yes, I wouldn't laugh to this injury, but it's like, yeah, it sucked.
I'm a gas.
I need gas gas gas.
I'm going into shock as I'm singing that.
So the flop sweat and the paleness.
Yeah.
So it's actually pretty impressive that I managed to make it topical in that moment.
Did you know that's actually an Aerosmith song too?
That's I'm a gas.
They don't do that one as much anymore.
It's an old one.
Yeah.
The original version was ash on an escalator.
They cleaned it.
They cleaned it up a little bit.
Well, you can get really fucked up on escalator too.
Yeah.
There was a gas waiting.
That's potential.
Yeah, that's true.
OK, there's one other in the end, just as we're doing a grab bag here.
This one really spoke to me, Andrew, when you sent the email, just getting the vibe
and getting the magic.
You know, most of these acts do their separate acts, right?
Now here's now here's Michael Jackson.
Now here's Donna Summer, whatever.
But they don't they maybe doesn't.
I actually I don't know.
I've never seen a show.
Maybe at the end they all do something together.
But what you'd like to see is the cross pollination of living.
And what does Lady Gaga sound like with Steven Tyler?
But you get it in this a clip that you sent from their YouTube channel.
This show also used to happen on the Atlantic City Boardwalk.
Hey.
Which experienced a rough time with Hurricane Sandy.
And they entertain all the great entertainers knew they had to lend in helping and and lift
spirits again.
So we ended up with this song that came out in the wake of Hurricane Sandy.
And this is being performed by Elvis, Steven Tyler, Michael Jackson, Donna Summer, Lady Gaga,
maybe blues.
But I don't recognize half of them, to be honest.
But it's more about the message and what they're singing.
Yeah.
Reason for the victims of Sandy is where he will be.
Back on the boardwalk.
It wasn't destroyed.
He can still be enjoyed.
Back on the boardwalk.
It wasn't destroyed.
He can still be enjoyed.
Very good.
OK, so some context for that.
One, Atlantic City certainly had some flooding.
And yeah, there was some slight damage to the boardwalk.
I'm glad they're fundraising for victims.
That's very noble.
The Atlantic City Boardwalk held up pretty well.
And I think the reason.
That's what they're saying.
It wasn't destroyed.
And they're like, come back to the boardwalk, which that picture appears to show fall or
winter.
And the casinos certainly stay open and the boardwalk is open to an extent.
But it's like, I feel like they haven't come back because it's November.
Jason, I'm going to toss something out.
And here's just a thought exercise.
What if?
What if they didn't care if the boardwalk was saved or about the victims?
What if they just wanted people to come see Legends in Concert live?
And they saw all their favorites together.
Yeah, that's true.
They thought they were like these.
Perhaps they are fundraising for themselves.
It's as good as if they were alive.
When they're all together, that's, I think, my favorite.
There's tons of pictures on the website where they're all on stage at the end, I think,
waving goodbye.
And it's just so many impersonate.
That's where you got rock and roll heaven.
To see current one that we've got.
Justin Timberlake, however the hell you do that.
It's like a Fedora.
Does that do it?
I don't know.
But then other ones that are a little more clear cut, like a Rod Stewart or the big crazy wig.
That's funny.
I think the Rod Stewart's are my favorite.
I didn't watch any.
There's been Rod Stewart's in every pamphlet they've ever made.
People's hunger to see someone else be Rod Stewart inexplicable to me.
But I love, I'll look at photos of fake Rod Stewart's all day.
Like Kevin Spacey's brother.
In another interview, Johnny Stewart tells a story of getting a call from a high up
producer at a casino to go audition somebody on the spot that day.
And he's like, it's a big producer, so I go do it.
I call him back right away.
And he shows up to this hotel pool and he's like, OK, here's the Rod Stewart.
And he's like, hey, can I just sing for you here?
And he's like, well, if you come back to the theater, blah, blah, blah.
And then the people start laughing around him.
And it's like, it's the real Rod Stewart.
They had just brought him out to goof on him.
And like play like he was.
And then he tells this other story that like so Kenny Rogers was also he knew
because also he's in Pigeon Forge.
There's all this Pigeon Forge stuff with Johnny Stewart, too.
He like runs.
He runs a show at a theater in Pigeon Forge with Ricky Nelson's twin sons now.
The one the fame and Nelson, the band.
Yeah.
But then also he knew like Kenny Rogers and Dolly Parton from there, too.
But like Kenny Rogers wanted to come in and do his show as an impersonator,
but he's Kenny Rogers, right?
So like and then he also Jay Leno is tied into this because I apparently when Jay
would do Las Vegas, he would have the legends come out as like his closer.
Really?
What that's what he says in the interview.
And then also so like Jay Leno was like, if you do, he tells Kenny Rogers,
if you do like fake you, they're not going to like you as much as the real fake you,
which ended up being true because he like practice with them all week and
John Johnny Stewart didn't tell them until the very end that it was the real Kenny Rogers.
And like everybody was pissed off and started like being like, oh yeah, I'm the real
Marilyn Monroe, too.
I'm glad you finally said it.
And like Kenny Rogers got offended and walked off and almost didn't do the show.
And like it was his whole thing.
So like he's he's having real celebrities do fakes.
It's like a lot of levers.
That's really strange.
Wow.
I'm trying to get anything to get to before you wrap it up.
I figured out what we have.
Okay.
I figured out for Jason, we call Johnny Stewart and we say we have an idea death cab for QT
tribute.
Jason plays a Ben Gibbard.
You're Gibbard.
Oh, yeah.
That he looks like a little Gibbard.
Yeah.
So it's all about hair.
I think you do the right hair.
Oh, you know what?
Yep.
I see this.
Okay.
So we get a death cab postal service.
We'll have to find a Jenny Lewis.
Okay.
So now we so we're putting together we have his numbers.
So now we could put together an official new legends.
And what does our legends have?
We got Ben Gibbard.
We got Burton Cummings from the guest who we have a Billy Joe Armstrong who hates Billy
Joe Armstrong.
And then at the end, we all do quick wardrobe changes and come back as the Blues Brothers
from the movie with the kid.
Yeah.
Unless you want unless it has to be the originals, in which case, I don't know, I guess one of
us could get up on a bunch of risers and hope that we don't fall and get a big gash.
Our songs are about gashes separately from that.
And then the parody of Scatman John's I'm a Scatman called I'm a Gash man.
And then that's what Jason does is you should bring up the Scatman.
I have this is our biggest departure.
And you are saying that I'm really on board with the Steely Dan and hating on Green Day.
But I have a clip now in the world of impersonators.
You know, there's clips that people love to impersonate and check this out.
This is a Japanese game show and you'll see someone impersonating.
Oh, my God.
Scatman John.
Let's take a look.
He's got the outfit on to.
That is amazing.
Wow.
Now, just wait.
It gets better.
Oh, horse.
I'm Scatman.
Is it the real?
Wait a second.
Who's coming out?
Everyone is in rapture.
Oh, my God.
This looks like it was shot in 1985.
This is the loudest audience ever recorded.
I would have lost my mind.
Is he lip syncing?
Sounds like he's lip syncing to the track.
Well, he's nervous.
He's worried he's not going to top fake Scatman.
Yeah, he's lip syncing.
That's right.
The real Scatman John comes out.
Holy shit.
Scott, does it help you at all to know that the origin story of the Scatman John song
is because he stuttered as a child and that he uses scatting to get over stuttering
and he wants other children to not have a problem with that?
I honestly, it is kind of nice.
It's nice to hear.
He seems like a nice man.
I don't have a stutter, but I'll get caught on words here and there.
And it's something you don't feel the best about sometimes.
You stammer.
If I could weaponize stammering somehow, then I could make a hit song off of that.
So you know what?
I do like that.
I do like weaponizing your quote unquote flaw.
Scatman's world is a utopia that was just like he wanted us to live in.
Scatland.
He wanted us to live in Scatland.
Scatman's world.
I'm calling out from Scatland.
I'm calling out from Scatman's world.
You're right.
Yeah, that is what they say.
And then also when I was Googling Scatman, I just, you know, you like Google
and it's like one of the popular questions.
What was Scatman John's last words?
Was it?
We follow up.
Were they scattered?
Apparently his last message, whatever God wants is fine by me.
I've had the very best life.
I have tasted beauty.
Scatman John's last public words before his death.
And then it's then it's like he and then he woke up a little bit right before he died.
He said, I'm a cash man.
Oh, we're in there.
He had to like a surprise appearance on the variety show.
He had to get one in there.
The dirty joke.
I can't think.
I don't know where to go from Scatman John's last word.
Well, you know, actually here, while we're staying to stay a little bit like
a heavenly mortality and also a little bit dirty, I think we all we know that
Johnny Stewart sold the franchise, but he's still around.
He's calling me.
He's looking for his next opportunity and people are maybe worried.
People are worried about what happens to this guy.
But you know what?
You don't have to worry because he's not worried and neither is Ninon,
the person he's talking to in the functional bar.
Bar.
So I'm really living for the life here after more than this life.
So you're not afraid to die.
I'm not at all afraid to die.
So you and I have something in common because I'm not afraid to die.
In fact, I'm quite interested in what's what's going to go on up there.
And I can't wait.
But it's getting so bad since you're not afraid to die and I'm not afraid to die.
It wouldn't be bad for us to plan to kill each other.
Didn't happen.
Make a little mixture up.
We would just do mouth to mouth and not let either one of us go.
I'm quite like that.
I like that idea.
But not many.
That was said in the same room as his wife since he was 19.
Oh, my God.
So he's not afraid to die.
And until he and Ninon fulfill their mutual destruction and lock lips
until they run out of air, I think we can expect a lot of great more shows
from Johnny Stewart to come.
He wants to kiss another woman.
That's the only way he can even vocalize it.
It was me as Elvis.
It wasn't Johnny.
I get into it as a you're a better dog.
And then I plant them plant one on you and I suck all the life out of you.
For some you wanted it because you weren't afraid to die.
So I figured let's just take care of it together.
And I sucked your soul in.
That's what happens.
If you ask me, I suck your soul in and I kill you.
And if you say you want your name on the marquee, I snip your strings.
When I get behind the wheel of an automobile, I always whisper, I'm not afraid to die.
And then I turn the key and get on the road.
Oh, my God.
This is what we're going to do.
We're going to film a video of you doing the death cab for cutie song.
I will follow you into the dark, which is about dying.
And then we'll send it to Johnny and see if he thinks it's good enough for a tribute show.
You know the song I'm talking about, right?
Yeah, I know it's something.
Okay.
Wow.
Well, I guess we have our mission.
We know what to go to him with.
Andrew, you're a musical person.
Maybe you could help put it together.
Sure, I'm available.
Yeah, put some beats together for Jason's show.
We'll all put a demo together.
But for now, I think, Andrew Cothe, you survived podcast The Ride.
Sin City Nights.
Oh, my God.
What a thing you brought to us.
Thank you.
Saying something, one of the craziest guys, and we would not been on our radar
and in my voicemail without you.
I can't believe he called you back.
Thank you.
It was a thrill hearing the voicemail and then getting one back.
Oh, my God.
Two.
You got two.
Yeah, thank you so much for having me.
I really appreciate it.
And you guys are great and keep doing your thing.
My favorite podcast.
I'll be honest.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you for supporting.
And hey, let's exit through the gift shop.
Anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, follow my Twitch channel,
Twitch.tv slash Andrew Cothe.
I DJ one or two times a week.
I DJ all vinyl records, all genres, jazz, funk, hip hop, drum and bass, all kinds of stuff.
Check out my work with Bugman.
We haven't touched on a little bit.
And funny enough, like I saw a comment recently on one of your posts.
It's just like, I still don't you never explained what Bugman is on the show.
You mentioned I was going to ask you this exactly.
Yeah, it seems like a good opportunity maybe to keep the vague.
Listen to the music of Bugman.
I have produced many, many of the songs on our four albums.
We have four albums out now.
We've done a lot of shows.
Scott, you've been to three shows.
Yeah, there was a time, I think I said on the show, where I've been to four concerts
since COVID and three of them were Bugman.
Yeah, you were at the first one even.
You were at BugCon 2021.
Was that the first show you ever did?
That's the first show we did.
Wow, geez.
Well, it's something.
Must be seen.
We also have you to thank for the Space Las Vegas.
You guys did a show there.
Oh, yeah, that was great.
Nice presented by Sabato Mobile and you helped get us to that venue, which was wonderful.
Shout out to Emily Boss Bitch.
She was the one who set that up with the space and we had a great time with them and with her.
And you guys crushed it.
I watched the live stream.
Oh, thanks for saying that.
It was the first episode back after the groove.
Yeah, we haven't recorded since the Las Vegas trip.
Yeah, we're all bleary, still recovering.
But yeah, I don't know.
I think we successfully blended some groove.
I think so.
I think we did.
Check out Bug.
Did you do BJs?
Are you part of BJs?
I mean, I like mix and master all of them.
I didn't make the B for BJs, but I love BJs.
BJs are really good ones.
Yeah, it's a strong one.
Anyone you want to shout out in particular?
Is there like what's been happening lately?
Oh, man, just always working on songs.
I'm always in the group chat with him and Van and they're constantly sending things
all the hours of the night and we're always like sending songs back and forth to each other,
trying to work on like a live DVD.
We have like a lot of our shows shot.
So we're trying to edit something together and do some different stuff.
Yeah, but to understand the Bug main, listen to the Bug mains music.
Listen to the beats I've worked on with Bugman.
You know, and then go to the show because if you're looking for themed immersive
entertainment with a mind expanding visual content courtesy of Pest Guest Van Robich show.
Yeah, Van is a master.
Van does our live visuals and he really he kills it.
Yeah, no revelatory.
Well, I hope we hope to get some dates on the books.
Get that calendar a little more loaded than the current Blues Brothers calendar.
I'm concerned.
Get out there.
Get us some guys.
We want to see you again.
Otherwise, we got to get Jason up on some risers.
Yeah, and that's going to be scary.
That's a one way ticket to Gash.
Yeah, and I'm losing some blood.
Trust me.
The Gash man.
Jason's got to go to Gash City.
Yeah, I don't mind if I do.
I tell you, I'm going to Gash City later.
Dennis Miller is talking about a last little thing.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I contacted the Bono for legends.
Oh, Pavelle, Sephora, Mike.
I asked a question on your behalf.
I said Pavelle.
If I may ask, have you ever appeared as Mr McPhisto?
Oh, good morning to you, Sir.
I have not appeared as Mr McPhisto.
I keep my and he wrote parents.
I think he meant he's just misspelling.
I keep my characters as to the updated version of Bono himself.
No characters.
Thank you, Pavelle.
Dist.
Dist by Pavelle.
So no McPhisto.
No Mirabell Man.
No Fly.
He hasn't played him in a while, I guess.
Or on tour he hasn't because he played him, of course,
in the Jimmy Kimmel episode.
But maybe he didn't even see it.
What a good of course.
So we're all thinking about it.
We all remember it.
The people who were here for the episode about it definitely remember when he was on
the Jimmy Kimmel.
Well, you got to be Mike Phisto then.
It's on you.