Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain middle-aged ghosts, tedious boat lines, askew elevators, and a themed hotel that started with an intricate story that had to be experienced throughout three attractions in sequential order, but now is just a place where people do e-sports and carrot top does prop comedy.
It's the Luxor on Podcast the Ride, Sin City Nights.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, Sin City Nights, the sleazy desert cousin of Podcast the Ride, much like Snoopy's cousin Spike. I'm Scott Gertner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
That's right, we're like Spike. We grew those long mustache danglies.
Yeah, those very concerted, we all grew eight hairs, eight thick hairs out of our face, that's all we can do, Mike Carlson.
I'm here and I've also grown those long mustache danglies, says Jason, it's not just a long mustache, they're mustache danglies, in case you don't know.
It's a desert term, is what it is. Yeah. You'd know if you were sleezing around in the desert, says we have been.
Well that's what Spike is, he's a desert guy. You know? Yes. Yeah. That's what I said, but yes. Yeah.
I'm agreeing with you. Now this I was checking the levels, so to be fair, I wasn't zoned out, I had things to do.
I came in with show energy. I had things to do, I'm sorry.
For sure, no, your ability to focus for the most part, given that you're riding the levels, is admirable.
Listen, I'm going to dive right in with something that is not Vegas related, and I don't want it to take over the episode, and I fear that it may open Pandora's box.
All right. But I feel like I got to say it because it is part of the series, even though it's not Vegas related.
And it is this, if you can imagine, I've been doing some further thinking about Space Mountain fans.
This came up in the MGM Grand episode two weeks ago. There was a little discussion of disagreement.
You might say a loss on my part, that was how I chalked it up in the episode.
The notion came up of whether Space Mountain speed is partially simulated due to the fans, due to fans that are potentially blown on you, that blow cold air as if to simulate space travel or something that a faster roller coaster might do.
Right. This was something that Jason brought up. I balked at this notion.
Mike went a Googling and you discovered enough results that made me feel in that moment as if perhaps though I balked, it seemed like, well, that's enough people who have maybe brought up the idea that the speed of Space Mountain is simulated with cold air fans.
I didn't like taking the loss. It didn't feel good to me. I kept thinking about it.
It seems like you didn't stop there.
No, no. If you can imagine, it seems like the best thing to do in the moment was just to admit defeat.
But I've realized that the best thing to do for the podcast in general is to rip this thread wide open again.
Hey, in Vegas, you got to double down, you know.
Yeah, I wonder if I already did. I think this might be a triple down on my part.
I'm reopening this again. And here's why.
I felt a little pummeled by the amount of source. This is what you were indicating where you were sitting. Mike was like, I don't know. There's a lot of things that are bringing this up.
I started feeling like, well, if there's a number of them and not just one weird source, then maybe I should admit defeat here.
But as I'm thinking about it, I'm like, what are these sources exactly? And I went looking. I looked in a couple of places.
Theme Park Center. Yeah, we all know theme park. We're all hanging out on theme park.
That one on the episode, I said one that one out as like a do we know that?
And we're like, maybe we don't. I'm looking at we've never been to theme park center.
We've never been to the travel dot com. We've never been to an expired Tumblr called Disneyland secrets.
And then the main source and this was obviously flagged when it came up was that this this fact was touted by inside the magic.
I don't know if they're the most trustworthy. If their headline is ladies still swooning over Johnny Depp's perfect abs, you can, you know, audiences demand Johnny Depp's rippling abs back in the Pirates franchise.
You can trust them on that. Anything depth related. I'll give that to them. That's their beat.
They were on a terror about woke Cinderella this week. Woke live action Cinderella. Right.
And the right one that happened already. No, it's going to Rachel Zeigler Academy Award winner Rachel Zeigler.
Are you sure that Disney didn't already remake Cinderella? I'm sorry. Snow White Snow White. I get them always. I get them mixed up.
Oh, my God. Yeah. All right. Well, yeah. So they you know, they have their things that yeah, they're they're experts on woke culture.
But are they experts on Space Mountain fans? I don't know. I looked at their article. This is how much I want to.
I'm really sorry that I clicked and came close to giving them any ad revenue or anything, but I did give them a page click.
And it's one of those in classic Inside the Magic fashion. It's like Disneyland is a park that has entertainment over the like let's let's do 19 paragraphs where we say every key phrase in theme park world and
By petal humans enjoy amusement and vacationing.
It names. It's like you have to get through the entire existence of man. They go through the Book of Genesis.
They Jesus is discussed for a while. And then before and then finally they bury what you're actually there for.
And they say, well, a fan figured out that actually fans are used to simulate the speed of and then it's just it's a tick tock.
It's something called the mouse lits and they say, did you know that fans are used to simulate cold air on the all right for more facts.
Check out the mouse lits on and I just started thinking, where is the good source on this? Yeah.
Where is and I'm this isn't about me saying Jason's wrong. I actually would like to take that out of it in this.
I'm just trying to figure out what's what I'm trying to take fake news out of the equation because I think we're dealing with a lot of fake news here.
And in what I've just said of where this is discussed, what haven't I said I founded on Jim Hill, Lentesta Expedition theme park, Martin's vids.
None of these sources that we usually go to that we usually tout say anything about Space Mountain simulating with cold fan.
Now there's also some Reddit threads about it. Right.
And I'll give it that. But but I don't know if you can trust a TIL today.
I learned as a definitive source on this issue and I'm not saying there isn't a definitive source out there.
This is just this is why I bring it up. I want to know I want a source that we can trust to verify that fans are used on Space Mountain to simulate that it doesn't actually because I'm just not I don't see the proof.
I'm not buying it right now. Truthfully, I had already forgotten about this and I thought you were talking about Space Mountain like enthusiasts and I was like, oh God, what discourse did I miss this in between the like, you know, Haunted Mansion going like I'm going to run to the rallies next door for a burger to calm down.
You know, like the product placement, the aggressive product place, the the recent Internet trend where I wake up every day and learn a new of like bizarre thing about the Haunted Mansion movie.
Yeah, no, it's been it's been a pummeling lately. A lot of strange decisions. Yeah, apparently I haven't seen it. But apparently it's like, let me get out a pad and paper that I got at CVS.
Really weird. No, no, no, you moved on, Jason. You moved a lot. You took your victory and you moved on and I stayed in the weeds. I said, wait a minute, wait a minute. And I've been I've been connecting yarn on pins ever since Charlie Day meme or yes, I am a living Charlie Day meme right now.
Right.
But what do you now that now that I've brought all this up emotionally, Jason, are you like, go ahead, do your thing or do you feel confident in this fact? Still, do you think I'm the crazy one? Do you think it's possible that I will be disproven again? Or I don't know.
How are you feeling that I bring? No, I'm happy to see. I mean, I, I, you know, when I brought it up, it was mostly going off of like memory and, you know, going through the lights on once or twice on both coasts, you know, and like, I swear I saw a fan and like, it's very cold on my face going through here.
It seems far too cold for it to be 35 miles per hour. It's a cold room. I'll give you that. I say what we said the previous time this came up. I don't doubt that it's possible that there are fans in that building.
But that to me is different than fans with the explicit purpose of blowing on you. The writer, like if you think about the physics of it, Aaron brought this up back. She was like, if you stuck your if you were driving 35 miles an hour and you stuck your head out the window, you would be getting a general wind flow there.
Right? Yeah. Yeah. Imagine what would have to get added to that to register to even like enhance the effect. You know, that would have to be they would have to be like head on fans in that instance. Correct. Which seems harder to do in my mind because where would you put the fan?
There's that one need to be in the car with it. Just be super powerful air conditioners. I mean, making it colder traditional fan for you. You know, I think you have to count a big air conditioning unit and a fan that's a traditional.
Well, again, I that's a good point. I do think that I mean, if I think there is air conditioning in the building, that's not what you pointed. If it's like an air conditioning unit pointed at you on like a turn.
Turn that one because I don't know what is one going to do? The facts is implied by inside the magic and the mouse. Let's and my beef is with them, not with you, Jason. At this point, this being presented definitively as if this is a crucial part of the space.
Can we contact the mouse lits and find out who are they? I would love that. That's a viable way. First of all, who are the mouse lits? Where? Secondly, where are you getting your information from?
Are they just tick tock only? First of all, I'm going to become a mouse lits fan regardless of what the answer to these questions are, because do you have a tick tock account? Do I? I do. But I'm not. I'm not post or anything.
Just for lurking. I yes, I lurk on a lot of places. Yeah. Reddit. Oh, I know. Yeah, that's part of my thing. I lurk. Yeah. So Pleasure Island Facebook group. Pleasure Island Facebook group. I love the pleasure Island Facebook group. Yeah. So I think okay. If it's air conditioning units, you would consider though that Jason was still correct. I'm not saying that's not even a discussion of would it matter? It's not. I to me. Here's where I'm drawing the line. If there are air conditioning units, I'm not saying that's not even a discussion of would it matter.
Here's where I'm drawing the line. If there are air conditioning units in the building, that's not enough. Not enough. I agree here from a source that's quoting an Imagineer or somebody involved in the ride that there were especially large amount of air conditioning units put into Space Mountain.
Good looking. And your
that gets the speed. So I'm willing to say I'm wrong.
Yeah, sure. Well, which is again why I'd like to divide it. I think
I think the beef is not here. I think my beef is with these
sources that are quoting nothing because I like here you are maybe
bending what you think is happening in there and that's great. These places
that have published this thought with zero evidence.
Yeah, that's why I think what I I'm sure I'm trying to take these guys down.
I'm trying to take theme theme park center. You're in my crosshairs already gone
Tumblr Disneyland secrets. You're in my career. That's why they're gone
because they're publishing. I think so. News. I mean also in
addition to this, I because there are reddit there's a number of reddit threads
saying this is possible. But in the comments of those reddit threads you also have people
saying I don't know how this myth got started. And I've also
I also and I don't know if you could trust this but somebody said my professor
was an Imagineer who worked on the original design for this exact ride at Disneyland. He confirmed
that there were no such fans along the track. I don't
know. You can't trust that maybe as much as or you could more than you could trust
anybody on reddit. But isn't this I'm just
interesting. I think it's interesting. That's more why I bring it up than any particular
thing. However, I will acknowledge this that this does
go back to you said something I scoffed. I
seem to have been proven wrong in the moment and I might be proven wrong again. So though I don't
want to keep it personal Jason. Here's what I'm going to offer. If anyone
and this is where the listeners come in. I say contact who you got to contact.
Let's start digging things up. I'll save you the work of watching
the behind the attraction episode that Disney put out because I did
and there is no mention of the fans. But if we I think I think this is very possibly a job
for Jim and Lynn. If anybody feels like. Yeah yeah yeah.
There was ever a job. This is a big one. I think but if I am proven
definitively wrong in a way that we can all agree on. Here's
what I will offer you Jason. Oh my gosh. On three occasions
in theme parks or generally themed environments or just anywhere out in the world.
If we are near a place where a treat can be
purchased or achieved. I will not only purchase you this treat.
I will offer up the humiliation factor of if you
to know that you are in the mood for a treat. I will allow you to say
oh treat boy and then
I will go and buy you and will pay for on three occasions.
I will do this. I want there to be speaks to this. That's how much
I am I'm invested in this thing and would like to figure this out.
Hungry. I will
accept that. That can be part of it. You can't you can say hung we with a W.
So listener and I think it would probably behoove this entire
situation if all three of those were filmed and posted to our social
media. Oh yeah. So that's what I'm
putting out there. I don't want to you know
I'm more invested in this than you are maybe so I don't want to force you to
do anything but I would put out the possibility of if I'm correct
and proven definitively correct. If on one occasion
I am in the mood for wine. Yeah I was going to say do you
want some wine. Monsieur. Monsieur.
I do like that. I mean I was just going to do the same of a wine boy.
Maybe you follow it up with like a wood varietal Monsieur.
I mean I think all
of us are having fun either way. It keeps it in the run of fun if mild
humiliation for somebody. But does everybody sign off on this plan?
Sure. Yeah we have an impartial witness. I think you can help weigh
in on this. If you're feel free to make a ruling of I'm
sorry Scott this does seem like a credible source. But I really
feel like it's got an imagineer has to be involved. There's got to be a book.
It has to be because I think Disney likes to reveal their little secrets.
I think typically some of them yeah. Yeah yeah some they keep mysterious like a
Haunted Mansion thing like what you know which CVS the pen in the pad came from.
Yeah they're sharing a reveal ad in the film. But otherwise I think they
like to own up to this stuff and I think it's suspicious that this has never been.
Well I completely agree with what you're saying. On the Disneyland
Space Mountain there is a large like asteroid or something
that you know what I'm talking about. When we first enter sort of space. Yeah.
And you're slowly waiting to actually hit the fast part of the ride. Yeah. And you
can't really see it. You kind of have to squint to see it. Sure. And I'm just wondering like
does it count if like there's a fan somewhere pointed at
the car up there even. And you're saying it's like
part of space atmosphere. Right.
So it's even before the speed happens. No I think this is about
speed. And even though I think Jason's point of view on this
is adjusting. I accept that to create a spacey
cool atmosphere that there are little like swirls and gusts
of air conditioning. That makes sense to me. But again I'm going to the
letter of the law here with these articles and I'm saying that these I think it has to be involved
in the simulation of the speed. Specifically. Specifically
speed. I think so. Because that's the part that I think is
weird. I think ultimately the ride doesn't go that fast. Right.
But these are big weighty vehicles. And I think you have to have absolute
cannons to have any impact beyond what just gravity
is already doing. And like the tightness of the turns.
I think that's in the darkness as we said. Well I will say this
I will be impartial. On the
hyperspace mountain it is a lot more lit up in there.
So I guess we would have seen. I'm trying to think where the fans
would be. I feel like you would have seen something. Well and not only that
there's a lot of ride through. You know everybody's get. If anybody gets the chance
to ride space mount with the lights on they're turning their camera on. Yeah that's
true. And they're putting it to YouTube. You can watch YouTube's. I don't see where these fans.
I don't even see like big old fans at the top of the building. I'm not seeing fans.
Sometimes I'll see a little something and I'll say could it be. And then I think that's a camera.
I think that's a speaker. But if. But if. This is another way a listener can be helpful. If you
want to go through videos like that. Yeah. In Peru. And don't just photoshop
fans in there. I want to see.
There has to be a way to verify. And if. Don't just take a picture from a Sears catalog.
And just drop it into a frame.
I don't know. I want to see what talents our listeners have.
I would like to see that. I would like to see their photoshop skills. If you do that then you have to say
parody like the rules of Twitter. I'm sorry.
Or XR now. Where if you're going to do a parody account of something
it has to say parentheses parody. And don't bring like a big
office fan on the ride with you and during the photo op hold it up.
That's not funny and it's dangerous. I'd say it's very dangerous.
I mean it's funny. I take it back. Yeah. I was going to say it's very funny. It's funny but it's dangerous and don't do it and then we'll be responsible.
So don't do that either. If it just drops and it doesn't hit you
then you got cars below you. Two employees. A lot of bad things can happen here.
I don't know. So don't do that. I don't want it to become the new Flash Mountain
where people are bringing fans on the actual ride.
I would be impressed if you were able to smuggle one and then like
be in a seat belt. Is it a pull down? What is it on Space Mountain?
Yeah it's a pull down I believe. Oh then how are you even. Boy.
Or is it lap? I can't remember. Oh it's lap. It's pull back on lap.
Oh okay. I've only been on it a hundred times.
Yeah right. It's just been a while. Yeah it has. I oddly have not been on Space Mountain
in a while. And maybe if I went I would plainly see fans right away.
That's possible. And realize the foolishness of my way. I might get kicked down
real fast here but I'm willing to do it because I think it's interesting.
I think it becomes a little hunt that the audience can help with.
You know hey everybody's a winner if Jim or Len get involved.
Let's just see what happens here. Well Len tried to do a big one. I am very willing to be.
I think I was using fans and air conditioning like strong air conditioning
interchangeably. I just like. There's a lot of air flow.
The fans is enough repeated online that I think you probably saw that somewhere.
Probably infected yeah something in my brain. Oh and a listener
said like I've known my mom told me about this when I was growing up. I thought this was common knowledge.
And I hate to be I don't mean to be sounding like your mom was wrong.
But is it possible that this is one of those like urban myth things
that sounds cool. I like the idea of it. Yeah I just don't know if I buy it
in practice. I'm being a skeptic here. Sure. Well we'll find
I think we'll find out quickly. I think so too. And boy and we
will try to you know we'll just make a moment. If
it happens quickly and I'm wrong we'll try to make a moment happen quickly where I am
I become treat boy and I'm forced to fetch a treat for Jason.
We'll knock one of those out in a non-theme park environment. We'll just run to downtown Burbank.
You good with the Ben and Jerry's? Yeah I was going to say yeah plenty of basketball.
He's good with the prices of Ben and Jerry's. That's six thousand my friend.
Yeah. Hey you know maybe I'll put on a little costume too.
We're going to have fun either way.
These are the stakes and I'm sorry that's a bunch of non-vegas but
it's a runner in the series now. We'll find out by the end of the series. No maybe
hit a local. Yummy cupcakes is pretty convenient for most spots in
Burbank. That is the real business. How much is a cupcake? I don't know I haven't
been in a little while. I would assume a few dollars at least.
I feel like there were like four dollars. I feel like there were four dollars
like ten years ago. So I don't know. I feel like
reasonably it has to be a treat for one person to have. I feel
like it cannot be a dozen of something
and then you like put them in the fridge. Well I feel like when I've had
it before you're either buying one or you're buying a box of the four
big ones and you're taking them to something or
splitting. Oh I'm not going to make you buy a box of cupcakes. Like I'm not.
The price of cupcakes nowadays you know. Well thank you for taking
that into consideration. There's a crumble cookie coming.
That's a chain. That's a popular chain. We should probably get to Vegas before we list every
different treat in Burbank. Specifically in localizing.
I haven't called that localizing in a while. Well Randy's donuts by the airport is delicious.
Cookie dough dreams over downtown Burbank. Yeah you know I've had that a couple times.
I don't like it that much. They do strawberries sometimes. No you're right we're done. We're going back
to Vegas. We're going to a different
strange piece of sloped architecture
with rides inside multiple rides inside. We're talking about the Luxor.
The of course the Egyptian
themed hotel and casino.
Which I think has gone a little astray. I think it's lost
a little. Yeah yeah yeah. I mean we'll get into that.
I think as with all this is a great example of
the theme that will come up you know multiple times in this series
of the family friendly Vegas of the 90's where now they've made efforts to make it
just kind of generic and all the stuff you'd usually want
in a casino but in the 90's this was
an indoor theme park. This was like the primary thing
almost was like a new concept in a
themed entertainment center. It was nuts. It was nuts in the 90's. Yeah one of
the most ambitious themed experience of like three
interconnected attractions and a
boat ride that goes around the lobby. Like a boat ride
with pretty bad per hour ridership I believe. Very bad
I believe. Very bad. Yeah. Well this is the experimental nature of it.
There's a lot they were just they were willing to try all of this stuff as
foolish as it might be. Badly priced or as badly
enumerated as it might be. But it's
really notable and worth talking about and a lot of things about it that are like
just big and unprecedented and stupid.
And that's why it deserved an episode here on the main strip. Yeah it is stupid
and I knew a little of it but then like just watching and reading you just like
oh my god. Like they really
gave them like carte blanche to just make up their own mythology
and make up characters and make up technology
and like stuff that doesn't even seem like it would be popular. It seems
like this would be. Yeah. Not because of any
lack of effort on the part. Right. Or imagination. Masters putting this thing together
but it just sounds like maybe we just we know this
in retrospect because we've seen a lot of things like this
where it's not IP and it's an original world and that's cool and to be
commended but it's certainly everything you hear about the story of it and the world of it
you're like that sounds like something that will not do well. Of course. Unfortunately it's
way up our alley. We love it but yeah. For like again like dads especially
90s dads. Yeah. Oh yeah they're going to track like this
pre-Egyptian like society. It's a story
that takes place in past present and future. A perfect pyramid
of tales. Yeah and like it's just so it just seems so like
impenetrable to know what's going on versus just any like generic
Disney thing where it's like pirates are yelling at you. Got it. Great. You are
in a haunted mansion. That is true. You know what and I was going to open
the bigger narrative of why doesn't original
theme park IP work better out in the world. We love
what look what's original pirates and haunted mansion and you answered it right there.
You understand what those are before you're even in the gate. You look at the
sign. I don't think you understand you need a lot of
explanation to figure out what is it all called. It's all called secrets of the Luxor
pyramid. Yeah. And yeah that doesn't tell you much
of any that doesn't tell you you're going to be time traveling and with archaeologists. No and it's
by the way I love this. Yeah I really do. I think there's better
versions of what they conceived of that would have worked much better.
But I do love it as an idea and a concept so I don't want to say I don't want to
put it down but it's not like oh yeah you're going to go get chased by
a mummy or something. Oh it's Egypt. Got it. It's mummies. It's pharaohs
done. You're right. Maybe it should have been a little more basic
Maybe. Maybe. And there's things that are basic. I'm
actually I'm going to propose here backing up a little bit and like entering the building
because there are things about this place that are very impressive and unprecedented
before you even get in there. Yes. You know beyond just the
attractions. So let me step it back to
opening which is October 14th 1993. It's 93
like all of the 93 now it's clear the end of 93 the peak of
the pyramid peak of insane family. Yeah. Las Vegas. Because I think
Treasure Island. Treasure Island. Pirate shows around then. Luxor
and MGM Grand. Luxor only for
like a few days was the tallest building
I think on the strip and then Treasure Island immediately built
beat it. Wow. Oh weird. Oh that's crazy.
It's also I mean first things first it is an actual
pyramid and it's not built in some fake way
that makes it not a pyramid. It's not a simulation of a pyramid. It's a real
pyramid and as such it's one of the tallest
pyramids ever built. It's taller than only two
of the actual Egyptian pyramids. So it's in the top ten pyramids
ever built. It's I forget the amount of like
is there a bigger pyramid. Oh well if you can't you know what's a pyramid is the
Transamerica pyramid in San Francisco
which has some other there's like a more of a traditional building shape. Right.
Caked into it but you know what I mean the San Francisco pointy building. There's an
interactive like chart where you can see how big it is compared to other
stuff. Unfortunately it did not include the Bass Pro Shop
pyramid. No I know. I mean that's the only we have the same
thought we're looking at real history stacked up against the Luxor and we're both like
yeah but what's the where's the pyramid I know. Yeah. The weird one in Memphis.
I guess it's too small. It doesn't rate. Right.
But the Luxor rated. The Luxor is huge. Thirty six stories.
Entire establishment three hundred seventy five million dollars to open.
Built by but no longer owned by
Circus Circus. So I think there's a through line and we aren't
doing an episode about Circus Circus this round but Circus Circus
we're talking about like why does all this happen. The the family vacation
of Vegas and some of it you got a tribute to Mirage I think that that's a big
Disneyland free attraction and that
popped a lot of eyes. But then Circus Circus has got to
get a lot of credit too. Even though that was going since
the 60s right. I mean that and yeah. The guy's name is J
Sarno. I didn't find enough about him to make him like an official guy. Right.
The thing that we did but the he sees his powers too and
it he kind of combined. How do we lure people in well with some
big gaudy theme. And so he kind of
revolutionized Vegas in that way. So I guess it makes sense
that Circus Circus thinks what else can we do. How do we go further
and how do we kind of like Disney Worldify elsewhere
on the strip. So they're responsible then for Excalibur.
Which is like
I mean I remember hearing about Excalibur when I was a kid.
Get me there. I want I love Disneyland.
But I don't get to stay in the castle. Yeah. I get to live
in a castle. Like not knowing the actual vibe. Right.
Excalibur would be if I were to go. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean I still felt that whenever I the first time I went to Vegas was like
2007 and even just seeing Excalibur even in its like decaying
state I was like hell yes. I didn't stay there but it was still
like that kid kid brain of like yeah. Yeah. I want to stay in that
dumb castle. Yeah. Yeah. You also I love looks or
for the existence of it if not in practice. I like
in the same way that I love all these where as
the stuff pops up in the early 90s and I was saying I think some of it's got to come from like
Disney Decade and Eisner era that there's a pyramid
next to a castle. Yeah. And then you're not far
from the pirate ship and the it is like it really starts to feel like
Disney World where you're like here's the here's the Hawaiian one and here's the future one and
here's the Caribbean one. Yeah. I mean I like that stupidity
of Vegas. What makes it feel like a big miniature golf course. Yeah.
Yeah. Just like random landmarks. Yeah. Yeah.
And various monorails and people movers connecting
true each other. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. With an aesthetic that has nothing
to do with the hotels that it's passing by. You're right. That is exactly like Disney
World. This is probably at the root of all of our love of Vegas. It's all like
you know we've all separately like fractured into different things that we
like about Vegas. But like isn't it like it's like a
stupid or trashy or Disney World all like crunched and only
the hotels. 100% Yeah. 100% it is.
Just seeing this dumb nonsense when you're walking down the street is so
important to people with theme park brains. I just
want mini golf courses so right on. I just I want the world to
be like a huge miniature golf course. Yeah. I was looking when I was there
because I stayed one night at the Luxor and I stayed two nights at New York.
I forgot where your first night was. Okay. It was at Luxor because I
didn't know if I was going to be there and then I got a cheaper room. So that was the Luxor.
It seems like that's the thing by the way. It seems like Luxor is a
last minute really cheap room spot. But New York, New York
I was looking at it as I was walking down the street and I kept looking at it going
okay this would be a good basis for a
Marvel area with the height of a New York
skyline like this in a theme park only do what you know that we've talked
about these photos from this never built Marvel thing that was going to be in Dubai.
I think so. Yeah. But I was just looking at it and I was like I was like imagining New York, New
York in a different context as like the hotel itself because it's
if you haven't seen it it's just giant. They're not as tall as the
skyscrapers in New York but they're very tall. Yeah. Like the scope of them is so big
and crazy. And then all like mashed together as like the you know the New
York that never was. Right. And they're all like a little more. It is very
Marvely. You're right. Yeah. So I get like I just add like Dr.
Octopus's tentacles coming out of a window and add like
Spider-Man on the side of one. And I'm like man we're like this is so close
to what I want. Yeah. Which we won't ever get I don't think. No I don't
think Marvel. I don't think Disney is going to license out Marvel to although they should. I mean
look if they're trying to you know crank up some profits
here. It's too. Why not. Yeah. It's going to be too realistic like everything's going
to be realistic. That's the yeah. That's because of the movies.
This kind of dull take. Yeah. Yeah. It's fun. It'll be another ten
years before they learn that one of the most important characters in the Marvel
universe is the city itself. New York
City. Yeah. New York City. Yeah. Yeah. Hopefully they'll realize that.
Hopefully they'll realize it. New York New York and to
some extent Luxor obviously the theming has been pulled back but there's still
a bit of it in Luxor. But I have found those casinos
in terms of just like sitting at a slot machine
and like posting are very fun. New York New York
especially with all the fake city streets and all and the facades
and all. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. New York New York and we'll talk we'll talk more
when we're talking about our trip but New York it is fun and especially it's fun and I wasn't
at this point in this trip but it's fun if you want to
like really get hammered and have a
piece of pizza and go into a piano bar and just be
annoying with a bunch of other annoying people and I mean that in a good way because I saw
that happening every night or both nights. Oh sure.
$25 a head at that piano bar to get in. Is it that much? You're guaranteed a seat
if you pay that. It is small so that's actually maybe not bad. It is very small but you can also just
hang out outside and hear the piano kind of. There was a lady
screaming the lyrics to like piano man because I walked by
and I was like I'm not in the mood for it right now but they're
depending on the trip sometimes you are in the mood to enjoy
something like that. I don't think there's any amount of alcohol that
could get me in the mood to enjoy a dueling piano. What if she was
singing that Beach Boys problem child song.
And it was five o'clock on a Saturday. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I guess
well I would do a double take but you know I'd also be upset that even
a non classic was getting ruined. Okay.
I okay so big thing about this I remember
very clearly when this place opened because we'd
get like in LA we're not far so we're getting local news reports about it.
I'm like oh alright something's happening in Vegas and I for sure remember
like the news or my parents telling me how yes there is
there is a pyramid hotel and there is a light that shoots out
of the top of it and you can see the light from space.
What a stupid thing. I love that it was nice to see it. I don't think
they run it as bright. I think they tone down the brightness. Yeah. Yeah.
At some point it brought down two satellites probably.
Started a war. Yeah. McCarran Airport now a Harry Reid
Airport. Not a fan of the light I believe. Oh sure.
Because you can like I saw that you could see
you could see the light potentially from Los Angeles. At cruising altitude
yeah you can see the light. Let alone you're in the airport
literally next door. I saw the phrase strongest
beam of light in the world and yeah.
So dumb. So pointless. Who went in there because of that?
It's a very good question. Did it ever did it help business? Do they have to do it?
It seems like an aggro move of like our light is the fucking strongest
light on earth. Like we will signal
like did you see Reid that it has its own ecosystem?
Ecosystem? Essentially enough animals. Yes.
Enough animals and species are up there because they're so attracted to the light.
So there's like moths but then there's also bats and I don't know the intricacies of it
but I saw that in multiple sites now I don't know I didn't source it but
it seems like they've set up shop there. Certain animals have set up shop there.
And it's like a you know upside down ecosystem
because it has its own rules where like you think the bats are in there to eat the smaller animals
but actually like the bats and the moths get married.
Yeah yeah yeah. They're monogamous. Right. They treat each other really well.
It's one of the some of the more loving relationships. It's beautiful actually.
And if you saw them make love you would weep. It's also I believe
it was 2012 there was a UFO sighting.
I don't know if you guys are UFO-pilled like I am in the last few months
because there's a lot of UFO stuff and this is totally sincere. There's so much UFO stuff
going on. There's a big hearing like a couple days ago.
A bunch of people on the record like pilots and people in the military just being like
here's the video. Here's how fucking crazy this little
object was behaving. I don't know what it is. And then there's other people
in the government that are saying crazier things like yeah we have had
contact with alien species. They have killed humans. There are
agreements in place between humans and aliens.
So like it really. No I have not tracked down. This stuff is not I don't know why everyone's
not like at least talking about it. I'm not saying this extreme version of
this guy's details. I always catch a little of it and I'm always
interested when it comes up. I do know I saw that the one of the
people testifying about it was really into like other dimensions
and he's like well of course Mussolini and the Vatican
found aliens. Yes that's the Mr. Grush is his last name. Yeah.
He's a government official who people say is credible
but he's the one who's definitely saying the wildest shit about aliens
versus other people who have just. There's like so many pilots who just have
videos from their ship just like of like a little craft just
justifying the laws of physics. Just so many of these videos where people are like
it's scary. It looks scary. We don't know. So there's all this going
on but apparently there was a big sighting in 2012.
We're in the from there. To the beam of light. Yeah yeah. And I haven't found the
video. I should go find the video before and post it if they have it. Did aliens find the light?
Because you could see it from space. That's what I'm wondering because the light was so strong.
Maybe it did attract some of the aliens to the light.
It's ironic because Luxor and the Egyptian like
employee costumes do come into play in the movie Mars Attacks.
Oh right. Yeah right. Oh yeah yeah. So that light
I do believe maybe has attracted alien life.
It's so strong. It's shooting into the universe. You think anybody you think any of them
are up there or is anybody bothered to ask one of the bats are you an alien?
I don't think they have asked probably. And then they just immediately like alright you got me.
They kind of like unzip their body and then they're 10 feet tall.
I crunched all my organs up here just to blend in to simulate one of
your human bats. Anyway I'll tell you my deal. I'm 5000 years old.
Came from Xyral 4. Somebody's got to climb up there and figure it out.
Yeah. It'd be a good place to introduce them to us.
The Blue Man group can communicate to them with sound and
visual things and then you can show them the bodies exhibit
which is like yeah we don't know where these ones came from but this is what humanity is.
This is all it's in us okay. You can trust us. Look
our literal insides. Our heart is on display for you.
You can trust us. We'll show you that titanic exhibit. We'll show you
our folly. We are but flawed creatures.
When we try to build might it blows up in our face don't you see.
That's a heart. They couldn't turn that down is what I'm saying.
No better play and then human and alien can all laugh together
at the universe bonding comedy of Carrot Top.
Oh yeah.
He made a toilet seat do what?
Even we understand the Monica Lewinsky references.
We knew all about that in Xyral 4. It's like an Mars Attacks Alien
and like a human with arms around each other guffawing at the same time.
So you got a big light
that's attracting bats and aliens. I don't know
when this stopped because I specifically when I drive by it
if I'm on there or if you're going to see the sign that's something we haven't
talked about is the famous Vegas sign which every once in a while like
okay I'll do the sign and only then will I pass by like
the front garden of the Luxor which now
kind of sucks. It's specifically like a bad area and often
like they ruin the grandeur of the pyramid
with just like a big poster for their eSports arena.
eSports arena and then the other side is the biggest
Bet MGM logo you've ever seen. I know I pulled into the parking
garage and it's just like this big fuck hole like it looks like shit.
It's pretty bad. This is what they've all the aesthetic of at its worst
a lot of these like dumb it's the fusion of
dumb 90's aesthetics that we like with just modern trash
and they think like the funky blend of it will be
what's interesting. Why a pyramid with an eSports but really it just doesn't
work at all. They've got other problems too. I watched a local Vegas news
report where viewers wrote letters to the news
and asked why is the Luxor so dirty?
Did you find that when you were there? Yes.
Did you feel it from your window? Did you see like gunk caked on?
Or was it just like in pulling up? No just pulling.
I got to the Luxor episode.
I got there. There was the longest line ever. I was going to try to see if I could get like an upgrade
or something. I don't know if it was going to be a $20 trick. Probably not. But the line was
so long so I just checked it on my phone and I was trying
to get to the hotel room and the elevator I was trying to get to
was broken. And I was like oh god. And the hotel, the carpeting
looked extra dirty. There's bad vibes in there. It's just a bad
vibe. Especially when you go up. It's just kind of a bad vibe.
I don't mean to correct you Michael. The inclinator.
I was waiting for a pause to say inclinator as well. I'm going to talk about the inclinator.
The diagonal elevator. I'm so sorry. I am so sorry.
Which I tried to pitch to Jane once. What if we stayed at Luxor
for a night? You know you take an inclinator. It's a diagonal elevator. And she's like
I watched some videos looking from the higher floor. She's like absolutely
not. Here's a reverse pitch. What if we stayed somewhere safe?
Yeah. Well that is funny that you say safe. Oh no.
So I'm trying. I have bags. I have my Comic Con exclusive toys.
Which are going to come up every episode this month. I just unboxed Ernie Reyes Jr.
It's a great toy. He's got his little scooter. Kino from Secret of the Use.
I got everything. I'm just lugging this shit. And I'm just like oh
where's my room? So I'm walking, walking to find a different elevator.
So I get to this other bank of elevators. It's not the right bank.
It's like one through eighteen and then eighteen through whatever. Like you have to find
certain. Okay. Oh it's not the right one. Alright I go to another one. I finally find
an elevator that looks correct. I get in.
I scan because now your phone is your room key. I scan the room key
on the thing, on the whatever, the button pad in the elevator
and the inclinator and it's not working. It doesn't fucking
work. I didn't get a real key card because I skipped the line. So I keep scanning.
Not working. I just want to go to the room and put all this shit down.
I hate the Luxor in this moment. I'm so mad at it. I'm so mad that I didn't spend like
fifty more dollars to stay at a better place. So all of a sudden the elevator
door closes or maybe it was closed already. All of a sudden the elevator
starts, inclinator starts moving. Now it's, I'm like okay
I guess somebody at the top maybe hit the button and is looking for the inclinator.
I don't think this is what happened because there was no one at the top. I
shoot up from first to thirty six or whatever. I forget exactly
what the floor is. It is the rickety-est ride
I've ever had and that includes Tower of Terror simulated rickety.
It's rattling. It's like this. I didn't know that.
And I'm literally, I'm freaked. I'm completely freaked out. I have all
the, like I'm so tired and I'm just like, it's, you can hear
like stuff rattling and I'm going and I'm like when is this going to stop? I'm
expecting it's going to be like Charlie in the great glass elevator. I'm going to shoot out the Luxor.
It's going so fast. You gotta say goodbye to your loved ones
Ernie if I don't get a chance to tell you. I love you.
I give Ernie a kiss. I rip open the box.
Which is ironic. I'll bring this up now since you're talking about
elevators. I took the elevator out to my room at the Park MGM
done floor 27 once, opened on floor 24. Who did I see?
But the Carlson family, Mr. and Mrs. Carlson. Well because you were all
staying at the same hotel. We were all staying at the same hotel and we just high
by. That's a different, yeah those elevators work. That's a cute story. Anyway, back to
your horror show. So it's rattling and I'm just like oh my god.
So I end up at the top floor and it opens. No one's there.
But it's not my floor so I'm not getting out on the chance that
I can get back down again. So then I go
back down. And it's just as bad
and scary. And then it's like I'm so freaked out. You know like when you're in elevator
and it seems like there's an extra like five seconds and sometimes your brain goes
are we stuck? Is that ever happened? Yeah. It feels like
45 seconds in my memory. Oh god. Of the door not opening.
And then I'm like scanning and scanning. It might have been 20 seconds
of a panicked 20 seconds. It feels like 45 seconds.
So like scanning, scanning, scanning. Finally the door opens I think because somebody else
had hit the button. And then somebody else scanned me up to the right
floor finally. I think, I was honestly, it's so
blurry now. I may have just gotten into a different elevator.
But I was just like so freaked in
that moment. And none of the other one, because I went in a couple different ones the rest
of the day or the day and then the next morning. And none of them were that bad.
But that one was crazy. I've never been in a scarier
elevator situation. And here I am imagining
especially Jason like we should stay at the Luxor for the inclinators.
The might of man. The inclinator.
I'm going to die in this inclinator. It was
really awful. I did read, wait I don't remember
where this quote came from. But somewhere printed
the phrase inclinator. An elevator that ascends at a 39 degree angle
and rocks like a ferris wheel carriage. Yeah I guess maybe that
I went into, because it was the set of inclinators
that went to the top. They go fast. So because of the
angle that just is normal. That is so upsetting to the, well between
this and the New York New York roller coaster, this corner of the strip is just
shaky ride alley. Shaky. Luxor also, if you
look up the phrase Luxor cursed or Luxor haunted.
There's a lot of different, like some obviously
people have died. It's a hotel that's been open for a while.
But then some of the deaths are fucking bonkers. There was like a car bomb
that was rigged to like, alright I'm just going to put an upside down
cup in this guy's car and there's an explosive in there so if he turns
the cup over the thing.
Truly crazy deaths have happened. A pipe bomb
and I believe it did kill the intended target. A guy worked at
the Nathan's Hot Dogs in the food court because the
bomber's ex-girlfriend was now seeing him.
And the two bombers were sentenced to life in prison. They avoided
the death penalty. Jesus. Oh my god.
Wow. Well first of all, RIP to a real one. To a
Nathan's Hot Dog employee. To a Nathan's True Blue Young. But also like isn't that the
like you wedge yourself into a relationship. You cause a break
up. It probably does not occur to you that the person might have
a vast knowledge of how to build successful bombs.
Of car bombs. I think someone also may have gotten grievously
injured or died falling down the shafts of one of the
inclinators. No. No. Yeah. And then you go look at the
article. It says here it happened in 2023 and his name was Michael Carlson.
Michael R. Carlson. Ah! And then Mike disappears.
What was that? There was a flash of Luxor Escalate and then Mike
was gone. Wouldn't it be cool though if a ghost was your third host?
Yeah. I mean as long as I showed up. Yeah.
As long as you put in the yeah look I'm not splitting the Patreon money
with an apparition. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cause I understand. Did you guys see
in somebody said this that the rumor
was that the whole place is haunted because it was a place where
mobsters used to kill and bury their enemies? That's what the
property was? Yeah. Yeah. I mean I'm sure that's probably
every place that there was a hotel or there's a hotel now.
Well I also saw that in construction a handful
of workers died but it was like oh estimated
three but it might actually be seven. And like
that's haunting. I saw one video that said it's cursed
because if you build a sphinx to protect a pyramid
you have to build two and they only built one.
So there's so many old fads. There's so many. Like curses
that haven't been awakened in this century. They defied so
many law. They defied so many different laws
essentially. They built on a burial ground.
They didn't do the two sphinxes. Mobster curse, mummy curse.
I don't know if there were any others. I don't know the other types of curses.
Well they probably built two fads. I mean this whole thing was built in 18
months. It's like poltergeist probably. One of these days it's just gonna like
get absorbed into a ball of energy and go to hell or something. Sure.
I don't know why it hasn't happened yet but. That's a good way
because I love my Vegas implosions but how do you top that? Well by the entire
entire Luxor being taken back to hell.
If hell could take back a casino that would be the ultimate
implosion. That's the one it's eyeing. The video I was watching
these couple who do like Vegas videos. They were like oh there's a
middle aged man in like a pinstripe suit that walks the halls.
That's a ghost at the Luxor. And you're supposed to like get out of his
way. Like that's how we just make sure you get out of his way. No problem.
And everything is fine. Good rule of thumb. Yeah. They didn't
Did they film him? Did they get him? They did. They did. I got a release.
You can't. You have to get out of his way but he will sign a release form for YouTube.
He understands how media works. No I get you. Yeah.
I was saying you release. I know. Hey we know an other worldly
Yeah that's true. Pinstripe suit man.
They got a jewel store in here somewhere?
The Luxor for sure is haunted. You can feel it. There's a
weird vibe in there. And all the Vegas hotels have a weird vibe but that
one does feel haunted to me. That doesn't surprise me that it's haunted.
But also I won a hundred dollars playing slots
there a few years ago so who's to say. What slot machine?
I don't. It was a very generic. It was one of the ones where
it's like. Adventures in babysitting. It only plays 80's movie.
I did and we did okay on the Wizard of Oz slot machine
at the Bellagio. Okay. That was pretty fun. Little shop?
Little shop treat you. Hide a little shop story. We'll save it for another episode.
Okay that's a good Patreon tease. It'll be on the trip report. Park MGM
does not feel cursed to me. It doesn't feel haunted. No and that's
Circus Circus Entertainment at some point did own 50%
of the Monte Carlo which is what Park MGM was
before. And if you there's some very there's like
2012 videos of like walking through the Monte Carlo and it
looks busted. Like it's like oh this got redone it
just the right time. They got all the ghosts out of there before.
Some of the best vi. We found ourselves back in there over and over again.
Really good. Okay so Mike didn't die. Mike didn't become
one of the unhappy haunts of the Luxor.
Didn't succumb to the Pharaoh's curse. 99.
If that story kept going.
So then we're getting I know I'm getting afraid and now they see the numbers climbing like to
I'm sorry I'm on floor a thousand and then the roof of the
elevator dissipate just turned it just scattered into
ashes and then I went into a ghostly Pharaoh's mouth.
He screamed your soul is mine forever and I went
into it and then I can't even describe what I saw in there.
Well I met 900 dead mobsters.
The genre I like you know what I like the genre
mash up here of the mobster ghosts plus all the
Egyptian stuff. This is a real Cowboys versus Aliens. Yeah yeah.
It's mobsters versus mummies.
This would have kept it open if this was the sort of basis for all of the rides
and experiences. It's a little bit of a streamlined yes. Yeah. Easy to wrap
your head around. Right. I wonder Scott do you know about
how that got me like that that was
in the mid 2000s they made it as
a comic book first Cowboys versus Aliens.
And it seemed like a thing where they were like practically
giving it away at stores where it's like I don't
how is this making money like and as it came out they were like there's a movie
like it seemed like really shady.
Sure to be hit movie. Sure to be hit movie. Yeah.
So I am wondering like oh are their stories going to come out
if they haven't already come out of like the Ponzi scheme that got
Cowboys versus Aliens made you know. I'd love to know.
Well let's start a Ponzi scheme for mummies versus mobsters.
Yeah. There's gotta be some shady financier
out there. Look we might be talking asylum if we're lucky it's asylum. Yeah
we'll go sub asylum if we have to to get our vision of mummies versus
mobsters which is a bit which is a more of a mobster versus
mummies versus mobsters. Mobster versus mummies I think. Yeah. Okay. All right.
Yeah. I do I know I said I was I was thinking
that we don't have any commercial pilots in our audience and I have yet to be proven wrong.
I think there's pilots in our audience but not commercial pilots. That's what you want.
But is there any are there any shady movie producers in our audience.
I hope so. If so what are you doing.
If you're a fan of this you if you're a fan of this podcast you know
we're chomping at the bit to make the worst movies ever made. Oh my god we would love to.
We could do it all together. We could each have our own bad movie and you could finance
them and hang out with us. Come on. And also with like
mobster like you can get like it's a genre
where you can get like great actors who have
played mafia characters before you can get you can get Al Pacino
living soprano actor. Well that's true. So easily just like
but a modest amount of money. Pacino will do it. Yeah that's true.
Give him the earpiece and just feed him the lines and he doesn't even need to yeah
see a mobster. He's maybe not to spoil it but he's maybe a
mobster who you realize is secretly a mummy. Of course he's a mummy.
Of course he is. A mummy. A mummy this whole time. And nobody
knows. The Tribeca Film Festival is solely
to gain life force for
his mummy spells. The Tribeca Film Festival?
Are you confusing De Niro? Did you say Pacino? Yes. Oh I thought
you were talking about De Niro because I know De Niro has done a lot of
those direct. You said you had to listen to the impression and then still thought it was De Niro.
He can get pretty mad. He can get pretty
mad. I don't know. I don't think De Niro is shouted in a movie in 30 years.
He is not able to shout anymore. He's physically not able to get that
excitable. He's gentle. He's like he's the intern. You know? He helps
everyone out. Pacino makes Pesci and De Niro look like
he's 15 and they're 80
in the Irishman. He has so much more energy than they do. Thank God.
When Pacino loses the ability to scream that'll be like the snuffing out
of the great art of the 20th century.
But I know Pacino is still hanging out with Guy Fieri and
Sly and everybody. He's doing great. He just had a baby.
Oh he's hungry. Oh that's why you got confused. De Niro and Pacino both had babies.
That's right. Proud Papa. Proud Proud Papa.
Was that De Niro or Pacino?
I think a modern De Niro person is just like
doing good. Yeah. Excited to be.
I don't know if that even picked up. People in watching Killers of the Flowers
the Flower. Killers under the Flowers? Killers of the Flower.
Killers of the Flowers? I don't think I'm under. What am I thinking? I think it's under.
I was saying people are going to be watching that in the Paci
and the De Niro scenes. They're just like turn it up.
Can't hear him. You can just hear the volume. Sit closer to the speaker in the
theater. It's the only way. Plement seems like he's screaming in comparison.
Somebody's riding the levels on that. You can hear
the hiss of the white noise in the background. That's the sound of the moon.
No we put it in there on purpose. Okay keep getting through rides.
You have a ride before you. You have a ride that I think initially
you didn't even have to pay for. And the ride, well I don't even know if it had a name
initially. It became the Nile River Adventure.
Okay so confusing history here
where this was, oh first of all with this giant pyramid
space we now have the largest atrium in the world.
Yes. You got to fill that with a lot of stuff. And you have a
kind of marvely little indoor, it's a little bit New York but
mixed with Art Deco, mixed with Egypt.
It's real strand. That's still there. They can't get rid of that. They still have
to like, I don't know, whatever nightclub crap we're doing
has to work under this weird Marvel city. So that's there.
But this boat ride was initially a big
part of it where you would, it was crazy reading the phrase
that you would climb aboard the boat, the reed boat, not far
from the check in desk. Mike you described this difficult
process of finding the right elevator. What they imagined for you
is that you're whisked away on a reed boat. Alright just
follow the boat sir and then you climb aboard a boat and that takes
you all across the world's largest atrium. So it was meant to be a
boat that took you around the hotel or the lobby
until they realized that doesn't make any sense. Well and the waits were
like 90 minutes to get on the boat which I don't, who
didn't bring this up? This is one of the most, well you know what's going to happen to you
right away on day one is lines will form.
Yeah this is really weird. I understand, like this, no one brought
this up that like, this is going to back up. You know you can see
great footage, there's a very slick
special, like 27 minute special about the opening of the Luxor.
Yes, great special. Which we'll pull from a lot when we talk about these, the big
ticket rides. Yeah. And you see a couple funny things about the
boat ride. One, within the first few shots of the special there's a
massive crowd waiting for the boat ride. And two, later on
you see one of the boat ride hosts
doing the spiel, holding the script in a microphone
to an empty boat as they're putting final touches on the
whole place. And that is very funny to see.
Well the notable thing there is that she is practicing her spiel and
welcoming people on board the boat for when it opens and she says, hi my name is
Cricket. I'll be your, I also noted that her name is Cricket.
That stuck in my mind too, yeah. Wow. That's cool.
I hope Cricket had a good run before the Nile River adventure wrapped up.
So basically, so this was meant to be like a transportation boat, this was meant to be more like
the Epcot boats, so the Island of Adventure boats, but that doesn't make
any sense and really just what it leads to is weird imagery of like
here's the, because it's also, okay, all the rooms are facing that
atrium, so it's like the world's largest motel basically where
you don't have private hallways. It's all like as soon as you're out of your room you are
public facing. So that's the case and if you're on one of the lower
floors you walk out, if you're on floor two you step out and maybe there is
a reed boat full of tourists going by immediately.
So the creepiness of the boat just moving through the
little hotel corridors is very strong. Really weird.
Yeah. And I think it's smell, I think it was very
chloriney or whatever, or like pirates water smell, like that was
really, that wafted through the entire lobby. Oh, had to be.
And I believe, correct me if I'm wrong,
I think I saw the mention of like this and some
of the other attractions gone by 1996.
I think so, I think the main Luxor things made it a little
while. But 96 kind of, that's where it all started.
Unraveling. Because 96 is when all that Wizard of Oz theming we
talked about on Club 3, that's when that went away. And I think when
half of MGM Grand, nearly half of MGM Grand Adventures was gone.
So 96 was a big like sober up moment for this weird
family time. Boat rides gone, most of MGM Park is gone.
But you could probably feel, like it always seemed to me, Theme Park Vegas,
Family Vegas, it seemed like by the second or third week of running
this stuff, they were like the contempt, the people running
it probably just had for this stuff, you know? Yeah, really.
The idea, again, just from somebody who you get done with your long drive,
you've probably got bags with you, you're waiting to check in,
you check in and the next thing you have to do is wait in a 90 minute line
to get on a boat just to dump your shit.
And keep in mind you don't have to, you could just
walk to the elevators, which undoubtedly will be faster.
Well sure, yes. So this notion of
transportation boat ride is just defeated instantly.
Yeah, but they were obviously encouraging, I would assume a lot of people
wanted to do the boat. Because you go, we're going to this big crazy hotel,
let's get in line for the boat. But then the boat takes 90 minutes and you got your shit
and you just drove. It's not even like, oh we hop right on the boat, we go right to the room
or whatever. The idea of this extra
two hour chunk before you get to your room is crazy.
I don't know who thought this was a good idea. The larger Vegas casino
hotels, I am skeptical of
the relaxing, like when it's like New York, New York is a little
like this too, where it's like, oh if you're in that tower you have to cross the casino
floor with your luggage to check in.
Yes, that drives me nuts with a lot of these places. Because the thing we like about Park MGM
is like the check in desk is right there, right behind it is the
elevator bank. Yes, you know exactly where it is.
I was at Bedaro, which is part of Aria and that's completely the deal there too.
You don't have like the silly fun, but you're close to the silly fun.
You can maybe get a little calmer escape. Not a bad thing.
Yeah, this is crazy. So they stopped making
this, they threw out the transportation element of it and it just had to become a
ticketed boat ride called Nile River Adventure. But I don't think there was much
to the adventure. Because it wasn't supposed to be, it was just like going through
hallways. Some of them quite narrow. It's a little creepy. You go through like very
little, because probably right above you people are walking by to the rides of the restaurants or
whatever. So there's some low clearance. And then like
a guy on board, all of them, there's somebody on board, like Storybook Land.
I only found one video and they are
not making jokes really. This is like real, they're pointing out real hieroglyphic
stuff. But it's all fake and they're trying to incorporate
sometimes the mythology of the rides that we'll get to.
Our main archaeologist, Mack McPherson,
was spotted around these parts. Which again, I love. This is
so on my alley. This dumb boat ride in this part, like connects to the other.
Love it. But it's being said by this gruff Brian Doyle Marie
sounding guy who does not seem to be thrilled with having to
parallel. And then there's no animatronics. You don't like encounter, it's
a pirates without anything to look at besides stuff that you could just walk past
in the hotel anyway. They thought that, yeah, they thought the idea of
it being transportation would be enough.
Obviously they didn't think it was just going to be a ticketed ride, but they thought they didn't have any
foresight that that boat ride should have some sort of really unique
theming or robots or anything to it. Yeah, anything.
Yes, it's just, it's pointing out hieroglyphics that are
not ancient. They were put up there three months ago.
Similarly, this place also had a recreation of King Tut's
tomb, which are like, why? Who would care if it's not a real,
well, what if I told you it was green lit by the Egyptian ministry
of antiquities and they oversaw it to make sure it was like
the real tomb? Well, I would say still then
it's just a, if it's a simulation of a real tomb, but it doesn't have like a
mummy trying to get out of the tomb and try to send me to hell and spit scarabs
at me, then why bother to make it realistic?
It's a very good point. Really weird. Some of these, I'll say quote-unquote
artifacts, because they were all recreations
when they were closing stuff down or pulling back on it, they did donate
to a local Vegas museum, so that's nice.
You can see, so now a real museum has a fake King Tut tomb. Has fraudulent
artifacts. I think there's still
some sort of like King Tut exhibit.
In the Luxor, with the Titanic
and with bodies, you know. Okay, okay. And the
fantasy, the topless review.
That's at Luxor? I didn't see, I forgot to go see it.
You did? Yeah. Just kidding, I didn't see bodies,
I didn't see dead bodies and I didn't see nude bodies.
Well, they were both nude actually. It all sounds a little
bawdy. That does it. Bodies. A couple spellings
in place. That's my new, yeah.
Did you scribble that on the feedback card when you were like checking out?
Put clothes on those bodies. Every time
I walked to the Luxor, I was like angry or for some, like I was just like
oh, I just like, get me, transport me to the other side is dumb place.
So there's no boats. The idea was you get all,
you would just wait 90 minutes for a 15 minute boat ride. Yeah.
Yeah, rest your feet. But it was not to be. But, look,
ultimately, you know, if there were some flawed concepts
here, it's because the big money was put into the center
piece. The trilogy of attractions, of
high end theme park attractions, secrets of the Luxor
pyramid. And again, we will recommend the special that's on YouTube,
the making of Luxor. I think that'll find it for you.
And where you can watch the creation. They have cameras present for
every step of putting together really high end, the highest
end outside of Disney Universal. Maybe higher than some of what they
were doing at the time. Yeah. This was top tier stuff.
Plopped into this casino to be mostly unappreciated.
The work they put in for, the work they put into
the appreciation ratio has to be off the charts.
I don't know how to explain. You know what I'm saying? The amount of work, the amount of
effort versus the amount of people that actually gave a shit.
Yeah. When you compare it to like. It's just so much versus so little, I assume. Same era.
Indiana Jones Adventure. Right. And it is like,
it comes out to rave reviews and people still are just like, trembling
when they, I love it so much in reunion panels and it's the great,
I want to take my kids on it and pass it along and they refreshed it
and they, I, like the emotion present in, and I'm not
saying these were better than that, but it was like
top tier themed entertainment talent. Yeah. Getting nothing.
Did anybody tell him I liked it?
It's possible no. I guess I'll say if somehow someone
is listening who's part of these, I can't say I liked it because I didn't go.
I wish I could have gone. These seem incredible. Yeah. 100%.
The thing I had always heard about it was the one guy
associated with Douglas Trumbull who worked on
Back to the Future the Ride. Directed it. He's the reason for
like, the reason for the premise. He saved it. It was like
potentially going to be a disaster that just made people nauseous.
They built a theater that was not to his liking and he's like, what can we do?
And he figured out how to make it work. And he remade that
one of the greatest rides ever. Yeah. And I think another was known
for the special effects on close encounters of the third kind.
2001. 2001. 2001. Yeah.
Blade Runner. Star Trek motion picture. At some point went to
left Hollywood and started working
more in themed entertainment. Under the shadow of
Natalie Wood's death which occurred while he was directing her in a movie. Dear
God. Yeah. And he like, I'm sure I said this before, but yeah, he's
just on the record. Like, and after what happened to Natalie, I just, I didn't want to be in this town
anymore. And I, crazy. Can you imagine that? You're like, no. You were the
person with her when this still mysterious thing occurred.
Wait, he wasn't on the boat. No, no. You just mean he was working? Yeah. I was like, wait, I didn't read that.
I can't believe what happened. What someone else
did and I won't say who, but you can, hey, it's up to you to
go ahead and do your own story together. Check out this big miniature.
It's pretty funny, right? It's giant, but it's tiny. The rides are gonna be fun.
That's what we should focus on. But no, a giant in
the field of early special effects. Yeah. Who, and also in
experimenting with different frame
rates to create different crazy effects. So you don't
have, I don't think, what Peter Jackson later did or
James Cameron later did with, you know, not standard
frame rates without this guy. And especially in this ride
forum, because he started doing everything 60
frames a second, which did not happen much then, but
worked really well for ride purposes. Yeah, one of the attractions
that, the names of the attractions, by the way, Insert of the Obelisk,
Luxor Live and Theater of Time. Insert of the
Obelisk, kind of the straight, more straightforward simulator ride,
Luxor Live, like starts as a talk show with in-person
actors and then becomes more like CG
footage and then Theater of Time is like, that's
the future one. That one I think pretty quickly replaced with just an
IMAX theater. Regular IMAX. Yeah. So it's all
screen based, but in this like,
you know, when that was nearly impossible to do
in a way that really worked and where you needed people
who were part scientists to do the math and to
build the domed screens. What they had to do to do
this, because, okay, so he, for Back to the Future, the ride
was not happy. He had to like, we already built the theater, we're stuck,
can you save it? And he had to like work around that. He got to build these theaters
from the ground. This guy had a huge say in the layout of the Luxor
in general. Was involved in building the theaters. He was
involved in creating a custom robot to paint
the screens so that the screens were even and you could
light them correctly, which is also admirable. And then
you just read about the history of this, that like, the film started going to shit, that nobody
was maintaining it properly, which happens so often.
Like it's so, I appreciate the optimism that
we can put a really top tier technical process
in this casino and that somebody will take care of it. Because
I don't, I think a year in, maybe less, maybe as soon as
Doug Trumbull left town, they're like, alright, and put a 14 year old in there and
we aren't good. You know it got bad so fast.
Unless he was, I wonder like, does he, how long does he even stay on
I don't think this is documented at all, but like how long does he get contracted for
past opening? Okay, it all works. Does he
check in on it every six months or after a year he's out? Maybe not, because
if there's no, yeah, assuming there's no new money in it for him to
then why would you? He can't. I think
the whole thing was part of, I found another interview with him where he was saying this was part of
something, okay, he coined this term. He was imagining
a world full of high impact entertainment centers.
He wanted there to be a ton of things like what he did
in Luxor. Every city has something like this where it's a theme park
and it's high end original movies with a story and that was part
of it to him. He thought of making them all correlated. They said we want three rides,
he said the rides should be connected so that you get more invested in these characters
as you go. You know Schomburg was going to have one of those.
I suspect somewhere around me would have had one Glendale Galleria or whatever.
Like, we're King of Prussia Mall. We all, if he got in his way,
we would have had such insane arch stories
that our dads don't understand and we're
begging to keep going back to these weird things that are too adult for us
and scare us, but we're chasing the scariness. God, I wish he'd got
his vision of the world. I really have to get behind here
because he's, we've said this from day one on this podcast, like
more stuff like this and just like malls. It's exactly what he wanted.
Film based micro theme parks in shopping malls,
multiplexes and casinos. That was his whole detailing of his
vision. Any bit of it that we ever see, we're like, oh look,
one of those. He wanted there to be everywhere. There was the Vi, I mean,
there was, you know, Disney Quest. They wanted it everywhere.
Blockbuster. Blockbuster had that entertainment
and there was only ever one, maybe two of them. What's that called?
Entertainment City? Something like that, yeah. And there
were Sega in Australia. I think there was a Sega
sponsored thing. There were multiple kinds of things in Japan. There was a Sega thing here. There was
something called Virtual Land in Luxor too. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah. Where you could get
in those like orbs that spin around and go 360. Oh yeah,
massive arcade here. Yeah, yeah. And rides and
three attractions, a boat ride, like they were going for the Disney
dollar here. Oh god. If I ever, just listener, wherever
you live, just imagine where you know it would be and imagine
what year it would have disappeared. Yeah. Probably 96 to
99 sometime. Imagine what the fond memories you would have
in 1995 of going to this barely attended
too dense of story theme park near you, you know,
in whatever, in like Glendale, Arizona. Right. I,
oh god, oh the world of these I wish was there. There's, I still,
we're not done yet. This still is trying, like it's not the same thing,
but like the void was trying even though now that's over. Like this is still
an idea to put so much more themed garbage everywhere.
Yeah. I think it can, as we get older and as we
theme park pill our kids more, I feel like we're just
priming the world for it. And as shopping malls die, and
we don't know what else to do with them, they're big crazy spaces, why not
just turn them into, you know, Meow Wolf we were saying on the second gate
is a good, you know, they're trying to do these off the beaten path. The thing is, you know,
crazy experiences in, you know, not the three
primary cities and without like a billion dollars to do them.
I'm hopeful. And how long did that Austin Powers Bar last
in Glendale? That's a themed bar that lasted a couple years. Enough
for me to go a couple times. I think I went twice. For me to feel some sticky textures of chairs.
Yeah. See some shady people. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The dreamers of the world, the trumbles and the
powers is. The fake powers is. The unauthorized Austin Powers
Bar. Oh, there was an unauthorized Star Wars bar on Hollywood Boulevard.
Oh, it's still going. I believe so. Kevin Smith does his shows there still.
Oh, okay. Pretty sure. I'm pretty sure I see him in front of. So the dream is alive. Yeah.
I'm pretty sure I see him in front of like the bar. Like the mausoleum looking bar
when he's talking, talking about flicks. Okay.
So I think it's still there. I'm saying that it exists. This idea
exists. It's not dead. Douglas Trumbull had a dream and I think
it's still alive. Does Kevin still have a key to the Kevin Smith podcast lounge
on the top floor of the John Lovitz Comedy Club, formerly
Wizards, you know. What is it now? What is it now? It's nothing.
It's nothing. It's a bunch of boxes. It's storage and the signs. Bats and bats.
Is it the third floor of the. I thought it was.
Yeah. So in the circle in the bamboo ceiling
area, it was the third floor. It was like at above Carl's. It was later. It was added on
later. I know, but we're actually, this is really, I would like to know, do you know specifically where it was?
I don't know. I was never there. I wasn't either and I feel bad that
I wasn't. There's no diagrams of this. There's no Martin's vids breaking down
where the Smodcast theater was. But it had to be like above the
what is it now? What is Carl Strauss now? Oh, it's
Starbucks, isn't it? Starbucks. It's a Starbucks.
So above the Starbucks maybe was where John Lovitz. I think you know, no, the other side.
It's above the. It was next to. Johnny Rockets.
Oh, OK. I think. And then Wizards, because Wizards, you see the pictures
of the. But Wizards was the Carl Strauss in Starbucks.
Or am I completely my geography? I don't know.
This, it's not well recorded. Interesting.
It's almost like they thought no one would care about this. No one should even
we don't need to write down one bit of where any of this is. It's like we have to do, it's like
we're going to have to do more city walk, though. Yeah.
Let's keep moving.
Let's talk about what these actual rides were.
So they're all there's like a there's like a kind of an aesthetic
that is strewn through all of them, which is
like the future of Egypt. And you hear people mention
in the special how it is the like millions of
years down the road version of Egyptian
technology where like they're like anything that the Egyptians
thought of now is in use in the highest tech way
and it works great. So every all tech, all human technology
is ancient Egypt based. But also don't do they say at
some point and this is a society that came before Egypt
where it actually got less technologically advanced. Yes, they
do say that. And because they say the pyramids are like less good versions
of what were originally built. I think they say both.
The Luxor is supposedly like a better pyramid than the real pyramids that were
built because it was built by the people before the
whatever society before the ancient Egyptians.
So your hotel is shittier than whatever was there
before that we don't remember. No, no, the hotel is better.
The hotel is better than those fucking garbage pyramids in Egypt
and the crap old casinos. Yeah, yeah. Then the real pyramids.
I'm sorry, then the crap old pyramids. Yes, that's right.
I think that's what I got from the special at least. Wow. Okay. So we're
introducing like an entire race of people
that has mostly vanished and then also a whole
future based on ancient technology. Yes.
All right. So Dad with a big yard, are you
ready now? So are you ready to learn about ancient but future
technologies and peoples? Yes, yes. Dad who just wants to
gamble and just take a nap.
Gamble with the big cup. The cup that had your quarter.
Yeah, your coins. Oh man, yeah. Do you miss the big cup?
Did you ever do the big cup? Growing up so close to Atlantic City,
there were definitely relatives who would like, if we would see them
they'd be like, hey, here's a big cup. You know, this is good for the beach.
And honestly, the big cups were good for building sandcastles.
Oh, so you get their big coin cup but it was empty. Yes. And I hope
cleaned before anything was drank. Oh, cleaned. My mom was definitely big on like,
yeah, clean that because it's probably disgusting. Yeah, clean your
coin cup. Clean the coin cup before you take it to the beach.
So, first one, you were
supposed to do this in an order. Yes, yes. And Doug Trumbull was
frustrated that they did not force people to do it in the order
that he wanted. I love this maniac. Yeah, I was able to do the second one first
and the third one, the second, and I went, oh, it all went haywire.
So, but if you did it under Trumbull's vision, you started
within search of the obelisk. Can we even
How would, I don't think I am capable of describing
the story of in search of the obelisk. These things, and they're not
There's precisely one video of the actual ride other than brief
clips in the special and it is like, it's somebody filming one
corner of the screen. You don't know what the hell is going on. Yeah. It's tough.
Let's try to, as if sifting through ancient ruins, can we put it together?
Okay, you're in a ride vehicle that is called the monolith?
The monolev. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Mono-lev.
A monolith is a full, I know. I believe the architect character is like
oh, I guess you're coming with me. Mack. Yes.
Yes, an archaeologist. Yes. Mack.
Wait, I had it earlier. His last name. It was Mack.
Tonight. It's Mack McPherson. Okay. It's Mack McPherson.
And then you've got Cricket. No, that was just the one woman doing the ride. Cricket's not in the video.
Cricket's not in the rides. And then you've, he has, Mack has a friend
named Karina. And Karina is gone because she is in search
of the obelisk. So we need to find Karina
because she's my friend. Right. And maybe in doing so
also get the obelisk. Now I don't know what is crucial about
this obelisk. Maybe we don't know yet, actually. Yeah. That might be something we don't
learn until Luxor Live. So
do we miss anything? Well, I mean there's like villains. Well, yeah, you go through, well, okay,
just like what happens, I guess. Yeah, yeah. But yeah, with the villains you want to.
Well, I don't know. I just, I don't really know what they are. He's fighting a villain, like Mack, so
you're in a basic simulator, like Back to the Future something. And on the screen
Mack is basically on the front of your vehicle.
So it makes it look like he's hanging out like right on the tip or the hood of your
obelisk. He's on there with you. Yeah. Or model. Kind of surfing it.
Does he steer it? He like has a steering mechanism. Yeah. Yes. Up there too.
From the pictures, that's sort of what I can decipher. And yeah,
you're going through like a grimy looking
practical effects sets shot with cameras.
Giant miniatures, motion control cameras.
And by the way, like, you know, regardless of story, which is
hard to figure out, the cool thing is if you like Back to the
Future the Ride very much, it is same director and thus it is
really similar aesthetic, shot on similar film, shot on
same kind of camera. Like just the
degree of visual effects are very similar. And like compositing
and the way he lights it and the way light is treated. And Alan
Silvestri score as well. So this was kind of a
second Back to the Future ride that was only in Las Vegas.
So that's pretty notable. It is. Yeah. And it is. It is. Look, it looks some of some of the
scenes almost look like Mortal Kombat, the movie I've talked about Mortal Kombat
recently. Yeah. A fan of Mortal Kombat. You've seen Mortal Kombat, Jason? I
years ago. You got to watch it. Yeah, I got to rewatch. We should. There's some broader
way. I mean, we will certainly throw in movies that we want to watch. Yeah.
And talk about them, especially on the second game. But is there some way to frame it that it's like the PTR
Canon? Just that we are we talking about the films that we think are the most fundamental to us
as people, but also better the most theme parky and the most in line
with like. Oh, yeah. Like David Hasselhoff, Nick Fury.
Yeah. I mean, I've never seen it. I'll put it in the PTR Canon. I can only assume.
But if people are down for more of that
then you get some Batman forever, I would imagine. Well, of course. Yeah, you'd have to.
If you have a better name, if you have a name for the PTR Canon, throw it out there too. Good question.
But mainly find proof of the fans. That's
task number one. I send you in search of the fans as Karina is
in search of the obelisk.
I love I do love what I can see from this. Yeah.
Yeah. Big fights happening on the front of the going through like
it's an underground pyramid and there's a bunch of giant floating
obelisks, but not ones you can grab. Yeah, those are like
levitating. You got to weave through them and not crash the I almost
think there's no I'm trying to think and back to the future. No one's ever on the
hood of the car and back to the future. No. Yeah, that's a lot more ambitious. All the
characters are on the screen in front of you. So that's way more ambitious. This is almost like a precursor
to Spider-Man, the Islands of Adventure ride.
Where you're really getting it's a simulator, but you're getting characters up front
which gives you that, you know, personal touch that you might want from
a dark ride. Intimacy. Intimacy, if you will. Well, some of the
stuff is also precursors to like the
soaring fly like they figured out like, OK, here's how we do kind of a
flying theater before the soaring flying
theater comes along. Yeah. Yeah. Also you mentioned Spider-Man
a company that worked on that later worked
on this called Kleiser-Wolzak. Oh, I did do that.
Also part of Honey Has Shrunk the Audience, part of Azillian Things and seems like
one of them is a prolific director, but one of either Kleiser or Wolzak
built the sculpted the Michael Jackson history
statue. Really? Remember that? Remember when they were sending big scary
statues all over the globe and one of them is still in a McDonald's
parking lot? Oh yeah. In possibly Russia? Am I making
that up? It's definitely somewhere weird. I don't know. There's still
Michael Jackson's scary statues floating out there all over this world
of ours and made by the same, which I understand like aesthetically I see
what you know, the big ancient ruins and statues make sense. So
you have, yeah, some Spider-Man folks cut their teeth on these. To keep
in perspective the CG and the footage
stuff, at one point they talked to like the engineer, like the
computer guys working on this and they're like, and we've got a specially
made computer and like one image from this is 90
megabytes and that would fill up someone's home PC
instantly. Oh my God. And it's like, I think
I clipped, I think I screen recorded a clip from the special
that probably is like around 90
megabytes. Oh it's got to be more probably depending. Yeah. Yeah, yeah. No, our notes files.
Like 20 seconds of HD footage, of HD footage
of standard death special. My God. Yeah. Wow.
There is some bad looking CGI in this too. Oh yeah. But that's
to be. You got some typical mummy kind of,
right. But there's so much practical stuff and it looks, it just looks
like a weird kind of low budget 90s
movie like this. I don't know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, totally.
Which is, you know, and it's shot well where you even take, you know,
even like some dumb movie is still like,
is there a movie called like the Great Panda Adventure? Does that sound familiar?
Let me not go into that movie. What about like Warriors of Virtue? Even Warriors of Virtue
shot on beautiful pristine film movie. Yeah.
Nobody's really seeing or liking. Apologies to Virtue heads out there.
The poster for the ride looks bad, I would say. Yes.
The poster looks shitty. I think the cityscapes look best.
Cause they're just practical miniatures. What you're showing looks like some
like creepy. It's like,
I was gonna say a Christian movie, but I mean like the shadiest
of Christian movies. A Christian movie with an agenda.
It's the ships that the Animorphs travel in, you know,
on the covers. There's things I like about the poster, but the poster overall
doesn't look as cool as it should. Pretty cruddy.
There's somebody named Claggart and he's yelling
get off of Claggart! But I don't really know what
Claggart is. And then there's also, there's another enemy whose name
is Dr. Osiris. I forget if he's part of this
first one or if you meet him later. But Dr. Osiris is also part
of the Luxerverse. The secretverse.
The Piraverse. I'm not sure which verse it is.
Do you think, cause I don't know, I forget what year
MGM bought this, but does MGM now own the IP
of all of this? Oh fuck. Probably. I don't know. Or does Circus Circus
still? Or yeah maybe. And what is Circus Circus anymore? Did Circus Circus
get swallowed into something? Cause the hotel itself I think is only
that. I don't think they are major landholders in general.
Yeah maybe. So yeah, does like Circus Company, I think the name
was the Circus Company maybe? Could be. Before, yeah did they own Mac
and Dr. Osiris? Dr. Osiris. I'm now, I love a good
crazy doctor name. Yeah. I want to know what else can be done
with Dr. Osiris. Yeah we'll put that into the- I don't think I know what he looks like or how to find
a picture of him or if anyone saved a picture of him. Doesn't matter, we'll re-imagine
that. I love his name. I think Circus Circus might technically
be under the MGM brand. Is that right? Cause I think it shows up
in some of those iPhone games. You can go
to Circus Circus. Oh right, right, right. Yeah maybe. That's probably right
if they're showing up there. They might be trying to sell it off although
if you look up Luxor and like
there's lots of Google question results of like will the Luxor
be destroyed? Like will it be demolished or closed?
Yeah will it suck inside itself and go to another realm? Yeah.
There's talk about different floors being like, has the basement
been condemned? Wait a minute.
I was just gonna say MGM bought it in 2007 so like all this stuff was long gone
but I wonder if in the language of the sale they
said and we also buy the rights in perpetuity to Dr.
Osiris, Carina, Mac,
the Obelisk. The Obelisk itself, the Maglevs. Yeah right.
Yeah. Is it just floating out order? And if they ignore it, I say if you
find that contract and you do a little find and search and you don't
find Dr. Osiris or Maglev that means they're up for grabs and
we can make a very frustrating graphic novel about all of this.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Oh and trust me any of the publishers
that would, there's a lot of indie comics
publishers now that it's like yeah we'll get your comic out, we'll get a public
and they like pay dog shit rates and they're like and of course
we'll keep the intellectual property and we will immediately
start selling it to the major studios. No way. We're not doing that.
We have to learn the lesson of Aaron Fector who would not give up his
intellectual property of his characters, the beloved
Rock of Fire explosion and he kept them and he holds them proudly
they're the greatest weapon in his arsenal. Oh my goodness. As soon as he figures out
anything anybody wants to do with them he's back on top.
He crushes Chuck E. Cheese because he wouldn't let them pilfer
his valuable IP. Don't count him out yet.
He's scheming in that warehouse that has room for 400 people but
it's just him and a bunch of like Billy Bob's robot
oil spilled everywhere. He has a bunch of rotting Billy Bob's
that will sometimes move and he's like oh is it coming, is my creation
becoming real and then just a bunch of rats crawl out of it.
He could have had some of the Five Nights at Freddy's money, he could have had
like the at least the current weird Alf where it's like oh
yeah, Alf's back. They're doing some short
they're doing mobile commercials? Yeah the Mint Mobile like Ryan Reynolds
has teamed up with Alf for Mint Mobile commercials. That's so freaking epic.
Yeah, you better believe it.
Okay I think that covers In Search of the Obelisk
except, spoiler, you do not get the Obelisk.
You get what's important. You save Karina, Mac's best friend
or lover or associate or maybe he has better friends. I don't know.
Karina matters to Mac and you get her. On to the Maglev.
But you don't get the Obelisk. So we're still in search of the Obelisk
after In Search of the Obelisk. Do they call in that special, do they call like the
two of them like quintessentially 90's or something? No maybe. They describe
then? They say that within the 90's? Maybe they don't say quintessential but they definitely
say both of them are like typical 90's people.
And by that they mean white? I guess. Yeah, the most generic
white humans. Boring?
So then if you continue
the story or if you realize that this is what you're supposed to do
apparently, I think this footage where you enter the ride and it says episode
one really big on it as if like, so you get it? These rides
are episodes and I think the tourists partially drunk probably
did not. But if you went to episode two that was Luxor
Live. Luxor Live is an out of this world talk show where you will behold
a fabulous 3D solar eclipse. It's kind of like a campy
version of Geraldo. Now I'm lost.
What does this mean? Now I'm in! I just don't think I get it.
Luxor, okay, so and now we're in the present. That's the idea.
The idea here is that Luxor, the casino you're staying at, has
a live Geraldo-esque talk show. Yeah. And
It's not like the serious Geraldo show that you're used to.
The straight ahead, very played, like a news
piece of serious news Geraldo show. No, no, no. This was the wild
times with the weirdos where he's getting into fights. Yeah.
I guess. So, alright. The visitors
are part of a studio audience of a fake TV talk show with a debate
between, well when Luxor Live, today Luxor Live,
alright everybody having fun at the casino, you're hanging out by the pool. Well today we've got a treat
for you. We've got archaeologist Mac McPherson and Colonel
Claggart and they are going to have a debate about ruins
and whether we should use technology to get
items from the past and bring them to modern times.
I guess, I guess. Yeah. I suppose. This all happens
in front of a talk show set that has a Johnny Carson-esque
cityscape but it is not of Hollywood.
It is of the two properties that Circus Circus owns.
So there's a big Circus Circus clown and there is the Excalibur Castle.
And in this setting there is a debate about archaeology that happens
before a live studio audience. Now here's what I've always tried to figure
out. I first saw this special a few years ago.
Did they have the actor who played Mac McPherson
on retainer to be there in person or did they
just like, alright we need a white guy with brown hair.
They can't have right. And he's far enough away. Well they'd have to have
multiple Macs I would assume. I would assume. I think maybe that's the idea.
I bet. I bet that's just like Terminator 2 kind of deal.
I would think. Yeah. You couldn't count on Mac forever.
Something that I'm confused about though is when it transitions from
live to movie because a comment
I read somewhere, somebody described being there as a kid and then
thinking this thing was confusing and unremarkable until one of the actors exploded
into particles. And so then I don't understand.
I don't know if like what if all, it seems like it was live actors but what if some of it
was projected or I don't know or there was a screen in front of them that made a
I don't know. Whatever was going on here maybe this ended up being actually the coolest effects
wise due to the surprise of it. And then like the screen cracks apart
and you go into like a fully. It seems like Terminator 2. It does seem
like T2. Like that really like there's. You don't know it's screens
until something crazy happens. But then you watch a bunch of
Crystal dance. Oh I love the Crystal dancers.
They are touting the liquid. Are they Crystal dancers or liquid dancers?
I saw Crystal. Crystal figures. But I don't know what I got this from.
They are talking up those Crystal figure dancers in that special
as well where they're like and they like captured real life human
movements to make these new. Like they're really blown away
by these and obviously. They did MoCa. They did MoCa. Yeah essentially
original avatar. Yeah. Yes. But it sounds like
dry description of this. First liquid human beings
emerge from the life giving source of water then solidify into male
and female glass dancers moving in harmony. But they
soon grow wary of each other. Put on armor and start fighting.
Culminating in a nuclear blast. This is sounding
a little obtuse. A little or like
too pointed or I don't know.
I'm very. Would I love Luxor Live or
does Luxor Live collapse this entire experience? It's a good
question. I could see there being a lot of cringy stuff during Luxor Live
but I don't know that the dancers were as impressive as they thought.
But if somebody blew up into particles. It does look like the
eventual TLC waterfalls video.
Which was very impressive to the MTV viewers of 1995.
However, the technology was probably
better then. You accept things a little jankier in a
music video maybe. I don't know. This when I was
reading at Luxor I discovered. I had seen it years
ago but I didn't put it all together. Or it didn't
really mean anything to me. But the getting jiggy with it music
video is filmed in the Luxor lobby and then they're in front
of the Mirage volcano and then they're in front of New York, New York.
Yeah. It's kind of like traveling
all over but by way of just Las Vegas.
It really encapsulates that era and all of the big silliness
going on. And specifically the one side of Las Vegas Boulevard.
Yeah, yeah true. Does he not do kind of like walk like an
Egyptian dancing? Is he not in sort of a headdress?
I believe he is. He is and the backup dancers are. Yeah
there's a lot of Egyptian stuff.
Maybe he saw these shows and started thinking about like wow so there's some crazy
stuff out there. I should maybe pursue like you know I passed by this building
that said Scientology on it. I wonder if that has anything to do with
the. That's very possible. Is Colonel Claggart
part of that? Is there a scientist part of that obelisk obelisk in
Scientology? What are the secrets of the obelisk? Maybe Scientology will open me
up to those secrets. Is this Douglas Trumbull was just maybe trying to create a
religion based on an obelisk? Maybe obeliskology. Yeah
this is different. The Luxor was going to be the center of obeliskology.
The celebrity center of his new religion. All hail the obelisk.
Did someone find the other like pop music connection?
No I didn't. That when Tupac Shakur was killed
in Vegas. He took a picture here the night I saw
he was staying here. Whoa. Oh I didn't know that.
He gets killed elsewhere in Vegas.
He was staying. Someone of his wealth at the time
was staying at the crappiest hotel. Well maybe
in 96 it was still okay. I don't know. Wow. Do you think
I'll just type it into Google. Did Tupac meet Dr.
Obelisk and Colonel Claggart? Did he go to the rides?
Very good question. That's so creepy. There is a room at that hotel
that is the, it could have been where you were staying where it was
like the room that Tupac did not return back to that night.
Jesus. My God. Yeah. This place really
is, this place does need to fold into itself.
Like a priest needs to come or an army of priests from different
religions. From a real religion. Yeah from the good religion, Christianity
the one that makes sense. The ultimate 90's religion.
Get the top priest from each state and
get them over to Luxor to get the spirits out of there.
Everyone hold hands, surround the building. Yes. Then and only then
will it return. Now of course Carrot Top can keep playing there. He's not part of the
curse. No he's good. He helps fend off the curse. He balances the
life. He balances the bad with the light. Carrot Top is a force of light.
Wikipedia says so Tupac was at the Tyson
fight at the MGM Grand and then there was a brawl
and it says after the brawl Shakur returned to his hotel, the
Luxor Las Vegas. Wow. He went back there? Yeah.
He stopped there first. Whoa. That's insane.
I believe he was killed closer to Flamingo Road. I forget the
intersection. Yeah I've been there. I was in a cab and somebody was like
you know where we are. Oh god. East Flamingo Road and Koval
Lane. Koval. Wow.
Crazy. He might have waited the 90 minutes for the boat ride.
Maybe he got them. Maybe they're like oh we'll take you.
They should have let him cut the line. He could have met Cricket.
Or he got. Tupac and Cricket could have met on this
if he'd been on the boat ride. If he'd done it. If he'd been patient
and then waited. What if he like then people were like looking for him but he's
having a blast on the boat. Yeah it's possible. He's in a secret
tunnels of the Luxor. Anything's possible. Do you think a crew guy
on the Will Smith video is like you know Tupac was staying here when he was killed. It's like
Jesus don't tell me that. Like
a fucking haunted Egypt hotel. That was what
cursed Will ultimately. That's what led to what happened 30 years later.
Took a while. It took a while to manifest.
Okay so now. Well basically the special says like
the audience shares Karina's discovery of the true meaning of the obelisk.
Okay again. It's hard to imagine.
Okay so now Nell armed with my knowledge of the true
meaning of the obelisk. Now I can proceed to the theater of time.
And the theater of time is set. So this
I don't know if you stole it on this too. You encounter a big sign and the sign
says enlightened society for global transformation.
Which also sounds like a Scientology. I was going to say the full logo looks like Scientology.
It really does. The phrase looks like Scientology.
This might have. I'm deciding it. This open Will Smith's
This started him on the path. This picture that I'm showing
of the sign. This is what would greet you as you entered the theater of time. And now
it is at the neon museum. This is sitting around somewhere.
If you go there in Vegas, which I'm not but I would like to. I'd like to see that sign because it's actually
a lot like Alien Encounter or something. It's very like very 90's theme park.
And then. And this was a. This was like a
screen tipped. Like movie screens are thin and
long ways. Imagine if you turn that. If you went 90 with it. If you go
90. If you do Quibi freestyle. You turned it on its head. They did
it. So it was a big. It was a tall long screen.
Is what this was. A tall TikTok.
I think of it as the original TikTok.
And eventually this just became a real IMAX theater. They just like
put more screen on there. Why do we have just one. We can only play one kind of
movie. Much like what befell Quibi ultimately. Yeah.
Maybe having some more flexibility in what you could show here is good. There's not a lot
about theater of time. Did you guys. I don't really understand what's
happening in this one. It seems. Is this a mainly a sit down movie?
But with a little bit of movement. It's not a full simulator.
Yeah. It seems like it's just sort of an IMAX.
Like a little bit of an elevated IMAX. I guess.
I've seen some of this stuff. Seen a little proof of concept.
I think it was. Cause he's like this is my chant.
I have like. Doug Trumbull found this rare pile of money.
To prove his high impact entertainment center concept.
And I wish it had been proven better.
I know. It's like I admire his big reach
for the nonsense. Like just doing this much dumb nonsense.
But it's yeah. It's like if it just it was a little bit more accessible.
At the very least it could have lasted longer than this stuff did.
Well it's obviously mobsters versus mummies. That is the
very clear story. Much like Pirates of the Caribbean. You know what it is
when you're going into it. He should have had the idea that we just had 30 years later.
I agree. The only other pitch I had on it is that he licensed William Shatner's
Tech War. Of course the William Shatner verse.
It is surprising Tech War is not part of Luxor.
Like today. Oh not today. Oh good.
Visit the Tech War experience. It will open in 2006.
The William Shatner supposedly created future story of the illegal
drug known as Tech. Is it just in our world or
like it's not. Tech War is not in another universe. I believe it's in the future
but I actually don't know if it's in another universe or not. Okay. Yeah. Tech War is definitely
in the canon. Tech War is in the PTR canon for sure.
Because there's a variety of things we need to watch and read.
I want it filmed at the Eden Center in Toronto. Well I'm on board.
The future as seen through a big tall mall. Sounds good to me.
Hey that you know I got a couple things. One Douglas Trumbull
credited it with working on the first flight simulator ride.
Which I think you can see footage of online. It's called Tour of the
Universe and it was in the basement of the CN Tower.
Of the Tower. In Toronto. Pre-Star Tours. Pre-Star Tours.
The other thing you know we were speculating about like how did Luxor
get made. How did this all happen. And there's
a clip in that special.
This is Clyde Turner. He's the president of Circus Circus
Enterprises. And this is I mean when you see this clip
when you hear him talk about it it's just the most dynamic thing you've ever
encountered. But the vision is somewhat big.
And what happens is that you then seek out the best and the brightest
of all you can find. And you have intense brainstorm sessions.
And out of that comes ideas. He's just describing
the creative process. If that's making you like
you're probably electrified hearing that 20 second clip of
this man who appears to be falling asleep on camera.
And then it cuts to the table.
It cuts back and forth between the table of like this is the casino manager. This is Douglas
Trumbull. This is an engineer. And it's the.
You've never seen so many receding hairlines in one place. No offense.
No shade fellas. I'm right there with ya. But it's like
yeah there ain't a woman or a person of
color around for miles and miles.
Sure. Yeah well look this
thing I don't think it went away right away. I don't remember when they start. I think you know
it just the theater of time became a regular of
IMAX theater. I'd like to know more about theater of time but it's not. You can watch a big clip
of it on one of those Mind's Eye videos that keeps coming up. You can watch a big
extended like a minute and a half sequence of it. And it's very impressive. It's very
you know what it's like. It's like being in Hill Valley 2015 in
the Back to the Future ride but you're not rushing through it. And there are cars and stuff
coming at ya. None of that exciting shit. What if you could just hover above
a gentle Hill Valley future. I like that. Sure. It's pretty
cool. But then I take it back there is one woman and one person
of color at the table of bald men. Not a single. No one's gonna be found.
I just wanted to clarify. You're sexist racists. Wouldn't allow them in the room.
I just wanted to clarify. They were stuck at the door. Get out of here.
These very bald men did let a couple people.
You were right about the baldness. Yeah I was right about the baldness.
So these things start disappearing.
The attractions they can't really get rid of these facilities. They're
baked into the building like certain theme park like Yeti.
So they started using it for other stuff. When I was first in
Vegas as a not child in 2006 I remember
that one of the presumably formerly the Obelisk ride was home to something
called Reboot the Ride. A ride based on the
early CGI television show. Reboot the Ride is maybe
worthy of its own episode. I don't know. I assume. I'm not gonna try
to rush some version here. But it was at
a number of theme parks I think. And somehow provoked
a second one. I'm sorry. Okay so it was at Adventure Dome
first. Formerly Grand Slam Canyon. My favorite name.
And then moved to the Luxor. And then somehow. I don't know
where this was. If it was the Luxor. Oh I think it was in Canada maybe somewhere. There was somehow
there was not only Reboot the Ride but later Reboot the
Ride V2 Journey into Chaos. So we got
two Reboot rides to grapple with with a full methal.
And unlike the Obelisk verse which nobody is tracking and taking care of
Reboot fandom is massive so we can find every detail.
So we'll get into that. Is Reboot doing Mint Mobile commercials
yet? I don't think so. I don't know. It's been calculated if he's epic
enough. Maybe Mac tonight. Or not Mac tonight.
The Mac and Me. Maybe if Alf meets Mac and
Me. How much does Mac cost these days? Ryan Menels
did do it. He's gonna do Biker Mice for Mars. That's true. That's not a joke.
Everything this guy does is so epic.
It's kind of like a Spiderverse version of. I shouldn't talk my name.
This could be a job for any of us. Oh yeah. I grew
up with Biker Mice. I loved the mice. I remember
all of their names and I'm checking my hand for an unrelated reason.
When the name them all. When the Biker Mice play an exhibition
game against Wrexham Football Club. Oh boy.
It's gonna be something. Welcome to Wrexham Biker Mice for Mars.
The weirdest thing though about all this.
The Luxorverse did not just stay in the rides.
There was also a CD-ROM. Which makes all the sense
in the world because this aesthetic of all of this is very CD-ROM. There was something
called Secrets of the Luxor. I took a shot of the box. It has
the pitch of what this thing would be. And it has all. By the way this is
Dr. Osiris. It's the characters. It's all of it.
This morning you were just another archaeologist exploring an ancient pyramid.
Just another archaeologist. Yeah.
Now you're 300 years in the future trying to convince a madman
not to blow up the sun. Some days you wish you
just stayed in bed. And I downloaded an emulator
of it. But I don't know why I have no emulator program. But anyway we can play Secrets of the Luxor.
Explore Dr. Osiris more fully. See if he's worth
trying to explore in an IP sense. I bet he. First of all we know he is.
But of course we need to watch. Or play. Excuse me. Not just watch.
This is. I wish
this had worked in some sort of way. I mean is there really like
I know we're simplifying it but is there a way if
everything was just better would it have stuck around in a way where it was like you can't
get rid of this. Or is just the nature of Vegas that everything is so disposable. That it's almost
impossible. Maybe then. Maybe if it was like due to the experiment
that like ultimately it's not a family destination. This is not a place to do
story rides. Yeah. Like that inherent footwear. I think this
could have worked. Maybe this you know this transforms Niagara Falls
and Myrtle Beach and all those cities where all the weird crap is.
It was just the wrong. It was the wrong market. But Drumble had to grab it while
he could. Much like an obelisk. See what power he could wield.
It is an admirable yeah. An admirable idea at the time.
If we're. The name Jim Grand Adventures
episode I brought up Blackjack rules. Hit stand. Double down. Cash out.
I think clearly the answer was double down. 100%.
Let's literally double. They didn't provide enough material to make us
care about Mac and Karina. They needed to do six attractions not three.
They should have added every year. They should have kept hitting and hitting
and hitting. And they should have gotten rid of the hotel rooms. Turn those into mazes.
You knock some of those out. Now there's nowhere for Tupac to stay. Maybe he changes his mind.
Doesn't come to Vegas. And we're still getting Tupac albums to this day. I mean we are
because he puts. He's the most prolific posthumous artist of all time. But I mean
actually new made by an alive Tupac. I think you've just yeah that's a future
that we can get behind. And if we had just gotten behind Douglas Trumbull's vision
that in his work like in his world you think
there were like every hotel had
interconnected like like you would see Mac in
different hotels in different contexts like you could believe this story into different
hotels. Yeah. Like in the grandest vision of everything.
It's a huge like Disney like see Disney not Disney see the theme park but
to see the organization which is decease. Now you go into a pre Rome universe
that was better than Rome and a future that uses Roman technology.
Right. And now Karina is in search of the column.
Of course the column. I'd love to see Mac help this would get the mag
Lev to help Karina find the column. The crossover potential
like the Avengers of the Vegas casino
universe. All different characters for each each one and then they all
get together and like they all meet up. Yeah. That experience
the slot machines and cheap drinks table games
shrimp cocktails that'll bring the people in you know. Yeah.
You got to give them something else to do. What do you do how do you make them stay with great
storytelling and the problem is there wasn't enough of this. They should have taken over
Mirage and that's about like a society of volcano people which
is that not kind of what Avatar 3 is going to be about. That is absolutely what it is.
I hope they would have gotten on that first that needy idea and then
like you know if they and if they didn't feel like well how are we going to come up
with all this volcano related mythology. Well it already exists. It's from the mind
of this writer Elrond Hubbard. Then you just plug in all the Dianetics
stuff. So now that's what I want. I want that it's 1998
and Douglas Trumbull is helping Elrond Hubbard achieve
his perfect cinematic three rides that tell the story of Dianetics.
You go into the volcano verse with Mac and
Karina. And the New York skyline these are these were buildings built before
the people built New York. They were early societies that
the ancient New York the ancient old Orchians. The ancient Orchians.
I don't know why I dropped the Y. Sure. Orchians. And
eventually that roller coaster what do they get.
Well they get you know Samsung
touch phones in VR lenses and it's
aliens. Oh right. It does become an alien thing. Yeah.
It was always heading there. The Trumbull is not supporting Trumbull.
Trumbull should have had three rides a trilogy of rides in every single hotel.
And that is the reason. And then it wouldn't be a gambling city
anymore. It would be Trumbulltown. Trumbulltown. Trumbulltown.
Well this makes me hate Las Vegas. This makes me want to get out of there. I agree.
I'm not going to talk about it anymore. But it's too late we're stuck.
And thus you survived podcast the ride Sin City Nights.
I wish it was Trumbulltown. I wish they would have changed the name for him.
There was this brief time where they flirted with gambling and they
hadn't discovered the power of storytelling and the power of the obelisk. Oh yeah.
Dark times. Yeah. But as it stands
because they didn't do it the Luxor should absolutely fold into
itself. Yeah. Oh yeah. Disappear and take all of the
lost souls with it. Or spit them back up. Bring
spit Tupac out on your way into crumbling. Yeah. I mean I
was just looking at it. Specifically the UFOs above in 2012 were orbs.
So the orbs could also absorb the whole
Luxor and take it back to its home planet or they could blow it up too.
Or implode it. Well now I told my wife and
child they could come back in the door because we've been recording forever. So now I'm going to actually wrap
up while they come in and probably as she washes my son's hands. So
you survived podcast the ride Sin City Nights. Sin City theme courtesy of Mike Carlson.
Sin City Nights logo and current child care courtesy of the wonderful Aaron
Kertner. Keep up with PTR Sin City Nights on the bad socials like
X at podcast the ride. Oh yeah. We'll talk about what to do about that. More episodes
coming on the main strip. Bonus episodes on podcast the ride the Fremont Gate and our
high roller tier club three. You will find all of that at Patreon.com
slash podcast the ride. But for now all hail the
obelisk. All hail the obelisk.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page
on Facebook.