Club Three.
A blowout is what we're dealing with here.
That's what we're diving into here on podcast,
The Ride Club Three.
The only way you could describe what happened in the poll,
a blowout like you've never seen,
like frankly like you've never seen before.
Mike Jason, hi, welcome.
Hi.
It's very flattering, it's very flattering
when people wanna know about our personal,
our continuity, our personal continuity.
Well, I mean, is it still when it's about
our personal embarrassments,
at least in your case's personal embarrassments.
I see it differently.
I see the audience thinks of us now as fictional characters,
like the great fictional characters,
like Atticus Finch or Jay Gatsby.
They think of us now in that way,
and they just wanna know about our trials and tribulations.
So, sometimes it's hard, they're not even thinking about,
oh, we're gonna have to make one of the hosts
bring up some really like unpleasant memories
or memories where he was an idiot or failed or whatever.
Like they've unlocked secret texts seemingly.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, wow, did you know this one never got published?
Well, it's getting published today.
Yeah, it is.
Just stats wise, interesting from the perspective of,
I was like, I knew this was the biggest victor by far,
but I didn't know that the whole time
we've been doing these Club 3 polls,
no topic has ever gotten more than 50% of the vote.
This, we're dealing with 67.
Wow.
Over two thirds.
It's not quite rushing.
It's not quite Reagan winning reelection, I don't think,
as far as popular vote.
I can't remember, maybe it is.
Close to, it's yet similar.
Yeah, similar.
Marvel Adventure City in Niagara Falls
only carried Wisconsin.
Is that the correct state?
I don't remember where we're on, Dale.
But yeah, way ahead.
So, we'll get into our mandate here,
but the runner-up, cartoon all-stars to the rescue
from 1990, the somewhat notorious anti-drug video
starring all of our favorite cartoon characters of the time,
or at least the ones that Disney
or the other companies would loan.
Yeah.
And of course, President George Bush,
to keep things in the political.
Keep things exciting.
Yeah.
So yeah, hey, that's tailor-made for us, could be great.
Back at 12% behind.
I think that's the lowest runner-up number.
Wow.
But yeah, could be a good one.
If you got anything else, suggest it,
and we'll see if we can beat it,
but that'll be the incumbent for the next one.
Wow.
But for now, we dive into, I mean, okay, on the poll,
we called it Jason's Food Service Adventures
featuring Mike's Big Story.
Oh, I didn't write down who suggested it.
My apologies.
I know there's like a couple of people nominated it.
I credit Aaron within the episode with saying,
hey, let's maybe do the stories episode.
Let's combine them.
Stories made it, thanks to whoever officially
did the nomination, but now we're here.
That featuring designation, I don't mean to downplay
anything that Jason's about to bring to the table.
No, not at all, please.
No, that's the main event.
That's what I feel.
Yeah, I was gonna say, it feels like the feature
that might overtake the main artist.
This is the Nicki Minaj on Monster.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It could, I don't know.
I mean, it's up to you.
It's hey, it's your shot, only you can tell us.
But it is it's Starship featuring Mickey Thomas.
Is it like, is the Mickey Thomas,
maybe he thinks he's a big draw there,
but I would still say the Starship,
the idea of Starship and playing all the Jefferson Airplane
songs and stuff, that might be more appealing
to a lot of people than just hearing Mickey Thomas say.
Well, yeah, maybe sometimes the featuring can be
kind of a sad assertion of your own power.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, featuring can be all kinds of things.
But that being said, it's gonna feel like
it's what we gotta build to.
Yeah, I agree.
And I think that we, let's just go in that order
and let's dive into Jason's Food Service Adventures.
As uncovered in the last episode, if he somehow missed it,
Aaron said the word waffle while discussing
a okay breakfast at the Vegas Rainforest Cafe.
And then that split us off.
And this whole world of Jason, we had no idea about
making waffles in his college as part of a work study.
It was only because it was like one to one.
It's like, oh, I've made waffles before.
No, it wasn't a tangent.
Yeah, yeah, you were speaking from expertise.
Never, never, you don't ever have to explain
why you brought up the fact that you were making waffles.
No, don't apologize.
Never apologize.
We celebrate that this was brought up.
Never having to apologize for bringing out
how you made waffles in college.
Waffle complications, yeah.
Yeah, so I mean, I guess just to explain,
I, like a lot of people who went to college,
had a work study assignment and a part-time.
That is that there is some money guaranteed here,
money knocked off tuition, assuming that you do this gig.
Yes, so you do the gig and you get paid hourly
and you put it towards living expenses, books.
Okay, okay.
And I was probably mostly buying
takeout calzones and comic books.
Was everybody a freshman?
What's the amount?
What's the amount that you gave freshman 15?
I was gonna say 40, I thought that was overshooting.
Freshman 40.
No, freshman 40.
I gave freshman 40 during the first year of baby,
I feel like, but not in college.
No, no, you look for that.
I actually lost weight freshman year
because Ithaca is so elevated, the campus is in a hill
and there's so much declines, inclines and stairs and stuff.
That would have been me if I went to Pepperdine.
I remember the right of my school, Loyola Mary Mount.
That is a very like in the Malibu Hills.
I think you're on stairs nonstop.
So, okay, okay, so you like naturally worked some stuff off.
Or at least broke even
because ice cream counter at dinner every night.
Calzones, wait, that's a good question.
What is like the worst thing?
Because getting to college is a big,
and I imagine for all of us,
sure there's getting to go drink and your parents are gone,
but maybe more like, you mean I can get this
in the cafeteria all the time?
Mine was that they had bread bowls.
I would get just like bread bowls and clam chowder
too often.
Like not a thing to have.
You eat the whole bread bowl?
Yeah, thanks for the meal.
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't shock me.
Yeah, all right, no, I think not that I-
This is funny.
Like bread bowls in the last decade I've had,
if that, are at California Adventure.
California Adventure.
Yeah, yeah.
And even then I'm like, I'm doing a couple of dips
and I'm still leaving that bottom,
but in college I'm devouring that bread bowl.
I, the first semester,
I think I was definitely trying everything.
So like I would talk to my dad or whatever on Sundays.
And I was like, oh yeah, I just ate dinner.
I had half a slice of pizza, half a cheeseburger,
some pasta, a salad, like not finishing everything,
but just trying to be like,
trying to figure out what's good.
Like the very hungry caterpillar.
Like the very-
To talk about kids' books that were,
is that it, or Hungry Little Caterpillar?
I don't remember, something like that.
Yeah.
I read it and I don't remember the name.
I was home visiting recently
and my mom had found some old like kids' books.
And I forget the exact name of this book,
maybe you guys know,
but she said it without the context.
Like I was, I didn't know she found the books
or I didn't see it.
And she's like, oh, did you see the hungry stranger?
And I was like, do you mean outside?
And she's like, no, the book, it's on the floor over there.
And it's like, oh, I think it was a kid's book
called The Case of the Hungry Stranger or something.
No, there wasn't a hungry stranger outside your house.
Like you're not getting in on your family dinner.
Any pies getting left out today?
I mean, that'd be you more than it'd be a stranger.
Exactly.
So I worked work study in the one big dining hall
at college at Ithaca.
The dining hall was mostly run by work study students.
I will say primarily poorly trained work study students
and then actual like union employee,
like union prep cooks, like, who know what they're doing.
People who know what they're doing,
who are then given 18 year olds with no training.
Like I didn't know about, I don't quite know how,
do you know the concept of like shift meal or crew meal?
You explained this last time
that you had to get there early.
I had to get there half an hour before
and I clocked in early and then you eat,
but that means you didn't really get a lunch break.
And I think this is a restaurant industry thing.
Yeah.
I used to, I film weddings sometimes
and there'd be like, okay, well everybody like.
Oh, everyone eat at once.
Yeah, or like all the way at the end or whatever.
Anyway, sure.
Okay.
So you're making lifelong friends, I'm sure.
Lifelong friends, everyone I rate,
a lot of people either sleep deprived or hungover
and just hustling for that six or $7 an hour in 2003 money.
God, is that what it was?
Yeah.
So, so not a lot of training.
So the first semester I was assigned like
Saturday morning shift, like Saturday brunch
and no one's in good shape Saturday mornings.
Like.
Oh wait, I was gonna ask how many days a week
you're doing this.
I just did it like the one day a week, the first semester
and then the second semester I did two days a week.
And like two days a week dinner shift,
which kind of sucked.
It was just the way my classes were.
All my classes were early.
So I had the nights free and that was too often
to be working at the dining hall.
Okay, yes.
Yeah.
So you're dreading the end that you're working
Saturday morning, the thing nobody wants to be doing.
Yes.
In college.
And let me, okay, some things that were established
in the last one, this is as far as we made it.
And then I kind of, I re-listened to know like
what stories were left and teased.
It mainly came up because you were a little waffle maker
with a little hat and a little apron.
Yes.
This would require you to deal with a nasty syrup vat
is what you said you do.
You do not like the consistency of the.
Yeah, I mean, if you pay attention in any cafeteria
dining hall setting like that, you realize like,
oh, that they're making omelets with a vat of eggs,
of scrambled eggs.
Like that is not cracked fresh.
Like better to ask for an egg over easy
where they have to crack it fresh, you know?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Oh, this is similar in like some,
I've been staying at Embassy Sweets,
which I recommend the brand.
I like Embassy Sweets. Sure.
But you get free breakfast, but that vat of eggs.
That is not fresh. Tread carefully.
Tread carefully.
But you also, I've been surprised that Embassy Sweets
have the like actual omelet bar.
Oh really? Just as a free, yeah.
So that's, yeah, you wanna watch them make your,
they'll make the same thing.
They'll just make you scrambled eggs.
Right, but sure. You don't wanna go out of that
that egg beaters egg, but what a horrendous.
I can't imagine. Pretty nasty.
Is anybody into egg beaters somehow out there?
I prefer them weirdly.
I don't, there's gotta be somebody.
Someone out there. Yeah, yeah.
I don't know. Maybe it's just a weird thing with me.
It also, it mainly sparked our interest
that you would come home with pockets full of cups and forks.
Yeah, just like cleaning up.
Like they would give you like,
people would leave stuff on counters or like,
oh, if you see something dirty, clean it up and stuff.
And you're just kinda like grabbing stuff or cleaning up
or like they kept giving me utensils to like scrape off
excess waffle from the things.
The cups and forks I think was in sophomore year,
one semester pretty much the whole time.
I was in the dish room.
You know, the conveyor belt that you put like your tray on
and plates on, I was on the other side, like pulling it off.
Oh my God.
Which was. I cannot imagine you doing this.
It's unusually meditative, but it's like hell on earth.
It's the most humid place imaginable.
I can't, I just, I just picture the airplane gag
with the sweat, like just pouring down your head.
That semester I left covered in flop sweat every shift.
Yeah, I think I know exactly what this looked like.
Not that this is a fun job that anyone would like
or that anyone wouldn't feel stressed about.
I just can't imagine you just do constantly pulling dishes
for like hours and hours.
Well, cause you just like are dumping them
and then they go through a cleaning vat.
And then the actual like full-time,
like people who run this room
and like run the back of the house,
they are doing the actual work.
So they let the 18, 19 year olds do the brainless stuff.
Funny I say brainless stuff
cause the worst part of that semester
there was this guy who I was in a bunch of classes with
and he, bless his heart, he was so dumb
and he just talked so much.
So those shifts sometimes felt twice as long.
Oh boy.
Cause I'm just sweating, dehydrated, like,
and then just this, like, I just like a Looney Tunes,
the mobsters on Looney Tunes, the little mobster
and his doofy henchmen.
It was like working with one of the doofy henchmen.
What did they sound like?
Does it, do you recall the,
if you had to do an impression of that character,
I'm trying to remember.
Oh, we gotta get him George.
Oh, right, right.
Like that kind of.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which way did he, well, that's the dog, right?
Which way did he go George?
Which way did he go?
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Is he, did he mean well?
Like he's trying to pass the time?
Was he talking about his life or what you're doing?
I could never tell.
You were very rude to him.
No, I gave him the benefit of that so many times
and then I was just like,
there is another 90 minutes left in this shift
and he's still going.
My God.
But the, I think the position I worked,
I did scoop ice cream once or twice.
Oh yeah, we, yes, this came up a little bit
and was left unflashed out, I think.
You got, you being an ice cream scooper.
It turned out like more uneventful than you would think.
I think the thing that stuck with me is that like.
What do you think we were picturing?
Oh, me just killing a gallon?
Like we just.
Oh, like one scoop for you.
One scoop for me.
Yeah.
But like the thing that I didn't realize
until the very end of the shift, it's like,
oh right, we have to clean all this up
and there is like a toppings bar
and as much as I love marshmallow syrup,
like marshmallow goo, like you have to get
some elbow grease going to scrape that stuff off.
Yeah, you nodded to that.
Is that just, I can't even picture like marshmallow sauce.
That's just, it's kind of.
It's just a little and it's just a little.
It's a little thick.
Marshmallow goo.
A little runny, yeah.
The ice cream came after your,
you were shifted to ice cream after the incident
where you cut yourself. Stabbed myself.
Yes.
And scarred yourself permanently.
Can you show us that?
Is that clear?
I have to get closer to you maybe.
There's a small white scar right here on my, like.
Okay.
So not insane.
I have a college related scar from not my own college,
but from visiting a friend at USC
and then like being in a pool area we weren't supposed to
and then suddenly getting caught, like, oh, they're coming.
The security guards are coming
and then having to scale a fence.
Oh my God.
With pointy tops.
And I got impaled.
Oh yeah.
And was like, if you can imagine,
pretty inebriated for this.
So I think not until the next morning did I realize like,
ooh, I'm going to be looking at that mark for years.
I think it's gone now,
but I would say for like three years I had,
it was like akin to that.
Yeah.
Maybe it's still there if you look close,
but those are, yeah, hey, college is scarring time,
I guess, if you're dumb.
Although do you, how do you rate your own?
Because you, you're slicing meat,
you're wearing the like the falconer glove.
Well, I'm wearing like a latex glove
and then the chain mail glove and then another latex glove.
And like, I don't, they told me to do that,
but it kind of didn't make sense to me
and it probably didn't help my grip.
Again, everything kind of poorly trained.
There was like a handful of full-time managers
and they couldn't have been older than 30, these people,
but one or two of them had such a stick up their ass.
Like, if you have time to lean,
you have time to clean, sort of asshole.
Okay, okay.
And that's, I was gonna say that I think the position
that I got into the most antics was this semester
I worked at the pizza and pasta counter.
Oh my God. Okay, all right, great.
So.
I don't think we did any of this.
Here we go, let's go.
Let's go.
So it was always like one or two employees
and then this guy, this older guy,
who I have no idea,
I cannot still to this day place his accent.
Like he could be Italian
or he could have escaped a Soviet block country
and like the CIA would really like to talk to him.
But he was really-
It's from the nation of generica.
Yeah, he really was very brusque
and he took making the shitty pizza very seriously
and the shitty pasta.
Like that was within the first week of school.
I'm like, okay, pizza and pasta lost cause.
Like this shit is not good.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
And so he could be very jovial,
but he was usually annoyed
probably because he had to watch 18 and 19 year olds so much.
So the pretty early on,
I think the most notable thing I did
was attempt to pick up a vat of marinara sauce
and very quickly drop it on the floor.
And the floor is now covered in marinara sauce.
Is this public facing floor or backstage?
Oh, this is public facing by the way.
If you had to put a equivalent like on your own height,
how much of your body is the vats?
How big is the vat?
I would say the vat is maybe like a foot deep.
Okay, wow.
Like this is a sizable thing.
And I think I probably just didn't use enough
of admit circular and it was just hot, hot, hot.
And then I just.
You just said no choice, this has to go.
This has to go.
Okay.
And.
Jason, oh man.
How much would you love to see Jason spilling a big fan
of marinara sauce?
Oh, it's all I want in this life.
No one is telling us how to do these jobs.
No one's telling us.
The one time I worked like in the prep kitchen,
the guy's like, okay, we're gonna chop these mushrooms.
So here's how you do this.
To prevent a cutting board from sliding,
you fold a towel and put it on the cutting board.
And then you chop the mushroom until you can chop it.
Like chop it in half, turn the flat,
and then just chop it fast.
And I was like, these are valuable skills to have
that I have not acquired in other roles.
So, towel under the cutting board,
if anyone's having trouble,
you're heading where it's sliding around.
That's a good tip.
That's a good tip for cooking at home.
But this thing, just like, how do you,
it's just go, go get it.
Go pick it up.
Go get it.
Start a fire, basically.
You know?
So, right next to the pizza and pasta,
I think I had some very good, like, specialized kitchens.
In the other dining hall, there was a vegan kitchen.
Kind of the first I ever encountered, like, vegan cuisine.
And that was nice,
because no matter what garbage they were serving,
you could always get sweet potato fries.
So, that's pretty nice.
And then next to the pizza and pasta
was the kosher kitchen.
So, everything prepared kosher.
They used their own, I think it was all disposable,
plates and forks and stuff.
And so, the food, a little better,
a little more, like, freshly made and stuff.
Notable, I remember the first time, like,
trying, like, a falafel pita.
I was like, oh, that looks really good.
And they're like, oh, we'll wrap one up for you.
But the one night, I specifically remember this,
because they had, like, a giant tray of chocolate eclairs.
And I was like, oh, boy, those eclairs,
I call it, it looks so good.
And they're like, well, here, take one,
put it under there, you know,
because that was the big rule.
They did not teach us how to do much,
but they said, don't eat on the job.
That was the one thing, like, okay, fine.
So, I had placed a chocolate eclair, like, under the,
like, where we put our backpacks and stuff.
And boy, that shift was slow,
and that eclair was calling my name.
I love it.
Jason, come down here.
Hold on, real quick.
I just like, you saying, maybe I'm wrong,
but you saying eclair instead of eclair,
you're saying it almost like Slim Pickens would say it,
which I'm really enjoying.
I'm an eclair.
I love chocolate eclair.
And I'm loving it, so.
Like an etart.
Yeah.
Hi, yeah, it's just probably the, you know,
South Philly trash dialect.
Keep saying it like that.
It's fine.
And I was like, no one is,
I haven't seen a manager in ages.
Oh man, you're gonna be bad in this.
The old guy could not give a shit.
He's just leaning, like, no one has come by for Pete.
Like, so I crouch down and I kind of like hide,
and I go to take a bite, and it's like almost in my mouth,
and I feel a tap on my shoulder.
And I turn around and it's being like,
This is so good.
Shit, manager.
And he's like, throw it away.
Throw it out.
And I was like, you gotta be kidding me.
Oh no, but throwing it now, we're gonna waste it?
Yeah, so now he tossed it.
And like.
Not giving it a good home.
And so, and of course by that point,
like they were done next door,
or they were shutting down, or like.
So I was just like, you motherfucker.
I can't believe you.
Oh, what a dramatic, you're almost there.
You're like preparing your mouth.
You could see the cartoon closeups.
You could see your mouth unfurl like a little red carpet.
I'm sorry, your tongue unfurl.
Like, blip, blip, blip, blip, blip.
Almost, and then like you're almost like getting
chocolate mist, it's like cringling.
It is so, it was like so aggravating.
All these stories are like three panel
Beatle Bailey comic strips.
Where it's like he's working in the kitchen,
and then something, like one ends with him
spilling marinara, this one ends with like him,
like maybe this is more of a Sunday one,
and it's like six panels.
And he's like, kind of like nothing's going on,
and he glances over, he sees the eclair over there.
He's thinking about it, he doesn't wanna do it,
and then he goes and gets it, and then Sarge comes in.
So you're proposing like maybe a little like,
I was out here, go ahead.
Oh yeah, no, Sarge for sure.
Because like the other employees did not give a shit.
The Kocher kitchen guys were the nicest,
and they were always wrapping stuff,
like oh here, I'll wrap it in foil,
take it to go, take it back to the dorm.
But would you think they would have been upset
if you ate on the job?
They don't give a shit, no, they didn't care.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure, 100% sure.
But you never did in their presence,
you never saw them eating.
They were happy, no, they were just,
they were thrilled, you know.
They weren't aware of the draconian nature.
They weren't aware of the action.
It was their own operation.
I was gonna say, you're probably proposing,
I don't know, maybe for any enterprising artists out there,
illustrators or comic drawers,
that it's like a con, like I leave it to you to name it,
but what's in my head is like something's cooking.
And so like starring Jason.
If you just do these high jar,
like does it inspire other little misadventures,
however you want it to be?
Yeah, it could be, I mean, it starts very simply probably.
Depends how much space we can get in the paper,
first of all,
because it could be just single panel for a while,
and then on Sundays, it goes three panels or six panels.
Yeah, but you know, I think it does beg like a close up,
at least, you know,
because that's what I'm picturing.
I wanna see that distance between,
the micro distance between a Claire and mouth.
Yeah, that's true.
You would wanna get some more like,
sort of real feeling like real time was going on with that,
because that's sort of the fun of that beat.
That's so sad.
And maybe as I was to do that,
the Claire is talking to you, is like calling to you,
or like, or that you're like,
yeah, your little like dream bubble is the a Claire with,
like, you know, like a sexy human eyelash,
like fluttering eyelashes.
I want you Jason.
Buzzing me a Claire.
Shoving up some dough pockets.
Hey, sure.
I mean, look, well, they print the paper,
might not print that,
that might have to be for just the collected edition.
Yeah, that's for the Santa crap.
That's for the art comics.
That's for the art comics,
but something's cooking is a good idea.
Maybe we should just do it.
I don't know.
See if King features is interested.
I like that you had so much experience
with so many different genres of food.
Yeah, I, the best, you know, job,
I think the job everyone wanted
was just carting people into the dining hall,
because you just sat and you could like,
do homework or like,
Just a greeter.
Read, yeah.
And so I did do that like once
at the like back door of this dining hall,
and I didn't do like anything for like two hours.
And then they eventually, I think they're like,
Oh, we can lock that door.
We don't need people coming in there too.
No one comes in there.
And I'm like, oh damn it.
No, no.
The cake position.
You also, you teased a story of getting yelled at
by an unpleasant man.
Is that what you just described?
That was the eclairs story.
Yeah, yeah.
Cause I wasn't sure,
cause I didn't sound like there was a yelling in there.
It was more of a, of a, of a humiliating tap tap.
I, yeah, I, I, he looked so,
and looking back again,
that man could not have been older than 30,
but like he just had the worst like Oxford shirt
from Sears tucked into two tight khakis.
Like, oh yeah.
Do you, anything, if anyone were to draw this,
is there anything, you know,
they could use their imagination, I think,
to create this Sarge-esque character,
but is there any other physical attributes just to get it?
It was a black apron and kind of a blue,
not dissimilar from the shirt I'm wearing now.
Like blue denim, a chambray shirt.
But like, did this guy have anything on his, on his face?
Was there like a unibrow or a wore?
I feel like he always had a dumb ass lanyard on.
I feel like he was a guy who like-
Not when they had his ID?
Like his own lanyard?
I feel like he was wearing,
no, I feel like it might've been an ID.
You know when you work someplace with key cards
and they're like,
and wear it around your neck all the time.
Like he took that seriously.
Both people- Like an IT guy.
Like there are two, two or three
are just shoving it in their pocket.
Like this guy was like-
Wearing it proudly.
I'm part of this army.
Huh.
Well, yeah, I'd like to see more of this,
like to hear more.
Does that sort of cover the main adventures?
That I think covers it.
Yeah, I did find out like,
I was just reading about like,
if a good news and the college apparently took full,
like they used to use contractors,
Sodexo or Cisco or these big food supply monopoly.
Like they took it over and run it themselves now.
So hopefully it's cheaper for students
and better for employees.
I think they just carried all the employees over,
but they work directly for the college now.
And it seemed much more pleasant
than the like faceless corporation,
food slop corporation that I worked for.
I don't know.
I hope it's better.
I hope so.
I never had to work it, but I, just seeing it,
you go, these people are working very hard.
Much harder than we're working.
Yeah.
Supposed hard jobs.
Yeah, no kidding.
Well, thank you for sharing your full adventures.
Sure.
There's more to come in the funny pages.
Mike, have you been over there just going like,
I hope this drags out.
I hope this is too long.
We have to do a second night.
This is the like,
Yeah, it's, yeah.
You've been delaying this event.
You've kicked this down the curb a couple of times.
What happened is,
what happened with this story is that
it sort of got built up too much.
I was hoping it would just kind of come out one day.
Cause I think I've pin,
there's an element of the story we'll get to
where I pinpointed a specific ride.
And I was like, oh, maybe it will just,
I'll just sort of tell it in a 15 minute,
10 minute version on that episode.
But now it's grown to this point where I feel like
I have to give a lot of context and it's sort of,
it's grown in anticipation.
So probably the way in which it's told
has to expand as well.
Like become this, it has to, you know,
it was maybe going to be like a part of a seven minute
standup set, but now you have to make this like a big
Now it's a story.
Now it's a Henry Rollins storytelling hour.
Yes, it is a, it's like Henry Rollins storytelling hour.
And I have been rolling it around in my head now
for a few weeks.
I guess I should give a lot of context for things
and really explain it.
Cause I want to bring you into the world of Young Me.
You like half mentioned this,
it was kind of a crowded Club 3 episode
and it didn't feel like the time.
And then it kept, and I think it's only existed
in Club 3.
Maybe, yeah.
This has just been going, I think, I think all in 2023.
It's been alluded to in like three, four episodes,
as you said, built up too much.
I don't know.
We were walking, I think Scott,
we were walking to the Holiday Inn pre-pandemic.
And I believe I said to you one, I go,
I just thought of a story that's sort of tied
to Disney World.
Oh.
And I think I said that, and I go,
yeah, eventually I'll tell that somewhere.
And I think that's like,
cause I had even thought of it for a long time.
Jeez.
So it's been- Pre-pandemic.
It's been going since then.
That hotel's not even called that anymore.
Did we go to BJ's or something?
Maybe we were at BJ's and we walked to the Holiday Inn
or something.
And I remember saying-
The crazy nights at BJ's,
you're going to forget a lot of stories.
That's true.
They got all those different beers, Jason.
And the deep dish pizzas.
And don't forget the Pizzouki's.
Mainly that, if you're in a Pizzouki fog,
that's really when you'll forget stuff.
Okay, so I've sort of talked a little bit about
high school and my fear of intimacy.
I guess that's what it was.
Despite being now one of your favorite virtues
in a theme park.
Yeah, exactly.
So, you know, like many people, you're like,
I want a girlfriend.
I want to kiss some girls.
That's what I want to do.
But when you're also extremely scared of it,
you are not necessarily making decisions
that will help you accomplish your goal.
If that makes some sense.
So here's the thing.
Don't feel bad for me when you're listening to this story
because there were nice ladies,
nice girls who were interested
in being romantically involved with me.
And I would make every excuse in the book not to do it.
And I didn't know I was doing this.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Not consciously.
Did you do what I did in my type for a long time
when I was very, very young?
Was women who weren't interested in me?
Yes, that was so safe.
What a safe thing to do.
Because you'd never have to actually engage.
Yes, of course.
So this is what I did at the start of high school.
Very early, I picked one person
who I'd never spoken with before
and decided that's who I should date.
And then I never spoke to her
except for sending a note to ask to go to a dance.
This is insane behavior.
And in what universe was I going to go to a dance
with somebody who I'd never had a class with?
Wow.
And is that a level of-
Obviously it could have.
I think it's kinda cute.
It is cute.
All of this is cute.
Don't get me wrong, it's cute.
But as I relive it, I'm just like,
what if you're fucking idiot?
What's wrong?
You didn't actually want it on some level.
I completely relate. Of course.
I delayed dating, wanted to, of course,
but I hid in this long distance relationship
where I only saw the girl a week of a year
and nothing was ever really accomplished in that.
So I get it, I don't completely need to.
Someone needed to be like,
a female needed to be like, dude, here's the deal.
Here's how this goes.
Here's how kissing works.
Like somebody just needed to be like,
it's not that big of a deal.
Don't worry, calm down.
Don't worry about it.
I needed someone to go like, okay,
this is hard to tell the teenagers, do less.
Stop talking.
You needed to be- And ask questions.
You know who you need.
Just ask a lot of questions and stop for the love of God.
You needed like a Natasha Leoni from Can't Hardly Wait
where she tells Seth Green,
she's much cooler and much more mature than he is.
And so she's just like, dude, here's the deal.
Stop being an idiot.
This is what's going on. Calm down.
It's also a lot to,
that's also like a fantasy.
I feel very similar to you where I was like,
yeah, if only some, okay.
Somebody else made me comfortable.
Here's all I needed, girlfriend and a different
like really confident girl to take me over as a project
so that I can get a girlfriend.
Of course, it's crazy.
All I needed were these two girls to participate
in my little- Of course, it's wrong.
A friend though, there was a girl a year or two ahead of us
and she did kind of do that to my friend
and it gave me the creeps.
Like she had the worst vibes.
Well, certainly what I'm describing also could be bad.
It could be a bad situation.
She just had terrible vibes and I was just like,
why is she hanging out with these 14 girls so much?
Well, that's a different dynamic
than I'm actually talking about.
She was all 15 or 16, but like-
Well, okay, that's not so, it's not 19.
But she just had a weird like aloof energy
and it just gave me the creeps.
Okay, well, I don't know this person,
so I can't comment on the creeps.
I don't even remember their name.
We had people that were like dating like in,
when they were 17, like a 20 year old
who would come to the dances and we knew that was weird.
We knew that was bad.
So, and it was not like, he was not like,
oh, I met him in high school and now he graduated
and we're still dating.
It was like, I met this DJ outside of high school.
Cool job, dad.
Yeah. Stiddy.
I knew someone who, when we were seniors,
she was dating a guy who graduated a year ahead of us,
but he was a college freshman and he was in a fraternity
and she would be like, yeah, I spent the weekend
at the frat and I'm like, that's really weird.
Like, I don't, that doesn't sit right with me.
And also he's kind of a drip.
Like he's not really- A drip.
He was just kind of like a wet noodle.
Like he wasn't really handsome or jacked
and he wasn't very smart.
He's an absolute drip.
What are you doing with that drip?
I like the idea that you're like being catty
about everybody in high school.
You're like, that guy's a drip.
Oh, well, our favorite-
I don't like the vibes on that girl.
I did not like, I, you know, I think some of my friends
like drank and smoked whatever, 2000s,
Philly dirt weed was available.
But like, it seemed like me and my friends in high school,
everyone's favorite pastime was just being
recreationally mean to each other.
Yeah, that's what we did too.
Too smart for our own good.
We were like a little on our high horse, like, oh, you know,
we don't drink or whatever.
But like we were just mean to each other.
And then we were like, we both backyard wrestled,
we fake fought each other.
And then we would fight each other all the time.
We would like just fight.
That's healthier.
Healthier than what?
Than what?
Than not, than going like, you know,
being mean to each other,
like getting physical aggression out.
I think it's more particular.
I don't know.
It depends, it depends what it is.
I, you know.
We would fight, like we would like get into like
30 minute long UFC style without,
we would say like, don't punch each other in the face.
But everything else was sort of on the table.
Not like hitting each other in the dick, I guess.
But other than that, and it's like, we were all just like,
we had a lot of energy and no one hit a girlfriend
at the time, at least.
Eventually a couple of these guys would,
which I'll get into in a few minutes.
Now they won't punch me anymore.
Yeah.
They're too busy getting.
We were all corny.
So we were fighting each other,
is sort of what was happening.
Look, Fight Club was huge on DVD.
That's true.
You had to.
I mean, 30 minutes.
I remember like looking at the clock after we were done,
cause we would make each other tap out.
We would literally make each other quit.
Wow.
So like, I look at the clock and I'm like covered in sweat.
And I'm like, we've been fighting
for 30 minutes on the floor.
We've been like amateur wrestling forever.
This is strange.
This is a strange piece of the puzzle.
Yeah.
I don't think I knew these details.
We would fight like, and there was definitely like
a hierarchy, there was a ranking sort of unofficially of like,
well, this guy always loses.
Everyone beat this friend of ours.
And then this guy's, I think I told this story before.
My one friend who would beat us constantly
in this amateur UFC fight style match.
I told a real amateur wrestler
on the wrestling team in high school.
I go, you know, my friend Ryan, he could beat you.
And he goes, he can't.
He doesn't, I'm like good at amateur wrestling.
That's what I've been doing for years.
I go, no, no, no, no.
He's really good.
I'm sure he could beat you.
And I was like, hey, Ryan, you gotta,
I think the other guy's name was Ryan.
You have to fight him.
You should do it.
And so we did it in somebody's backyard.
And my friend Ryan got concussed.
Jesus.
You made this happen.
He fell.
He got like, he got taken down.
He hit his head on the grass, probably got a concussion,
bit into his tongue as well.
So he was bleeding from the mouth.
That being said, he beat him.
He won.
So I was right.
But I caused my friend to get a concussion, which I don't,
I'm not happy about.
That's not good.
So he, I mean, that's an odd way to define winning.
Certainly.
That's fair.
But he was very good at wrestling.
He could have been amateur wrestling.
But what measure, if you get concussed,
and then how do you, are you also still the winner?
Well, he made him tap out.
Okay.
He put him in an arm bar and he made him tap out.
Okay, okay.
He tapped out.
So even much like a SummerSlam 2000 or 2001,
Kurt Angle had a concussion.
He still finished the match.
My friend finished the match and he made him tap out.
So anyway, this is sort of what was happening.
And then we were very like, oh yeah, we don't drink.
We don't blah, blah, blah, blah.
And it's like, I'm not,
I don't think we should have been like drinking guys
who were just like carousing.
And there's always a bad vibe when it's like a 16 year old
who knows too well how to like hook up.
Yeah.
Like that is bad usually.
That's like creepy.
I'm not saying having a boyfriend or girlfriend is weird,
but like there's the guys who get too mature.
And I feel like that's bad news in that way.
That being said, if we had a beer
and we could kiss a girl once in a while,
I think we might've had a better time.
I think we might've been a little more relaxed.
I think so.
No, Grant, I was not, I can't say I was,
I didn't start drinking until I think I was 17.
And actually, I don't know
because I was drinking just like shit vodka,
just like blackout.
Like I was drinking so poorly,
it kind of left me like emotionally all over the map.
I, the year that I decided I drink and smoke weed
and smoke cigarettes, now I was definitely,
that was a miserable year.
So you could be rough.
Like until I knew how to do it, it wasn't good.
There's a lot of factors there.
But the high horse about not is interesting.
Yeah, I don't think, like I remember my one friend
when he heard that I drank at age 20 was still like,
what is he doing?
Wow.
Yeah, I was a little in this territory too, here and there.
Yeah.
And obviously like,
Were you all, were you like scared of it?
Yes.
Yeah.
Everything is fear.
When my friend started smoking cigarettes in front of me,
terror.
Am I supposed, do I have to do that?
Will it kill me after I have one?
Yeah.
And obviously like there's scary elements to all that stuff.
Obviously kids were like doing stupid stuff
and getting in trouble.
So it's not like there was no danger there,
but yes, there was mostly fear in general.
Things like the potential Next Club 3 cartoon all-stars
to the rescue, things like that made us feel like either,
if you try anything, you are hardcore addicted.
Yeah.
The idea that you could just like kind of casually ride
drinking or drug use was just never.
And I get, I know that's complicated to experience.
It's not the message you want to give to a 10, 11 year old,
but as soon as once we all got there, like, oh,
this can be part of your life and it does not have to make
you an absolute mess.
Yeah. Well that, yeah, that's, it's hard to think.
Like nuanced lessons are hard for kids.
Yeah.
And then they oftentimes don't do that nuanced lesson
and that makes kids reject it.
So I don't know how to teach kids anything.
No.
Cause we had so many like,
Good luck to us huh?
No, I know.
We've had a lot of discussions about date.
Like how are we going to do?
I don't know how to explain any of this.
I got no plan for anything past tomorrow.
Well that's what, that is what happens the day the baby's born
because you think, oh, I'm going to plan or whatever.
I'm going to man.
No, no, no, no, no.
No time for shit.
There's no time to plan.
Oh, what's happening today?
Okay.
Let me just muddle through it.
Like that's really how it works.
Better though.
As you're an over thinker, I'm some degree of an over thinker.
Yeah.
I don't know how to talk to girls and it's 2004.
I don't know why they're wearing dresses over jeans.
I don't know what's going on.
So yeah.
So, so, so much of it was fear that we're like,
this girl like asking me to a dance
and I'm like trying everything to get out of it.
And I'm like, well, this isn't the,
this isn't the bride I chose six months ago.
Like just weird, like weird stuff.
And I'll always try to find like a reason
why stuff's not going my way.
And it's all, yeah, all fear-based
and it's not, there's, there were plenty of people
who probably at a, there weren't as many.
And I think there wasn't, it sounds cocky or something.
There were a handful of girls who would be like,
she's interested in, didn't you?
Have I told you this story?
My friend who broke up with his girlfriend,
who he said at the time when he was going out with her,
he goes, you know what?
She says you're not as cute as me, but you're really cute.
And I go, oh, okay.
And then I went to, after they broke up,
I went to like her empty house for off-campus lunch
for like six months with her.
And?
Nothing. Nothing.
We ate lunch.
What?
We just ate lunch.
Whoa.
And it never even dawned on me till later
that her inviting me to this house over and over again,
was there might've been something going,
like she was thinking of something.
After month one, maybe she has lost.
Well, of course everyone lost.
They're like, what is, what's wrong with this guy?
Yeah, all right, I guess I won't put him in that.
Which is a theme.
Again, don't feel sorry for me in a way
that some people were feeling, you know,
like this is a completely impossible task.
When there were moments like this
or things that were happening in my life
where the opportunity was there
and I was just too afraid of it, which is fine.
So yeah, that's, I just, I wanna check my privilege here.
You had the privilege of two girls thinking you were cute,
but not as cute as someone else.
I'm just saying that's better than some other people.
And I acknowledge it.
Sure, sure.
So anyway, so I think, okay, it's,
I'm probably gonna get some things out of order
because I didn't wanna ask the people involved to clarify.
So.
Oh, give me the information, I'll ask.
Well, a lot of these people I'm friends with.
To whom it may concern.
A lot of these people I'm friends with, so.
But I still don't wanna ask.
I don't really wanna bring it up.
Although they would think it's funny.
So my friend's sister, who's a year younger than us,
all of a sudden starts showing interest in me
and wants to go to the prom with me.
And I hadn't really considered this per,
again, I'm still like stuck on this person
that I've never talked to that's rejected me once in a way.
Like that's still what I'm thinking.
Like one of these days, I'm gonna really show this lady
that I'm the guy for her or whatever.
Is she also like kind of like social status
that you're never gonna be in that?
No, actually not.
Really?
I should say this too.
We were not like, we were in like a sub,
we were not like dorks.
We were dorks, but we weren't like hardcore dorks
and we were not cool.
We were like chip on our shoulder guys
who thought we were better than everybody in some ways
for no reason.
There's really no, I don't know what we were up against.
No one really was doing anything.
But we did comedy stuff.
We made videos.
I was in a band.
And I'll say this right now.
In case this episode isn't satisfying to a lot of people,
I will play a track from the band I was in in high school
at the end of this episode.
Just in case you're like, this is kind of boring.
What's the name?
Carlson's story is second level.
That's right, right.
Oh, you're gonna drop at second level?
I'm gonna play Like the House at the end of this episode.
Oh wow.
Wow, what a dream.
So yeah, so that'll be played in case you were like,
this doesn't live up to expectations.
The second level drop and the song is?
Rock the House.
We talked about this in one of the episode with Kyle Mooney.
Yeah, that seems right.
Yeah.
I may have to, yeah, anyway, we'll hear it.
We'll hear it.
I don't know how I got to get this story.
You wrote some lyrics, I feel like.
I feel like he likes the vibe of second level.
I was listening to it again and I was like,
it sounds more like 311 even than it sounds like
right at Chili Peppers.
Wow.
That wets your whistle.
So my friend's sister all of a sudden sort of wants
to go to the prom with me.
And I'm interested, but I'm just like,
this is my friend's sister.
This is, I can't, this isn't right.
And like, again, all excuse fake stuff.
My friend has never even really like expressed
that he's mad about this or anything.
It's like a little weird, but ultimately it like takes,
I feel like I labored over this decision for weeks,
like confiding with people.
Is this the right thing to do?
What do we do?
A couple of things become clear later on.
One, there's only so many people in your high school period.
And two, this might be brainwrap from movies and TV.
That helps so much.
That certainly helps cloud a person who's afraid
because it's hard, like you're all,
you're like supposed to find a special person
and that's the person.
And if you really examine it, it's like,
obviously there are better choices for you than others,
but there are many people probably in the world
you could get along with.
There's not a magic unlocking the key
for this perfect person.
I took far too seriously because I was like,
oh, okay, well movies and TV has showed me
that you are friends with someone
and then eventually you confess your true feelings
a long time later.
And then eventually you realize like,
oh, movies and TV are written by neurotics
who had tough times in high school.
I see, I see.
There's probably some part also where there's like a mix up
where a lie is in play.
Yeah, you lie to me.
So things get all the way darkest
and then they come, so that they can reset
and then somewhere dramatic, like on a pier or something
that it all actually comes together.
Primatic lies so that we can show growth and forgiveness.
That's how the world lines up that way too, yeah.
Yeah, so that gives you a lot of cover
if you're afraid as to be like,
well, this isn't the person that came to me in a vision.
Like this isn't like God didn't set this,
like I just a bunch of nonsense.
Not that I ever actually actively thought that,
but I think that's part of it too.
So yeah, eventually I go, yeah, okay, yes,
we will go to prom, yes, we will go.
And it was still like, I wasn't even acknowledging
the reality of it being like romantic,
even though that's what that is.
This wasn't like in hindsight, it wasn't like,
well, we're buddies, so let's just go.
So I think the weeks leading up to this,
I was not showing any romantic interest.
I wasn't doing anything that would give this person
the impression that I was interested that way.
But we were going to prom, we did this or whatever.
And about a week, I feel like it was a week before prom,
I started hurting, like I heard rumors.
I heard rumors of something that was happening.
And I think I ignored them when we went to prom
and we had a fine time.
And again, no kissing, everyone's kissing.
No, I'm not kissing, no.
I turned into Trump there.
I was kissing, I'm not kissing, whatever.
My prom experiences and my friends' prom experiences,
unless it was people who were already dating for a while.
Totally platonic.
Yeah, which again, all these things I'm saying is fine.
I'm not so mad, but I'm just like,
some easy layups here, man.
And that would have again, made you just,
I think a little bit calm, maybe not.
Maybe it wouldn't have been calmer.
But so anyway, so prom happens.
And then all of a sudden I catch wind that like,
there's like another maybe relationship going on
with my friend's sister and somebody else.
And again, keep in mind,
I haven't shown any romantic interest,
but this bothers me, this is upsetting to me.
Oh boy.
Okay, this is upsetting to me.
Look, kissing or no, I own her.
Yeah, I just bizarre, bizarre behavior, bizarre thinking.
And then it turns out it's a good friend of mine.
Okay.
Which again, like makes me so upset
and fight yelling, fighting.
What, in hindsight, it's crazy.
So let's fight it out, bro, let's fight it out.
So yeah, I don't think we did not fight,
but there was definitely like, it was a wedge,
it certainly drove a wedge.
And then it's like back and forth
and there's so much drama and on the phone.
And again, no romantic interest.
Never showed that anything like this
was something I was interested in.
So I think even a couple of weeks later,
I was talking to her and she basically said to me
at this time, I don't think I actually like him.
I think I like you, I like you better or whatever.
Oh, wouldn't that have been a good time
to like kiss or something?
Wouldn't that been?
Yeah.
I didn't do it.
I said, well, that's not the time.
What'd you say?
That is the most green light, green light I've ever heard.
I don't know what to tell you.
This is why all this stuff starts to make me cringe
because it's just like, it's fine.
I'm over this type of issue in my life.
But when you go back to your high school,
you just go like, I don't know what, why, what?
It's so weird.
So.
What happened in that moment then?
It was a little more in public.
There were people around.
So it wasn't like, for a guy who really was not comfortable
doing this, certainly I could say, well, there's people
around, I can't.
Sure.
You could like hold someone's hand or something.
You could have done something.
Yes, some acknowledgement.
Some acknowledgement would have been nice.
A little arm squeeze.
A little arm squeeze would have been nice.
So anyway, so I'm still living in this weird muddled reality
where this isn't like a, it's not, we're not like to get,
we're not doing anything.
So I can't, this is when I said I don't know exactly
the timetable on this.
So something then in the next few weeks gives me the
impression that it's not a, she likes this other guy better.
Probably because I didn't do anything,
but that's not what I'm thinking in my scared,
dumb 17 or 18, 18 year old brain.
So it's the, it's the end of the year.
We're going to Disney world.
We're going down to play late in the evening while marching
down main street.
Though this is a marching band trip.
And where does she factor into this?
She is actually in the band.
Wow. The other guy in the band?
No. Okay. No. Okay.
Oh, I, this, I hate this is so,
Oh man.
So the whole thing is just makes me just so cringe.
So, so, okay. Here we go.
Spike the park. I'm at the turn.
So cringe alert.
We're in a bus. So we, it's, but you take a bus down there,
which in hindsight, I'm like,
how much money were we saving for the bus?
I understand there's some big musical instruments
that'll be maybe cheaper.
I don't like what, what is the price?
I mean, were you saving a hundred dollars?
Like, especially back then, I feel like tickets to Orlando
in May, Chicago to Orlando.
What are we saving here?
I don't know. Buses maybe much cheaper than well.
No, this was the chaperones idea.
It's like when you take a kid to a park, it's like,
Oh, we'll tire them out for getting a nap.
It's like, okay, the band kids,
the most horny kids at the school tire them out on the bus.
So they'll actually play their fucking instruments
when they get to Disney.
I want to derail. Was that a, was that a chaperone?
Yeah. He said, yeah.
I like a macaroon.
That's another, that's another.
We keep finding them.
There's so many.
That one's come up before.
Yeah. We've talked about chaperones.
They have delicious cookies.
Yeah.
Who supervise you.
Even better than E-Clairs.
I'm a E-Clair in a chaperoon.
A chaperoon.
A Cheryphi in a chaperoon.
Anyway. So yeah.
And we, we're on the bus, but we didn't stay in a hotel.
Like we just straight drove, which is miserable.
To start a trip like that sucks.
So that's why I'm kind of in like in hindsight,
I understand they didn't want to make the parents pay a lot
of money, but a hundred bucks or something.
I put you could be a discount.
Well, they aren't checking like you, Mike.
They aren't checking like, especially back then.
They're filling out forms.
Early AOL days, they didn't have the same abilities.
To the degree you can now.
Yeah.
This is a thing.
This is like when you get a travel agent involved.
Like, Hey, we need to get 50 kids.
That's what I'm saying.
There's got to be some pork discount or whatever.
Anyway. So we take the bus down and in my head at this time,
this relationship wasn't going to happen again,
from some bullshit I made up or whatever.
And I don't quite remember the timetable or quite.
So I'm feeling like kind of like negative on it for no reason.
So I'm sitting next to my friend, Josh on the bus.
And I remember it's like maybe seven,
eight hours into the trip and we're at a rest stop.
And this different girl in band comes up to me.
And I have not talked to this girl very much ever, ever maybe.
And I would say she's very,
she's like kind of cooler than everybody.
She might've just been quiet in hindsight,
but she's definitely like cooler than everybody.
And definitely like people were like,
Oh, she's very cute or whatever.
So like this sort of mysterious cooler person in band,
who I've never really talked to comes up to me at a rest stop.
And she says, Oh, I'm sitting next to Kristen.
And she's like really hard to like sleep, you know,
she made something up that didn't sound real. And she goes,
could you think I could sit next to you on the bus? And I go, Oh,
whatever. And I go, Oh yeah, I think, yeah, yeah,
I think that would be fine. Yeah, that would be okay. Sure. Yeah. Okay.
So I'm like running up to a job. I go, Josh,
you gotta find a fucking another seat, brother. Like get out of here.
I don't know what's going on here. That's this is pretty, that whatever this is,
this is going, okay, here we go. So like Josh's like grumbling, of course.
He was like, I don't remember where he even went because he didn't switch seats
with her. He found a different empty seat.
In the undercarriage tubas hitting him in the knee.
It's very possible. I was very rude and was like, yeah, get out of here,
get the fuck out of here.
So we're sitting and we're like kind of talking for a while and then night falls
and then basically this is this part of the story that just is a night is a
nightmare to relive it in my mind.
This girl cuddles up to me to go to sleep and for the next eight,
nine, 10 hours I am awake,
not doing anything, just going, do I kiss? Should I kiss? How do I,
what should I kiss? Should I, is this, is this a, is this a sign?
Is she touching? Is this a, and I'm away. I don't sleep.
I'm awake, paralyzed with fear.
And I, I just like, I don't know what to do.
So like, I know you're also not, where's your, where are your arms?
I don't remember. I don't remember what was happening.
Maybe I put one arm around her. Okay. Maybe I did that.
But this was like being awake for your own surgery or something.
It's just like what part of high school is, is the senior year? Yeah,
it's done. I've graduated.
This is a rough aspect of it that this is not 14. This is no, this is 18.
18. This is why it makes it worse. Yeah. Yeah.
Firing up the voting machine for John Kerry, you know,
no, no, no, no, no, not John Kerry. This is L this is like two years after gore.
No, but yeah, it's coming. It's coming. Yeah.
You're getting ready to cast. You're getting ready to voter die.
Did I love John Kerry already? Yes. Of course I did. But I wasn't voting for him.
You're Wesley Clark. I too use a four star general Jason. Of course.
I would like to work on a turtle neck. I know you imagine the,
you imagine the stern face of John, the stern long face of John Kerry. Yes.
I wouldn't do that if I were you. So was this,
would that be patriotic to kiss this girl? Yes. No, you're right.
John, you're right. You're right. Of course. So she,
I don't know if she slept. I never taught. I never explained.
We never talked essentially about this.
So I am just like shaken by this whole situation because I'm like,
this girl likes me. I don't know what to blah, blah, blah. I like, so,
so I'm trying to figure out what to do because I'm like, maybe I,
maybe my shots not lost. I gotta try something.
So we get to Disney world and my memory is that we went to Epcot first.
And I think I mentioned this on one of the episodes we were referencing the
story. We, I go on a ride with this girl and I go, okay,
here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to try to hold her hand on one of these rides.
Now I've been trying to figure out,
I think the ride was journey into imagination.
The new one.
Well it's 2002.
Yeah, it's the new one. Yeah, it's the new one. Okay.
So you picked a romantic spot.
I'm pretty sure that's the ride parts because it was not spaceship earth and
like world emotion was,
it was closed and horizons was closed already too, I believe.
You're saying that somebody who had all these facts in their head and still
does struggles with dating and signals. I look,
here's what was going on with the land at that point.
Here's what my move would have been on journey into your,
into your ride. Yes. I said, you know, this guy, you know, it's Eric.
I don't, he was in, do you know, my Python? He's from money.
Did you see European vacation? Do you know, have you ever seen life for Brian?
European vacation. You probably know Casper.
Always look on the brights. Yeah.
I know that girls of a certain age have a thing about like it's one of the
actors and Casper was a lot of girls like awakenings is a,
which actor was that? Was that Eric? I don't think I explained Eric Idol at the
time, but it, maybe I did. I don't know.
The moment where that hunk came out of course, Eric Idol, the ghost hunter,
high school girls in the early 2000s loved hearing about money Python.
You can find it on PBS sometimes. Yes.
So I go in to hold this girl's hand on journey into your imagination.
And wait, sorry. Ride vehicles on this are, isn't it like, are you,
is anyone in sight? Are you sharing the row with anybody? I don't remember the,
the, the layout of the vehicle. Tiny, tiny. Okay. Okay. Small. Yeah.
You're not solo though. I don't think that's a good question.
You're in the back or something. It's dark in there and I don't remember.
I think I picked the darkest point of the ride to try to do this.
Cause that's a very dark ride. Less physically and more spiritually.
And I, I go for the hand and there's nothing, I get nothing.
I get like a dead fish and I'm just like, Oh, okay.
Oh, okay. And then I'm confused. I'm like, Oh,
so then at this point I'm at pleasure Island and this is where I'm trying to
figure out which I'm not sure which place we were at.
I don't think we were at mannequins. Were you at one of the clubs though?
In the morning, there was some sort of like teen dance party.
And I'm still, I'm trying, there's some pictures of it and I guess I got a,
I don't, I'm trying to think. So there was mannequins.
There was a list of the other ones for me.
There was the, Oh God.
The BT club later on.
The adventurous club where you were you were not the adventurous club.
No, no, no, no, no. I would have known that. Puppets were around. Yeah.
I don't know that, but there was a teen, like 11 AM dance party.
Essentially one of these places.
Teenagers famously on fire in the morning.
But we were at, yeah.
High energy at 11 AM.
We were, yeah. So we were at pleasure Island. There's a photo. You know what?
There's a photo somewhere and I don't know where it is.
You at least got to show the audience what you looked like at this time.
Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Picture that motive, Mike. Yeah.
And I then told this story to the girl I went to prom with.
And then we, Oh yeah. I told, I don't, I don't know what I'm,
I don't know. I don't know what to tell you other than just acting out of fear
and confusion. And then we went back to Illinois and she dated my friend for two
years. Wow.
And the whole thing is just like so confusing to live,
like to live again when I'm explaining it. It's obviously fine.
It's in an innocent enough story. I actually think I talked to the girl,
the bus girl. I think I hung out with her once actually, after this trip,
she was like clearly giving me no signals about being interested,
but then she was saying she was interested in my friend and a different friend
who was on the trip and we all hung out together.
And then he hung out with her alone and he said, uh, this girl,
she, they were hanging out in a pool and then she just started crying for no
reason. Uh, so I don't know exactly. I never talked to her about it.
I could never get like, Oh, she was interested in you.
But basically I use this,
this traumatic bus ride to completely destroy any chance of having a
relationship.
Both at the end of the school. Yeah. You got nothing from either one.
Yeah. And it's all essentially probably my fault. Wow. It is my fault. Yeah.
So it's weird. Just like,
what was her reaction when you told, did she,
did you sense she was upset as if like,
she just said, don't you not realize that I,
she just seemed like confused or kind of like, uh, to use a wrestling term,
like no sold it like, Oh yeah, that is weird. Okay. Huh.
And then it's really, the whole thing is just, I'm just like,
I don't know. That doesn't seem like me. It says, you know,
even when you think about your memories and you're just like, I don't,
that I guess that's me who did all that stuff,
but it's just confusing and you just get mad at yourself in a lot of ways to
relive stuff. I don't know. Like,
I feel like all of these memories to some degree haunt everyone,
you know, in ways,
obviously there's certain people that like really haunts them and it like bogs
them down in life.
But I think that there's so many of these weird stories you have when you're,
especially when you're younger, when you're in your teenage years,
that like you could like, you can bring it up.
You can bring the feeling back up pretty easily,
even though you know ultimately this story is an innocent story and it's fun,
like it's fine. Yes. Yes, it certainly is. But it's painful.
I hate it.
I had a few bubble up recently because like people started doing the push for
like the reunions in October. Oh yeah.
Are you coming to the reunion?
And I meet some other people where I missed my 20 year. No.
Yeah. I, I, I was doing the math of like, okay, hotel room flights,
a ticket for the album. Like this is,
this would be so expensive for one night for like a warm buffet dinner and a few
yinglings, you know, a few yinglings. Well, you can't get yingling out.
Oh, yingling beer. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, okay. Sorry. It's a pencil.
It's an East coast thing. That was your, you went deep into Pennsylvania mode.
Oh, you can get it up and down. You can get it in a Disney world, I think.
But it doesn't go, I think they just made agreement to start brewing in Texas.
Okay. Yeah. I had a look. I don't want to drive.
I'm not driving a half an hour for my high school. Yeah, that's not a, well,
I did, I did one, one, I did my, my 10 year,
which was kind of a disappointing, I guess in the, well,
in the interest of like humility, I think I was thinking like,
I bet these people here are going to know like my videos or that I work for Conan
O'Brien or, and like jack shit, not one. I like,
I really thought something was going to satisfy me on that level and zero no.
And so then I, then I'm just like, well,
I will just use this open bar and try to have some fun,
especially because I'm really uncomfortable at this as much as I was,
so nothing has reset. I'm exactly as I do not know how to talk to anyone.
And then I, so I drank a fair amount and then just like,
as the dessert tray is not getting picked apart too much,
I took some way too big piece of chocolate cake and shoved it in my face,
much like a Homer Simpson file photo from one of those episodes and just,
and then I turned right to like a girl who I thought was like,
I found awkward to talk to back then and just as much now.
And she just goes, you and walks away. And that is my strongest, like, all right,
no progress.
Whatever is in my head of like what I've accomplished is means a zilch and
the first half of that story sounded like a win to me with a cake party.
I have no regret. I actually, I kind of like that.
I mean, I guess my high school was like, if I was like,
I don't think I'm going to make a lot of headway socially and I like,
and I don't think the person I'm meant to date is going to be here.
So I'll just try to like a bug people when I,
I think I was trying to get us out of people and some,
well that was me in high school and I guess it's me now,
but I shall not be going to the 20 less and one less. I don't know.
If I hear that they have like even bigger bricks of cake available,
if there's more cake, you should go to entirely over my face.
But anyway, let's return back to yours. I mean, that, that ending is not like,
you're not doing anything bad. No, no, I know. It was just a,
such a poor read of, of signal.
It's just so, it's so like, yeah, it's a poor read of signals,
but it's also just like, it's weird when you realize,
uh, it's Taylor Swift's, hi, it's me. I'm the problem. It's me.
And you didn't realize it at the time. That's actually very,
I think that's maybe the most upsetting part, even though I knew I was scared.
I didn't know how scared I was.
So it's weird to like think back to years of behavior and realize the common
denominator is you, as far as the issue is concerned,
because you're making so many excuses. You're trying to know what's going on.
Dating at all costs.
At all costs. And it's, yeah.
I didn't go to any dances because it was like, well, look,
I'm in this relationship and I cannot,
I have a chaste relationship with somebody who is in Houston and I cannot,
I would, of course I would. Are you kidding? And I'd be such,
I'd be such a, like a dynamo. You have no idea what I can do.
Yeah. I'd rock that body. However, I'm just,
I'm in a thing and I can, and then cut to then the week where she's in town is
the most like tepid, you know, the,
what's that that term in school dances about like making room for Jesus.
On my own without anyone telling you. Yeah, of course. So bad.
There was no chemistry with this person. Yes. I need to do this or God forbid,
they notice I have an erection, you know,
that was more shunned from society.
I will be recently how the random erection is a much,
is that it really is a middle school, high school phenomenon.
I don't feel like I'm like often just like sitting somewhere and then, oh,
right. Am I crazy?
The dance one, there's a reason for it, but the random one, no,
I don't think just at the car wash or something.
That's just your body going. Yeah, no, it's a, it's a whole thing.
Well, we all really need it was a cool uncle to say, Hey, listen, you're 15,
16, 17. This does not matter. The stakes are nil.
So like be safe, be polite and go nuts. You know,
it's been going nuts. I don't know.
And go nuts. That seems like a, that's a good uncle.
Like don't crash a car. Don't hurt someone, but like,
put yourself out there. Take a, take a leap.
Take a crazy chance. Isn't that a, is that a Hillary Duff song?
Well, uncle Jason's not going to explain to my daughter anything.
Cause I don't like this idea that his wife is giving. But I'm still, yeah, I,
and look, I actually had a pretty nice time in high school cause I had friends
that wanted to do dumb stuff and fun stuff fight mostly, but,
you know, make a movie and being a band. I pretty much got along with everyone.
I did the plays. I had all the play friends. Yeah. I, I,
and we did some sketches.
I will say I still sort of want everyone's approval in high school
because you know, you're talking about like people knowing what you're up to.
I, I was like, you know what I'm going to do? We went to the,
we went to Las Vegas. It was very successful. I thought we did a live show.
The three of us. So less you mean. Yes. Yes. And I said, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to post a really normie post about this on Facebook.
I did notice that. Really? Yes. And I said, let's see,
let's see what happens. And it got so many likes from people in high school.
And I was so satisfied.
I still want all these people to know that I'm doing something that's somewhat
cool. Like on some level that's,
it's cool to go to Las Vegas and people come and I work a puppet and you know,
like that's somewhat more satisfied from the heat stroke you had all weekend.
When you saw, well yeah, when you saw my normie post, did you say,
what is he doing?
No, I just thought, well, I thought I was like, all right.
I posted like a grandmother or something was like, what a nice time.
It wasn't like, it wasn't like a joke. It was just like,
I think I just went and crushed it in Vegas. I said like to everyone who came out,
it wasn't clever. I was like Penn Teller and us or something.
Like I put some really like, I was like, don't overthink this, just post this.
And it was like, that's the, got like a hundred likes mostly from high school.
Well, that's what most people that are like not I like irony poisoned or like
worried self conscious people.
The rules are if you're in comedy and you do something you're proud of,
you have to K you have to cover it in a joke. So you can't show that you're proud.
Yeah. Cake it in shame. So the funny people,
I kept saying normie posts to put it down as if it was a bad,
but yeah, really what I wanted is people from high school's approval.
That's interesting to me.
That feels equivalent to you still wanting teenagers to think you're cool.
I don't fucking done with ice guy. I don't care what anybody from there thinks.
That's it. It's interesting. Maybe that will,
but also I felt so on the outside of it at the time I felt like a weird sort of
French person. And that was what I was trying to be.
I feel like you maybe did like the high school community a little bit so I could
see how you still have some, you wanting to think teens,
you're cool is the, I understand that one less than the douchey biggest pool
parties. I think that's, I think,
I think you're going to watch that ship sail so far. What happened to the ship?
The ship's gone. All the souls are lost. I don't,
I don't know the teens ever just blanket thought I was cool.
So I don't really know what I'm trying to cling to. But there's something,
I'm just,
I'm worried about when your daughter grows up and there's, you're going to have,
there's going to be a car ride where there's a few of them back there and you
turn around like, you know, and whatever comes out,
whatever band you mention, I think you're going to find yourself on the,
I think it's going to be a similar situation to not getting that handheld.
Yeah. No shoulder from the girl in the pigment, right?
16 year old, they're gonna like the hold steady forever.
70 year old Craig Finn singing. I'm like, you know,
he still sounds the same as a boy.
Mr. Carlson, you're right. The red hot chili peppers are timeless.
And they shifted through eras effortlessly and maintained their cool.
No matter what 90 year old, even as clean change that core energy always stayed
the same.
Will it well, yeah. Will Anthony, will they still be kicking around at 80?
Obviously they're in great shape. The two of them, Anthony and flea,
they do yoga. So like this new chili peppers really rocks.
Young people.
You know that band, you know that band, you've probably been seeing them lately.
Well, they were, they were just as big in my time and I saw them in concert a
time or two. Yeah, I did. Well, speaking, do you want to hear,
speaking of the red chili peppers? Oh, we get to hear it. This isn't like a,
yeah, I'll play it too. No, I play it too. I think you guys should react to it as
well. Uh, okay. Okay. Should I like wap, wrap it up and then make this the end?
Depends if you guys really want to like goof on it or something.
You probably want to make it a coda, you know, things that I, I gotta say we did.
Hey, you heard the story. You did this. I hope you liked all the stories.
Jason and Mike both. I'll try to humiliate myself further.
I just didn't want to crowd this one. There's humiliation that can be done.
I guess wait here. Now I will think I saw it.
I think this was officially thrown out by red K Alex and Tim St.
Aubyn. So thank you. He said, Scott, I'm going to find a story to, I'll,
I'll figure one out. Uh, but, uh, yeah, hey,
you survived podcast, the ride club three.
Thanks for, uh, your, your ultimate supportive podcast,
the ride here on club three, your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done freedom fighters, uh, send your votes in,
put them in the comments, uh, and poll soon to come. Uh,
but, uh, here now to play us out with a cut off their latest album,
second level that the bill O'Reilly intro that's wrong though,
cause he didn't say play us out. That was the phrase he didn't understand.
And here's a second level with a cut off their latest album. Take it away fellas.
And then cut to me standing silently and screaming and flipping chairs. Okay.
Oh my God, this is, this is huge. This is for sure.
Well, I wanted to make sure that the audience is satisfied.
So I wanted to give them a little tree when second love and how close to
everything you described, uh, age wise.
Second level. So I joined sex second level was already a band,
the singer left. Okay. And I said,
I want to be in a band and I want to sing. Um,
the singer of the band. Yeah.
Roll your own ticket there that, you know, this, this reminds me of like,
I was very uncomfortable in a lot of social situations and navigating all this
stuff, but I loved being on stage. Sure. I was confident on stage. Yeah. Yeah.
I felt, I felt similar. Um, but so, yeah,
so I think that we did this at the,
we did this at the school variety shows. There is a video of this somewhere.
I don't know. I'm sure I have my parents have a talent show at two years in a
round. That was my big like breakout.
Mr. Saxon was a show where we would do sketches and stuff.
And most people would just do like a choreographed dance. Yeah. Yeah.
And we were like writing sketches for it. Yeah.
I had a lot of like everybody just doing the perfect in sync,
like just exactly the more popular than the sketch original sketch. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. But I,
but the knowing that you thought that you fully generate, yes.
And yeah,
did my original sketch do worse than the guy performing the home star runner,
a trog door theme. Yes. But the pride I have in the originality.
So anyway, so yeah, we did this, I think the senior year talent show and,
which also I did a, you know what, actually we did a sketch,
but a second city sketch. I did another, I did like a sketch in that show as well,
which I know the band was not happy with because they felt the band was serious
and I shouldn't be goofing around.
We're second level and now you're talking about second city. Which second,
yeah. Are you part of which second is your allegiance point? You want to fight?
Let's fight it out. Let's fight it out. Right. You and me. You're tapping out,
bro. People were mad. And then the singer, my, my friend came back into the band.
So then we had two singers. Whoa. Nice. So you need lineup.
And I did not play guitar at this time.
So I was like rocking the mic solo with no guitar or anything.
So it's all on you. Then the stage presence has to be so high.
So high. The first night it went amazing by the way.
The audience loved it. The second night it was something was wrong. I don't know.
Cause we did two nights of the variety show. All right. Without further ado.
The photos are almost audible. I'll put it, I'll probably just put this in on the track to make it more
for this party. It's off. That wasn't a solo. You want the second verse in the chorus?
I get, I'm sure people are paying high premium for this. Yeah.
The constant hits that's just the transfer. I don't have an answer for that.
Okay. They put it in on purpose.
It's more authentic.
Going down.
This is a rocking part.
I think I would grunt doing this. Yeah.
Yeah. What are you doing? Physically?
Probably dancing. No, not skanking. That's for a stop.
Those people, they were looking at me. I think.
Were you singing the lyrics into a Folgers hand?
Those people, they were looking at me. I'm saying.
Oh yeah. Oh, and then this is I'll stop it here, but then there's a drum solo here.
Oh my God. You know, it'll really knock them on their ass.
The drum solo. Yeah. I don't know why the recording.
Yeah. Well, it was a big,
pretty good for a 20 year old.
I don't know where this recording is from. I don't,
there might be a better recording somewhere, but I don't have it.
I have other songs that are better recorded, but we're talking over this drum solo.
You have the quarter inch tapes of the other song.
I really should have been respectful of the drums.
Look, I'm talking to Giles Martin about remastering this at most and that,
yeah, Dolby Atmos and we're going to go to a Abbey road and we're going to sort
of find the original tracks and Rick Rubin's going to pull the,
he's going to do the faders and then try to find sort of the
actual like solo tracks.
Being afraid to rock the sphere.
Wow.
Yeah. So that's rock the house. What do you think?
I know it's not the best recording in the world, but the vibe wise, do you do?
I mean, it's, I think it's better than I expected. Yeah.
Oh really? For high schoolers?
Yeah, I think so. Yeah. I think that's, I think that's coherent. Okay.
I feel like, um, I like, I don't want to pin the, the problem on you.
It does feel like the tone is kind of,
I feel like you maybe needed some like inner, some like more aggressiveness or,
or grit. Cause as it stands, it's like kinda, uh,
do you think maybe, sure.
Do you think my, my, maybe I didn't know my artistic,
my voice as a literal voice and also voice as a writer perhaps that I wasn't
some like cool Anthony Kiedis guy who.
Yeah, I think yeah. It was like a some insecurity. Yeah.
Although you commit to that kind of like, uh, that the sort of a whine, I guess.
Yeah. That's huge. It is consistent. It sounds, yeah.
It sounds like three, like a three 11 like come or, you know, three 11. Yeah.
Yeah. Um, down, down or come originals, whatever. Uh,
so this was the first song I think we wrote with me in the band.
And I do think the band was like, okay, this is a step up from our song.
Did you write the lyrics? I sure did. Wow.
The lyrics are complete nonsense. Believe that or not.
It was a line that we wouldn't have been able to hear. Well,
it's like that's when they rock the house. Oh wait, we never got out. Oh,
come on. Can't you see those people were looking at me.
Wow. That's strange. What does that mean? I don't know. I'm not sure.
That sounds like, uh, you know, unconscious anxiety stuff.
Like everyone is looking at me. This is exactly, this is,
this describes Mike trying to throw away the mini monster in the city.
What? Yeah. Yeah. Those people were looking at me. What people?
You're like the woman on the plane.
There's no people.
Maybe one of the most sexless rock and roll songs I've ever heard.
The level of sex being had by the makers of it is pretty clear.
Yeah. I think that's right. We've established earlier. Yeah.
You can tell. You can tell in that. It is, it is dripping. It's empty.
No, with not sex. It is so dry. It is the driest.
It's also not the other end of the spectrum of like, Oh,
the punks making songs about being like isolated and not having sex and not
having a girlfriend. It is not that, you know, we are having sex.
You know that we are doing the best sex is something that I do have
under the shirt.
I can rewrite the lyrics. I'll let a friend sit. I'll let a girl sit on my lap.
On the figment ride. I'll try to hold her hand. I'll tell her other friend about it.
I don't even worry about it. I believe I performed that shirt and I was just
said what I was going to say. I performed that song and someone's backyard
and I removed my shirt to.
He had a pool though. So it was like, seemed like kind of like the vibe there.
Some people still, still.
See that's the sort of swing you need to take more of.
Taking my shirt off. Yeah.
Not enough second level swag. I think is yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well there's more, there's more songs in the vaults and I just wanted to give
that one as a little treat right now. Damn. Damn. Well,
thank you for opening up so much. Of course. All of our friends here on the fun level.
Everything's fine.
The story's more traumatic for me than it is for people here.
I'm sure people like this, not that big of a deal.
I don't think anyone felt traumatic hearing it.
Unless there are those listeners who are like,
there only one small part of it was about theme parks.
But welcome to podcast the ride. My friend.
Too late for you. Hey, wait a minute. I'm listening to the show for three years.
This isn't about a theme park. What the hell?
They just talk about the pronunciations on these coasts.
What is this? I've been tricked. I've come out of a fog.
I'm realizing now they're the problem. Not me. Well, that's true.
All right. We can agree on that. We're the problem. Hi, it's us.
We're the problem. It's us. Thanks for listening though.