Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is the final installment of our Las Vegas month.
It contains garbage fans, efficient firefighters, Rich Littles personal YouTube videos, and magic
set to new metal.
Get ready to have your mind free as Jason Wollner returns to talk Chris Angel's A Mystica on
Sin City Nights.
Welcome to the last Podcast the Ride Sin City Nights.
The final penny in the little shop of horrors penny slot.
Audrey too will grow no more.
Sadly, I'm Scott Garrett and you're Jason Sheridan.
I'm out here in the desert digging my grave.
Boy, things really.
How much money do you owe that the little shop of horrors penny slot?
My Carlson fellow host has a weapon pointed at me, you know, just like the end of it,
just like the one scene in Casino.
I'm about to finally do it.
We're about to make a new haunted casino property blossom or haunted a stadium.
So you're saying I'm about to kill you, bury your body in the desert and then build a casino
on top of you.
So it's haunted.
So it's haunted like the Luxor.
So as you can see, things took a turn.
Sin City Nights was a bad idea.
It destroyed the podcast, destroyed everything.
Can you imagine the people when they go to this hotel and they're like, well, there was
this ghost, but he was just sleeping in our bed all day.
Like he was haunting us, but it was really, he was just kind of like lazing around.
That's Jason's ghost.
Yeah, yeah.
He turned King of Queens on the TV and he's been watching a six hour block.
He started smiling.
Yeah.
He said, don't disturb my slumber and put ghostly earplugs in.
So that would be nice.
That would be like a real novelty, I feel like.
Well, look at that.
You got the story in.
I knew we wouldn't escape the month without the retelling of Jason.
Yeah, but it was in a different context.
So was the ghost context did add something to it.
That's right.
Hey, well, we're here.
We're wrapping it up and before we shoot Jason in the head, we're going to have a little
bit of fun on the way out.
We've done a lot.
We've done so much in this series.
We've talked 90s Vegas.
We've talked modern Vegas.
We went to Vegas.
We blended some groove, but there are two big missing presences thus far in this series
that we're going to rectify here on the last one.
One is today's topic, Las Vegas's loudest illusionist, Chris Angel.
We love to talk Chris and we're going to do it and we're going to do it with the help
of somebody who has been on almost every podcast, the ride series.
I don't think we've done a very barely an extended thing without our guest.
You know, somebody we can trust, somebody we can count on.
That's why we call him the Harland Rust of podcast, the ride from Baltic Omen and Bar
and Sub's good movie film.
It's Jason Waller.
Hey guys, thanks so much for having me back.
Great to be back.
I'm so happy you could do it.
Your firm guiding hand, much like Sheriff Rust.
Is he a sheriff?
I don't know.
There's so much mythology.
We've been focused on so much other stuff.
We're just going to have to find out when we all surely go see Rust the day it comes
out.
What will definitely be a theater and not an awkward to be release.
Well, the tension of that movie is going to be like, is it the scene yet?
Is it, oh, they're in the church.
If you see an exterior, but then wait, it was a trick and then just a horse went by
and you don't go into the church.
It's good.
Like that.
Yeah.
We'll all be on pins and needles.
It's horrible.
It's a horrible tragedy.
The man should be executed from.
Right after Jason.
But just for his Trump impression.
But in that scene, like the first half of the scene, like he'll like, what's going to
It'll be whatever it is, a showdown and he pulls his gun and then there'll be a cut and
suddenly he'll be like 30 pounds fatter.
He'll be like all tired.
Like it'll be suddenly you're in the, you're in the reshoot bags under his eyes that look
like you drew it with a marker.
Like every time you would see him, then it would, he would get puffier bags under his
eyes.
What happened to rust?
He's going to be all bags for the second half of the movie.
He's had three kids too.
You can tell in his face.
New kids since.
The only thing that can ease my pain is more children.
Wait, what did you say?
I said he needs to keep working because he's had so many kids.
He's got to put those kids through college.
Wait, when's it number 14?
When did that happen?
I just love every time I come here, I was originally referred to as the Alec Baldwin
of podcast the ride because I had done it a bunch of times, much like he at one point
had hosted SNL a lot of times.
Before the stuff happened, yes, they would allow him on the show.
Now we always have to talk about this horrible tragedy for a few minutes.
There's no way.
There's no way to have jokes about a genuine.
Avoiding something actually terrible.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, yes.
That's why I propose, could I now be maybe known as the Kevin Spacey of podcast the ride
in that I'm innocent of any wrongdoing?
Oh, that's right.
Yes, it is passed through several courts of law.
Yes, there is not a problem.
That means problem.
I'm back.
I'm doing well.
I'm working again.
Completely accepted.
Three of my teachers have been found dead.
That's true.
Yeah, he's right.
Get up, Kevin Spacey kills people.
But those ones aside, most media is not willing to cover it the way we are here on podcast
the ride.
It's more out there and we've been through the trials.
Oh, yeah.
Well, absolutely.
Take it.
The Kevin Spacey podcast the ride.
The completely innocent man of some things.
Jason, I'm so happy you could close out Vegas with us, especially because we've spent so
much of the last over a month talking about things that have gotten our attention because
of you.
We've talked a little bit of Chris Angel and Kblip.
Copperfield, of course, comes up all the time and the Blue 32 show.
You can't not talk about it.
Before we dive into Chris specifically, I guess, what was my question?
I guess, are those your two favorite findings or is there some hot new Vegas finding of
yours that you're willing to share or anything you think is on the bubble?
You've just brought so many amazing souvenirs back.
The Copperfield show I've seen seven times now, I think.
Wow.
It's one of my favorite things in the whole world.
Chris, yeah, we've seen a lot of his shows.
We've seen him through a lot of phases.
I'm excited to chat.
A Mystica.
Yeah.
His great folly, perhaps.
It's pure numbers wise.
The numbers aren't good.
I went earlier this year, I think.
There's nothing on that level right now, except I did see Rich Liddell's show, which is worth
seeing.
Oh man.
Mike was so disappointed.
We wasn't playing.
When the weekend we were there.
It was a rare weekend of.
Did he die?
Is he dead?
Due to dying.
It's possible.
I imagine that's the only reason we wouldn't be playing.
It's crazy.
It is like a living funeral for a person who's there like three feet from you.
But all of his jokes, he's like so right wing.
And it's all about how Biden is an idiot and Kamala, what the hell is she smiling about
all the time?
Does he try to do Kamala?
I hope.
I think he just does maybe a smiling face.
But most of the show is him kind of like settling old grudges and just like bashing people who
are long dead where he'll just be like, I forget there was a, who is that?
It was like a character actor from the sixties and he's like, I was guest hosting for Johnny
one night and this, oh, the guy who played the really like, was it the Nazi?
It wasn't the Nazi.
There's a really flamboyant Dick Shawn, I think in the producers.
Right.
Okay.
And he's like, this guy, I don't know what he was on, but this guy was a damn idiot.
And then he just moves on.
Like there's no joke.
So it's really just him on stage talking about who is now dead was an idiot or bothered him.
Is it Shawn in Captain EO?
Is he the guy?
Captain EO, the hologram guy.
Yeah, I think you're right.
That might be my only con to tie it into the first.
Did the audience seem to know who he was?
How old was the average audience member?
Very old, very, probably in their seventies.
Yeah.
I went with a few friends and we were the only people younger than that.
And what was the venue?
The venue is the comedy club in, I believe the Tropicana, which is like a chain.
Maybe it's like the laugh factory or something, but it's just like a depressing room.
Well, cause it's getting demolished.
That's going to be gone in a matter of months.
I think.
Rich May as well.
They're just going to leave him in there?
Yeah.
Let's just implode a man too while we're at it.
And then he does caricatures of people that he'll show on a screen and then they speak
in a really kind of ghoulish way.
And so he's doing impressions with himself back and forth.
And then it's mostly YouTube clips.
He sits there and watches clips of his life for about half the show.
He just like moves to the side or doesn't, or just maybe he's blocking the screen.
I don't know.
He does.
And just sits with you and watches.
Basically, yeah.
So it's just a Twitch stream.
It's a live in person Twitch stream from a man who would not know what that phrase meant.
No.
He does Obama, I know, right?
Well, he does, he Twitches sometimes.
So he does Obama.
His Obama wasn't great, I will say.
You don't say.
Was that the newest impression he does?
Probably, yeah.
But I mean, there's Biden, but I've seen his Biden on Huckabee on the talk show.
And it is just kind of an old man, which is what he is.
Not a stretch.
He doesn't have a take on it, you're saying.
No, not really.
Just that he might fall asleep in the middle of a sentence.
But Trump's old.
Trump is very old as well.
But he's, I can't, I say that, the man has energy.
We know this.
He loves to shriek.
He loves it.
He's becoming more twisted and gnarled day by day.
Trump?
Yeah.
Sure.
Demonic.
You don't even have to mention it.
It's just a given.
Well, Rich hopefully will be there next, when we go next.
So we can do a Rich.
It's worth, you guys should go.
You would enjoy it.
It's very cheap.
And there's no one there.
You can sit like three feet from him.
Does he take questions around him?
They're building a dugout.
Like as it's happening around us, the visitors' dugout is being built.
For the baseball stadium.
Yeah, for the baseball stadium.
You have to, you've referenced this several times and you've had to like, then we're blank
and then you go, because they're building a baseball stadium there.
It's odd.
It's very odd, you know?
Do you think Rich Little could play one night at the Sphere for me?
For you?
With the clips, because now we can find out there's a clip component to Rich Little's
show.
Oh, they project him in the Sphere.
Yeah.
We could see him.
240p quality clips at 160k or whatever the Sphere is.
He's still mad about Obama phone, you know?
He's still mad about that.
What's that?
You stumped me twice in a minute.
Well, the government used to give away phone service to low income people because it is
like, it's better that everyone has phone service.
It's better for emergency services.
So then as phone service gravitated towards mobile phones, they started giving away basic
mobile phones.
So someone put up a video saying, I got my Obama phone and Project Veritas and Fox News
just went nuts about it.
It sounds like Jason could fill in for Rich Little on certain nights.
Your current events whisperer.
Yeah.
It was like a tan suit era scandal.
You know what he does?
He does What a Wonderful World as a duet with him as Louis Armstrong and a Kermit the Frog
on his hand that he's puppeting.
And his Kermit voice is I think very similar to his Obama voice.
It's not very accurate.
Yeah, we'll do it next time.
He's pulling from the Danny Gans playbook.
He's one of the last classic Vegas impressionists, like a Danny Gans type guy.
Yeah, yeah.
I know you did the screening recently where you showed a project that you did that was
based on Danny Gans.
And that sent me down the Danny Gans rabbit hole where he definitely does Louis Armstrong,
What a Wonderful World, definitely does Kermit.
Didn't think of bringing them together.
That is a good impression crisscross that makes no sense.
Should I?
That project is secretly on YouTube.
We put it up.
I made a fake Las Vegas trailers account.
And I put it up six years ago and no one has discovered it.
I looked at it the other day.
It's got like 140 views.
And they're all me reloading it to see if anyone discovered it over the past six years.
Are you willing to speak about this on the?
Yeah, I might as well spill it, right?
Sure. Oh my God.
Happy to have the exclusive.
This thing is so funny.
It's called Billy Glimmer.
It stars Ben Stiller as a Las Vegas style impressionist along the lines of Danny Gans,
the late Danny Gans.
So a big movie star has been in a secret video for years without anybody finding it.
It was like a demo video we made.
We were maybe going to make a movie about it or then it became maybe a web series.
Then it became a secret YouTube video.
It became podcast, the ride bonus content.
I'm so sorry.
Typical passage of Hollywood projects.
But if you look it up on, it was announced at some point as a web series and then it never happened.
We did shoot this one thing.
It's on YouTube.
Maybe podcast ride fans keep it our little secret for now.
You check it out.
But let's see if someone discovers it.
But they didn't find it with this username top Las Vegas entertainment show.
That's so funny.
I thought so.
If you look at that account, I made that account and I just put up a bunch of like Vegas trailers and then hid this among them.
I assume someone would be like, what the fuck is this?
There are so many accounts actually like this, though.
Yeah.
Start looking up Vegas stuff.
Yes.
No one ever found this one.
Wow.
Feel free to subscribe.
It will never post another video.
I can promise you that I've lost the password.
Secret Stiller just for the Cliffords.
Thank you for that.
This thing is this video is so funny.
And I like when you screened it, I was dying at it.
And then I watched.
Like, I wonder what it was based on and was it exaggerated in any way?
And the actual Danny Gans sizzle reel is precisely what you.
Yeah, it is only because it only because of the accident quality of he is trying to make people laugh.
But then you aren't laughing the way he's intending.
But you're laughing in a new twenty twenty three way.
There's a lot of layers.
I think the real Danny Gans video is is funnier because it's real.
Yeah, he's not trying to.
Yeah, it's just hard to beat it.
It's so insane.
He does.
He'll just like announce an impression singing premise that makes no sense.
We're like, why are these people together?
And then like, ladies and gentlemen, Michael Bolton with featuring Dr.
Ruth and then do a bad Michael Bolton with a man, those woman and then switches characters.
He'd better wear a condom.
Why?
That's the punch line.
And then and then audience dying, dying.
An audience of twenty seven thousand people laughing harder than I've seen anyone laugh
anywhere I've been in a supposed comedy career.
Never have I seen an audience, even sat in an audience that's killing the way Danny Gans is killing.
It's crazy.
I saw this is only tangentially related.
This morning I was sent a clip of the guy who played Kevin from the office.
In front of like an office con group of like of attendees.
And there's a kid dressed as him and he just whispers to the kid like identity theft is a crime.
And I've never seen a crowd laugh harder or longer than this clip.
Camera shaking.
They drop it.
I'll never see anything.
It goes over with the audience.
I love office.
Sorry.
Fanda.
I love it.
It's going to.
Yeah.
This is.
Where is this hitting?
I don't know.
But I can't.
I'm a lot of your savings account to that Stanley.
I did.
Series that is being returned to you.
I sent twenty five thousand dollars to the actor who played Stanley on the office for
his project to make a Stanley spinoff.
But he sent the money back to me.
So sorry.
I'm sorry.
You have that money.
I want him to have what a waste.
I'm trying to get it back to him.
I'm trying to send him cash in an envelope.
You're trying to find him on Venmo.
Yeah.
I'm going to buy lots of Stanley action figures.
Just want to spend this on Stanley.
I'll buy Stanley Funko Pops.
Four hundred of them.
Yeah.
OK.
Well, these are great tips.
Thank you for the secret video and the rich little tip.
We got to go.
We'll go.
But let's talk about.
What's that?
He's quite old.
Time is of the essence.
Yeah.
Well, you're good.
Mike, if it lines up with your Sphere trip.
I'm going to Sphere.
You must.
You must go.
What are you doing in Sphere?
And I'd like to apologize to Lindsay in advance.
I'm seeing you too.
Oh.
Yeah.
No, I wish I was.
Is it cool, though?
How many impressions is Bono going to do?
I think very little.
Well, if he does the Mirror Ball Man and if he does McFist, though, these are different
voices at least, different characters.
Let's talk about the real, you know, the greatest entertainer who has not gotten the spotlight
in this series.
He closed out Celebruary long ago, but we got to talk about him here.
And that's Chris Angel.
Jason, you joined us for that.
You did a little guest appearance.
That's right.
We did a little week.
Episode where we talked about about some of your your initial Chris Angel fandom, your
Chris Angel journey.
So, you know, not to reiterate too much of that, but, you know, it's you did the human
giant sketch, which is based on him.
But you didn't actually like it was years later that you actually saw Mind Freak with
your own eyes, which was revelatory, seemingly.
A few years.
Yeah.
Believ, that was his like, and maybe we talked about this, his like collab with Cirque du
Soleil that was kind of short lived and I think very acrimonious.
Is that the I was I got confused about when it became Believ.
I even saw him and I don't I don't know if it was Believ or Mind Freak.
It was At Luxor at the time.
Believ was At Luxor, I think, and it had like weird Cirque elements, like a bunny rabbit
that like run like weird little people and like, you know, it had a bunch of that kind
of stuff.
Yeah.
Then I saw Believ, I think.
And then I think he changed the show to Mind Freak and now it's at Planet Hollywood.
And I went and saw that.
Which is what it was initially.
Like it was it was Mind Freak.
It was a version of the show, but live for many years.
Then this Cirque du Soleil thing that I did.
I'll get to this quote.
I don't know where this is from, but one of the most brutally reviewed shows in the history
of Las Vegas.
This will be a recurring theme of the episode, is his tortured relationship with critics
who try to drag him down.
But that was the first to you.
He is the Trump of magic.
We said it before.
Everybody's after him.
We.
And then years later, I was there with some friends and we saw the Mind Freak show.
And that's kind of like I wasn't really obsessed with him.
We did the thing on Human Giant and and saw his show and it was funny and dumb.
But it was years later we went back and saw Mind Freak and got like truly obsessed and
told everyone like, oh, you have to see it.
He's doing a crazy thing.
Partially because of that childhood cancer segment that becomes like a laser dance party.
That's just everything we talked about it last time.
It's just insane.
I forgot that I re listened to what we talked about and I forgot that some of this involved
a woman in a bald cap.
Yes.
Who gets her childhood.
Insane.
There's also an illness angle in the Copperfield show too, right?
You mean that Blue is dying?
No, no, there was before Blue even comes out, at least when I saw the show.
Oh, the guy with the sister who died that he makes the guy levitate?
Which is also in one of the TV's, one of the prime time TV specials.
OK, OK.
Oh, wow.
Wait, but it's always in there?
So is this a thing that he?
I've only seen the show once, but it was in there.
The guy whose sister died, not to give too much away, is there every night, yes?
I see.
Well, that's nice.
At least all seven times that I've been there.
He's got somewhere to go.
He may be in on it.
Could be a plant situation, or maybe just a big fan.
It was his sister's dream that I think David levitate him.
Wow.
Now he gets to do it every night.
She's dead.
Yeah, now over again.
David owns him now.
Yeah.
I forgot that in our initial Chris Angel Talks, the aspect of him being best friends with
Gary Oldman.
That is a funny detail.
And through a mystical, I'm sure we'll talk about, we learned about his other best friend.
Wait, which?
Mike Hammer.
Oh, yo, that one.
We'll get into it.
Yeah, I don't know who's closer with him.
No, no, no.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
Yeah, well, we'll learn all about Mike Hammer.
I mean, if you, unfortunately, will learn all about Mike Hammer, if you Google Gary
Oldman, Chris Angel, just photo after photo, something he tweeted, this was my favorite.
They're best friends.
Always kissing people.
I love Gary Oldman, the best of the best, class act and insanely talented.
So on it.
He's my friend.
Just, yeah, so much.
I went to Chris's Hollywood Walk of Fame ceremony just as an observer.
And Gary Oldman introduced him and gave the speech.
They are truly best of friends.
Do we know where this, Gary Oldman doesn't feel like he's from the same universe as Chris
Angel.
I think he just looks like a kind of dignified guy.
Are you thinking of like Commissioner Gordon version of Gary Oldman?
Yeah, am I like applying some air and some class?
Yeah, we might be projecting, or the Churchill.
Yeah, yeah.
Not too much the dilapidated slow horses, Gary Oldman.
Yeah, yeah, more of like the Chris Angel's best buddy, Gary Oldman.
The true, the truest true Gary Oldman.
True romance, Gary Oldman would be best friends with Chris Angel.
What do you think they talk about?
God, I don't know.
What if it's only public?
You think Gary Oldman's eating a ka-blip?
That is a crazy image.
You gotta come out, I'll comp ya.
I'll comp ya, Gary.
If he's staying at his house maybe, they get in like the limo and go?
Possibly.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Has he gone dirt biking with him in the beautiful Moapa Valley?
Definitely.
So, should we get into how we found out?
Basically, they announced that Chris, it was like announced in years before it came out
that Chris was doing a new show, was gonna have a show that followed his Mindfreak show.
And it was called A Mystica, and it was like his dream project, and it was going to be
about his life, a magic show about his life story.
And so we were all, we all got on a text thread and were like, well we absolutely have to
go see this.
And then I think we were like, we either bought tickets where we were about to, and then the
show got like, postponed, just like, right?
It got postponed three times.
Yeah, I think there was a three month that I remember, oh maybe there were, yeah, that
makes sense that we're all about.
And then they started, and we were like, oh, if we, yeah, if this is about his life, this
is gonna be, like, we have to see this.
Also, I think we had a hunch that it wouldn't last very long.
Yeah, sure, yes.
And spoiler, listeners, if you're curious to see Chris Angel's Mystica, you cannot.
Well, I'm sure Chris did not make it out of 2022.
Well, unless they get the international tour off the ground.
Sounds, I'm optimistic, I'm optimistic.
Just some numbers, okay, opens May 2022, closes October 2022.
Now that is not a long run for a theatrical endeavor in any respect.
No.
But especially in Vegas.
It's been a long run for four years.
Forever, and like, Mindfreak is still pulling like 1200 people a night.
Well is it?
That's what the Los Angeles Review Journal said.
But they made sure to note that the closing night of a Mystica for a theater that seats
1400, there were 150 people there.
Oh my god.
Yeah, wow.
We did the same as them.
In the weeks leading up to our trip, so we got a little group together, and we were like,
we're gonna go to Vegas.
Which Mike and Jason were invited to, they were not cut out of it, you guys couldn't
do it, but you could have experienced the manager.
But I had COVID, so I didn't go.
Mike had COVID.
Oh, you're right, oh, because it was right after New York.
I was out of town.
I said that Mike and I were two of the designated comedy survivors, like us and Tim Heidecker
were not on the trip.
You guys texted, you agreed, you texted Tim.
Yeah, yeah, we texted fellow Forever Dog, a host, Tim Heidecker.
Friend of the show.
I don't know.
And because this was like, it was you guys and Eva and Tom Sharpling and John Daly.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was like a big comedy contingent.
It sure was.
I don't know, it was just so many of you pulled it off, like got together and organized this.
And you know, anticipation is building as we're, you know, trying to settle on a date
to do it because little flickers of information keep coming out about it and how it is different
and why it goes deeper and hits harder than the typical Criss Angel show.
And by the way, I guess, you know, the typical Criss Angel show already, because I was looking at reviews
of like the main one and the reviews often are like, there were like five tricks over the course of 90 minutes.
Yes.
It's a lot of loud music, a lot, you mentioned last time, a lot of Jonathan Davis from Korn.
Oh my God.
Did a bunch for it.
And it's all stuff of that style or kind of this like Evanescence variety.
And then a lot of like, I also saw reviews saying like, I don't know if he was doing illusions or something.
I couldn't tell because he was blasting strobes at us the entire time.
So I don't know exactly what he did or didn't do.
So, but basically, you know, the main show.
And we should say this is this was a collaboration with Franco Dragone.
Yes, who was a major director of Cirque du Soleil.
Yeah, he was.
I think Chris says a big part of establishing the look, feel and language of Cirque du Soleil.
He directed all the major shows from 85 to 98.
That is so so a big figure.
And he passed away in the fall of 2022.
And then I believe that part of influence the decision to close a Mystica, although he passed away in Cairo.
So it wasn't like he was.
What was the order of events, though? Did he hear it was closing and that was too much for him?
No, no, I'm saying he passed away and then the show killed him.
That's what I'm suggesting.
Seeing his name on an ugly billboard killed him.
Killed his body.
He got one text from somebody like, hey, I saw the show.
And then he came out when we were there.
He was there. Yes, we got we were graced by the presence of Franco himself.
Franco comes out with Chris, right?
Yes. Yeah. In the beginning.
And what does he say? I don't also is very drunk.
But we saw this show.
No, me as well and only got more so as it went.
So I was relying on some.
Well, in this case, a smuggled video and I knew that I like I knew the risks of filming at a Chris Angel show via you, Jason, because I know you were kicked out of a show.
I had been previously removed.
Yes. And forced to delete all your photos in front of a watch and guard.
But no, we got we got a little special intro from the from the two minds from Dragone and Chris.
I don't remember if this is anything or interesting, but I'll play it.
What you have been through because this would be a model for the young generation.
So this is a message of hope, love and light.
And we hope you enjoy this presentation, ladies and gentlemen.
And by the way, make sure if you bought a ticket, you're going to stick around.
Oh, yes. OK, so not much there, but it's a story of hope.
It's a story of love and light of love.
And that's that's all big stuff. That's heavy stuff to get into.
It's bigger than your run of the mill magic show deals with.
We and and then before we went on this trip, we I found on Vimeo a video from August 2000.
So over 20 years old called Chris Angels, a mystic.
And it's like this it's before anyone knew who he was.
This crazy, like kind of 80s, like hair metal kind of song.
It's like into a mystic car.
And it's this like Terminator knockoff robot walking.
And Chris does this thing. It's up there. It's still up there.
I look today and it looked crazy. It looked great.
And it's like, oh, wow, he's been this is the show he's been planning to do for 20 years.
We're going to see like this guy's masterpiece, which is like the zone you want to be in of just someone like what was so great about his other show, about the childhood cancer thing.
It was like, oh, this is such a bad idea and in such poor taste.
And no one's saying no to him.
And I was hoping that this whole show would just be that of just like, oh, you're getting this kind of dimwitted guy's life story who thinks his life is like so important and heavy and melodramatic.
And and so the expectations were very high when we saw this show.
Yeah. Well, and the mythology, you know, before we even get into what it is, I just want to build the picture of what we're coming in with, because there is the legend of this.
We know that it is a prequel to his regular show, a show with no story, a show that's a bunch of stuff and a rave in the face of childhood cancer.
How do you do a prequel to something that is just not a plot?
So there's that.
Then and there's the discovery that a mystica is a word that he uses in lots of things.
He tried to mount a show.
He posted on his Instagram.
I forgot about this.
An old photo that says a mystica.
This was my license plate 25 years ago.
Like a young, much like a very jerseyed out.
But it's crazy with an emoji.
Crazy mind blow.
Is he is he saying that this like it wasn't a vanity plate that that just happened to be the letters he got when he got a car?
Yeah, it was the sign.
I got some random letters and I knew I had to turn it into a show.
Doesn't he also have an amistica tattoo?
No, does he?
And he didn't name one of the kids a mystica, did he?
Because there's I know he has all these words that he recurs.
What's the thing that it's that elusia, I believe?
Elusia is his coffee.
Wait, the coffee.
I think it's the coffee and one of his children.
Yes.
Elusia is one of the kids?
I think so.
Yeah, yeah.
OK.
So there are a number.
So basically, Chris Angel is a guy who thought of four words 25 years ago and his whole career has been about like just releasing them one by one.
Sure.
And then all caps the caption on that.
Never give up on your dream fire.
So the more this builds, we're like, boy, this is like completely what is in this guy's heart.
And it's his personal story.
And then but then bits of information you're getting that we're probably texting to each other on the way to it just make it seem stranger and stranger.
In fact, I don't remember this, that the show was originally titled Mr. Smiles and Molly.
Yeah.
Do you remember what that refers to?
I feel like we knew it at one point.
I don't remember.
Is it in the show?
Is there a toy that's Mr. Smiles?
I think it was probably cut from the show.
Possibly.
Much like Christos.
But we'll get to that.
I was trying to remember that.
OK, well, that's a detail.
So we found out from just researching it, the original name of the show was not a mistake.
Mr. Smiles and Molly.
And it was actually announced.
And there's an article in the Las Vegas Review Journal from twenty twenty one, which is like, oh, very right before it opened.
I think so.
He had I mean, like everything.
It's like this whole plan.
And then he's like, fuck it.
Just call it a mystic.
This is dumb.
Like it is like he like the name of Mr.
is almost like when you're a kid and you just like write the same word in your notebook like a hundred thousand times.
He fixates on these things.
Or like when you think of like a fake production company name, if you did that like little filmmaker Scott in high school, like you like make your logo, you make your logo before you make anything.
Yeah.
Getting that Stussy.
It's like America.
The mystical.
Is that what it means?
Yeah.
What is it?
Let's talk about the phrase.
What is something?
It's like a.
Yeah.
Is it a mystic?
It's America.
But it's like it's a whole country for magic basically.
Well, he's very patriotic.
That's another thing about Chris saying.
But he said the back half of the word was for swastika.
What?
No, he didn't say that.
He said that's that's daring.
We're getting some actual going for two minutes.
Yeah, we would have.
He's like a big Nazi guy.
Martin and Lewis, Sigfried and Roy, Alan and Rossi, Penn and Teller, Donnie and Marie.
And now Mr. Smiles and Molly.
That's how this article begins.
We're talking about Dragone and Chris Angel collaborating in a new venue under that title.
And it was going to be some it wasn't going to be anything like what we saw.
It was like a club or it was interactive, immersive, euphoria is how they described it.
Dragone says it's a bold fusion between the world of electronic music and theater.
They didn't announce where and when a surreal pre nightclub experience.
It sounds nothing like the show we saw.
By the time you saw it, it's not even a magic show.
It's what the what was it?
It was like, well, OK, one thing we realized that we didn't know until we were there is that Chris Angel is basically not in the show until like the last 15 minutes.
Yes.
Well, there was this question in the lead up to it and then and in the press in the lead up to it that like, wow, it's Chris Angel's new show.
But will Chris be in the show at all?
And I found an interview where he kind of like, well, first of all, here's an article.
One thing to say here, too, is that we found that Chris had, I'd say, lost the like what he he like the Vegas Press has had a very cantankerous relationship with Chris, a very combative relationship where like some stories have been written about this guy that are rough.
So people I think the Vegas Press was like excited to watch this thing fail and looking for cracks because I'd see articles called Vital Vegas and a writer named Sam Novak and these guys, I think all pretty after Chris.
So quotes, Chris Angel, the most hated fraud in Las Vegas.
Wow.
One of the nastiest shit balls I've ever encountered.
And these are the places that are supposed to just be posting puff pieces of, hey, check out Chris Angel's new show at Planet Hollywood.
And instead, they are they are posting.
They are trying to take this guy down.
That's like, you know, like whatever mice chat being like this motherfucker Bob Iger or something like the theme park press, which is a very favorable thing.
Yeah, it's usually extremely positive.
No.
So it's it does seem rare.
So one of these sites said because also you want access in like the theme park world.
Yes.
Well, anything that's like a niche market that has a press quote unquote has to be very favorable because you just get iced out if it's not like podcast the ride like podcast the ride.
Right.
Except Vegas.
Yeah.
You just well, they.
Well, I think like he was there's a famous story.
I think was it this one or something that he he kicked a guy out who had written about him.
Do you have that?
It was this guy.
Sam Novak, who I just mentioned.
He was writing for something called Vegas 411.
He wrote an article called I was thrown out of Chris Angel's new show.
He much like James Dolan, which we talked about kicking people out of the garden who've been critical of him.
Yeah, and that was right to do it.
And he was great.
He was absolutely correct.
Don't mess up Mike's fear.
So he wrote a big angry article.
He just like he was in his seat about to start and then two suited men come up to him and like, wait, no, this cannot stand.
And then he wrote a bit like a very defiant article.
My expulsion from Chris Angel show was nothing more than censorship blocking the public's access to information.
It damages tourism and the entertainment community.
And then he goes on to say, I am a longtime fan of co-creator Franco Dragone.
I've it is my dream to one day see his down House of Dancing Waters and Macau is a biggest dragone head, but he was yanked away from getting to experience dragones, possibly final work and certainly worst work.
And I'm so guaranteed worse thing he's ever been part of.
So this is the tenor of the press going into this.
So when rumors start leaking about this show, they're asking questions.
Here is an article I found, I think, from Vital Vegas.
The biggest problem is probably the terrible name of the show.
The second biggest problem is it's unclear if Chris Angel actually appears in the show.
Try and spot him anywhere in this promotional video for a mystica, which is true.
The video videos he put out, you can't make heads or tails of him.
It's just like screaming and lights and maybe a guy on fire.
And I can't figure out what he's not in most of the show.
And then we found out afterwards that he was like so basically the show we saw he showed up towards the end.
He showed up to be introduced it.
Then it's this like kind of really half assed like play about his life that wasn't even it wasn't funny like he wanted to be.
It was just like this kind of like scary, scary, but like lazy, like no actual impressive physical feats.
The only impressive was like a guy came out and did card magic and he was like very good.
This big like muscle bound guy, which is had like making thousands of cards appears like that was incredible.
A guy did like a Houdini water torture escape and like was just like trying to get out of this box of water for like three and a half minutes or something.
I was like, oh yeah, he looks like he could die.
Yes.
And and but he Chris tries to keep a presence in it regardless.
You hear his voice.
And in that part, he says like this guy's about to hold his breath.
Please do it along with him.
Like in solidarity.
You're wait, what's the what's the quote?
You're oh, do it.
Please.
You don't have to bet your life along with it.
He does.
So you're encouraged to hold your breath along with the tank guy.
And I was going to say I did find again the Los Angeles or Las Vegas Review Journal kind of gave a definitive answer after the show closed of Chris Angel's presence in the show.
Right.
It says Angel himself did not appear in the production other than in voiceover after performing the goth magic character Christos.
That's Christos with an X in the first few shows, which by the time we saw the first few shows,
by the time we saw it, he shows up at the end and does a trick.
But then we read a review saying that Christos or Xristos, it's X, X, R, I am with an X at the beginning.
They were like Christos is like devilish, you know, Joker character.
But when we saw it, he clearly was just too lazy to put on the Christos makeup because he just showed up, did some tricks and left.
And then we found a clip of him on a morning show in Vegas talking about he said like,
that's right, I'm currently in the show.
We're like, what he's planning on just like fully like this was so fully what we expected to see like his opus.
And it was so much just like a cash grab that he thought it was like a Larry Sanders kind of thing.
He thought he could just like a Hank something Hank would do.
Like he would put his name on something like these idiots.
The first night.
And like he and then he's like, I'll phase myself out.
And he just really overestimated the amount that his name above a banner.
If you give people a bad show and so and the other part of the show that was massive was the comedy portion of this guy, Mike Hammer.
And look, everyone look, we're all living our lives.
I don't want to shit on everybody.
But like it wasn't, you know, our cup of tea.
It wasn't the kind of comedy that we like.
No, it was a kind of comedy that involved bringing up audience members of certain.
That's what he did.
And then we found a clip of him on his Instagram doing the exact same thing.
It doesn't matter what they said their name was.
He would just make a sound.
And it was just like full racism.
Yeah, yeah.
Just watch.
Just like, what the fuck is this?
It's like a half an hour of racism or being like a pig towards women.
And that was just like, oh, this is like so it's like it was just boring.
And then, yeah, the show sucked.
It was really it was terrible.
It's really bad.
Yes, it's so he's clearly trying to build this like where where do I go from here?
Where do I I've got my nightly show, but I'm getting bored with it and I would like to make some more money.
So could I attach my name to another thing?
There's a question of if I'll be maybe I'll be in it and I'll certainly be a presence in the voiceover.
So you're getting the Chris Angel vibe.
But after and then we'll get the reviews that I'm sure will be great reviews after that first month where I am in it kind of for 15 minutes.
And then we will phase out even that 15 minutes and I will not be in it at all.
He thought this plan would work.
I mean, variety shows, I guess, work in Vegas, but it was like very expensive.
And and the Cirque du Soleil element, you go to like you go to like that show, Ka, or like the state.
Have you ever seen that?
It's like the craziest thing you've ever seen, like the whole the whole stage moves like 360 degrees.
It's like mind blowing.
It's almost vertical.
It kills people.
It's like an incredible show.
And and this had it's just like people like kind of spinning around.
There was nothing physically impressive that you would see in a Cirque du Soleil show.
The magic. Yeah, there were like two impressive magic tricks, not by Chris Angel, and then like 40 minutes of shitty comedy.
So much.
And just like comedy pseudo magic.
But they're not really mostly comedy.
And by comedy, we mean questioning the last names of people who are different than him.
But there was one truly wonderful bit in the show that we haven't talked about yet.
Well, let me look.
Before we get to that, just to build to that, although I think I've alluded to it on the show before.
But the you talk about there wasn't anything impressive, like a big Cirque stage that that rotated and everything.
Jason, you're forgetting about the house, the big house.
You remember the big house, right?
That's lived with you since April 20, 20, when we saw it.
Look, I've I've forgotten a lot of this show.
Well, you're going to wonder how you could have missed this big house.
But when I show you this video where Chris Angel is on his Instagram, Chris Angel is next to a house that's almost as tall as him.
Wait, was that in the show?
It was. And I barely I faintly remember this.
But wait, listen to how he builds this thing up.
And the caption is my new house cost over one million dollars, but it can do what no house in the world can.
Technological piece of magic or illusion in the history of my art.
There's nothing even close to it.
He's lying over a million dollars.
Find out why. Check out a mystica coming to Planet Hollywood.
What did it do?
I don't remember. No, he's lying.
I remember the house.
I remember the house being rolled out and maybe something was like projected onto it.
And I found another video where it seems to like split open.
I think it opened.
That's like that's very what came out of it.
Any Broadway show.
There was just like there was like a desk and then an actor came and sat at the desk.
Find out what was in the house.
There was nothing impressive or memorable.
There isn't for him to claim that is the most impressive thing in the history of his art.
And to stack that we've got drag on.
You got your let. Yeah, that's just a pure lie.
Do you think he's going to listen to this?
Will he just do to like a lack of Christ angel?
What how do we fit?
Well, we all have we if we have his ear, what would we like to say?
Well, you can hear it in the recording that I'll play in a little while.
Oh, you get that. You talk to him.
So you're not proud of it.
It looks like a child's playhouse.
Uh huh.
Like where I grew up, if there were was like the outskirts of a hurricane pass through,
you would go outside afterwards and they're like, oh, playhouse is gone.
Like that doesn't look like a thing that would cost a million dollars.
I don't know how I did.
And I didn't remember it in the least.
It looks like a doghouse for a Saint Bernard.
Yeah. It's just like a big doghouse.
How could you possibly spend a million dollars?
It's a doghouse. Yeah.
And I think it collapsed on stage.
I think so. I think the roof like maybe it didn't work the night we saw it.
It might not. Was it part of the tornado bit?
I don't know.
Oh, maybe like in like Wizard of Oz or something.
It wasn't anything that I'm sure you could talk to any of us who were on that trip.
No one can recall what.
So what did you think of the house?
All of us blank. Was there a house?
It didn't. The house didn't land, but something else did.
You're right. I talked about this briefly on the on the second gate,
but let's actually let's hear it from your perspective, Jason.
I'm trying to remember the set above it.
At one point he does a memorial to his dad because that's always part of shows like this.
And then I think he implies that his dad, this was like a tribute to him or something.
I just wrote a note of that.
I was going through our like iMessage thread trying to piece together what this show was.
Yeah.
And I think the dad deaths segues into he talks about the like the great tornado that hit Las Vegas and then simulates.
Las Vegas? Yes.
Is that real?
There was one in like twenty nineteen years. Someone posted on the thread.
That reasons?
Yeah.
That's your duster.
Like anyway, he creates a tornado in the theater.
They wheel out what three giant fans on stage that are like twenty feet tall.
Taller than a house. Taller than a million dollar house.
And they just turn them on and they just create a tornado inside it,
which means they are just blasting garbage like into your mouth.
So much trash.
Just garbage starts flying.
Just more trash than air in front of you.
Just crumbled paper and trash and confetti.
Just flying around this whole place.
And we were all like, wow, this is actually pretty cool.
And then it's like, and then it keeps going for like what felt like fifteen minutes.
So we're all just like screaming, laughing because this thing doesn't stop.
Nothing else is happening.
And it's just like flying around going everywhere.
And it's like really like we had we had drinks.
They were going into our drinks. They were going into our mouths.
If you and Eva had not gotten to a glass of wine, maybe it had a couple sips.
And then just like now it's all just like literal toilet paper.
It's just I don't know. I'm not going to ask if it's recycled or not.
But either we even clean toilet paper.
I don't want to get it in my beverage.
Toilet paper, paper towel, confetti, cardboard.
Yeah, just like hitting you in the face.
It's just like a big roll. It's like something big.
You would say ow once in a while.
Yeah, it was so funny.
We were all just looking at each other like we couldn't believe it was real.
And that's how we closed the show.
I think you just they do an encore of the trash tornado.
They just do it again.
They did the and now for the ending the middle again.
I think because it's all on the floor already.
And the fans just whip it right back up and spin it around again.
And it was on the you remember it was on the floor at the beginning of the show because they don't.
I think they don't clean the theater.
So that's where the garbage starts. It starts on the floor.
So you're walking into a theater full of garbage.
It's a spoiler.
It's a spoiler on the floor.
This trash is from my dreams. You'll see.
Oh, it was so good, though.
I mean, I would have, you know, and that's when they said that.
So the show abruptly closed like a few months after.
Yeah, we see it drag going drops dead.
The show closes and they lie.
Like everything with Chris Angel is just a lie.
And he's like, we're closing it so we can get ready for a big European tour.
It's like there's no way they can travel those garbage fans.
There's they wouldn't fit on an aircraft carrier.
So the talent of the show really is just ownership of giant fans.
That's what he's really displaying.
I bought these or at least them.
I don't know.
Oh, the other thing, another detail he does.
He saws a woman in half his female sidekick with a giant saw.
You remember this, Scott?
And then he goes, he tells the crowd, I go through a lot of women, but I always keep the lower part.
And we're all like, oh, do I have sex with a pair of legs in a vagina?
It's like, hey, fellas, isn't that what we all want?
Get rid of that part that talks and laughs and loves.
We found out in a review that they said this joke has survived like for Chris Angel show.
Somehow I didn't remember it or see it before, but like he loves that joke so much.
He's been doing it for like 15 or 20 years.
You also, when you were on previously on the Kblip episode, you brought up a joke.
This was before we had seen the show and you brought up a joke where he like, it was just like the width of something that's going to get cut through or a blade or something.
And like three inches, three inches.
And he did exactly that in this.
Yes, it was always he brings a guy up from the audience and he's like, how thick do you think that is?
And the guy's like, I don't know, three inches.
And he's like, three inches.
I bet you've said that before.
Just like bring up a guy to humiliate him.
Say yes.
The premise is that he said it.
He said this like three inches.
Okay.
Do you want to do this or not?
Yes, it's hard.
I'm sorry.
Don't make me say it out loud.
How did those jokes do in the room?
Can I ask?
Nothing did well.
No one was laughing.
I mean, no, my camera, my camera eats shit.
Eat shit.
It does terrible.
That was the only thing we saw.
I would check the like tickets, like the seating chart every night and see like no one's going to the show.
And when we were there, like, yeah, there were over a thousand empty seats, I think.
Right.
Yeah.
Entire areas that you know, you could they were also starting to give away tickets completely for free.
They're just like, how do we get bodies into this?
We was not free for us because Jason, you had the determination to meet him because he was offering this for anyone who bought a certain.
Who bought a certain level of ticket.
Oh, yeah.
So they said like, because there are more people there.
We looked right before the show started and it was still completely empty besides our row.
And then we went there and there were like a few hundred people there.
And then you had a meet and greet after the show where if you bought a ticket, you meet Chris Angel.
And then we get online with like a few hundred people.
And then someone's like, this line is only for if you paid for tickets and like a hundred people leave.
It's like, oh, yeah, everyone here is just comped to like, like they're just like handing out tickets.
They're just like handing out tickets in the casino or, you know, beforehand or like half the place like taxi drivers.
They're just like, please come, come be body.
See the show.
As soon as we saw the ticket prices, I slash them 25 percent.
But so we did. OK, so we did that meet and greet.
Yes.
And we waited to meet him and you get a picture.
And I was wrecked.
And I was somebody handed me a drink that they decided they didn't want.
And I was going to wrap it up because I did get my drink down before all the toilet paper went into it.
And by the end of the line, by the time we got to him, I was definitely like, oh, boy.
And now I get to meet Chris Angel. Whoa.
And I also I was so just like blown away by the thing and in the spirit of it and just laughing so hard.
And the sheer volume of trash on the floor was so crazy that I and I'm sorry if I embarrassed you or anyone.
I was whether if you noticed or cared.
But I just like took a lot of the long strings of toilet paper and just wore it like so many scarves.
And I had like draping down from almost like, you know, like like the way Chris would dress with a bunch of like danglies and spiderwebs.
So I'm draped in trash and drunk as we step up to actually meet Chris.
So we go up to meet him. So I was recording the audio.
I do have a clip. I weighed whether or not to play this.
It's very embarrassing. It's extremely intimate.
This is me very drunkenly like gushing to Chris Angel.
It was magical to watch because I was like, who's going to do the talking here?
Not realizing you would do 100 percent.
I went in so hard and also was not shy about my opinion of Mike Hammer and his comedy.
I was like, I was trying to save the show. I was trying to make the show something better, something more entertaining.
So this is a let's see if let's see.
So much paper and plastic in my mouth.
It was the most I've ever had.
It was so much paper in my mouth.
I really, I really love this so much.
I'm so like, I'm like just.
That's why we're here. We will. We will. We love you.
Totally immersive. More of your life.
Then Tom Sharp, like he directed Borat.
Like he just says that as we're walking away.
And he said what?
He's like, oh, OK.
Like I think Tom was like, just like this is not like a mentally disabled guy.
I know you might think that from how he's just telling you how much he loves you.
I thought it was very constructive.
I thought it was very kind and complimentary.
I was trying to help. But it's definitely embarrassing to listen.
I love you. You're incredible. Your life is incredible.
Your life is incredible. I remember that in the moment.
You know what? My metaphor for it, you know what it felt like to me was like,
you know, in Taken when Liam Neeson's on the phone and his daughter is going to get taken
and he says, just shout anything you see, just like until you're out of the room,
say anything you see about who's taking you.
And that's how I've that's how that interaction seemed to me was that you were like,
I know I'm only going to have 30 seconds here.
And if I could get any of my real thoughts into his brain and register them.
So I'm just going to fill the air with opinions from second one to second 30 and shout them all.
And maybe one will actually impact. You know what?
What I wasn't counting on was how phoned in the show is.
And that is ultimately, and I'm sorry if you're listening, Chris,
but I do think he's a lazy man and I don't I don't think he really tried.
And what I was hoping for is like the Chris Angel like masterpiece,
like really trying to be like this is what's moving to me.
This is my life. This is like how I want to be remembered.
And so to see it that night and see how phoned in it was and just like a bunch of,
you know, filler basically it's and so much bad comedy.
And then, of course, we go through his Instagram later and see like Mike Hammer like there,
besides Gary Oldman, I think is his like best friend in the world.
They comment on each other's posts constantly.
So I was like, I definitely wasn't winning any any fan like no angel by saying,
oh, you got to cut that Mike Hammer guy. He sucks.
He's not funny. Oldman sucks. That movie, the Churchill movie is boring.
But I'm letting him do interviews. Cut him from your life.
A few months later, he posted due to recent unforeseen events,
a mystica is being converted to a touring show for international locations.
Chris Angel will continue to feature and promote the production on his new television series,
Chris Angels Magic with the Stars, which was a show that he he did.
So basically they're like, look, we already filmed the show.
He's going to be talking about it in every episode.
But the show is closing because no one is seeing it.
The timeline is really insane of just what befell Chris Angel in this in this stretch of time.
Show only opens in March. We saw it in April.
September 30th, Dragon dies, which so funny to have like just the way this evolves.
We're like, have you heard of Franco Dragon? Why?
No, I have not. Suddenly we're on a text thread and I'm talking about Dragon every day.
Wow, Dragon and Dragon's part of it. The legend Dragon.
And then we're there. Dragon is here. Dragon is in front of me.
Dragon is in front of me. Viva Dragon.
Several months later, Dragon is dead from zero presence in my life at the beginning of twenty twenty two to deceased at the end.
I always just this morning I watched a video and Scott, I sent it to you.
It's like four or five minutes.
It's from a channel on YouTube with a very generic name like I Hollywood TV.
Chris talking up a mystic so hard and he's like so I said it was very Trumpy because he's just talking such a big game and he's like there's seventy five illusion.
Some video. I don't think there were three illusions.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe that was his trailer on his way because he has his own account with very intense trailers plugging his shows.
And it was just so odd compared to what I knew your guys is experience was big fans and been racist comedy.
And then we left. Yeah. Yeah.
Garbage in your drinks. He was on this morning show.
And when he well, OK, you heard how we describe the show.
Now here's him before people had seen it.
It's my story of how I became Chris Angel.
But it's really everyone's story.
It's the first spectacle after covid.
We're bringing back optimism.
It's the purest form of magic.
The magic of emotion.
This is how he is building what we've just described as a grab bag hit or miss variety show.
Yeah. Very big on saying it was the first big new show back after covid.
You know, there's video of me walking down Las Vegas Boulevard, not a car in sight.
And you can see a bus go through the background.
And he's like, it was so weird.
It's not a car.
You know, but the TV show, The Magic with the Stars.
Do you know the detail about that?
Well, here I was going to say in the timeline.
OK, so so September 30th, Dragon dies.
October 14th, some headlines for Magic with the Stars.
Is this what you were going to bring up?
Just two weeks after his like is the guy who shepherded his show.
Then like, all right, I guess I'll focus on my TV show.
And then again, the Los Las Vegas Review Journal in published reports, R&B star
genuine was left gasping and lost consciousness after attempting a water escape routine,
proving there is high risk on and off stage in Angel's empire.
So he almost after his partner dies.
Then I contend that almost certainly faked to try to get some press for the show.
I hadn't thought of it at first.
And then someone was like, there's no way.
No, like, I think, yeah, that sounds like we got to get people writing about this.
Let's what if I almost killed genuine?
Are you saying do you think genuine was in on it or is he's like,
we'll we'll leave him hanging for a couple of minutes.
He locked the tank.
Wait for it. Wait, when? Not till I give the signal.
Sorry, genuine.
You'll see it. It's going to get it's going to get butts in the seats that you show.
It's hard to say because magic is like professional wrestling.
It comes from the lineage of carnies where it's just like, oh, this could be amazing
or it could be amazing. And you might also be lying.
It just might also be a lot of lies.
Wait, and when was the blip fire?
So OK, so September 30th, I go and dies October 14th.
Genuine almost dies October 16th.
The final of Mystica is blamed on the death of Dragon.
But also it was not nobody was ever there.
Then I think early November reports of arson at his restaurant.
Kaplip Kaplip almost burns down as an article pointed out an event
that was oddly left unreported by the media.
I think we're all still confused. We did all episode about it.
I think we're still confused about the details of the Kaplip arson.
I think Chris set his restaurant on fire to try to burn it down.
Seem and keeping.
And as typical with everything he does, it was like done incompetently and lazily.
And it didn't work.
The guy can't even like get his shit together, do a proper insurance scam.
I do fire stuff all the time. We got a guy in the show.
He's going to run through on fire. It's going to burn the restaurant.
They just like one one wall got singed on the outside and they put it out.
Damn.
He didn't count on how good the Overton Fire Department.
Neighbor runs out.
Is everything OK? Should I call it? No, no, it's fine.
Oh, Wilhand. No, it's it's probably better if it burns.
Honestly, this place is ancient. You'll be glad it's gone.
He's trying to tell the firefighters. No, it's OK.
Don't worry about it. It'll be fine.
So you're probably more needed somewhere else.
The great city of Overton is probably someone having a heart attack.
Go save class. Circle back.
Oh, my cat's in a tree a block away.
I can hear it. Do you hear it?
Get my kitty out of the tree. Not the restaurant. I don't care.
I'm just remembering now. Wasn't a mistake a part of some covid relief money scam?
Well, I got all that too.
Sorry, Scott, we don't mean to interrupt you.
No, no, no. Things come back to us.
We made such a mistake not getting the covid money for this podcast.
I really think we could have done it.
I think PPP loans are like the most successful scam in the history of the country.
We should have done it. And we didn't. Yes.
I am mad about it. Kind of legitimately upset with us.
OK, wait, Scott. OK, you're ahead of me on this.
The number I had forgotten.
The number. Well, do I build it up?
Do I build it up? OK, all right, I'll do this.
Loans given to his company Magic Revolution LLC.
Six point six million dollars.
I'm reading 11 million on that.
Well, you see, that is filled in by the four point three million given to Angel Productions Worldwide Inc.
OK, so that's what this was. So when you add them together, 11 million.
OK, so I forgot this aspect of it and it makes everything click into place.
Is that he had this name he thought of when he was 13.
Covid happened and he's like the government's giving it drag.
Go and the government's got they split the money.
Dragone has a you look at his wiki, a massive history of tax fraud allegations.
Yes, a huge scandal in 2012.
Scammers who were like Chris Angel's like, give us the late show.
Get 11 million dollars.
Put together a show for a few hundred thousand dollars and the show will be disaster enclosed.
And they fucking kept the money and then Dragone was probably going to spill any fucking killed him.
Allegedly, allegedly, allegedly, allegedly for everyone in the room.
Chris, it is getting too hot.
That's really good about this.
Shut up, Dragone.
I'm going to clear my head in Egypt for a little while.
Yes, you do that.
I got you a trip to Egypt, Dragone.
He suggested it.
Why don't you go take a nice, relaxing trip?
You fucking killed him and then closed the show.
Oh my God, I have no doubt in my mind.
It is weighing on me so much, Chris.
I'm not like you with your magic and your secrets.
I have to tell what my secrets are.
Dragone, get in the big box.
I want to show you a new trick.
Get in the big box.
I have an ass been there.
I've always wanted to show you.
That was the other thing.
He auctioned off all of his tricks like a few years ago.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, right.
He sold everything.
He sold all his wires and big cages.
OK, this was a COVID relief scam.
That's what a Mystica was.
I can't believe we forgot that part of it.
Wait, because a Mystica, the subtitle was like the mystery revealed, right?
It was called a Mystica, the secret revealed.
That was the full name of the show.
It's still listed as that on chrisangel.com.
They forgot to take down the page on chrisangel.com.
It still says get your tickets now with the official trailer.
And the secret revealed, yeah, the secret is that it was a COVID scam.
I think there's never been an episode that would make one person more furious.
Maybe of any podcast.
You know what he might, I mean, because I know I met this magician Harrison Greenbaum,
a really talented guy, funny guy who does the show at New York, New York.
And he did that fake kablit menu website.
Oh, yeah.
And Chris's lawyers pounced on him.
So let me know if you guys get any emails.
Yeah, sure.
Well, you might know before us.
You've been worth cutting.
I might start with you.
No, everything I say is satirical, obviously.
This is a comedy podcast.
It's an important comedy podcast about theme parks.
And that's where all we make up crazy make-em-ups.
There's stuff that we don't think.
The cold open of this episode is just one of us saying allegedly dozens of times.
Ugliness, satire.
We just need to spray allegedlys all over this episode,
like so many bits of trash being spewed out by giant fans.
A hurricane of allegedlys.
He 100% killed him.
Okay.
Only you with the poor amount of money here.
You know Jason's uncomfortable if he brings up the guest's money.
Not the first time.
He did Borat.
We all know Borat.
We all love Borat.
Oh my god.
This has a good arc to it that we did solve the mystery of the Mystica.
What is the mystery?
Solve it.
It might take you months.
You might have to do a podcast about it.
He might be proud of us for figuring it out.
Yeah.
Because we figured out the mystery.
Boys, you did it.
So many fools never learned, never figured out the truth, secrets.
It was like the producers though.
Yeah.
But with some new tricks that the producers themselves didn't figure out.
There's so many scams around this time.
This is just one of the most high profile ones.
There was another guy, this is lower scale,
but there was a comedy hypnotist named Marc Savard.
He got $300,000 presumably to keep his show open.
That's the idea of the loans.
Now you have to keep working and keep paying people.
As soon as he got it, he said, well, due to mask mandates, we're closing.
We got it, these masks.
But why?
I'm with you, Mike.
I think everyone listening should be upset that you didn't get in on the loans too.
I assume that people listening didn't get in on the loans.
Most of them.
The people who did are laughing and laughing at us.
Us the fools.
Of course.
It's a sexual business.
It's like registered.
That's right.
Guests to pay.
Yes, even though COVID did not impact the production of the show in almost any way.
There was a half second delay when we would make a joke
and not know if the other thought it was funny.
There would be all these times where we'd go, no, no, no, you go.
I'd have to cut those out when I was editing.
That's worth $100,000.
You deserve $100,000 for your editing suffering.
Well, look, when Trump gets back in, we'll retroactively do it.
Yeah, when the next one.
The new round.
That's it.
We cracked the mystery.
Any final observations about this thing?
Is it possible to run this through?
I've half-assedly tried to do the rules of Blackjack with the things that we've talked about.
What should these things have done?
Should they have hit or stood or doubled down or cashed out?
What should have happened to Chris?
Did he not do enough?
Should he have done a third show?
Is that the problem?
I think he did cash out.
I think he did the ultimate cash out.
We were expecting too much of him, I think.
His heart's not in it.
I think he's a businessman.
He's just in it to grab cash.
And he grabbed cash while we all ate trash.
There you go.
Yeah, for us, it was a trash grab.
And I did.
I wore it.
I proudly wore it.
And I had a good time doing it.
I wouldn't have done it without you.
Jason, thank you for being the lightning rod that got me to a Mystica.
Thank you.
To a magical evening.
And we found the underground house that was also about cryonics.
That was a very strange experience.
Yeah, there was a whole other weird scheme being run.
Whatever the underground house is.
Do these places find you or do you find them?
I don't know. I just keep my eyes out for stuff.
We found out there was an underground house in Las Vegas.
Wait a second.
In 2016, it was listed at $48 million.
The cryonics house?
No, this is a different one.
Okay.
Listener, if you want to know what we're talking about, there's a really easy and fun way,
which is look up the Imagine Dragons music video called, I believe, Monday.
Watch this music video.
And this was entirely filmed in this bizarre underground house that's meant to be an indoor-outdoor house,
except it's all in a bunker so that it's meant to survive an apocalypse.
We were at a place where this was filmed.
Undergroundhouse.Vegas.
And that's the house's official website.
And yeah, it was built as a bunker, but I don't think it had any kind of nuclear bunker qualities.
It's just underground.
And I had no plan that you could live there.
So it couldn't survive?
No, I think it has a ventilation system so you can breathe air.
But if there was a nuke, you would just die pretty quick.
I think you could survive.
There's like 16 hours of air that you would live on.
So everybody in the underground house would get a lot of phone calls like,
hey, you got any room in there?
And then lots of people rush down and then just die two seconds after everybody.
I bet it's still for sale.
It's 3970 Spencer Street, Vegas.
It is still currently listed at $5.9 million.
And if you look at the listing history, yeah, it's been on Zillow 188 days, but we went more than that ago.
So I think it's probably taken off and put back with a different price a few times.
And it was built in the 60s.
It's really cool.
Oh yeah, it was listed in 2019 for $18 million.
It's weird though.
It's a weird house.
You never want to live there.
You'd go insane living there.
It's cool to walk around.
It was run by a guy who was like a big cryonics guy.
He went into the room and he talked about how his body was going to be in there for like 40,000 years and whatever.
It felt kind of like Sex House kind of vibes.
It felt like...
Yeah, there were like poles.
I think you could rent it for parties.
It was like a club random with a cryonics chamber.
Bill wishes.
Easy, easy, don't get too excited.
They weren't doing tours.
So another, I'll give you another little scoop, a little confession here.
We had to pretend that we were interested in buying it.
And so I emailed the realtor and was like, hey, you think you could get us on a tour of this underground house?
Yeah, do you want to buy it?
I was like, yes.
And so, you know, we can't afford that.
We had to pool like the finances from like a bunch of us on the trip and send financial statements and be like...
And I said, yeah, we're from a company.
I'll read what I texted the thread for our backstory when we were heading over.
We are from a yet to be announced venture considering buying property as a Vegas headquarters.
We're working mostly on metaverse focused ventures with an AI machine learning bent.
As we gear up, we're also launching a vertical and streaming production.
So I was like, everyone remember this is what we're doing.
I don't think I remember there was an AI.
This is well, this is 2022.
A little head of the curve.
And so the guy gave us a tour, but I think he could kind of see through us that we just wanted to check out the underground house.
But you can do that with any realtor, even mansions.
You just have to convince them that you could afford a down payment.
So between like four of us, we showed if we had a, you know, showed your Eva one of them.
You showed your real financial information.
That was the only way that they would let us in.
Sound like IMDb's and stuff.
And then this guy's other business, he was very sweet guy and showed us around.
And then he had, he sold this money.
Do you remember he sold money with gold in the money?
He's like, this money will never lose value.
He sold gold embedded his own cash.
He made it.
It's not like a U.S. currency that he just like, no, it's like, I mean, I don't know if it has his picture instead of a president.
But basically it's like, he's like, this is money that cannot lose value because there's gold in the money.
Okay.
Can I hold the money?
It's called.
Sure you can.
Goldback maybe.
Is this it?
What?
Are goldbacks legal?
I think this is it.
They are not accepted as legal tender by the federal government.
Goldback has a Wikipedia page and check out Goldback if you want to, you know, survive in our coming apocalypsy kind of world that we're going to be entering pretty soon.
Listeners, here's your hot tip.
Get all your money into goldbacks.
In the goldbacks.
And if like a bunch, you know, hey, if a bunch of listeners met and got along at the Groove Blender and decided we get along great, we all like to live in Las Vegas forever together, then just send all your information to the underground house.
Go to the website.
And I love the idea.
Just invite us over once in a while.
Let us come party at the house that a dozen fans all share together.
With waist high stacks of goldbacks.
Yeah.
We promise we won't take your gold back.
Uncle Scrooge diving into the goldbacks.
They said one Vegas goldback is worth $3.75 at the end of 2021.
So that's not too bad.
Okay.
They've been appreciating.
Geez.
Okay.
Well, hot tip.
Oh, now it's worth four bucks.
Hey, shit.
Is that just while we've been recording?
The world's first.
In the episodes so we can survive goldbacks.
Just check out goldback.com, the world's first physical interchangeable gold money that is designed to accommodate even small transactions.
How's the website look reputable?
Definitely.
I'm going to put all my money in goldbacks.
Okay.
Well, then I'll see here.
I'll start winding it down while you while you get out your wallet and start and make your first gold back.
This is great.
I'm a certified wallet inspector.
So I'll start the process.
But for now, I'm so glad we caught you before you became a goldback millionaire.
Jason Warner, you survived podcast the right in city nights.
Thank you for closing it out with us.
We couldn't do this, especially this month without you.
Thank you guys.
What a always a pleasure.
Happy to come over and shit talk and burn bridges, criminal, make enemies and criminal anger.
People who have been litigious against people, you know, I mean, Chris, like you think there's a possibility that Chris Angel hasn't killed people.
Well, we'll all be the first to find out if I die.
This will be crazy to listen to if I die mysteriously.
And weirdly, they know what was so well, we dedicate the series to Jason Walters memory.
At a certain point, I just wouldn't be able to buy a ticket to his show.
I've been thrown out of there.
I've harassed him.
You yelled a bunch of stuff at him while meeting him.
Life is incredible.
You said your life is incredible in a way that he could maybe question.
I also like remember I said this on the show, too, that he's like we we said we all went to Kiblipp when he was like, oh, come on.
We went your arrest. That is a commitment.
We all live in Los Angeles.
We flew into this town, drove an hour more in an hour.
That's based on the lie that's on your website that says 45 minutes bullshit.
We did the drive. That's our 15 minimum.
We all did it and then and came and what three of us are wearing the shirts and your response is.
There's more shirts in the hotel rooms, too, because you brought us.
I mean, you could just like eyeballing security.
He was dripping with disdain at the indignity of having to meet fans because the show was not selling tickets.
Like this was not what he wanted to be doing.
Look, the hogs are going to get me.
This is what it will also.
You know, one more thing before I write it down.
Do you remember how I don't know what order to present this in that you you say that he phoned it in and yet the stress seemed very high with him because he's trying to mount this show because we all went out to dinner at the nice restaurant next to the theater.
And then we were so I think I went to the bathroom and then I came back like I'd seen a ghost but better than a ghost.
I was like this part of the story.
There's a little room.
It's like the private dining room and the walls are lined with nice bottles of wine and he is in there.
It's him and he it looks like he's got like a bunch of papers out like as if he's doing his taxes.
He had a bunch of receipts out and he had little glasses on like what Homer wears when he's dealing with business.
Little half glasses.
Hmm.
And and then and I think you then tried to tap on the glass.
Yeah, I tried to get his attention.
I tried to talk to the guard and I was like, hey, oh, hey, we're seeing him.
We're here to see the show.
I was like, yeah, he's not talking to you.
Mr. Angel is a busy man.
So you escorted out of the theater, escorted out of a Ruth's dress.
But then there on it, I was going through Instagrams from this era and there is a photo of exactly what we saw.
A view of him in the little wine room with the half glass looking so stressed out.
And here is the caption.
My life, a tortured creator striving to turn imagination into reality.
Months of creative challenges focused on achieving that one incredible moment that makes it all worthwhile.
Then in the blink of an eye, I'm back to the monster I created and have become a slave to.
I mean, the incredible moment is checking his account balance to see like the covid money came through.
That's the moment it made it worthwhile.
And the stress is definitely like, what do you mean?
I got to pay the dancers like as like the money that he's like trying to like scam is getting less and less with how expensive the show is like it's fucking garbage.
How much could it cost?
Well, it's like a whole theater full of paper.
You're going to need like a thousand bucks a night.
It's trash.
You reuse it.
Go to the dumpsters.
It's what they deserve.
Well, it gets in people's mouths, Chris.
It's got to be clean trash.
Little clean.
Ah, they must have clean trash in my mouth.
These demanding sons of bitches.
What do you mean the syringes in the dumpster?
People get stuck with syringes.
People probably use them.
There's no liquid of any kind in the syringes anymore.
There might be nice stuff in the syringes.
Get some high.
They're probably all junkies.
All these people are going to look like the end of the movie Beethoven.
That's what I think.
Dragon.
The show was meant to tank and close.
Actually, when you go on Ticketmaster, you would go on.
And if you search Chris Angel, a mystical would not show up.
He did not put his name in the title of the listing.
So even if you're a huge Chris Angel fan and we're going to Vegas, you couldn't even search and find that show.
So I think what probably happened is he was just like, we won't spend any money on it.
It'll close and move on and then we'll keep the money.
And Dragon was probably like, Chris, we can turn this around.
We can make this better, Chris.
And the Dragon magic, it's in me.
I can do this.
And that's why he had to pay the price.
Which could have been the price of a meal or a gold back transaction.
We don't know.
Jason has not fully defined what the price was.
Do you think any time like one of his employees is giving him trouble, he's like, you look stressed.
Maybe you need a trip to Cairo.
He's like, OK, I'm backing off, Chris.
Forget it, Chris. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I know this really nice spa.
There's a great Jacuzzi you can get in with a lid that closes on top of it.
Genuine knows all about that one.
Genuine almost took a trip to Cairo.
All right. You survived you long ago.
So let me now say, well, let me ask.
I'm never sure when I make this offer, but let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
No, we're striking.
Yeah, nothing right now.
That's right. You can't. Yes.
I'm not plugging.
I'm not. No, I have nothing coming out right now.
Everything's coming out.
Unless New York Times.
I don't know if you.
Oh, when does this episode come out?
Soon. It might be out.
Oh, well, I've heard August 20th, New York Times.
There's going to be a mention of my animatronic robot, Dale, that I built and have been performing within Los Angeles.
Yes.
You could probably do a whole episode on that.
Jason, if there's any if there is any possible Dale interaction, if we could have him, if we could.
I don't want to go supposing because Dale is a mindblower.
Dale is more mind blowing than even Chris Angel's incredible house.
It really is genuine.
You have like you really have like created something pretty unreal.
Better than anything Disney's done lately.
Yeah, I agree.
Being that Disney's not doing anything lately.
So yeah, read about Jason's animatronic cowboy in the New York Times.
I'm so psyched about this.
Hopefully. Fingers crossed.
Maybe it'll get cut.
But yeah, check it out.
Geez, great.
Well, congrats and thanks for closing out the series with us.
So happy to have you.
As for us, we really hope you have enjoyed podcast the ride Sin City Nights.
For anybody who came out to the Groove Blender, thank you so much.
Hope you've enjoyed kind of getting off of your regularly scheduled theme park programming.
We've really loved it.
If you want to do this again, if we should do a Sin City Nights to raise your voice, I don't know to who to us.
It's not like you have to tell forever dog to let us know.
I don't know.
It's up to us.
Right to the Las Vegas press.
Let them know to give us good reviews.
And if we see an article, then we'll do another one of these.
But I hope so because there's so much Vegas.
I think we left on the table.
And I'd love to do more.
Thank you, Mike, for the Sin City Nights theme.
It's a banger.
Thank you, Aaron, for the logo.
It's wonderful.
We now, after all this stuff, after a bunch of mega episodes, we're going to take a summer break, at least two weeks, on the main feed.
But the party keeps going on the Patreon, as always.
So bonus episodes are there.
Podcasts are at the second gate or on the VIP tier Club 3.
All of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
But for now, the Sin City Nights are over.
The dawn is coming across the breaking across the horizon.
And I guess we go back to mostly Anaheim and Orlando days.
Yeah.
Mostly.
But, you know, sometimes.
Talk about a lot of fucking other bullshit, too.
Yeah.
Yeah, mostly Aerosmith.
It's like Hop in the Grave.
Oh, yeah.
Bye, Jason.
All right.
And now for Jason's trip to Cairo.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.