Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, where the topic of today's episode is maybe
possibly being considered to be the recent announcements of the Destination D event in
Florida.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined by Scott Gardner.
Yeah, we're always dreaming up possibilities that could change the course of Podcast The
Ride forever.
Anyway, bye.
Bye.
There's nothing more to say about that.
The new PTR fiscal year starts October 1st, and we cannot make any official proclamations
until that.
Michael Carlson.
I'm here, yeah, and I just want to not go on the record with everything I'm saying today.
Everything I'm saying today is speculation and a possibility, but it's not something
I necessarily believe.
Morsels, morsels to be dreamt on, banteed about.
Can I just get to the cut to the chase here?
This is like trying to feed someone dinner and it's just like one potato chip, one French
fry, it's one pretzel bite and going, isn't this nice?
This is a big meal for you, huh?
This is nice, huh?
A bone from a chicken.
Yeah.
Like now this came from the kind of rotisserie chicken that could be possible at a future
dinner.
Yes, yes.
The one bean, the one bean with a fork and you're cutting the slices of the bean.
Right.
Except that most people are like, okay, beans here, let's talk bean.
So, Disney's dropped the new bean and we're here to talk about every quarter of it.
Let's go.
Well, there's a lot of content creators, including us, that need to stretch this out and need
to have some excitement because of the excitement.
Luckily, we've built in not having to be excited.
Yeah, we don't need to get invited to anything.
Sometimes I lament that because we would be rich.
We would be rich as pirates if we were, but no, it's good.
Pirates like the kind in the lounge, in the lounge bar that's coming to Magic Kingdom.
be like, not rich, but maybe wealthier.
I don't know.
Maybe that's wrong.
That's the same thing, isn't it?
Maybe not a little wealthier.
More rich and wealthy.
Wealthier could be we make five more dollars a month.
Sure.
Okay, okay.
If you're setting the bar there.
But then with a wear and tear on our souls that we have to do the YouTube thumbnails
with the bug out faces and that why is the new thing, Mr.
Beast has led the way that
now it's not enough to just have an irritating photo of yourself.
It's got to be like an illustration.
It's got to be a fake piece of art.
It's a render.
Why did that get decided?
That's new, the new, and then you cut to Dar Man.
I don't know if anybody listens to or everybody watches the great inspirational Dar Man content.
He's made the choice that he's the one, he does all of these like morality plays like
father, shame's daughter in wheelchair lives to regret it.
And then it'll be a thumbnail where like they have fake eyes.
They have like Muppet eyes.
He's gone one step further than the bizarre like, and you're staring at it like, why did
you?
So it's a regular eyes aren't enough.
They have to be so like perfectly piece of paper white that you can't have real eyes
anymore.
Dar Man recommended.
This is the most like AI content not generated by AI you've ever seen.
Mr.
Beast may have had a small come to God moment because I feel like he posted about
like we uploaded some new videos and we found that the thumbnails where it's a picture of
me and I close my mouth, we get more views than the ones where I'm like doing a giant
open mouth smile.
That's okay.
Well, that's a good realization.
It's probably made them a little less irritating, but I still wonder why it's paintings.
What was that calculation?
And then also like you imagine having to be this, like, you know, when people go off on
old man Scorsese who doesn't understand, but he didn't have to make his movie posters like,
yeah, like, okay, so we found out less people will see casino if the we need them all the
mouths to be closed.
We've run the numbers on like this is a hell.
This is a hell.
Yeah, it's all no matter how much money they have.
Yeah, somebody should do like run the algorithm on just like things we say and then be like,
you know, you can't you have to say whatever like a magic.
About 15 more times and you have to say wishes 25 more times.
And this is this stimulates the brain enough to make somebody want to listen to more.
It sounds hellish, but it is where content is headed.
So yeah, yeah.
Computers.
People are already doing the work computers do.
So the AI is what you're saying.
The AI is here.
Well, you're describing a theory.
You're describing a theory called human bots where people decide to bot themselves.
This is a very come up with by a friend of the show.
Buzz Buzz.
I think it's one of you.
See, you walked right into it.
He's been saying this for years.
I and you look, we agree.
He's a controversial figure, but you got to agree with a lot of his teachings.
I well, he and I agree on a lot of that type of thing.
Yeah, yes.
We've talked about many things.
Yes.
Aging.
We've we're going to he thinks we're going to not we're going to be the last generation not to
live forever, which I believe that was at least a couple of years ago.
Maybe he's different or he's changed his ideas now.
But yes, that makes a lot of sense.
And Mr.
Beast has bought it himself and he's reaping the rewards.
So you say so.
But you're you agree with Bug, but you're also a pro botting yourself.
I don't know what I am.
I can't decide.
I have bought myself a check in, though.
I have bought it myself as much as I can when it comes to checking and getting alerts.
You're competing with bots because you're trying to get alerts as fast as and get those
toy sales as fast as bots are.
Right.
You have to be partially a human bot.
Absolutely.
I do.
And you could probably automate some of that if you taught yourself a little bit of.
Well, I tried.
I got a Swedish.
I got a guy in Sweden to make me a bot.
I just never ended up needing it.
Right.
Well, that's the problem.
It's too many little men.
You need to be the bot.
I need to be the bot.
Be your own bot.
Speaking of being my own bot, because I have all these alerts, I got a free 10 pack of
about two or three weeks ago.
Oh, free chocolate bars.
That might be the key to botting yourself.
If you the contents biggest human bot, if you eat enough of his bars, that's the secret.
If you have like three a day, you'll be a bot within a month.
Yeah.
Well, I didn't eat enough, I don't think.
But I if there are more free ones somewhere, I just got an alert said you want 10 free
Mr.
Beast bars.
I said, all right.
I clicked it and they showed up.
How are they?
They're pretty good.
You get them in Target.
OK.
Yeah.
It's just milk chocolate, like four ingredients.
Oh, wait, I've seen these in Target.
OK.
Yeah.
It's nothing that weird, I don't think.
Oh, so they aren't like healthy bars.
These are no candy bars.
Those are chocolate.
I mean, it's better than probably just nerds.
But a lot of things are better than nerds.
Not taste wise, but health wise.
You know, this guy knows what I'm talking about.
I know what you're talking about.
Your intestines are all nerd lined.
Well, that's your little chocolate boy, you know.
So I'm interested.
If you got a colonoscopy on the way, like, what is that?
Doctors are seeing something they've never seen.
And then it's all like it's all nerds and they're all alive and singing.
My lower intestine looks like a nerd's rope, the gummy rope with the nerds stuck into it.
That's what happens when you eat a lot of nerds.
Sure.
It's not weird.
It's not bad.
That's what happens.
OK.
So this is OK.
Just if you're if you're the kind of listener who pays very close attention to the things that we say,
we I think teased a second gate that is not what you're listening to.
Yeah.
What I call Disney's first screen ride.
And that that is recorded.
That is coming.
But we shoved it down in the order because of the thrilling announcements
brought to us by Daddy Tomorrow at Destination D23,
an event that was definitely on my radar, on my calendar.
I blocked off the weekend for all of the exciting new
Disney parks announcements and dreams and wishes.
And we're going to break them down for you here.
Yeah.
Now, I have to say about this, but I am going to pay them a compliment.
I think these I knew that I knew this was coming at some point,
because these are the off year events that they do in between the like big Anaheim
conventions and this.
Yeah.
So explain the difference.
This is a way in the difference.
OK.
So this is held at the Contemporary.
So this is in Orlando.
Is it always an Orlando event?
They do them in, I think, Japan, too.
They have.
Yeah, I can't remember what is it.
Do they call Destination D in Japan?
I don't know the answer to this.
Yeah, no, I they do events in Japan as well.
They do.
Yeah.
And so this is like
it is it's essentially a smaller convention,
but I think it does seem more pleasant because
it's a lot fewer guests.
OK, you get to hang out at the convention,
the Contemporary for a few days, which is nice.
And all the programming is like sequential.
So you're guaranteed getting into everything.
Oh, you're not hustling.
And that's OK.
OK.
So now it is.
And I was surprised.
So it's like a three hundred dollar ticket for like three days of programming.
OK, that sounds not reasonable.
OK, keep going.
It's on par with like you had to see the plush pile when you came in.
Oh, that's what this is for.
Yeah.
That'll be referenced next week.
Oh, yes.
They do offer discounted Contemporary in Grand Floridian.
Oh, so it's only eight hundred dollars a night.
Exactly.
No, I know.
Hampton in size.
Sure.
But the to buy a ticket, you have to pay.
You have to be a D23 gold member.
Oh, and what is that?
$99 a year.
God, God.
Yeah.
I can't be so mean.
I'm sure there are people listening to this who who do some of this
and attended this, and I hope that you get joy out of it.
It's fun to be had.
It's just maybe.
Yeah.
You don't see the dollars.
Money's piling up.
You got a con guy also.
No, we're a con guy.
And, you know, they they do always do a very good job of like
very specific merch, like they had all them
a bunch of Muppet Labs merch this time.
At one of the previous rounds, they had like a full suite of Pizza Rizzo
merch.
Oh, and that and and again, it's not it seems less like D23
or Comic-Con where you're like, you know, fighting to get it before it's gone.
Is any of the merch free?
Uh, I can't speak to that.
I have a guess.
I think you maybe got an early chance to get your picture with large figment.
Wow.
Who kind of?
I don't know.
He scares me a little.
Yes.
I'm large.
He's large, but his head is very small.
Yeah.
What happened?
Why are people accepting this?
All you have to do is make a suit.
You didn't redo the ride.
You're teasing and one of your god favorites might come back.
And then all it it's not the new ride.
It's a new suit.
So you didn't have to redo a whole ride that's bad.
All you had to make was a suit.
And what caused the head to need to be tinier?
Yes.
There was a walk around.
Did you like the old one?
I don't I don't know if I ever saw it in person, but I've seen side by sides
recently.
Just make the old one.
Why is the head so small?
I don't know why that's scary.
I have a whole nother take.
I don't like him big.
I know he's walked around a lot.
Sure.
Give me the baby Groot version of it.
I was going to say they've been working on the small guys.
Small.
Why are people swallowing this and enjoying it?
Well, this line.
OK, if all right, if I'm really even better than that.
It's a nerd's rope.
Imagination you can make him however big or small as you want.
Yeah.
In which case, make him real small.
Make him like fit my shirt.
So you're saying everybody who goes up for the photo op should decide
how big they want him.
Oh, boy, that would be good.
Bring in mid-sized, please.
You hand them a sheet that has his specifications, his size specifications.
You can say how big you want his head.
You can say how big you want his body.
Just fill out a form.
Yeah.
I don't know.
This whole thing.
Someone pointed out that, like, boy, that portal sure looks exactly like
the one Ralph would walk through when this was a wreck at Ralph.
Yes.
Well, and it also many people pointed out, it looks like the tunnel from A.
W.
Dynamite.
It looks like the pro wrestler's entrance.
Oh, is he coming out the good guy tunnel?
No, the heel tunnel, the bad tunnel.
There are two tunnels, one's good guy, one's bad guy.
He's a troublemaker.
Yeah.
Makes mischief.
There.
Yeah.
There have been.
This has only been going for a couple of days as we record this.
Recording this Monday morning for context to the two days before it comes out.
And I know that yesterday I saw just like
shrieks, beetle shrieks for this costume.
And I'm like, have fun, guys.
But I think you're performing this a little hard.
Yeah.
And for five hour lines for this
figment size that makes no sense.
And no.
Yeah.
And then right before I came over, I don't know if you guys saw this.
Something happened.
I saw it.
Yeah.
This is he fell.
We were OK.
Boy, that sums up all the announcements.
He just provided a visual metaphor for everything.
The Disney company, the current company, Bob Iger himself.
Yeah.
I think we retroactively should take all the anger towards Chipick
and throw it on Iger, too.
Well, that's what some of this article was about.
I feel it was kind of like, remember all that stuff that we were all.
We were really mean.
We gave his whatever we call it.
We call it Mr.
Turd's wild ride.
I remember he left.
And now it's become clear that some of the things like the Scarlett Johansson
really bad PR and the being muddy, but don't say gay, that maybe Iger
had his little mischievous figment pause.
That's right.
In some of these messes.
Maybe he was hoping that Chipick would pull a figment and collapse.
Well, that's the one walking out.
I never talked to Bug about this theory, but it's certainly a theory
I had right when the pandemic started that this was the plan the whole time.
Was to make this guy fall on his face.
I think that big article.
Where was the big article?
Yeah, I don't know.
I remember a couple of weeks ago.
CNBC, maybe.
Yes.
If you didn't read it, this big Iger, Chipick,
why the succession plan worked out so badly.
This big expose.
Yeah, it definitely lent a lot of credence to what you might have called
conspiracy theories before.
Yes.
You call them theories.
There are theories.
Well, this is unfortunate because I've already made a salt T-shirts
that say I live for those two shower days.
So I thought that was pretty cool.
A man who wakes up at 415 a.
m.
to start his day and exercise and then look at his phone
only after exercising and then works all day
and then insists on having the shower office that was built for Michael Eisner.
Eisner got the shower office.
I have worked for a company where someone told it's like,
oh, you know, the CEO has a shower in his office.
I was like, boy, that's weird.
And no one else was like, I feel like I was the only one who kept talking to me.
It was like, she had been the shower.
That's kind of strange, right?
The guys.
But aren't you?
But what are you saying now?
Eisner, who we love,
commissioned the shower office.
So don't we have to like shower offices?
We do have to like it.
That's the rule.
I thought you would like it that I thought.
I thought you uttered the phrase.
I love a two shower day.
It's very funny.
I that the company I used to work at is I think he
his two shower day was he would shower at the office.
And then he clearly had season tickets to the L.
A.
opera because they were always mass emailing the company.
Like he cannot use his opera tickets tonight if anyone
to opera tickets.
And it's like, didn't you just tell us all there's no money for raises
this year and you're offering us opera tickets?
Well, if to be fair, if he well, OK, it implies that he is making a lot of money
if he can afford constant opera tickets he can't even use.
So I guess you're right.
But at the company, it doesn't seem like
this is something to dive into telemarketer style, like get down to the bottom of it.
But I don't it doesn't sound like the company's paying for the opera tickets.
Well, that's hard to say, because the company cars
that are meant to be doing deliveries were often picking up dry cleaning or coffee, you know,
blurring the line of what the job is.
So, you know, so anyway, that's why that company declared bankruptcy
eight years ago.
I was curious.
OK, OK.
So as as Disney, as the Walt Disney Company might
things keep going the way it really is.
Maybe being the rumor that comes along every year, maybe Apple will buy them,
which I feel like at the early 2000s, it was the other way around.
It was like, maybe Disney will buy Apple.
Really?
Oh, early 2000s.
Early 2000s.
I mean, then the iPad or the iPod.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Changed everything.
Yeah, sure, sure, sure.
I think that's happening, by the way.
Mm hmm.
It just feels like that's inevitable.
That's the way the world's going, that kind of thing.
And maybe I'm just depressed.
And that's why.
But yeah, I think it's.
Hey, hey, bought yourself.
Say what you like about it.
If you want to make that wealthy money that the Disney vloggers
in the yellow checkered cabbie hats make, start being positive about this stuff.
OK, well.
What do you like about Apple buying Disney?
Well, that all the characters will know everything about me when I go into the parks,
that it'll all be downloaded into their robot mouths that move.
You just need to give them.
I mean, not quite.
You know, the characters don't hug you anymore.
You put your hands up to their hands and the hands scan your fingerprints.
Yeah, yeah.
Suddenly, the characters have a lot to say about you.
So they'll know everything.
Yeah, they can read and they know your eyes from the goggle.
The unpleasant goggle VR.
Well, they know your eyes from the when your face unlocks your phone.
Oh, that's true.
So it really knows your face.
So Mickey, oh, hey there.
And then it's from far away.
You might want to wipe your history more often.
Your eye close almost full.
Did you enjoy a recent purchase of the sugar
egg cover of Abracadabra?
It rocks a lot more than the Steve Miller van one, don't you think?
They really brought something new to it.
Yeah, so that's good.
That'll be good.
There you go.
Well, now we're being positive.
Yeah.
Watch that money pour in.
How about Wendell singing?
We don't talk about Prudu.
Pretty cool.
Oh, is that a good place to start?
Well, that's a good place to start.
I'm going to propose ending there.
Yeah, you'll find out.
You'll see why.
So let's OK.
Well, we talk.
All right.
Is that what we had to say about tiny head figment?
He fell.
A tiny head figment.
Poor guy.
We were we were watching some of the not so scary parade
like live stream someone was doing last night.
And Jane was very concerned about the Ursula folding.
And I was like, I think it's like balanced.
Like, I don't know.
She said it was a pedal thing, kind of like it looks like a giant contraption.
Someone in.
Ursula fell in a parade?
No, no, she was concerned.
Like, what happens if that cast member falls?
What's happened?
Is Ursula on their own or are they on a float or?
No, she's on her own.
She's kind of but she's got the tentacles and everything.
So this is a hypothetical fall.
You're just worried about a possibility.
She was concerned.
Yeah.
But I was like, I think that one's balanced.
But I don't now I can't say it figments eating shit on like day two or three.
But figments on there, you know, there's no mechanism.
Yeah, that's just a person having to feel their way through.
He's a, you know, waddle.
He wiggles around a lot.
He moves a lot.
You know?
Yeah.
For imagination purposes.
That's how you get the brain juices flowing.
Yeah.
Shake those arms.
So we got a falling figment.
We got they have they haven't announced
adding infrastructure to Ursula's float, but hopefully that's coming.
Oh, my God.
Clear out the OK.
This is going to take 20 minutes.
Harmonious is now luminous, the symphony of us.
God, you guys just want to you want to break recording and high five for a while.
Yeah, we could do that.
Now, that one, I think I laughed when I read that name and Jing was in the other room.
And it was the whole it was one of those moments like
you say something.
Did you need me?
I was like, no, no, that never mind.
I'll explain later.
Jason was laughing like Joker on the bus uncontrollably
to himself alone.
I had the cards.
I had the cards explaining.
Yeah.
Yeah, this was maybe the most nonsense is phrase.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know what to say about it.
I don't know.
No, I don't know what it is.
We liked harmonious.
There's a lot of slight a hand going on here in this presentation, too.
This is a three card Monte of a presentation is this way.
I like to think of it all.
Just keep moving.
Keep moving.
Distracting.
That's one thing.
There's more coming up.
OK, cool.
Or where's the ball now?
The balls on that one, right?
No, it's not.
OK.
I it's a shame because I thought harmonious was pretty fun.
We thought it was very moving and like cool pyro, cool screens and stuff.
But those giant black barges for years.
Just hanging out, ruining the view, I think, did it in.
That's what dams that.
Yeah.
coming to Epcot.
World celebration is about to open Epcot's newest area with no attractions.
It will soon be open to the public.
That's right.
The gates will come down so you can explore a world of nothing.
What is it?
I don't know.
What are these announcements?
Yeah.
Well, there's that big fountain kind of carve out
that someone showed from the aerial view looks kind of suggestive.
What is it?
Oh, it looks like it looks like a vulva from above.
Oh, God.
Really?
Yeah.
Epcot put in a big vulva.
Well, I'm sure it just looks like fountains and seating areas from below.
It's all about the Disney words.
Wish celebration vulva vulva.
He's at the tenets of Disney.
That's weird.
OK, there was a confusing attraction announcement.
Test Track 3, the rubber match, the test track rubber match.
Is it the confusing or is it just why?
It's an update.
Well, the reason is because it's got us.
That's one of the last rides that actually has a sponsor
that's willing to pay for that's what I was going to say.
So they got a Chevrolet.
Right.
So like that's the closest thing to a real announcement.
That's that's what some people were saying.
That's the closest thing to going, oh, cool.
There'll be like a new thing to see in a couple of years.
We were kind of with the concept art.
It's like, hey, the forest, the forest from the beginning.
OK, fine.
All right, cool.
I'm not that high on test track in general these days, but, you know,
throw something in there.
Inspired by World of Motion.
I like that.
That's the thing I like.
I like the sound of it.
Yeah.
And we know when Epcot says it's going to be like the old thing,
they always deliver on that.
They always you can trust them.
Maybe a certain mischievous purple dragon will return.
Not in ride form will be giant scary creature with tiny head who falls.
Oh, it's just funny.
Again.
Yeah, Mike, you're probably 100 percent right that it's like
maybe the sponsors like, well, I think 100 percent.
And 11 years and cars are starting to look different.
Every other sponsor is like bailed on these rides or is like
doesn't want to pay a ton of money for a refresh.
Yeah, but they're on this second test track refresh.
I feel it before they've refreshed journey into imagination
because they probably presented to the what Chevy?
They presented to them and they go, yeah, we'll spend two hundred million dollars.
A hundred million dollars or if that makes it jump the line, huh?
If you don't have why would that be the priority?
Is there enough track record now
that the company, all the companies that used to sponsor attractions
have all figured out that there's no point in doing this?
I believe so.
Yes.
They have like that Disney shell game that started by Walt.
Now like we really haven't seen any uptick in sales
because we've been we paid for this ride.
Well, they've also made too many documentaries where it's like,
well, figure it out.
The secret you get these other schmucks to pay for.
Oh, yeah.
They revealed it.
They revealed their tricks.
Yeah.
Look what all the attractions sponsoring did for Monsanto.
They sponsored like five things and look at them now,
kind of gone or hidden or merged into something
so that you don't remember that name that has bad associations.
I assure you, Monsanto is still around.
They're just working in the shadows.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, they just got hidden and folded.
Haynes stopped sponsoring the Rock and Roller Coaster.
It was Haynes.
Yeah, we did.
I'm not sure about that in the episode.
Haynes, I think these.
How do I forget some of these details?
Yeah, that's an interesting Disney fact.
Top of mind.
That should have been a big announcement like Haynes is back
sponsoring Rock and Roller Coaster.
Haynes, I think, was one of the companies where I was watching
one of those videos about like company mergers and, you know, breakups and stuff.
And it's like, I think Haynes and Champion might have been owned
by Arm and Hammer for a while.
Really?
In the way that Philip Morris is just like, hey, like half the companies
you use in your daily life are OdeFi, Unilever, Philip Morris.
We own baking soda and underwear.
Yeah.
OK.
Well, we'll look into that.
We'll look into that.
Mm hmm.
So what owns forever, dog?
I'm afraid.
Halliburton.
Yeah, Black Rock.
We've never asked.
DuPont chemicals and weaponry.
It's CIA backed, actually.
Oh, OK.
I'll explain some of the nice stuff around here.
Yeah, yeah.
So, yeah, test track is the most exciting thing that was announced.
They well, second probably.
But but yeah, it's like, oh, it'll be a new thing.
OK.
Or do you think the first is Animal Kingdom?
No.
OK.
Because I want to talk about this.
Yeah.
I misinterpreted.
And it'll seem foolish, my misinterpretation.
I thought it was saying so
imagineers have been spotted recently walking around the Dino land area
and they announced like in Canto and the Indiana Jones.
I assume that was a done deal.
I thought they were both coming to Animal Kingdom.
But some some bloggers said the same thing.
Oh, country.
I I the more I was looking at my chat, I was reading
Arthur Levine, Substack, someone who's he's covered the theme
car industry for a long, long time for multiple outlets.
And it became clear the verbiage is
and this was coming up on Twitter a lot
being considered.
Yes.
Everything is being considered.
So it's and or so it could be both
or it could be one or maybe it could be neither.
Yeah.
Neither is a good neither is probably what's going to happen.
They're probably not going to do either of them.
Yeah.
So by the way, nothing's getting better.
I think may have said this on recently.
Nothing's getting built for seven to 10 years.
There's not another ride happening for a long, long time.
They're about to get rid of other than Tiana 2025 by that.
Pick you up by a full theme park down.
It's coming so hard for them.
Still like there's stuff they could at least do to like help, I feel like.
And they are not going to do it like they are going to just run
right into this headfirst into a brick wall.
I feel like not to clear past if there's more to say about
in Kanto and Indiana Jones.
One thing, but go ahead.
I my only counter to that is do you think maybe
Avengers eat ticket because they teased it a little more.
It's not like they've broken ground or anything,
but they gave us a little more info.
I'm not I'm not seven to ten.
Five years, maybe I'll give you.
That's what I'm saying.
Maybe five years from now.
I'm not optimistic.
I know this then that seems like a tron that's going to take forever.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe that one.
But that one.
OK, other coast.
That's West Coast.
Yeah.
To the the concept art seems to be
not just shifting, but devolving.
Like it just gets.
Oh, it's just a screen, right?
It's just going to be a sort of ripoff man.
Yeah, right.
And then it's going to have like holes in the wall
that look like the transports into another screen.
It's just if only they had like, say, 60 years of Avengers art to pull from.
Some might say 60 years exactly the month of September.
You want the dawn of the anniversary.
It's a funny thing to be so
arguing about the we're in the month.
You said that and the troops must be honored to like celebrate.
But this fall is the 60th anniversary of both
the first Avengers comic and the first X-Men comic.
And I feel like there's like not much going like
not a whole lot going on.
Companies hanging on by a thread here.
Well, that's yeah.
They didn't even acknowledge the an anniversary.
I'm not shocked by this.
But I'm just saying like the first Avengers
ride discussion, it was like very specific.
And I think they scaled back on that after the reason
this passed away, the reason is art doesn't look like anything
is because they have not approved anything because they're still going to.
They want to make sure like they're not going to over promise at this point.
So it's going to be completely like shit.
They haven't shown the show you version as you go.
Was all multiverse stuff, which that means like, oh, we could be anything.
And then I feel like they've did.
They.
I actually didn't see.
Catch this.
Did they mention anything about the multiverse this time?
I think kind of.
Yeah.
You can jump between.
So I think the premise of this is what you're going to get to see like
Toby McGuire.
Well, the premise was like, OK, it's dark technology
and they can use the Xanadar gates and I'm like, yeah, yeah, I saw that.
And then what was the third black panther or something?
Oh, Wakanda technology.
I was just and there's like, is it?
Wait, Xanadar?
Well, that's that's from Guardians of the Galaxy.
That's not Xandar.
Xandar.
Yeah.
Isn't it Xandar?
No, I'm saying I think even I know that.
Well, Xandar is I think is that the planet and Xanadar is that the term?
Oh, I don't know.
They have a Xan.
No, it's still Xandar.
Xandar.
I beat you on a Marvel thing.
I did it.
Wow.
The cosmic stuff and the magic stuff.
I can't.
He doesn't.
I can lose.
It loses me when they go to space.
I don't know.
They got the planets and there's so many.
But even that's getting incomprehensible.
I love when the X-Men go to space.
But they don't run into these same Guardians characters.
Yeah, no, they're more day trippers.
I know that she are.
I know the Star Jammer.
Sure.
Those are my space characters.
What is I have another thing, though, Jason, you said that you implied
that something about Chadwick Boseman's passing changed the premise of the ride.
It seemed like the original iteration was going to be heavily like
you go to Wakanda and fight off an alien invasion.
And you think it was due to the death, not due to let's cut this budget
down to a quarter of what it was supposed to be.
That's my feeling.
Well, I think that is one thing.
And I think like, I don't know how the box.
It seems like the box offices for all these movies are like getting kind of tepid.
The first version of this looked like the coolest ride ever made.
Yeah.
And that's where you were going to break off and be swung around.
And then they went, no, let's do something a lot cheaper
and then let's keep making it.
This is just a ship at night, which is funny because it's like, you don't.
I know your post-production, you make the special effects scenes at night.
So you have to fill out less of it, but you don't have to make the concept art at night.
Well, again, they're not going to show you anything cool
because they're not committed to making this cool yet.
They're not.
They haven't greenlit making this cool.
They don't know if it's going to be cool yet.
Again, I think that like benefit of the doubt is like, OK, well, it's still on the board.
Kind of.
Well, it is a good sign that they're saying it's exist.
It exists.
That's true.
A little more details than like the expansion behind Big Thunder Mountain,
which, folks, is going to be terrific.
It's going to be the best expansion I've ever seen.
Frankly, they've never seen anything like that.
No details.
We're not going to get into the muck in the mire.
They haven't even that is just the same as the last time we did this.
We've started dreaming about what's behind Big Thunder Mountain.
So anyway, we've got a new bathroom coming like they just there's no.
How many more times can they do this?
How many more times can Daddy Tomorrow get away with this?
But I feel like the expectations are much lower at these off year events, these smaller events.
So announcing like a figment test track, it's like, well,
but it's something I guess they don't.
The last the 23, I feel like was the first time they did such a crazy, big fake announcement.
I've never seen them do that before.
I've certainly seen them disappoint everybody over and over again.
But I've never seen them give a fake announcement like that.
What was like, look at this.
Maybe like that's never happened.
They they had they were so low on cool stuff.
They were desperate.
And so they go, I guess let's just say like maybe we're going to do this.
Like that's how bad the situation is.
And it got and it got it did not improve in the interview.
No, it got worse.
Yeah, it's still just well, have you ever noticed you ever gone on Google Maps
to see that there is technically property behind Big Thunder Mountain?
We noticed too.
So we're thinking about it.
Yeah, we're going to maybe we'll maybe we'll chop a tree down or two.
Well, it seems like they confirm that the parks panel and some of the other big
panels will be held in the Honda Center.
Well, that's a wild decision.
That they're going to have to do this for the next few years with fake announcements.
Yeah, they better have this center.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
That feels like they're going to do like a musical performance
or something in there.
Is the Honda Center can you can someone to refresh my memory?
Is the Honda Center by Angel Stadium or is it by the pond?
It is.
It is the pond.
Oh, it's the pond.
OK, yeah.
So all right.
It's at least next door to the convention center.
No, they don't know someone to the desolate parking lots around the
angel state.
It's very far away.
Oh, the Honda Center is.
Yes.
OK, yeah.
You're going to have to like bus people over.
They're going to have to drive.
I don't know what the plan is for that.
There's nothing near there.
And they didn't even build Mike Love's Club Kokomo feet away from it.
So nobody will know anywhere to decompress and listen to some island rhythms.
But maybe none of that gangster ramp.
Yeah.
So I don't know what that plan.
I don't know why the hell they would do that other than just to make more money
and keep what is the only one.
Can they say that that will make the rafters shake?
How what is and what is an arena sized announcement
that what what what what befits that venue?
Disney Sky Park in Japan and a fifth gate in Japan.
Well, and what about third here or like the expansion here with both parks?
The expansion here plans have been so odd.
I it would have to be pretty concrete.
What if they said because, you know, there's been different sites
talked about for where does Disney expand and their Anaheim options are limited.
So what if they say third gate coming in Anaheim,
the very spot of this arena set in the wrecking ball
and somewhere that's safe, that's free of people or not, whatever.
Who cares if some people get it?
Wrecking ball comes in right then as if to signal we're doing it here.
The center's gone.
Wow.
A fam, we're checking out the new wrecking ball
that is currently heading toward our skulls right now.
Little Easter egg.
It's actually as I see it swinging at me, it's actually got a hidden Mickey on it.
He's got the ears.
The balls got the ears on it.
It is my honor to get killed by killed by a giant Mickey.
My co-hosts are currently in line to buy the exclusive hard hats.
And I'm just getting word they've sold out.
So we might be done for.
If you purchase a ticket to D23 next year, you automatically are insured
under Bob Iger for a life insurance policy.
So he collects when you die.
Oh, yeah.
Kill everyone in the Honda Center.
That'll save Disney financially.
That saves.
Yes.
That is you being a soldier.
You're being a Disney martyr so that maybe you won't get to experience
the third gate, but somebody in the future will.
The third gate, that'll just be like mostly Apple product placement.
But yeah, you die so that it can be born.
My dream has always been for the Walt Disney Company to kill me
in a double indemnity type insurance.
That'd be great.
Yeah, that's right.
Well, that's going to happen next year in the center.
That's the plan.
Be there.
Get killed.
That's it's fire, fam.
Let's go backwards, though.
Is it what anything else about this?
Indeed, this is interesting to fully explain this.
This this is actually kind of an odd, surprising
Disney acknowledgment of the possibility.
This feels very fan theory, something that's been talked about for a long time,
that if you've been on the dinosaur ride, it is essentially
it has a lot in common with Indiana Jones.
It's the same type of vehicle technology.
They've said it's the same track layout, although I don't know
how exactly true that is.
And I don't know if they have I don't know how you do like the bridge
in the full like, you know, Mara Skull Room or whatever.
But you could see how you could take the bones of that building
and ride and mod it out into something closer to Indiana Jones,
like in Disneyland or Tokyo.
So it's I was a little like, oh, it's kind of weird to even see that they
did artwork showing what that would be like, even if it never happens.
Right.
Yes.
I it's weird.
I first of all, I think it's not going to happen because certain
archaeologists didn't do so well this summer.
The dial of destiny pointed at the point in south.
Calista didn't do as well.
I don't know.
I was going to say I believe that I was going to say Indiana Jones
seems like it'd be a real animal himself.
But Carrie Fisher said it was more like a three month long one night stand.
OK, now I know deciphering the joke with Jason Sheridan
explain the joke.
Oh, Carrie Fisher and Harrison Ford revealed 40 years
after the fact that he did have a three month long affair making Star Wars
briefly rekindled during.
And you're saying he's an animal like a sack.
I was like, oh, I bet he's a real animal.
I was hoping you were going to say rekindled during Force Awakens.
Oh, yeah.
Man, if only.
Boy, there were paparazzi photos of them in the Falcon.
What's that in the window?
Why is it so foggy in there?
That's how he knocked the accent.
League was flailing around, knocked the door over on his own.
Oh, yeah.
Carrie, I'm home.
Yeah, I don't.
It my reaction initially was like, well,
are there that many animals in Indiana Jones and in Canto?
You're right.
In Canto, yes.
And there are a lot of animals.
Yeah, I kind of I'm of the perspective of now that that movie's
been on in front of me a fair amount as a parent.
I'm like, I kind of wanted the tree house to become in Canto
as opposed to this generic whatever they're doing now.
I'm not quite a Swiss family, but not quite.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's Nate's.
I don't understand what it is.
Maybe I'll like it when I see it.
Indiana Jones, though.
Well, hang on.
Snakes, rats, the end of list.
But that's good.
Oh, monkeys, CGI monkeys.
2008 monkeys.
If we're swinging with 2008 monkeys with Mutt, then we're then
premise justified animal kingdom.
My pitch, and I don't know that I made this up.
I may have seen it somewhere over the years.
I don't know.
But my pitch is you keep the dinosaurs on the ride.
Oh, and he has to go back in time.
Oh, that'd be good.
That's a great idea, I think.
I don't know how it works exactly.
He's going back to get you can keep Dr.
Seeker, Dr.
Seeker is and he's like you film new stuff with him.
Like, you know, and I got this old fart.
I'm sending back with you.
He's all dismissive.
Yeah, he's his age now.
Yeah, yeah.
So it's not younger Indiana Jones.
Or it's his father, Dr.
Seeker, the first.
OK, there's grandfather.
Oh, you'd have to.
Yeah, Dr.
Seeker, senior.
That's good.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
I know that seems really fun.
They're not going to do that.
But I think that seemed that actually was like indie punching a T-Rex.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right.
And that's good.
Going keep guys.
Yeah, like he's trying to block the T-Rex's eyes.
So you can't lunge at you.
Yeah.
This dark back in that time.
Maybe he's like hanging from the rope and the T-Rex comes out at the end
or whatever the last thing is.
Whoa.
That would be cool.
I mean, that'd be very cool.
Yeah.
And it feels like it would be cheaper, too,
because you don't have to get rid of all the dinosaurs on.
And then you you you catch Indy at the end.
He saved you like at the end of the Disneyland ride.
But he he lost an arm.
His arm got bitten off and it is canonical.
So like this declares that Indiana Jones lost his arm.
So he's a fake arm in the movies.
Yeah.
And then if they ever bring it back.
And I got to say, it's looking good in number six.
Then he's got to tie kind of a Star Wars homage.
Yeah, that's good.
Like C-3PO.
Red arm.
And then he gets a red arm.
Now I've got a red arm.
I found an artifact that grew my arm back, but it's red.
It is C-3PO's red arm.
It is the tie the universes together.
It got very, very like.
And then there's some space adventure where he found it.
They dug it up.
My my feeling about like the theming at this point, it's just
we've been worn down by this.
And I try to be optimistic just if it's a new ride
and it doesn't look like shit on the outside.
Put it wherever.
Like, yes, ruin everything.
It's fine.
I'll take it if it's a ride and it makes like the area look interesting or cool.
And and you're I mean, the animal thing, absolutely.
Is it concerned?
Maybe there's be a new premise that involves animals more
like what Mike has pitched, which is good.
But it is at least it would at least fit in the ruins.
You know, exotic, the roadie verse.
Yeah, of animal kingdom.
It would at least aesthetically be a fit.
Yes, would in content, I think.
I think.
Sure.
There's enough like nature to it.
I'm pro that, you know, I hope it's more than like a walkthrough.
But yeah, but neither are happening.
So yeah, so let's not speculate about things.
Yeah, yeah.
Won't occur.
OK, so Zootopia, this was another seemingly concrete announcement.
There's an original Zootopia movie moving into the tray of life,
kicking out tough to be a bug.
Oddly enough, Kevin Spacey's Hopper is staying and he's recording the voices.
A fully vindicated space.
Yes, yeah, he's back.
He needs work, too.
So if people thought like, are they going to do because they they've
announced they've shown a lot of the Shanghai Zootopia.
That little fly through look good to me.
And like this is a robust, real land.
Big.
Yeah, it's big.
It looks a little like Seuss landing to me in places, but I guess that's not a bad thing.
How dare you say that's a bad thing in front of Jason.
I know you big Seuss.
Yeah, yeah.
Good.
I mean, I like Seuss landing.
I don't think you like it that much.
I kind of breeze through it.
I like the curved trees, the hurricane safe trees.
That's all right.
It's a little difficult to the color palette Dr.
Seuss books when you paint it in reality in the harsh Florida sun.
It looks immediately sun bleached.
Well, yeah, any cartoon thing you have to keep up like painting it every other week.
Stay on.
Yeah, yeah.
But I don't know.
I like what they're showing.
She is big.
You get to go on a police car adventure.
But yeah, the ride's a little they people were like, are they going to build the ride?
That's like you're all cops now.
Awesome.
Hooray for cops.
That's what it is.
But they which it's.
Hey, we haven't seen it.
We don't know what it is yet.
We know we don't know what it is yet.
Yeah.
We'll never ride it because it's not going to be built here.
They did not build the ride here.
Maybe it's a maybe they're going to clone it for the Avengers.
Somebody also was floating the idea that the Avengers is a clone of the Peter Pan
ride that's opening Japan because the ride vehicles look similar.
Really?
Yeah.
What is it?
I don't I don't know what that ride is.
I don't know specifically.
I just it's like it's a I think it's a trackless
in the eyes, right in the new fantasy springs, where it's just like
something's going to make you feel like you're flying or something.
And maybe and there is it an attempt at like let's do a big Peter Pan.
Yes, it's like a big up with so that it's not like jamming in two people at a time.
I believe that's the idea.
It's a big closer to maybe probably all three of those are probably a ticket.
I think.
Yeah.
Stuff got to get back to Japan.
Oh, my God.
I know.
Yeah.
Springs, right?
Good news there.
Yeah, that stuff looks awesome.
Yes.
That stuff was the footage of that we've seen.
Rousings.
Yeah.
Yes.
OK, I'm being serious here.
I know it's based on the animated Peter Pan.
Did the live action remake ever come out?
Which one of Peter Pan on Disney Plus or in theaters?
I know that now there is a diff.
There is a live action remake every three months made by some entity.
But the Disney one, I couldn't.
The Southern Wild director did one.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's on the Disney one.
No, that's not that was the smaller.
Jude Law was in the Peter Pan, right?
Was Jude Law and Jim Gaffigan were hooking Smee?
Jim Gaffigan?
I think Jim Gaffigan might have been Peter Pan.
I think it's actually pretty good.
I don't have a fucking clue.
And I like Peter Pan and Wendy.
OK, hold on.
Hold on.
It came out April 28th, 2023.
What?
Oh, so just a few months ago.
Oh, yeah, we were because we were sending it to you.
We were teasing you about it.
And it is Gaffigan is me.
This movie exists and has been out for months.
Right, right, right.
It is utterly unfamiliar to me.
Granted, I'm I'm trying to purge Peter Pan from my brain.
This is already uncomfortably long to be talking about Peter Pan,
only dealing with it because it's a ride.
But this this film, I can't believe this happened.
And Wendy, yes, there it is.
Which I think is different from Peter and Wendy.
Yes.
Which might be different than Peter and Wendy.
It came out, though.
But yes, I know it's not based on that, and I think it's based on the cartoon.
It's based on the cartoon.
OK.
Yeah.
So anyway, what is wrong with the person on this earth
who tracks every quarterly Peter Pan film
and can know the difference?
The Pan world's number one pan enthusiast.
We should look up if there is that person.
Well, there was there was a reigning that person, but he died in 2009
at the hands of Dr.
Conrad Murray.
That's a very good point.
The title's been up for grabs ever since.
Point.
There's got to be a number two, though.
No one's going to beat him, though.
Yeah, he's the all timer.
He had the resources to make the lifestyle happen.
To track Disney Plus, all the stuff episodes
we did in 2019 where we're like making fun of like,
oh, the world according to Jeff Goldblum or whatever.
Like all of those are first wave of original Disney Plus things,
I think are gone, gone, wiped, wiped, gone.
Yeah.
Did you hear that the the quibbys that moved to Roku are now off of Roku?
Are they off?
Yeah, right.
Roku.
Golden arm is gone.
I think Golden.
I mean, I would have to consult the specific list,
but architecture is gone.
Oh, no.
My can I name any more?
Murder House Flip is gone.
These poor orphan quibbys.
Anna Kendrick with the sex doll is gone.
Dummies gone.
Uh-huh.
They're all gone.
These poor orphan quibbys no longer have a Roku to call home.
Oh, so sad.
Mm hmm.
Well, they'll find a place somewhere.
Maybe.
Well, yeah, Exumo.
Exumo, the newest pre streaming service.
Guess what?
Zumo has the quibi Rokus.
These sentences will grow and grow like somebody gaining maiden names from divorces.
Oh, yeah.
Like the sentences won't make any sense.
It's in the contract, though, that you have to keep saying quibi.
I can never be a legacy thing.
You have to.
They got me.
I did download Zumo because AW had a lot of commercials for it the other day.
And, you know, they have the fifth element.
I like that movie.
But then there were also Zumo originals.
And I'm like, no.
God, how can anywhere have originals?
Haven't you learned originals are the way to bankruptcy?
Nobody wants originals.
Don't stop making originals.
Because the only chance anybody has to get employed in this town is when some company
thinks they want to do originals for four months and then bails on the entire thing.
Yeah.
But.
And about you, reboot is real.
It happened.
God.
Yeah.
Spectrum original.
This what I learned about Zumo.
Fifty percent.
It was started by the company that owned MySpace.
And then it was bought.
Then Justin Timberlake on MySpace.
Huh?
Didn't Justin Timberlake buy some of MySpace or was that part of it?
It's been sold off after that.
Maybe he suggests to drop the my it's cleaner.
Yeah.
The owner of Zumo is 50 percent
Tom Cast and 50 percent charter.
Who is Spectrum?
OK, I've lost the ability to track this.
So the difference is so it's a half and half.
It's a half and half.
How much more Zumo information do you have?
You're the first person ever to see no one listening has ever heard the word Zumo.
No.
I well, first off, we're assuming that this is how you say it.
I didn't catch how they said it in the commercial.
Zuma, Dar.
You pronounce it Zuma Darian.
If you watch it, you're a Zuma Darian.
It's more Marvel Cosmic stuff.
It's a big mess.
I don't understand Zumo.
Zumo.
I've been following the X-Men nonsense since 1992.
I know 2B and I'm happy with it.
I know 2B.
I know Free V.
And that's what I like.
That's what I watch.
Zumo announced it will begin producing its own original content,
starting with Bold Soul Studios White Elephant.
So there's been a Zumo original film called White Elephant.
Assuming that got finished.
White Elephant.
I wouldn't assume anything.
I don't know if it did.
Yeah, Zumo's not finishing their originals.
Disney isn't building any of these.
I don't think they did.
I can't find any proof that there's a movie called White Elephant that exists.
Well, it might be.
It might be above Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
You don't know what's going to be in there.
We might set up filming it back there.
Wait a minute.
No, wait a minute.
It says available now.
This is the shadiest poster I've ever seen.
What?
This is like a flyer for a local Christmas.
It's on all of them.
It's on Zumo and Voodoo and Prime Video and Tubi.
So if you're keeping track, White Elephant is a Zumo that's also on Tubi and Voodoo.
White Elephant is like we what we where I was growing up,
everyone called it Pollyanna, where you're like, get a name of who you're buying gift for.
That's a new East Coast thing too.
I've never heard that.
Pollyanna?
Yeah, I haven't heard Pollyanna now.
Wow, that's a new one.
Pollyanna is a white elephant.
White Elephant is a Zumo and a Tubi and a Voodoo.
What you what you would do in in like elementary school.
No, I know what it is.
I'm saying I've never heard that name before.
I think it's going back.
It's like, you know, when when I when we first knew each other,
I called an Ottoman Hasek.
Yeah, I remember that.
It's a very old, old term.
Look at this other poster for White Elephant, where it's a bunch of like preteens.
And it says White Elephant, this Christmas, they will open more than presents.
What?
What are they opening?
We're all in that photo.
We're in the movie.
This is like the shining photo.
When did they film this?
How did you get my image?
New Year's.
Scott's a human bodied into a white elephant.
I like that Scott described this as teens, though.
Some of them are, I think.
I mean, some have facial hair.
You're right.
One thing's for certain, we've always been the groundskeepers.
OK, too many of them are too young looking to have that phrase above it.
And then it also says that White Elephant is what does this say?
The link is in our bio if you want to watch on your computer or phone.
Otherwise, Zumo is available on your Magnavox, Phillips, Sanyo or Vizio
Channel Plus powered by Zumo.
This is how does anyone wonder why media is collapsing right now?
These look at the sentences they've given us to read to put.
This is the like we are all solving Indiana Jones level.
Oh, yeah.
It's like a hunts and mysteries
boxes in order to watch the movie White Elephant with no recognizable stars.
It's very funny when it's like, you know, small operations like us
were like, hey, good news, I got podcast to write at such and such website.
And these giant companies
do not seem to have that same impetus to like, hey, make it less confusing.
This is I've used the phrase for a long time, content moat.
A lot.
Most shows that come out, you in order to watch it,
you have to cross the content moat.
And the people at the companies believe that people are willing to cross the content.
Even if it's free, that's why they have something like free V.
They got to say like free put free in it.
Otherwise, they were actually very smart with that.
But all these other places like, well, it's very easy to watch the go 90 content.
All you need to do is enter your out out.
Everyone has left.
Yeah, he's flooded out of the building as fast as they can.
If it's something other than turning on a box that's in my house and it's on already.
Yeah, you're out.
It's just falling over like the kitchen table, falling out of it.
If anyone's like, oh, that sounds really cool.
How do I watch it?
It's just really quickly trying for us to like, here's the episode.
Here's the page.
This we have a very clean system, very clean.
We have a system that is much cleaner than Zumo and then Voodoo.
Yeah, we're very lucky.
Yeah, why podcasts are we're working a little bit.
That's right.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Oh, you know, this is we're all breaking.
What can we get?
Let's get off of Zumo and get on Asha.
Well, Asha's coming.
Asha's coming.
The star movie.
She's the star of the star.
Asha from Wish.
The star.
Is Wish a star?
I think Wish is the name of the star.
Okay.
So who's Asha?
The star of the star.
The star of the star movie?
Asha is the star, but Asha isn't a star.
They're on first base.
I told you that already.
Third base.
Some of that classic.
I don't.
Asha's coming.
Ahsoka is coming.
Ahsoka's scenes in Star Tours.
All right.
At this point, that's something.
Okay, Star Tours, is it just that she's going to like appear in between when,
like, there's a transmission or is there actually a new level?
I think it's scenes.
So there's going to be a new like planet.
Maybe a scene from the show.
Yeah, planet maybe.
Because I read something that made it seem like, well,
there's just going to be an Ahsoka projection once in a while instead of like Yoda or BB-8.
Sounds like.
Sounds right.
Uh-huh.
Sounds easier.
It's very easy, yeah.
You got her for the day and the volume, you may as well get a couple shots of her.
The coverage is, the verbiage, I think, at these panels was so vague that were,
the coverage should be the same.
It should be one press release.
And it says, this is definitely happening.
This we're looking into.
But then you, but then now they've showed their cards.
Yeah, yeah.
Now we're not getting fooled.
They want to fool us.
Yeah.
Leave it all, to leave you think, you're so confused that, all right,
I think, I think that Indiana Jones is coming to Animal Kingdom.
So, for sure.
So therefore, I'm going to buy a ticket to the Honda Center when they announce the date.
And then, so then Daddy Tomorrow says, it's September 4th, 2029.
And then I can go, yeah, I'm so glad I paid hundreds of dollars, plane tickets,
hotel tickets, D23 gold membership, then a separate ticket,
then a bus ticket to the Honda Center so that I could yell when a date was said.
Well, there is, uh.
I think I'm being cured of my Disney interest within this episode.
Wow.
You're the fever.
I think it's all, all the, it's all leaving my system.
The fever's breaking.
Finally, 30 years later, 35 years later.
OK, we have to somehow swing this into things that are a little more positive.
Yeah.
This is, though this one is not earth shattering, obviously, because it's happened before,
but not in Epcot.
It is good news and funny timing also that Soren over California will be returning to
Epcot.
Funny announced just right after our episode about it.
Jason, I feel like you did a good you're welcome.
That's where you took credit for on our behalf as you should.
Strange that nice acknowledgement, though.
It is funny that, like, at this point, it is now like the classic mode of the like.
It is old school.
And I like that they can do this.
I like that they can put California in.
Sometimes you'll see people say, can you not trade out old star tours?
And you can't because you need wrecks, you know, you can't just like suddenly put in
unless you like give all that dialogue.
You'd have to give C3PO.
I don't think you're you would just have to perma make one cabin, but then everybody would
want to pick that anyway.
Soren, you can trade in and out.
And it's cool that they do it and go back to the old school in which we had fun talking
about the other day.
Coming back at California Adventure in 2024, they didn't bring it back.
I think we said on the episode for the food and wine back a couple of times so far.
Yeah, yeah, they cycle it enough.
Seasons of the fine occasionally shown as well.
Oh, really?
And that's still that's Jeremy Irons himself.
Oh, wow.
I forgot what you did that one in the near future.
Oh, yeah.
But so that's the the Soren announcement.
However, something else happened at destination D23
that was not part of this announcement panel.
There was a separate panel.
We got two little flag downs on Elon Musk's ex
from Ryan Bray and also Chris at Ben Talk,
indicating that also very strange timing.
As we put out this episode where the big controversy is discussed,
Eisner Gate, that apparently at a panel,
it was discussed whether or not the golfer is Michael Eisner.
And the people on stage said it is not Michael Eisner.
I I almost I'm so skeptical of this because of the timing.
I don't think these people are probably telling the truth.
And it probably is right.
And I'm not skeptical that it wouldn't be him.
Sure.
I'm just skeptical that this happened a day after two days.
It's a little strange.
I'm trying to get a handle on what.
And if somehow anybody listening to the show was was part of it
or who saw any of the back and forth with Jim Hill, which has occurred
much as happens just since the posting of this episode several days ago
as we record this.
But I do.
Yeah, Mike, I've I don't want to color what you're coming in with
with this.
I what I feel on your end is like, who are these people?
What is that?
What was this panel?
What was this?
It is that is what I feel.
I feel like you're trying to debunk the debunkers.
It's just the timing of it is insane.
Obviously, like we like that episode influenced it.
Maybe.
But I don't look at let's name the names.
They're archivists.
Right.
This is a panel called Down the Rabbit Hole.
The Disney you didn't know.
It was moderated by Kevin M.
Kern and Stephen Vagnini.
Two people said it.
So that makes me more likely got two sources on it.
To believe it, because it's just, you know, somebody can be.
Ah, isn't that funny?
I'm somebody said this thing in a panel.
I thought, yeah, I mean, trying to get us get a rise out of us.
Right.
I do believe I'm not I'm not saying I don't believe it.
I do believe it.
I just believe Ryan and Chris.
But Kevin and Stephen, you have some questions.
Yes, I have some questions.
OK.
So but I was just like, oh, is it anybody archive this?
Because I started looking last night.
There is not a video.
I made sure to find out that this was a real panel.
Yeah, yeah, I looked it up.
Yeah, yeah.
Real panel.
Because what are we getting out of all this lately?
Is the need to vet and do our homework.
So as long as we all do that, you don't get these falsehoods that go.
The exciting.
Obviously, I want it to be Michael Eisner as a golfer.
That's true.
But the exciting thing is like,
it does feel like the influence is there.
Maybe I'm crazy.
Maybe I'm full of myself.
But that's days later.
This is we are a rare piece of media that had just come out
that is poking holes in this long held Disney urban myth.
And if we get the official proof, we get proof that we all sign off on,
we'll forever impact that story.
This fact is out there as fact.
Eisner is in the IMDb for Soren.
Right.
And if we we podcast the ride, which often is nonsense,
we will end up being the official source that closes the door
or opens the door to a glorious future where we know it's Eisner
and we celebrate it.
I think it's good either way.
But we need to we're firming it up.
That's the point.
No, I.
There's streaming down Mike's face and he keeps whispering.
It's still real to me.
Damn it.
The song Fix You is playing as I cry
knowing that he's not hitting the golf ball at me.
Yeah, well, we're going to we're close to firming it up.
I agree.
It would be nice to.
I believe you came before we started recording.
You're like, does anyone have video of the panel?
You're like, you're trying to figure it out.
It's the proximity to the episode release.
That's really what it is.
I just it sounds even though obviously people listen to the show.
It's still sometimes it's hard to believe.
Yeah, that it would get into like the official Disney convention
or something that quickly.
That's really what I what's more about.
Well, but discussing bug main theories and maybe it's a little bit of simulation.
But yeah, yeah, I liked all the people.
They were like, what did they know?
What a podcast or I know.
And it's like, well, hmm, we'll never tell.
Well, you know, both you guys were the ones who brought it up.
So just asking questions.
Like, oh, we were just asking questions.
I accepted it like an idiot, like an idiot, like a blind idiot.
Well, look, you know, you shouldn't feel as as did I, by the way,
until we started looking at it just like, you know,
it is very influential to like
start to actually do research on a ride for an episode.
And I have my go tos, you know, Jim Hill among them.
Yeah.
Like, who can we trust with some of this info?
And when you're looking for a piece of info and it's not on one of the five
trustworthy ones, right.
And you're on a lot of like, you know, mouse gloves dot heart.
It's half of it broken.
Angel's fire 2003 just demolished by pop up ads for companies
that went out of business in 2005.
Yeah, just can't even if you can manage to read, if you can manage to read.
But then you're like, well, they do have like a perfect scan of an old press release
or an old memo that doesn't exist.
There's one thing that makes you think they're trustworthy.
But it's yeah, that's what it's about is asking questions.
And by the way, this is the other here's my little
I'm not going to declare this official yet,
especially because as we record this and maybe it will have been cleared up
by the time you the listeners hearing it, Jim Hill has weighed in.
I took the initiative.
I tweeted.
I said, let's bring in the big guns.
Jim Hill Media is Michael Eisner, the golfer on Sorn.
And he started thinking about it,
and then realized the connection to
Rick Rothschild, who was a longtime Imagineer, somebody
part of I believe I believe this is the director of the ride film.
Yeah, I think it's not one of the primary.
Yeah, definitely one of the primary people putting the ride together.
But I think also he may have literally been in the helicopter directing that shot.
So that will I think if we hear back from Rick Rothschild via Jim Hill,
yeah, seal the deal on Eisner Golf Gate.
Right.
But I'm just excited he's involved in because I've heard that name.
I've heard interviews with him where, by the way, he did not mention
directing Michael Eisner as the golfer in Soren.
But this is the guy I think he might have thought of the premise of Captain EO.
Oh, that is who is now part of it or at least like led the initiative.
I think when it became Michael Jackson's coming in, we need ideas.
He led the team, right?
Gave him the three out of which he was picked.
Alien encounter is a big part of.
So I love that this guy, this is dangling out there.
There's a question that he needs to answer in his inbox.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that's and it's just a matter of you do inboxes fill up.
Wow.
And as he actually busy and employed in
because Jim said he's part of these flyover.
Yes, yes.
That's I was excited to learn that too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's interesting.
And somebody brought Soren carried over to the other.
He just stole the idea.
So I took it with him.
Why not?
So I think that's when we can maybe when we get the news on this,
if we hear back from Rick, that is the but I got to say it's not
it's not looking good.
Jim Hill himself said he has concerns.
I would certainly bet that it's not now at this point.
That's the money I'm putting.
Someone's got the call sheet.
The next question I would have, which might be impossible to find,
is I would love to track down where the rumor started.
That's very interesting to me.
Who started that rumor?
He's never said it himself.
Yeah.
Somebody's made it up once.
Was it a misremembering of watching him promoting
the book camp did somehow something about him promoting a summer camp book?
Not I wonder.
That's so interesting, because like it's seems a random.
It's a really it's a really specific rumor.
And that's almost the reason to believe it, because why not?
Right.
And California Adventure was very his era.
And yeah, you could see I've you know, when we did like a little straw poll,
do you believe this or not?
I think most people just felt it to be true because it seemed like
something Eisner would do.
Yeah.
So, you know, anyway, I hope I'm not.
I hope this isn't a big Santa Claus isn't real for everyone.
I'm not trying.
It's not about bumming everyone out.
I just I I want to know the other way to.
Yeah, no, you're right.
So we'll see.
We will see.
What are before we get to what I think is the biggest news?
Anything else?
Any other grab bag we want to be?
Pirates of the Caribbean lounge.
Oh, yeah.
Bar thing coming to the Magic Kingdom.
With very unspecific concept art.
It was a parrot leaning into a room full of rowdy pirates.
And I'm like, where the where the guests sit?
This doesn't look like a bar that I could go yet.
Yeah, it's yeah.
I like I heard I'm trying to remember which source I heard this from,
because I want I have a new guy I like.
I want to say of sources.
So I like the way do we have a new a new trustworthy
so far, there's a OK, there's a guy.
He looks like he's 23 years old, 22 years old.
His name is Braden.
I don't know if you watch him and I got to find his channel.
Braden, all 22 year old fact, all 22 year olds are named to Braden.
Yeah, all young people are braided.
Mickey Views and he's got a lot of subscribers.
OK, Mickey Views and he kind of does like a daily show, little YouTube video.
He's very young.
I've seen his tweets before.
And he predicted a lot of this stuff before it was announced.
He see he was like tweeted very kind of like he tweeted
like Zootopia coming to Animal Kingdom, but not the land or it's not.
He tweeted something along those lines.
He knew the bears announced them that we're going to get to.
And I was like, and I think maybe he was the one who said like.
There is a big push in Imagineering now to do like bars,
restaurant type things next to classic attractions.
Or just expand them out, which I think is what's happening.
A haunted mansion in Disneyland.
It's not a it's not a restaurant.
Shop, but it's a little shop.
But you're expanding the grounds of it a little more, which I think we're all
totally into.
Yeah.
I mean, obviously is the first one that did this.
But sure.
So, yeah, in theory, I mean, I like a bar better than a store.
But yes, if we're heading in this direction, I think I heard somebody say
Haunted Mansion restaurant in Florida is on the table, maybe.
But so I like where they're going with this, but I don't know that this is the
ultimate this pirates is the ultimate version of what I could imagine.
Yeah, I have to see.
I mean, animatronics being involved in a bar is good news.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, we need more information, I'd say.
Yeah.
I mean, I think there is a desire for them.
There's a hunger from the public.
Well, you want we've said this many times.
You want to eat and drink near one of your favorite rides.
That is what people want.
The Hollywood Tower Hotel bar that was like about to be built in Florida.
I think they were concerned it would just cause too much back
or just be too much of a mess people wise.
But like they're very good with intimacy, but they they.
Huh?
I said, make it bigger.
Make it bigger.
Yeah, you got to you got to somehow simulate intimacy while making it bigger.
Like those princess halls that are like a trick where the the meet and greets,
where you meet the princesses.
There's like you seem like you're just going into one,
but there's really like six or seven.
They should have built three cantinas that size is size and galaxy's edge.
It's like Smuggler's Run that there's there's so many cabins.
Yeah.
So then you still got a feeling of like, oh, it's cool.
A little tight space, but there's more capacity.
Yeah.
Three cantinas is a very good idea.
Yeah, I just don't know why that to me.
I don't know what they're doing.
I don't know if it's I don't think it's hard to get into now,
but it's still I think it's packed usually.
Yeah.
So like, I don't know why stuff like that.
I don't know that that small budget, the kind of stuff that is
bumming us out about all these announcements.
Yeah.
So like this, I will say, is a much cheaper way to get us a little more excited.
You build shit like a place you can drink near a ride and we'll go,
oh, I want to go drink with my favorite ride.
Like I will.
So yeah, so I do like that trend if it continues.
Yeah.
I don't know if this is the ultimate pirate.
Pirate.
What else grab bag or do we?
What do you know?
What else is in here?
There's a couple of little things that I don't care about.
If we don't care about, let's talk about the big one.
If nobody can think of it, then I think let's.
I have a little list, but it doesn't.
I don't care.
Yeah, I think we mentioned.
All right.
Country Bears.
Country Bears is the big country bears.
The big one.
This is a win.
I think I hope so, because as Brayden said,
and I believe Brayden, my new guy, believe Brayden.
I knew this thing was has been on the chopping block for years.
This was a fight to keep the country bears
it all in the park.
And I 100 percent believe that.
And the idea that they're going to put new robots in, I think,
like they're going to change them from the old school robots.
You think all of them?
I think so.
I think that's what someone said.
We'll see if that happens.
But they're going to make them the newer.
Disney didn't say it.
Somebody claims that maybe that's not true.
I don't know.
And I don't know if Brayden claimed that,
but somebody claimed that they're going to make them
the newer version of robots that are new.
If it's fully new, all new country bears, that's a major victory.
But I wonder about that.
Maybe that's not maybe that's not going to happen.
I mean, they can redress them.
They redress them for the seasonal show.
Well, I can't remember what the there's still like the old.
Was it the hydraulic animatronics that have like fluid that need fluid to work?
Oh, the fluid that sometimes looks like blood.
Yeah.
So so those are hard, much harder to maintain than the new animatronics.
Somebody claims that it's new.
I don't know if that Disney has that confirmed that.
So we'll see.
But just investing any money and keeping the bear characters there is absolutely
the poster win completely tells you that it is the characters,
which makes me think they would just use at least some of the old ones.
But that is good.
Isn't it good?
Like it felt like they need to get ahead of that.
So we don't start thinking like, you know, yeah, yeah.
Is there like a new like a cool new bear?
It might remind you of Lil Nas X for the Old Town Road,
which it wouldn't be bad if they added him with the old characters.
But yeah, if it's like if it's like we're going to make them look like the kid
in the country bears movie, the bear kid and like, OK, good.
It's the same characters that are funny and that we like.
There's one that they renamed, so it doesn't have the name that's somewhat problematic.
That's right.
He is now named Romeo McGraw.
Which is fine.
He's got the hair.
That's cool.
Doesn't somebody else have a new nickname?
The dude is that one of the other characters they kind of renamed as well.
Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah, I was a little confused by that.
But maybe that's something to do with the song of the songs.
The character you formerly know as Dixieland Johnny is now the dude.
Better.
Yes, better.
So it's Disney.
They're going to do Disney songs, but they're going to new versions of Disney songs.
Do we is it fully?
That's what it sounds like.
It's all.
Yeah, it's all old.
Well, not old, but like it could be let it go or something.
But it sounds like it's all going to be country versions.
Bluegrass country versions.
So this is maybe this is their calculation, maybe of keeping it relevant
and making like a young like a child understand.
Yes.
So that's I think how they sold it to the money people.
It's also it's very telling that they call it that the new show will be called
Country Bear Musical Jamboree.
It's like it's almost like if OK, if you are a modern six year old,
you've never heard the word jamboree in your life.
Yes.
So let's put the word music in there so that it is clear
that this is a thing where songs are sung.
Yes.
So and it's it's good that they didn't add four more words.
That's also a win, I think.
Yeah, just one.
Yeah, that is a real victory.
Right.
Yeah.
Simplicity to that.
Country Bears, some might call in talking bears
that aren't human, who presents like it could be.
It could be worse.
So the bears then them doing again, it has to happen, I guess.
So maybe that's not there's a chance, I guess it doesn't happen.
But it seems like this is progress, though.
This one feels like it's pretty close.
They didn't say it's possible.
Yeah.
He said it's happening.
Now, there's people in our little social media world, I think,
who they hear this announcement and they go,
oh, Mike must be upset because he loves the country bears.
And yet in the original is getting changed.
But there but in tandem with that, there is a piece of news
that I think 100 percent gets you on board.
Well, yeah.
So so, yeah, up until this piece of news
you're talking about, I'm a realist about this,
that I know this has been on the chopping block.
There was a rumor for a while it was going to turn into a full
like Toy Story musical review, which may have been a honey pot.
That may have been a trick to try to catch a leaker.
That was confusing because bears like honey.
Oh, that is true.
I really could say that it may have been a false fly.
It may have been a trick where they fed it to people to see who like, OK,
we were able to report that as I don't know this again.
We're this message for jargon.
That's there was that like WDW patriot.
That was never the case, but it was fed to some people
because they were trying to suss out who was leaking stuff.
You got to say, because you you misheard it and you thought are people
being fed honey and I wasn't invited.
Look, my head's already caught on.
But I brought this from home.
I'm sure, though, all of this stuff, there's so much bureaucracy at the parks.
There are 200 versions of everything just sitting in a drawer.
Yeah.
And I somebody said I saw somebody online say,
this is an idea that's been kicking around for longer than five years.
I've been kicking around for 10 years or something to try to, you know, freshen the show up.
So, yeah, no, I am going to hopefully the new show is weird.
What I like about the old show is that it's weird.
You know, there are bizarre song choices.
And yes.
So hopefully they put a it's still a little weird, hopefully.
But the thing that was revealed, they did not announce this on stage.
You had to know a certain man's face to do.
They feel like the general audience will not know this face.
They felt like maybe this man is not known to a general audience.
But on a couple of social media, they posted clips of musicians
playing the new song, like a new version of the Bear Necessities.
And in that clip was revealed Mac McAnally,
who is Jimmy Buffett's right hand man.
Rest in peace, Jimmy.
Mac is going to be singing.
It sounds looks like he's singing to do in the.
Yeah.
So he's going to be like, it was like he's doing big hours.
You do, Henry, who knows what voice he's doing.
But Mac is involved in this, which is pretty great.
And he is also like a hit.
Like he has written hits for people that's hung back where I come from.
Yes.
And him would do.
So that is a pretty big feather in this new attractions camp.
Just made for you.
Simulation buzz buzz.
It is perfectly.
Yes.
Another simulationist.
It's like weirdly news that you might be nervous about.
And then right in the wake of Jimmy's untimely passing.
And you get this this big Mac news.
Jimmy's last performance was a guest spot in a Mac show.
He popped up on stage and did the hits.
And that was over the summer.
Right.
So and then Mac, I think, is already like, you know,
he's played a show and paid his tribute.
Yeah.
And what a crazy what a whirlwind.
This is now part of the Disney family.
Weird.
I mean, this is close to the Daniel Roebuck playing Grandpa Monster.
As far as the simulation.
Yeah.
Caving in on the characters.
Oh, if only it was Frank Marshall playing them, doing the voices.
It's possible he's involved.
We don't know.
We don't know everything.
So that is it'll be exciting to see who Mac is voicing in the country bears.
That's going to be a whole new show.
I don't know.
Maybe he's just a singing voice.
Maybe he's going to do the care.
I don't know.
We'll see.
But the bears being saved is a big victory.
Yeah, this is a it could be a big probably going to be a big change.
But the other option is the wrecking ball.
You know, yes, which I thought was happening for sure.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
Obviously, the bears, I think, are still very popular in Japan.
They still do their three shows.
You probably get to see the three shows for a long time if it's still popular there.
So, yeah, I need the ground swell here and maybe I don't know.
Hopefully this plan helps or just modernizing it helps.
Yeah.
So but I mean, I got to get I got to get to Florida and see which we are going.
I'm hoping they're not shutting this thing down before.
Oh, that's a good question.
Why don't they have to?
I don't think I probably I could maybe the start of the next year I could see it.
But hopefully maybe this is too new that it's still can see one last
Jamboree on American soil.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
Well, I had a thought about this.
Well, first of all, I tweeted a joke
that the finale of the show is going to be Rich Bears North of Richmond.
And, you know, in tribute to the surprise,
controversial country hit from this year by Oliver Anthony.
But I do think that, you know, like, you know, there's
if we're going to if we're going to they said they're going to reflect
different country styles.
Yeah.
And which is a smart thing for its relevance.
And I think if they want to keep it current, they really got to keep their eyes
on the charts and on recent country pop cultural impact,
because it's not just Richmond, North of Richmond that's had a big impact this year.
I mean, maybe the country song of the year
might have to be Try That in a Small Town by Jason Aldean.
Try that in a fair town.
Yeah.
Well, Jason, I've been doing some thinking.
Oh, my gosh.
And I because I think I think they're leaving money off
on the table if they don't reflect current country music, current pop culture.
And this great this stirring song about standing up and protecting
the rights of white people.
I mean, small town people.
It's you know, it's it's such an inspiring anthem.
And yeah, I did a little bit of thinking.
And this is free of charge, Disney.
I know I've been critical, but I think this might be a direction that
that you want to take it.
Mike, I'm going to hand you a speaker.
You can cut out the the base.
You're handling.
Yeah.
Well, as we know, Disney and the people that work there
are listening very closely to this show, to the Patreon.
So to the Patreon specifically.
Well, yeah, this is good because I was wearing on my pitch for the
it's like Pekos Bill on a date night.
You go to talk a bar.
Yeah, keep going.
I keep going.
We don't even need to.
I don't need to cut it out because you've been talking inside
because it's pouring monsoon.
OK, so here now my pitch for the biggest
the big song to put in the new Country Bear musical Jamboree.
Sucker punch some badger on a sidewalk.
Car jack, a woodpecker in a red light.
Steal a jar from the owner of a honey store.
You think it's cool to keep the mule if you like.
Cuts out a skunk spitting his snout.
Stomp on a jug and light it up.
Yeah, you think you're tough.
But try that in a fair town.
See how far you make it up the creek.
Round here, we love the great outdoors.
If you won't join us, we are going to chase you up a tree.
I reckon that we will
try that in a bear town.
Got the gun that killed Max Buffett, Melvin
that they say woke Disney wants to round up.
Well, that shit might fly in tomorrow land.
Good luck.
Try that in a bear town.
See how fast we claw you in the face.
That's all I got.
That's Jason didn't write more lyrics, so why should I?
Yeah, no, please.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Well, let's get into it.
All right.
Well, that was pretty nice from Wendell Albean over there.
Rhonda Santis has made this his new campaign headquarters.
This is if he can like, if he can attach to it.
And I was I was my pitch, actually.
I worked with a young, a non woke comedy writer in California
to get my vision that saves the whole thing.
Wow.
Yeah, that's great.
And then maybe and that could maybe carry into that.
Which one?
Trixie Trixie.
Yeah, it could go into a speech about open carry laws for big submarine sandwiches.
Whatever they whatever they want to take it.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's great.
I think we have to scrap the plans for whatever they have now.
I think so.
I hope they aren't too far down.
I hope they can get Mac back for another or forget Mac.
Get Jason in there.
Get Jason.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Wow.
All right.
Well, I guess you survived.
Podcast the ride.
Yeah.
Second gate.
Now, hey, I know a note of optimism.
If they can tap into current pop culture.
Yeah, I think it'll be a that makes me feel better.
Uh huh.
Hey, if you want to dig even deeper, join us on our VIP
Patreon tier club three, where you get one more bonus episode every month
and our regular episodes ad free.
What's coming to that cartoon All Stars to the rescue?
Come into that beloved 1990 anti-drug classic.
Barely squeaked by by a couple of votes.
We'll be talking about that.
And yeah, now all eyes are on the pond or on the on the Honda Center
for the next set of pointing out land that exists.
Yeah, that technically a theme park company could build stuff there.
I will not get invited to that.
Like we never we never get invited to that.
Unless we start the Disney Daddy's podcast and pretend with some other guys.
And then maybe we try that as an experiment a month before.
Put two episodes out and then email.
Well, and if if if all the Disney Daddy's have mustaches,
maybe you can't tell that it's us.
And yellow cabbie hats.
OK, well, yeah, of course, we have yellow cabbie hats.