Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
where today we're going totally 80s,
by which I mean a ride from the 50s,
set in the 80s, which was the future of the 50s.
I'm Scott Gerritner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hi, I'm here, and even though I know exactly
what you're talking about, I'm working
without what you just said in my mind.
It's pretty, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a tad complicated, but you know,
not really once we get into it.
No, no.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
And a version of this ride was active in the 80s.
Yeah, the 90s.
The 90s.
Made it into the 90s.
That's true.
You rode it a couple times in Florida in the 90s.
Okay, yeah, I did not.
I don't think I made, or I was like somehow,
it would have been there still at Disneyland,
Mission to Mars, that is, first time I went,
but I was probably scared of,
even though it wasn't a thrill attraction,
I don't think they're taking a five-year-old on that.
Oh yeah, that's interesting.
Or whatever it was, yeah.
Would you have been scared
because of the idea of lifting off?
Yeah, you know what, I wonder if a lot of people
had this reaction, and again, I didn't go on this ride,
I wonder if this is the kind of ride
where you expect some shit to go down,
but then, like it has an air as if,
and then watch out and all the seats are gonna drop
or it's gonna start spinning around like a centrifuge,
but kind of nothing actually happens.
It seems exceptionally stationary.
Oh my God.
Except for a moment of vibration or two.
I think so.
I've said this before on the show,
that at Pirates Cove, which is a local little place
that I went, a theme park I went to as a kid,
they had a UFO ride.
Yeah.
And it was tiny and it probably could fit 20 people,
25 people, and all it was was you got on,
there was a screen that showed the UFO like lifting off
from like a third camera, like a different camera,
and you went into space, and it was certainly,
the weather on the video was different
than the weather that was outside.
Sure.
It scared the shit out of me as a kid,
as a four or five year old,
because I thought we were leaving the earth.
Yeah, that's a whole dimension of, you know,
I forget, and I'm gonna start to experience this
as I head towards those ages with my son,
but that, you know, even if you say
the ride doesn't do anything scary,
some of it is psychological, some of it is the illusion.
I could see the light coming in through the door.
I saw the light around the door,
and I remember even like, I think,
telling myself like,
well, that's probably, it's the light from outside,
we haven't actually gone anywhere,
but I still, it freaked me out so bad.
Yeah, yeah.
This isn't the world,
although how old are we talking?
I think five, but, but, could have been eight or nine.
Could have been.
I think it's important, again, again,
as I start to remember what happens at what ages,
I think it's important to not, you know,
yes, are we good boys?
Yes, we're scared of a lot of things.
Yeah.
We can cut ourselves some slack for some of those early,
this stuff is scary, stuff is psychologically scary.
And you never know what is gonna be with which kid,
like, my sister did not have nearly like,
these reactions that I did, for whatever reason.
Well, scary, I think too, I,
it's a compliment to the creators in that, like,
when they would tell me, they're like,
all right, you're going to space,
I was like, holy shit,
well, that's an adult telling me,
or an adult robot telling me.
If it was a robot, it was smaller than you than whatever,
but a big towering robot.
So I'm just buying it hook, line and sinker.
Yeah.
There's a magic to that age where you just,
you just buy it.
Trust adults.
All adults for whatever reason.
I was gonna say, in horror fiction,
I was like, yeah, there's a magic that goes on too long
if you don't have enough going on, you know.
I need to go to college, it's very important for me.
Oh, okay, I guess.
The power of illusion.
Who would have known?
Complete waste of money.
Okay, so today is part of kind of,
we're heading back into the orbit of something
that we said earlier in the year.
There was a declaration that was,
this will be the year of Tomorrowland.
We're gonna do a lot of Tomorrowland stuff.
We're gonna tackle the Tomorrowland problem.
We have not made good on that at all.
No.
And look, I don't know, it was a soft promise.
I didn't mean to, and we, look, we did Vegas,
and Vegas was a lot of fun.
We had a lot of guests we wanted to get to,
various other shiny distracting objects.
But we remain committed to this goal.
Will it eek into next year?
Almost certainly.
But look, I still like the idea of it,
and that's why we're going back to Tomorrowland today
with some old school stuff.
I said I have an idea for us to do to fix Tomorrowland.
I don't want to reveal it here,
but I think we can get to that by the end of the year.
Sure.
So we'll be doing things.
The things will happen.
Well, also, like in the spirit of the way
the Disney company sometimes treats Tomorrowland,
we're like, oh yeah, yeah, let's get back around to that.
We do have to do that at some point.
Or we could, I don't know,
we could redo the tree house for no particular reason.
Yeah, kind of the way America and the world at large
is like, oh, the future.
Yeah, I guess we should think about that.
It's a heady thing to think about.
Should we paint some parts of Tomorrowland?
Or I don't know, let's just add Baymax to California Adventure.
Yeah, okay, let's just do it.
We'll sell some more Baymax merch.
Let's put a bunch of Japanese text under English text
and call it a new land.
Yeah, it's a land.
It's a land now.
There you go.
Hey, yank out those Tomorrowland ferns, plant cabbages.
Hey, look, everything's edible now.
Nice, nice.
You're referring to the Tomorrowland 98 redo.
Right.
Where, unless I'm wrong, where like,
well, part of our future theme is that everything is edible,
so all of the plants that you see will be.
I think you could just pick it up and eat it.
Can I do that?
No, absolutely not.
Do not do that.
Do not reach out to the planter.
Am I thinking about something else?
No, that's what I was referring to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And that was a true full redo, and that's what we got,
was edible plants.
There's a lot to get to.
What's that?
Rust-colored buildings and edible plants.
Yes, and also cigarette butts and some of those planters,
because it's still the late 90s, you know?
Sure.
Yeah, and maybe we're avoiding Tomorrowland things for a reason,
because we're going to be cranks about it.
Understandably.
It's a land where some of the best attractions of all time have lived,
some of the best aesthetics in any of the parks have lived,
and then also a bunch of junk.
It's always been the case,
and we need to keep working and diagnose the problem.
Are you specifically referring to Disneyland?
Because Disney World, they injected a bunch of money into in the 90s.
I called Tomorrowland 94, I think they called you Tomorrowland.
Well, I know that, Chase.
You don't need to explain that to me.
It's up there, it's up there.
It's one of mine.
It's in better shape in some ways.
Better shape.
But they've also let that aesthetic kind of decay a little bit too.
It's not as fully there as it was in 94, 95.
I like those crystals.
I'm on record.
I like those things coming out, whatever you call them.
The big jutting out rocks at the entrance?
I like that.
Okay, sure.
So they got those.
Yeah.
But they've kind of tamped it down.
They've made it a little more restrained than the loud neon greens and purples,
and doodads and stuff.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think somewhere before they started doing that, they're all full of…
We'll talk about one of them today with the Moonliner,
but they're all full of like, here's what Tomorrowland is now.
This is what it's going to be.
It's going to be this forever.
Three years later, I don't know, put this up.
I don't know, this is here.
Something that doesn't match any of the rest of it.
Yeah, it's like you're doing the Macarena, you know, pretty quickly.
There was months where it was like, it's going to be Star Wars now.
It's just going to be Star Wars.
It's a Star Wars holding pen.
Yeah, it's going to be the Millennium Falcon.
The Star Wars themed lounge.
Tomorrowland means Star Wars.
That was going to be it for a few months.
Oh, you mean if they were going to…
I meant before Galaxy's Edge, that was the plan.
Oh, sure.
Millennium Falcon on the top of the whatever people mover track.
Would have been okay.
I don't know.
I mean, okay, it would have gotten some money and it would be fresh.
But it's at least, yeah, I mean, the hopeful thing is that you get a whole new Star Wars.
Sorry, it's the Star Wars, this area of park we didn't even have before.
And then Tomorrowland also gets a big refresh.
Right, which the rumor…
And yet…
Every year, that's the rumor.
There's a rumor here, all sorts of rumors.
Who's working on it, what it is.
There's a little piece in the Imagineering doc.
You see that Joe Roady picks up a thing and actually that's for Tomorrowland.
I think that's Space Mountain's track.
Oh my God, he's doing it.
We're doing it.
Let's go.
Joe Roady walking around.
Yes, Joe Roady's walking around.
He's counting steps and he's counting the amount of track he needs to put the people mover back in.
And as soon as he counts, he finishes counting.
We're getting it.
It's coming.
He's doing one of his beautiful illustrations that he like jots out in 30 seconds and is
more beautiful than anything I've put pen to paper to in my life.
Your way your bar is beating you.
Joe Roady is a better artist than me, Jason.
No, no, I mean like if I tried my hardest to make such a masterpiece today, better than
what he just like shits out.
His Post-It notes are like, well, that's stunning.
He drew on his Instagram, he posted pictures where he was drawing on a dusty car, like
in the dirt and dust.
Drawing with dust?
Drawing with dirt and dust, like drew like a landscape or something.
So, Roady's Dustlands, turn it into Roady's Dustlands, do anything.
They're going to make it all with dust.
Well, I'm sure the future is bright now with all the headlines we're getting about the
Disney company.
I'm sure they'll put all of it, everything they got right into.
Man, I really, there's like so much Apple, like selling to Apple rumors.
And then there's some like fan, like fan fiction being created.
Well, you know what though, they should do, they just sell to Apple, but the parks will
be its own business.
And Apple won't own that.
And I'm like, that is not what's going to happen.
Why would that happen?
I don't know.
I like the idea of that.
Agreed.
I agree that that would be fun, but that's not going to, yeah, Apple's like, oh, we don't
want that theme parks that make tons of money over, like, why would that be?
Yeah, leave that out.
That's no thanks.
That's all we can do is advertise our product at these things indefinitely forever.
Yeah.
Oh yes.
And that where there's all these like stray future areas where we're supposed to be like
letting you know about futuristic products and it all has stuff from 2012.
Yeah.
If you're lucky.
Right.
Apple would love to put Apple stuff in all of those.
Maybe that's the only way this gets done actually is if Apple buys it and they go, well, we
got a Tomorrowland.
Let's put the it'll be all app Apple land.
Sure.
Look, if it makes it all white again, then great.
Honestly, if everything looked like an Apple store, if it was a land that looked like a
big Apple store, it's better than what we got in most of them.
Yeah, sure.
Some.
Yeah, that's probably right.
As long as the Mickey tumbling thing is still there.
Of course.
No, I know.
Yeah, that needs to be carved out like a national park.
You don't touch that.
Right.
There was a period like 10 plus years ago or so now where when the Disney stores were
still in malls, they're like, we need to make these more appealing.
And they consulted with the Apple design team to like, how do you do store?
Like, and so if you remember a very small period where like the Disney stores were a
little more restrained and then they died.
I do remember that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was a bummer.
Yeah, no, we need our bit.
We need our giant plush piles and which day I just saw destination.
What is it called?
Destination D?
Yeah, they had like a big plush pile.
When you got there, like they remade the plush pile from the Disney stores.
This is a little kind of that.
This is like, how desperate are we?
Like I think that I paid a lot of money for they briefly have for a day.
They had a thing that used to be 10 minutes from me.
Vloggers.
I could always go to.
Please just make it look a little more busier in here so I could remember.
Hundreds of vloggers weeping at the foot of the plush pile at destination T.
This is why we don't get invited to stuff.
We won't go and cry at the plush pile, the foot of the plush pile.
I am baby again.
I'm mommy.
Mommy milk, please.
I have my plush.
I know I need my milk.
And I'll make 100 vloggers doing that.
They're all on the ground.
All with the camera on portrait mode.
We're here at the Oogie Boogie Bash and it's the bad guy from Big Hero 6.
And then we're just off to the side like who the fuck was the bad guy in Big Hero 6?
I remember the kid and I remember Baymax.
That is true.
I don't remember the villain.
I know what he looks like, but I don't remember who the villain was.
We're just so cold.
We don't we aren't ready to burst into tears.
Well, as Billy Corgan made the distinction on that podcast, he's not a Disney adult.
He's a Disneyland weirdo.
I like it.
I feel much closer to that.
Not that we don't like Disney movies.
Good distinction.
I like it.
Anyway, let's okay.
So if we're tracing this Tomorrowland problem, let's go way back all the way, almost all the way back at least to 1955.
This is some original Disneyland shit, some original Tomorrowland shit.
Rocket to the moon.
But this will this history will also include it kind of evolved or I don't know, kind of.
It changed at least into some other rocket to the moon, flight to the moon, mission to Mars.
I think it's all one thing.
But if we start digging in and we're like, flight, there's a lot to flight.
We can we can certainly splinter it up.
Why we undersold flight?
But we'll see.
Let's see where it goes.
But basically, let's start calling this rocket to the moon and see where we land.
Sure.
Yeah.
This is unlike the sword episode we did recently where we're like we're peeling off soaring around the world.
This one within five or ten minutes of reading about these attractions, I was like, these three share one Wikipedia entry and one yesterlain page.
That's what I thought.
Exactly.
Because initially before we knew anything, we're like, and then mission Mars is its own thing.
Yeah, mission Mars would be its own thing.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, I think so.
And then we all start reading and like, is it?
There's almost is no space on the Wikipedia.
And if we're wrong, tell us we're wrong.
If we're if we do all of this and we're missing a big area of something that's great about one of these, then let us know.
The podcast.
Smack us in the face.
Yeah, you might.
Yeah, let us know.
I mean, a mission Mars is its own episode, but you'll get a 30 minute chunk of like the update on my Larkana collection.
That's what's going to happen if it's its own episode, which is fine.
But you know, it's funny is between recording whichever that was in and it coming out, I saw comments about I'm glad Mike's doing Larkana.
I between that, I forgot what Larkana is.
It's one of those things.
I have my Instagram.
No, a collectible card game.
Oh, right.
It was it's you're saying it's a new it's a magic.
It's like a magic gathering collectible card game.
And yeah, like anything.
Just so you know, say whatever you want.
Anything you say after this, I will not remember and ask you about in several episodes.
That's OK.
I'm not offended.
But it's got like a new art things and like Mickey's in like a different wizard's outfit and stuff.
So like they've recontextualized the characters even had like Mickey.
Yeah, Mickey's in it.
That's how much I was not paying attention.
Like little John will be able to like give Cruella de Vil a concussion.
Is that?
Well, that sounds interesting.
Yeah, they have different powers and like different abilities.
So, yeah, you can.
I don't know that it's specifically a little John is a TKO punch or anything.
But can I get a card that's X-rays of characters with broken?
Well, maybe in the second wave of you're not going to if you have Bianca and Bernard in your deck, their fatality together is really impressive.
They rip out.
They rip out someone's throat and eat it.
They go inside their body and know.
From the inside.
And then right.
Wow.
And then each of them go out one eye socket.
Much like the downtown Disney ordeal flick from a bugs life goes into your eithra and destroys a person from the inside.
What a specific poll from our own continuity.
Yeah, of course.
I'll never forget what happened to Mitch on that episode.
Eurethral matters.
Yeah.
OK.
But it's not Lorcan.
Feel free to do that.
If you want to do the episode without me, if you want to do an official or can probably will do or I'll just be or do it at my place and I'll just like zone out.
Yeah, I'll just be in the recliner and kind of nod off.
We did try years and years ago to play Mike's old Marvel at a game called Overpower, which is like Marvel Marvel from the 90s.
And you will not believe how quickly people tapped out on this thing.
So I don't still don't know how to play.
Still, it's impossible.
It's a little confusing.
OK, so broad strokes.
I mean, the reason as we teased in the Soren episode, I think there's there's some notable stuff about this attraction, especially the first one from 55.
I do think this is the first Disney screen ride.
It's notable for that.
I think there's a number of things that make it like, oh, this did kind of set the stage for this attraction, that attraction, often Tomorrowland stuff.
And so in the biggest way, the fact that this is the first Disneyland attraction where you go to space, which there have been many since.
So it's it's notable, I'd say, for that and that the main source of it's it's round auditoriums that make you feel like you're going inside a spaceship and you have screens.
But screen around screens, one up at the top and one down at the bottom.
And one shows you where you've been and one shows you where you're going to talk like Doc Brown a little bit.
But that's that that seems that's like what I knew before I started looking into anymore.
Yeah, it's interesting.
I wonder.
Yeah, like there were probably I guess like if you really like what's the first screen?
It's like some maybe it's the train coming out in the movie theater.
That's really the first.
Oh, yeah.
From the first moving picture.
Can we do an episode about that?
I think we could.
Yeah.
But yeah, this is the first like big attraction that's recorded.
Maybe there's a World's Fair thing or something that was vaguely like this.
But yeah, well, yeah, I bet there's something else that uses like you feel like a really, really simulator.
But I think for Disney and like, am I wrong?
Is it the only thing in Disneyland that was some when it opened the first couple of years where you're in a seat and you're meant to think that you're moving?
Yeah, I think so.
I think you're right.
I think as far as I know.
So it's it's big for that reason.
The the the general idea beyond that, the year it opens is 1955.
It is set, as I said, in 1986.
And this is one of the big culprits of that early Tomorrowland thing.
That's kind of odd that it's set in the way off future of 1986.
And the prediction about 1986 is that moon flights will be so common every day that you don't even think anything about.
You're like a little impressed, but, you know, you do it all the time.
You're taking trips to the moon, at least.
It's like it's like being in L.
A.
and going to New York for a few years.
You know, try to go once a year, at least.
Well, and all thanks to our friends at Transworld Airlines, TWA, the sponsors.
TWA.
And that's part of why that's the premise is that, you know, they're putting a friendly face on airline travel.
And then it's fun to be on TWA.
It's aesthetically pleasing.
And we've got those stewardesses.
You like them, right?
Well, eventually we will be doing moon travel.
So all the customer service you come to expect from TWA, you're going to have it as you go back and forth to the moon, including those stewardesses.
That was part of it.
Yeah.
In the early, at least in 55, it was, I think, maybe not entirely, but a largely female staffed ride for that reason that, you know, like we have to like gender specify.
Stewardesses are with.
That's the term.
And that's it's going to be that in space, space stewardesses.
And they also they have to wear vaguely humiliating costumes.
That's going to be part of it as well.
Yeah.
I don't know if you saw any of what women had to wear on this attraction.
Here's a picture.
Now, there's a man next to her and the man's in like a jumpsuit and sunglasses.
His is kind of it's just like a shinier version of just kind of like a jumpsuit.
The woman is in these like crazy round.
David Bowie costume.
Yeah, a little bit.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
And like kind of cinched space belts.
And then this like, I don't know how to it's like she's got like molecules in her hair.
Yeah, got a beehive hair and then like a little like sprig of a pixie dust tree poking out of her.
This is this is a little silly.
This is a little silly.
For sure.
Yeah, a little silly, but she is more clothed than I was expecting.
You would expect like the short dress of the flight attendants of the day.
I think that's what they did.
I think we talked once about the we talked about the Tomorrowland Rocket Man and the equivalent.
The Rocket Girl was in like a short skirt and space boots.
Right.
But they didn't go with that here.
Space go go boots.
Yes, this will continue.
It should have.
I mean, why do we let go go boots go?
It's very interesting.
The the 50s optimism of like not only is this company going to be around to get forever,
it's eventually going to go to space.
It's not going to like limp into a merger less than 50 years later with American Airlines.
You know, just kind of become a sub brand.
People remember because it looked cool.
Yeah, a nostalgia act.
Yeah, yeah.
It's before it's before NASA was founded at all.
So, you know, before we knew, all right, this is the space agency.
That's who will handle the space flights.
It may be plausible that TWA will be that the airline companies will be.
Yeah, yeah.
Trips to the moon.
As far as anybody knew pre NASA.
Sure crazy.
The time, the amount of fairly short in the history, like the amount of time it takes from there's no NASA.
This is right is open.
And then we're on the moon.
Yeah, it's so short.
Nobody cares about the moon anymore.
We're on the moon.
Everyone cares.
The biggest thing you ever saw in your life.
Two years later, the moon again.
Yeah, get rid of the moon ride.
Yes.
It's a period of time where it's like, look, either TWA will take us to the moon or we got to figure out something to do with all these ex-Nazi scientists we got like skulking around.
We don't want to make it anything worse.
We don't want to make anything that kills us.
Yeah, I'm so like ignorant on timeline stuff with history.
It's just like reading all that.
I'm like, God, that's crazy.
There are a few only a few years really.
Oh, yeah.
Scheme of things of like what's how much stuff changes.
Mike, I'm right there with you because researching this episode, I had to remind myself, oh, twelve people have walked on the moon.
Six Apollo missions.
That's the full.
Made it to the moon.
Yeah.
Wow.
It seemed like I don't know.
Again, I'm ignorant to a lot of things, but it's just like we were like, well, we went there a couple of times.
I don't know what else we're going to do.
Like, Mike, I guess we can.
The only other thing in my mind is like you set up full colonies up there, but the big pain in the ass.
That's going to be hard to do.
And why is it?
I don't think it's better in any feasible way to be on the moon.
No, there's no resources.
You got to bring everything right.
Mars is closer to closer to being livable, but you'd still have to do a lot of work.
That's and it's farther away.
Remember the point in time where it was like Elon's going to do it.
He's going to like set off nukes.
It's going to terraform the surface of Mars.
And everybody, we're all buying, even I am kind of like, well, maybe.
Yeah, no, this guy has not shown his cards of being an absolute incompetent maniac.
Yeah, a couple of years it really worked.
The PR really worked and I'm gullible.
I fell for it for a few years.
I think once he just he had like a cushion of people around him.
And the more direct it got, the more we're hearing straight from this man and his destroyed rotting brain.
You'd watch Star Trek, the motion picture, which there that's basically the plot.
There's something called Vagir, which is like an old satellite, something that's got gained sentience and terraforms a planet.
Essentially, he must have watched that or something and it was like, I know what I'm going to do.
Like people like, yeah, OK, like set off two nukes.
Yeah, OK.
That'll seem like clean plan.
Fix the problem of making Mars livable.
It seems like he had a big PR team or a big crew around him and then seemed to get into a mood where he's like, I'll speak directly to the people.
And after a few years speaking directly to the people, it's like, can we just send you to Mars alone?
You start laying the groundwork.
Yeah, just we'll give you a shovel.
Start digging.
Yeah.
Well, Bill Maher still thinks he's cool and smart.
As he told Billy Corgan on a recent Club Random.
Billy Corgan's on his way to becoming a guy.
So we're right on the line.
We're right on the line.
There's like a lit like it's soon there will be a little too much Billy Corgan talk for my taste.
But right now we're under where we're currently under.
But like at any point it could rupture.
Yeah.
Well, Billy was skeptical of Elon.
I'll give him that.
That's good.
Yeah.
OK.
He was like, no, we're the smartest guy I know.
And I'm like, yep, that checks out.
Was Billy in that Knicks like floor seats where it's like Zazlov and Bill Maher and Woody Harrell?
If you expanded the photo, is like Billy Corgan on one side and like the thing nobody wants to say is that the padding people are conveniently cropping out.
That isn't it.
Michael Michael, you know, someone we like shit, shit, shit.
Michael B.
Jordan stuck in the nightmare blood rotation.
No one wants to point out that Woody Harrelson is a bit like loves a lot of Bill's theories on stuff too.
Woody Harrelson is at a good route, like a second round of his career.
And then he did one of the worst SNL monologues ever.
Yeah.
I think he I think he beat Elon, actually.
It's very possible.
At least Elon just did jokes, didn't just like monologue for seven confusing, sometimes scandalous minutes.
Trying to make a poor analogous point.
And it's just like, hey, man, just do a cheer scan.
Like, come on.
That would.
So if you were there, you'd be like, sorry, not canceled.
You're doing a cheers monologue.
It's going to be a let's remind me.
Let's do a throwback.
Yeah.
It's been a tough couple of years, man.
We don't really want to hear about this.
Just promote triangle of sadness.
Is that what it's called?
I think so.
OK.
You know, the last thing I'll say about Billy real quick is he addressed the Big Thunder meme of being looking sad.
And he said, I had a great day that day.
I had a one like it was wonderful.
Somebody took a picture of me.
I looked sad on the ride.
It's funny, but I was not unhappy being at Disneyland.
I love Disneyland.
So there's that.
So easily he gets get some points there, too.
Yeah.
For being happy on the show.
Other him and Eisner are my top two right now to go after together.
Oh, boy.
Seems seems pie in the sky.
I just knock them both out at once.
Get those guys together.
Maybe Michael's a big fan of melancholy and the infinite sadness.
I don't know.
It's possible.
We don't know much about his music taste.
We don't.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
So it is interesting the public's feeling about space travel and how stuff like people like there's so much UFO stuff these days.
Nobody could people could give a shit about that.
So it's like that's the other one I'm worried about rupture.
There's going to be a day where Mike is like today's the UFO one.
I'm diving in.
That might be my birthday episode next year.
We'll see.
But yeah, so it's like because I think like for a long time, space and kids loved space and I certainly loved space as a kid.
But I wonder if that is like if kids now care about space, kids are even interested in it in the same way at all.
I don't know.
I don't have an answer.
My child is not old enough to give me her opinion on space.
Yeah, mine's not into space yet.
Yeah, I'm sure to some degree they'll be.
Oh, that's cool planets and learning about how big it is is cool.
But like I would space people were obsessed with space and Star Trek and everything.
And I think maybe it's just so much in so much pop culture that it almost isn't novel anymore as much.
Maybe.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
We found it all.
Yeah, OK.
It's big and it's planets.
Got it.
But it's yeah, this ride is reflecting the time that it's right before all that we're figuring it all out.
And it was part of the Disneyland TV specials.
There were these like the specials that Walt would introduce.
I think we're like made genuine a time.
It was definitely like science fact more than science fiction.
Or it'd be like a split.
There'd be these little vignettes of like here's what people used to think about space.
And it was a bunch of silly cartoon stuff.
But then they would legitimately discuss here's how we think these missions will work.
And they'll use the gravity of the little swing around the moon.
And like they made a lot of predictions that were pretty accurate.
And this ride is definitely that.
This is not like you go up and see a space girl and like golf into craters.
Right.
This is like let's try to accurately predict how space travel will be.
Well, and there is, you know, there's some footage of this ride.
There's a lot of tributes to this ride on YouTube.
I found one where someone made like a semi recreation that was pretty good.
I think the footage that really survives is the astronaut on the moon going like, hello, you know, just like talking to you.
Is that right?
Is this the one?
This is it's funny.
There's all this Disney footage that you're like where I've seen this.
But where was that from?
And what is it?
Because I remember another thing is that part of the same thing where like there's two space guys and they start they pick up a third space guy and throw him back and forth like a football.
Is that from flight to the moon?
I don't know.
I don't know if it was in the rides or this was just old Walt specials.
Yes.
I got a look.
I think I have one of the metal box.
Yes.
One or two.
I have one or two of those.
I got to go back and those big DVDs Leonard Malton would introduce.
Right.
Would introduce.
I bought one at Disneyland, which was very foolish looking back because it probably cost a fortune.
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
It probably cost like 40 or 50 dollars as opposed to just ordering it on Amazon.
And all the clips are just on YouTube.
A lot of the worth money though.
Yeah.
Look like those are shot up and probably I have I think I have a Tomorrowland.
I think I have Tomorrowland and like Disneyland opening.
Yeah.
But yes.
There is footage of like one astronaut like greeting you and he's like, and this is my climate controlled suit.
And this is our little Rover.
And it this might be you're saying the first screen ride might be one of the early instances of like very stiff, very specific theme park footage acting.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure.
Yeah.
Yes, you found my climate controlled suit helps me adjust to the elements here on.
The first thing where people talk very stiff and dull.
I mean, is it different so much different than the Neil Armstrong?
One small step.
One.
No, they predicted that.
Yeah.
That astronauts would be kind of strange and un-caring.
He wasn't like, holy fuck, I'm on the moon.
Holy shit.
Can you get a load of this?
There's a dust and I can see the earth from here.
Yeah, he was just like one small step for a man.
One giant leap for mankind.
Like show some enthusiasm, man.
He didn't say look at me.
He didn't say we.
Yeah, he didn't say we.
He didn't say.
He didn't flip off ex-girlfriends.
Right.
Yeah.
In hindsight, I think I would have been a little more excited.
You didn't know you were fucking a moon man.
Yeah.
Let's say every girl would turn him down in high school.
He unfurls something you think it's a flag and then it's just a list of everybody who's wronged him.
It's my enemy's list.
How do you like me now?
I'm on the goddamn moon.
Yeah.
Missed opportunity.
So that's just how adult men talked.
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Reserved.
Stiff clipped.
So dead inside.
Kind of a deep voice, but then kind of it could only do that's a lot of your ever get excited being on the moon.
Do you think there was ever like when the cameras were off?
He's like, holy shit.
Buzz.
Hey, you fucking believe this?
Cheers.
Hey, quick cheers.
Yeah, maybe beer open.
I don't know.
Mm-hmm.
It is like the Mr.
Show sketch, right?
He's like, well, we did everything we could up there.
Walked on it, played golf on it.
I don't know.
Yep, yep.
Yep.
Well, that's what happened.
We just ran through everything.
Yeah.
But it was still, it was all ahead of us then.
Everyone was still a moon dreamer.
It opened four days later because a disgruntled electrical worker severed a bunch of the cords.
So they wouldn't like, John Hench himself had to like go figure it out.
Oh, yeah.
Enjoy your moon ride, folks.
Oh, you really, how, you want your moon ride?
Bad enough, you're going to, maybe you should have treated old Ed a little better, huh?
Oh, man, we got to do that episode where we try to catalog all the disgruntled.
Someone was doing Twitter threads.
Disney's Menace Men.
Yeah, where, where about like the guest who got too drunk at Epcot and wander backstage and started beating up guests.
Remember it?
Like it made it through a lot of the utilidors.
This was like five or six years ago.
He got into the tunnel?
He got, he wandered into closed interventions, eventually got into the tunnels, got a golf cart.
No one was really injured.
I, this is like.
What was this?
This is like five or six, yeah, this is a true thing.
Five or six years ago?
It's reasonably recent.
The utilidors are under the Magic Kingdom, not to Epcot, so that doesn't necessarily square.
But there's still some backstage.
This was not, this was a cast member or just a patron?
No, it was a person drinking around the world who got hammered.
That was a beauty.
That was really good.
Thank you.
I know you like it.
Long age.
Beat up employees.
Anyway, I'll bring it back to the subject.
Since you mentioned John Hensch, John Hensch credited it with designing the rocket, which the white and red TWA rocket.
Yes.
Looks pretty good.
The Moonliner.
There's a nod to it now.
Early Disneyland icon, tallest thing in the park, taller than the castle, pre-matterhorn, that's the probably the most impressive thing in the park.
Yeah, and probably it's not the worst downgrade that involves in this, these attractions, but going from the TWA one to the Douglas aircraft rocket is pretty rough.
How so?
Oh, it looks like shit.
The Douglas rocket that just says Douglas along the side.
Does Douglas look that much worse to you?
It looks pretty bad.
This is a take.
I'm going to look at this.
Yeah, I gotta look at this too.
We're talking about when the sponsor changed.
It went from one now defunct company to another.
All right.
Yes.
TWA, sporty, red little stripes.
I don't look, I don't think, I think looks like shit is a big reason.
You're saying Douglas, this is Douglas.
Yeah.
Looks like shit compared to the original version.
Well, there's a side, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
There's a side of that rocket where it says Douglas all the way down.
You say that as if it's inherently bad.
What's so bad about Douglas?
It's just kind of ugly.
I guess so.
I feel like the TWA one says it like up top, kind of small.
It's going, yeah, it's going horizontal and Douglas is going vertical,
so it takes up more space on the rocket.
This is not, I am not alone on this.
I saw this take online, but this was my reaction too.
Douglas Moonliner looks like shit.
I agree that it's a little more functional.
I just, I think you've, I think you've, you've gone so far and it's still a big rocket ship.
I'm speaking a little flippantly, but like, I mean, look, I,
I don't know what the flight to the moon poster looks like,
but the poster for rocket to the moon is pretty good.
Like they sell recreations of this.
Sure.
I guess, okay, I like, cause the, the like stripes on the bottom,
the red stripes on the TWA rocket.
The white and red, I prefer.
I prefer.
Yes.
But yeah, I'm not offended by the Douglas as much, but I agree the TWA is better.
I think the TWA is better.
I did wonder whether flight to the moon, the second one version of this attraction,
whether it was kind of the redheaded stepchild,
but I was interested to learn that when they transitioned from one to the other,
they demolished the building and rebuilt it.
Yes.
To make it a little bigger.
Yeah.
Got a little more capacity in there.
If you, if you had more to say about rocket to the moon, forgive me.
I didn't mean to force us to move on.
Oh, no, no, sure.
Hey, it's look, it's fine.
It's a little interesting.
I think we, we talked about in the, when Tomorrowland was weird episode,
how they were stuck making the rocket out of aluminum
because they made a big deal with Kaiser aluminum.
Yeah.
Even though an aluminum rocket doesn't make a lot of sense
and it like shifted weight and shape in the sun.
So it would like make big creaking sounds.
Expanding contracts in the hot and the heat and the cold.
So this assignment is good.
John Hench designed the rocket and this assignment is given to him.
And he's like, how am I actually?
Okay, so we have to have aluminum somewhere as part of this.
Well, to build the bay, it's going to,
steel is going to have to enter into it for it to like stand
and be a big, tall rocket ship.
So we'll use steel and actually aluminum and steel,
if they touch, can create a toxic reaction of some kind.
Like they're not supposed to touch.
So the shell, the aluminum shell they were stuck building
couldn't touch the steel frame, which is what was actually,
what made it work.
just made no sense.
It was one of the dumbest deals they ever cut.
There's a blog of the Douglas employees on the Douglas rocket
and one man is smoking a pipe.
I have that on my desktop.
all right, it's a little simulated rocket ride.
Why?
It'll be very common to go and yes, you'll be able to take a pipe.
Yes.
Which I think you're still not, wasn't supposed to,
but I guess the Douglas employees.
Is that why?
Okay, I didn't have that context for the picture.
That's interesting.
It's from stuff from the park blog.
It's Mr.
Douglas himself.
So that's Ronald Douglas.
CEO of the company, Donald Douglas Jr.
But I don't think that's the guy smoking the pipe necessarily.
It's a funny picture.
There's only one child.
Everyone else is like wearing suits and big coats
and they're already ancient.
60 year older.
Yeah.
Might not have been, probably people our age in there
and we just think they look older.
But yeah, I guess the employees were allowed to smoke pipes on the ride.
Yeah, yeah.
They made some other declarations about what, okay,
so it's going to be an eight hour trip.
That's something they said.
Its speeds exceeding 172,000 miles an hour.
These are the official like TWA projections.
So if, I mean, that's like, that's a, not even an international, you know,
as many, it'd be much longer to go to Australia.
Much longer to go to Japan from here.
I just want like in their vision, what's on the moon?
Is it like, are you only going up there to work or scientists up there?
Or are we, are we playing on the moon?
What is TWA's, like, do they make it so we can like,
we're going to fill those canyons with water and it's a beach destination?
Are they going to build a big aluminum frame?
Once we've built our aluminum moon shell,
then you'll be able to breathe inside.
It'll be relaxing, full of lakes and rivers and water skiing.
Sure.
The ride wasn't fantastical like that.
So yeah, it's so, I don't know that they had thought about it.
What's the end game here?
What are we?
We'll put some nice stuff up there.
Shuffle board courts, boxes of Canadian club whiskey,
Chesterfield cigarettes, everything you want on a vacation.
Yeah, you could smoke a cigarette on the moon.
Which is cool.
Yeah.
So I don't know if even like space tourism right now,
right now space tourism is just going in like,
just even escaping Earth's orbit a little bit.
Like that's what Blue Origin is doing.
And like, it's not like you're going even that far into space.
You're just in space for what?
Like 10 minutes, 15 minutes?
Yeah.
So maybe they even, they thought this through and were like,
we don't know what people are going to do when they get to the moon.
Let's just send them into space.
That's kind of as good.
Well, not many people have been to space, so they'll pay so much money for space.
Yeah.
So yeah, I don't know if anyone's cracked the code of what are we going to do when we get there?
It's been, I guess, one of the big mysteries.
Yeah.
We figured out how to get there, but you need to build what you put on it.
You need to build a theme park on the moon.
That's the only like, that's what happens around tourist trap things.
So really what has to happen is that there has to be a bubblegum shrimp on the moon.
Yeah.
Ripley's believe it or not, all the usual suspects.
You need to just do that.
Kind of like a, like, yeah, the moon realistically today would have like the motion 4D theater.
And it's an old movie from, you go on a ride that's like,
meant to be the second, the Scooby Doo 2 on Monster Island.
Like they haven't changed the Scooby Doo 2 movie on the moon.
And the theater stinks for some reason.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a bubblegum shrimp and it's whatever is it, the Niagara Falls Mall.
Before colonies, we need to build like, yeah, the Niagara Falls Entertainment District.
Yeah.
And the only difference is that like the iFly, you don't need a fan when you're doing the skydiving.
It's still an iFly, but it's just naturally.
It's iFly, but no fan and then gravity is the other thing.
They put a roof on it so you don't float all the way out of the thing.
Exactly.
So that's, but other than that, it's basically City Walk.
They got it.
They had a Virgin Megastore, but Virgin went under.
That's just nothing.
I think people are, people live in there now.
People stowed away.
There's four people who've been to the moon who we haven't tracked.
And either they floated into space forever and died and their heads exploded,
or they live permanently in the closed Virgin Megastore.
When the Virgin Megastore was somebody accidentally opened the back door
and a bunch of old CDs got out and are floating in another space junk.
Yeah.
Like whatever era.
They kept gaining speed until they hit a Russian satellite and just severed it in two.
The first two floors are Spirit Halloween and no one's been up in the third floor for a while.
We don't ask if there's aliens anywhere, it's up there.
Whatever the alien equivalent of bats are.
This is a joke, but also it's not, it is how everyone thinks.
I guess that is…
The moon, it would get crappy so quickly.
So quickly.
That area, that Clifton Hill Niagara Falls area is so insane.
And it's funny, but it's also a reminder of like, wow, this is kind of like as good as things are.
They have like, this is like themed entertainment.
There's a beautiful site and then what do we put around it?
A bunch of like screaming irritating shit.
We can do anything here.
I don't know about a big hamburger.
That's what the moon would be too.
It's very funny.
I've watched some videos about Pigeon Forge.
Oh yeah.
And I feel like…
Scott's voice got lower.
Oh yeah.
I feel like the Niagara Falls vibe is tempered a little in Pigeon Forge.
Because there is so much stunning natural beauty.
Okay, sure.
Like the mountains and the forests and just the wooded areas.
Oh yeah, Niagara Falls is like, let's go see the natural beauty and then everything else is…
That's in a corner and then there's much more crap.
Yeah, yeah.
You can just imagine eating your plate of fried shrimp at the Bubba Gump
and staring out into the nothingness of space
and have your William Shatner Blue Origin moment where you're like, nothing matters.
Nothing means anything.
You're eating your shrimp.
You bought your Bubba Gump shirt and you're just staring.
The shrimp makes me feel nothing.
You're looking at Earth and you're like, I feel nothing.
I thought this was going to be the answer to all of life's questions, but in fact it's the opposite.
Well, you're feeling that way because you bought a non-alcoholic ice cream drink
and you're wondering why you're not getting a buzz.
Yeah, that's part of it too.
The Applebee's isn't even…
There's a little moon inside.
You can sit in a booth that's like a moon rover, but it's not that cool.
This is as good as it gets.
Wow.
Or on the moon.
It's a Mars simulator on the moon.
Or a moon simulator on Mars.
We're always pining for something we aren't at.
Yep, that's a good point.
So, yeah, we'll see.
I don't know if anyone really…
The only practical reason now is just to get people off of our dying Earth,
which is still going to take a few years, I think, before it's completely dead.
Before it's not livable.
Sure.
Well, now the mood is completely dead.
Sorry!
I think it's going to be a few hundred years at least.
It's going to be a little while, but we've got to get working on that 40 theater for Rango the Adventure Continues on the Moon.
Yeah, that's true.
We wanted to be in charge of a theme park project forever.
Maybe a moon one is what we want.
Yeah.
Maybe we need John Binkowski to put a rock and roll theme park on the moon.
Or is this moon-based rock and roll songs?
You know, moon-age daydreams.
Fog hat the ride.
One silly thing.
One other odd thing about…
So there's the moon liner outside the ride, and then like, was that the ship we're getting in that?
No, no, no.
The real rocket will be much bigger.
It'll be 240 feet in length, and it will use nuclear energy as fuel.
So these are nuclear rockets.
You will take a TWA nuke jet to the moon.
I don't think anyone thinks they're getting into that Millennium Falcon that's in Galaxy's Edge, but it is a little bit more like, that is what you're supposed to assume.
Yeah.
And this is definitely like, oh, cool, it's a rocket.
A child might probably.
I buy it as like, that's the story.
I know I'm not, but…
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I actually, I bet like regular people might even think that you are like, you're born and then you are inside that.
Maybe, yeah.
Well, I am saying that I think they do a better job of that.
Sure.
But then I, for some reason, I do assert that I know better.
The cockpit does a lot of lifting.
The like movie perfect cockpit, you know.
Yeah, as a kid, that would be really cool to see what you're going, what you think you're going into, but they make that distinction on the ride.
It's very fact-oriented.
The experience is nine minutes long, which seems too long for, yes, for something that where I'm like, I'm looking through a transcript.
Is there a funny line in this that I can say on the…
No, no, there is not.
It is extremely fact-oriented and then you meet Captain Collins, okay?
Is Captain Collins nicer, make a joke?
No, not really.
You know what it reminded me of, I realized, is how this is early Disneyland.
They're figuring it all out.
They don't know yet that things can be like jovial, silly, fun.
Jungle Cruise didn't have jokes when it started.
Jungle Cruise was just meant to, we just say real facts about lions.
And it's kind of like that.
Like now you might have like, whoops, and something goes right.
And then they kind of injected humor a tiny bit in the other iterations.
But early Disney is like, no, we're here to teach.
Education.
Yeah.
Which is funny, because you still see a lot of people like Epcot has strayed so far from its original.
And they're like, okay, so is this what you want?
Show a ride-through video of Rocket to the Moon falling asleep halfway through.
Yeah, well, Mission Space is in the same vein as this for sure.
And it's awful and I don't like it.
And I know some people like it, but I don't.
Gary Sinise in both Mission Space and the movie Mission to Mars.
That's right.
Which doesn't seem to have a lot of connections besides the name and touchstone.
That's right, yes.
Yeah, it's weird.
But I don't think it has anything to do with it really.
And then, but and kind of Gary Sinise is in the ride.
It's a ride where you go to Mars and he's in it.
But I don't know if he's supposed to be that character.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I know.
I could be wrong.
But that's why it's him though.
Is it is a Mission to Mars tie in.
Right, right.
But I don't know.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I guess I didn't even think about that.
That's at least why they had a relationship with Sinise.
Oh, you know what?
I think this is where I have to talk about this.
I was recently pursuing a gig.
I was meeting somebody to potentially do a project with WGA sanctioned in the clear.
It would have been fine.
But so he is kind of like catching up on this case.
So you did this and you did that.
And I'm talking about my history and what I've done.
And then he's like, so this podcast I got to ask you about.
You're like, it's a theme park thing.
Yeah.
And he says, yeah, yeah.
Disney daddies.
That's interesting.
And I was like, no, it's not that.
It's way.
Where did you get that?
Because that's a phrase that we've said.
And he's like Wikipedia.
That's on your own Wikipedia, my man.
And I was like, oh, God, crap.
And this is me.
I was meeting somebody for the first time and esteemed and older, older man.
And and I'm like, oh, shit, what was all that again?
And I really I remembered.
Yes, I remember.
OK, here's a big I this is my own fault.
Right.
Yeah.
I asked the audience to put a this because of mission space.
Right.
It was something it was something where I wanted Father of the Year data.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Gary Sinise had some unsourced thing of being father of the year.
And I wanted to take it from him.
So and basically, like it's been through somebody.
Bless you went and added that to my Wikipedia.
So my Wikipedia for a while had this strange distinction about like he was beat out.
Gary Sinise in these several years to be one of the Disney daddies.
Oh, my God.
This has just been in my Wikipedia.
But at some point, oh, gee, because it connected to his at some point that got flagged.
Like, OK, we know Sinise was not.
So the Sinise got pulled from it.
So here's what's now on my Wikipedia.
Gardner has been voted as one of three Disney daddies with a Z by prominent members of the theme park journalism industry.
So now it's just this like like Tomorrowland.
We're pulling elements.
It's just this decaying husk of a fact or a joke in an award section on my Wikipedia.
That just that just means nothing.
And that came up in a job interview.
And I had to.
There's a minute.
This guy's coming to meet me and he's like, oh, my God, this guy seems all right.
But he is he's the host of a podcast called the Disney Daddies.
Well, it doesn't say that he got confused there.
But yes, this is a moment that I had in my life and I didn't get the job.
Let me just say, I don't think that's why.
But I would say it is not why.
However, my goodness, this look what I did to myself.
Look what the pit that listeners helped me dig for myself.
Wow.
Now you're never going to get to write the sound of freedom to.
Now you're never going to get to do a pass on the Polly Pocket movie.
I've got I was I was so like I went I even print up the poster with the taglines.
Got to be never trust a second pedophile.
Never trust a pedophile again.
Oh, my God.
Disney Dad.
Just seeing Disney Daddy's written like that.
Yeah.
What happened now?
That just means nothing.
Now the part that I asked for is gone.
His body.
I was voted as one of I had to be voted this.
Who are the other two?
I think it's both of you.
Well, why?
Why would we have to be voted then?
Yeah, the voting is I think that's where it because the voting was originally that I beat out Sinise.
Yeah.
But now it's just the stray.
Now it just now it just means nothing.
Yeah.
The more we the more we yank, it makes less and less sense.
Well, look, you were number one.
You were the first one to have a child.
Mike was second.
I was immediately eliminated because I don't have children that I know of.
Mr.
Jason or Mr.
T as we call him.
He doesn't even know the tea and podcast.
He was when he when he we don't know what Jason gets up to when he goes to the Jersey Shore and he was in a taffy haze.
Who knows with tea just exploding out of him.
Who knows what he got up to?
A body falling apart.
By Mr.
T we mean taffy.
I've been to the doctor so many times this year, but my tea is at an all time high.
Maybe I need to get my tea down.
You lose one sense and then another becomes a superpower.
Yeah, that's you with tea.
Jason, maybe you could introduce a new product testosterone infused taffy.
You know, people with low T.
Tea taffy.
Yeah, tea taffy.
Should we start a new thing to put to replace your Wikipedia with right now?
Do you want that changed and we'll have a listener do it?
What I really make it worse.
Could we?
Gairdner has been voted the top Disney daddy in the theme park community.
Like, let's get us out even out of there.
I mean, the worst the worst thing would be if you added I'm like, how can you change it with just one word?
And I think if you can get in, Gairdner has been voted as one of three little Disney daddies.
I'm going to I'm going to delete it as soon as I can.
But I but I somebody should try to add it just so we can see what that looks so it can be there for a minute.
Scott Gairdner accolades are is include the number one Disney daddy and the one of the three musketeers along with beloved men Bob Iger and David Saswab.
Known for front row Lakers is front row Lakers seats with David Saswab.
And Disney daddies.
I wish actually was more accurate to my view of what the Disney daddy's is, which is a podcast hosted by three single dads with three sons each.
So if they could change it at least to that to change your because it does say about your family and you're also on your Wikipedia.
But if they could change it to that, a single dad, Scott Gairdner is a single dad that has three sons.
He's been voted as one of the top three Disney daddies who have three three children.
Three.
Yeah, I don't know.
However you want to do it.
Yeah.
And then it's but then I'm taking a wrecking ball the whole time.
All right.
That's I had to lie.
This this came to bite me in the ass and my award section needs to go.
But let's have a part.
Let's demolish it before it gets imploded.
Right.
Let's let's spray a bunch of graffiti all over it before we get rid of it entirely.
Unless they won't let me myself do it.
OK.
I've been meaning to bring that up and then it's a nice like oh man, I have to talk about it.
This the ride itself in terms of like what does it do?
It does.
The seats vibrated a little bit.
This is the original 40x.
Right.
Is how they gave you any bit of space travel feeling is there's a little bit of shaking going on while you watch screens above you and below you.
Unless I'm wrong.
That's kind of what this is.
The shake a little while you get serious moon info.
You get to see the backside of the moon.
That's part of it.
Yeah.
This is described as one of the thrills of the ride.
There's a bit there's light flares.
Right.
And it will allow you to actually see the backside of the moon.
And the big reveal is the backside looks the same as the front side.
Sure.
Yeah.
But there was a thought I think at the time like I don't know maybe that's where all the aliens are hiding.
Right.
The dark side of the moon.
Of course Pink Floyd will have a ride on the moon when John Binkowski gets involved.
Oh that's perfect.
Dark side of the moon and the coaster on the moon.
Right on the dark side.
Yeah.
Maybe the dark side as the cheese maybe as the babes you know.
Oh the cheese and the babes did you say?
Yeah that's what they were thinking back then.
The space babes.
Babes will feed you cheese.
Space babes.
Like green like Star Trek green ladies.
Oh yeah beautiful green ladies.
Yes.
Otherwise look like humans.
Maybe if you want to maybe for fun you throw a third breast in there.
Yeah total recall style.
If you're feeling silly but otherwise yeah they are our normal babes.
Anyway that's sort of what this is.
I think for the 50s pretty good.
I think a little dry by our standards but it's a ride.
It's a you go to space.
There's some there's a little bit of a pre-show.
Your seats shake a little bit.
So you know I don't know if you have maybe you don't have star tours without this.
I mean you don't have space mountain without this.
It started carving out an area of Disney rides so it's important for that reason.
I bet it was cool for a short amount of time.
I bet like just being in Disneyland and being in anything even though Tomorrowland was kind of crappy versus the other lands.
It was still like pretty cool for a couple of years.
Oh and the part of the space race I'm sure it was awesome.
Yeah so I will give it that.
Yeah.
Because I don't always sometimes you look back at some of these things you go this doesn't even look like it was fun then.
But I could see this being fun at the time.
I think with fresh like theme parks are not around us all the time eyes.
It's different than it's not like a carnival ride.
It's you know I don't think there are there's I don't think there's a lot of things where you like enter a room and the room is like special and feels like another kind of room.
Right and outside of like movie theaters it's like these screens are big like yeah that too.
You don't see those everywhere.
Yeah.
So just even seeing it used in a different way I'm sure was pretty cool.
Yes.
But then TWA stops sponsoring it and the theaters are too small so they wreck it.
It's gone like my awards section soon.
And it's also the big tomorrow the first big Tomorrowland redo is coming.
Tomorrowland 67 which is where we get the Carousel of Progress.
It's where we get People Mover.
I think that's where the rocket jets move up to the top of that structure.
So kind of the biggest overall that leads to the Tomorrowland we know today.
So they get rid of this and almost the exact same spot.
They build bigger theaters though not radically bigger.
It's still two domes that are supposed to be rocket ships.
Right.
And it's not rocket to the moon it's flight to the moon.
Don't know why.
Right.
Yeah.
Maybe did rocket feel like limiting like.
Flight seems less flight seems more mundane because of flying from air travel.
Yeah.
So maybe there was the idea like oh it's just going to be normal.
Sure.
Commonplace.
Is this where because I had a hard time tracking this.
Is this where the mission control room full of animatronics shows up.
I think so.
I think it's at that point.
So that's probably the most notable addition here is that now there is a true pre-show.
Yes.
And I don't think I knew this was there at all.
A room full of audio animatronics.
I didn't either and I was so excited because again I knew this was a little dry going in.
But then I discovered this and I went OK here we go.
This is footage that has escaped me in my many years looking at this crap.
Robots we didn't know about.
Yes.
Yes indeed.
And this is the home of a name that is used for various things in theme park lore and
one of our favorite vloggers Mr.
Morrow.
Mr.
Tom Morrow.
Yes.
I actually didn't know that either.
I thought it originated from the people mover but no it's here.
Oh that it was just like a joke.
It was just a pass by joke.
Yeah.
And didn't they also call wasn't the Nathan Lane Innoventions robot where you can see
his insides called Tom Morrow.
Is it the weird little one?
I don't remember if he was little but he sings It's a Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow while
you wait for Innoventions to open.
So he's only one animatronic I think speak turns around acknowledges you speaks to you
interacts with a cast member that had never happened before.
The live person cues then even has a little back and forth with a with an animatronic.
So Mr.
Morrow is from this.
Do we get any sense of him really to like him beyond that they did it.
He's not as quirky as like John from Carousel of Progress.
No.
But he still has you know old style animatronic charisma.
I like seeing this style of Disney animatronic.
I feel like they were they really the robots were all made by crusty old men and they were
really good at making crusty old men.
Made them in their image like God.
Yeah.
So that's good.
But yeah I don't know.
I don't know that he's so memorable but I don't know maybe I don't know.
Is it because he wasn't as entertaining or is it just because this ride wasn't that popular
or it going away.
I don't know.
I don't I'm not saying he's great in the sense and great like John or something but I'm now
he did.
Now forgive me.
I don't remember this distinction.
I don't remember if this is Mr.
Morrow or here's where you get into like how many episodes
are these and you realize like that.
OK.
It's just what was the change was that they changed the name of the it's not Mr.
Morrow
it's Mr.
Johnson.
So why is Mission to Mars different.
Mr.
Morrow is now Mr.
Johnson.
Otherwise it is the same voice actor.
And I don't remember if it's a different animatronic entirely or anyway my point is at least I
know Mr.
Johnson is John from Carousel of Progress.
Peter Rennaday is who is here.
Wait wait wait.
Sorry sorry.
Is in Mission to Mars and his name is third officer Collins.
OK OK.
Collins I believe is a callback to one of the characters in Flight to the Moon.
Yeah.
Let's get it straight.
Two Collins different Collins.
Sorry sorry.
Morrow is not Johnson.
OK.
I got confused.
Sorry.
Tomorrowland I will give them credit.
One thing they are good at is doing like comic book or professional wrestling callbacks or
nods to previous continuities.
Yeah.
Yes.
What I was saying was that John's the voice.
They it's just the same animatronic.
Yeah.
I think that's what people thought.
These people said he looks remarkably close to him.
The other the other difference.
But I don't think we said this was also there's a version of this in Disney World both Flight
to the Moon and Mission to Mars and in Florida Mr.
Johnson had a mustache.
But in Disneyland he was clean shaven.
Is everyone keeping this straight.
Yeah.
Get all these down.
Make sure you know impress people at your next party.
Maybe that's what they'll do with Hatbox Ghost.
Then Florida.
Mustache.
Sure.
That's different.
Does it travel with him or what are the physical properties of a mustache.
Does it stay on your face when everything else goes?
That would be cool if it hovered.
Everything that way.
Everything goes except the mustache.
That'd be fun.
But I also I think feel like it would mean that he has a fake mustache.
Although do any of this ghosts have mustaches.
Some of them have like facial hair.
They like mutton chops.
Mutton chops.
Yeah.
There might be handlebar mustache or two in the Haunted Mansion.
There's got to be.
So I feel like the mustache would travel with him.
But maybe that's the gag.
That's the joke.
That it just hovers there.
Sure.
I like that.
Speaking of the Florida mission to Mars.
There is a restored 19 like July 1992 mission to Mars.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Watch that.
The whole ride through and the sounds a little distorted.
But the footage is very clear.
Mm hmm.
And you can see how that would become Alien Encounter and Stitch.
But the the Mission Control Room.
I was impressed.
Mr.
Johnson for 1992.
He is moving a lot.
Mm hmm.
That animatronic.
It's kind of a long like a long pre-show.
It is a long pre-show.
For what I would assume it would have been.
Yeah.
Almost feels equal to the ride.
An albatross.
A big albatross.
I think if you grew up with this ride and you were fond of it the albatross was the was the big good part.
Was the thing.
And they retained it from the moon one to the Mars one.
Got to keep albatross.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
The other thing that was interesting to me is like that footage is from mid-July 1992.
This ride looks empty.
Yeah.
That is wild to see because it would be shoulder to shoulder now I feel like in mid-July.
Anything would be.
Yeah.
In 92 there's no one going you want to go watch the movie on the floor.
Like.
Yeah.
That's we've seen rides.
And like okay so here's us before recording this is thinking mission to Mars once we I'm sure mission to Mars is kind of a radically different thing because Mars is way different.
Yeah.
So once we start and then realizing that the main difference is that one character has a mustache.
I'm sorry.
Wait wait.
What are the main differences that Mr.
Morrow is now Mr.
Johnson.
Otherwise almost the same ride.
They repeated some stuff.
Same structure same pre-show room.
Yeah.
So you know in my head I didn't I never knew what mission to Mars was.
I don't maybe you like maybe you met an alien maybe some scary con type villain shows up and like sure he's big enough to grab your ship and he's going to shove it into the core of Mars and you're going to be sucking lava until you die.
Well I don't know what happens.
But instead you just land and that's it.
The first part of the resistance is like this.
That's the pre-show when you're on Lieutenant Beck ship there's a front and a back and it's making you see where you went and you think you're going there.
True.
But there's so much more action and so much stuff happens.
Sure.
Versus yeah watching the movie on the floor or the ceiling.
So yeah 92.
We're getting a little.
This is a little.
For unless you like well clearly the only move and what I was just saying.
Star tour exists.
Yes yeah that's the big thing right.
Absolutely.
That's weird that they overlapped.
Yes it is.
I hadn't thought about that at all.
In both Disneyland and Disney World there is a very active ride with thrills and characters who you love from movies and you go to sci-fi worlds and then a couple feet away you leave that gift shop and then you can go right into one.
It's like now we're going to ease off on the thrusters.
It's the same premise basically too.
It's like space tourism.
Yes.
Yeah so like.
But they have they actually have jokes about how like.
Doesn't this feel like an airport and it has the tropes of like it's like as familiar and kind of like mundane as an airport.
They were doing like a comedy rocket to the moon basically or mission Mars.
So I mean I'm sure imagineers are like this thing should go.
We got to get like I'm sure it was just like well we don't have the money to replace it yet so.
But yeah it is funny that they overlap for years.
Wow.
This.
That cannot have been kind.
No.
You go on those back to back.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's crazy.
Well but yeah but you're moving less and it's air conditioned.
So maybe you devote the time just to like get out of there.
If we were doing this podcast back then Jason would be like you know what's a better ride than Star Tours.
Mission to Mars.
Longer you're in the air conditioning more doesn't jostle you around as much.
Doesn't jostle you around.
You get a little dozing.
Nobody's yelling at you.
Nobody's I don't like when the guy comes on and says Star Tours.
What are you doing.
I don't like getting scolded.
Too loud.
That's a punishment.
I want I want a sleepy Mr.
Collins to explain what he's doing while I relax.
Mr.
Collins is Jason's favorite character in fiction.
Can I say I alluded to like a bad downgrade and this is the it's in Disneyland.
Yeah.
And it's Mission to Mars closes in 1992.
The building sits empty until part of it is used for something called Toy Story fun house which seems kind of like crappy.
It seems like it was I think I never got to do this in either but this was like a interactive like an activation essentially that was next to the El Capitan when original Toy Story came out.
So you see the movie and then you get to go into this whole Toy Story land.
It's like this temporary carnival and I think it was pretty cool in that form like this extra thing and Hollywood on Hollywood Boulevard and I like Toy Story.
I want to see real army men and whatever.
But I think then you take then they thought well this went so well let's plop it into Disneyland for a minute and I don't think it was it didn't compare favorably to like the real permanent rides.
You know yes it was meant to be a temporary thing so it was not there for very long.
And then in Tomorrowland 98 the building eventually turned into Red Rockets Pizza Port.
Yep.
So that's where you are when you have your increasingly expensive pizza.
Boy that just keeps rocketing up and up doesn't it.
Yeah.
But by that point Alien Encounter with some of that arc had already played out in Disney World where it was embattled and people thought it was too scary and too much trouble to put it and it's too expensive to put into.
So the space that just sat empty while they wait while we waited for a ride to come ended up opening as a quick service pizza restaurant.
And it's what it still is today.
And if we're diagnosing the Tomorrowland problem this is a crucial one isn't it.
Ride.
The space that was essentially a ride from 55 to 92 becomes a pizza restaurant that's been there now for 25 years.
That's how long it's been.
Yeah 98 to 2023.
Yeah.
Food into I mean food in Tomorrowland has been a bad.
That's been a food black hole for a long time.
Yeah.
Except for Mike Mitchell who loves pizza port.
I don't know anyone else who's such a champion of it.
There's no I can't see any sort of pizza riso fandom at the pizza port.
I haven't felt it at least.
Maybe there is.
But yeah it's got to come with a lot of like well and but and I know qualifiers.
Yeah a lot of qualifiers like I need to eat something.
I wouldn't mind cafeteria pizza.
Yeah and it's I like the exterior of the pizza port fine and it's got the rocket there and that's nice.
Now it's yes now it's a little more Toy Story which is fine.
But I don't you know what I I do like that as opposed to Red Rockets pizza port was always pretty ugly.
Seeing aliens is a nice thing but that zone is just is chaos to me.
Yeah.
This is where the Tomorrowland all right if we're gonna go bronze let's stick with or whatever what did you call it like rusty.
That corner chaos.
Marble ball that's not like a whole fountain like it used to be when it opened because there was too much like pee and poop in there.
So all right it's now it's just a marble ball and not a fountain gone.
Rock Moonliners coming back the rocket and now it's going to be on top of a Coke cart weird ugly like transporting you away from thirst.
I that thing's ugly it doesn't match the aesthetic of the rest and then it's just Star Wars junk.
Now there's the aliens.
I that Douglas aircraft thin is still kind of there.
That's still yes the marquee that little swoop essentially is so where it says alien pizza planet that corner just junk to me.
That is where like you should be in the heart of a cool aesthetic as you were when it that area ruled when it was Space Mountain with the ramps.
The big neon logo the starcade the near me on Mickey.
They destroy it now it's just like it's a like five things that don't all make sense together.
It's a bummer.
It's a disappointing pizza restaurant.
It's an empty in inventions which is just a gift shop.
It's an empty theater that plays previews for movies sometimes.
Maybe I literally don't know what's there as we record this starcade that once in a while is like an event space.
It doesn't have a second level like a two level arcade.
No gone not anymore.
And then if you really walk back you go to start Space Mountain and now we're back because I love that that big that that metal wall.
You just you got to like yeah of course now it's just this like layer of awful aesthetic before I get to one of my favorite parts in any park.
But that that layer that's a lot of brush to cut through.
You're you're saying maybe one of your fixes go back to the past of the 70s like with the speed ramp.
Yes and such don't go back to the past of the 90s chaos of like we're out of money.
Just start re reuse the thin for the pizza place.
Yeah well we will talk about it when we ever we figure out how to do our fix up.
So but it's my opinion they need to like demolish almost everything except for Space Mountain.
I think I think almost everything has to be leveled to the ground.
Sure yeah yeah that's the way like I get I'm sure there are fixes but I bet there's a way to hollow out that carousel building and use it as like a waiting area or like the foundation of something if we had to cut them a little break.
But ultimately hey utopia submarines blow it up gone.
I know the massive environmental catastrophe that little yeah pocket there.
But ultimately I was going to ultimately demolishing the interventions building can that be that much more money for going to build a giant other ride next to it.
I don't think so.
Yeah me as well.
Yeah true.
I'm just trying to I'm trying to get my head start.
Otherwise we don't get anything.
It was as soon as demolition enters the picture.
There's got to be a way to do Tron.
Just figure it out.
That's what they wanted to do.
Hey by the way Douglas aircraft eventually absorbed by Boeing in much the same way that marquee got absorbed by the bad pizza restaurant.
Sure.
Two absorbings.
Two limping.
And like I guess we'll use this.
It's just OK.
Well you know I think this helps to start like I think that's a bit that's a big tomorrow land juncture that that's a that's a path division where they could of course correct even like if they.
I mean maybe they would have done alien encounter and then it just would have led to stitch and then it'd be nothing like Disney worlds.
But even if there had been a time where it was alien encounter something new and you just keep that space because that that that space is only going to keep being a restaurant.
You don't go from restaurant back to the only way that happens is if there's a total demolition.
Yeah.
And you can easily build a restaurant near there somewhere else.
So it's a it is a different.
It all seems like one big structure but it is different than Space Mountain right.
Which is it would have to be because that building existed before Space Mountain.
Yeah.
Then sure.
But yeah I think that this this facility's got to go.
Sorry Mitch but this this has to be for the for the sins of not just making it a new ride immediately.
You know who could save it.
Plek to you think Plecto's happening now.
I think Plecto's Supper Club.
I'm not against that idea.
And for listener there was going to be this thing that replaced the Carousel of Progress called Plecto's Intergalactic Review or something.
Yeah.
There was this going to be this like crazy it's America Sings but a bunch of aliens all singing for you.
Sure.
But even that that was Carousel building.
I don't think they're I don't think Carousel building could host a true Carousel show anymore.
Yeah.
Because of the demand or because it doesn't.
I think I think they changed the building enough that you couldn't just make it even if they said let's just bring back original Carousel of Progress.
We're taking it back from Florida.
I don't think they could do it.
You have to probably dismantle some of the spinning and gears and stuff.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Don't go man.
But yeah you're probably right.
I mean you probably just have to rebuild it.
Of course I'd love they should try Plecto but yeah I don't we know one thing we're not getting is like an 80 animatronic show.
That's part of like a thing that Tomorrowland 2055 sounded awesome.
And Tomorrowland 98 I think will make for fun awesome episode of a podcast.
But beyond that.
It was a disaster in reality.
It's its final use.
Well that's something we'll get.
We need to speaking of our subdivision we need there's like a bunch of Tomorrowlands we got to figure out how to handle.
If there's ones you're particularly thirsting for audience let us know.
We want to revive this Tomorrowland thing and commit to it more than Disney has.
So please tell us what in Tomorrowland lore whether it's weird old 50s crap we missed or are you dying for 98 rocket rods.
There's a lot of stuff that we got to start getting through.
Yeah.
We'll try to do it all without getting too sad.
I know people are getting thrilled at the idea of comparing where the mission to Mars movie falls in Brian De Palma's filmography with Scarface and Untouchables.
We are wondering.
I am wondering like how did he how how did they what an odd.
Is it a director with a real stamp you know to do that to do some kind of forgotten Disney sci-fi.
And what am I like is is it like his like Spielberg did Bridge of Spies.
I like Bridge of Spies or other people like wild about Bridge of Spies.
Why are you comparing those.
Well I'm just saying it's kind of more like an in between genre a movie major work not a major work but there are known actors in it.
This is a bizarre comparison to Bridge of Spies and Mission to Mars.
Well is there another people saw Bridge of Spies.
Yeah.
And liked it.
Didn't Rylance win an Oscar for it.
I mean Rylance is terrific.
Don't get me wrong.
Well is there more of a Spielberg like you know Journeyman kind of terminal movie.
Terminal terminal terminal probably probably terminals better.
Yeah.
Well we looked.
Do people want us to watch this movie.
Do people want us to just do water down blank check.
That's a good question.
People very good question.
By the way Griffin Newman I think was starting to text us corrections on a recent episode.
I saw a couple things pop in.
He thinks I called wild old dogs wild hogs which I don't think I did but I don't know maybe I did.
OK well let's just deal with it now.
I hate to play corrections department Mike but wild hogs was 2007.
You guessed way early on that for sure.
I thought I said that on the episode too.
You did I think.
Yeah.
I think I called it old dogs and then I started with like 2005 and then I said oh it's 2009.
And John Travolta's every little step music video which we will cover more thoroughly.
You're begging for it was for old dogs not wild hogs.
But we could have called you look I could have made a mistake.
Griffin I know Griffin that you are an expert in this area and in this genre of film and that director I forget his name.
It's not Walter Becker he's from Steely Dan but it's a name like that.
Well somebody look up who that director is.
See if I'm right.
But you know there are people out there myself included.
I think we all get a little confused between wild hogs and old dogs.
By the way I know where the video is from Griffin.
I know that's not from wild hogs.
I'm not crazy.
But wait a minute but did you say it.
If you said it in the episode.
Maybe I said it but I did not.
There's no way I meant to say that if I said it.
Oh it is Walt Becker.
Walt Becker is the man's name.
That's confusing.
Wow.
Very confusing yeah.
Two of the greats.
Music equals in music and film the Walt Becker.
I've never sat down and watched either of those movies.
Maybe I should.
They're bizarre.
Does the audience want us to do that?
I don't know.
Well that's for sure watered down in Black Check.
Has Black Check gotten to Walter Becker yet?
Walt Becker.
Walt Becker excuse me.
They should.
Well you know make sure they do.
Oh he did.
That is a good filmography.
He did Van Wilder.
Alvin and the Chipmunks the Road Ship and Clifford the recent Clifford where Clifford was not
big enough.
The awkward Clifford the awkwardly sized dog was Walt Becker.
Scott is like popping a vein in his forehead while he's saying that.
What he's upset?
He's like that's his thing.
The size of.
It's like wow I've never seen this before.
This is Scott's like line in the sand.
Like Clifford needs to be really big.
He's scared of that though.
Look much like you saying yeah I know but I'm willing to be I'm willing.
I probably am upset by I don't like that Clifford could fit into a house.
Yeah right.
Clifford look do a Google image of Clifford the dog.
He's bigger than a barn.
Right.
That's the size of Clifford.
Yes.
They made it weird and too small.
Awkwardly in between.
Slightly bigger than Marmaduke in that movie.
Just like people just like a lot of people are saying that Douglas Rockett looks like
shit.
I'm not the only person saying that Clifford was an awkwardly sized dog.
That's true yeah.
There's a growing growing more people that are saying you're hearing it more and more.
Hearing it more and more.
Yeah.
Okay let's get to the door.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thank you for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three where you get
one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
Do let us know what you want in the Tomorrowland genre or do you want us to bail on it all
and figure out the difference between wild hogs and old dogs.
I would love to see the people who's like I fuck Tomorrowland.
Like I don't.
There's got to be some.
Real quick before we're done on the Wikipedia they have a picture which I really like which
looks like they gave you some sort of certificate.
Did you see this?
Wait.
For for.
Oh for being on the ride for like on the ride like Mark Twain if you like you were the captain
of Mark Twain or whatever and it's a really you wrote you wrote down who like your name
to say that you've been to the moon and the one they have the picture they have says no
all ye by these presents that Vice President Nixon has rocketed round trip to the moon
from the Disneyland spaceport via TWA rocket ship and is hereby awarded this lunar flight
certificate.
And then it says how well how many miles it is and it's signed by Collins.
It's signed by P something Collins.
Nixon got of I'm a little rocket man certificate.
Yes.
Official little rocket man.
Collins is one of the White House plumbers.
8 11 50.
Yeah 8 11 1955.
Wow.
He did it early.
So that's the date on this thing.
Geez.
One of the first.
Yes.
One of our.
Well you forget one of our first astronauts Richard Nixon.
Collins is on the enemy list.
He probably felt the same way that you feel Jason about your Mark Twain captain certificate.
Oh yeah.
I was a little rocket boy.
I achieved much in this world but nothing better than being a little.
Morrow is one of my few real friends.
Collins dead to me.
Mr.
Tom Morrow.