Five, four, three, two, one.
We're too excited to podcast.
It's Podcasts that Ride the Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson.
Are you too excited to say more than hi?
Yes, I'm so concise in my words.
But now you're doing it.
I guess you're gone.
Jason, hi.
What do you think podcasting's gonna be like?
They say every year it's more magical than ever.
The Hollywood Reporter says it's more magical than ever.
Folks, either you know this one or you don't.
I don't think they're…
Because if you've seen it, you can never unsee it.
And it's like, it's simultaneous.
It's a big part, I feel like, of theme park and Disney World culture.
And we've nodded to it here and there.
But this is the first, I imagine by anyone, anywhere,
deep dive into a particular commercial that Disney World put out in 2002.
One that you can only call, I think, it has a real name,
but I think you can only call it We're Too Excited to Sleep.
Yeah, this feels like when you sent this in our group text,
this felt like a Manchurian candidate activation.
Like, had not thought about it in a long time,
besides tangentially touching upon it on this show.
And then as soon as you did…
Can I…
I hate to just go back to saying what we said in text messages,
but you said something so funny in a text message.
I want to remember.
You said something along the lines, like Scott said, should we do this?
And you said, excuse me, can you repeat that?
As if we were in real life or something, instead of just saying,
oh, what are you talking about?
Or could you clarify that?
You said, could you repeat that?
You said something along the lines that made me feel…
Well, we were talking about another topic.
We were talking about another topic and you two had a full conversation
and I was like running around town.
But I'm pretty sure…
No, I did say that.
I did say that.
It just amused me because you were like, whoa, slow down.
Repeat that.
It almost felt like, are you serious, man?
That's what it felt like.
No, that was more like, oh, I'm sorry, I'm an idiot.
I'm confused.
I just want to make sure I understand this correctly.
I think you are a little incorrect, Mike, because when I do remember,
I said like, should we do an episode about this?
I sent a GIF of a child who is the star of this and I felt support right away.
And honestly, I think we were too excited to do this.
I guess so.
We backed up other topics.
You're going to have to get in line, buddy,
because we got a 30-second ad to talk about for way more than 30 seconds.
Can I tease?
This is the first second gate of September.
Oh, yeah, and we're sort of officially back from a little hiatus, at least here.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
So at the end of the episode, I'd like to announce my birthday shot.
Your birthday shot because your birthday is in early October,
but we'll do it a little early to clear the haunt cast season.
Yes.
So you know what you're doing.
You know what shot you're calling.
Well, it involves a little legwork, so which I will take care of.
OK, but you want to run the legwork by us.
Yes, because I haven't mentioned it so far.
No, no, no, we have not.
Yeah, we're in the dark on this.
OK, wow, wow.
So a lot of business to handle here.
Future topics jumping out.
But before we could go any further,
you know, you've been waiting for us to come back on the second gate for a while.
What are they going to return with?
What monolith of theme park culture?
And it is this absolutely unforgettable piece of theme park media.
Maybe the best thing to do here for anyone who doesn't know or needs
or needs the Manchurian Candidate activation is to just play the ad.
So, again, this is from this from 2002.
The actual name of it is Anticipation, which appears on screen.
And that's why we know it's a very like Folgers coffee ad kind of.
I don't think they do this anymore.
I don't think the little like ad auteurs name their pieces right.
Right.
Same way.
Well, maybe they do.
But behind the scenes and we don't know.
Yeah.
And they're and they're always referred like like saying really quickly the, you know, you know,
so like so we're like, all right, so the machine, we're going to sort of machine.
And, you know, I'm thinking back on soda machine.
It's like how do we top the heights of soda machine?
I hate to give a little bit.
I hate to be too inside baseball here, but on the, you know, Jason, I've done some commercials
and you do see the name of the commercial that they don't say in the actual 30 second or 15 second spot.
So the Allstate commercial I was in forever was called Check, Please.
Wow.
But I never said check, please.
Nobody ever says check, please in it.
Is that line in it?
No, I don't think so.
Unless Dennis Haysburg said it, but I don't think he did.
Yeah.
I sometimes I wonder, are there new listeners?
This is another, I think ads are all like mentoring candidate activations.
What they're supposed to do is like lodging your brain and then you're buying something or paying for something and you don't know why.
Sometimes I wonder if people remember your ad, like you and this girl at the table.
And then I'm sure we've talked about the show before, but like it was one of those where there was a period where like every time I'd met you.
And then every time I was in a bar, it was always like if you're in a bar for an hour, it shows up.
Crazy.
Yeah, it was.
Yeah, it was great.
Occasionally you get that title and like the sentence you're supposed to.
I've been on shoots where they are like, hey, let's go to set.
And I'm like, hey, no one has given me a script.
Oh, well that's a whole.
The only thing you have to say is sentence.
So they just hand you the storyboard.
That's a whole other thing where you're just like, oh, you just kind of get, they just push you and they go, hey, do this.
And you go, what am I doing?
They go, oh, yeah, sorry.
I just push you.
I forgot that part.
Yeah.
A director showed me a really cool diagram.
They had doodled once too of like this sentence needs to be two seconds.
This needs to be three.
This needs to be ten.
Then there's a card for five seconds.
And I was like, that is insanely impressive that you did that.
But it makes sense.
You get a free breakfast quesadilla.
Oh, the best.
The best, yeah.
Well, yeah, this is a clearly like down to the minute 30, you know, down to the second 30 second ad where it's like things are overlapping.
You can tell it's like and then they got their messaging to put in.
Oh, yeah.
But the only thing the listeners need to know is that it is in a child's bedroom and it is the it's a brother entering his sister's bedroom.
And it is the bluest, glowiest suburban room you've ever seen.
It's all in extreme close ups, I would say.
It's like it's all about emotion.
It feels like like E.
T.
is about to join or something like the room is very feels amblyne to me.
It feels like they may as well just go to the window and see an alien friend.
Childhood magic.
Something's in the air.
That's completely clear.
Before the famous line even is said.
Also, I thought this ad was a lot older.
And then at some point they show the Disney World logo and a website.
So and I was like, oh, this is much more recent than I anticipated.
Yeah, I didn't know either when it was from.
And now I know some of the forums in which it appeared.
I'm sure it was on television, but also on some tapes.
And that might be why we know it really well.
But anyway, let's let it speak for itself and let a famous quote be said.
Here's the full ad anticipation.
Are you sleepy?
No.
What do you think it's going to be like?
Mom says there's even more magical stuff now.
OK, guys, back to bed.
We're too excited to sleep.
Imagine how excited your kids will be when their favorite Disney stories come to life on a magical Walt Disney World vacation.
You sleep?
No, too excited.
I heard that.
Big boom, big boom.
Very like old McDonald's ad.
The hijinks of McDonald's and Ronald's and fun.
So, you know, there's all right.
It's a it's a nice little scene at the beginning.
Then you get some good Disney World footage and a website and a dad act.
Look, the parents are fine.
But how much does this dad eat shit to the kid in terms of winning the ad?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He's nowhere close.
Not even in the ballpark.
He should have done that.
Somebody should have directed him to do it like the kid, at least.
Oh, like a little more of a maybe they didn't know.
Maybe they didn't know what take they had, what magic they had.
That's a good point.
I just wanted to give the full context.
But obviously all you need to know about is this.
We're too excited to sleep.
It's almost Gilbert Gottfried.
It is.
Wow.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
You know, it's interesting.
The kid didn't actually talk like that.
That was an F.
That was a character that he put on.
His regular voice is totally normal.
I don't know.
I feel like that's a kid saying something in a way only a kid can say.
Like, I feel like that's not a delivery you could prompt someone for.
I don't think so.
And it's like imagine just like reading the script for that and the copy for that.
And maybe it's an OK ad.
And they did a lot of ads around this time in this style with the little name next to the little mouse ears at the top.
And it's you know what?
We're not just going to show shots of the rides.
This is about the emotion and about like how your kids are going to feel and how their relationships are going to grow.
Right.
From you going to Disney World.
There were a lot of these, but none of them have the staying power of this moment, which is absolutely just an organic, weird little kid moment.
Yeah.
It's pretty remarkable.
Very iconic.
Out of the gate.
First time you ever saw it.
Well, you want to know, like, did the kid audition like this or did they like say to the kid,
You're going to Disney World tomorrow to juice him up.
And then after the take said that was a lie.
Yeah, you're not going to check.
OK.
I mean, you can go if your parents pay up, but we're not going to ban you from going.
We don't have the power to do that.
You're getting your non-union one hundred and fifty dollars for this commercial kid.
See if mommy and daddy pay up, though.
Technically, it's not look, it's actually for VHS pre rolls.
Those ads are different.
So those rules are different.
So you don't get any from that.
I don't know.
I don't know what prompted it, but just imagine if it's the exact same ad.
All right.
Come on, kids.
We're too excited to sleep.
Nothing.
No one remembers it.
Nobody ever talks about it.
That's what how they would do it now.
I think so.
I don't think they would allow for it's like too weird.
We get more normal.
You get kind of like a more there'd be so many.
There'd be immediately a flood of like twelve identical people like, yeah, we're wondering if we.
I mean, he did create.
He's doing really great.
Yes.
Just note the thing to death.
They bring in a kid that was like went to like NYU Junior, like a little acting school in NYU and was like, I am too excited to sleep.
And then they'd be like, that's great.
We love that.
It's like, you know, it's John Hartnett, Josh Hartnett's son.
Yeah, of course.
He's like, you know, it's got to be somebody or he's like some or he's some billionaire's kid or whatever.
A situation where a director will say, throw it away, which usually translates to like just don't just have a lot of content for the like,
And then like a kid actor who will say, I love that.
Uh huh.
And it's like, well, that's a weird thing for an eight year old to say.
Do you think just throwing it away is a good thing to say to a kid because then it gets it could shake them out of their like stiff kid actorness?
We've talked about that in various specials.
Yeah, kids have a mode that and understandably, I'm in performance mode.
I have to talk this way.
I have to be a little robot.
I mean, I take that to mean you say it very dry.
Don't have a lot of inflection and don't make it too funny.
You know, don't deliver it too much.
So it might be good for a kid actor.
Just throw it away.
Related question gets us off the kid a little bit.
But with you both as esteemed commercial actors, has the direction, just have fun with it ever helped?
It's a very good question.
Just have fun with it.
If it's helped in the sense that it's ever been used, no, for sure.
No, because I know you're told this in auditions and I'm I think you're and you're probably like, I only just caught up with what this is.
It is not fun.
It's all jargon.
There is no way for a real human being to have fun with it.
That's just something a dumb person says because they like have seen other directors say it.
If just have fun with it means do whatever you want.
I've had fun in the take, but it's never been used.
Yeah.
Yes.
Because it doesn't make sense.
Then you're piecing it together and like, well, I'm glad they all had fun.
It is usable.
I mean, I wouldn't I didn't do like something completely like unused.
I would try to get in the zone of usable.
But yeah, just have fun with it or yeah, do do one like a fun one.
Sometimes somebody would say, hey, let's do a fun one or on this take.
Yeah, on this take, do whatever you want or something.
But yeah, no, not usable.
And if you if you having fun with it takes longer than two seconds, then there's no room for and some comedy premises or choices require a little tangent.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
It's going to be long and it's probably going to be weird and you're not going to use that.
Yeah, doesn't have a it doesn't fit in a title thing like this.
There are there are videos.
I mean, maybe they've been deleted, but there are videos of me in callbacks.
There's like 10 minutes of just having fun with it.
Thirty minutes.
Jibberish.
Yeah.
You're just giving it away and not gotten hired.
Well, I just on some of them I have on the commercial.
The first thing I ever booked.
There is a video of me, I think, improvising for twenty five minutes in the room at a second callback.
And there's no dialogue in the spot.
None of the characters say anything.
You see my face for about two seconds and they worked me so hard in that callback.
I've gotten it.
Someone's given me a so they're like, we're so sorry you're still here.
Here's a soda.
I have only once or twice been there so long.
I've got a check in the mail because sag rules are such that they're supposed to pay for auditions.
Oh, after.
Yeah, auditions.
It's very rare.
Yes.
They have to really.
Two hours technically.
Something like that.
You have to make sure to sign in and out to indicate it.
But it seems to me then you just got to like suddenly become Charlie Chaplin with the sign in.
You have to like, yeah, you know, like then you slip and then the papers go everywhere and there's a mess to clean up and no, no, no, I'll get it.
Yeah.
You make the ink go everywhere.
If you can just like through business, make your audition take longer than two hours.
You just wrote yourself a check.
Sure.
They have a person though monitoring that list that a callback very, very aggressively often, not all the time.
Yeah.
So you got to deal with the list.
Meister.
Yeah.
You would really have to.
They're on.
They've experienced this scheme before.
Yes.
Mr.
Magoo.
Yeah.
Hello.
It's like a stick.
You're like hitting around.
I can't see anything.
Whoopsies.
And the person, the list Meister just kind of listlessly ducks right when the game comes her way.
I've experienced this before.
The list Meister went to lunch.
So sorry.
Yeah.
No, we'll sign you out.
This doesn't matter because usually now it's just like on a MacBook like webcam, just like doing it from your house.
Yeah.
And I think all I think I can't even book.
I can't book a goddamn commercial to save my life anymore.
I had the hottest streak of all time for a few years.
This is going to be like the Bruce Springsteen Glory Day song where I'm just like, you know what?
There was one year.
GE.
Direct TV.
All state.
Taco Bell.
German beer.
A German beer company.
Only aired in Germany.
I don't.
Well, is this, as you've done before, a message to any ad bookers in their audience?
On the Patreon?
On the Patreon.
I mean, yeah, I guess it's possible.
Very hyper specific casting directors.
Yeah.
I mean, it's possible, I guess, if you're out there.
No, this is not.
This is not the direct pathetic plea I've made on the main feed.
Yeah.
You need to cast a wide net to do that.
That's on purpose.
Look, let's get back to this kid's glory day.
Of course.
His glory take.
I mean, what have many commercial actors scaled this height?
Is there a more memorable kid line?
I mean, there's been, you know, there's like, there's Where's the Bee.
I was going to say, what are the most iconic commercials we remember in general?
It's like, it's not this for most people.
You have to kind of be into Disney World to know this.
Yeah, yeah.
On a wide scale.
But I but it's it does feel up there to me in terms of quotability, relatability.
I are commercials and this quotable anymore.
Well, it's hard because so many people skip commercials and you got different ways to watch TV.
So I feel like we're not we don't collectively all see the same ads.
This is some this is some monoculture right here.
We're all watching the tapes and seeing ABC shows with Disney World ads.
I watch mostly pro professional wrestling on Wednesday nights.
And the ad I see the most is Frank Thomas's ad for something called New Genics, right?
Genics, which is I think a low T like a low T pill or a low T powder.
Yeah, I looked at I read about it.
It's it's all like kind of it's not actually testosterone.
It's all like just vitamins and ginseng and all that.
OK, so it's a natural way to boost testosterone.
It's not some sort of aggressive testosterone replacement.
And they didn't call you in for this one, Mike.
Not yet.
Well, they know my testosterone is still actually pretty high.
Oh, you know, they know they wouldn't people wouldn't believe it.
They know I'm, you know, maybe an older man at this point, but they don't believe that I would have low T.
They like the big hurt, big, big 60 years old, even though he looks great.
And maybe maybe we should doubt that he even has low T because he's a celebrated athlete and he looks great.
So I don't know.
They should have though.
I should have at least been on the callback list.
You can you can play low T.
It doesn't mean you have low T.
You're right.
Yeah.
I looked it up after I saw that.
Were you going to get it?
Well, I was interested in it.
I bet your T is pretty high.
I bet my T is pretty high.
I bet it's high.
When Jane comes on the show, that's to be believed.
Well, don't check the T.
That's a very good point.
Go back and check those episodes out.
This motherfucker's got the highest T on the show.
I guess he puts the T in PTR.
Couple of T's, brother.
So on the commercial, they're like you get it for free.
But I think the hook is that they automatically sign you up for a monthly plan because otherwise it's like 70 dollars at GNC or CVS or whatever.
So you can just buy a bottle of a big cup.
Why'd you want to buy this?
I don't know.
Just fucking around.
But that seems like a thing.
I feel like you've complained about people running their powder scams, right wing grifter, and suddenly like, oh, a powder thing, a non-scam.
Let me just run the pricing.
What?
It's a scam.
I don't know.
I'm a mark sometimes.
I like to be worked.
Well, you're watching Adster.
They show this during wrestling all the time.
They show it during AW.
There's a line and they like it too.
And she likes it too.
And it's like a lady, meaning like, yeah, and then fuck sometimes.
Sheila, I'm an older man.
That's what it is.
Grow up if you're upset with what I just said.
The powder is good for me too.
I don't have to take the powder to get to benefit from it.
That's the most famous commercial I know at this point.
That's a current commercial.
I'm not saying it's like, where's the beef or I don't know.
To you.
Well, this speaks to the fractional nature of ads.
Right.
After our imaginations the way this, we've sure done a lot of talk of tea for a dad about a little kid.
Well, there's a dad, there's a tired dad.
Very dry delivery from the dad, by the way.
What were you saying?
I don't care for it.
It seems like an ice cake.
You don't like it?
No.
I think it's mostly set up for the daughter to go, I heard that.
How can she hear it?
That's what I want to know.
Yeah.
He says it so quietly.
And she's just full volume as if she's, maybe she's just in the room.
So of course she can hear it.
I guess in that, yeah, with that logic, yeah.
But what a gig.
Lying flat on your back with your eyes closed, delivering the one line.
What a gig.
Jason's dreaming.
That's the analyze, that's like Monday Night Football where you get out the board and you circle things on a play.
If Jason could analyze commercials and how comfortable each role was on the actual day, I would really like that.
Not swimming at all.
Not like me and Hulu.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So if you could do a Twitch channel where you get out the board, like the John Madden board where you can circle on live television.
Or Vanity Fair does these breakdown of scene things.
Yes.
Jason breaks down how comfortable the actor's got to be.
No, no, just a ballpark like going rate for commercial actors at this time.
So if you think about what they're making per hour and they're spending most of that hour in a bed, this guy's got it made.
It's got it made.
You see this bus by Commercer Hill, Grandpa here never actually has to sit in the chair, meaning he was in the chair from the start of the shoot till the end of the shoot.
This is a good day for Grandpa.
This would be an A plus role.
Like this would be a I would this, by the way, is a great idea for you to do.
And then it's like a Wheaties ad where Wheaties gives somebody the energy to go do a track meet and Jason's like, no, no, no, no, X, X, X, X, X, X, X.
Do not answer this call back.
If you get it, don't get tricked into doing a track and field spot.
The whole spot is him sprinting.
You know how many times he probably had to do that?
At least 15 times because look at all the different shots.
Look at all the different setups.
You can tell it's the same man.
They did not use an extra note.
I use it.
No doubles.
So this would not have been a good day.
He's wearing his own t-shirt and slacks.
Maybe he gets an extra forty dollars for using his own t-shirt and slacks.
That is good.
That would be good.
But that doesn't count for shoes or belt.
It's technically a dry cleaning fee.
Oh, yeah.
Now, the dad is and he's covered up by a sheet, which means probably they were not even if they weren't considering pajama pants.
And then he probably just brought his own.
What I'm saying is I think he avoided maybe an elongated, you know, like try on fitting day.
So, you know, so it's less time for him and that.
If you can never see you have your bottom half shown, now you're saving valuable time.
This could be the newest, hottest Twitch stream.
I thought you were going to say Twitch stream of me sleeping because there are people who live stream them sleeping.
Let's do that, too.
Let's put that together as well.
No, no, this actually is going to be more work for you.
But oh, look, this is a four hours.
He slept on the couch and now he's moving to the bed after he brushes his teeth.
Let's just turn a webcam on in your bedroom then.
I guess if there's a slip, there's a now you got a Truman show it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's true.
If you need a couch cam and a bed.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, either either option is fine for what we're going to do.
OK, let me OK, we can talk about OK.
Question one, what is it that makes this particular delivery so compelling?
Is it like is it the way he does it?
Is it the emotion?
Is it the relatability of feeling this way about Disney World or about any vacation?
Any like big, exciting day you got coming up?
Well, here what's really the core of why we remember this?
I would say number one, it's cute.
It's very cute the way he says it.
And you understand it immediately.
You've seen it.
You've done it.
You've said you've said it before to your parents.
I think I've come around.
I do think it's cute.
And it's easier for me to think it's cute now having a toddler and like knowing what fun it is
to have a little goober run around saying weird stuff.
Yeah.
I think there was a time where I would have might have been more likely to like make fun of it
because it is strange.
He also does like turn into like a weird little troll.
Yeah, yeah, but I think that's yeah.
And the angle, the angle makes it memorable, too, that it's like this.
It's like facing up.
So like chin is down.
So his face is just like all weird and like he is.
He is this odd little monster.
He's like he's like, who's the guy from the guy?
The kid, the Barney's the character only you like, Barney.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's got a fry.
I'm Gryff and I got a saxophone.
He's so excited to play saxophone.
He can't he has to channel it through the saxophone.
Just like this kid.
The anticipation is so intense.
He's so excited.
He's like crawling out of his skin.
Yeah.
Which you really I don't know you feel that's not easy to do naturally, I don't think.
But then the other half of it, I was saying, is is is it like we we all flash to when we felt this way or seen people in our families feeling this way?
How much do we relate to?
We're too excited to sleep.
I relate to it.
Yes, especially when I was little.
I knew we were going on a trip there.
From the commercial, they've excised the portion where like and also we're going on a plane and there's always a chance it could crash.
You know, there's a little.
Well, yeah, that's OK.
We are going in unfamiliar, less familiar environment, but it's God knows what could happen.
I'm too excited to die.
I haven't experienced anything.
I've only been excited four times in my life.
This is this is the story of my life.
This commercial, this is I whenever I was aware of what Christmas was, my mom is just like you woke us up every 45 minutes that Christmas Eve.
What is he saying here?
Is saying here?
And she's like, it just like at 545, we just I just got up.
Yeah, I have I think that was me a lot.
There's one that my mom will not let me forget because she was in a she was in the choir.
She would like perform at masses and she did midnight mass on Christmas Eve, which is a long service.
That's maybe you're maybe not, you know, in bed heading to sleep until 2 a.
m.
And that was the year that my sister and I were this ad like, is it Christmas yet?
And five there, my Santa was and she's like, no, no, Santa was.
Of course he was here, but I don't.
And then we didn't.
She just had no choice.
She had to get up.
And it's one of those that you have like one thousand of those, I think, that your mom won't let you forget.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So there's a greatest hits for sure.
The listeners are listeners are aware of like the best 12 to 15.
My brain is so my brain fucks with me so easily still to this day about, yeah, with their fear, excitement.
I remember it'll do it with random stuff.
I remember in 2011, the night this is no boy, the night before Wilco's, the whole love came out.
I was like really excited to hear it because I like whatever song or two that was out there.
And I remember like waking up in the middle of the night being like, is it out yet?
And like I did a drink that was out.
I'm like, I'm an adult here.
And it's like, that's not that crazy.
And it's not even like they were at their full peak or it's not like it was a follow up to Yankee Hotel Foxtrot or anything.
Was it out?
What was when you checked?
I don't think it was.
I think like whatever it was, I don't remember what was a download or what.
And are we in like iTunes store at that point?
You could instantly remember 3 a.
m.
on the East Coast, Medina, West Coast.
I don't remember what the details of the release was.
I don't remember.
But just like I remember being like, why?
I remember being aware of like, why?
Why am I waking up?
I think I get very, I try to get excited about things, which sometimes keeps me up.
What is that?
Like, papa?
I'm very into, I got very into it.
And cards, you know, you heard this?
I was about to say, all right, no further explanation needed.
And I won't let it derail.
Lorcanapax, I got it.
I'll let it derail a different episode.
But Lorcanah is the new Disney collectible card game like Magic the Gathering.
Like Overpower.
Yes.
You're going to do this now.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Are we going to play it on mic?
In your late 30s with a child, you're going to start doing Lorcanah.
Let's see what happens.
It's collectible.
That's what I mean.
I don't have to play it necessarily.
I can just collect them.
You just put them in a binder.
Put them with my other binders.
This makes me so happy that there are not many things I collect.
I guess you look, you get joy from collection.
So that's good.
So I, but I just, if I, sometimes I run the numbers.
How much I save a year.
I'm moving right now and I hate these comic books.
I hate them so much.
This does, you have alluded to this, that the main thing, the main stress in your moving is the comic.
Comic books and paperbacks.
Uh huh.
I'm a big.
Your crime novels.
My crime novels and literary novels.
All your Elrond Hubbard tales of valor.
Well, look, you know, I just love adventure.
I love space and you know, if I pick up some moral guidance along the way.
Yeah, well, you're there for the story.
You're there for the story, not anything else.
No, no, no.
So, so yeah, I was, I was excited about that.
I, yeah, I know this does make me want to, you know, what I have, I was thinking like when, when today do I feel too excited to sleep?
And it's kind of more, it's actually more after the fact.
If there's something even I'm excited about the next morning, that's a little more anxiety because I want to be rested for it.
So that can get negative.
That can be bad.
Actually, I'm more like, if I come back from a, you know, like a great bar hang, we're like, wow.
15 people who are so funny and who I really like, we're all around.
My birthday, you guys are both that.
That was a, I'm too excited to sleep.
And when I need to report to Erin, I'm a little out of it.
I got home and I was just buzzing.
She will sometimes say, you're too excited to sleep.
It is a, it's a really good short.
Erin and I both said it for, she said it separately from me with her sister, any vacation.
It's very like, we, it's definitely always been a, and I feel like she probably said it the first time.
Without asking me, do you know what this is?
I think she just went into it and like, oh, I know exactly what you're talking about.
Scott, I feel like when you do, sometimes if you do a funny voice, you're channeling the spirit of I'm too excited to sleep.
Just other voices?
Just when you're, yeah.
If you have to do a funny voice or like your voice acting or something.
You're saying that's the core of all of his impressions?
The spirit of, what's that?
You're saying that's the core of his impressions?
Maybe.
I don't know.
We all have different touchstones and stuff.
But you know, when you hear me do that voice, it's, you just see other things.
You nail it so well.
You do such a good job.
I checked before I got out of the car.
I was like, let me make sure.
Cause it's got the, it's got the step down.
That's really, that's important.
I saw you looking in the rear view mirror.
Like, what is Ron doing?
I go up with it.
No, no, no.
Now go down with it.
And then I started punching the mirror.
Sorry.
Now that I know you were watching me, I'm really embarrassed.
You're a star.
You're a fucking star.
My knuckles were bleeding for another.
It's just something, it's, I miss my skin is getting thin in my age or something.
It's not because I punched my mirror aggressively.
Look, we all have our process.
You know, we all have different process to pay for recording.
Let's take a big scoop of Nugenics before recording.
Oh yeah.
That's the year it's star.
Yeah.
I'm ready to go now.
Jack, I'm ready to go now.
I got Nugenics in me.
I'm ready to go now.
Okay, go now.
There's something, another thing about this, I think.
I was thinking how this ad, I think clearly comes from a post Lipnicki era.
Oh yeah.
It's way post.
That's six years after Jerry Maguire.
But, you know, Lipnicki captured America's hearts.
And that was, it seems like the appeal of him was he's a natural weird little kid saying weird little kid stuff.
And he's not polished.
He's not Dennis the Menace or whatever.
Not to throw, no offense to Jay North.
But you know what I mean.
Like kids can feel very stiff and staged.
And it was, you know, Lipnicki cracked it all open by just going, having fun with it as we said.
Yes, I agree.
This is also post Haley Joel Osment, like Sixth Sense.
Which I feel like is the other end of the spectrum.
I was going to say kind of underselling it, like much more reserved.
Well, you're so, so we're cracking open what kinds of kid acting there is.
You know, there's not just one mode.
We're in the wake of Jake Lloyd and the Phantom Menace.
Jake Lloyd, Mara Wilson from Matilda.
That's a few years prior.
That's much prior.
Yeah.
I'm just thinking of notable interesting child performances.
Yeah, I'm not saying she's good.
Where a few years before Winner's Bone, I guess Jennifer Lawrence was pretty older.
Yeah, wait a minute.
We're doing big reaches here.
We're looking more Bill Engvall show.
Happy Dermen from the Pilot of the Munsters had just 40 years prior performed.
Frank TV was on and I bet Frank Kelly played a kid at one point.
Okay, Haley Joel Osment has come up.
Haley Joel Osment is relevant to some greater context that I wanted to give.
We probably saw this ad on television.
I imagine this was on television, but the most accessible way you can watch it on YouTube.
And by the way, almost a million views on one of the copies of this.
Clearly the reach of it is massive.
And then also when you Google it, as you guys probably found, there's page after page of Reddits and weird Disney message boards.
Bumper Car Boys forums where people are saying, like, I quote this all the time.
My family quotes this all the time.
It's just it is a really good shorthand for especially the Disney trip experience.
Very fond remembrances.
Some message boards from like 2004, 2007.
People trying to find it.
Yeah, yeah.
We're like, is there some is there some website where you can watch old ads?
Yeah.
My 2005 friend.
You have no idea what's coming.
Yeah.
Everything.
Most thing.
There's only like three things left that aren't posted.
And even there were getting progress on some of these.
King Koopa's cool cartoon.
Yeah.
Somebody just found some old clips of it and I think determined that they were not good.
But at least we have them.
There's some comfort in that.
But anyway, I discovered that there were a couple.
There's probably a number of VHS releases from Disney that this ad was on.
But the most prominent ones, possibly a Beauty and the Beast re-release in 2002.
And also in 2002 or maybe three, the main VHS release of Lilo and Stitch.
Stitch, I believe, is that big ogre, the comical ogre.
You got it, my brother.
Okay.
Just making sure I have it straight.
But so other things on the this this really paints the picture of Disney 2002.
Here's what else was in the pre-roll on Lilo and Stitch.
Spy Kids 2 Island of Lost Dreams.
Inspector Gadget 2.
101 Dalmatians 2 Patch's London Adventure.
Stitch the Movie.
Already there was Stitch the Movie on the video.
What was Stitch the Movie?
I kind of remember Stitch.
I don't remember anything about it.
I remember it was like a direct-to-video spin-off.
What year is Lilo and Stitch?
The year before, 2001 or earlier in 2002.
Eisner had this thing just cranking.
He cranked these things out, I guess.
Yeah, at this point, he narrowed the gap between the 90s ones and their straight-to-video.
Now they're just ready to go as soon as can be.
And then the biggest gap, this is in a world of twos here, there is Jungle Book 2.
And Jungle Book 2 was on my mind because I was just flipping through Disney+.
What have I never, and I don't think I remember that there was a Jungle Book 2.
I brought it up because Mowgli is Hailey Jelosment in it.
Elsewhere there's an ad for Country Bears, Jason's favorite film, also voiced by Hailey Jelosment.
He's the king of Disney around this time.
It is nothing but Indian characters voiced by white people.
Of course.
Like who voices the character Shanti?
Ah, Mae Whitman.
Oh, yeah, Mae Whitman.
Just weird details about this movie and just watching it.
I'm like Jungle Book 2, what are you talking about?
And every day, like John Goodman is blue.
That's weird.
That's okay in my mind.
It was fine.
Yeah, that's as good a casting.
And for a straight-to-video thing, solid casting, Phil Collins acts.
Only acts.
What?
One of the vultures.
One of the like, whoa.
Uh-huh.
I guess was around the studio doing Brother Bear, Brother Bear 2.
Yeah, sure.
In Miami Vice, sir.
So that's fun to me.
But then a couple of weird details.
Due to a legal dispute, King Louie could not be included in the film,
but he is used as a shadow puppet that recounts the events of the first film.
A legal dispute with Louie?
Yeah, I don't know what that means.
And the Wikipedia had no further information.
Kipling estate?
Like, why would it be?
I'm not sure.
I feel like there were weird lawsuits with the voice actor Louie Prima,
but I can't imagine that the Louie Prima estate was still holding Disney to the fire,
what, 40 years after the fact?
I don't know.
Or the character himself, if there's any footage of King Louie appearing in a courtroom.
Wow.
So, but King Louie was Christopher Walken in the Favreau version, I believe.
What?
Really?
I believe, right?
He's a monkey, yeah.
Christopher Walken?
I believe, yeah, because Bill Murray is blue and Christopher Walken is King Louie.
Does he sing?
He does sing.
Yeah, he sings this song.
That's strange.
I will admit I liked it when I saw it.
Yeah, you were a big fan of that.
Now, maybe I'll go back and I'll not like it, but I did like it at the time.
I went to pave the way to Lion King.
We wouldn't have Lion King and Mufasa prequel without, so we owe it so much.
That's true, we do, yes.
But here's the main thing I wanted to bring up about Jungle Book 2.
You hear that and you're like, oh wow, that shit, and they were really cranking it out,
and Eisner's really like, boy, this is so cynical.
Here's the thing, Jungle Book 2 did come out in theaters, by the way.
I had no idea.
And the numbers on this.
Budget, $20 million.
Worldwide profits, $186 million.
Oh my God.
You laugh at Jungle Book 2, like crap, they're pumping out.
That's unbelievable numbers.
For today?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Like, okay, you know, one of Disney's quote unquote hits of the summer,
Indiana Jones and the Dial of Destiny.
Budget, $291 million.
Made 381 worldwide.
So it made, Indiana Jones made 1.
3 times its budget.
Jungle Book 2 made 9.
2 times its budget.
5 times its budget this year?
Barbie.
What we view as like the biggest hit we've seen in the recent past is just currently barely above a Jungle Book 2.
Pure ratio wise.
I would say that the cultural impact is perhaps a little bit more on Barbie.
But like Disney would fucking, you know, if they would like, if somehow like sniping customers in the theme park,
like if somehow, right, if we sacrifice 20 people in Disney World today,
that will get us a hit the size of Jungle Book 2.
Get the guy up on top of Cinderella Castle.
What you're telling me is very clear.
What the lesson should be here, bring back Eisner.
Of course, obviously.
Bob is a public enemy number one these days with his shitty comments left and right.
His arrogance, time to bring back a man.
We trusted.
Arrogance free.
Who undoubtedly.
Now look, I will say this, there was a big writer's strike during the Eisner era.
I don't know any shitty things he said.
Maybe there were less opportunities to say shitty things.
But like as opposed to Eiger, who has famously shitty things, a couple rounds of them.
No, a good trustworthy man who we certainly is not absolutely greedy.
Saying shitty things, but also apparently very touchy and emotional.
That's the rumors that Zaslav and Eiger are like hurt by these labor strikes.
Yeah, that's what came out a couple days ago.
We worked hard on the deal and they said no, they didn't even look.
Yeah, so they were.
Did you see which this one number went up barely?
It's been a tough year for us.
We haven't had any Jungle Book 2s.
We'd give you the money, but we don't have a Jungle Book 2.
I think really this spate of labor actions has really shown that these heads of these companies,
you really go like, what do you do?
What do you contribute, you freaks?
Well, I don't know, Zaslav is staring at it.
He's like, here's one of my properties on a screen,
and then there's a paper telling me about another one of my properties.
What if I put that one on that one?
I own CNN.
What if CNN Alert was in the middle of you're watching Treasure of Sierra Madre on TCM on Macs,
and then it says, guess what, Giuliani's getting sued.
Giuliani's being weird again.
Look, Bob Iger, California Adventure, people didn't like it, so he said,
oh, let's build some good rides.
That's smart.
That's a smart thing for him to do.
No one else could have thought of that.
Build some cool stuff, make it look better.
Are you kidding me?
I couldn't have thought of that.
I was like, this park, just level it to the ground.
I think the wheels started moving on that when Eisner was still in church.
Yes, you're right.
For the Cars Land stuff?
No.
No, that's all Iger.
He was out in 2005, 2006.
I think he was ready to let that thing rust.
But you know what, he was right.
He was probably right, because he's smarter.
He's a good guy.
He was a yo.
In some way, we'll figure out how, but it was correct that Eisner made California Adventure bad.
Yeah, if he was in longer, we would have seen the full plan come to fruition.
As with God, it is hard to know all of the divine reasons, but we have to trust.
We have to trust them that we know what they were doing, what was right for us.
He needs to come on this GD show and talk to us.
We don't say that full word.
Not when we're addressing God and we love Eisner.
Right, exactly.
That's why I said it.
Okay, so that's bigger context.
What have I missed about the…
Oh, I got a big one.
Okay.
So, we were saying how this maybe is not as magical without the natural…
Whatever happens to make that kid just actually be excited in that moment, really be fit.
You're thinking, well, okay, the same ad without that moment maybe is not as magical.
And then I realized there is a practical way to prove that because almost essentially the same ad was made in England,
I guess, trying to get people to…
more aimed at Disneyland Paris.
And I discovered this through some confusing Reddit threads and such where people…
There's the discussion of, does anyone remember this ad where it's like a blue glowy room and there's a kid who's too excited?
And then they say, here is a link to that ad.
And they say, no, no, no, no, it's a different one because it has the word mum in it.
Oh, wow.
So, there's discussion of, is this a Mandela effect?
Am I making up that there was this?
And I had to find a video on Twitter, in fact, to prove that the British one existed.
So, here, listener, it's almost the same thing.
It's almost shot for shot.
It's a blue glowy room and a brother and a sister.
But does it have the same magic?
Same ending.
I guess it was for Disney World in that period.
Is that as charming?
It is pretty charming.
It's pretty charming.
It's very British.
Yeah.
I mean, these little British kids doing this is really good.
I really like it, but it doesn't have the moment.
Look, I don't dislike the children.
Yeah, you can say you don't like them.
But Aaron and I, maybe we're too excited to sleep-pilled or something.
But we were both like, I don't care for this.
Really?
I don't care for these British imps.
Oh, I'm too much of a sucker for a little British kids doing like talking and stuff.
Mem says it's better than era.
They're doing too many, they're inserting too much, it's too British.
They cranked the British up.
You could tell the director was saying, more British though.
Fit more vows in.
I wish they were like, it was like a period piece.
It wouldn't make sense for Disney World, but I wish it was like the Kenzian era.
And like shaking snow off their pajamas, even though they're inside.
Kid had a crutch.
Yeah.
Oh, and then in that wind, because he, look, he gives a little more, that's context for the listeners.
He doesn't fall back into bed like American Kid.
He gets up and does a little spin.
So if that was him getting to throw his crutches away, Tiny Tim style, the excitement of Disney World has cured him of his rickets.
I want to go time traveling to Disney World, Mom.
Mom says, Mom says we're going to get in something called the time machine and we're taking it straight to somewhere called Orlando.
Weeeee, 12.
Yeah, that would be better.
I agree.
But yeah, it's not as good.
But I still, I like, I do like this.
The dad's kind of made a meal of the line.
This guy?
Yeah, the dad did not make a meal of it.
It was too long.
I feel like the note would be like, can you say it twice as fast?
You're like the American dad better.
Because it's short and sweet and then it's mostly set up for the punchline of like, we heard that.
But here's this, here's this thought.
The British dad is kind of, he seems to be more comfortable in the bed, in my opinion, because he's on his side, which is how I like to sleep.
And the American dad is more kind of on his back.
Yeah.
And like this guy looks like he could even be like out.
He's so like comfortable looking.
Okay, that makes a little more sense.
He's almost half asleep.
So that means he's like soaking that cash.
Much better day.
And for Jason's channel, we got to determine like what is the, I don't know, like dollar to pound in 2002.
I don't know who's like making better money for their lying down.
Right.
Yeah.
Which nation of dad made out more like a bandit here?
I'm a left side sleeper.
And which I think they say is good for you to sleep on your side, sleep on your side as opposed to right side.
Really?
Why is that?
I don't know.
I think it's where the heart is to sleep.
You have to sleep on top of your heart.
Well, no, but it's elevated.
If you're sleeping on the right side, you don't want it to be elevated.
It's working less hard.
You're saying I think so on the left.
I don't know.
I toss and turn a lot.
Sometimes back, sometimes left, sometimes right.
It never gets to rest.
No.
Jason's heart is restless.
I've got new genetics.
I've got like days worth of new genetics coursing through my veins.
I'm too excited to sleep.
I can't sleep.
I'm drinking too much ginseng.
I watched your new genetics down with Arizona iced tea, green tea.
Testosterone went straight to my heart.
Made it heavy.
Just have so much love to give and testosterone.
I'm the heart of podcasteride.
My heart has to be pulsing at all times.
The pressure of being the heart and putting the T in PTR.
If we're also picking these ads apart elementally,
something to note that you, Jason, mentioned before we started recording is that it goes straight from iconic shot to excited asleep.
To what's our hero shot?
It is the barnstormer.
It is Goofy's plane roller coaster in the Toontown Fair area.
And Goofy is on it.
He's on it.
So that's good.
But does it not strike, did it strike you, Jason, that there, then the hero shot is a ride that's like fine.
Right?
We've never talked about the barnstormer.
Well, I think that's one that it's like, OK, it could be a kid's first roller coaster.
I think it's elevated by like, OK, you're riding it with Goofy.
For sure.
By the way, I think now that coaster is called the barnstormer starring the great Goofy.
Because all of that stuff is circus themed now because of the big Dumbo, which as we all remember Dumbo,
they make the circus seem awesome to be part of the circus.
Yeah.
It rules.
It's very true.
Terrifying at all.
You also, then the next shot is like a bunch of kids all doing like duck walk, all like wagging their duck tails
as they head into the castle behind Donald and Daisy.
Yeah.
This is a bigger area I hadn't thought about.
But when I, to this day, see Disneyland, Disney World commercials, I think that there is a real false advertising going on
in that they imply that you will get to like be at a party, like dance and have fun with your favorite characters.
This does not happen.
This is not an organic duck walk that you get to do.
You might get a hug you'll never forget.
But besides that, there's not organic party fun happening with the characters.
Not often, but once in a while.
Because like, you know, famously I've talked about going to the Tomorrowland stage and seeing the country bears partying with everybody and just hanging out.
Slapping asses.
Slapping asses, yes.
And you welcomed it.
They got towels?
May I have another?
They're rolling up the towels.
There were towel slapping incidents with the country bears in Tomorrowland.
That's correct.
Being in a locker room.
I want to feel like I'm in the locker room.
They're dirty frayed country bear towels.
Yeah, they're regs.
They're nasty.
Oh, so that hurts.
That leaves a mark.
They're weapons.
Like, yeah.
There's some welts from that.
Yeah, security confiscated their zip guns and their homemade guns from the hauler.
It'll happen.
I mean, at the ticketed event for the retro 80s night, we certainly were dancing with totally many for like an hour.
But it's not a common thing.
That at this point seems like one of the most formative experiences of your life.
Well, it's right before the pandemic too, so it's the last bit of joy.
So every so at the at the depressing height of it, you're just you fall asleep and go straight to like, Mike, dance with me.
Holding out her hand.
I have a video of it.
Yeah, yeah.
Lindsay too.
She's okay with it.
She knows we have something special.
Mike imagining like walk around Max and Roxanne from Goofy Movie and throwback 80s gear, dancing to Obsession.
My obsession.
They're doing the robot.
They're joining hands and doing break dance moves.
We're all drinking tab.
It's a glorious night.
Yeah.
Well, what have we missed about this?
What have we picked apart?
Every elemental detail of this 30 second ad.
Did we do the voice enough?
It's only about nine seconds, 10, nine, 10 seconds of the parks.
It's mostly the scene.
That's something that's interesting format wise, isn't it?
It seems like about halfway through it switches and then it goes back to the back to the scene.
They felt the narrative was too important versus just showing glamour shots of the park.
Do we think that this is effective and an interesting idea to like not just like maybe you feel like you're being advertised to when you see shots of rocks?
But when you get to see the emotion, when you get to see like this is how it might make your family feel.
This is your if you have if you have several children, they will bond over this.
There's something there's something heartstring pulling about it.
Yeah, it does capture the anticipation element.
I am surprised over 20 years later, they have not got the kids back as adults to shoot.
Doesn't that seem like that's a good idea?
Because the optics are like not great for Disney right now between the writer's strike and then like the parks are so crowded.
The parks are empty.
The parks are so expensive.
Yeah, and all their other movies are fucking suck shit.
I have no idea.
I have no idea if they've had a run of hit movies or run of box office flops.
It's hard to tell.
I really can't tell.
I just know Barbie made a billion dollars and everything really.
You show a clip of that and then like get them to recreate it.
I mean, that's the you know what one thing if you're looking at this episode title, you're like maybe like, oh, did they learn where the kids are today?
No, there's no way to find that out.
I tried.
I'd like to know.
And I hope that the kids are doing well.
And I would like to see this kid milking it.
I want to see him at a convention getting to say we're too excited to sleep and everybody.
I want twenty thousand people to light up, say it with him.
I mean, I want everything that's this this guy if he's not like maybe I should I like I'm not a publicist, but I feel like I've got a good.
Oh, I thought you were going to say I'm going to pretend to be him.
Wait, sure.
Well, what does he look like?
Can I fake my way through?
I don't know.
It's a dark kid.
I don't think I resemble this kid at all.
I don't think it matters though.
Yeah, maybe just by putting it out there, I'll just side by side.
I think you just feel like you're walking up to my table and like glancing.
All right.
Him picture him picture.
Yeah, sure.
You know what?
Yeah.
They just don't want to believe that it's me so badly side by side you now with that kid, but then put the same blue filter on it.
And I just fool people into thinking.
Well, and I just always like myself really blue.
I get that's my writer for when I can appear at a convention.
I need the bluest light.
Right, right.
And you'll do anything like in the contract.
This is how many times you'll do the line and how like it.
Well, like you'll do it only five times for a certain fee.
Jason will negotiate this with you because.
Oh, yeah.
So help me penny.
I'm going to squeeze everything I can.
John Madden, Katie Porter, White Porch drawing.
Here's here's here's the plan.
We will.
All right.
They're going to want to see you in context.
They're going to want to see you in a bed.
Right.
So we wheel in a bed.
That's also part of your writer blue lighting.
And you do it all from a bed.
They were like, we'll they put a microphone right above your head.
Put it on a stand.
Get it above you.
You don't get out of it.
You literally don't get out of bed for less than fifty thousand dollars in appearance.
And then as opposed to all these other people at conventions who have to walk around for steps cost money.
Yeah.
Yes.
So here's your price for autographed picture video of you saying I'm doing it.
You know, we we got we got a big menu for that.
We do want to let the Brits in on this.
So he will say mum for a price you can't if you grew up with the British one, but he will not get up and spin that car.
We're talking a two hundred grand appearance fee if he's going to do a spin.
And that price will be tacked to the current exchange rate.
So the dollar is better.
It's pounds better.
That's what they're paying.
Yeah.
We even if this is happening in nine years, we're locking it in its best rate right now.
I just want to tell the listeners because this is paywalled.
So just don't don't tell on us.
Don't tell on Scott about the grift where we're about to pull.
Yeah.
Yes.
Because you can be you know you can be you can be you're in on the ground floor like I you know I listen to this guy when he was just doing a podcast and I didn't even realize that he was we're too excited to sleep.
Right.
He's so humble honestly that he didn't bring it up.
In six years.
Yeah.
Because I if that were me I'd be talking about it all the time.
And now he's finally getting rich off it.
And I said good for him.
Honestly good for him.
So yeah all all few thousand of you please lie.
Help us.
Please help us.
Please.
I like the line so much and I think I appreciate this ad a little bit more having a kid having a little boy myself.
And I was like I wonder if I can get.
A little bit.
And you know hey I'm not holding him to the impression skills that I might hold an adult to but I was like well this sound like coming out of my son I don't think I don't know if he's ever been heard on the show before.
Yeah.
But here's here's my little boy.
To a side this week.
Oh wow.
That's adorable.
Naturalism you can't you can't buy that you know you can't coach that.
I think I forgot I only I did it this morning and hadn't really re listened and that.
Hey that made me feel.
You shit.
It is really.
I'll get him to do it in an English accent.
No British.
That's too cockneyed.
Do it like a current British kid.
Get your accents straight.
Wales.
I suppose that is all I think you survived podcast the ride the Sego gate.
I'm glad you weren't too excited to survive or too excited to subscribe.
And oh wait here I'll do my wrap up but thank you for subscribing to the second gate if you want to dig even deeper join us on our VIP patron to your club three where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
Please keep subscribing to the second gate where at the end of the month you will get a special treat from Jason apologies please explain your leg work.
Okay so I was trying to think of what I want to do for my birthday shot and I was trying I was like oh I alluded to like oh the islands of adventure lighthouse and then I started.
Come I started thinking of other things and I narrowed it down to five and I was a guy who's of islands of adventure huh.
Outside of islands of adventure.
There's more islands of adventure.
I so I narrowed it down to five as Mike said the phrase Jason month at some point and I was like well if I had a program what would I do and then I was thinking I started thinking of other topics and then I decided like well why don't I do something different.
Why don't I get the listeners involved why don't I make it a party.
Oh my gosh a party a party a voting party that's right.
I chosen five topics.
Oh my god we're doing it.
Shot poll if you're not on club three it's polls every month where the listeners get to pick get to submit and pick topics but this is this will be a rare second gate second and club three poll okay yeah we'll get to get that if you're close to yeah yeah right.
Okay so here are the five potential birthday shot.
Ferros lighthouse is one of them island skipper towards the short question.
I have a question.
Okay.
I learned about the original lighthouse is based on one of the wonders of the ancient world.
We know that.
Yeah.
Did you know it before this year.
No the answer is no.
I knew there was a lighthouse and the wonders of the ancient world they didn't know.
Okay.
Ferros lighthouse island skipper towards the short lived boat ride that would take you from port of entry to Jurassic Park.
Holiday Inn's holodome.
Do you know about the holodome.
This has been suggested for the second gate before.
This is a good yeah I've never looked into it deeply but what is what's the quick sell on.
So the quick sell on this these were holiday inns with internal courtyards built around like an indoor pool and like shuffleboard or mini golf.
And I think there's one or two you know they're not how they ends anymore but they're kind of still holding on.
Okay.
I think having room doors that close to an indoor pool I think some of the criticisms where this is disgusting.
Yeah.
That's still indoor pools create just the worst stench.
But okay great.
Yeah.
Number four.
This is an episode I'm calling forgotten cartoon theater which are another podcast.
No no.
So they were going to talk about it shows that I loved as a little kid that I feel like I've seen very little.
One example.
We're talking James Bond Jr.
Has come up for BOTS master which notable for Aviarad.
Is that how you say Aviarad.
Aviarad produced this like kind of.
And we're going to do all of these cartoons or just one.
We're just going to touch on them.
Okay.
So.
All right.
That was also that was bold to say Aviarad.
No further information.
Aviarad.
He produced a lot of the 90s Marvel stuff.
He rescued Marvel with like Pearl Mutter because he owned Toy Biz in the 90s.
So if he's a friend of Ike then he's a guy.
Yes.
They're all buddies.
I think he permanently has to have a producing credit on all the Spider-Man movies.
Oh wow.
There's a recent conversation with Bugman.
Yeah.
Aviarad is good.
And then the final choice of the 1996 made for Fox movie Generation X.
I know what I want to talk about.
Based on the Marvel comics.
Matt Fruer is in the I don't even remember what character he plays but he's like the star of it.
Yeah.
Fox in the late mid late 90s made a bunch of like event made for TV movies.
There was a Nick Fury.
David Hasshoff one.
They also did a Doctor Who one.
Which I.
American Doctor Who.
Interesting.
So yeah.
So that there we have it.
So I will put this.
I would like to add a sixth choice.
I don't know if you can do that on.
We made Jason take new genetics for a month and we check in and see how he's doing at the end of the.
That's the episode for your birthday.
Well thank God only as five.
I'll pay for the new genetics.
I think they have more than five.
I think you can keep going.
No choice.
Yeah.
Let's get you on the monthly.
That all sounds good.
Those none of that.
That all of those sound like a lot of fun.
So thank you for all those options.
I'm excited to hear where we go.
I'm so curious to see what wins.
Yeah.
Well nice of you to bring the listeners in on it and listeners I just I hope that you're not too excited to vote.