Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain fake stories where Amelia Earhart is an asshole,
real stories about mule piss, and overworked PAs who must abduct children and clean toilets.
Your quest is to not lose your phone so you can hear guest Django Gold and the Good Boys
talk Legends of the Hidden Temple.
On Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to the Temple of Unnecessary Knowledge, I'm Scott, your guide.
The Temple is filled with many dry facts about things from our childhoods that don't matter,
and one of today's themes teams will get to say more of those facts than anyone else.
Will it be the Silver Sheridans?
Maybe.
It could be.
This is a temple that's a lot less nerve wracking than the television show temple.
Than the temple that we will be talking about within this temple.
Yes, alright, so mild conference in the Silver Sheridans, or will it be the Magenta Mikes?
Oh I think it will be, yeah, this is my excitement level, like in my mind I'm doing an excitement thing,
like what if I was a kid and being a Nickelodeon?
Yeah, you've got like an enthusiasm ceiling, that's a lot of kids I think in any public
forum, you can just sense, you can see that line that they can't quite make it over, much
like some of the obstacles we'll discuss from the show.
Yeah, yeah.
Or will it be a special competitor visiting us from the East Coast, you may have seen
him on the Late Show with Stephen Colbert, he's got a special out called Bag of Tricks
on his YouTube channel, Django Industries, representing the gold golds, it's Django Gold.
Yeah, what a perfect name, I could have gone with that in a million years.
I had another one and then I thought, wait a second.
I think you were saying.
There's a color, I was like proudly staring at another one.
No, no, why reinvent the wheel?
The color is staring right back at me.
Did you have gold gold first and work backwards?
No, I was saying, I had an entire other one and then another color, it was just the Jade
Jankos.
Oh, okay.
I like how that sounds, that's the thing.
J with a D, that's not bad.
Yeah, yeah, and you add a D to it.
That's pretty good, I think you can take that one too.
These are both good names.
You should be able to pick your own name.
Choose your own, only you can choose.
We're talking about legends of the Hidden Temple, the seminal Nickelodeon game show
from, that ran from 93 to 95, filmed at Universal Studios Florida, Nickelodeon Studios.
Fabulous Universal Studios Florida.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The tags on every show just haunted our dreams.
I made like, I must make it to this movie.
I mean, they really were just like giving you like this golden apple in the horizon.
Imagine you'll be there where the water runs like, or the slime runs like water, the fountains
and all that stuff.
Just dip a cup in, we don't even charge you.
You would never, yeah.
The real life Willy Wonka Chocolate Factory of some, like this is a place that only your
dreams could be concocted in.
Did any of you guys ever make it out?
I didn't.
No.
I took the tour and I watched the fake, there was a fake game show that they would do.
To make it, to give you that flavor.
They call it like the lab.
Just like this generic game show.
It was like, it's kiddie pool.
Theme park competition.
Pretty much.
And they would, I don't think they could ever do this now, but it's like there were two
sets of bleachers and one were the parents and one were the kids.
And I was like just terrified.
I was not going to find my parents.
Oh man, yeah.
Even though that is their main job, reuniting families afterwards.
Kids get lost in these theme parks all the time.
I got lost as a kid like at least 10 times.
Me and my sister, we would just get separated so easily.
Our parents weren't as worried about it as they would be now for example.
But yeah, I empathize for sure.
Although more easily solved now you would think.
Yes, that's true.
That's true.
But did any of those lead to like you had to find adults?
You had to, like an announcement had to be made?
Oh yeah.
We were regular visitors at the White Emergency Tent with the PA.
100%.
What would always happen was we'd be at a theme park with our dad for example and he'd
be like, all right, I'm going to go to the bathroom now.
You guys wait here for one and a half minutes and like 20 seconds in like, dad's dead.
We got to start moving.
And so we'd move off and that would be that.
This chaos would ensue.
But like this would just happen 100% of the time anytime we'd go anywhere.
We were just totally irresponsible.
Did I ever tell the story about, I think I didn't say it when we talked about the Santa
Cruz Beach Boardwalk, but stop me if I did.
Where I got lost, I just wandered off at the Santa Cruz Beach Boardwalk when I was a kid.
Not now as an adult.
No, no, no.
I was just there but I did not get lost.
My child had eyes on me.
It's my main memory from being up there that I just wandered off.
I was just like dumb and thought I could leave.
And meanwhile, my mom was getting some business from like a kind of like a card tricks guy
on the pier.
A three card Monte table?
Maybe.
Oh yes, a three card Monte table.
Yes, before it got converted into a weed table.
And then my mom looked around and I was gone.
And she made the leap that this is a distraction that is being used to kidnap me.
Like when she put it together, she spit out something that was, I don't know the exact
phrasing, but it was something, it was just this like, because it's her movie moment.
It was maybe the chance to like, I swear to God if you have my little boy, I will move
heaven and earth to get him back.
She did like a Liam Neeson taken speech.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
I don't know that she's specifically referred to a special set of skills because I don't
know if she has one, but she might've said like, but I will, you know how you get super
power strength if you, you know, you can lift a car up in an emergency, said, Hey, that's
what's going to happen to me.
And I'll throw you into the ocean unless you have information to give me.
Every parent has their child saving fantasy.
Yeah.
The same way that every guy has their like what I would do in a fight type fantasy.
Every mom and dad is like, I know what I will, you know.
Although, well you say that, but like, do you?
I think I'm petrified of this situation coming up.
Yeah.
You know, I have there's been a couple of times where I've had the thought that like
it's not too detailed, but that I would kill to save my child.
So I do.
You start to like your you have a little fantasy about I don't know, like
it's usually like a little more fantastical in my version where like an ogre bursts into
the house.
Fighting a troll.
Yeah, it's more fun at least in my version, but I still am like imagining killing something
to protect my child.
I feel that.
But I think my mom had a much more realistic version of this in her mind
growing up with things from our world and not like you're in your version.
Like you stomp a face in and yellow goo comes out.
Yeah, yeah.
That yellow bastard is in the city.
It's not you fighting some crystal meth addict.
Just trying to pawn your child.
And my mom, my mom was probably like whatever the last dateline she watched, whoever
that was on that was probably who she was imagining killing to protect me.
Sure, sure.
But I have.
Yeah, that's that has entered my mind.
I have specific memories of in the mid later 90s.
My family invested in a set of I don't know if this ever come up.
Maybe it has.
But a thing that caught on right before cell phones was, OK, we have
walkie talkies.
Oh, you had little walkie talkies.
Oh, my God.
And you would have like a two to eight channels.
And it's like, OK, we're going to be on channel number six or seven.
And very quickly we learned how many radio channels are occupied by emergency
services, beach patrol, Disney security.
I turned it on once and got like this is a private channel reserved for Disney
security.
Please vacate this channel.
We told you to leave.
Yeah, that seems pretty hackable.
They really should have some sort of secure channel for that.
Yeah.
So some kid with a radio.
Disney company doesn't have any money or anything.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
I feel like we had those two, but I can't.
I'm going to ask some questions when I get I'll ask my parents.
They occasionally worked.
Yeah.
But the other thing is, oh, what a nursemaid.
Yeah, exactly.
We lost a few kids, but the more or less we lost a few kids.
The other thing is other families would buy them and we would start hearing other
people on the show.
It's like on a baby monitor.
You can pick up radio or you pick up the neighbors, you know.
And did you sense like any particular peril or like, you know, like, did you feel
like you saw too deep through the window of a broken home or something?
No, it's just kids cursing at us.
You didn't develop a relationship with like a trucker or anything like.
No, no.
You seem like you've been a CB radio kid.
I you know, it never came up.
Huh?
All right.
Well, a little past the track.
Never too late to start.
Yeah, I'll get you one.
Anyway, I just felt bad in pencils.
Situation that the guy who was running a scam on my mom was in that moment he had to
go, no, no, no, I'm not scamming.
I mean, I am.
I am.
But it's not a kidnapping.
It is a much lighter monetary scam.
It is like a $15 scam.
Yes.
Not what's the I don't know.
What's the cost of a child?
What's a child going for?
These days?
Yeah.
50K.
Is that then?
Now, is it where this is 1994?
Right before?
Yeah.
Would you pay for me in 1994?
That's pretty good.
All right.
And with inflation.
That's right.
We're the one who say Tannic movie studios and ask like, what do you guys
sell?
What do you sell kids around here?
Legend of the Hidden Temple.
And you brought this to us, Jane.
What was calling out to you about this of all strange themed entertainment?
It was a show that I really loved watching as a kid.
And it was also a show that I loved watching as like a stoned college student, because
it was always on like the like whatever the throwback channel is.
And what really appealed to me about it is that it is so hard.
They make these games so impossible for like an 11 year old who's developing their
brand eye coordination, who doesn't quite get logic and like object permanence and all
this stuff.
They're not quite, you know, their brains aren't at the adult level and
they make this game impossible, like so difficult.
I sent you that doc with all those like trivia facts and it said like, what, the temple
run completion rate is like 26 percent.
That's crazy low for a kids TV show.
Right.
Every one of every four episodes.
Yeah.
That's that's pretty nice.
Three and four and with failure, which is it just feels like crazy to me.
Am I wrong?
Like, no, no, no.
You would be frustrated.
The only more frustrating game which we've talked about is Nick Arcade.
Yes.
Which was like kids would never win the final round.
And I remember just driving me so nuts.
Well, that was also like kind of like wonky or controls of our talk.
Yeah.
This is just like is all physicality.
It's made impossible.
Frustrating to.
Yeah.
I just was frustrated by it, too, because you wanted kids to win.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
You don't want this kid to be humiliated and like, you know, sad in front of a
national audience.
They get no trip to space camp.
They get no keyboard or whatever the hell, you know.
And you get that you see the list of what they could have and then you watch them
in three minutes later.
Usually watch them be denied.
It's wild, man.
It's a show, I guess.
It helps you measure your expectations.
Maybe as a kid.
You know, we were saying we all dreamed of going to Nickelodeon studios as
children and then we're watching people get to.
But yet they get a dream, but also much of the dream is crushed.
Yeah.
So just based on the difficulty of it, that's why I think it's so enthralling
because you're watching someone like attempt what seems like the impossible.
So when they do get it, it's like amazing.
It's like genuinely stirring.
I was watching these clips on YouTube and I was like at
the edge of my seat watching these kids from like 25 years ago or whatever doing
this.
I was like, oh, go, go.
No, the monkey.
No, he's got to twist the monkey.
Like I was just like so into it.
That's why I think it's so good about the show.
It really just kind of draws you in just based on how hard it is.
I saw a snippet of an interview with Kirk Fox, Kirk Fox, excuse me.
That was the host, right?
Yeah, that was his name.
It was an interview and he was just like shaking his head at the end of the interview.
And he's like, you know, three year basically three years break down to like three
seasons, 93, 94, 95.
He's like, like eight teams a year.
When learning how this show was made was a true I think I had heard it
in passing before, but really just taking a second to figure out how they did it.
And like the 12 to 14 hour days and like brutally block shots like the money.
Like it all said, it does when you learn anything, it spoils the illusion of like
this temple is up there for like a year's time and they're giving kids the ultimate
fantasy of like, no, this is just this temple was up and running for two weeks
and then shut down and we're we're on to something else like the deadwood set.
I had a question, though, about that when you're talking about the you're watching
it stoned in college.
Yeah.
For me, if I was stoned, then the frustration and the futility of it,
I feel like would weigh very heavily on me.
Well, it does.
Watch it will not succeed and like be trapped in a box like the paranoia.
It really is like a bad dream where you're like digging through some hole.
You can't like the doors on opening, the doors on opening and like you're being
attacked and grabbed by a temple guard.
Like it's just like it really is like some horror show.
I could see myself getting paranoid and sad about for me, mostly just just kind of
like it's good, clean, fun, you know, punctuated by just watching sad children.
Which in at least a lot of success along the way, it's like devised to, you know,
like it weeds out the losers.
It sure does.
They all start with so many.
Yes.
Kids.
Thirty two teams won in the history of the whole thing.
That's out of one hundred and twenty episodes.
You multiply that each team has two kids.
That's sixty four out of one thousand four hundred and forty.
That like and that's because it starts with what it's it's
six or eight teams doing that opening, like water traversing.
Yeah.
Always always a situation.
So you and that that weeds a ton out.
Yeah, that's the real eugenics.
It's like absolutely like, all right, we don't need any purple ones.
Those are like they're like the sperm that don't pretty much really.
That's not we're not even at.
In a way, Legend of the Hidden Temple is a metaphor for sexual intercourse.
Oh, and that the I wonder if that reflects like the no, no, probably being a sperm is more
futile, but it's all but it's similar.
So you do the temple to fertilize an egg.
Olmec stands in for God,
judging you for your sin or your righteous act of procreation.
Olmec is God and the temple is a womb.
Simultaneous simultaneous metaphors.
It's like a Ulysses or something.
It's like a lot of shit's happening.
Really, every text is in there.
So you might as well just use this as it's our creation myth.
It's actually Legend of the Hidden Temple.
That was one of the episode titles, The Lost Chapter of James
Joyce's Ulysses.
You'd say I defined it.
I feel like the show Flora's Lava is the only thing I've seen
that feels like as ambitious as this.
I've never actually watched any.
I know that I know that all older kids at parks that I go to are playing.
Really?
Lava and the yeah, no, that that's like I didn't know kids like that.
It makes sense.
But Flora's Lava is a recent show, right?
Yes.
I'm just saying I can't think of another like theme, like highly themed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Pain in the ass to set up show.
Well, like most extreme.
What is that?
Is that what it's called?
What's M.
X.
C.?
Most extreme elimination.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Like American Ninja Warrior stuff.
That's crazy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But it's all American Gladiators, kind of is too, in a sense.
Yeah, but also all kind of like it's like that.
Some of them are like pylons and just like industrial equipment.
Right here to like have a whole little little world that you enter.
But those aren't his theme.
You know, I'm going back.
Those are that theme.
They're just giant and massive in scale and crazy to set up.
But like Flora's Lava is like cool.
They do set up.
It looks cool, I think.
Yeah.
And the episodes I've seen early days of pandemic lockdown.
Just sitting inside watching Flora's Lava.
Yeah, I was like, I don't know if this is helping or hurting,
but I think it's making me feel more insane.
Not not playing it, though, you're saying you weren't up on your couch.
No, I was not worried about walking around my home.
I was not worried about the dangers of that.
Solo isolated Flora's Lava by yourself.
Yeah, it's all we could do.
Hopping back and forth from your refrigerator to your.
Somehow switching to Tiger King was healthier.
American Gladiators and Indiana Jones or Young Indiana Jones,
I saw as a reference point a lot.
Let me say someone whose first job in L.
A.
was working on the American Gladiators remake, also a pain in the ass to shoot.
Sure.
You know, you I don't think you've ever said this on the show or to us.
Well, I bring it up now because there's a documentary about America.
There's two.
Oh, wow.
Competing ducks.
They are competing.
My my friend John, who was my college roommate, John Katz,
technically my boss on the show is interviewed in the ESPN plus one.
So you can get a real peek behind the scenes.
This feels like it always feels to me like not if not your superhero.
Is it your super villain origin story?
I was not a good time.
It's definitely surreal of like, ah, another writer's strike is happening.
You know, mm hmm.
They didn't try to get you to be a P.
A.
on the documentaries just to like, you know, no, no, I haven't been.
Rhymes.
I haven't been pulled back in.
You know, yeah.
Once you once you leave the gladiator lifestyle, it's always calling you back.
Right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Dreams of firing Nerf balls at you from a cannon.
I wake up screaming at night thinking I'm still in the Sony soundstage.
Like people would imagine themselves being in Saigon.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's the P.
A.
's main duty was testing the cannons and the balls.
Yeah.
Run, run.
Faster, boy.
What's also the legal liability for these shows?
You wonder when you have children like doing kind of like, yeah,
semi dangerous stunts like, all right, so we're going to have a kid
try to scale a 20 foot pole while you know,
Temple Guard throws things at him.
It'll be fine.
All those parents are in the audience.
Right.
I don't know.
And I can't tell if this was a particularly dangerous.
I think anything where you have like a sliding thing that you have to climb up,
you can easily.
Yeah.
And anytime there's like human man jumping out at a child in a tight space,
like a kid's going to fall and hit the wall.
It's going to like that is a crazy element.
That was always like the only scary part of the show.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
A man is enveloping that child in his arms
and going to take him back into his little den.
Yeah.
I couldn't have done it.
Of course.
I would have like panicked, I think.
Yeah.
You know, if you know it's coming because they come out every which way
in these in these like secret doors like, you know, yeah, it's traumatic.
Yeah, I couldn't.
I don't think I could.
I wanted to do it and I probably would have agreed to do it,
but I probably would have just frozen and then the episode would not have aired.
It's a miracle that any of these kids got through that temple in one piece.
Yeah.
Yeah, it really is.
Even without that, even if you remove that component and I'd be less
afraid of kind of the the magical elements and the like swinging on the pit
or getting lost in the, you know, in the whatever the packing peanuts down there,
then just like a ladder, the hidden stairs.
Yeah, those I feel like are the biggest that you're you're nervous
and people are yelling.
Yeah.
Is appointed like imagine how much anxiety you get now
when you're trying to do some complicated task and people are watching
and you don't have like a hundred people screaming at you
and knowing all your school friends are watching on TV.
Yeah, it's a lot.
Oh, yes.
And if you mess up, you will be made.
Everyone will.
When you mess up, you'll have kids on the playground like, hey, dumbass,
you got you got to go to the top door.
Hello.
It's obvious from a third party perspective.
You try to put the monkey's idol head in where its ass should go.
Yeah.
Doing you fucking idiot.
That is apparently one of the most troublesome elements.
Like, oh, that's what I mean.
Not the monkey.
Yeah, the kids never could do the monkeys.
There is a there's a YouTube channel called Peeled Eyes
that has some compilation videos and they're like, here's the best temple runs
and here's the worst temple runs and best or worst.
Everyone's having trouble with that monkey.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I feel like they made it too big and they made the podium for it too tall.
So the kids are constantly reaching up past their eyeline.
Yeah, it's just really you got to have had a growth spurt.
The deck is just totally stacked against all these poor little kids.
This is yeah, that is the because it definitely became a real thing.
The difficulty of the of the silver monkey.
And I've seen that defense now that like they have to get pieces off of tall shelves
and that when they're doing so, first of all, that it probably just tumbles
out of their hands.
Yeah.
And that's where they're starting.
And that which then like obfuscates, it's like in shadow.
Which piece is this?
It's not iconic to them.
They probably especially the first ones.
Yeah, the first one.
No point in reference.
They're all taped in like three days.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we know we all are thinking we could do this easily because we have it.
And we watch this all the time.
But if you were the first astronauts into the capsule, you definitely don't know.
But you like, yeah, yeah.
If you if you don't if you can't make out the basic shape of it
and then you have to stack it in the right way, it is I think like some forgiveness
needs to be shown to these.
Yeah.
They should have gotten three tokens to save them from the temple guards.
That's what I say.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Do you think it was maybe it was kept low
because there were not a lot of temple guards?
I feel like there were a lot of temple guards.
I remember seeing many episodes in which both kids would get blanked out by temple guards.
It feels like a higher probability than like a whammy.
Yeah, definitely more traumatic.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, you didn't feel the drama of when like a whammy walks out
and then like four others and they're doing a conga line.
There should be more game shows, though, where a guy just pops out
and drags a contestant away.
Like a real fortune, for example.
Yeah, like you get like a consonant wrong and then you just get dragged into a dark room.
Yeah.
I mean, it's really only the and I don't know if you'd call this a game show
besides this element, but it's really only showtime at the Apollo.
Oh, with the Sandman.
Yeah, it's the only other.
But he doesn't physically grab you.
That's the difference, I think.
Oh, yeah, true.
Yeah.
If Sandman was just enveloping you with his huge feathered arms,
that would change the vibe.
Yeah, true.
Or if his if his famous broom
in which which he whisks the contestants away.
Well, if he's if that is much, much bigger and you actually get caught
and the bristles sure ground up a little bit.
Yeah.
Well, I you know, we talked about on the show that we were all scared
by temple guards before.
But I think I neglected to think about the thing that was most scary,
which is the room with trees that you have to reach into.
And one of those trees could be possessed by the spirit of a temple guard.
Yeah.
Fucking kidding me.
And the tree grabbing you, it seems 10 times worse.
Yeah.
And there's this moment of tension before the kid reaches in.
Where it's like, is this tree going to be OK?
And they put their hand like, ah, you know, it's like a really, really traumatizing.
This is we did an entire episode about scary trees
that scare me specifically.
And I don't think this even came up.
Yeah, it didn't.
Oh, wow.
I actually maybe this was the fuel.
Suppressed memory.
Yeah.
So this is really separate.
There was I watched a few episodes and it wasn't until a latter day
one where the presence of the trees made themselves known.
And I just like, oh, you're kidding.
I don't think the kids made it there.
Thank God.
And like they got eliminated before.
I'm just picturing these temple guards like coming like, you know,
after the taping with a kid in the family going back to the hotel room.
Temple guards jumps out of the adjacent hotel room and grabs the kid
and brings them out that extra door that hotel room.
Yeah.
The balcony ways in bed after the after the night.
Temple guard comes out from under the bed and drags him down to hell.
Mini fridge.
Yeah.
It's a false mini fridge.
There's room for a guy in there.
I'm being taken by a non-union actor.
This is a temple guard, by the way, the most non-union.
Well, I was actually thinking about this.
I was wondering if they might be like stagehands or something,
because there's no way there's like a full time temple guard position.
I have a little insight into this.
I read an interview.
There was an AV club interview with is it Scott Stone?
I think one of the creators and he a recurring segment,
if a recurring theme rather, if you can believe it, is the cheapness of the show.
And one detail, it wasn't even something he was like,
it was just in the middle of something he was saying,
that the whole show was really cheap.
Everybody in the show had a million jobs.
My cousin Jed was a was the writer, applying one single writer.
And he was also one of the temple guards and also in half of the legends
themselves dressed up in costumes.
So there was no money.
So which was well, again, we should maybe like step through an episode or something.
That might be a good way to do it.
But like we've neglected that.
There's this minor educational element of every episode, which is like
it teaches you about Christopher Columbus's spear or whatever like that.
Yes.
Yeah.
Like they are the magic spinning top of Ponce de Leon.
Where you kind of start to suspect like, wait a minute.
I don't think every historical figure had an item as an object has a totem.
Yeah.
Find Harriet Tubman's walking stick.
It was on that.
I'm like, oh, I don't know about that.
Maybe possibly a lot of very metaphorical.
Objects.
Yeah.
Not necessarily historically accurate.
If you had to, that just does just make me think like there are objects
associated like with Trump, for example.
Oh, yeah.
But if you are right, it's it's a hundred years from now.
And Trump only gets one object.
What's the I know what it is.
What is the Diet Coke button?
Oh, very good.
The button you would hit to get a new diet.
That's pretty good.
I was going to say the hat.
But the whole way.
Sure.
The hat.
Yeah.
Donald Trump's hutch.
More iconic, I suppose.
Yeah.
But in my heart, it's the Diet Coke.
No, I think that's a good one.
It's pretty good.
I mean, I flashed it could have been the orb.
I remember when he told me it was fine.
The orb is good.
Let's let's just like step through how this worked a little bit.
And I think some like some anecdotes will spill out along the way.
But like basic premise is kids are doing feats of strength and little
getting feats of knowledge or at least like memorization
that eventually lead them to a trip through Olmec's temple,
an ancient stone head god who co-hosts and narrates the show as well.
It all culminates in a big run through the temple where you must.
You learn early in the show about one of these magical,
definitely real historical objects.
And then you get the chance to go, I mean, like pillage the temple.
Oh, yeah.
It is like a point robbing.
I didn't consider this.
Essentially
to try to then colonial.
Yeah, the guards are protecting their shit.
That's true.
Yeah.
The guards are the good guys.
The children are the bad guys.
Right.
You really should be rooting for them.
I don't know.
And like, oh, I don't discount that the children are the bad guys.
That's definitely true.
But they are also like pawns in a way.
They're kind of like to go to get into another tomb,
the or the you know, the Cave of Wonders in Aladdin.
Yes.
But it's really it's Jafar using the kid Aladdin.
I guess who's Jafar in this?
Kirk Fogg.
Yeah.
The malevolent Kirk Fogg.
Puppet Master working for the East India Trading Company,
sending these kids to pillage, you know, beloved ruins.
Well, they're going to think it's fun to them.
It's a fun little child.
But within we get all the but we they trade in these like
artifacts worth millions of dollars.
And we convince them, you know, they just want like bikes and
pocket calculators and that will about, you know, that'll satisfy them.
And then we keep the profits.
It's kind of like the Chipmunks movie from the 80s.
Oh, that's right.
That's one of those.
Yeah.
They're like smuggling.
They're having the chipmunks and chipmunks smuggle like diamonds and cash
for the bad guys.
And they don't realize what pawns they are.
Right.
Uh huh.
Isn't this all of it?
Isn't this like the writers, everybody?
Aren't we all just serving the profit of some billionaire masters?
That's correct.
The Archfiend, Kirk Fogg.
Yeah.
He's a it all goes to Kirk.
Yeah, he ultimately he's like the Soros figure.
He just running town.
Your conspiracy theory.
Yeah.
Kirk Fogg has his hands a lot in a lot of pies.
He's been suspiciously present in a lot of calamities throughout the world.
Yeah.
You know, there's a way to go massacre.
If you look at the back of the video in 2019 of Kirk Fogg saying
there's going to be a pandemic in 2020.
You know, Kirk Fogg lab leak theory.
Yeah.
It all goes back to Kirk Fogg.
He took the monkey.
He took the silver monkey and used it to smash the sealed windows at the lab.
Oh, yeah.
He cracked it.
Makes perfect sense.
All adds up around the globe.
And he does a little repelling repels in.
Yes.
God, you're right.
He does.
I forgot.
Well, you know, he didn't at the beginning because I watched an early one
and he just he's introduced and then he just he just shows up calmly,
walks down the stairs.
So then what a shock it was to leap forward and he swings in on a rope
and the camera kind of like turns around him perfectly.
A hell of an inch.
I mean, like this guy must have been feeling himself.
There's a slight budget increase.
Season two and three went to carabiners and rope.
And they're like, well, we got Kirk doing this exciting entrance.
So we can't we can't get the kids top pizza with toppings on it
while they sit in the break room.
Yeah, that's good.
It's all she it's all she's made.
Kirk's vlog is coming on jetpack.
And these kids are like receiving like $15 of Hasbro merchandise.
Hey, he's the one who's got to pump them up.
But they got to do it.
That's true.
Olmec positive feelings about Olmec growing up.
We do we all like the wish we could have seen him be operated in person.
I loved Olmec.
Olmec was a really weird discovery that D Baker, the voice of Olmec.
I mean, it has a huge filmography like TV and film.
Voice actor extraordinaire.
The oddest one was discovering that he is Klaus the fish on American Dad.
Oh, well, I didn't know that.
Yeah.
The world of voice acting is relatively small.
It's only like 100 people in total.
Yeah, it is true.
Yeah.
It's always the same.
Nice and nice and fat off these roles.
If you get in there, you're in there for good, which I think he did launch his.
I think he was a purely Orlando actor who like this kicked off the whole thing for him.
And he's one of the primary guys for that.
He was doing Orlando productions of King Lear and so forth like that.
I think I think that's genuinely true.
I do think that's the thing.
And also Epcot thought he was in the something called the Anacomical players in a.
There was like an area in Disney World themed after the human body.
Basically, I don't know one second of what I like.
I have the like some ghostly remnant in my brain, the phrase Anacomical players,
but I could not tell you what that comprised.
It seems like a tough thing for improv to, you know, you want like any topic in the world
to be on the table for you.
You ask the audience for a word and you could take it anywhere.
So to limit it to to take 99.
9 percent of topics off the table for your improv.
I got stomach again.
Nice.
We got bladder.
Yeah.
Somebody said penis.
I got to pretend we didn't hear it.
Yeah.
Would you ram bunctious children name any body part you can think of?
Yeah, that doesn't sound like it's going to go wrong.
That had to be in the wonders of life pavilion.
I'm assuming.
Yes, that was at least it was air conditioned, you know.
That's the improv outside in the Orlando.
That sounds like you're dressed like a spleen.
Yeah.
Again, you're a kid and you imagine that this is the infinite budget
and that the people doing it have made it and are set for life.
And just the, you know, the glamour in which the show is made to then discover
that, first of all, that Olmec is I think I was picturing like it's the ninja.
It must be the ninja turtle technology.
And by that, I mean, oh, yeah, a little puppet that is like attached
via airwaves to a suit and that like that's how it's syncing up.
Right.
The same radio waves that Jason used with his old with the shitty
with the crappy walkie talkie.
Yeah, yeah.
Shopping network walkie talkie.
And as long as like legends of the hidden temple is on,
that's committed on Channel seven.
Nobody else.
Nothing else.
Yeah.
Make sure no kids in this park use Channel seven.
That's the ambulance driver nurse line for like the kid who eats it
and on the swing in the temple.
So then you suddenly hear a nurse's voice coming out of a line
and nurses voices coming out of Olmec.
We lost another one.
Sorry, I was asleep.
I've been here for 10 hours.
But instead, no, this was the actor.
D Baker is like down at the bottom of Olmec.
He's got a two by four attached to the bottom lip, which is the only part.
He's doing it himself.
Yeah.
So he's just like moving a piece of wood for it.
He has his foot on two by four, moving the jaw or his hand.
I think I think it's hand controlled.
Maybe I can't.
Well, what I can't picture is if he's like, is he does he get a chair
or is he curled into a ball so as to be able to give him a chair?
He negotiated in season two.
Yeah.
And they gave him a child's chair.
Right.
Or he does this.
That's the budget increase.
Man, I wonder where that head is right now.
I yeah, I'm not sure what I want to give to have that in my possession.
Yeah, really.
Is there is there like a Nickelodeon vault?
Like because there's I there's like a dub.
If you're a wrestling fan, there's like in Stamford, Connecticut,
there's a W.
E.
W.
vault that has like the famous cages from certain matches.
And it has costumes.
Yeah.
A vault.
They have like a big warehouse type thing that has all this stuff
from the history of the company of the of the evil company.
And even the bad stuff.
Do they need to start a fire in there?
They probably should in certain parts of it.
But like Little Corners.
Yeah, I wonder if Nickelodeon history.
I wonder if there's got it's got to be somewhere.
There might be an Orlando based, you know, repository warehouse.
Yeah, I was like, what's his name?
The the show was pizza guy has a big warehouse full of shit.
I can never.
Oh, yeah.
Aaron Aaron.
Yes.
Uh huh.
So like there's got to be a bunch of weird warehouses in Orlando,
is what I'm saying.
Possibly.
Or it was all or like they assumed nobody would.
It's not like people are going to get fixated on this for decades and decades.
Potentially spend.
You have four adult men
this passionately disgusted discussing the
mechanisms of how a child's game show head work.
Yeah.
Forget Olmec.
I'll I'll settle for the two by four.
I want to get to D Baker's to buy.
So that could be that could be one of the artifacts in like the reboot.
D Baker's to buy for
the extra splintery to buy for the friendly.
D Baker.
But yeah, so that's that's pretty lo fi.
And then they start the basically they set it up.
Let's test it.
It looked bad.
It wasn't enough.
And they realized they needed one more element.
And they thought, what if we made the eyes glow?
Maybe that will step it up somehow.
But again, you know, he's already D Baker's already moving wood back and forth.
I don't think he can like flick another thing.
He's not a puppeteer.
So right.
One man banned things.
So that's like a bellows and like symbols on his knees.
Between his knees.
Yeah.
Can we attach something to his blinks?
Can we control?
Now, Olmec, how would you like to favor us with a song?
And you know, no, quite plainly, Morgan.
Not today, please.
Yeah.
So they're scouring for what's the solution there.
And they go to a radio shack that has a disco ball
that is voice activated.
And they just like they dig the mechanism out of that, put it in the eyes,
just like solder it them.
And again, this is the creators of the show.
Yeah.
Just like Jerry rigging this up to the end.
That ended up being enough and this works well enough.
That's American community right there.
Yeah.
We're all, you know, you know, in in in strike era,
we're all talking about low staffs and you're like this thing.
I think there were I think there were four forget writing staff.
There were four people behind the scenes of this show in general.
Yeah.
No one worked on this.
The fewest amount like, OK, can the temple guard, can we give the temple guards,
can we space out the runs enough that the temple guards can also go
get the pizzas and come back?
It's yeah, this is crazy, though, because like, I guess Guts is probably
technically a more dangerous show for kids because you got kids on bungees
jumping off five, ten feet like platforms.
But still, it feels like all these shows are like so understaffed.
I am surprised there was not more kid injuries.
And this is also in the air before like crazy private equity optimization.
So it's kind of surprising they weren't willing to show a little more money
on a show like, you know, cost very little to make.
And they turn them out.
I'm just amazed that they were so cheap on this.
I think Florida is not the most in the 90s,
maybe not the most safety focused.
Sure.
Occupational states are really not the friendliest to a lot of the unions
ever in general.
Like Florida was dangerous.
The Temple Guard Union was broken up immediately by Pinkerton's, the TGA
support the TGA was wild and crazy kids.
Orlando as well.
What was I think that was all over?
I think I was like on a farm somewhere.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Really nondescript locations.
Was that like in Ventura or something?
Yeah, I think it was around here sometimes.
They found the raging waters.
I feel like I recognize a park sometimes.
Right.
And yet wonder why.
Why aren't they asking me the coolest kid in the San Fernando Valley?
I'm the best kid here.
Why didn't they?
Are my parents not getting the word out about me enough?
The Valley's top kid that was
three years running.
That was the thing about legend.
The hidden temple.
A lot of the kids.
Were from the Orlando area and it was like ages 11 through 14.
But then it would take so long to get around the chute.
Sometimes those kids were like 15 doing that show.
You know, some kids with a little gross little mustache.
Just just dominating Robin Hood's maze or whatever.
So now this one kid is really tall, but isn't very coordinated.
He's trying hard.
Got to impress his girlfriend.
It's going to impress his kids.
Yeah, his girlfriend drove him here.
She is 16 and has a car.
This was a misperception I also had about these shows a lot that the
could you guys tell this at the time that like that the kids never seem like they
know each other or have any chemistry?
Yeah, I think they get randomly paired up.
I think so.
Yeah.
Because the connection is they aren't looking each other in the eye,
especially if it's boy, girl, their their nerves.
They just even be I'm next to a girl on television.
You feel that's tougher than the temple.
There's a lot of missed high fives, I feel like.
Yeah.
You don't sense that the camaraderie.
That doesn't help the success rate either.
Well, you're just paired up some random feels like your childhood buddy.
I bet you'd do better at it.
I think so.
Yeah.
There'd be some trust there, I think.
But instead, yeah, you could tell that it's
they probably had not met before that day.
And yet this is all right.
This is some mental gymnastics I did when I was a kid.
It was all right.
The prize, the big prize at the end is probably a trip that we know.
There was space camp.
There would be space camp.
But that's like a group, right?
Sometimes it's like in one that I watched, it's like you're going to the holiday
in in Mexico City.
And I feel like I would think,
but it doesn't seem like these people know each other very well.
Now they have to take a trip together.
That's amazing.
I wonder if they sent them together, if they gave them.
Basically, we've been told about the budget.
Imagine they probably had both families, one hotel room.
Possibly.
Yes.
Yeah, maybe just just for.
It's a suite.
Have a suite size.
You can rock, paper, scissor for couch.
There's a big sectional.
Can sleep on the long part of it.
Yeah.
Nice bonding, actually, for a family to sleep in one triangle together.
One year.
You guys love adventure.
Come on.
Yeah, this is part of the adventure.
The adventure continues using using the dinner voucher for Denny's
with some random family.
Yes, you do all have to split this.
Oh, you brought other kids.
Sorry.
That was the winning.
Meant to be a six way split.
That trip costs under four hundred dollars, right?
That they're giving people.
Yeah.
After you.
Well, I mean, the holiday in felt kind of.
Yeah, unless it's a night.
Sometimes you get a nicer holiday in.
Sure.
Sometimes.
There's a lot of variance in that particular brand.
Yeah.
Also, back in the 90s, we didn't maybe I didn't as a child.
I feel like there was still like this illusion that hotels were like
of that nature, were like kind of like fancy in a way.
Yeah.
Oh, the best Western.
And that was as an adult, you know, it's like, you know, you know, it's a flea bag.
But back then you might you might be.
Oh, has a swimming pool.
It's a nice hotel, you know.
Uh huh.
Right.
It's the right photo.
And yeah, when you when you don't know any better, we're doing it
just that it is a hotel.
Yeah.
It's not my house.
Take me there.
I learned this number seven or eight years ago or so.
I missed a flight at L.
X.
A.
And they're like, well, give you a voucher for really cheap hotel room.
Do you want to go to this Hyatt
that costs like 40 more dollars?
Or do you want to go to Armada in?
And I didn't I was like, oh, the money.
Ramada's are usually nice, right?
No.
Immediately placed in a room next to a conference room
that was having the loudest revival church service you've ever seen.
And had to go back down and go like, hey, can you
can we have another room?
There's a church revival still going there.
What time was that still going on?
It was like nine thirty at night.
Really?
Wow.
Yeah.
And it was just like you should have gone in there, though.
I I don't know why I didn't just take a lift back to Los Angeles.
I don't know why you didn't just get born again.
Yeah, that could have been your lucky break.
You'd be in heaven right now.
Yeah.
And if and if everywhere is perfect, then it doesn't matter
how bad the hotel room is.
You were the El Segundo.
God's what?
What what I think, yeah, because I would always
you would sense the lack of chemistry, but like Double Dare was families.
So you would end up rooting for just whatever family you thought you liked better.
But they did like a smart medieval times type thing here with branding each team.
So it's more like you were rooting for your sports team every episode
versus you cared at all about the kids themselves.
That's a good point.
And really, I mean, maybe are you like
two questions and anyone answer, did you have favorites?
And was the favorite more based on the color or the animal color?
Color.
I'd say so.
It's the it's the more prominent.
Yeah, the animals are a little harder to make out.
They're a little abstract.
Right.
There's some real cocoa pellies.
Yeah, just six cocoa.
Yeah, the red cocoa, the blue cocoa belly.
His drawings all made by Kirk Fogg's brother.
He's an artist in New Mexico.
Yeah.
Do you feel that way, though?
Did you feel like and did you have a favorite?
I can't remember.
I would assume based on my values as a kid is probably the silver snakes,
as was every boy's I imagine.
But who knows?
Just due to snake being the like snake.
And so silver is cool, you know.
Sure, sure.
But I also don't remember to be.
I think I feel like I would gravitate to the more extreme, like
what I now know are like, you know, like like the Memphis colors,
you know, like an old Taco Bell.
Oh, yeah.
Because these colors were new to us in the 90s.
Also very southwest.
So like I I still have to consult.
You get the pack of 64 crayons and they would have those color.
I remember like you get like if we get a double the crayons,
you would get those colors you're talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they felt they felt novelty.
They were being used in our code.
We were the first generation who were getting those colors in our clothes.
Yeah.
So I feel like I would go green
monkeys because it was kind of a more of a turquoise.
It felt like an extreme green.
Yeah.
So I think so.
That's a question.
If you had the if you had to pay your silver snakes,
you think if they if they let you choose, which is a big if.
Yeah, I imagine everyone piled on the water to colors and everyone else had to suffer.
Yeah.
The dregs what's left in the pile.
You also OK.
It's red jaguars, blue barracudas, green monkeys, orange iguanas.
That's a good I mean, because iguanas also feels like that.
That also felt like an animal of the time.
Yeah.
That's an animal that we're sunglasses.
Not all of these would purple parrots.
I don't think you're catching a parrot in some.
But that's what I was my team.
You'd be prepared.
There's no this is like guessing.
This is just I was I was like, that's my team every time.
I was never win.
Oh, and then I was disappointed.
Yeah.
Jason Blue Bear Acudas.
Blue Bear Acudas.
Yeah.
It was a calming shade of blue.
Yeah, I agree.
Yeah.
Barracuda is an interesting animal.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
It feels like educate.
It feels like it's not a primary.
You know what I mean?
No, it's not.
Bear or dog.
Yeah.
Those are the primary animals.
Bear and dog.
Bear, dog.
Yellow dog.
And so that's all like a name, I think.
Yeah.
Sometimes you think of cats once in a blue moon.
You remember cats.
Anaconda.
I well, so we don't overlap.
So we wouldn't have a problem.
Yeah, we'd all be fighting to the death on that.
Yeah.
Then you just take it to the moat.
So that's the first challenge that's right up at the top,
which is kind of good for excitement.
Real fast.
You can maybe get a little tease of what the
legend is, you know, and then you're just right into the,
it's always a moat challenge.
And maybe you're jumping across inner tubes.
Maybe you're going across some wire or something.
Either way, it's chaos.
And either way, at least one team is really eating shit.
Yeah.
I read that this would sometimes take half an hour to do.
For each taping.
Yes, for each tape,
which this might be a good chance to talk about the tedium.
I really, truly, I think I knew the bare bones of this,
but that they would shoot five episodes in a day.
My God.
And then do all the moats, all the steps, all the temple.
You just had like hundreds of kids
in a holding room at all times.
Oh, God.
That's the worst part.
Green monkey seven, green monkey seven.
Getting confused about which green monkey it is.
There was one job, one number to remember.
A break room with like arcade games and pizza.
And how sick must you have been
of being in that fucking break room by the end of the day?
Well, imagine like that lighting is not good.
The smell is not good.
Like old because they're just leaving those pizzas out.
And you are bloated from pizza and like store brand soda,
like public store brand Dr.
Pepper,
just guzzling it over and over.
Dr.
Special or something.
Yeah, Dr.
Good.
Dr.
Temple.
That's their in-house.
Yeah.
They probably brew it up.
We save money by making our own Dr.
Pepper.
If we just make all our soda for the year,
right before the tapings.
If we use the boat water and it's flavoring.
With rubber-made containers and cans of seltzer
and buckets of syrup.
Okay, so Jed, we need you to write three legends,
then go mix up the soda.
Put it in the carbonation machine.
And really rinse that rubber-made out
because the kids were getting pretty sick yesterday.
Also, you're the lifeguard,
so make sure you have these teams drown
in front of their families, please.
Brush up on CPR.
We can't give you a full lesson.
We can't get a specialist out,
but just like find a book if you can.
If the kids want to drink a water,
tell them to go drink from the moat.
We don't have running water here.
Remember, you can't put makeup on
until after the moat sequence
because you did it in the wrong order last time.
You scared a kid, they nearly drowned.
You could put a little zinc on your nose.
That'll just read as lifeguard materials.
But don't push your GD luck, okay?
You hear me, Jed?
I don't want to say this again, Jed.
The whole thing is on Jed's back.
But yeah, this thing was done maddeningly,
I mean, not quickly on the day.
It seems like these tapings were probably incredible slogs.
But okay, the breakdown on this, 40 episodes a season,
all done within two weeks.
So that's like what we all watched over the course of,
for the first time they aired a couple months,
but then you're still watching it in college.
Like where do I put it on, on Peacock?
Not Peacock, what fucking streamer's wish?
It's on Paramount Plus.
Paramount Plus, god.
It's two weeks of these people's lives.
Multiply that by three, three seasons, we're up to six.
And this is, for somebody like Kirk Fogg,
this is what he'll be known for forever,
for something that he did over six weeks of his life.
It's pretty crazy to think of it that way.
That's shorter than some plays get.
How long did the moon landing take, you know?
That's true.
Hey, hey, hey, you know what, if we're crunching numbers.
Kirk Fogg, Neil Armstrong, Tare Potato.
Big important things in American history, so yeah.
Yes, true.
Yeah, you know, the QAnon shaman is famous
for something that happened in just.
Yeah, that was like two hours.
Just three hours.
Yeah, same deal.
So actually the two weeks is pretty meaty.
Do you think a day of shooting a legend in the hidden temple
was worse than like a day of shooting Elf?
Because like Elf notoriously would be like a slog,
because like you couldn't get the puppet wouldn't work.
The angle was wrong.
Puppet engineers were banging their heads
against the wall.
Everyone was just miserable.
At least that's just one component.
Yeah, you don't have like a bunch of impatient children
if you get wrangled all times.
I guess that's true.
It's more controlled, I suppose.
And you do have a puppet, which I imagine
that that plank of wood came out,
like the duct tape connecting it.
That seems a little foolproof though.
It's just a lever, you know.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, maybe that is,
it's pretty basic engineering.
Olmec does have to display the range of emotions
that Elf does, you know.
I bet Olmec was easier to do than Elf.
Yeah, I agree.
From controlling the character.
He's stationary, all he does is his mouth opens
and his eyes glow, you know, that's easier than.
Yeah, and they never had to give him sunglasses.
Exactly.
Yeah, worst case they could ADR Olmec.
Yeah, yeah, true.
They could get footage of him dead on
and then like later in a sound booth have him
talk about Benjamin Franklin's little glasses or something.
Let's talk about some of these legends.
That's a good, because I completely forgot this.
I completely forgot.
I forgot everything but the end of the show.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
I don't think anything else about the format of it.
The end of the show is obviously the thing
you want to get to.
The rest has a certain chaff quality to it
where it's like, all right, let's go through
these kind of like generic rope climbing games
and all that while we're waiting for the freaking temple.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it feels like time killing
and not all of it can be as like big scale
as the big temple run.
But yeah, I 100% forgot that there's this zone
where Olmec weaves the tail of the item
and how it ended up in the temple.
And then you have to remember what he said.
Oh, that's right, it's reading comprehension.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Listening comprehension.
It's a little mini SAT thing.
And it feels very Carmen and San Diego inspired to me.
Yes, yeah, true.
In the sense of like, we're gonna give the kids
a little something they're gonna use.
Yeah, yeah, except that it's nonsense, right?
It's all lies about Abraham Lincoln riding a horse.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, his favorite, Abraham Lincoln spurs.
Why wouldn't it be the hat?
The hat's right there.
Abraham Lincoln's also.
I still am so history deficient
that it took me a long ways through the episode
the jewel encrusted egg of Catherine the Great.
Me as an adult to think, wait a minute,
I bet Catherine the Great didn't have
a jewel encrusted egg.
Teaching his kids all these useless fake facts.
on tests and reports.
That gets lodged in their head.
The real Benjamin Franklin one is called
the Electrified Key of Benjamin Franklin,
which we all kind of know that story.
That's rooted in something.
But we all know that is apocryphal.
But I don't know that we can track down
the broken wing of Icarus.
It's been lost to history.
Wait a minute, yeah, we have character,
for example, there's Amelia Earhart,
a fairly recent historical figure versus Icarus.
Icarus, a fictional allegory.
The scales of Pontius Pilate.
Oh, the silver, Judas' little baggy of silver.
Yeah, Judas' little silver.
What is the most, is Amelia Earhart the most recent person?
That has to be right, right.
I'm trying to think.
I don't have the whole list in front of me.
Like, Jimmy Carter's mobile phone.
Magic Johnson's NBA Championship ring.
Did you just steal it?
He was here for the All-Star game or something?
The jersey of David Justice.
The Gordon Lady's gun.
The dried Japanese banquet vomit of George Bush.
Oh, yeah.
Bill Clinton's saxophone.
That was the only one done real time.
Like, hey, we're planning a show.
That's great.
Somebody called his buddy at KTLA.
Like, hey, could you?
Can someone take it to FedEx, please?
Hurry, six o'clock is the last drop off.
Orlando ASAP.
It's a pretty strange assertion
that every historical figure has a primary item,
and you can tell that they are stretching with some of them,
because you end up with, the Amelia Earhart one,
you're like, oh, is it her goggles
or a little propeller pin or something?
No, it is the lucky pot-bellied pig of Amelia Earhart.
Well, I guess she didn't take it with her.
You got it.
Exactly, yes.
Like, Broken Wing of Icarus, maybe they thought,
well, maybe it fell to earth,
but since we don't, I guess they're like,
the wreckage of Amelia Earhart,
we don't know what happened exactly,
so how would the wreckage of, that would be a clue.
So they did think this through.
Like, it's gotta be something that she didn't take,
so it was like, her little buddy,
like, fueling up the plane or whatever.
This is a weird story.
Carved her a little wooden pot-bellied pig.
Here, take it for good luck.
She says, no.
Doubly weird, because here's something for good luck.
No, thanks, I won't need it.
I, Amelia Earhart, will make it.
I'm doing a perfectly safe task.
It's a very time-tested, very easy function to do.
But also, I crafted this especially for you.
I did wood carving for you.
Fuck you, engineer, working on my rickety plane.
So yeah, if you take anything away from this,
it's that she's mean.
She's rude and thoughtless.
Yeah, yeah, so we can all feel a little less sorry
about Amelia Earhart passing,
because now we know she was a terrible gift non-acceptor.
Just appreciate her employees.
The one kind of face on a person that struck me,
Lawrence of Arabia's headdress.
There's no way the kids know.
I'm sure the writer even was like,
they're not thinking about the real guy.
They're just thinking like,
I saw that movie at like 2 a.
m.
on TV.
Yeah, the headdress of David.
No, Lawrence, Lawrence of Arabia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's also funny, because you're always right around
the corner from horrors,
where if you look up the real story,
because the real stories are from terrible times
and about terrible people.
So like the jewel-encrusted egg of Catherine the Great,
because I first Google, did Catherine the Great
actually have a jewel-encrusted egg, like a dumbass?
And then you start, then you learn real,
one of the facts that the kids have to remember
is the name of her friend, Gregory Orlov,
who I think was actually some like.
Oh man, that's gotta be a tough one.
What was the name of Catherine the Great's friend?
The kid's like, Gregory Romolf.
And yeah, the pressure,
you have to remember Russian last names,
or you don't get a huffy.
That haunts a kid, you know that, for the rest of his life.
Mom, dad, why didn't you enroll me in Russian history classes
when I was 11?
Okay, you know, when I would watch these game shows,
I thought like, okay, I think I could do the flags
on Double Dare, I think I could handle what would you do.
That's what it was called, right, the other Mark Summers?
Yeah.
But this show, I think the only part I was like,
I bet I could do that, like the step on the ground
answer a question that the giant stone man said
90 seconds ago, you know?
Would you be worried though about,
because what was flashing through my head was timing
of the probably janky step to light it up.
And you know that's what gets you even on current game shows
on Jeopardy is the like, getting the rhythm of the thing.
You feel like you got the reading comprehension,
but do you think you could master the perfect step?
I'd be worried every step of the way.
I'd just be worried about every,
I'm sure I would try to like hurt myself
like trying to nail in the floor.
Which I'm sure the response time on that floor,
like you said, the Jeopardy buzzer,
no way that was super accurate.
You may be a little ahead,
you gotta be a little ahead of it.
And yeah, I don't think they're mastering the rhythm.
It would be great to see a kid so stressed
that they just puncture the floor.
Yeah.
They go all the way through.
Kick Jed right in the head.
He's under there for some reason.
He's just turning light switches on and off.
That's the one man band too.
He has like one, two, three, four platforms.
He's got two with his fingers and two with his toes.
I hate this guy.
I turn the corner in this building
and he's always there doing something.
And he seems so tired and so sad.
Smoking cigarettes every time I see him.
Jed, I told you, don't smoke under the steps.
The one, this one really seemed like a stretch to me.
The golden pepperoni of Catherine de' Medici.
Who, and this was.
It's almost like an Italian slur or something.
It sounds offensive, yeah.
Well and what's weird about it,
this is about the Queen of France.
Yeah, she famously loved pepperoni.
Yeah, so why are we, and then the story is about
her therapist, Linguini.
I think maybe they just didn't,
they just didn't do this right.
They got some names wrong.
Well this is also before the internet,
so you just had to kind of go on
whatever knowledge you already had.
So you're just kind of patching it together.
Who's gonna call you out, a bunch of dumbass kids?
Yeah, they don't know.
They're wrote listening to these stories
so that they can step on a button correctly.
They are not gonna correct.
But in this case, was it like,
was Catherine de' Medici from France, Italy,
kid says France, then they like, no, uh, whoa.
Oh wait, uh oh.
Maybe.
What do we do?
Back to one, everyone.
We need to redo that.
The camera ran out of tape.
Oh, side fact about it, I am happy though
that they made, I think maybe they needed
to make up some bullshit about Catherine de' Medici
because in real life, she was under a lot of pressure
to like continue the family line and have a lot of babies.
A recurring thing of all of these,
like were the real people's lives as fun
as Olmec's legend told?
And then it's like, they had 15 children
and the three survived.
The horrors of being all of these people.
But this woman.
You would all be dead, children.
You should be begging to go the Punta Cana Ramada.
It's better than any palace
that any of these kings could have dreamed of.
The real woman, she had to like continue the family line.
So she had to reproduce and fast.
So she had to do all of the known at the times
perfect ways to ensure that you will get pregnant.
Those including drinking mule urine
and covering her vagina in cow dung.
Yeah, this is a royal we're talking about.
This is a queen has to put cow shit.
Was there a rationale for both of those things?
Not that I saw.
because if she asked, so why do I drink mule urine?
It's a lot of, look.
If you have to ask.
It took an hour to explain it.
It was mostly himing and hawing.
Yeah, you're not gonna get it I don't think.
You're not gonna understand it.
That's queen shit.
It's a science thing
and we don't wanna burden you with that.
We don't, we just want.
You just keep your head on in the game
of fucking and drinking mule piss.
Look, here's my guess for the shit
is that it's like shit is fertilizer.
Sure, there you go.
Oh!
It's surely a semantic device.
everyone is pretty miserable.
It's pretty funny.
It's a very grotesque film.
But it's very grotesque
and the only people who are happy are just constantly,
even they just have to be constantly backstabbing everyone.
They can never let their guard down.
So they can be one of the two people
with living in the comfortable life of smearing couch.
Yes, and it will probably drive them insane.
Yeah, that too.
Yeah, yeah, everybody.
If you aren't dying from one of the diseases
or from just random animals and bugs being around,
then you go loony.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The other thing, not to get into too uncomfortable,
you brought this one up, Harriet Tubman.
I think it's strange that there were three episodes
that had slavery figures in them.
Yeah, sure.
Because besides, look, there's weightier reasons
why that is weird, but also how did all these artifacts
from the South end up in this Mesoamerican temple
that otherwise has things that Icarus used?
You're saying?
It's a real catch-all temple.
It really is.
It's a temple of the mind.
Yeah, I guess maybe, yeah, that's a good way to think of it
versus an actual location.
Yeah, if you had a pinpoint on the map,
it would be like, not be detectable by a GPS.
It's everywhere and nowhere all at once.
Lay lines converge on the temple.
It's like a multiverse inflection point,
and that's how items end up there.
Multiverse of history and myth, all colliding.
We have done more backstory, by the way,
in a little over an hour than they ever did.
We have access to the internet.
We have established more concrete logic
than the stone production people.
Because we all have computers,
and we don't have to win Encyclopedia Britannica's,
like some of the kids on the show.
You have knowledge back there.
You won We All Fortune.
Odd outmoded prizes.
They wouldn't give that to you actually at the show, right,
where you'd have to buy two suitcases to take it home?
They'd probably ship it to you, I imagine.
I would think.
Could I just get the hair gel?
That seems easier to pack.
LA looks.
I'll take the LA looks package, please.
Can I say one that I like?
Oh yeah, yeah, please.
Robin Hood and Marianne's ladder.
Ladder.
Or Marianne, sorry, Madey Marianne.
Their ladder.
Is that like a Rapunzel thing or something?
I guess, because yeah, he rescued her,
but wouldn't it be, there's more fun.
Yeah, it's Bo and Arrow.
That's probably my go-to.
Is Hal with the feather or something?
I don't know.
The ladder is funny.
Her tree does not factor in or anything that he robbed.
Right, like a sack of gold coins.
Ladder.
Well, maybe it'd be interesting to see
what ladders used to look like,
as opposed to our fancy modern ladders.
This is educational.
Wow, so they couldn't fold up back then, huh?
Wow.
Boy, we have it pretty good, don't we?
Yeah, so these are insane.
So you get past this zone,
the kids, as we said, are just like sperm
not making it very far into the fertilization process.
So you don't have, we don't care,
you don't learn the kids' names even at the beginning.
You get nothing.
It's only the teens.
So then eventually you get
kind of an awkward little banter segment.
They've picked out just a couple detail
that are usually just like,
so you do dance, huh?
because this zone can be a very awkward zone.
Kirk's interviewing like 30 of these kids a day.
He's already talked like seven Kevins today.
He doesn't have
He can't keep it straight.
So you do soccer too, huh?
Wow.
You like hamburgers, huh?
Yeah, Kirk Fogg has been awake
for like 48 hours at this point.
He's just like, all right.
By his own admission,
because I've done some interview with him
where they ask him really generic questions.
And I like this one.
What was a typical day like at Nick Studios?
Typical day for me was showing up
and walking around the set,
trying to figure out what the show was about.
That, what?
Did they not even brief you on anything?
You know what?
Seems like he was as lost as anybody.
He was in a fog.
That wouldn't shock me.
Kirk was in a fog.
Oh yeah.
I didn't get a lot of hands-on guidance.
So it was a bit overwhelming
due to the nature of production.
He also says that he got the part
because they didn't have a lot of time.
I don't know, get him in.
He's in, he's going.
That episode of success is just showing up.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Sometimes.
It's half the battle.
So he doesn't know any better than anybody else.
And then you're on to Temple Games.
And I don't have a lot to say about Temple Games.
Because this is also,
it's like you're just waiting for the
Yeah, the Temple Games are filler.
They're basically just like another version
of what you would see on Guts or Double Dare.
Yeah.
Like it's nothing really
very Temple specific.
And you know, it's like, all right,
put these balls in a basket.
You know, it's
The only interesting thing maybe sometimes
is that they do have to tie into the story.
Right.
So you now have to fold in
real historical events into what is usually just like
going up and down or like being on some boxes.
Maybe throwing some items to knock other items down.
For instance, in the one that I mentioned
about like Russian history, it was like,
they had to, in order for her to get in power,
they had to depose some czars.
So you need to knock out four czars to win the
Yeah, yeah.
And it's some like filler.
So the kids are defeating czars and that's the game.
It's time to make Anastasia an orphan
by knocking these bottles over.
I also, one of them was like
the Underground Railroad, right?
Sure.
Because it's part of that story.
Oh, that's right.
With like the mine cart, failing to understand
that it's a metaphor.
There's no actual railroad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you don't get the fun.
Yeah, you can't do anything with some train mechanism.
But they do, and again, they're trying to keep it educational.
So they're telling you a little bit about how that worked
and there'd be like hiding spots
and then you're trying to make it up to Canada.
And what that ultimately leads to
is just the funny line from Kirk Fogg.
All right, so the green monkeys, they made it to Canada.
That means they're going to the temple.
Really simplifies that.
Most of those facts can be true at the same time.
Yes, technically, it has lower stakes situations
than higher stakes situations.
The slaves are freed and more importantly,
you all will be competing for the bikes.
That's in the past and right now what's important is
you get to get a walk in.
Get to that cave.
Gravity of this moment is.
Yeah, I was thinking a moment of silence
to appreciate this and now Olmec explained
what they're doing.
The temple games were the pendants rounds
and I was stressed out.
They gotta get enough pendants.
You gotta have the pendants like winning the trivia.
To get the advantage for the big game, for the race.
I mean, I was like.
I felt relieved if they would get two pendants
because then I think.
Then they're impervious.
Yeah, they're pretty much.
But man, if you got a pendant and a half or one half
and you had to find that other half,
I was like, oh God, they're not gonna make it.
That's like when you would go into a video game
and you're like fighting a boss
or in the last level and you have one star.
It triggered, like that would trigger my same anxiety
about it like I'm not getting out of this.
I do not have enough going in.
This is all I got.
Yeah.
Temple guard in the second room done.
Game over.
Yeah.
I have a very specific memory of watching my dad
taking a nap in his recliner.
Very 90s dad thing.
Taking a nap in his recliner.
I wanted, the show came on and like as I got closer
to the temple run, I like just scooted over
and just sat in the chair next to him
because I'm like, if I'm gonna jump out of my skin
and if I'm gonna get scared,
at least I'll feel better if he's close by
even though he is totally dead asleep.
Yeah, he can't do anything against those temple guards
if they were to jump out of the television and attack you.
I don't know why I didn't just change the channel.
I guess because the cable provider
had not given us Cartoon Network yet.
So I was like, well what do I watch besides Nickel,
I mostly watch Nickelodeon.
That's your whole life also.
You're gonna not watch some Nickelodeon?
You have to.
You're not gonna be watching the best part of the show.
Yeah.
High drama, man.
It was our job at the time.
It was all, I felt a duty.
I have to consume four hours
of whatever this channel is showing me.
Probably the repeat that's gonna air in two to three hours.
And I wouldn't remember,
I feel like I would just like not even know
they were repeats sometimes.
You just kinda get full, like, did I?
I'm gonna watch the same one, I don't know,
like 14 times and not know.
There could have been five episodes if I didn't know.
Yeah.
The discovery to me, watching the best of compilation
that there were not just some teams who won,
but teams who won with one kid going through.
Like they had a medallion, they had a pendant,
they got taken by a guard,
they never encountered any other guard
that got the artifact and then they got out,
either with a lot of time or with the skin of their teeth.
And I was just like the solo winners
of like you are a god to me.
Buy a lottery ticket.
Do you think they're all doing well today?
They're all Fortune 500 CEOs, I think, the winners.
If you look at the list, you start to go,
oh wow, yeah, Temple, Temple.
Warren Buffett ran.
Blue Barracuda, yeah, yeah.
I think you could rewrite the Bruce Springsteen
song Glory Days about a Legends of the Hidden Temple winner
that's now at a bar near the Nickelodeon studios in Orlando.
I would never stop talking about this if I won that.
I would be talking about it every day of my life,
every new person I met, 100%.
Yeah, percent of like,
you and like Olympic level athletes,
that's like how hard it is to win this.
So I would, you should be proud.
Also on top of that, the Olympics were boring
and for grownups.
100%.
This air, they kept rerunning,
the Olympics didn't get rerun on Nick.
That's true, that gets rerun once and forgotten.
So better, better than the Olympics.
I agree, I respect these kids more than I respect
Michael Phelps, he trained.
These kids were just thrown into it.
That's a good point, yes.
Full of pizza.
Of course they're good, they thought about being good.
These kids, the odds were completely against them.
Absolutely, paired up into the terrible.
A complete stranger told lies about historical figures
and forced to memorize them
and then put this impossible puzzle
with fucking adults ready to grab them.
Absolutely, these guys are the real heroes.
Screaming audience, they've been separated
from their parents all day.
Fed crappy pizza, only Jed tending to them.
100%.
There should be an Olympics where.
These kids should all be on Mount Rushmore,
it should be like 90 kids.
Oh, I'm for it, yeah, yeah,
I'll blow up a couple of them at least
and refashion them as all of the winning red Jaguars.
They should also have an Olympics
where the people don't train at all.
That would be awesome.
That's a million dollar idea.
Olympic swimming pool and you just find some people,
keep them in a room for 10 hours eating pizza
and then you go, oh by the way, you're doing swimming.
You're getting in the pool.
So I think that people would.
Yeah, you really can't train for this in any real way.
Yeah, it's not like you're gonna get the layout
of the temple.
No.
It's not like a mission impossible mission.
You could, I guess if you knew the sequence of events
and you could utilize, have your parents help you,
you'd have to use every room of your house,
assuming that you're in a house
and then get up on the roof probably.
Oh, you mean like.
I think you could do speed runs.
Obstacle course, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Try to send a better call Saul
or he's like running them through.
I'm just thinking that's a lot.
How you're gonna steal all the suits.
Yeah, I think you could rig up,
but it'd be guesswork unless you knew somebody
who had the blueprints or something.
But if you know that person
then you probably have more inside information.
It could probably scam the system in some other way.
Yeah.
The only thing I think in all seriousness
that I could do to train for this as a kid
would be to desensitize me to being frightened.
That's the only thing that would help
is I don't know how you do that.
You just pay a friend to fucking jump out.
I get jitters so often.
Yeah, like every day.
Yeah, scare me.
A couple kids are gonna jump out at me during the day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So you just have PTSD permanently going forward.
It would damage me, but I would be less reactive
when it would happen on the show.
Maybe you need a network of people
because I think there's a fear of the unknown.
They're wearing masks.
That's part of the scary thing.
And if you kind of know it's your friend,
even a shock gives you a little.
So you need to like get a friend
to get all the people he knows who you don't.
Well, they need to coordinate with everyone, yeah.
So they just need to coordinate and it can come from anywhere.
Yeah, yeah.
That's a good point
because the one thing I saw about the show
is that the temple guards were told,
switch up how you jump out.
Get them sometimes when they first get in the room,
get them when they're almost out of the room
or halfway through.
I remember this very well that sometimes you go like,
okay, there's no temple guard.
Ah!
And then sometimes it would happen immediately.
Yeah.
Because I would be freaked
because I would be like, oh, is it okay?
Okay, okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's all right.
And if we're all too afraid as viewers,
then imagine in person.
I can, yeah, I think of all the shows,
I probably would have said I wanted to do this one the most,
but no way in reality.
Maybe you've been a little relieved
when you didn't make it all the way?
Yeah, because this was the story of my life as a kid going,
oh, Alien Encounter is gonna open in Disney World.
Oh, Mike, it's open already.
Oh, it is.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't really know if I wanna,
are you sure?
It's right here, it's open, there's no line.
Oh, you know what?
And then I didn't go.
My little sister and my dad went.
I might need to have lunch.
It's 8.
30.
We had a giant buffet character breakfast.
Yeah.
But I can't even remember the lie I told to try to,
I did get out of it.
I didn't go on Alien Encounter.
But we were sitting right there and I go, oh,
I think I said to like,
it's too bad Disney Adventure said it opens in August.
Yeah, yeah.
No, Mike, it's open now.
Well, as we tell ourselves.
Jay, what was your level of frady catness?
Because we, the three of us have some,
we're somewhere on the scale of frady to not frady,
as cats are concerned.
Sure, sure.
What did, like, do you think you would have been able
to handle this decently?
I feel like I probably would have been out
in one of the earlier two rounds.
Yeah.
I doubt I would have done well at the moat.
I might have done well with memorization,
but God knows when you're paired with some rando,
what their level is.
I would certainly get eliminated by the temple game.
So it'd be a miracle if I was among the last team
to be there, for sure.
So you think you make it a little bit of the way.
Maybe, yeah.
I don't see myself, if I'm being perfectly honest,
I don't see myself ever making it to the temple.
If you ran the simulation a hundred times,
I might make it like twice and not win once.
That's probably me too.
Which how cool would that be to put in stats
about ourselves as children?
Run it through a reconstructed temple and see
what would happen.
And then watch this, that it like, wait a minute,
I peed myself when the temple guard
showed up?
I drowned in the fucking
styrofoam room?
I died?
You're not supposed to die.
On run number 51, I got so scared that I started
eating the packing peanuts and then choked.
I choked on the monkey head.
Fell to the bottom.
None of the crew stopped me.
Kirk and Jed didn't help me.
They laughed.
The other children, they brought out all the children
waiting backstage.
Hey kids, you gotta see this.
They all mocked me in unison.
I just rewatched Moneyball recently.
Let me be like Bill Simmons, holds up.
Have you watched Moneyball?
I think I'd like to better now because I watched
more baseball.
So, and it's very much structured like a,
it's a little boring.
It's kind of structured like a baseball game.
Yeah, you can come and go.
You can talk to people, drink a beer.
But there is early scenes.
Jonah Hill is explaining to Brad Pitt, like,
okay, here's what Saber Metrics is.
All the players have all these different stats.
We need to add them up and we boil that down to one number.
We try to get one number for everyone.
So to do the Saber Metrics, I would like every kid
who ran Legends of the Hidden Temple,
like did the game show and it's like,
who is the best kid?
We know we can't afford a star on the Purple Parrots,
but it's about building a smart Purple Parrots.
Yeah, exactly.
We won't win this year.
But we won't win 11 years down the line.
It's a rebuilding year for the Purple Parrots.
Oh shit, we gotta move to Las Vegas, all right.
By 1995, yeah, the kids are great.
But the Sadie of
By episode 119.
There should have been a coach for each team
that was consistent with all the episodes.
Oh sure.
Like almost like on The Voice or something.
So you'd have, yeah, whatever, six coaches.
Well, I think that they, I think there maybe was
that element on the reboot, on the CW reboot from
Yeah, I didn't forget about it
as much as I didn't know it happened at all.
I missed this 100%.
Well, I remember, the only reason I remember it existed
is because whenever it was coming out at Comic-Con,
Olmec was on the show floor and I took a photo with him.
And that's the only reason it was on my radar
as being around, because I was like, why is Olmec here?
You found the casting notice at some point.
Yeah, I thought about submitting for it.
You were trying to get me to do it.
And you refused.
Yeah, because I was doing physical therapy,
I think for my shoulder at the time.
And I was like, I absolutely don't want to do legends.
It's always something.
No, I'm full of ailments.
The podcasters, burden, yeah.
How's your, you guys peeing regularly lately?
How's that working?
Yeah, how's your streams?
The stream is, Scott, as I explained,
the stream is fine, it's just when you're a man
and it's later 30s, sometimes it just dribbles out a bit
at the end, that's all, it's normal.
Django, you're our guest, you don't have to disclose,
that's how your streams look.
But if you want, I'm just gonna give you the floor.
Well, just check my website,
it should have all my pertinent medical details.
Okay, great.
Oh, great, that's very nice of you.
Oh, cool.
Just get in front of it, put it out there.
Board type and all that jazz.
Like my chart, but exclusively for you
and your comedy, comedy dates and blood type
and the miles per hour on your stream.
Yeah, yeah.
Horsepower, I don't know, however you want.
They're measuring quarks.
Okay, got it, got it.
I, yeah, it came back and I think it may have had
the element that Kirk Fogg was your mentor.
They felt like they had to keep him in there somewhere,
even though the host changed.
in the movie.
Made for TV, scripted movie.
Made for Nickelodeon movie,
which came out in November 2016.
Oh wow, I had no idea.
A cursed time.
But I watched this, I skimmed through this a little bit.
Also on Paramount Plus.
Not Yank Down, the recent shows Yank Down.
That one is still making them a hefty profit, I'm sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
People are watching that one every day.
And then, gotta keep that.
No, weirdly this whole thing is on the back
of Legends of the Hidden Temple movie.
If Legends goes, now we're gonna sunk.
It all implodes.
And we gotta sell, we gotta merge.
Mission Impossible, Top Guns, Legends, scripted movie.
That's what's holding up Paramount Plus.
Kirk Fogg kind of the Tom Cruise of his time,
because he really was him on the rope.
I don't know if you can tell.
No CGI there.
He insisted, I'm doing the swing every episode.
And if it kills me, it kills me.
Gotta go out swinging.
I watched a little of this thing.
It exists in a confusing universe and timeline
where the Hidden Temple is a theme park now.
It's kind of a chintzy theme park where Kirk Fogg works.
And they use his real name over and over again.
And he's presented as like a cheese ball.
Like the show is not very good.
It's a very theme parky animal actors kind of show.
But then there's this kid who's like insist like,
yeah, I know you can say it's fake if you want,
but the legend is real.
I know it is.
And I'm gonna find it.
And then like, and he talks to Kirk who like believes,
no, I've always known it's real.
And you're like, wait, but does the show exist?
Why do they all know who he is and his full name?
And it's kind of strange.
And then in the end,
Kirk gets his wish to go live in the temple.
That's what it seems like.
He doesn't want to do this minimum wage
theme park job anymore.
So the door closes and seals.
Say goodbye to your wife and kids, Kirk.
You're doing your dream of living inside a temple.
It's close encounters.
He like, his wife and kids are nothing compared
to the chance for adventure.
It's like when Bumblebee says he wants to stay on earth
with Sam Witwicky.
I watched the end of it yesterday.
Oh, I see.
The Bummi oddly a little more on your mind.
It's difficult.
Sam before wrestling.
The premise of the movie is not dissimilar
to the Revenge of the Mummy Ride in Florida,
where it's like, okay, this is the set of a movie,
but also we've stumbled upon a real temple.
You know?
And also the Brendan Fraser movies exist in this world,
but so do curses.
I love that they keep Kirk in the mix.
Yeah.
It feels very thoughtful.
Heretical for them to pretend he never existed.
He's like the only, him and Ulmer are like
the only two consistent things you remember
about that show, really.
Yeah, pretty, yeah, that is the franchise to me.
The idea of a temple is still kind of generic,
but if there aren't these two guys involved,
then what do you have?
And this one, they make him act.
He has this other, you're pushing into it.
It is played like, you know, it's true, all of it.
He gets to do that to this kid, making him like,
I know your friends make fun of you,
but the legends of the Hidden Temple are real.
I know they are.
Your friends make fun of you for being a fan of a show
that was on 20 years ago.
Yeah, I don't know.
I like seeing it.
It makes me smile to see Kirk.
The show's fun.
It's fun to think about for a little bit.
Fun to hear the lore.
We missed how Kirk said that a girl threw up
in the pit of despair at one point.
They had to stop the taping, make sure she was okay,
and then keep going.
They do still owe the remats of material.
Yeah, of course she had to finish the goddamn show.
Statistically, there was probably more throw-up incidences
than teams that won every season.
Yeah, that temple was just a fucking crawling germ factory.
Scared children vomiting in various crevices.
Yeah, the bathroom, kids might have had
nervous shit in that tiny bathroom in the holding area.
So many kids.
It was a miserable taping experience, I'm sure.
Jed, got that problem again.
Jed.
No, you can clean up the bathroom with the makeup on.
We don't give a shit, okay?
You just can't be on the cameras.
Can't you be calming these kids down?
Learn balloon animals.
Jed, Jed, start doing balloon animals.
Jed, you're the counselor now.
You're the balloon animal counselor.
Get a DJ set up, do some songs.
Have him do the chicken dance, that'll keep him calm.
Have we missed anything?
Have we missed any big ticket items?
I just wanted to say one of the titles of another episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, go for it.
The mush pot hat of Johnny Appleseed.
The mush pot?
The mush pot.
Is that like where your cauldron you used to make apple mash?
Yeah, whatever he wore on his head.
At least that's what I remember
as far as the legend of Johnny Appleseed.
Yeah, I don't remember him having a hat,
but I guess I haven't really thought about it.
I don't think about Johnny Appleseed that much.
We had like a pan.
Yeah, it was a cauldron so he could do apple things.
That's a mush pot.
It was a mush pot, all right, come your ass down.
Jason, you should know what a mush pot is.
Listeners, you can't see us right now,
he's standing and shouting and pointing at us.
He's slicing open the couch and pulling the stuffing out.
I didn't even know he had a knife on him.
Yeah, I do, the knife of Michael Carlton.
The rarely used knife of Michael Carlton.
The podcasters box cutter.
Yeah.
I'm surprised, Jason, I am surprised you'd be like,
oh, you've never cooked something in a mush pot before?
Like, that's an East Coast thing, I guess.
Williamsburg, yeah, we use a mush pot all the time.
Growing up in the colonies, being in the Boy Scouts,
we certainly did a lot of interesting dishes
in Dutch ovens, which is just a large cast iron guy.
You can throw into a burning fire, you know?
But you didn't, they should,
like the scouts should teach you that, you know,
if you're in a situation, if you're overheating
and you don't have your hat,
if you do have your pot,
a mush pot can easily be your hat.
Right.
And that you should spread apple seeds wherever you go,
just to make it look like the world.
You can just do that automatically, you know?
Well, that's nice, just to keep the world beautiful.
Also, we didn't, maybe the one other thing
is that the reboot ended up on the CW,
but it was supposed to be on Quibi.
Oh.
Yeah, right.
Which itself almost is sort of lit.
10 minute episodes of Legends would be interesting.
You just cut all the chaff
and basically just go straight to the temple, I imagine.
Yeah, that's true, yeah, yeah, yeah.
They probably all should have been.
Yeah.
Well, again, this would have saved,
Paramount Plus is riding on Legends and Quibi,
I think it would have saved Quibi.
Yeah.
Would you, can I ask, if the offer was on the table,
you'd have to do anything other than somebody called you
and said, I need you to help me out
on Legends of the Hidden Temple
and it's the CW version's back,
it's tomorrow and you're available.
Would you want to do it?
Is it a paid position?
You get, you get 150, it's non-union,
but you get like, let's say you get like $300.
I'm not breaking the WGA strike
to go work on Legends of the Hidden Temple,
the second reboot.
That's my stance, you hear that, WGA?
No.
Well, look, it's, you know, it's an iffy,
you could call it research, I know we read a legend,
but is that really writing?
I'm a union man, I'm standing with my union on this one.
Okay.
But in the, let's jump ahead.
In a vacuum.
After we get a perfect deal.
I guess it depends on how much I'm getting paid.
Not even $300.
Yes.
100?
Okay, 100 is the line.
So win a prize though.
Well, it depends what the prize is, I guess.
It's a Huffy bike.
No.
If it's an adult road bike, maybe.
Yeah, the Huffys look, the Huffys are maybe a little.
Does Huffy still make bikes?
I think they might be around.
I'm not even, is it all kids?
Acquired by Yamaha at some point.
Right, is there some sort of absorbing of.
Yamaha is now owned by the Saudi Wealth Fund.
Well, that's, yeah.
I wonder if Huffy is an independent company.
So is this show, all things are.
All things are, yeah.
We didn't tell everybody we got bought a while back.
Yeah, so yeah, I'm doing, I'm.
You're doing it no matter what.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I also wanna do floor is lava.
I think I could do it.
Yeah?
It looks hard and it looks like you get hurt a little bit,
but I think I could do it.
Well, you need to just get like a video reel ready to go
of you just like tumbling and jumping
and I guess mainly not getting scared
by people jumping out at you.
That'd be a great reel.
Just you blase as people try to scare you.
I'm Mike Carlson and this is my non-shocked reel.
This is my standing my ground reel.
Iron Mike, that's the name I want.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess that doesn't sound like.
Well look, if you need to pull a gun out
over the course of it, then you do.
Whatever it takes to stand your ground.
To prove that I am tough enough to be on a game show
and make $200.
So I'm in, are you in?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Okay.
I think I'd be pretty awful at it.
Yeah.
Although I don't know.
I don't know that I would be good either.
I'm just saying.
Wait, what am I saying?
I hate haunts.
That's probably why I hate it.
That I don't wanna do it.
And Jason would be out too.
Yeah, no, I would take the $300 a day
to come up with like the tissue box shoes of Howard Hughes.
Oh, you'd write on it.
You'd scam.
Yeah, I would.
Oh no, no, after the perfect.
After, after, after.
Okay, sorry.
Come on, you'd admit it.
You'd scam right now.
The tissue box shoes of Howard Hughes.
Jason's making $300 a week to come up with legends.
Wait, well, he noticed $300 a day.
No, not for a week.
No, no.
It's for performing on the show.
No, you're getting Jed rate.
You're getting Jed 1983 rates.
Can I lease right from home and just hop on Zooms?
No, you're coming in.
Oh no.
And they're shooting down in Culver City.
Oh man, that's supposed to be a part of town.
Yeah, and it's not at the Sony lot.
It's a different place.
And they're doing it.
And it's outside on the hottest days of the year.
Yeah, legend of the hidden temple in the sun.
Finally, the newest obstacle, heat stroke.
Jenga, do you feel like you have,
if you had to get boiled down to one item,
it's 200 years from now.
Ooh, that's a good question.
My phone?
For all of us, it's just our phones.
Yeah, the sad thing about today,
the phone of the guy.
Yeah.
The nondescript phone of Jango Gold.
from the other dirty cases.
Yes, it's a clear dirty case
as opposed to the black dirty case
or the gray dirty case.
Well, thank you for weaving part of your legend
here with us today.
Yes, this is part of all our legends.
Yes, for adding a chapter to all of our legends.
Jango Gold and your nondescript phone,
you survived podcast the ride.
But hey, you're not walking away empty handed.
Ooh, what am I getting?
Let's exit the, while you're getting the,
you get to do a plug.
Oh, great.
That's a prize worth all the huffies in America.
That's a, yeah, it's a prize in a way.
And there's some greater,
in two years it'll be a prize
when there's awareness of what you're doing.
Absolutely.
Yeah, listeners, by the time this episode airs,
my standup special entitled Bag of Tricks
will be available on YouTube.
You can probably just Google Jango Gold Bag of Tricks
or go to YouTube and go to my account name
which is at Jango Industries.
Go there, subscribe, watch the special.
It'll be great.
It'll be really good.
And it's just you, there's no temple guards.
Very, very few temple guards in the special.
Although I'm still editing it, so who knows?
Maybe I could drop something in at the last minute.
Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, isn't that a night, you know,
we're trying to reinvent standup specials here and there
and you know, maybe I do it without an audience.
Maybe I do it with jump scares.
With spooky, yeah.
Spooky monsters.
Scary guys in masks trying to throw me off.
The first ever standup special in a haunted house.
It's a pretty good idea.
Spooky Bag of Tricks by Jango Gold.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
Well, you got your scary name already ready to go.
So the rest, the rest writes itself.
Besides that you have to now write
an hour of spooky standup material.
About haunted houses.
If I start now, I'll be ready by Halloween.
Yeah, well, get cooking.
I think you got a hell of a gimmick on your hands.
As for us, you can find us on the socials
at podcast the ride.
Merch is available in our T public store.
For three bonus episodes every month,
check out podcast the ride the second gate
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You will find all that at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
This episode not taped before a studio audience.
Nickelodeon Studios, Universal Orlando Florida.
And this one did take 10 hours to do.
Yeah, yeah.
We cut it together into two.
You're some 40 other guests in here.
Yeah.
Bang them out.
Yeah, yeah, we did the, we like,
we did all the regular fact parts and then everybody's
and then we, we shoveled them out, all had pizza.
And then we all did the riff part.
So if anything funny that happened.
It was cut out.
Oh yeah, we did it out of order.
The last four episodes with guests, we've all been,
and then there was some of the same.
There was an hour of American gladiators anecdotes
I cut out too.
Yeah, yeah.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.