Forever.
Dog.
Boo.
The following haunt cast contains child television producers, wholesome TV romance, a deep conspiracy
to yet again make dad look foolish, and names, names, and yes more names.
Adam Sass joins us to talk murder she wrote, mystery theater, on today's haunt cast, The
Fright.
Welcome, foolish mortals, to haunt cast The Fright, the haunt cast about scream parks hosted
by three good ghouls whose hair is turning gray from fright and also age.
I'm Scottlejuice for the C's great, and over here, Frightful Narlson.
Frightful, I'll write him down in case I introduce him, Frightful Narlson, and to my left.
Jagged Slash and Drain.
Okay, let's, slash and drain.
Like, slash and you drain the flood.
No, no, I get that, it's the, like, I guess, you're taking the D-E-N and turning that into
drain, it's the same bookends of letters, I guess.
There's stuff floating around, yeah, the same letters are mostly floating around.
I think I like it.
Mm-hmm.
This is kind of, this was the path I took too.
Thumbs up for our guest.
Mine was just an, I finally fixed what, that lasts so many years, I think.
I think that, mine is like, I didn't make a new one up, I just corrected the mistakes
of the past haunt cast.
You just, like, nudged what had been in the past.
Yeah, well, I felt like, I've been reflecting on our past haunt cast, the Frights, of which
there have now been many, and in my head, every single one of them has, like, ten minutes
of name discussion.
This one's no exception.
Now, but maybe, that we've cleared this up, I gave everyone advance time to come up with
their names, now, we just plow ahead.
And we're gonna do the podcast now.
The names that we love, and now we're free.
So, future haunt cast, you know, unless you change a couple episodes in, we fuck it all
up again.
Well, we'll see.
That is fine, that's acceptable.
It is haunt cast, the Frights season, this is kicking it off, so a lot of fun stuff planned.
We're hitting some haunts, and by that I mean Mike, and Mike only is hitting some haunts,
because he loves them, as established now.
But we're not just attending Halloween events, we are also hosting Halloween events.
For the first time ever, we're doing a live haunt cast, the Frights.
We've got two Halloween shows, live and live streaming, or live screaming, thanks to Dynasty
Typewriter.
That is Friday, October 20th, I believe.
Tickets available for both, for now, but grab them while you can, and if you're not in LA,
live scream it.
And we're, I think it's exciting that we get to dimensionalize this season, and to,
you know, do our attempt at a haunt.
I agree, and I think if you, I think you, from what we're talking about doing, I think
you're going to want to be at the haunt cast shows.
I think so.
Yeah, yeah.
So I'll just say that.
Fun stuff cooking up.
But, before we get there, we are kicking off the month at large with the scariest shit
you could ever imagine.
An attraction with the word murder in the title.
Can you imagine?
Does that justify putting it in this month, which I've now started to question, should
it have not been in the month?
Because it's just a pleasant attraction about the post-production process.
Well, but there's lots of secrets to be uncovered in Cabot Cove, you know?
Yes, true.
Well, it is a place, yes, there's a setting that has a lot more horror and intrigue and
such.
We're talking about the Murder She Wrote Mystery Theater.
I think that name was nudged here and there, but that's what it is in my head.
And joining us to talk about this, a longtime listener, first-time caller, someone who's
very passionate about Murder She Wrote, much like Jessica Fletcher, is a novelist, and I
suspect this is not a coincidence, and we'll get into it, we'll talk about it, but the
award-winning author of LGBTQ Young Adult Books for Penguin Random House, including
Your Lonely Nights Are Over, it's Adam Sass.
Hello.
I am so, yes, I am a longtime listener.
This is very like a Clifford Will Rise moment.
I'm very much having an out-of-body experience right now.
Like you made it to Dinosaur World.
For real, no, for real, I'm having the Martin Chord face right now where I'm just like
petrified, like petrified with joy.
Yeah, this is great.
Surrounded by three Larry the Scary Rexes.
That's right, yeah.
Hopefully not so scary.
No Charles Groden's, no.
I don't think I...
Well, one.
Well, hey, hey.
He's our Uncle Martin.
No, I think, no, and no, I think, I was approving of Slash and Drain earlier because it did
feel, I was going to say it did feel, I wanted to wait to be properly introduced as his podcast
fashion, but I wanted to comment Slash and Drain, I feel like is very H.H. Holmes.
It feels very, it feels very like, oh, you have a methodical system of like, oh, you
slash and drain it, like you have a, like it's like, it's not just murder, it's like,
oh, you just did it once.
Like, no, you've got an apparatus.
It's like Sweeney Todd.
Sure.
Yeah, the boarding houses with the gas pipes going into them, the barber shop chair that
like dumps you into the contraptions.
Slash and Drain, you got a system that felt very correct.
It's just like cold, it's industrial.
He doesn't even think of it as killing.
It's just like, you know, I do this, I slash and drain.
Yeah, it was Slash and Drain, you know, it's a service he provides.
Well, last year everyone was going crazy for Terrorfire 2.
Oh, yeah.
I never sat down and watched, but I watched the clips of, and it is like, uh.
This was the thing with the clown.
The clown.
You all yelled at me for not remembering the clown, who then we determined was not mentioned
when it came up.
Is that, that's that one?
Well, wasn't it like, wasn't it maybe said in like a big cacophony of noise or something?
The name, we checked this.
This was with Griffin.
I can't remember.
There was Marshall Gate, and then there was that like, you don't remember the name of
the clown?
It was just said.
The name of the clown was not said.
Okay.
I don't remember the details.
It was another, it was one of those where yell and yell and yell and check the tape.
We yell a lot on the show.
Yeah, it is my goal as a listener to like gain the confidence throughout the show to
then like badger you about something that you don't remember.
If you're at all any from the backlog, because you are, and thank you and bless you for this,
you have, you've listened to like, it sounds like everything you've been a supporter of
the show, which we really appreciate.
So that said, yes, if you recall something that I shit out of my mouth one time, there
was that it was incorrect or wrong.
We're going to open with the list of grievances.
Yes, this is how we're going to do this.
No, I mean, listen, yeah, I was introduced to you through through the pandemic.
And it was, it got me through it.
And this is when I was writing all of these books.
And so like this was, you know, as I was writing this, which is a very, um, um, contrary to
what the show Murder She Wrote would have you believe it is a very long involved draining process,
not just happily typing.
And then, you know, she just then Murder She Wrote as a show.
We're going to get to this, but like, I do want to pull you all with like your knowledge of the show
itself, because there's the mystery theater.
But then we're talking about the show as well, because I think that's a little important to
understanding the power of what Original Universal did with this with this theater.
But anyway, no, no, everybody here got me through like an immense up and down.
I had put out my first book in the first year of lockdown, which I do do not recommend.
You can help it.
Creativity on top of all that was was tough for anyone.
I was going to say like anybody who had to like release anything and then it was, you know,
but then it's like people are releasing stuff now and we're in the middle of something now.
There's going to be something that's going to fuck up the release of something.
But like also writing, I feel like can be like a I mean, you tell me I feel like it can be like a lonely process, an arduous process.
So that on top of pandemic seems a little crazy.
It's like I know we're all like making fun of like parrot.
That's a parasocial relationship now.
But I'm like parasocial stuff got me through it.
I think like you can have a very healthy parasocial thing as long as you remain in control of it at a certain point.
But I think you do need because like I'm an extroverted person.
So like it didn't come naturally to me to be like, oh, just like be in my room and then I'll write everything in my room.
And then it's the pandemic.
So I'll release the book virtually in my room and then I'll just stay in my room.
And so that's kind of how my first two books went.
And now I'm at my third one and I am finally getting out and meeting readers for the first time.
Oh, sweet.
And it's been amazing.
It's been like I did like my first book tour and it was it was fantastic, which is something Jessica Fletcher is always doing on Murder, She Wrote.
She was basically like solving murders on book tours, essentially.
Though that's a lot of the justification for getting her to these different places.
There'd be like stops.
Yeah, there'd be like a third of the season would be Cabot Cove, her town.
And then to shake it up, she'd like and then the third would be like New York City.
She's dealing with some publishing industry stuff.
Someone's adapting once it once a season, someone's adapting something and then she's dealing with a Hollywood kind of murder.
And then there'd be like tour stops or like a niece's wedding.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, because otherwise, how do you like how do you keep it small town charm?
But then don't have like you're not stuck in small town for every to do.
How many seasons were eleven?
Is that right?
Twelve.
So that's 12 seasons, 264 episodes and four post series movies.
Movies.
So many murders.
So many murders, yes.
In fact, I'm wearing a shirt.
Yeah, nice.
I killed them. I killed them all.
That is a popular online joke is that she was actually she was a slash and drain.
And it was her doing it, which is which is actually a theory I don't subscribe to.
I actually think it's a little bit more metaphysical than that.
I think she is sort of such an entity and it's such a force for good.
She was sort of metaphysically drawn to these areas of immense conflict just before a murder was about to happen.
And it almost like she, you know, I think it was a lot more spiritual than that, where she just happened to be in these locations when there was so much tension in the town or so much tension in the place that it happened around her.
Wow. Yeah. So I have a very I've been with the show for a really long time.
So she's this guardian angel figure.
Yes. She can't stop it necessarily, but it's better that she be she's like there and planted on the ground and ready to go when shit hits the fan.
Exactly. Her role was usually to clear the name of an innocent person who had been wrongfully blamed by like an incompetent police force.
So again, these the shows are very rewatchable because the shows like running theme is like these police can't do a thing.
They just are arresting the wrong person on purpose just to wrap this up.
And so like a lot of this stuff sort of a lot of it really does just hold up to today.
Timely. Very timely. Yeah.
So there's a way that there's a there's a there's still a comfort to this show.
But yeah, it's it's it's writing can be a very solitary thing.
And so I think, you know, and definitely like experiencing podcast the right during this time was was because, you know, because theme parks were and are like super important to me, not just Disney, but just any any of the theme parks.
I grew up right outside of Gurney. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. For Six Flags, my sixth person as well.
And Universal, which obviously I'm going to get into on here with the universal original universal Orlando, Florida is my preferred anything like to anything now at all.
Yeah, for sure.
Almost to the point where I'm like, I almost can't go to the current Orlando because like I'm just so like, none of it's the same.
I'm too roller coasters every like taking over those sound stages.
This should be calmer and drier.
I was like, yes.
Well, you know, so I had the and I remember there was an episode we all brought this up, but there was the VHS tape that John Forsyte hosted.
Oh, yeah.
That we all know and love retail price at the time.
$40.
My parents had no choice but to pay.
We had to leave with it.
So I was like nine years old by Charlie.
I was like, no, I don't understand because no, because so this goes even further back because like the bug first hit me when like in 1989 when Disney MGM opened, they like John Ritter hosted a special.
I don't know if you all saw this.
Yes.
They, you know, forgive me.
I get because there was so many specials.
They've made like four specials when that I definitely remember John Ritter run around those been being in the boat that where that rocks back and forth.
He's getting hit by the wave.
Yeah.
So like, no, it was an important special in my house because I just was such a like movie kid at such an early age.
And this was like and it just made Disney MGM feel like so huge.
And so and John Forsyte is in that as well.
So he like crosses both like he joins the world kind of Angela Lansbury as well because she was such a universal person.
But she's also Mrs. Potts.
Yeah.
So her voice is playing.
They're still using the recordings of her because Mrs. Potts is like a big suited.
Mrs. Potts is a big lumbering teapot as tall as the beast.
Strange aspect of all these shows.
But yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
You have these sort of like like John Forsyte and Angela Lansbury really did like kind of cross this boundary between the two.
If you went to both parks around 91 or 92, you were like it there wasn't such a war on now.
You know, there was that there was a little reaching across the aisle.
Sure.
You viewed it all as one continuum.
I did.
Yes.
I was super into this John Ritter special, which is very I urge anybody at home to watch it because it's all on YouTube.
And it's the most 1989 thing you've ever seen.
It is like there's this opening act that they do down the main drag leading up to the Chinese theater.
Is it one of those where it's like there are 200 ladies with big feathered hats.
It's like all 40s Hollywood glamour.
Yes, exactly.
There was so much kickline stuff.
There was like Ann Miller.
They got her in a kickline.
Yeah.
And but they're like it's like Ann Miller and the Pointer Sister.
They were very Team Disney.
Yeah.
You can force them out of there.
Then we got the Golden Girl.
They were always pulling those Golden Girls out for DM.
So but then you got me into the VHS of the of the John Forsyte thing, which is probably the best way you could view unless you're finding something I did not.
Probably the best way you could view what Murder, She Wrote Mystery Theater actually was.
Some of the actual.
Yeah.
Well, queued up here.
You say you say John Forsyte's name three times and he appears.
Here's his intro.
I love the you know if you can play these for almost every universal OG attraction, which we're running out.
It's a curtain.
I know.
We are almost out of the original stuff.
I don't we've not done earthquake special effects.
Or maybe that might be an extra.
That one another.
Yeah.
They've named that three different times.
Like that was the span of the opera.
Then it was Gory gruesome grotesque horror makeup show.
And I've tracked all this.
I've tracked the decline to me.
It's so much more famous and popular now.
I'm sure.
But but like but not to me.
Yeah.
You know you like the original way.
But here you know I love handing it off to John Forsyte to do the succinct intro.
The succinct intro of the attraction so we don't have to.
So let's let him.
It's murder she wrote and it's post production time.
The most challenging drama of all takes place after the cameras stop rolling.
Editing.
That's true.
Recording dubbing special effects mixing.
They're just some of the elements that finalize each episode of Angela Lansbury's hit series.
Cut cut for us on the set.
But when we go into the heart of how motion picture history is made you the visitor will be the star.
It's great entertainment because Universal Studios Florida is lights camera action.
That could have been said at any point in the longest.
Never let an old fart like that do that now.
They'd never.
Oh yeah.
So great.
Like that's the end of a that's the end of the empire.
Especially I think yes.
Both parks I would say but especially universe what I remember like looking at like brochures in the hotel room when you go or in the hotel lobby when you went to Orlando in the 90s that you'd leave through that.
And yeah there's maybe the centerfold of it is back to the future the ride with big dinosaur in the center.
But like they also they take pages to show you all of the kind of elderly classic actors who made a point of being there who are now I can't but I feel like you know they're there was there like they were like oh yeah.
Well she was I'm not sure if she was at her line.
I know she was at Hollywood when they did something out there but yeah there was that type of like I think they had.
Yeah exactly all those type of you see a tribute was a thing you could do.
And yes and I would say Lucy was not in her prime.
I mean in the sense of popularity obviously she was sure.
I'm dead at that point.
It's all such that I when I think about Universal Florida 90 to 92 I think about like older ladies with kind of like you know like what's not pompadour but like you know just like yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah that kind of hair feels like very powder and maybe like maybe wig and maybe dye and like it was so much a part and that it all that and that you go in and it's all Schwab's pharmacy and it's all classic 50s 50s.
Yeah Golden Age of Hollywood you were saying like John Forsyth and Angela Lansbury kind of tied the parks together but the other thing that would tie them together was Golden Age of Hollywood.
And if you got an older actor who had seen the Golden Age of Hollywood they were set you know.
It was amazing like you could I mean I'm getting all blurry now I'm like I'm like Mickey Rooney was one of them.
But yeah yeah but I remember them being like because that's the other thing was you know you'd have like even this this video this VHS that was so expensive.
So neat.
Very stiff.
But children love rewatching stuff.
I did and I like what rewatched it so many times and now I'm like rewatching it and I'm like showing it to my friends them.
I was like I'm about to be on this you know show we're gonna have to you know catch up on this stuff.
I like John Forsyth he's like I'm like oh this was like my guy and then like I put it on and my friends are just like watching him go in 1861 Thomas Edison.
And I'm like I don't remember being how it opened.
And this is you as a child this is who you liked.
It's a theme park for children.
For children.
But this alleyway was for mom and dad and the grandparents Alfred Hitchcock at the one end and Angela Lamsbury at the other.
You know.
It's truly it's truly a bygone era and I almost want to say like you know like to anybody at Universal who's currently listening to this.
No I'm because like so my mom was visiting six months ago and she was like oh you know she knows she remembers she was like oh you love Universal.
I'm like did but she was like oh we'll go to Universal and then I was and then I was going through like what they currently got.
We were going to Universal Hollywood it's obviously different.
And then I realized I'm like well it's just a lot of herky jerky you know rollercoaster.
So we end up going to Disneyland because I was like there's just not a lot my mom could like do.
Yeah.
And then we ended up not doing it like because it was like well they can't really do the whole family much now because you the idea was that you were like you would do Jaws Back to the Future King Kong the Ghostbusters show.
And then you'd then you'd be like all right here's old Hitchcock he's gonna you know here's you know Shirley MacLaine she's gonna remember old hitch.
And you know and then you do the Mervishing Rose and it took seven minutes you could sit down in the cool like I just feel like there was.
And the tour is probably giving you a lot more that you know they're stressing more that like and this is where Music Man or Bye Bye Birdie was felt like they're reaching.
Now I think you go at the furthest back anything is there's psycho because it's just perennial classic but otherwise it's like Back to the Future is now like a classic film that's as old as they're.
That's as close as they bring up.
They're even mentioning it like I mean they'll mention it because it's like the Clock Tower is on the tour but like is it I don't even know if it's on the I haven't done the tour in a while but.
Kind of depends on what's filming.
Basically yeah exactly so.
Not a lot right now.
Well.
Yeah now you just I mean like they if I would like to if I was a tour guide now I might just break down and go like and recently we've been filming.
Look it's all in Atlanta okay.
We got nothing.
Nothing happens here all right.
We're doing the voice again.
The actors are on strike so we're.
Heroes.
We might be shooting like Hot Bench here or something some judge show but that's about it.
We can't take you in there.
The voice.
Oh look it's the sound stage and it has the voice set in it.
It has the voice and it's the voice for now until we bulldoze it to make more Nintendo.
Yes.
Probably.
But that was kind of the thing where you know you have.
You know you'd have these sort of attractions for everybody and I'm not trying to be like well you know don't chase the youth but I think that's sort of one of those things where it's like I don't know what like.
Your grandparents like if your grandparents were going to like take a kid to the universal park now.
Yeah.
Like I mean maybe they they probably just have to go on all the kids stuff.
Right.
Not to talk like you know Walt at the festival but like what could the parents do.
But it's kind of a little bit of that.
Like I think there was so much of a purge of that.
Well isn't both.
OK it's not.
Not to jump ahead but I believe I believe murders this murder she wrote attraction in Florida and the equivalent which is the like Foley stage and how we make sound effects.
The version of that in Hollywood both replaced by Transformers the ride.
So both of the like sit down process oriented these kind of like these these pleasant for everybody attractions replaced by one that like isn't quite for everybody.
Correct.
Well I mean why don't what Mike what you think.
Yeah I know.
Thanks for covering my well I will say that yes to transformable fuck you up but then it will break your heart.
Yes.
So so grandparents should endure the potential physical trauma in order to get to that because if like do you want to weep.
Do you want to.
And probably like the feelings of your whole life are coming to you in that Optimus Prime.
Yeah I mean I actually made my mom go on this a couple of years ago because I was like remember you love this Spider-Man ride when we went on in 2000 and she's like OK.
She did like it.
She remembers that.
And she went on and she hated it.
She was really upset by it.
Did she just know did she just hate it because it's worse than Spider-Man.
Was that what fed into it.
In arguably worse than Spider-Man.
That might have been it.
I would be honest if that was why.
But I believe that your tolerance for getting jerked around changed in 20 years.
Yeah.
It's kind of one of my things.
And I think you know you've said this Mike on several occasions where I'm like I'm just trying to stay fit so I can do these rides.
Yes.
As long as I can.
Yeah.
I'm like that's truly like I'm like because I'm seeing myself being like OK because my husband is like starting to tap out on some things where I'm just doing and I'm like great single rider line like not like sort of keeping the existential dread from my head every time he says something that he's like you know I think it might be done with Space Mountain.
I'm like cool I'll do a single rider then that's cool you just have a churro right here in this you know this Tomorrowland dump you know and then I'll just just go over here.
You're asserting that like you being done with Space Mountain does not make me be done with Space Mountain.
I'm not accepting my mortality.
This is not a marriage decision.
Yeah.
I will I will probably go through years of like secret pain before I like before I admit like I can't do Space Mountain anymore.
I think that's good though.
Yeah.
I think that's what I'm going to do too.
I think that's like that's a good that's like a will to live.
That's what I feel like it is the trade off is the joy you're robbed of like that's like what I would be robbed of that joy.
Yeah.
That would be of life would define.
And you can appreciate the landscape thing and the place making more.
This is going to willingly tap out.
I you guys knew I had family visiting and I think my my main tap outs were my brother went on the mummy and I'm like I don't do the mummy out here the last time I did it when it comes to the dead stop I got like slammed into the seat.
Fair.
That's fine.
My dad and brother were like we're going on the Matterhorn.
I'm like God speed.
I couldn't do that at 20.
Like I really like yeah yeah yeah.
I think then I was like a laughing at like my dad sure enough I met up with them afterwards he was like yeah I don't know everyone.
It's a room full of quitters here and so sad disappointing because like the Matterhorn hurts but it makes you feel alive.
So you have to go on it sometimes.
I'm not saying every time the other things make you feel that's not the only thing that makes you feel like one of the top 10 things that make you feel alive on this planet.
So did eating a very cold Mickey bar in the Plaza restaurant.
I don't like because you and I could go pretty hard together for a long day and I don't like hearing this from him.
I also thought it was interesting.
It's a hard thing to accept.
What Jason just said I was almost like meant to be followed by like a big applause or like you won the rap battle like cold Mickey bar in the plaza.
Probably not Tiffany chandeliers but in the style.
I know people at home are like going I agree.
Yeah absolutely.
You got some O's there.
Yeah.
September late September heat wave in Southern California that air conditioning strong.
Was it there?
It's been pretty cool lately.
It was hot.
It's any day I was at the size maybe the one day but like the day we were at first it was so hot it was so crowded.
It's kind of just a hot plate.
Yeah.
It's a hot planet.
All of it.
And California adventure like too.
Not the most certain parts of the most shape but that's San Francisco.
Man they're still figuring out the restaurant order.
That was brutal.
This is definitely the future of this podcast is definitely Jason going like oh but the heat.
Oh yeah.
The heat.
Well because the next five years.
I can barely enjoy the bench.
My agony is.
Because the next five years of like at least Disney is going to be like just restaurant development.
So it's going to be a lot of like all right well they're going to have to it's going to be pretty focused on that which you know better than no I think that I'm there's there's some restaurants that I'm like OK you could ask.
Sure.
You could add some more there.
There's some there's some stuff to balance out but yeah you do have to figure out the ordering can get a little chaotic.
Yeah.
Tiana's palace and San Francisco were like just slammed.
But then I'm sure that once that food arrived once that Instagrammable food arrived that it was some of the finest food you've ever consumed.
That was alright.
OK.
Yeah.
And it's and that's it's not like it's not going to get any better than that's all right because we know how these things are like they're they're they're watching these places for the first month.
And then we maybe our little ant man food starts to get a little less manicured a little less detail oriented.
Yeah.
So yeah my husband and I loved the Pym test kitchen and we just noticed we've like gone back we like went back a year later we were like this is not so Pym.
Mr. Pym's hands are not all over these items.
Get all normal.
Yeah.
Too busy fighting crime to focus on his kitchen.
Don't open a restaurant if you're not going to be there every day Pym.
Mr. Pym.
Jurassic Cafe and I was like oh we should go back to Jurassic Cafe.
Had a pretty good meal there at the open like around the time.
We've been saying you've been nuts about that one for years.
I have been nuts.
And the Jurassic Cafe is a good restaurant.
Getting rice and beans and mollo pork and arepas.
And this time it was the pork shredded pork dumped on a massive plate of rice and then handed to you.
I can't I'm I'm dial back dial back.
I'm surprised that you're surprised that the Jurassic Cafe is not of.
Oh I don't.
I was just it was just so crowded.
Look serves me right for me once and again and again shave on me.
I think as the restaurant sort of like sort of normalize out and you know maybe kind of do so.
So the snack carts are the ones that like always like deliver for me 10 times.
Oh sure.
I think the little cosmic eats outside of Guardians Tower always delivers with the like purple custard orb thing.
I always get that.
Oh I've never done it.
That's a dessert thing.
It's a dessert thing.
It's a little cards a little trolley just outside the tower and it's dumb getting the name wrong cosmic orb.
It's something like that.
It's like a giant cream puff.
Giant cream puff and inside is like really really really cold purple custard.
Was that all shade for Mike?
You don't know that's OK.
Oh no I said that's OK.
You don't know the name.
Oh OK.
I was like I went on here being like damn it a year ago I would have known.
I'm sure people out there are yelling with the name of the thing but nobody's had these orbs.
I have not had the orb.
No I had the orb once.
Yeah it was pretty good.
I'd say like yeah if you're in Avengers campus I would say like the shawarma and the orbs like just delivered 10 times.
The shawarma is good yeah.
Are they keeping up the shawarma?
I haven't had it recently but the last time I had it was good.
And then of course Ronto wrap is still good.
I think that's another like kind of short order thing where they do one thing.
Yes.
And they just pow pow pow pow pow.
Yeah.
They got a really limit.
It's got to be like original McDonald's as portrayed in the founder.
We do burgers and we do fries and let's not get too much more complicated.
No gumbo at Ronto's Roasters.
No please don't.
No matter what space gumbo name they come up with.
That does sound good.
Yeah yeah.
But it belongs in the hanger or whatever seven not the other one.
Let's okay back to Murder She Wrote a little bit.
Forsythe's introduction let you know that this is they're putting a couple of things together.
It's a kind of it's a making of Murder She Wrote experience but this is also the attraction in original Florida that is representing the post production process.
So the rooms are editing Foley and then sound mixing.
Like ADR.
ADR.
Yes because I was going to say that sounds very very dry but what that actually becomes is now people from the audience have to live do lines of these actors over the dial.
And it's a gag every time.
I'm telling you like I'm watching these and I found some other like just very poorly camcorder shot stuff and even then the comedy just bled through the screen to me.
I did this I went through this attraction twice as I was like I was thinking I was like nine.
Yeah my family did this.
I don't know what it is with like Illinois and driving to Orlando but we did we were like Aurora Illinois to like Orlando was like the thing to do.
I don't know what we were saying.
How many hours are you talking?
22?
From Schaumburg it's like 20 or 22 hours.
Yeah essentially.
Are we stopping?
Yeah.
Where are we stopping if we're stopping?
We stopped at like.
Tennessee?
Georgia.
We were always like I remember we always stopped at like once I started seeing I remember getting excited.
I remember getting excited to see Waffle Houses because then whenever we hit the Waffle House I was like we're close we're close we're close we're close.
Get me out of this car.
So like we were not just like so it was like me my brother my parents and my brother was littler and so like but we drove like with my aunt as well.
Like so she it was a really like they feel like they just don't do family vacations like this.
Hopefully people fly.
But yeah there I remember like specifically we went down and I just saw my aunt on the book tour and I was telling her that I was going to be talking about the murder she wrote show.
Oh wow.
And she was like oh my god I can't believe it because she so this was this long ago like she got like so she came down with us and like we were literally like so young and little that like in the car this is like an old station wagon like she was in the back seat and like my brother and I were like in the wheel wells of the car basically like sleeping.
And we were like so like a cat down there and it was being like so like hilarious at the time but now I'm just like that didn't need to happen.
Didn't need to happen.
But then yeah but then as soon as we hit Universal Orlando which I had been like you know psyching myself up for because it had like back to the future I'm a super back to the future guy my dog's name is Marty.
And that is like I remember just being so keyed up by the time we got in there and I didn't know I didn't I didn't watch murder she wrote really like I had seen like a few episodes with like my grandma I didn't really it didn't really pop out but I known Angela Lansbury from Bedknobs and Broomsticks.
And I think at the time yeah Beauty and the Beast was out.
Oh sure.
Just those that's huge for kids.
She's a legend at that time already.
Oh my god yeah and so like and so I did it like twice like I think we went two days in a row and my parents were both just like oh great well we did that I don't know if we need to go a second time the second day and I was like oh no we must go again.
I had to really learn the process of this.
Yeah take notes about the post-production.
I did I did.
So it's a longer show 25 minute show.
Yeah I feel like theme park shows they try to keep on the shorter side nowadays.
It was so I so I when I was catching up on this I caught up on this and the MGM studio sort of analog which was at the time monster sound show with Martin Short and Toby Chase and they did all three like at the same time and I remember like I remember the video that like they were rushing
for like nine minutes.
So you're not because you aren't you aren't moving it's all in that's all in one theater as opposed to this where you get what you get like a mini show and one exactly and you move you move all the way down to the end of the row all the way to fill in every
you do it again which like I feel like just just the having to move spices it up and give some energy to them and that you like that one host isn't sweating it for the full 25 solid for 10.
I'm excited.
Yeah.
These are three actors a day who got to do like a real meal.
Orlando improv actors are eating.
This was that's very exciting would think at the at the time here to maybe introduce it a little further.
I got one more.
You're right that it's hard to find really good quality of this thing where you're dealing with a lot of camcorder but you're helped out by the John Forsyth video and you're also helped out by the 1990 Universal Studios Florida electronic press kit which gives you full frame footage of the show but also have a little bit of Angela Lansbury introducing it herself.
Here and she explains some of the premise.
I am so delighted that you've agreed to help out and become our executive producer.
You know it takes more than 200 people to make a single episode of murder she wrote and of course the executive producer is responsible for absolutely everything.
Which that statement is it is it is either totally true or the executive producer literally never is goes to the set or is part of one meeting or it's the worst scumbags in Southern California or that or just like the celebrity who they needed to sell they needed their name on to sell the show and they would not begin to have time to participate in either it's it's already on Larry Sanders who's the executive producer.
It's it's already on Larry Sanders is doing it's all on his back or they don't ever show up at all.
I'm so happy you played that I've been like literally was like my whole body just like yeah I was like so rocking out.
But like it is because it is like it's perfect that like we're executive producers us the tourists in the audience because for some EPS you might as well be like just some tourists from Aurora Illinois like for as much as involved as you were.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah Oh thank you you're you know Reading.
It's good like that's why I came back like on the second day I was like I was like no Angela requested me I'm her executive producer I need to check in make sure the show's still going okay yeah maybe the new person maybe the new people aren't as like effective as I was nine years old you know at producing this show.
Yeah yeah I'm on a tight leash and it really is funny that like the transformer stage is in there because it gives me the same rush as like Optimus because she's like.
I'm so delighted you're going to be my executive producer I'm like I will executive produce this show anytime thank you so much I had such a great time.
I'm comfortable is everything I can't believe we had to do a satellite uplink again.
I was like thank you so much for being in again yeah I know I'm telling you like this or there's there's something to this realm this this epicenter of universal Orlando where it's like the good vibes are there like the sort of like affirming the cell right right right is there your bravery has saved the show.
Well done executive producers.
Yes it filled me with that much love and watery eyed joy and that is why I dragged everybody back again to learn Foley again and ADR again.
Your family is still like that's something called Foley invented by Jack Foley.
They go my god there are rides here.
Yeah my brother is just like jaws jaws jaws he said we're going to do jaws.
I was like yeah but like you know I'm just going to check earlier in the day make sure she's okay make sure she's got everything she needs.
Nice fruit basket in the dressing room everything that's here liking do we like bananas are we off bananas right now.
I was thinking that like old school universal wait times chalkboard just get higher and higher with wait times on back to the future jaws.
You emerged from the second helping of Mercheroad.
I was like no that's first.
Oh 80 minutes for jaws huh.
It's right there when you walk in may as well start the day there.
This is a cycle with my brother that would repeat because like they would like from like as time went on I would like leave him at some place that was sort of like kid appropriate and cool and then I would go do some like mature woman thing.
Like so it was like it would be like so I remember vividly going to the I was like my mom was like take your brother to go see D3 the mighty ducks and I was like sure and I left him there and I went across the theater and I saw the first wives club.
I had a great time and she was mad that I would leave him there because he added me out but yeah.
Let me bring up something not to veer away from Florida but while we're talking murder she wrote in the universal theme park world something that would have brought together your and your brother's interests.
On the universal tram tour which I did jaws as mentioned and murder she wrote live together because you do the jaws experience you're in New England what's called Amity Island at the top of it and then you're veering your way out of there and you're still in the little pleasant New England vibe.
And you as a tour guide if I've now played my clip about because you got a long path out of there you really got to like fill it and they give you the clips to fill it so one is about how the shark the shark the shark is not working.
I repeat their shark is not working you get a shy.
And hit.
What's that.
Serotonin hit just now.
Oh good.
Yeah.
Richard Dreyfuss impersonating an intercom.
But then then is the part where you get to say but you know some less scary stuff happen around here because this same location was the town of Cabot Cove on murder she wrote and I that was a part that I look forward to doing as a tour guide because like you've done your scary stuff you've heard your you've heard your John Williams jaws score and then so it's maybe the audience is a little like freaked out or they're just like energized amped up and then you get to give them a little pleasant little bit of a
I get to like get calm as they get calm and it would it wouldn't make anyone laugh that's not a laugh moment that jaws and murder she wrote of the same area but it but like calm smiles from everybody in that trance I really liked watching the wave of people like all murders well that's nice that's nice and one of the top five TV show things that you've heard about.
Like the murder song is pretty untouchable it's a banger I don't skip it I never skip I never skip a very calm song to call a banger it's a yes sure it bangers can be what's your top what's everyone's top five real quick greatest American hero oh god I don't know if I'm gonna do all five but I'm sure we're gonna do all five.
Say your definitive list now I'm going cheers is number one I think yeah start to track the next generation is number two. Yeah taxi. Taxi's a pretty good theme yeah. I'm a twin piece person so it'd be the twin piece theme. That's really good. Very good. I'm gonna go with the
There's a show nobody knows called give me a break with Nell Carter and that had two theme songs the first one's kind of inessential but the second one is done by Jay Graydon my favorite studio musician Steely Dangai look up the song greatest song so the second give me a break song.
Every other sitcom in the 1980s was called give me a break at some point. Every network had one. So this is give me a break ABC okay I want give me a give me a break CBS. Yeah I had a lot of respect for Murder She Wrote as a kid because I knew that was my grandparents' name.
favorite that Matlock yeah and I like the theme song and I would kind of have watched these shows. What's that? Saying you have respect for the funny way to put it. It is like a like I respect my elders kind of show it. Yeah the shows radiates with the goodness that's in the
that's like not and it's not this like oh the way things were sort of Reaganite with fake goodness where you're like oh yes this is evil underneath but like there's like an actual like it holds up she holds a fairly open minded views on everything and I think that's the thing that's really cool about this show.
like oh the way things were sort of Reaganite with fake goodness where you're like oh yes this is evil underneath but like there's like an actual like it holds up she she holds a fairly open minded views on everything like there's not like a lot of like her being like she helps everyone.
helps everybody yeah I so I watched I was gonna watch the pilot and then jump ahead like five or six years because I think that's a decent way to see like how TV shows kind of change and stuff then I found out the pilots part it's a two parter oh yeah so I watched the second episode and I was really enjoying it until the very end the conclusion of the two part pilot is insane the solution.
it's the one with the pool lights yes the pool lights and the plot of the count of Monte Cristo comes into play heavily it's like she and she makes a lot of deductive like it's a lot of jump to conclusions where it's like you put that to get like like someone references the count of Monte Cristo to the killer and who's like a friend of hers which would be a recurring theme where it'd be like she'd have to because murder sure would end like one of two ways it would always be like a freeze frame and it would be like a freeze frame on her
just laughing like and then they'd freeze and then they play the and it would be again huge serotonin hit but then like a third of the time it would be a sort of a grim ending where she'd have to arrest you know she was gonna have to aid in the arrest of of a beloved person or would be like a very unfortunate situation and then it would just be her sort of shaking her head solemnly and would freeze on that and there'd be sort of a long sting yeah and then the then the end credits but in that yeah this one is similar where you
like she nabs the guy because like he has a background that's sort of kind of Monte Cristo is yeah yeah and but then it does have a freeze frame at the on the train oh she did on the am track yeah she makes like Adam West Batman deductions sometimes where she draws just an insane conclusion that's absolutely correct and you're like well wait a minute it's like and gets there and like you just care about both of them so much you're just like yes sure
she's a genius thing yeah it also it was reminding me watching it now it shares a lot with Colombo in that the star of the show is acting circles around everyone else doing the like yes well I work at the office you know like I'm doing kind of stiff TV acting though but
Colombo's full of fucking killer actors. So does Murdasheer wrote in Murdasheer. Correct. That's what Colombo has like John Cassavetes shows up Robert I guess I was gonna say Robert Colombo. Jason does Tom Bosley not mean anything to you? Well Bosley's not in the earlier episodes. Bosley's not. It takes it's so funny. Ned Beattie is in the pilot he's great. It's funny because like Murdasheer wrote is one of the like I talk about Murdasheer wrote the way a lot of people talk about shows now
I'm like just hang on till episode 11 it's great like and you just like because the first 10 are just like rough and then they find their way but I would say once you hit season two that show just hits like season two and three hit everything is a hit and like it is this hit like so there is like so there's these sort of tiers where like obviously Angela Lansbury is just doing the circles then you have like a lot of just like just haven for bit parts but then you've also got a lot of
like in Colombo where there's like a lot of all the guest star names are either young folks on their way up or like old folks kind of on their way like sort of out of retirement. Oh sure. And you'll get like there's like one episode in season two called Menace Anyone that is young Bryan Cranston and a young Linda Hamilton. And it's like the mashups are insane. Yeah. There's my favorite episode of all time is a season two one called Jessica Behind Bars. I've tweeted
about this show kind of once a year because I'm just like begging you could watch it on its own. It's a bottle episode where she like does like a writing course at a women's prison and then like someone is murdered the prison and they go into lockdown and then like literally like the prisoners like riot and take over the prison. Whoa. And she has to solve the murder before like the National Guard comes in and wipes everyone out. They firebombed. No like then the like tonight on murder she wrote of this episode is 30 seconds.
It's more exciting than die hard. You're like what? And it's like you're screaming at people and people screaming at her and the guest stars and it's like Adrian Barbeau, Yvonne DeCarlo and you've got oh my gosh Vera Miles from Psycho and like just name after name Eve Plum, Jan Brady. Yeah.
Wow. And she's like but she's rocking kind of like she's a prisoner. She's like yeah I'm a prisoner. And it's great. Yvonne's Eve Plum. Fuck. The audience is a whole pooting and hollering at Yvonne DeCarlo. Yvonne DeCarlo is like playing like the sort of like crooked chef. Like she's like the chef who's been like skimming and like like the meals are like cruel and unusual because she's been like selling off the menu to like better people. And she's like she's like she's like the chef.
She's kind of like wrapped into it and she's kind of like crabby lunch lady. She's like yeah what are you going to do about it. Like it's great. I don't think I've ever seen a non Munster's performance from Yvonne DeCarlo. That's the thing. If you want to see Yvonne DeCarlo like outside of Munster's. Wow. Wow. She's freaking it. I might not recognize her. Yeah. Jessica behind bars season two. But like you'll have so you'll have these like these casts that are just so so great. And then actually speaking of that was where as we're recording this hopefully they are currently.
Somewhere in town negotiating sag after sag. Yeah. Hopefully soon. This is something that was that has kind of come to light a little bit more lately. Something that Angela Lansbury basically did for. She basically used murder she wrote as a way to ensure sort of aging or ailing actors and actresses to continue their sag benefits.
Like so you see actors that you like. Oh I'm not the Cairo like or show up in one episode like because back then you do one episode of a big hit network show. Right. That would be enough to like extend your health benefits. That would be enough to like keep your house. That would be enough to like kind of keep you around. And it kind of became this open secret that like if you sort of were in the business and you kind of been around and you were in trouble. Find get word to Angela and she'd get you.
Just five lines on murder she ran so she kind of used this as a way to shuttle many many many older actors and actresses who had not worked in years decades maybe. I'm like welling up a little. It was so yeah that is beautiful. It was beautiful. No. So so she was something she actively did and I think this became a little bit more known after her passing. And which was just this last year she hung up for such a long time. It's an amazing person. But no the Drew Carey.
I think I could be a little bit more active for time. Truly. She was doing Drew Carey level stuff where she like again but it was kind of a similar like no no thanks needed. Like she just kind of wanted like she  just had this immense power within the show and she was like great.
You know so and so to be in this thing you know and then there'd be like kind of more up and coming younger folks like there it would be a mix of like this young star Jessica Walter who was like the victim the killer and a suspect across like she played like.
I love this about old shows like this where they would just come back and they'd a new character.
Oh yeah. Robert Culp. A lot of Columbo. Culp was in so many Columbo. I just finished watching it because I had been such a murder she wrote person and I was like all right we'll give Columbo a shot and I got like so obsessed and then I was like Robert Culp again.
Amazing. Different guy. Different guy. And that happens you see that on the law and orders a lot with New York actors or Broadway actors where they're like yeah there's a victim one season a murderer the next a lawyer the following season. Beautiful. Beautiful. And it's like hey they got health insurance.
Yeah. So I mean that's the thing. So like that. So as like. So what she would usually kind of do for some of her closer friends was they would be regular townspeople in Cabot Cove. So you'd be in like three or four episodes a season towards the end seasons eight through 12.
She leaves Cabot Cove and she moves to New York City and you can tell they start doing like the declining ratings. Let's change the music up thing. So they do like they hit that like early 90s saxophone every time they do like a scene change like they do this sort of saxophone like jazzy sexy sax version of the theme.
And it's very jazzy. Watch night see it's very it's a little you're starting to get to that. They sort of get a little shaky. But in that time that's when like she had she kept a lot of folks you could tell. And there's a and there's a few actors who you can tell like have maybe maybe serious ailments. I think one actress had like survived a stroke. And but there is like a character who like is sort of like she runs a shop in town and she has like maybe two every time she goes to the mall.
And every time they do a Cabot Cove episode there's like she has three lines and they see her and like she goes out of her way to just say hello to her at a shop. And that's it. And that's all she does. And then got her like insured for like the rest of her days. And it was an amazing thing.
So this is this is an attraction starring a hero hero hero and more so than Optimus Prime even.
Well that's I put it to you. I put it to you. He might be good. I was probably might be getting health insurance for the other transform. Yeah we know about that.
They're unionized. Yeah yeah the other.
Jessica Fletcher could find the all spark if it was Miss A.
I she potentially could. And I and this is it's it's funny back back to the to the to the to the attraction here. There is I don't know how much you're able to like see through the thing but there is a sort of a what's it that they have to get in this.
The black pearl. I have to admit it's a little confusing from camcorder. Yes but there. Yeah I mean this is a question I had for you in general is like the if knowing the show so well.
How do you think. How well do you think they pulled off a mini mystery that has to work in this theme park show setting.
They had like great because they have like two and a half minutes of time. Not an hour.
So what they did so they had like so like from what I can remember the plot of this is there's they're looking for the black pearl which is wild because when Pirates of the Caribbean the movie came out.
I was such a like fan of this ride. They were like it's called the curse of the black pearl. I was like well I can't do that because the black pearls part of murder which has been gone for a decade.
I was like well like I don't know like how do they like do they make a deal with like universal because like that's pretty famous.
The black pearl from that from that show. Like no one major IP. The people I was with on the trip.
So every time like I see the parents of the Caribbean or I see it like on you know flip through on Disney plus I'm always just like black pearls.
Stolen.
It's stolen. It's stolen.
Acting like you guys.
Stolen.
One MacGuffin.
Yeah it's.
She goes into this creaky haunted house which seemed to be like the thing both this and Monster Shannon show did where they were like person enters a spooky sort of manner and they kind of bump into creaky things.
Because we got a lot of opportunity. What this really is setting up is doing all of the foley.
And you know you could do the foley you know for a scene that's her talking to the shop owner but then you wouldn't have like the box that you tumble with all the junk in it or the howling wind or so.
Or she that she bumps into a suit of armor.
Yeah.
So you.
They clearly need to set up a scenario where all the foley gadgets.
Yeah there's like a Zoltar like fortune teller machine.
In the house.
Yeah it's in the house and like and they're never interacted with it's funny because like then she goes in and she's and then like there's people that she's clearly already interacted with.
Because she was sort of arriving at that moment that's in the last final minutes of every episode where she's been around she kind of knows what everybody's situation is there's this sort of you know this beautiful alluring woman Leilani.
And they're all kind of on the hunt for this black pearl and someone has been murdered and the black pearl has been stolen and then there's this like nasty Dr.
Ashbrook or something and make his name is.
And then.
And then there's like the local sheriff character so it's pretty true to life and then it ends with.
With like a big guest star gag in the form of Mr.
Tom Selleck which it doesn't show up in the John Forsythe thing.
OK yes.
Now explain this to me because it was a little hard to parse the full full context thing.
There is some joke made and we'll talk about like the hosts the like editors and all these characters.
Yeah.
Earlier in the thing there is a joke about what if we could put Tom Selleck in it.
Because Tom Selleck being like the the go to for hunk at this time it seems to be the context.
But then I honestly in watching the camcorder version couldn't tell when Selleck shows up is that footage for another thing or did they they shot custom Tom Selleck footage for this.
Wow.
To my understanding like it's not from an episode.
So why does he show up.
Well in the editing sequence the editor is showing like here we have a shot of Jessica reaction reacting and there could be it changes based on what she's looking at.
So it cuts to a young couple making a kiss.
Yeah.
Or a gun.
A gun.
This is like a very like this is a very like film school kind of like your your little editing 101.
They do that demonstration of like change the the significance of the shot by what they're looking at.
So that's a that's a good little genuine.
Communicating ideas with visual.
Like it's yeah by the time I got to film school and they were like it's called the Kuleshov effect.
I was like I understand.
It's from the Murder She Wrote Show.
Into the mystery theater.
I was the executive producer for one episode.
I had a little film experience.
I'm a little above this.
I have been an executive producer already.
But one of those things is or you could get to Tom Selleck.
They kind of swoon over.
So it's a callback at the very end of the show.
So it's supposed to be just like a gag.
It's not previous.
It's not it's all it's just like oh we could do Tom Selleck and then she's interrupted by like you got to go to the next sound stage.
So you don't see the shots you're to kind of just think like oh she's making a Tom Selleck reference.
And then by the time you get to the end and you see everything pieced together when Tom Selleck shows up it's like oh they really got him.
Wow.
And what what does he do.
Why is he there.
Is he a character.
Is he because she's in a.
OK.
You're saying this is the end.
I'm sorry I'm asking basic plot questions but boy is the footage not great.
I feel like this is I feel like this was so lost in the burning of the Library of Alexandria.
But like this is like I'm like the one surviving person who recalls this ride.
Yes who was a child who went and because other kids were there of your age then.
But maybe it didn't like your brother didn't land but it land you remember.
I'm there I was in it I absorbed it I chose to let all of this information and I am the keeper of the information.
Yeah there are not copy in the way that you can watch the whole Hitchcock show.
You can see the wandering around the show area.
Real.
Yeah.
So this but it's that so you're in a she's it's essentially cutting straight to the end of an episode she's in a creaky she solves the mystery.
But then it's these characters established but then sell it.
Why what is he.
So in a regular murder she wrote episode we kind of mentioned before like how sometimes there's like this little epilogue where she just then goes to meet a friend and it's a freeze frame laugh.
And that's kind of what this is which is like she solved the mystery and she's like all right I'm expected somewhere.
And then she goes to dinner and then in the new meetup with Tom Selleck who did show up on the show because she did a crossover two parter with Magnum P.
I.
Which in which Jessica Walter was on it.
Wow.
So this was so there is a Magnum P.
I were she's in it and then there's a murder she wrote where he's in it.
Oh so the universes have tied together this.
I had to like hunt down Magnum P.
I to like understand the first half of this episode.
Oh yeah.
I was like I was like I had a good time with it but I was like I'm not it's not he's not one of my guys.
So like I was like a little bit like well let's just get to the her stuff.
While we're talking plot the Black Pearl thing is ultimately solved in this pretty silly way where she's after the Black Pearl and then the Black Pearl is discovered inside a baseball.
Yeah.
Peels apart like.
And then everyone's like oh my god it's the Black Pearl and she goes is it.
And then she drops it it shatters.
Oh and it's a fake out fake Black Pearl.
And whoever the real killer is has the real pearl on them.
Oh they have they from the farthest reaches of my memory they did not set up like why it was important that we then have a fake because they never there's no proceeding stuff like there's no set up.
What's the Black Pearl also.
It's just a big black pearl.
Yeah.
It's a gem.
It's just something that somebody wants it's not like the proof that somebody did something.
No no no it's like a Maltese Falcon.
It's a yeah yeah it's like a little just thing the dreams are made of.
Yeah it's a McLaughlin and it's like yeah which I feel like that that also is one of the most famous like throw it on the ground and shatters and you know it's fake.
It's a yeah.
Yeah.
So they also did that because they needed another with the real reason they did because they needed another thing to Foley and they needed something else to happen for the ADR moment to happen later because all the characters sort of react to it.
Oh yeah.
Shattering and it's very like upsetting to a lot of people.
Sure sure sure.
OK.
So like also just functional stuff in the show.
Let's just like room by room in a little bit.
Yes.
Editing.
Editing is stretched.
You get the little demonstration of like what reaction shots could do.
You also get this kind of odd really specific of its time that like they didn't put the powder on the shoe so we can paint we can use our digital machine to put and you're like what what could this possibly have been what proto CGI.
It's like MS Paint probably.
Yeah.
Like it's something very simple.
What you get what unites all of the stages I would say is that they all the actors and all of them make the choice that post production people are all kind of bitter and kind of Brooklyn.
They're working class Brooklyn people.
This feels like the origin of the Universal Studios New Yorker which is like the very famous the street folk.
Yeah.
They're all kind of doing this.
Come on.
Like there's a lot.
Yeah there's a lot.
They're they're doing the thing which is like they need you to hurry up.
Hurry up get in.
Like you know so there's not a lot of sweet stuff.
They're kind of like hurry up get in.
It's also something that like a lot of performers can do quite easily.
It's not an it's not a you can kind of just kind of usher folks.
Like some like thin slurry like you're from Finland.
What's a really specific dialect.
It's not very specific.
It allows someone to make a choice.
It's nice and broad.
And I think the thing that was kind of cool for you know me who was like kind of like I had done Disney so much and then I did the sort of step up into Universal which is sort of like you go from being a kid to being a preteen.
And when you're a preteen and that's kind of what universal sort of is is this sort of like OK you've aged up a little bit from Disney and you're going to get these rides that are a little more intense.
You're going to get sort of humor that's a little more.
Oh wow.
He said that.
Knowledge violence.
They acknowledge romance.
If not sex.
Right.
It's a little body.
Little.
Like Jessica Fletcher.
Jessica Fletcher.
Big body.
So Jessica Fletcher throughout the show.
So when we meet her in the pilot she's lost her husband.
She's like this widow who was a schoolteacher and then she just she wrote this book and then her nephew her grown nephew like reads it and then like submits it to a publisher without asking her.
And they're like I think it's fabulous.
Why don't you come down to New York City.
And she's like always in over her.
She's like oh I didn't want anyone to read that.
So she's got this sort of like throughout she has many suitors throughout the run of the show.
Some regular some one offs but she never goes further than like a little sort of dalliance a little like sort of anytime they get close enough she's just like oh I just wouldn't be right to Frank's memory.
Like it was like it's a little they were very clear about where it would kind of begin and end.
Always refuses to drink.
She was very teetotaling but like not in a judgmental way.
Well that's what you want.
Yeah yeah it's not because you shouldn't either.
She was just like oh you have whatever you have your third martini I will have a little sharing.
That's like 60s Batman.
He was the orange juice.
No that's right.
He does he is judgy though because in the movie there's that part like oh yeah there may be drinkers Robin but they are also people too.
Well but you know hey I love that I love that.
They all are very everybody is also very like frizzy hair and very big glasses like what I'll read to the back row is kind of like somebody in a like a nerdier profession is maybe what they're convinced somebody's in dark rooms a lot.
So everybody they all look like MTV's Kennedy.
I was going to I was I was saying like I think because this was happening across like literally across the street from Ghostbusters the show like everyone here is doing either Rick Moranis or Annie Potts from like they're doing like a Janine Malmas or they're doing a Louis Tully in visual form probably.
And I guess they're a little bit of a green there too but yeah you know Rossi's they seem stressed.
That the show isn't they need you young nine year old Adam Sasse to produce the show.
They're a little this is irregular but you know it's not so uncommon I mean to like portray all put you know I'm an editor to some extent and I like to portray all post people as like you know the malcontent.
You know like it is constantly stressed and peeved and like but it is there is kind of a truth to that like as the last step of the process that everything gets like piled on and like you know I'll start we're running out of money and you got to do it quick and fast now and like say you're going to get up a long hours and.
It's a frenzied nature to it.
Yeah yeah they aren't wrong about that and feeling like underappreciated maybe even more so at that time because editing was so clunky big old machine oh yeah like the boy slow and.
And you had to do a lot of stuff.
Live like I mean there was I mean I think at the end they make a reference to like I can't do a live.
Next.
I don't understand.
Well I mean that is universal nonsense I think because that's all it's the same format as the Harry and the Henderson's thing which we talked about years ago on here but that the construct that like we're shipping this out to the network but the sound dropped out so we just have to so the actors have to go on it becomes Saturday Night Live for a second.
Well you.
But only like one scene only one act like in what world is that specific technical problem.
They eventually cut that specific because there were too many like precocious 10 year olds in the crowd going like how would it did you made a tape do that.
Explain exactly how that audio track goes away.
But the videos fine how would it only be the video and not the audio why wouldn't you just like stop airing the show entirely.
Why do we have Angela's dialogue but we don't have this other character.
It's a stereo.
Two tracks.
I guess yeah they mixed everybody else on the right but that doesn't seem wise so I think you got a center at all.
I mean but God bless it then becomes a perfect way yes to get like you know bad mom and dad actors to like miss their cues slightly.
Did you guys ever do a version of this I bet we talked about this in special effects stages but it was a long time ago I don't remember.
The like where you volunteered for that specific for I think kids could only do fully and I think kids are doing them the voice parts.
My brother and I were perpetually like.
Big brave kids not scared of nothing except when it was like hey why don't you be on superstar TV.
Or how about you join in this then and then I was like I will disappear into this couch right now like I'm going to raise my hand down.
Yeah.
Don't have hands as far as your day I was driving to this like I was driving here and I was like I was getting the like the anxiety of like superstar TV or I was like.
I'm just going to like go do this fake Gilligan's Islands episode I'm like get in there and I'm part of the show.
That's how this feel being on podcast.
That is a blank part where they it's pre recorded Mike Scott and Jason and then I say something.
And you know you're like here's your home VHS tape like yeah we give you a copy.
I'm going to tell you at the end this is not for public release we did this just for you I swear to God I would be fine with that.
I would be like that's for everybody that's for everybody but like I this was just for me.
You know what's interesting is I feel completely the same way I still have kind of a divide.
Like I've lost nerves and that I can do this podcast I've been in a bunch of sketches and stuff and there's nothing that stresses me out about that.
But anything that resembles broadcast action that like still and there's less of that in the world now but like the level of I get to be in several Conan sketches in front of the audience.
And that is like fuck me you're fucking like yeah like like if you have one line it is scary it is so much scarier than this talking for hours.
Like any construct of broadcast which I felt doing these shows were like a little red lights going to come on and they're saying it so fast and you're like wait but where and what if it doesn't and what and like everybody I'm going to fuck it up and everyone will the whole show will come to a stop and everyone will point and laugh at me.
It's just different.
Any things with this feel.
There's also a slight addition to that that's that's that's a little that the nuance to this that also is more my fear because I've gotten up I've done book tours I've done where it's just me speaking I'm doing like Ted talks on this book and I've.
Again like I've done a bunch of stuff like I should not be nervous about this I think I think the the specifically the theme park who wants to be who would like to be here.
It's the act of you have to raise your hand everyone's going to see you raise your hand and if you if they pick that that person to the that other person then you have to like do that slow lowering of your hand and I go you didn't get picked there is something to that there is something that.
Yeah like I threw my hat in the ring you put yourself out there myself out there again at nine was not doing in life I was only brave at the theme park not at my school or in my life but.
I think you're three can relate but yes yes.
Bravery.
I'm like okay I'm like so I'm only brave here and I was like but there is an element of that where it's like you're putting yourself out there you throw your hat in the ring and.
And it's like you weren't and then everyone saw it's the everyone saw everyone saw everyone knows but then but then that's all of course that's all made up nobody saw but you feel like everybody saw exactly yeah yeah.
But that hey to that end if you came to the Vegas groove blender and I didn't pick you to come spin the wheel of my yeah and if that's how you felt you felt like everybody saw and you would like I don't look it was it was random so now I found this is a there's probably three people who I hope feel better now yeah.
Blue 30 saw you but we didn't.
He knows.
He's so you put up the signal yeah you didn't get picked.
What a big disappointment for you.
You're you're all alone just farting root beer there is this sort of like little great kazoo that sort of lives on our shoulders that's like well that didn't go well.
You tried and you thought you thought you could do something to me.
Yes guess you're invisible maybe they didn't see you at all we should call you and they rejected you would not have worse that time.
Nice try dumb dumb.
Next time I should do us a favor and just keep your hand down.
Don't go anywhere don't go in public anymore yeah I know that's this is that's absolutely all psychologically there and in this kind of thing.
But then so they don't know what they're setting people up for the stress they're causing children but that you know and I feel like I have less to say about Foley Foley is like we've seen these Foley shows you turn the cranks and you back the big sheet with the wind.
I feel like I'm maybe the most interested in stage three in this ADR zone.
Yep and I maybe I'm saying that because the video that I watched that's on YouTube I am 90% sure that the person at that stage is Paula Pell.
You mentioned when we were just DMing that this was yes this was an early role for Paula Pell.
Great longtime SNL writer star later of girls but also the she did a qui be which was a murder she wrote.
Oh right.
Maple worth.
Maple worth maybe.
Yes.
So that's interesting that that like and I and I found that when she was doing press for that show and they're asking why murder she wrote what's the murder she wrote.
Well one of my pre SNL I worked at the murder she wrote show and like lived this whole murder she wrote experience.
Yeah yeah I think she was on like Seth Meyers or she was talking about like that she got the call to audition for SNL like from.
Like from the murder she wrote.
She was like wow.
The middle of doing like oh right I wanted to get in here we need to go right here you you you over here over here you you you.
And then like she's good at it.
And she was yeah there is a it has to be her in this video because we did see it we were we were trying to find clips and not.
Again this is no shade on the other performers who did that but like there was something about what she was doing.
A first of all she wasn't doing a Brooklyn like she wasn't doing this sort of.
Oh yeah.
Everybody else was sort of doing like an impression of the Simpsons impression of John Travolta.
They were all kind of do well yeah I should come over here like like no like there's a little Tony dance in there like that's a it's a it's a lot of things.
Yeah I once but hers was like kind of just she's doing a polyp thing.
Yeah.
And like she's just confidently being like she's doing like frenzied.
I read everybody in OK.
But you can tell it's lived in she's comfortable in her own skin.
She's it's just her speaking.
She's got that right of like mundane ity just like a regular person.
She like she's very good at which already she was polishing as the because I think she was in Orlando.
Just doing like what is all the Orlando stuff.
I think she was on the adventure club adventures club like whatever she was part of that show.
But she would also be like the mom in sketches for M.M.C. and all that.
So she's already like she's done what she does on TV.
You know before SNL even.
Well she's doing like she's I mean she's putting in the yards on on on so much.
Yeah.
Probably just like completely second nature.
So by the time you do get to the SNL stage you've got that sort of like again doing it must be like it must have been almost frankly almost nothing to get up in front of like Lauren Michaels and have this like kind of flat like reaction that he sometimes does with folks when like.
However many damn times a day she's like looking at like just half board Orlando tourists who maybe are just trying to get out of the sun.
Some are sleeping.
They don't know murder she wrote.
They don't care how a show gets people from other countries who don't know the show.
So they're just like blank staring at it.
Like just like my fussy brother who's just like jaws is happening right now.
And he was just like when is this over 20 minutes.
And was a dream probably.
She's just doing it.
Yeah I'm sure she's I mean working like that kind of crowd that must just be the like the coldest crowd on earth.
Yeah.
Like it just must be like you know it must vary.
You probably like it got a great crowd.
There's a lot of great you know people love stuff.
They have really good planned laugh lines especially with the stuff.
But that's got to be touch and go.
There's got to be certain ones that I mean from my tour guide experience is definitely that we're just like there's not one today.
Nobody's given me anything.
So you can counter it's a couple of things.
It's like at least in that job it's tough audiences.
So it steals you up against that.
But also you kind of I was so nervous shy never done anything performance wise when I got that job.
So it also was helpful for me to go.
Some audiences are nothing.
Yes sometimes they just aren't paying attention and my every little tick or even they don't notice tiny fuck ups that I would typically be in my head about for days after.
It was kind of a nice like you don't need to care so much about like they are not that engaged so you can let shit slide a little bit.
That's a cool thing about a theme park job.
And doing the same thing over and over again.
There you develop a level of precision I feel like.
Sure.
Like she did.
Look I got I got I was sloppy on many occasions.
She I feel like gained some precision.
I think I just mean like like preciseness of speaking or like confidence of movement.
Well I definitely had it on the like the town of Cabaco Vaughn murder sure.
Exactly certain parts I'm like oh I love doing the little like the one way you say that.
Yeah you can just really like nail that part.
I ran a week Jane and I ran into we're at universe Hollywood and ran into an old co-worker of hers who was doing the New Yorker couple.
And I wasn't me.
I think the one thing about doing is like oh you are casting this because you keep it up.
Like she had full conversations with us.
Oh she was in character like Daniel Day Lewis style.
Like Daniel Day Lewis style.
She was like how are you how are you doing.
And like did you get roasted.
Did you get roasted.
Look at the chest guys.
Look what you're wearing there on your head.
We got roasted a little you know they were talking about like the building was under some construction so they were sitting at tables outside.
But I think being able to sustain it for both time and then like eight shows a day for like something like this.
Endurance is huge.
I remember early on when I was like like a kid and I was like kind of auditioned for some like local theater thing and like a big thing.
And it was like I think it was like Wizard of Oz or something.
There was some musical thing and it was like my earliest memory of rejection.
And it was but it was like a big part of it was like they just had like every kid and it was like 100 200 kids.
It felt like the whole theater was just filled with kids.
And it wasn't I thought it was going to be like oh we'll do we'll do parts we'll do parts of the show.
All they had you do was sing happy birthday over and over again.
And you didn't stop.
I really.
And it was like what they were doing was testing.
Can this kid sit down and like keep it together and then keep their endurance and their energy up for like an ungodly amount of time without fidgeting without getting bored without letting their energy fall.
Probably very abusive tactics.
I don't know.
Yeah that sounds like it was.
That was a big part of it was like yeah like testing like like how is your energy.
Can you keep that energy ball up in the air for that long.
And yeah I do.
I was like I was annoyed.
So I like I sang it like twice and I was like I sung it twice.
I sung it.
I stopped like it was like part of the first wave cut and I was like what are you talking about.
Wow.
I did the full Pearl.
I'm a star meltdown.
But I you know I was adding up that like Paul Pell killing it in this show at this time in the same distance like not even the buildings like next to each other.
You've also got Wayne Brady Ghostbusters.
You've got Cheryl Hines in Hitchcock show Orlando actors in early uniform.
And those are big.
Those are like gigantic comedy careers that came out of.
And then you got it's not the same thing but over it you know Nickelodeon you got you got Keenan you got young Keenan starting an endless career.
And there was some I think there was some just general comedy actor mojo happening at early Universal Orlando.
They were letting folks play there.
I think they were letting folks kind of go and I think they were trying stuff out in that first few years.
There needs to be like more of like the mythologizing of the Orlando scene and I'm not even really joking I'm joking a little bit but like there needs to be like Tom shale's book like of oral history is like just Orlando theme park scene of people who like made it pretty big coming out of there.
Oh Dee Bradley Baker.
Legends didn't tell what we talked about no longer.
That's a huge career that was just around there.
Yeah.
Probably ones we're maybe also maybe people who are quieter about their maybe more embarrassed by their Orlando theme park.
Yeah everybody should because I hear it and then I I light up like knowing this about Paula Pell.
If anyone listening to this has a connection to Paula Pell she'd be a dream guest.
Let me put that into the world but given all that experience.
But yeah I don't know.
It was.
You're right.
It was a scene.
Maybe that's maybe you should try to.
Or we all could try to pitch that as a like an HBO miniseries that should be two episodes but is stretched out to nine episodes.
Yeah.
Sure.
The typical format.
These days.
I think so.
Yeah.
So hopefully.
But what have we missed like in terms of beats of this.
Well any big moments that you enjoyed.
So they did.
So they did the full bit like so like during the ADR section to wrap that up they did.
So the big laugh line they would always do because you because you've got these kids because they have to you have to replace the dialogue for the sort of elegant this elegant couple you've got like Ash Brooke and Leilani and you've got this sort of just like tuxedoed and
gown and everybody sort of fancy and then they always picked the most like like mom sure like like just wearing the night shirt as a day shirt like kind of just tourists fanny pet like and it was always funny because you know you've got this like elegance on the screen and then you've got this sort of like you betcha Fargo accent.
And it was great every time and like it was always like that mean it was always like the Leilani would I remember like both times the Leilani would like be great and like hit the mark and hit the and hit the dialogue beats correctly.
But it would just be the voice was so funny but then the Ashbrook the guy was always just like seven seconds late like he was always just like then they played and that would be funny because he'd like you know then when they did the replay at the end you'd have the character.
Sort of mouth moving and then just as he's finished speaking you'd go it's a lie like you'd have you sort of like you think they like that's yeah maybe that's a design to talk about humiliating dad is the big laugh always in these shows.
Yeah.
You gotta humiliate them up to fail.
It was and I was I can probably attest to that because I went both two days in a row when I went the dude was late almost to the second.
Yeah.
Every time.
Well you're like and I to a point where like I at the time I was of course not thinking galaxy brain like this but I was imagine if I was I was like they did this on purpose they're trying to see they're doing this on like I would have how far would I.
Case.
My thinking was that advanced at that point.
But no.
Well that was one of my reality break is as Star Wars Galactic Star Cruiser has come up a lot recently as it was closing.
I think one of my things that it would have been harder to break reality is like these people don't spend 48 hours on the ship like we do.
They have to stop at Target for a few things on the way home.
Oh yeah.
Well I am like sleeping.
That's just two in your head.
They've got off the ship.
Yes.
Yeah.
Don't live.
They didn't build them a little a little caught.
I have to stop at gas and I'll probably just run in the little Caesars next door.
I really don't feel like cooking.
Yeah that's that's what I'm so glad you all brought this up on the Taron Killam episode I just listened to where it was like we're talking about the during the kiss good night sleeping in the castle thing.
Where it was like where does the where does the butler what I don't know what that situation is.
Yeah.
Like he's got to be somewhere.
You want to be able to leave or.
Or there's two butlers and one is a night shift.
One is the I don't know.
I'm still fascinated by that.
I feel like I need a resolution on that.
Yeah.
We got to find somebody who's actually stayed in the dream suite seemed like that was like Taron got a brief tour but who has done.
And if there are other people who stayed overnight in the dream suite who weren't like.
Kings or queens.
Or who aren't like the captains of industry who we've been.
Struck.
Oh sure.
Are there.
Good people.
Dick Van Dyke was up there yesterday at Disneyland waving to everybody.
Yesterday.
Yeah I think.
Are you two days ago.
In the last two days.
In the dream suite that's where he was.
I believe so over pirates.
Didn't they flip one of those to an elegant dining room.
Perhaps perhaps that's the balcony he was in.
I don't know what he was up there anymore.
I'm not saying he was staying there but he was up on that balcony area so perhaps.
The club 33 balcony area waving at people.
So maybe it was just that then.
Yeah.
Maybe it was just the club 33.
Still.
Love that he's.
Pretty good.
Yeah.
97.
Still waving.
I was going to say get out.
Let's bring back diagnosis Murray.
Oh yeah.
No speaking of the show these pleasant.
He was on a worse one.
He was on.
Wait no no no because don't when you're making that list don't throw out Cosby mysteries.
I just remember literally this week.
Remember there was the Cosby mystery.
That was so short lived or.
Yeah that didn't make it.
I know for years.
Yeah.
That was.
Oh so you know Cosby is fucking so mad.
Yeah.
I'm the this is the only one that doesn't run for over a decade.
And he was the more current star obviously he had had a huge hit.
Pretty recently.
It had another one just Cosby soon after.
Yeah.
Well it was funny because because you've got Angela Lansbury and Dick Van Dyke both of
whom had like pivoted from you know it's not it's I feel like Cosby was pivoting from a sitcom.
Yeah like murder.
But then like Dick Van Dyke was you know Dick Van Dyke who is a killer on one of the
Columbus and I was always I've seen that one.
It's very sinister.
He's got like a beard.
It's it's again.
I got very it's like with I hate how lizard brain I am about this where I'm like no you're
not bad.
I can't accept that into my body like seeing Angela Lansbury in Manchurian Canada I was
like I don't yeah I don't think you maybe I don't watch this.
Wow.
So evil in that.
She is evil in that.
Yeah.
So evil and so good and yet.
It just bugs you.
Yeah but I've seen it like I think I've seen it like once and I was like OK but like I don't
want to see it again.
I don't need to like I can't like I can't just like always be seeing this.
But do you accept her in Sweeney Todd.
You know I do because that's that's a whimsy plus like we got our guy who is Sweeney Todd
to her Mrs.
Levitt who is a regular love interest in Murder She Wrote.
He shows up and once a season he is I think he's like an Irish like secret agent.
My it's it's I want to say like he's with like M.I.
Six six like and I don't know like but then he's Irish so I don't know.
Yes.
James Bond is Scottish.
Right.
He's in M.I.
Six.
Yeah.
That's right.
So yeah I think he's like an M.I.
Six agent.
He's always like once a season she'd get wrapped up into some international intrigue thanks
to him.
Michael Haggerty was his name.
And and they had the that's the closest she ever came to having like a torrid affair.
And like that's one of where I could convince myself were like whenever they cut away they
were like together.
Because it was always like out of time was far from they were out of the United States.
They were always like some vacation spot internationally.
And it was usually like he was getting her involved in like the Russians every time.
It was just like some Russian attache was like the thing and then he was murdered and
like she was still the only one who could solve it.
It was very funny.
Now do we in the torrid affair area they don't show it because it's a theme park show.
But do we think she and Tom Selleck hooked up.
So I think so it feels very date night because he's there and he's got like this again
they're wearing incongruous outfits because he's wearing Magnum P.I. sort of like open
shirt the hairy chest sort of the Tom Selleck kind of look.
Is he supposed to be Magnum is that subtly implied.
Is it just a shot from Magnum.
You know what honestly I need to look at it because like it doesn't reappear anywhere
else and there is slightly different.
I remember it being like so wild that I can't remember like my like best friend from high
school's name but like I can remember like the lighting on the murder she wrote Tom Selleck
shot was like slightly different.
Not it was not quite matching the lighting on Angela's face so it could have been they
pulled it from a Magnum episode.
But I don't know why they would do that and not just reshoot it.
Well because maybe getting him is tough.
Maybe they just found something that correlated maybe decently.
Who knows.
He still has to sign off.
He still have to like get paid and get signed off.
Yeah but maybe but then he doesn't have to like go drive to a place and do.
Yeah.
True.
Be in one camera setup.
I think they were both universal television.
If I remember the wall of DVDs at the backlot tour on the on the lot itself.
Murder she wrote was next to Magnum.
I'm going to solve my own mystery here and say I think that was pre-recorded Tom Selleck
because there is no two shot of them.
They are abusing my executive producer editing.
The thing remembrance is there's you cut there's her talking and it's a it's a they
just keep cutting back and forth between the two of them talking and it's slightly dimmer.
Yeah it's a slight gag.
It's a glorified like a gag.
Yeah.
The magic of editing magic of editing and they had in the ADR section they had the
crowd could get involved.
So I don't know if they didn't shoot they didn't show this part in the in the whole
camp in the in the John Forsyte video but like they did show it.
You can hear it if you see the like when she walks into dinner with.
Oh there's a bunch of like clap trap.
Like the audience all makes a bunch of noise.
So they're like they had us do Walla Walla.
They're like OK yes and the crowd does a Walla Walla Walla.
So we're going to record a Walla Walla Walla Walla and I say Walla Walla Walla and it
just turned into screaming.
I say the video is like what's happening.
Why is this restaurant.
I was wondering that about you if you all saw that.
Because I was like out of context it has to be like what's what's wrong with this audio.
It sounds like the prisoners in the pit and Dark Knight Rises doing that.
She's going to make the the the faith jump.
She has wandered into a restaurant where the like demons from hell are feasting and she's
in evening wear.
Yes.
Something's amiss in this restaurant that's nothing but demons eating.
Hellraiser box has been opened.
Yeah I hear the steak off.
Pop is good here.
So yeah so you recorded a Walla Walla Walla and then you were thinking you were creating
a nice sort of dinner sort of a sort of conversational tone and then you hear it and you're
just like this stinks.
We overdid it.
We didn't do good.
So the second time you went you're like OK and you tried to like the next the people all
around you.
I was.
Take it down a notch.
Take it down a couple notches.
Yes unfortunately my authority was undermined by my height.
Your EP level of control.
Oh you know also I think when in that Pellipel version when Tom Selleck appears then she
like melts to the floor so happy as she to see Tom says she just she falls out of her
chair at the mere sight of Tom Selleck.
It's who wouldn't.
Yes fine acting.
Big theme park feints.
It plays to the back row.
Also what you mentioned this in the DMs I forgot we make in the list of great performers
at that time in Orlando.
Moe.
Yeah right.
From Guts my record did this job to which you remembered from our episode and I forgot
but this is one of the things she was doing.
Wait maybe concurrently with being on Guts like she's on Guts but they you know they
block shoot them so she also still keeps the theme park.
I think what Moe exposed at least to me and maybe to y'all during that episode was like
oh there's just like it was not like Nickelodeon was not this like well you can just
retire off of this.
Yes right.
Because I was like oh well you're just like set you know you worked on your Moe.
Yes I know.
So you're just like yeah you know you're currently living in Brentwood off of your Guts
money.
How it should be.
The world and a great voiceover career.
But still like she should have that should have been a choice to keep doing it.
So you should have got it.
You could have wrapped it up in 96 if she had to.
Recording with Mike O'Malley and just racing across Mrs.
Doubtfire like to the Murder She Wrote Theater.
I got to catch the 530 show.
I put my big Janine glasses on and go hey what's going on over here.
Like it's.
Stopping at a hot dog cart for a quick lunch.
Yes.
And becoming Janine.
You like that part.
Well I like that part.
But the hurrying.
The hurrying is not as hot as that.
Mel's whatever is there.
What's on the way.
The stomachache burger.
Yes.
Well it's a great little condensed Murder She Wrote.
It's a great vehicle for performers.
You know true movie making process the thing that they've lost a little bit.
This goes away and becomes Hercules and Xena.
It's funny I don't want to throw an episode under the bus but I remember we brought up this Mo one.
How great was she.
She was so excited.
That's when I think of that nice pandemic episode.
Yeah that's high for sure.
Then I think about when the period of time where we're like we're going to be back together in person soon.
What the fuck can we burn off that sucks where we aren't doing it in person.
Hercules and Xena maybe Hercules and Xena.
We can jam that out on Zoom.
That's one of like two that I did participate in.
I was excited for that.
You were in Hercules and Xena.
You had the bravery.
I had the one time I had the bravery to do a reaction shot like wearing like.
Amazing.
Oh that's right.
See I'm telling you I forgot because the pandemic episodes I started blacking out.
I'm so desperate for them to be done.
You know what we should do.
We should do like an office ladies about our pandemic episodes where we do reactions to the episode.
I would like subscribe to a fourth tier for that.
And that will give you perspective on what we were thinking behind the scenes.
And then like if we were proud of it and proud of each other.
And I'll say remember this was the day we had to do this under the under the shadow of that was when Trump blew off all the bombs around the church.
And then we had to pull it together.
That's right.
So that we could talk about you know the what's the most mundane thing.
The photo booth where you could film music videos with your mom.
Yeah we had to.
You remember what a tough time in America.
Yeah I think it's a great idea.
And most of it will be like I'll re litigate how much laughter I got for jokes that I said like I'll be like well that was a good one and you guys didn't laugh enough.
It would have worked in person.
That was the technology was just lagging and other way if it had been a person big laugh.
Right.
Also because like you know if you all are anything like me that sort of first at least that first year.
Like I have started like in like one division style sort of stitching that year out of my memory.
Oh I don't believe like I've completely like because I moved to I moved to North Carolina and then I came back and I'm back in the place where I was in like 2018 2019.
So my brain continues to believe it's 2018.
Yeah no me too.
And so I'm just like I have this sort of like vertigo where I'm like it's not 2018.
I say last year about 2019 or 2018 constantly still I did it two days ago.
I go well we went here last year and I really meant before the pandemic.
It's really wild how there is sort of and it timed out this way there is sort of a lost Thanos snap five years.
100 percent.
It's horrifying.
Yeah.
And it's like OK well you know I would revisit some episodes because you probably don't remember them.
No I don't remember a lot of them.
You're probably just like oh yeah.
I struggled to think of one we actually did especially like there was a minute where like it was fun.
It's like a fun little summer camp.
We all get to stay.
We got to stay indoors and it's actually interesting.
We're doing an episode over Zoom.
That's not what. And then by month 14.
Fucking God you know the only one I remember going that was good was McGruff 2.
On Patreon.
I remember going I think McGruff 2.
I forgot we did that on Patreon.
I think I think you're I mean I mean I was zoomed rather.
Yeah.
Yes but your patrons during that time were very good.
I will say they were all very good but I would say the patrons were really singing because like I think it's best during these times when people get a little delirious.
Sure.
And so that's sort of the pay in the sort of second gate.
That's when everybody kind of get a little silly.
You've got to become a little.
You're not really sticking to you don't have to.
Sure.
Stick to.
We're going mad.
Listeners are going mad.
We're all let's just all go mad together.
It was a little validating in that way.
That's nice to hear.
That it's all tangents and it's about this topic that's it's not just like oh this beloved thing it's like a really wild never thought about that thing.
Like well it was I remember early on saying fuck it we're doing Kevin Spacey.
I.
Now is the day it's a fuck it time and this is happening.
When the question marks popped up I was like whatever this team.
Excuse me.
What is this from the theme park podcast.
Oh even it's back.
Oh that's good.
Like what's now happening.
For who.
For the devil himself.
My god.
Yeah.
Kevin Spacey.
Sitting.
Sitting in my bedroom and on the small TV having rented a digital copy of Beyond the
Sea and that opening where he's like I'm like hell Joel's to mama.
I'm like oh no.
Oh my.
This is so odd.
I can't go anywhere.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
That was your bottom.
That was mine.
Yeah.
This.
I feel partly responsible for this because I did sort of right before the Kevin Spacey
stuff came out like I did feel I did say something you know to a friend I was like you know I
wish I just wish more like celebrities were like you know who are closeted which like come
out and then like the monkey's paw finger curls.
Oh yeah.
What is this you mean?
I have an announcement to make.
I'm gay.
I'm like we're like not now.
Now I have a smoke bomb to throw.
I need an apology to make.
It really was like okay.
I know everyone's coming out story is unique and different.
Usually there aren't suspicious murders circling.
It's very it's very interesting and then like a few short years later like you know you
know so I am I am a young adult author of LGBTQ stories and we are part of the rise
of book bands and I'm part of all the don't say gay and all the groomer talk.
So there's a lot of that.
So it's very delightful that like a few short years earlier he sort of set the stage for
like yes it'll just sort of sort of mix the word cloud in people's minds of like coming
out and allegations.
Oh yes.
That's great and underage.
Most people just aren't really paying to check down not really paying attention.
They just go I remember him coming out like some yeah he did something.
He did something.
No matter how many trials overturn things for him you're like you're not going to forgive
this man for he still did something that he can't take back that is awful.
Funnily enough no.
Yeah.
That's that's actually fascinating.
That's a very good point.
But to fictional murders any anything we want to say before we wrap this up it goes away
Hercules and Zena for a brief time that gets pulled those pretty quick becomes Transformers
the ride becomes the the the home of the greatest moment in the park sincerity.
Of course.
Yeah.
But and I don't mean to pit you guys against each other but this is like you know one gets
but very different types of theme park entertainment in the same spot and I know you miss one.
I don't know how can we all still be friends.
Well I think so.
I would just say I was really trying to figure out what would be in a meeting in the middle
here.
Well like because you know this is such a classic early universal we talk about they
brought making the movies with such the theme and that was very interesting to kids some
kids not every kid but some kids the best one.
Us.
Yes.
We did like that stuff.
But I was trying to think like is there there's definitely a better murder she wrote ride
experience than this.
There has to be.
So I was trying to figure out what's it going to meeting not maybe it wouldn't still be
here today but if they had built a ride what do we think that I like that.
Because I think I think there's there's a case to be made that they still could do this
because we've been seeing on Screamscape lately they've been talking about doing these pop
up sort of old attractions and I'm like well it's going to cost so much money to do a pop
up jaws.
Sure.
How little would it cost to do a pop up murder she wrote.
You would have I know you have gay guys around the block like you for sure would like again
you have like just tons of people.
I feel like there's like that like the fan base of the show has maintained.
So I feel like you could do like a pleasant maze.
Sure.
Yeah.
With a little.
You could do some scares.
Yeah.
Like there's sort of old trickery happening there.
But yeah I feel like you can get her in her.
They look if you had enough like street performers in the classic trench with the flashlight
which is they kind of have her kind of in a lot.
Is she not kind of bike around town.
That's not very active.
So we got like maybe bike ride vehicles is the way to go.
OK.
Yeah.
It's not.
Maybe you keep that open air.
Maybe you build a little outdoor or take over in here in Hollywood.
You could just have that be in actual Cabot Cove.
Sure.
Yeah.
I would absolutely.
I can if you did if you took over the Cabot Cove area because it's really right now they
do the shark jaws.
Yeah.
But then I think but then the shark is sort of like foreground all the Cabot Cove stuff
is background.
You got enough room.
You could have people like you could have.
It would interfere with it.
Exactly.
Because people completely separate.
Yeah.
And then you have the tram folks going.
Shark keeps attacking.
You know they don't that sound doesn't have to travel and you can have these sort of frankly
you could do like an immersive Wizarding World type where you're just sure Cabot Cove.
Right.
And just you know we're all you know theme parks are going.
We're not doing rides anymore.
We're doing seemed restaurants and pubs and those sorts of things.
True.
So fish houses.
Fish houses.
Lobster houses.
Do sort of like all those sort of like you know you know just sort of down east Maine
you know sort of sort of stuff.
And if I don't see in theme parks there's not a lot of that.
Like here's the Maine.
Yeah.
Right.
Sure.
What's that like the Columbia Harbor House type like food.
Yeah.
Where you're like oh yeah you go in there and it's all just like nautical and woodsy
and you could kind of do that.
And then some walk around Jessica Fletcher's or kind of interact with you like have you
seen I'm looking for I'm looking for you know I'm looking for the sheriff.
I have some information.
You could do like a Nazi's ghost town alive or something immersive like that where if
want to participate you can sort of run around town all day and help her solve things.
But if you just want to eat lobster rolls.
But if you just want to eat a lobster roll great.
They'll give you a necklace.
They'll give you a necklace who you don't want to engage with Jessica Fletcher.
It lights up.
Sort of like a Fogo to Chow thing where you like flip it to red if you just don't want
to die.
Exactly.
Yeah.
You don't want to keep walking.
Leave the mysteries to you.
That would be great.
If they did do like a murder she wrote Dark Ride.
I think we've seen how you can adapt a TV show well with the ride in Europe based on
the Swedish hit Vipa Salt Kraken.
Oh yeah.
That was a pandemic one.
That was a pandemic episode.
Yeah.
Vipa Salt Kraken.
I'm getting submerged from the fog.
I purposely placed over all of those memories but I'm very happy that that's been raised.
It seems like a very pleasant ride, a similar setting, not a ton of conflict.
Yeah.
There's a little just a smattering of conflict but it's just about being with your pals from
TV.
An animatronic Jessica in three or four minutes could easily start with a mystery and solve
it by the end of the ride.
Yeah.
And then like oh and I couldn't have done it without you.
Your bravery saved my case.
I'm telling you.
Freedom Fletcher.
Even if she was like I'm Angela Lansbury, this is all a TV show, I would be even more
happy about that.
You could do the thank you for executive producing my show.
Like please I kind of need that hit back in my life.
Watching that video again really brought that back where I'm like I did need to hear that
again that she was very delighted that I'm going to produce her show.
Well then let me say how about we amend the end of the episode and I say Adam says thank
you for executive producing our show.
Oh my god.
It feels justified because you brought so much to the table.
You knew so much.
You filled in gaps of knowledge that we all had because it's getting a little bit lost
to the sands of time.
I brought the frog DNA to the dino DNA that was necessary.
Yes.
The missing piece.
Right.
You filled it in.
But the regular one too.
You survived podcast the ride and what an absolute delight.
Like this is it's an ideal kind of episode.
Another thing to put into the world when we run into these things where like it's the
hard pitch on something that nobody's ever brought up as I want to do that and not even
as anybody's runner.
It's never been on a list and you come in.
I love murder she wrote mystery theater.
I will bring the passion about it and it's just what you did.
I really appreciate it.
I could not have been more delighted to get a response on that.
That was very very cool.
This was yeah this was definitely a shooting my shot moment that was that I'm that again
I'm glad I quieted that scared.
Don't raise your hand for superstar TV kid inside me.
It was like don't get involved.
Everyone will see everyone will know you DM your favorite show and didn't get a response.
No this was very cool.
This is very cool.
And I knew I also listening to these I knew you were making your way through all the OG
Orlando and you want to see it go away without your circular you were circling and I knew
that there was like maybe not a ton of like because I knew there was a ton of knowledge
out there that existed like to research.
And there was important stuff outside of that.
And and yeah is this the first was this the first attraction universal closed permanently
in 96.
God was it.
It's also something we didn't say it also has the reputation of like it was it was an
opening day attraction and one of the only ones that worked because all of those big
robotics based ones were really fucked up technically.
But this one like I think it's the same producer.
Yeah as maybe Hitchcock or maybe one of the other or maybe the horror show.
I'm not sure.
But like it was like this this one woman like well for real her stuff ran perfectly.
I think Spielberg has a lot to thank after he cut the big film strip with the scissors
and then like everything sort of felt all the big tech stuff that was right flashy flopped
you know.
But this is about that's about personalities the actors in the room local landsbury helps
actors this is about this attraction is about people.
It's about people and I like as we're getting back to that as a film industry it's a film
and television industry.
We are hopefully returning to that place where there is it is more people centric a little
bit more.
I think it's I think it's the perfect way to to start off a haunt cast.
I could not have been more delighted.
I hope so.
I should have said you survived haunt cast the fright and I should say look I'm just
spitballing let's exit through the crypt shop.
OK.
Oh yeah.
You would like to plug.
Yes.
My newest YA novel is called Your Lonely Nights Are Over.
It is I'm pitching it as Scream Meets Clueless.
It is a teen slasher.
It is if you see if you if you look up the cover it is basically my notes were like do
Fear Street do Christopher Pike and it's channeling that sort of like 90s teen thriller.
It's sort of like a lost Kevin Williamson 90s slasher film.
But it involves two gay best friends Deary and Cole who are at war essentially with their
larger LGBTQ queer club in high school because like in Clueless Deary and Cole are sort of
like popular and funny and hot and the rest of them they call they call them the flops
and they are all to them they're like oh you're just jealous and so there's these and the
flops are basically like oh well you're not really involved in the queer club you're not
raising money you're not raising awareness you don't come to the meetings and they're
very like you know kind of livid about that so it just becomes this sort of like who's
the better queer person sort of fight which is very very queer community right now.
There's a lot of a lot of a lot of a lot of dark satire about how I feel about being in
the queer community right now.
The idea of like fracturing.
Well it's like who's bad for the community who's good for the community and why.
So there's a lot of intro fighting and it gets all very nice and juicy and cutthroat
silver tongue dialogue but then into that drama comes Mr. Sandman who is a masked killer
who starts targeting members of the queer club they start dropping and so Deary and
Cole because they have been such enemies to this club are blamed and so Deary and Cole
basically are like very annoyed that they have to solve this series of slayings because
if they don't they'll either be next or worse they're gonna probably go down as the killers
for this so it is yes it is a it is for spooky season I suggest everybody pick it up if you
like a good because that's the other thing is that I've noticed is that like because
I know like you know I know you love haunts Mike and I know but like I know like there's
some type of like uh you know Halloween time I've noticed people sort of go into two camps of
horror like the movies they watch or the kind of stuff they read there's like the the hardcore
types who are like I'm watching uh all the gory stuff I'm watching Saw I'm watching you know
Hellraiser I'm watching all this stuff and then there's sort of this other group over here very
valid still that's like I will watch um Nightmare Before Christmas I will watch Halloween Town
and I will watch maybe one scream and scream seems to be the sort of like connector between the two
factions I've noticed literally I have I've never seen scream and I have a DVD library copy right
now so I'm about to go into screen I am so excited it's really good it's it's great it's like
because the thing that makes it different than like an 80s like a Freddy or a Jason or Michael
Myers is um it's well a it's sort of like a speaking of Jessica Fletcher it's a whodunit
the screen movies are always like the killer is someone you have met it's it really is an
Agatha Christie sort of thing but it's like it's it's and it's got a slickness to it that I think
helps make the horror of it go down for folks who don't usually like fuck with horror oh oh this
might be a good gateway for me I think so because like it's basically like it's sort of like
like one third horror and blood I mean it is bloody and scary but then like it's two
thirds humor so like it's just great it's a funny thing uh you know Wes Craven made the first four
and uh then he passed but then you know they're they're been keeping that going and uh they're
just incredibly slick they're full of just great performances um and that's kind of what I what I
wanted to do with Your Only Nights Are Over was um I realized that like this wasn't falling into
the same like oh god this this this movie again uh was with Scream because you loved the characters
so much you were having recurring characters and it was the characters and the people and the humor
that made you feel kind of safe within the scary stuff and so I really wanted to do that in this
book where it was like there's a lot of like bodies are dropping there is a lot of there's
there's some gore there's some scares there's some dread um it's but it is just a very kind of slick
funny Halloween time and they're kind of like your best friends and you're like oh my best
friends are here I feel fine and I'm laughing and I'm not too and I'm never too scared and I'm but
I'm scared for them so I wanted to hit that sort of note and uh I feel that I have done that so
yeah you can pick that up anyway sounds great yeah well congrats to you on having it out there and
getting to do a book tour not not being stuck solid putting your hand up into the world
truly this wasn't putting my hand up moment I was like I'm I would like to do the tour now please
because I could have done it last time but I was really I was really like um just sort of dusting
myself off and uh it felt like now was the time because it was a it was it's a it's a crowd
pleaser of a book so I wanted to then uh meet everyone so I could not be more happy to have
it out there that's wonderful well yeah check it out everybody I'm excited to to read it um as for
us you can find us on the ghost of twitter now known as x you can find on cast the fright merch
in our t public store and for three bonus episodes every month check out haunt cast the fright
the cemetery gate or one more bonus episode on our rip tier crypt three hell yeah you will find all
of that at patreon.com podcast the ride yes michael I and just two mere two days ago announced by my
beloved neka toys oh we forgot yes you mentioned this in the dm I sent this in a dm yes so this was
so mike this I was saying I'm like the simulation is very strong I know they just announced
Jessica Fletcher the murder she wrote neka toy is out this is like literally a manifestation it was
it was over the weekend yeah it was Saturday yeah Toy Fair was over this weekend so yeah I was like
I can't believe this is happening right you know uh it was it was everything was sort of merging it
and they just had their uh murder story has like a 39th anniversary of the pilot just happened so
yeah it's been out for 40 years it's wild yeah the neck I'm gonna get the neck a thing I have a I
have a funko of Jessica Fletcher yes and I was like I was literally I'm gonna be like because
it when I got it she was like 10 bucks and I was like I'm gonna show up with three Jessica Fletcher
funcos I was gonna give them they are now like over 100 bucks as is the eBay way well yeah this is
what happened I got my mom and Agnes Moorhead and Dora from bewitched and this thing's 100
dollars now too but she took it out of the box you know amazing like it's just these things feel
like they're just for me and then like they become these like huge sellers and these sorts of things
and I just I truly they didn't make enough uh Agnes Moorhead toys or funnily enough they did not
um well hey uh I'm looking at the uh uh old character actress bingo sheet and I'm now seeing
Jessica Walter Yvonne DeCarlo and Agnes Moorhead you got you got bingo oh yeah I do one actress bingo
right I was I was sad the episode was about to end and you weren't gonna hit it so if you couldn't
achieve that on a murder she wrote episode like I feel like you'd never yeah yeah we didn't even
know we needed to say more names I could sit here and you could just keep the the tape rolling
and I could just be like all right okay now now we're gonna get into yeah we'd fill up that card
that would be 100% that would just be the actresses I wouldn't even get to the other actors yeah yeah
when we splinter this off into this podcast right and then there's just names list the podcast my
dream oh yes yes no it's great it's where it's like uh Joanne Worley was on an episode oh yeah
serotonin hits we get them with every actress name she's on a cruise ship as long as they
aren't modern clearly shot on the queen mary it's supposed to look like it's setting sail
and I used to live in long beach like across the bay from the queen mary and I was like you can
see the the rocks and the docking and the pillars and yeah pillars you see the parking lot behind
it's like not glamorous but like everyone's like racing to catch like a steamer ship
no you're not uh queen mary interest that's huh maybe could that be a clue for a future haunt
cast we'll see only the true Jessica Fletcher sleuths may find out okay forever
dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.