Forever...
Dog!
Boo!
The following haunt cast may contain
socially conscious minds,
ghostly exhalations,
rock and roll DJs barely trying.
Plus, Betsy Sidaro joins us for a look back into the spooky history of Not Scary Farm
for its 50th anniversary.
Ha ha ha ha!
It's Haunt Cast, The Fright!
Welcome to Haunt Cast, The Fright, a haunt cast about screen parks
ghosted by three ghouls who are only comfortable with a monster mash
if it's a monster sized plate of mashed potatoes.
My name is Frightful Narleson, joining me as always, Scottle Juice.
Scottle Juice, yes. We are too scared of the monster mash.
The monster mash is terrible. This is how...
You know that we are wimps and we don't do... I don't do a lot of haunts.
You know I'm not going near that song.
I pee my pants every time. If it's on the radio, if it's in a store, I get out of the store.
I take all my groceries, knock them to the floor, and get the hell out of there.
Yeah, and it's not that we don't like the song, because the song is good,
but the actual act of the monsters having a mash would be too frightening.
If somebody would just please, I love the melody, it's one of the great melodies,
and if you could just unmonsterify it and just make it, we'll do the normal mash.
Yes, and then it's like the doctor was having a party, and he's a regular.
The regular doctor was having a party.
The regular doctor, like you'd see in a Nora Ephron movie.
It's about a high society New York doctor's dinner.
And they were planning their expensive new kitchen or something,
and they explain they're just working on the plan.
Yes, none of this gore.
Jagged Slash and Drain is here also?
Yeah, I mean I'm very fearful everything you've talked about, I'm scared of it,
but I'm thinking about that big plate of mashed potatoes.
I thought you would, and I thought when I was putting this together,
maybe I would make a direct reference to you liking the monster-sized plate of mashed potatoes,
but then I decided to make it all of us.
I love it.
You know, it's not a thing that I really make at home,
unless it's like a bag of instant mashed potatoes,
and it just doesn't have the soul, you know?
I do know, yeah.
You live a soulless life.
I live a soulless life.
My mom was telling me about this just recently.
She's like, yeah, we all love mashed potatoes,
but to buy a bag of potatoes and wash them and peel them in the mat,
it's so labor-intensive.
Oh, this is true.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
I'm not doing that much.
I've done it once or twice, but it's not as bad as some other stuff that I find tedious.
No, it's not.
As far as cooking is concerned, but yeah, yeah.
I certainly appreciate it when a restaurant serves it with stuff.
I appreciate it because I don't make it at home.
Like with short ribs or something.
I appreciate it too when they serve it with stuff in it.
We love stuff.
Let's bring our guest in to see if she loves stuff.
She's an actor, comedian, she's a podcast host.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Betsy Sadaro.
She's here.
Oh, I love this spooky name.
Oh yeah, well, create.
Let's figure it out.
Betsy.
Nice.
Sadaro.
I add one, if you just do a little rearranging and it's dis-saro.
Good.
I like that one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, not too bad.
Yeah, and then it's just taking everything that's already in the list.
You don't even have to add anything.
Thank you.
It's recycling.
It's energy conscious.
Yeah.
I love it.
Betsy, are you making mashed potatoes at home?
No, not one.
No, no, no.
God, no.
I'm so not a cook of any type.
It's ... I find it ...
I eat stuff up.
Sure.
I find that even when I make something, I'm so annoyed that I just made it.
I don't enjoy it.
Yes.
So I don't know what the point is.
Because you see all the dishes and stuff and you're like, that was so much work for like
two and a half minutes of just eating it.
Yes, right.
And I joylessly eat it.
Yeah.
Yeah, great.
It was better than a normal thing I ate at McDonald's.
Right.
But it doesn't feel I earned anything.
No, not one bit.
Not even when we've made fresh cooked meals thanks to our partners, but not in a long
time, from HelloFresh.
HelloFresh.
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
HelloFresh will take an hour and 15 minutes of my time.
Yes, those are ... yeah, no, it's like caused fights.
It's like ... yeah, it's a spade.
By the way, everything does taste as good as I've said it does in ads I've read.
Yes, that part's not a lie, but we don't talk about the psychological damage.
But we don't talk about how upset I am while I'm eating.
I'm also terrible about plating everything so it's all hot.
That's so hard.
So hard.
It's very hard.
It's too hard.
I started kind of just doing everything individually where it's like, okay, I'll heat up my veggies,
and while I'm slamming those down, I'll heat up the chicken or whatever so that it is all
hot.
I think that's a very crafty way to do it.
Thank you so much.
That's very smart.
And cool, because slamming sounds cool.
Yeah, that is for sure cool.
It's awesome to slam your veggies down, kids.
Yeah.
Like dunking it into your own mouth.
Slammed it.
Choking a lot.
A lot of like, okay, all right.
Oh yeah.
As long as you survive.
But you have like a backwards baseball cap on and you're on a skateboard.
On a skateboard, eating veggies.
Slamming.
Veggies.
Slamming it.
Slamming those veggies.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, very cool.
Very cool.
Well, today we're going to talk a little bit about Not Scary Farm.
Yeah.
50 years.
50 damn years.
Which is 50 years of the original haunt, according to Nots, they created the haunt.
Now I don't know if they-
The entire premise of a separate Halloween event in a typically snooze fest theme park
for little kiddies.
Yeah, yeah.
There's no slamming going on.
No slamming happening at Nots Berry Farm.
That's scary though.
No old prospector slamming.
No train conductor slamming.
None of the robots of mine workers that are on Death's Door, they're not slamming anything.
They don't have the strength.
That ride is so funny.
I love that ride.
The strangest, most depressing.
You're just seeing real, well fake real suffering.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's such a funny choice because pirates, of course the reality of pirates is they were
probably just like really nightmarish.
Right.
But Pirates of the Caribbean makes this seem like really fun.
They're just like, oh, I'm going to be a pirate.
I'm going to be a pirate.
Yes.
And they do not make that choice in the Knott's Berry Farm mine ride.
They basically are just like, let's just show what it would be like.
And everybody looks miserable.
They've aged terribly from the fumes in the mine.
Every character is 13 and below.
13 is an old scraggly beard.
I've seen so much.
But the scale is very impressive.
That one big scene.
That huge scene.
It's a great ride.
It is a fantastic ride.
It's just they went for the realism, which Disney did not when it was portraying some
real life situations.
Right.
It was year round horrors and the horrors of what laborers face, but they still wanted
to add on top of that and have more fictionalized horrors like Dracula's.
Yes, exactly.
Yes, they needed that Dracula.
We need some Dracula's around here.
It's not sad and scary enough.
So, Betsy, you're very into haunts and scary stuff.
I love them so much.
And have you been going to them like for a long time?
Because I'm a newer enjoyer of this stuff.
I feel like moving to L.A. was when I got really into it.
Like, as a kid, I was always so into Halloween, so stoked about the idea of haunted houses.
And I would go like my family very early on in my life would turn our basement into a
haunted house for like the neighbors to come through and stuff.
Oh, one of these deals.
I'm always very impressed by anybody with the energy to do that.
Wow, your family.
My dad would put it together and like we would help and stuff.
And then, yes, on Halloween nights, just let kids come in and we would scare them and stuff.
That's fun.
Wow, you were a character.
You were in childhood.
I did it a little bit.
Yeah, I was probably like three years old, just being like, hey, man.
With a mask on.
And then moving to L.A., though, it was a whole like, I had no clue Halloween could
be two months long of celebrating and scary stuff and everything.
And so in the last like probably 12 years or so is when I got really into it with the
haunted hayride.
It started.
We went on that and it was so fun.
And then they went to Shark Tank and sold out.
Is that right?
Those people.
Wow.
I guess I recall a haunted hayride set, but that's the L.A. one.
Yeah, yeah.
They would sell out.
They did the right move and got a lot more money and then decided to expand and stuff.
It's like, yeah, good job.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's different.
You know, it was better before those.
Yeah.
So what was different about it?
Before they there were so many more like.
Cool interactive moments, not just like fun, big.
Statues or whatever, like there was at one point, remember in Mad Max Fury Road, those
like dudes on those like the polls, the poll thing, they had that one haunted hayride.
And it was so fucking cool.
Like these people as crows just like flinging themselves at you.
And it was so rad.
And they had this one like church moment that went to the OOAA song.
Oh, the service of sickness.
Yeah, that does.
It was really.
And it was like in the old zoo in Griffith Park.
So that alone was like.
Just a great vibe all around.
And now they're just at like some baseball fields.
It's still pretty fun, but it is like it's different, man.
Yeah, it does.
It sounds like it was more dangerous back then.
I think so.
And I think that's why I like it.
More dangerous for all the workers.
Right.
For everybody involved.
But it ruled.
Yeah.
A friend of the show and recent guest, Joe Quazzalla, has brought up something that's
at the I don't know if you've run into this before, but this is a good way to see this
mythology.
He's brought up the haunted hayride, but also specifically something that's there called
the Monte Rivolta show.
I saw him.
You have seen this.
I saw him like last year or something.
He's a haunt.
He's like a zombie lounge singer.
Yes.
He ruled.
Really?
Friends, we were like talking about like, do we go back to the haunted hayride?
And everybody was like, I kind of don't want to unless Monte Rivolta is there.
Wow.
This is what Joe is saying is he's thinking about going to just that.
That's free.
You just go to that.
And you don't got to get scared by state.
You just get to see a fun.
Wait, really?
I think so.
I got to tell everybody.
Let them know.
We got to go.
He rules.
Okay.
And he's here this year.
I've been meaning to get this going as an episode or something.
But now the excitement that I'm encountering here, we got to talk Monte.
He sings classic songs, but makes them spooky.
But I wish I had specifics.
He was a blast.
Like to the point where it's like, can I hire him for like a birthday party or something?
This guy rules.
Yeah.
So he sings a bunch of classic songs, but then makes them spooky.
But I can't remember.
Is it in the rat pack genre?
What kind of what?
I want to say it's like all different kinds of popular songs through the era.
Okay.
And he has like a bit of spooky band and then like just spooky dancers and stuff.
He rules.
Wow.
And what's he wearing?
What's the outfit?
Well, I'm looking at like tuxedo.
Yeah, just a cool, you know, yeah.
Yeah, just a cool jacket, but that's a little like goth.
Like a little dusty.
His teeth are scary.
He's scarier than I thought he would be.
I don't know if you can handle it.
I was picturing him looking like Flabber from Big Bad Beetleborgs for some reason.
I don't know why.
But well, I think it's easier maybe on a lower budget to get some decent prosthetics and spooky makeup.
So yeah, Monte Rivolta has somehow topped the production value of Big Bad Beetleborgs.
Yeah, okay.
Well, that's exciting.
I would like to see him.
Wait, I didn't realize you could just go and watch him.
I think maybe.
Oh my God, I'm going tonight.
So this is exactly what you were...
Oh my God, I'm going every single night hoping he's there.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This...
Does it list with...
Rules.
Yeah, uh-huh, uh-huh.
And you don't got to, and probably like you just get to walk up and do that.
Yeah.
And they can not stand in a Hayride line either.
You think he changes the set up a little bit?
Yeah.
You think he changes the set up every night?
I think maybe a little bit.
You think maybe he throws in...
There's no band though, right?
There is.
Well, there is.
I think there is, if I remember correctly.
Well, he's joined by Rotley and Ms. Muerte.
Okay.
So that sounds like a band to me or at least some like...
Yeah.
Some dancers.
Oh wow.
Well, we'll investigate.
We'll do the deep dive.
You got to do the deep dive.
We have to do it.
We got to meet Monte.
Monte Rivolta, yes.
His booking email, you can book it, Monte at Monte Rivolta dot com.
There we go.
Okay.
And now the listeners have that too.
Does he have a...
Oh, it's on his public Instagram page.
So that's great.
Yeah, yeah.
Great.
Well, you can go straight to the source.
I wonder if he has like a different persona for every holiday.
Whoa.
What was Monte Christmas?
Rudolph?
Rudolpho.
Rudolpho, yeah.
Same songs too.
He's a human reindeer freak with a heck of a set of pipes.
It's the same look except he's got ants letters on.
It's the same face.
Honestly, spectacular.
I will hire him for every party.
Wow.
Okay.
So that's...
That's a do.
Yeah, yeah, good.
Yeah.
I was just going to say, so do you, is your like level of comfortability with scares,
is it like...
Is it like the knots universal or do you go harder, do you go to some weirder ones or
is it basically, you know, your big ones, your normal?
Kind of the normal ones.
I haven't...
I don't really have any desire for those like crazy hardcore ones.
Yeah.
You know, where they like take your shoes and stuff and they're like, dig through this
toilet of shit.
I like...
I've no...
That doesn't...
That just...
I'm like, I don't need to fuck it.
Do that.
Like I've had friends who did that blackout one.
Yes.
A couple of years ago that was like super intense.
Like, and yeah, they immediately take your shoes from you.
Yeah.
And like at one point like waterboard you and shit.
I don't need...
I don't want to do anything like that.
Yeah, I agree.
I don't need to be waterboarded.
I want a goofy storyline that I don't really understand and people being like, this way,
come, you need to help and be like, okay, I'm going to do this.
Help and be like, okay, I'll come help.
I'll come help.
Like delusion rules.
Yeah.
Have you done delusion?
Yeah, we did one.
Yeah.
That one's really cool.
Yeah, for sure.
I remember one year we ran...
My friend Luke and I ran into you and Justin Michael at Horror Nights.
Yes.
And we went into a couple of mazes.
I think we went into the Us Maze together.
The Us Maze was awesome.
I agree.
From what I remember.
I feel like some people were negative about it, but that was my favorite one that year.
Yeah.
It was cool.
It was really cool.
And because I always find that when you're in an area that resembles real life and that
things could jump out, that makes me more scared.
So when you're in the living room from the movie, I remember just...
And we were like, all four of us were alone.
For some reason there weren't a lot of people.
I don't know why that was, but it felt like we were almost more alone in that maze.
And I do remember you and Justin waiting for the scares each time, which I wasn't brave
enough at that point to want to do that.
So I was like, what are they doing?
Why aren't they walking faster?
We go through them slow.
Yeah.
Geez, really.
Because we are like, I want to look at everything and I want to get scared.
Yeah.
And there are some people who just walk through so casually.
It's like, don't you want to look around?
There's so much cool shit.
Yeah.
I'm better about that now.
But especially at the time we went, I was just like, I have to pretend I like this way
to do things.
Well, this is your transition period.
You would not fully decided that you like that you love haunts now.
What got you into it?
Like what?
Do the podcast peer pressure to prove something about my adult hood and my toughness by and
large?
Well, we went to nots.
Nots is the first time I ever really did it.
I did.
I've done like House of Horrors at Universal, but I hated it.
And then, yeah, we went to nots a couple of years ago and I was sort of like, I want to
force myself to get it.
Yeah.
And then I took me two or three houses to like realize no one's going to kill me.
Right.
You know, and you start to realize your brain starts to understand the limitations of what
really can happen.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then as soon as you kind of recalibrate to that, then you're still getting like, ah,
you still like going like that.
But you don't, at least for me, I wasn't as stressed about doing it.
Like a whole layer of fear goes away.
Then it's just like little spikes and stabs of fear.
Exactly.
But the broader like being afraid of the entire thing because you've like figured out some
of the system.
Exactly.
That makes sense.
Yes.
And you don't even consciously, I don't even know that was a conscious thought I had.
Like I understand and this is what could be possible.
It's just like your brain just goes, oh yeah.
I get this.
Oh yeah.
Wait a minute.
No one's assaulting me in these mazes.
You can go to some that will.
Well, sure.
Dig through a toilet of shit.
Look for a key.
And have your shoes stolen.
Yeah.
The shit at knots is just set decoration.
Oh yeah.
Cannot be dug through.
It's real shit.
But there's a little bit.
Please don't.
No one does shit though like Six Flags is Sewer of Souls.
I'll just say that.
Sewer of Souls.
Wait, have you gone to the Six Flags one?
I have been to the Six Flags one, yes.
Is it fun?
Justin and Marissa and I were talking about maybe hitting it up.
I think that Six Flags is a lot of fun.
And it is.
Six Flags is just like how you remember it if you've been 30 years ago.
Okay.
And that's fun too if you want to see Mrs. Taz.
She's around.
Of course I want to see Mrs. Taz.
Come on.
It is the same statue from 30 years ago.
You will see her with her purple pinkish paint chipping off.
But if you're okay with that.
I love that.
If you're okay with seeing her in a sorry state.
Zombified Mrs. Taz.
That's not even the Halloween thing.
Doing Haunts 2 I feel like now as you get a little bit, you do upgrade a little bit to the point where then you do want to get fucked up a little more scare wise.
Yes.
So like there was a universal Halloween maze and they had like seven Michael Myers on the way out.
And like that was actually unusual for the pattern of horror nights.
And like you just get like scare, scare, scare, scare, scare all on the way out.
And I went ah.
I remember.
Yeah.
They've had a couple of Halloweens where it's so smart where it's like let's just have a shit ton of Michael Myers.
Every room you everywhere you turn there's a Michael Myers.
And that's so fun and scary.
And I feel that was kind of the us maze too.
Like yeah.
The bunch of those people with the scissors.
Yeah.
With the scissors and stuff.
Because when you go in the basement area.
Yeah.
And you're walking to like that classroom and stuff.
Yes.
And that area.
Yeah.
So yeah.
So I'm definitely I don't think I'll ever get to the point where I want the full shoe losing experience.
But we went to like Meow Wolf in Vegas and I was like kind of like come on scare me a little more.
Jump out a little bit.
Well I wanted it to just because it was one room that was like sensory like fucking you up with like noise and like lights.
And I was like OK a little more because it is a creepy place.
So I like a sense of unease.
Yeah.
Yes.
The whole place is yeah there's a lot of unease going on.
But I definitely was just like I was like come on.
Let's have a couple more people popping out.
They're going to be built.
I don't know when it's coming but supposedly yes permanent horror nights in Vegas in that area 51.
15.
Yeah.
So they're going to do.
It's supposedly what next year.
It's not.
It's supposedly.
It's so smart.
Yeah.
We'll go all the time.
Who was I was just talking to somebody about I think maybe it was last night.
It was last night.
Some friends we were like how about a Halloween theme park.
Yeah.
Sure.
Where it's just a spooky town.
People would fucking lose their minds for that with coasters and stuff like.
Yeah.
It's all scary.
Well if Six Flags was smarter they would just embrace that full of that siren.
Yeah right.
It would be like let's just make it year round spooky.
Yeah.
Like the thing that they well I was going to say our best step but is that right.
I don't know.
Look this would sacrifice our you know our little kid Bugs Bunny rides and the big carrot.
Right.
Yes.
With all of the orange paint peeling off.
We'd have to get rid of some of our peeling looney tunes but besides that yes if they
just wanted to like embrace terror you're in.
Yeah.
Six Flags Terror Mountain.
Sure.
The closest yeah the closest.
I'm sure there's like a little like tiny little kind of haunted things but Universal is finally
they're doing a whole Monsters Land in Florida now for this new theme park.
Cool.
So it's going to have a big Monsters ride and it's a Monsters Land.
I think it's going to look kind of like.
Restaurant.
Yeah there'll be like two rides.
A spooky restaurant.
Yeah.
Eyeballs and fingers.
I will go.
That sounds like heaven on earth.
It's all well they do the thing like where you like they blindfold you and then you touch
the witch's hair but then at some point like it is spaghetti.
You want to eat the spaghetti.
Now eat the spaghetti please.
Now you are good.
Please.
You can eat it blindfolded and pretend you're eating witches hair.
Whatever you want we don't give a shit.
So that is the opening 2025.
Okay.
And the ride is supposed to the rumor is the ride is like amazing.
It's through like a castle like Frankenstein's castle or something.
It's got all the monsters on it.
Cool.
And the robots maybe and it's a big kooka arm like the Harry Potter ride.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
So you're getting close to your wish.
You just got to travel for it.
You just got to go to Vegas.
You just got to go to speedy Florida.
Yeah.
You got to get humid.
You got to get wet and stinky.
I'll get wet and stinky.
Get some monster stuff.
Yeah.
Wow.
So that sounds awesome.
That sounds very cool.
And I think they may eventually build it out here but not within 10 years or something.
Right.
Yeah where.
But I think it probably will at least the ride will make it over here eventually.
Cool.
But we'll see.
Yeah.
I don't have any inside information.
Right.
That's just a guess.
Sure.
So yeah so.
But first of all.
But for now your scares are limited.
They're a mere two months out of the year.
Just two months.
Maybe August.
Maybe November.
Maybe it's creeping more and more on either end.
It really is like.
Expanding out and why not.
Truly after like 4th of July I'm like hell yeah.
It's Halloween time.
Just round up.
Why not.
Oh yeah.
August is bad.
August is so hot now probably everywhere you are.
I don't even want to think about August.
Let's just skip all the way to fall.
Get rid of August.
Let's get right into fall.
Come on.
Can we make this a.
I don't want to get frozen for like many years.
I don't want to live into like another century.
Can I just get frozen every year just for August.
Skip August.
Just August.
Yeah.
My whole family will do it.
We'll all do it.
Just no one does August anymore.
Yeah.
There we go.
I love fall.
Like I love the weather.
And Halloween spooky times.
And like.
Not the actual haunts.
I hate them.
Terrible haunts.
Terrified of them.
You love fall TV season when all of NBC and CBS's.
All my favorites come back.
Yeah.
The best they have to offer.
All the game shows.
But I hate the end of summer when it's like end of summer back to school.
It still is mentally draining.
It's still like oh it's a bummer.
I don't have to go to school.
Or have children who go to school.
But you still feel it.
You just feel it in the air.
It just kind of bums me out.
Because everyone's like.
Especially this less out here.
But at the Jersey Shore.
They do like a lot of places like we're closing up the weekend after Labor Day.
Like we're closing for the season.
And they'll just close for six months.
You know.
So you go there and you don't know that's the day.
And then like all right throw the taffy out.
And then just industrial drums of taffy.
I'll get thrown in acid.
Right in front of you.
The Good Taffy Shriver's is open year round.
12 months of the year.
So the Good Taffy is always available.
But yeah every now and then like if I go back to visit in August.
Like places will be like really short hours or short staff.
It's like all our workers went back to college.
So the lifeguard like there was only lifeguards at like every other beach.
Because everyone is back at school.
You know.
I guarantee we'll save you.
Every other person.
Well Scott.
So Scott just did his first full haunt at Shacktoberfest.
Wait how is Shacktoberfest?
I'm so curious.
We really like Shacktoberfest.
Yeah yeah recommended actually.
Did you go to Dark Harbor before?
No.
Because Dark Harbor ruled.
And I'm wondering if Shacktoberfest is kind of that but now with a little bit more basketball.
Well there's no.
Well not a lot.
All it has is we said some of this on the on the Patreon.
But it's if you.
All right.
I imagine a lot of it's the same because it involves the ship and you're on the ship.
There's nautical themed stuff.
But on top of that you enter through a big inflatable shack who does pre-recorded announcements for you.
Like three of them.
I think I might have to go.
That's worth it.
The little cherry of Shack on top of your otherwise evil pirate Sunday.
Yes.
Oh I think I have to go.
We really.
I've been curious about it because I loved Dark Harbor.
What's going on.
Is that the.
Was it all like scary pirate stuff and you're in the bowels of the ship.
Yeah yeah.
Like there were like three mazes throughout the Queen Mary.
OK.
And then like five or six other ones in that part in front of it.
And it was just spectacular.
It really elevates it.
I think if you if if we're saying if Dark or if Shacktoberfest was just plopped in the middle of a parking lot without a historic ship next to it maybe there's not the shack flavor doesn't go far enough.
But yeah when when put next to nautical history when put next to a ship that nobody wants and it's sinking into the sea slowly.
Long Beach would kind of get rid of.
In 2019 it had to have been we a big group of us rented rooms on the Queen Mary and then went and did Dark Harbor stayed the night and stayed the night and we were like pretty drunk and like ghost hunting like four in the morning.
Oh yeah because they were.
I don't think we said in the episode when we went into this other thing that's the engine room which is apparently open year round and.
And even Anderson told us after our episode you know those red lights you were wondering about they are on all the time.
So there is always that that's that isn't just Halloween.
So that was not really a special Halloween thing.
Anyway when we left that thing people said did you see anything in there and we're like yeah red lights.
No no no I mean did you have because some people come with their like spectrometer apps and are looking for you.
Were you doing stuff of that and it were you trying to find ghosts.
Yes.
Well just in the just where like we just kind of all around in through the halls of stuff.
I have a very funny ghost app.
I put it in air quotes.
I got it for free and it like it makes fun noises and then like words will pop up and so you'll be like is somebody around here and they're like get red and crazy and then a word will pop up.
What were you like the words.
Anything can pop up like anything.
Sandwich.
When we were when we were doing it in the Queen Mary.
I was there with a friend and her name popped up.
But then it's also like I know they could be listening to us.
Oh yeah.
Because also ads will pop up and that's the scariest part.
Crazy loud ads about like a game where it's like take a bath or whatever.
Trying to help the king escape.
Yeah it's I love it.
I got to hit up Shacktoberfest.
You got it. You got to do it real quick though.
Do you have like have you ever seen a ghost.
Do you have like a ghost in it like I had my first interaction two years ago.
Really.
I didn't see anything but I heard it.
I was in Keystone Colorado with my sister and her family.
We were skiing there and we rented a condo for the night and it was pretty small like a nice like two bedroom living room kitchen two bathrooms and one of the bathrooms is in the front part by the door and then a bathroom kind of between the rooms and they the my nieces went to bed and I was
sharing a room with them and me and my sister and brother-in-law we were hanging out and then my sister's like I'm gonna go to bed so she gets ready and my brother-in-law and I are hanging out and then we're both kind of like yeah let's let's go to bed like we shut off all the lights and everything and he goes into the hall bathroom and I go into the room to get my toiletries and stuff to then use the bathroom by the front door and as I'm in my room getting my stuff I hear a great big loud noise.
And it sounds like my brother-in-law and I'm like oh maybe he's just getting water or something and I walk out and it came from the living room and I walk out nothing's there and it's dark and there's a very dark corner and I'm like I thought Nate was there but he's still in the bathroom and I was like what and then I hear it again.
From this dark corner I'm like what the fuck what the fuck and I'm like kind of excited because I'm like I don't know what this is and I'm hanging out to be like is it like a weird fan or something you know like something in this condo that the heat or something and so I'm like waiting to see if there's like a pattern or anything and I wait for a while and then I hear again with the light on and then I hear the sound of the bathroom and I'm like what the fuck is going on and I'm like I'm so excited.
I don't know if I can figure out like any actual pattern so I run to the bathroom and I'm like so I'm like shaking my body's freaking out like I've never reacted to anything like this before like I'm trembling I've never trembled before I'm like brushing my teeth and washing my face and I didn't have my phone and I was like I can't wait to text Marcy who I have a spooky podcast with.
I'm like I think it's happening I think it's happening so then I like get ready and then I'm like bracing myself to be like okay I'm gonna fucking like I'm gonna go and I'm gonna see what's going on and I'm gonna like look and try to see if there's anything there and so I like go out and I'm walking towards this dark dark area and I'm like oh my god oh my god and then it goes huh it like sucks in a gasp and then I run to the bedroom and I'm like oh my god I'm so fucking scared.
Wow really? Yeah. And was that the first like only night you were there? The only night we were there. Yeah. And I like woke up and I was like did anybody like had everybody because I slept good then. I was so scared I watched Tommy Boy on my phone I was so scared.
I was like oh my god I need to chill out I need to chill out. And everybody slept fine and I told them I was like I think something's up here and it was like I knew we were leaving and my nieces thought it was cool they were like cool man you know like but yeah it was something happened.
Whoa that's crazy. At least it was a satisfied sounding ghost. A relaxed ghost. That ghost was chillin. Yeah yeah yeah chillin. Like completely fine with everything not mad. Maybe that energy helped you sleep well. Maybe. That might be yeah yeah.
I want to give someone else I want to make someone else as relaxed as I am. Yeah it didn't feel because you hear stories and people are like it felt malicious or like it felt very negative like there was something there and that wasn't the case.
I just was freaking out because I you know yeah I was kind of excited I was I was like I think it's a fucking ghost oh my god. But my body had never reacted like that before too which I feel is also a sign of like something was up. Yeah you know.
It was an extra level of like heightened feeling or whatever. Rather than just like oh it's a heater or something it was like no something something was there. Well that sounds ideal chill kind of exciting but calm ultimately and most of all didn't kill you and everyone in the house.
Yeah. That's why you want to have a ghost. Kind of in one of my favorite place like I grew up around Keystone like in Summit County and so it was like it was kind of fun of like this is one of my favorite places in the whole world.
All right let's have a little ghost. Let's have a little ghost interaction. The founder of the town old Milt's Keystone. I'm just glad people are enjoying my city. Thanks for skiing on the mountain.
I love to share its beauty. Your sleepy ghost they call me. Have any of you had any any experiences or anything strange? I want one. I've seen UFO. I've seen UFO like I've seen a crazy I haven't seen what it looked like. I've seen I've said this before like standing outside right over here by my where my friend used to live I saw above Universal Studios it was not part of the show a light just appear in like a flash.
And this shoots straight up into the atmosphere which is like I don't know what that I got chills. I don't know what that and like it was crazy too because my two friends who I was talking to in this field like this field area across from over on Lancashire literally two blocks from here.
Their backs were to it. So I was the only one who saw it. So we're talking we're talking talking I look up and I go whoa I gotta make a huge noise and I go like it's gone already. And it was a it was really high too so it was like I don't think Universal was testing a rocket system into space.
Into space. I think it was farther experiment was farther from Universal to a way than just but it appeared as if like it was like like playing like where a plane would fly and just a bright light and then straight up.
Never seen like what was that. What could that have been. Yeah. No clue. The only other ghost thing I got close we drove down a place called Cuba Road where I'm from.
Once and I did this because a couple girls wanted to do it. So I was like yeah okay okay. Yeah I'm excited. Yeah. That sounds awesome. And we were driving there was like there's an old I don't even what you would call it a sanitarium there basically.
And like it is a legit dark no like it's there's houses there but there are no streetlights. So when you're driving your car and this is like 10 or 15 20 minutes from where I grew up there are animals in the road.
So like it's one of the things where you're like turned on a street and it's just squirrels and they scatter because there's no light. Yeah. And there are signs that are just like turn around please.
Please don't drive. Don't come this way. Like your kids. This is a bad idea. Don't do this. And I don't even know if that I think that the hospital whatever it was as it wasn't full of people but it's it's creepy as shit.
Creepy as shit. That energy from when it was. Yeah. So you're driving we're driving down and I'm just like trying to be cool. I'm 20 I think I'm like 21 or 20 at this point. It's too old really.
And we're driving I'm driving and all of a sudden I think I've told this in this pocket before. Over some we're driving and like the girls are screaming at everything. Any any animal or whatever they're screaming and all of a sudden we get like close. I don't know if we actually saw the hospital.
But the car stops moving. The car. It's like the car is on and then I'm like the car's not I'm hitting the gas. I'm like it's not the car's not. And for two what 10 seconds 15 seconds I'm just like everything's real like everything ever.
It's like a Dracula's like every I'm just like mine is racing and I turn the car on and off and it's still it's not move it's like won't move. And I'm just like what the fuck is going on or whatever. And I felt like 15 minutes was probably three minutes. Yeah. Probably one and a half minutes. And we look and the car was probably knocked by one of the girls into neutral.
Yeah. Yeah. That's yeah. And I didn't notice. There's this cars in some kind of weird state that is neither driving reversing. What is this. And I was like OK. And then like we drive around and then OK. But for I that was the crazy because I do like I was believing in everything. Yes. And stuff in that in the short window of time. So yeah no I don't have any legit ghost stories.
Sadly unless it wasn't an elbow or unless it was not an elbow of someone I've thought that thought you were with. I think that's possible. Right. You believe I do want to believe that. Yeah. Let's put it into in for but I think romance did Fox did Fox Mulder believe in ghosts or do you believe in ghosts.
Anticipation and I speak just alien martial arts was the editing is the react this is what make I most believe these you weren't much of a improviser to have a ghost doctor come this is one that you may encounter even as a int intermediate ethn Hogana
is unusual.
I think would have dealt with the ghost he wouldn't have like referred to another office I think he would have tried to deal with it.
There was no one where it wasn't supernatural Hasselhoff never dealt with a ghost or a vampire I am now I'm sure they watch I don't know the.
They watch they watch spooky they watch nights was the spin off and in season one it was just like regular sexy crimes but at night and it wasn't doing what they wanted it to do so in season two they got rid of lounge singer Lou Rawls.
They didn't want to pay Lou Rawls anymore and they made it and X files is popular citizens made it an X files so there's one where there's like a dead Viking or some others definitely goes the Viking was a ghost.
How are you watching this just YouTube YouTube I'm OK there goes my day.
Yeah I'm watching all of they watch night hop around I'm kind of deciding I mean like there I just saw my first one from season one where there's a murder at a drag club and Hasselhoff has to do drag.
Which is one of the most demented things I've ever seen but there's so there's terms to but if you want supernatural I recommend this Viking one where he's yelling Valhalla and shooting a flaming bow and he does a Viking funeral.
Oh my God perfect television.
Wow.
We're all the best television is ripped on YouTube and poor quality and if you can't find it there the Internet our daily.
Yeah.
All right well let's talk a little of that we've talked about spooky stuff in 50 years in the 45 we're not going to be able to fit the 50 all 50 but there's it's fun to talk a little bit about the history because I'm looking up the for I assume we maybe took a glance at the first haunt.
A tiny bit.
So yeah it's 1973 it was called something else.
It's Halloween haunt.
That's all we want.
OK yes they hadn't figured out the scary farm pun yet.
Right.
And it's three it was three days and that was it.
Yeah.
And there's a like there's it's not so well documented but there's a flyer online and they have a list of what was there.
OK.
Which sounds fun.
There was a thing called the haunted shack.
I don't know if you've ever talked about which was a little experience.
Not experience.
Yeah they made it even scarier for Halloween.
They called it the monster maze.
Great.
Yes.
Is it still there.
Don't think so.
No they recreated it recreated it sometime in the last I think 10 years for one of the haunts but it's not there right now.
But it had like some like illusion like if you'd stand at the corner of the house it looks like it was like the perspective was off like the Willy Wonka.
This is like a Rube Goldberg kind of like water will run up.
Yeah.
Yes.
There were gag gags like that.
I think there's still one of those at the Calico.
There's a mine town.
On the way to Vegas.
In the way to Vegas.
Yeah I've never been there.
That still has I think this mystery haunted shack.
Oh charming.
That time.
Yeah.
More to do more year round scary stuff.
Yeah I gotta go.
On the way to Vegas.
There was so they did they in 73 rethemed the rides which I was surprised to learn.
To be spooky.
Yes.
So the Calico mine ride was the ghost of Ghostway Express.
Great.
And Timber Mountain Log ride they have listed as Satan's Sawmill.
Hell yeah.
I don't think any any major theme park is going to bring Satan into the picture.
No.
All of Satan and if they did then libs of TikTok would be all over it.
Right.
Well that did happen.
That was Fat Knots right.
We were talking about this.
Yeah.
Oh this is bonkers.
They were complaining there.
There is a circusy kind did you see the carnival show.
And the stuff they always get mad about is like someone waggling their butt dressed like hot
stuff the little devil and they're like they're doing it right in front of us now.
And the Hollywood sickos.
You know everything in general culturally or entertainment wise moves so fast it's like
well I think they did the right thing.
They seem to just kind of ignore it because like accounts like that move on to like being
mad at a candy bar TGI Fridays.
Yeah they'll find something again to be mad at.
It's also like you know like you know what this is.
This is a Halloween like party.
Like you know what your goal is.
They framed it like they didn't know.
Like this is an amusement park for children.
What's at the nighttime version of the.
And a thing that's been going for 50 years that used to have Satan's sawmill.
You're more moralistic than conservatives in 1973.
They're acting like it was at like 10 a.m.
at this camp Snoopy's stage.
Well Snoopy leaves and then people in like leather and like feather boas come out.
Snoopy is on a leather diaper and he's waggling his tail to like a Kesha song.
They make people from the audience go into the diaper with their faces.
Go and Snoopy's diaper now.
Get gunpoint.
All of the conservative media is just hell in love joy now saying won't someone please think of the children.
And that was a joke 30 years ago.
But then they don't with guns.
They can give a shit with guns.
Yeah that's fine.
No no no actually kids should think about guns all year round and run drills every day.
Yeah.
That's fine.
It's almost like and I hate to say this some of these arguments are not in good faith that they're making.
Not intellectually consistent.
It's as if they're just cherry picking things to misrepresent.
I'm also seeing that maybe Satan's sawmill was called Terror Mountain.
Fun.
Which is a fun name as well but not as good.
And now children are going to be fearful of mountains.
They're ruining our mountains right in front of us.
Yeah the wholesome places.
Where wholesome minds collapsed on grizzled miners.
Grizzled wholesome miners.
Yeah.
There was a scare zone in the ghost town which is of course still happening.
And then they had entertainment like Seymour the master of the macabre.
This is one of these guys you like the gulardies.
He's like a local horror show guy who was there for a couple of years.
Yes.
Because like Elvira was there for so many years.
And they had like well hold on I'll get to it in just one second.
They had this guy then they had Hilda the Halloween haunt spokeswitch.
Oh cool.
Sounds good.
Who was at the main gate and then they were all they have listed here is that they had Phantom of the Opera in the Calico saloon.
Full performance too.
I assume it's the full.
Oh that's cool.
Yeah.
Andrew Lloyd Webber tested it there.
Yeah it was years in the making.
Workshopped.
There were spectacular fireworks which I don't believe they have any like they haven't had fireworks for a long time.
They had something called dunking of sea monster in ghost town which sounds like it's maybe a dunk tank with a person.
Probably with somebody like dressed up like a sea monster making fun of you.
Roasting you or whatever.
And then look at this land lubber.
Doesn't have gills like me.
You idiot.
And to me the most intriguing one I don't know if you saw this.
Which I couldn't find video of and maybe I didn't look hard enough is Tales of Rock Horror featuring Hello People.
What is Hello People.
You hear that and you think up with people.
Yes.
But that's not right.
Hello People is different.
But I think it's adjacent.
Must be.
So The Hello People which I've seen it referred to is a band from the 60s and 70s.
They were like put together by a record guy but they were very political.
And what.
Whoa.
They're doing it in front of our kids.
They're doing it.
They were doing it in front of the kids and I'll show you a photo of them.
Not only they were very political they were also dressed like mimes.
A band of mimes.
Funny.
Like this is them.
Now does it look exactly like Kiss.
Kind of.
Yeah.
Are you making an accusation here of Kiss.
This is funny.
Yes.
They are.
So The Hello People they supported Todd Rundgren on maybe two tours.
God that sounds.
Because it sounded familiar to me for some reason.
Maybe that's why.
Yes.
So I'm listening to some of the music and I don't it's not the songs are maybe not great.
But there's certainly like a 60s vibe you can appreciate.
OK.
It's like the strawberry alarm clock but without the song.
But the vibe of like incense and peppermint or whatever.
OK.
And I'm like OK.
And then there's a clip from the Smothers Brothers and the Smothers Brothers are just
like very kind of somber and they're like you know this is a controversial song and
we don't necessarily agree with this song but we feel that the opinions are important
to express and we're going to show.
And then there's about two minutes of miming.
No way.
And like pretending a guitar is a gun.
And then the lyrics are not.
I mean this probably was outrageous for the time.
So this wasn't a joke on the.
No this was a very serious anti-war song which I mean as far as I'm trying to listen to
the lyrics and it's just like we're all people and like it's just I think just the idea that
it was anti-war was a big deal wasn't like they were saying.
Smothers Brothers being like.
Yeah.
Can we say this.
No no no we are going to go we will drop bombs ourselves.
Yeah we will.
We will.
On break on hiatus from the show.
Yeah.
Sometimes stuff that got slapped with very political back then the song is like don't
dump gasoline in streams.
Yes that is kind of the vibe of this song.
Maybe and maybe I misheard I didn't hear like in a very like crazy lyric or something but
yeah that vibe was just basically like we shouldn't be at war and people like what.
Can they say that.
They should make like other mimes and shut up.
Here's the hello people.
I don't know.
Wow.
So we got to find this show but then so I guess they weren't all politics because they're
doing not scary the original conservative.
Yeah yeah.
Mike was this the flyer you were looking at.
Halloween haunt one.
That's awesome.
Seymour this is you know if you want to communicate scary guy idea I feel like wide brimmed hat
and mustache is just like oh well that's an undertaker of some sinister man maybe.
Yeah.
Very scary.
He looks like he's like a like a Carradine or somebody.
He's a creepy looking character actor.
Yeah.
Yes.
I was impressed with the line.
I was like I kind of impressed with the original lineup.
Yeah that's awesome.
And this has never been done before so they're inventing this.
They're inventing the genre.
I have one more a little bit of history and we'll talk about stuff from this year.
But yeah they do seem to have these like you know not I don't want to say mascots it's
like like performers like here's there's the face of it this year because that became Elvira
and for a while for a number of years it was Wolfman Jack.
Wolfman Jack raspy voiced DJ of American Graffiti and Midnight Special fame and God bless whoever
posted this on YouTube.
Hollow Studios posted a little bit of a Wolfman Jack show that you could see in the Good
Time Theater and this is in 1977.
Oh my god.
Does anything come to mind when I mention 1977?
Pop culturally.
Star Wars.
Yep you got it.
I mean first here wait I should have I should have said this part first that first he comes
out and has a real crow or a raven on his arm.
And he's got the big glove to support it.
And then he's and he's like dressed in crazy spangles and then he starts singing Shake
Your Booty with the raven still on his arm.
This might be the greatest show on earth.
Perfect that sounds awesome.
It's a Halloween show yes.
It's 1977.
I wonder how old he was at this point.
I don't know I'm timeless baby.
He was born in 38.
He was not old he was like 39.
Wow.
But so due to the 77 nature of it and you know Nott's has kept this up with the hanging.
They always address the pop culture of the year and Star Wars is new this year you got
to deal with it.
Incredible hair incredible goatee incredible big open butterfly collar.
Wolfman Jack so rad.
The Todd Rundgren song about him.
Todd loves Nott's I bet.
So we must have.
But anyway what the Star Wars thing seems to become at least a lot of it was posted
in this YouTube video is just the characters from Star Wars being introduced coming to
the microphone and saying hello.
And here's a little clip of what that is like.
What?
It's just chewy.
Yeah.
Sounds sick.
Start with the character.
What C3PO says I love so much.
Hello.
C3PO.
Okay so.
He.
C3PO just says hello and then walks away from them.
This is just a parade of Star Wars introductions and then they leave.
But what he says on the way out is alright give it up for PCPO.
He does a double P. We got RT do do here.
And then it becomes this little like he fights with Darth Vader and who calls it who very
insultingly calls him Wolfman Slack.
But he seems to win the fight and what's the best about this little Star Wars routine
happening is the a great reveal at the end of who is in the audience.
Now I want to point them out to you.
In the audience tonight is Mr. Gary Kurtz the producer of Star Wars and American Graffiti.
Would you stand up Gary?
He's out of breath.
And sitting next to him I think is Carrie Fisher who played a cost princess Leia from
Star Wars.
Carrie Fisher would you stand up please.
She's there.
He's so out of breath.
And then he says alright come back see us we got three more shows tonight.
But I love where Princess Leia from we presumably.
Shit.
Oh what is it?
I don't blame her because I didn't even think he was like a song and dance and certainly
not like a stunt man.
Oh I didn't either.
He just had to fight Darth Vader and he feels like we would if we had to fight.
Give me a sec.
I gotta keep screaming at you guys.
He's our age.
Yeah we are.
Yes I know how I was on the bounce floor at the Chektova Fest.
Give me a minute.
Hey okay Darth Vader he really took it out of me.
The only food in the green room is Mrs. Knott's fried chicken and biscuits so I am struggling
out here.
My bag got fried chicken, fried chicken, breakfast, lunch and dinner.
So old Jack's struggling a little bit.
There's no water just boysenberry punch.
Boysenberry.
Boysenberry everything.
Hey Luke Skykicker's been on the toilet all day so at least old Jack's doing better than
Skykicker.
I gotta get to the dressing room to do a little more space dust.
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah I want more before my next show.
I'm not really going to be feeling the force if I get my space dust.
Chewbacca stole it from me.
I was howling way before Chewbacca.
Anyway here's the turtles.
Jack no that's not you're not on the radio.
Oh okay sorry here's Crosby stills in a...
He doesn't know how to not introduce bands.
Man Jack.
Boy I wish I could have Carrie Fisher watch that.
Carrie Fisher the year months after Star Wars came out watched an out of breath Wolfman
kind of like half swing lightsaber.
Oh no I believe 19 years old.
Carrie Fisher.
19 or 20 yeah.
Boy living the best life that ever was.
She's right at the beginning this is where it's starting.
This is where it's starting.
Boy I haven't even started the screenwriting yet.
It's all ahead of you Carrie.
Ahsoka Tano is here.
And this cast of rebels.
Sabini?
Hey Ackinon's coming in.
Ackinon is Darth Vadeer.
That's a spoiler alert.
When I figure out how to log into Benzie Plus I'm gonna watch this.
Yiddle Yiddles here.
Female Yoda.
Dexter Detper.
The man with the diner.
Oh no he's haunting.
I started playing it again.
He haunted my life.
Wolfman Jack's haunting the studio.
Let him know.
Let him know you love her.
I love that he's trying to remember the name of everything and he's just been in a 10 minute
Star Wars sketch and he's like she was Princess Leia from Star Wars.
You know all that shit you just saw.
You get it.
You know I did it and she did it first.
I got her name right.
I should get points for that.
So that's man.
Now this is I don't mean to.
We're coming in.
The history is incredible.
So every year they've got a big job ahead of them to match the history of Out of Breath
Wolf Man Jack.
But did you either of you.
Betsy went and Mike went.
Did you guys see anything that you thought matched the quality of what I just showed
you?
No.
I mean not on that.
They fell short ultimately.
I will say this.
Everything is a little too polished.
And I mean that because there's not like probably a drunkish DJ on stage just like mumbling
his way through the copy they've given him.
Yeah they've been rehearsing.
Did you see.
Oh God we saw a show.
I missed I think the show you're talking about.
Yeah the like mad scientist and his little friend.
Oh yeah.
His little sister.
What was it?
They're trying to make the best lady or something.
Something like that.
One of the shows the outside show has a little bit of a send up of a recent Disney situation.
I don't know if you guys saw this.
Oh I watched this entire thing.
The show.
Did you watch The Hanging?
The Hanging.
No.
The Hanging uncancelled.
This is a show they do every year that's their like pop culture.
It's what Bill and Ted.
Which is you know like it's rude and it's not PC.
From that title uncancelled I'm like let me watch this crap and judge this crap and then
I'm watching it and I'm like I like a lot of the jokes.
I liked a lot of them because there was like somebody was trapped in a crate at one point
and they say that crate's smaller than a billionaire's submarine.
And then somebody gets shot and they say nice shooting Alec Baldwin.
I'm like you know what.
Those are pretty.
They actually are.
Yeah.
You know what they sort of are.
It's like Norm MacDonald weekend update jokes.
Yeah.
A little harsh.
A little harsh in a way.
And I was digging it up until like oh and okay and what you were referring to they made
fun of how the dragon in Phantasmac Disneyland caught on fire and has been gone will be gone
for an entire year.
Dude they had a dragon catch on fire.
That's great.
They made fun of World of Color.
They said that the dragon went down faster than Galactic Star Cruiser.
Like this is fucking this is kind of good.
This is a little edgy.
Dragon catching on fire is objectively funny.
Yes.
The park down the road has to do that.
I love that it's also like we got to make fun of the park down the road right.
They're the ones with the money.
They have it all.
They're doing fine.
Let's have fun.
It's punching up is what it's doing which it also does to there's always like who is
the big bad of the year that they're chasing and this year Elon Musk a correct target.
Honestly great.
Yeah.
That's who we should be shitting on and they didn't do a hanging because I think they're
finding that a noose is an inappropriate thing.
Sure yeah.
They make some jokes about that.
They're all like alright shut up.
But they do they have a special way to get rid of Elon which is we're doing a Twittery
branding and then they take a big hot X and they brand it on his butt.
That's good.
That's what Elon should get.
I gotta go back to that scary farm.
You don't have to go back.
I'm sorry to tell you.
Yeah yeah.
At least watch the video.
Check out the video.
Yeah yeah yeah.
At least watch the video.
Check out the hanging next year.
I always assumed I would like hate every second of this and I kind of like until they fall
into a pit at the end because they they're like wait but Elon's not the true villain.
Who's really bad who's on his platform and it's Karens and then a bunch of Karens come
out you're like okay all right I see that but then they get confused and they start
calling the Karens social justice warriors and saying like it's because of you that we
have paper straws that we can't and like well no those are no no no.
That's separate.
So they did not look closely enough at that whole thing.
But then they also make fun of their own little mythology and this is maybe something to talk
about for this year at scary farm.
They can't do the hanging the way they used to but they do it with something new at not
this year the no boo necklace.
Yes.
Which I like that they're making fun of their own thing.
So the no boo necklace is that a thing that you can light up that you put on to show that
you do not want to get scared in the scare zones.
Not the mazes the mazes you got no choice and they can't see you in those.
I did not know that okay.
Yeah so it doesn't apply in the mazes but I'm looking at I'm like I hate to be I mean
this apparently makes me a Karen if I would be in it according to their rules but I kind
of like maybe I would do the no boo necklace because something I don't like and that I
didn't feel so much at checktoberfest that you I don't like feeling like I'm going to
get scared all the time.
I'm going to get scared in the maze and I'm going to leave the maze and I'm going to get
scared more.
So I like the I like breaks maybe.
Yeah.
So maybe I would do this no boo necklace.
The necklace saying Sea World and Busch Gardens I think I've been doing this for a little
while now.
Oh okay.
Walking around.
Yeah and you get a little break you don't get scared walking around.
I'll say this though there are territories so you do have it on the map where you have
you know you can get sanctuary.
Oh okay.
The scare zone.
Yeah.
Johnny Rockets.
Johnny Rockets is a sanctuary.
Okay thank god.
Yeah I feel almost any bar.
Any bar yeah you're not getting like.
You're not spilling your yeah.
$20 yeah spilling a $20 pot down.
One dude got us all really well right after we went to the saloon and got some beers and
stuff and I was taking a picture of Mano and his husband sitting with those funny like
ladies those fake ladies.
Oh yeah yeah.
Yeah.
And I was like taking a picture and this dude came out of nowhere and scared us all.
Like I almost dropped my beer I almost dropped my phone.
But then and then like we all just cheered him on and he just slowly walked away and
then came back for a picture.
He was great.
Wow.
Yeah.
Not scare actors watching videos I feel like not scare actors are great at coming up you
know and doing an unusual scare but also I saw in some of the mazes they would just follow
you like someone just followed you.
Yes I got followed a couple of times.
Yeah and that is so unnerving to me.
It's so like where you're just like whew made it out of that let's go to this next room
and then like I would turn thinking it was Mano or Justin or someone and it's a fucking
creepy like creepy person stalking you.
It's so good.
We're like you kind of lose that at Universal now.
Yeah that's not there's not as much of that you got a little bit.
Yeah you get a little bit.
Maybe we got followed a little bit but not a lot.
Yeah not so you get followed more.
My other impression watching videos is that some of the mazes are very elaborate this
year like very long and very elaborate.
Super long.
Yeah.
And they are like every single thing is on purpose like there's it does it's not there's
not a lazy thing going on like every single thing.
Yeah they're incredible.
A lot of giant puppets.
Tons.
Tons of giant puppets.
Betsy what are the highlights from the year?
I loved the cinema slasher.
Yeah.
One.
That was awesome.
That's a new one and that was replacing the whatever the clown one was from last year
Dark Ride.
Which had been there for a long time which is in like a room they sometimes use for like
events I think Jason and I ate like macaroni there at a press event once.
Nice.
Spilled all over my press badge.
It was awesome you like enter into a movie lobby and there's like a zombie guy giving
you popcorn and screaming at you.
Yes that part was my favorite even like the lobby yeah.
And with this song like let's all go to the lobby let's all play and then you go into
the theater and like a movie's starting and of course there are all these like or not
probably like five or six people sitting in the like theater seats and you don't know
who's reading who's not and they get you.
And then you go through like multiple.
You go through the screen itself.
Yes.
Into the movie essentially.
Into the movie and then it follows like multiple kind of different classic slashery style movies
like a sorority house a very like Jasony camp one a Michael Myers vibe one it was awesome
and then you like you go through the lobby again and it's like let's all go to the you
know like all fucked up and shit and then you like see more of a movie.
It was spectacular.
Yeah it was you end up in the slaughter house I feel like a couple of mazes I feel like
you end with like pigs hanging.
Yes lots of pigs.
Uh huh.
Those let's all go to the lobby characters are a little scary these freaks made of popcorn
buckets and wieners.
You spoke at chocolate bar.
Oh there was a camera headed monster.
Yes.
That made weird sounds that looked really weird.
Yeah.
A camera head.
Yes.
He's mad because his film is dying.
Yeah he's hanging in there hoping that Tarantino or Christopher Nolan makes a new movie so he
can get a game.
Use me.
There's only like three guys that hire me now.
I'm not IMAX but I'm still good.
I'm still pretty good.
You can appreciate me.
This one was the only one where I was like brainstorming what I would do like I was like
oh they could have done like three more movies and made them get like worse or bad like in
the way the leprechaun goes to space or in the hood.
You could have gotten progressively like stupider with them.
That's really a fun idea.
You gotta go to space.
Because I really like this maze but I was like oh it didn't feel like it built as much
in a way that I wanted it to.
Okay.
And then I was like oh you know what you could have done.
That's really fun.
Yeah like a slasher in space or whatever.
Yeah or any of the dumb like seventh sequels for any horror movie.
This was a good I think I do like this one more than Dark Ride which I never I don't
know if you remember that one.
I went to Knotts two years ago.
Yeah it would have been there.
It was probably there.
I'm sure I had a blast.
There were clowns.
Nasty clowns.
Yeah.
And it was a good one.
Clowns are awful.
It wasn't my favorite one.
Yeah.
But yeah so there were what else was there?
So there were a couple that were from two years ago that I just loved.
Waxworks.
Oh yeah.
Incredible.
Waxworks maybe is the most unnerving one.
Because there are like you know like there's an evil we've looked we've said this name
before now I have to look it up.
The evil like wax man who like makes weird humans like half human half wax things.
Wax man Jack baby.
Wax.
It's eaten up.
And there's like vats of wax.
And you get little dripping.
You feel very much like I can't touch this hot hot wax.
Yes.
If I touch this it's going to burn me.
I love that one.
It is so incredible.
And once again like the detail is so nuts in there.
And that's all body horror to me is still like the scary maybe the scariest horror like
movie wise.
Like the first Hellraiser one is just like.
Oh my god.
Both the first two.
Just like the skin is ripped off and you're like that is too realistic and too scary.
But Waxworks gives me that feeling where you're just like seeing either it's a dummy or it's
a person in makeup and you're still like I don't want to get hot wax on my face.
Some of the other stuff I'm like okay I'm not going to be turned into like a fish man.
Right.
I'm not that worried about that but I am worried about.
But like a freak like turning me into a wax figure or a mannequin.
Have you seen the movie tourist trap.
No.
It's from like late 70s or early 80s.
It's awesome.
That's all I'll say.
It's streaming on places.
Check it out.
I don't want to spoil it.
From 79 it looks oh boy.
It's a blast.
It's wild.
I think for it's two years old or three years old Mesmer I really like.
Which is the.
Loved Mesmer.
I had the elephants farting right.
Yes.
The farting is happening.
Oh Justin brought this up right.
This is the elephant fart.
Yeah.
You walk into a I guess elephant stall or whatever and it starts like at first I didn't
even see the big elephant butts but they're like little clown dudes who are like kind
of farting towards you and be like smell it.
And then you continue walking and there are these two huge elephant butts and their little
tails are flapping from farts and then another clown keeps going like smell it.
Smell it.
And then this guy's like OK.
Smell it dude.
What does it smell like in there.
It doesn't smell like shit.
No yeah.
That would be too fucked up.
Too much.
Elephant farts smell nice like peanuts.
Yeah.
Is it like dirt.
I'm trying to remember.
I think it is kind of more just dirt like.
Yeah.
Like kind of stinky stall but not poo poo.
I wonder.
I think it's like a little bit of a smelly smell.
Yeah.
It's like a little bit of a smelly smell.
It's like stinky stall but not poo poo.
I wonder.
OK OK.
You know.
So Savannah.
Because there's fart smell in the Minions Rite Universal.
Oh yes.
Oh my god there it is.
Fart gun.
So there maybe is some manufacturer that does smell fart smell for theme parks.
I'm sure.
So I don't know what they're.
There must be and that calibration has got to be tough.
What's a like handleable fart.
You don't want it to be so toxic.
They had to.
Sulfury.
Right.
You want just a classic traditional that passes very quickly.
Yeah.
Pass fast.
They had to test it.
You know they had to test it.
Yeah they had to.
For weeks and months.
I'm the fart tester.
I make sure the farts aren't too intense.
It's nice work if you can get it.
You know what it is.
Worst jobs that could be doing.
Sample one made me puke.
Right down puke.
This one just made me fart a lot.
I don't know what that means.
Is that good or bad?
It's not good.
You want to use my farts?
Okay.
I'll get a jar behind them.
I'll jar them up for you free of charge.
There you go huh?
Keep hiring me please.
I think this works.
Please I need this.
Do I get residuals for my fart smell being used in perpetuity?
Every time it's used please.
Tiger wants to use AI farts and that ain't right.
I'm going on strike unless I get...
You can tell when they're fake farts.
When they're artificial intelligence farts.
I'm willing to go to the park and do them live.
Do them live.
In the FDG Fart Doers Guild.
You get me and my two buddies, you put a funnel up behind us and we'll do it all night.
We don't care.
We got you covered.
Don't worry about it.
We can't let AI take our jobs.
Just eat us the leftover Presmac and cheese.
That should get us going.
You can get a three pack it looks like on Temu, that website that sprung up overnight
and became suspiciously popular.
It did?
A different spray bot.
This is like Shine where it's just drop shipping junk.
These scents are smell from hell, toxic bomb and stinky ass.
Stinky ass.
Okay, we got to order that.
Jason order them.
Fart tasting.
Send them to your apartment, Jason.
That's for on cast next year.
A little fart tasting menu for all of us.
Very nice.
Can you guess what now?
I think this one, I'm going to call this one a stinky ass.
That doesn't seem like a bomb because I wouldn't call it a bomb.
Just a general stink.
A day to day stink you could live with.
Disappointed by smell from hell was expecting more.
When you use hell to describe something it's gotta be fucked up.
It's got to be big.
Yeah.
This didn't get me.
So they have a play, the one called the Chilling Chambers, which is new.
Which one is that one?
That's the one that's a best of essentially Halloween mazes.
Yes, that ruled.
It had a lot of cool doll stuff.
There was, okay so we talked about this recently, there's like a plot what I would call a plush
pile as fixed to the wall.
Did you say ooh to the phrase plush pile?
Yeah, that's so gross.
Okay, because that's what-
It's so gross.
That's what Justin Marissa determined last week.
Maybe I've made this phrase up plush pile and then Marissa said it sounded like a vagina,
which is not how I intended it.
Marissa!
You dirty dog!
No, she said that with a microphone in front of her.
What does it make you think of that's so gross?
Just nasty, like nasty old stuffed animal.
Yeah, okay so you're thinking literally it's just kind of gross to you because you've imagined
them all being like 30 years old on the drive.
Eww, yeah!
Dirty plush.
Where you're just like what's going on with these man?
You have like a really cursed birch or something?
Ernie.
I have an Ernie from when I was-
A cursed one?
Well, he's from when I was a kid and his crotch has been ripped open and his eyeballs have
fallen off and his ears are ripped and his hair is patchy and I still have him, he's
still hanging out.
I guess he's cursed but I don't-
People were, when we posted it online people were pretty scared of him.
I can see why you would be scared of him but I look at him and I just feel pure love.
And that's all you can do?
Yeah, but I guess he's cursed, yeah.
He's casually cursed.
He can still love someone who is cursed.
That was a really fun one.
Yes, and I was, because sometimes it's not always apparent what the lore of it is, so
I was reading about it and there's a Keep the Keeper character that exists in this maze.
Oh wow.
Right.
Yeah, and the Keeper is the Keeper of Haunt History at Nott's.
I feel Justin was explaining this to me.
He's like, okay.
So the Keeper's Cathedral, which is where we walked into that looked like kind of a
church, is where all the mazes go once they're done.
Right, because there were like graveyards and stuff with all of the different mazes.
You saw names of like, they were shouting out old mazes as well but then they would
go in a few of the highlights from over the years, which was great because obviously we
didn't get to do these throughout the years.
Right.
They should have, but there's one that has the plush wall, there's one that's like,
almost felt like Blade Runner.
You're waiting outside to get inside a neon bar looking thing and there's like loud music
playing.
There's like a lady dancing in a cage.
Yeah, and then you go by like a weird like bar top.
And the whole, like the vibe, the switching vibe really was fun to see like all the old
stuff.
And I was like, oh, these mazes are even better than the ones they have now.
Yes.
I was like, I wish I had seen.
They seem so cool.
So I do wonder, because there's not such great documentation.
I was like, I wonder if they like almost plussed up the way these are.
Right.
Or if this is just how they were back in the day.
Obviously they didn't save the wall.
They didn't save the plush pile, I assume.
Plush pile wall.
But it was a fresh one.
Fresh plush pile.
Nothing like a fresh plush pile.
Let's do a play now, everybody.
The mazes that were from the 90s and 2000s, so I guess they were newer, but we went through
the underground, which I believe is the club, the carnival of carnivorous clowns, lore of
the vampire, and then the doll factory.
The doll factory.
That part really messed me up.
If you like haunted dolls or don't, that one will mess you up.
Did you know you can buy haunted dolls on eBay and Etsy?
And the people selling them will have a big description of the spirit that's in them.
And it's very fun if you're ever bored and want to see haunted dolls.
It's so fun.
Because Robert the haunted doll is in a museum.
Are you a Robert fan?
A Robert fan.
So you have the haunted doll.
Sure.
If I were to ever go see him, I would not take a picture.
I do think of the ice rift.
It'd be shitty.
You can ask him, though.
The words you can say, excuse me, Robert, can I take a photo of you?
I don't even think I want to talk to him.
I think I'd be like, there he is.
Okay, I'm going to get out of here.
I would say hello.
I'd be polite.
You got to be polite.
And then I would move on.
Yeah, yeah.
Give him his space.
Good to see you, Robert.
What would you think would happen if Jason showed up dressed as Robert and met Robert
and didn't say anything?
Oh my God.
Because Robert is wearing a little sailor suit.
Right.
Oh.
So if Jason showed up and like kind of silently made fun of Robert in the case.
No!
It would be a tribute.
I feel like at minimum my flight is getting canceled on the way back.
That's what Kirstie puts on you.
Just a little convenience.
But the rental car is probably exploding.
Robert strikes again.
There's a delay on Delta flight 1213.
Well, and that was the last flight of the day.
So I have to wait.
And now you sit down with your sailor suit on.
Hulu's charging two dollars more a month.
Robert strikes again.
Robert.
How dare you, Robert?
I haven't finished killing Eve, Robert, and you know that.
Do they hook up or not?
Yeah.
Or kill each other.
The end of the doll one is like there's a moving floor that makes it feel like a doll
is holding.
Yes.
Yeah.
You basically.
Yes.
Which is pretty crazy.
It was so cool.
Yeah.
And then yeah, you leave through the graveyard so you see other names of mazes throughout
the years.
That one was maybe my favorite actually of the year.
It was really cool.
And it wasn't, that one wasn't as maybe scary as Waxworks or anything, but I just love it.
I love the history.
It was just so fun.
Yeah.
Love the history.
I told Justin I was coming on to do Not Scary and he was so like, oh, I want to talk about
it because he loves it.
Oh, no.
He loves it.
He's reading a book about the history of it.
We should have had him on again too.
I know.
I was like, come do it with me, man.
We put him in the Purge box.
Let's call it next year.
Justin, that's a message from me to you.
Yeah, I think next year be like, let Justin go.
We'll celebrate its 50th anniversary, plus one.
Plus one.
That's big.
It's big.
50th anniversary.
That's big.
It's big.
51th.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't sleep on 51.
I really enjoyed, and this was there two years ago when I went also, the depths.
Yes.
Yeah.
And that huge creatures.
These gentlemen toured the depths with the light on.
We toured the depths with the lights on and it was very interesting.
Cool.
It was very interesting.
It was interesting how they did everything.
Informative.
I don't understand how they do it.
It's so cool.
Yeah.
I've said this probably 10 times already, but just the effect of the laser with the
fog where you have the characters coming through above the fog, if it's water or a swamp or
something.
The first time that I ever saw that was at Queen Mary, Dark Harbor.
Oh, okay.
And it blew my mind.
It was like a swamp haunt or whatever, and the whole way through you're walking through
this green fog.
It was so cool.
Oh, wow.
Dude, people popping up from it and then going back down.
You're like, where'd they go?
It rules.
Geez.
Man, they aren't doing any laser ocean this year.
So you're not going to get that if you go to Shackatobos.
Damn it, Shack.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on.
You drop the ball on that one.
Hey, there we go.
But they do have, but if you do want Captain Shack's special rum punch.
So you got to weigh it.
No laser fog, but you do get special rum punch.
I do want Captain Shack's rum punch.
It's confusing because it can be a regular shot of just Captain Morgan or it's a shot
of Captain Morgan and Grenadine, but it's loud in there and you can't hear.
And you can only take one.
And they call it a chaser even though it's not just a chaser, it's a mix shot.
Oh, boy.
I'm so confused.
It was an accidental escape room because I thought I'd never leave.
I thought we'd be discussing the logic of the shots all night.
Scott tried to take two of them and they're like, no, no, no, stop, the curse.
Really?
Robert.
Yeah, because we paid an extra amount of money to get the shot before the maze.
Yeah.
But we thought it was a real bar, but it's actually a tiny room in a maze.
Yes.
If you wanted, you need Captain's combo to do the.
That would happen with in Dark Harbor where there would be secret mazes.
Oh, okay.
Or I mean secret bars within the maze.
Right.
Okay.
And it was always, it was fun.
And yeah, sometimes just like all we have is a shot of something nasty.
And you're like, okay.
Yeah, all right, all right.
I paid extra.
What choice do I have?
Betsy, it's 1130.
Oh shit.
You want to wrap it up?
Okay.
I should wrap it up.
Yeah.
Take us to the door.
Sure.
I mean, not scary.
I remember for years hearing people being like, it's the best.
It's the best haunt you could go to.
And I was like, I don't know, Horror Nights is pretty fun.
And then I went two years ago for the first time and I was like, yes, this is the best
haunt.
Yeah.
It wins.
It's prepared for a lot of people too, it feels like.
Whereas other places, like they add more bars.
They like, I don't know, they just felt ready for a big search.
We also went this year early in October.
Nobody was there.
Oh, that's a good tip.
That's good to know.
Okay.
Yeah.
We went on a Wednesday night and we like, we got the front of line passes, but we totally
didn't need them.
Right.
But it's still a rule to walk on.
But like, I think the longest line was 15 minutes maybe.
Geez.
Great.
Yeah.
That's great.
Well, they're pros.
They've been at it for 50 wonderful years.
They have what's up.
Rightfully wonderful years.
They've given us so much great live entertainment.
Uh huh.
Oh, you know it baby.
Oh yeah baby.
I'd be there if I could, if I was still alive, you know I'd be jamming out with the Jedus
and R.T. Beep Beep and all of them.
He does though in fact know Jar Jar Binks.
Jar Jar Binks is my favorite.
I love the Gungan city.
Ceboba, I know him.
Bossing ass.
Went to college with Ceboba.
Some things are sacred.
I don't mess those up.
So yeah, it's still, yeah, of the major ones, it still is my favorite too.
Yeah.
So yeah, I'm waiting for somebody, something to beat it or universal to beat it.
I don't think it's happening.
I don't think it's happening either.
They're in practice.
I don't think it's ever going to happen.
They're the best in the biz.
You know who else is the best in the biz?
Bootsy DeSarro who has survived Haunt Cast the Fright.
So happy you could do this.
Thank you for having me.
So glad you came.
Let's exit through the crypt shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, right now, Mano Gappin and I, we have a spooky podcast that's happening every Friday
in October called Too Spooky to Handle.
It's free through Earwolf Presents.
You can get it anywhere.
And we've been improvising, we improvised four horror movies with a bunch of our friends.
So every Friday a new one's released.
So check it out.
Oh, that sounds great.
Spookiest day Friday.
Okay.
And as for us, for three bonus episodes every month, check out Haunt Cast the Fright, The
Cemetery Gate or get one more bonus episode on our RIP tier Crypt 3.
You'll find all of that at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And as you're hearing this episode on October 20th, this evening is the big Haunt Cast the
Fright live spooktacular at Dynasty Typewriter.
That's in Los Angeles.
Two shows, two totally different topics.
If you're not in town, we're doing the live stream.
We'll have video of it.
We'll be in costumes.
There will be much to see, fun shows in general.
What will we be?
Will Jason be Robert the doll?
You'll have to watch and find out.
Oh, maybe.
Can you find a sailor suit in time?
I've already ordered so many items.
Hmm.
But not a sailor suit.
You should always just put one in every anytime you order any.
I have one automatically in the Amazon.
I'm getting double A batteries.
Better pick up another sailor suit.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.