Forever.
Dog.
When hinges creak in dork-filled chambers.
And strange Pennsylvania pronunciations
echo through the halls.
That is the time when good boys are present.
Practicing their discomfort at mild sexuality
and
Is this haunted intro actually stretching
or is it time to start the show?
There's no turning back now.
It's hot cast the fright live.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Ah, how do you do?
Hello, hello and welcome to the first ever
hot cast the fright live.
Oh yes, oh yes.
It's the only, it's a show that does not
just make out of date 1960s pop culture references.
Tonight we also dress like them, that's right.
For anyone just listening, you may not be aware.
Nothing, nothing.
That was fast.
Well, first of all, you may not be aware
Mike was wearing bolts.
He is now wearing half a bolts, not for long.
Darn, darn, darn, darn, darn.
Carmen.
May perhaps that all implies to the listener
that we have finally assumed our ultimate true form
we are last dressed as the Munsters.
Here, let's go, let's go down the line.
Who do we got over here?
Herman.
He sure is.
And I'm old grandpa Gardner.
Hello, hello.
Come visit my restaurant.
You'll find me reading a newspaper in the lobby
and I won't acknowledge you.
And over here.
And I'm little Eddie and I don't remember
any of his little things.
Although we did have multiple conversations
on whether I would be Eddie or grandpa.
I know, it felt like a default.
I mean, ultimately height order had to be taken into
consideration. Had to be honored.
Height order, costumes, all the best parts of podcasting
of an audio medium.
Enjoy it listener, but also enjoy it people here in person.
Thank you for coming.
Enjoy it people live streaming.
Thanks to dynasty typewriter.
Hello live streamers, hello live screamers.
We're so excited.
Here, let's take a seat.
No reason not to take a seat.
Well, Herman, if you want to do it in sort of, you know,
long legged, stiff legged fashion, feel free.
Not to put you on the physical comedy spot.
Yeah, fuck up that chair we don't own.
The bit was he would break things when he sat in them.
Oh, see again.
I think we're discovering we don't really know the monsters.
We just like dressing like them.
That's good. Yep. Great.
Okay. Wonderful.
And nothing is broken.
Oh, wait, wait, Jason, don't sit on your little guy.
You got a little guy with you too.
Oh, I got the little guy.
We did know that about Eddie.
Yeah.
Eddie has his little wolf.
And Jane found a little wolf man.
It's a dog toy wolf man.
Cause all of the others were,
the movie appropriate ones were 40 to $50.
And this one was significantly less
and we can give it to the dog later tonight.
He can have a good time.
It's a thrill.
It's a thrill to be here,
but it's especially a thrill to assume this,
this monster form.
And for me personally,
even being kind of like a cheap version
of a of grandpa monster feels really great.
Just given the like pedigree
of who has played this part in the past.
Of course you've got Al Lewis.
Obviously Al Lewis is the, you know,
the primary in the originator.
And he's great and his restaurant was great.
But last year in a new iteration of the monsters,
somebody else joined the proud lineup of grandpa portrayers.
And that is an actor named Daniel Roebuck.
Give it up for Daniel Roebuck.
Daniel Roebuck comes up a lot on the show
because he also played another role
that is very important to us.
The role of Jay Leno in the HBO TV movie,
The Late Shift.
Yeah.
Which we covered in one of our longest episodes ever.
The less theme park, the longer we go.
And I bring all this up for a reason
because are we up to, are our stills up?
Mike, can you bring up the picture
I've kept secret from you?
Look at that!
My bolts fell off, I'm in such shock.
Roebuck!
Listeners, I met Daniel Roebuck
and I've kept it secret from my host for weeks.
This happened on October 1st
and I wanted to tell you as soon as it happened.
What?
And then we keep doing episodes
and I'm like, is now the time?
Is now the time?
No, no, no.
And then eventually it just became,
I'm gonna be dressed as grandpa.
I'm gonna show everybody that I met a grandpa.
I met a grandpa!
Wow.
Look at that!
And that is, I know that background.
That is the historic Tam O' Shanter lobby.
That is it.
Tam O' Shanter.
I met Daniel Roebuck in the lobby
of Walt Disney's favorite restaurant.
Now I feel like doing it on stage is usurping the,
I've been wanting to see your guys' faces.
I'm shocked!
I haven't announced this news for so long.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm also shocked that you could keep a secret from us that long.
I told as many other people as I could
to get the Jones out.
But I knew ultimately I had to tell you on mic
and then eventually on stage.
History, I couldn't believe it.
What did the average person say
when you said the sentences
to indicate what happened here?
Well, you are assuming that I texted any average people.
Fair enough, fair enough.
Griffin Newman knew right away.
My wife Farron knew right away.
A gasp in a text message form.
And this photo was taken by a friend of the show, Buzz Buzz.
And he, yeah, well thanks for the woos for that.
It's crazy because on his very phone the day before,
he texted a photo of this man,
but due to his role in a Star Wars cartoon.
Here's a real test of the audience.
Does anyone know who Daniel Roebuck plays in Star Wars?
Grease.
Wait, Grease was the name?
Wow, thank you.
It's a video game.
Got some Grease heads here.
Grease heads here.
Grease.
This is also, it's really, it's just like,
it's an audience that has your back.
I knew I could throw that out and I'd be back.
Thank you so much for that.
Anyway, incredible.
He was super nice.
I said, I have a toy of you.
My co-host on my podcast gave me a toy of you.
He said, oh, you have a podcast.
We talked for a little bit and guess what?
I got them digits.
So.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
Nothing's official yet.
You believe?
You are not prepared for this on stage.
Should we pull the Monsters episode down?
We liked him a lot.
Not about it.
Not about J.A.?
No, possibly.
It's behind a paywall, I think that'll be okay.
You've all heard it though.
So we can pull it.
Unhear it.
Audio, denuralize it, whatever the Men in Black thing is.
Okay.
So anyway, possibility of Roebuck content to come,
but I had to do some live Roebuck content here for you now.
Oh, I need a lot.
I just need a second.
Yeah, I know.
Take it, yeah, me too.
This is like, I'm trying to think,
if it was you and Eisner in the Tam
and you got his phone number,
that's maybe the only other thing
I would have been more excited about.
I also, I wanted to be really careful
about how I did that little introduction
because I didn't want you to start thinking,
and ladies and gentlemen, here he is.
And then you get disappointed.
I hope the photo was enough, is enough.
It can remain up as long as anyone wants.
There it is.
Thank you, Daniel.
You were so nice to me.
Hopefully we can talk again.
That's amazing.
Yeah, how about that?
Oh, I know.
We gotta calm down now, I think, from this.
Well, maybe the thing to do is to put the spotlight
away from us and away from Mr. Roebuck
and say, like, okay, it's pretty,
I was hoping that I could check out costumes a little bit,
but it's pretty blinding light,
so I can't really tell.
But we stepped up our costume game,
and I am curious.
It was a little light.
If any, oh, thank you.
Thanks for doing something.
Our, okay, I see some stuff.
I see some stuff, but still people would have to call it out.
I guess the question is,
does anybody feel like they are wearing a costume
that is especially theme park oriented,
and oh my god, well, we've got a really good,
you know what, here, guys, come on up.
If it's not so insane to come on up.
I think you might have won already.
Wow.
Oh, why?
We have, I can't see enough that this is a,
Oh my god.
Wow.
We got an awe from the audience,
because that is a Winnie the Pooh and a hopping Tigger.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Oh, geez, come on up.
Wow, wow.
Oh, thanks for coming.
Thank you for dressing.
Wait, I'm like, wait.
The hand?
Whoa.
The hand goes.
This is, this was my like childhood beloved toy
was to squeeze the hand.
I feel like, can I give you a hug?
Is that okay?
I feel like, this is like, that is so,
I don't want, here, I won't leave you out, Tigger.
Thank you.
What are you guys' names?
Holly.
Will.
Holly and Will.
Great to meet you.
And I think Mike's got something for you.
You know what?
I have two little treats over here
for two people that dressed up.
And of course, I have little toys.
Just save the hopping, save the hopping.
Let's all say your favorite Disney character at once.
No, one, two, three, Dr. Lily Hawton.
Wow.
From Disney's Jungle Cruise.
Oh my gosh.
So I have two Lily Hawtons.
Wow.
You each get. Thank you for dressing up.
Wow, wow, wow.
Wait, Holly and Will, is that correct?
All right, awesome.
Thank you, give it up for Holly and Will.
Winning the Poo and Tigger.
Four listeners, incredible costumes.
That felt, I feel like I needed the hugs.
It felt so theme park quality.
God, that's fantastic.
Was it better or worse than hugging Minnie?
Well, you know the answer.
Oh, you're right.
Yes, well yes, because I went in for the hug
as opposed to, you all felt like
it was a misread of a signal.
The Disneyland Minnie did not want to hug me.
And I stand by that.
All the Orlando Minis wanted to hug me.
It was about eight minutes to park closing
and there was a line behind us with actual children.
You think that's?
Yeah, and I got in the line before them,
so I got a hug before them.
That's how it works.
Oh, he did call firsties.
He did call firsties.
Orlando Minis wanting to hug you feels like
we're somewhere close to like a Lou Baga
kind of song premise.
Should I write a song called Orlando Minis?
Absolutely, and I don't mean to dictate a genre,
but it kind of feels in the vicinity of Pitbull.
I couldn't love this out of that more.
You've been looking for a reason
to get those short leather gloves
to wear while you podcast and perform.
I guess the question is, does Pitbull wear?
It's like little leather gloves, right?
I can picture it.
I'm not sure if that's the kind of thing
you can ask them about.
I don't know.
Grizz or whatever, sure.
I feel like I saw another hand go up on this side though.
Okay, everybody's pointing at somebody.
Oh, I see it.
Okay, you want to come up here?
We have, oh, I don't have more.
We don't, we don't, but I have kind of a,
oh, yes, yeah, cool, go ahead.
Not a physical present.
Oh, you have a Dr. Lilly Houghton.
Look at this.
Wow, wow.
Here, Mike, do you want to, oh my gosh.
I think I know what we're dealing with here.
Wow, wow, what's your name?
I'm Crystal.
Crystal, thank you so, wow.
Thank you for dressing up.
Would you like to announce anything specific
about what your dress does?
I'm Bula from Country Bear Jamboree.
Nice.
One of the Sunbond and Trio.
That's what I was hearing.
I was like, you must know the name
and you clearly know the name.
Yeah, me and my two other friends
already decided which ones we were, so.
Great, I'm glad you sorted that out.
You have to.
Let me, here is the, that is an amazing costume,
much appreciated, and here is your present.
It's not something that you can take home,
but if you're up for it,
would you like to do the honors
of introducing tonight's topic?
Oh.
Okay, here you go, and I'll use my microphone.
Here is the topic reveal,
courtesy of, wait, sorry, what's your name again?
Crystal. Crystal, okay.
All right, here you go, and I'll give you the microphone.
Foolish good boys, please discuss the Haunted Mansion.
Yeah!
So much.
You can take that if you want.
Take a dirty bolt on the ground if you want to.
Or don't.
You want the dirty bolt?
No, it's, no.
No, please.
Give it up for Crystal, everybody.
Incredible costume, wow, wow.
And that takes us to this.
We have now revealed this tonight's topic,
the Haunted Mansion.
Yes.
Let's have a seat here.
Haunted Mansion 6, baby.
Haunted Mansion 6.
The first live one.
Well, yes.
Never been done live before,
but it felt like the thing to do,
the big ticket item in the Halloween season.
Now, let me ask this question.
Are people here generally familiar
with how we have dealt with the Haunted Mansion in the past?
Right, right.
Just to recap, just in case,
and in case anyone's wondering why Haunted Mansion 6.
Because the way that we have done this
is every year, Halloween week,
we cover the Haunted Mansion.
This was a decision that I made a long time ago.
And it's a decision that I have reconsidered
at Sleepless Nights about since.
However, I think it's been fun.
It's let us cover a lot of ground.
But I would say that the only underlying thing
with the Haunted Mansion
is that my co-host and I will sometimes have disagreements
about the speed at which we proceed
through this classic attraction.
Now, of course, it makes sense to do many, many years of it.
There's so much culture there, so much to discuss.
However, we're not always completely aligned.
I think that I maybe hit a bit of a wall in year two.
Yeah, that was fast.
In year two, I thought that it might be good
to discuss a little bit of the ride
in the podcast series about the ride.
And we discovered our disagreements together.
I was told to slow my roll
and that it was more important to discuss
the full history of American foyers.
And we're all looking at a particular host.
Well, look, there was a lot of woodworking
when you start the ride.
There's a lot of wallpaper history.
Was that the year that I said we should talk about the chair
and you lost it on us?
That's a pretty notable chair.
Or has that happened every year?
I assume, again, we've talked about things
that I immediately erase.
The pencil is followed right by the eraser.
There's probably a chair in every one of these rooms
that gets discussed.
That's true.
I think that's a year three thing.
I suggested moving through a room
and then it was a lot of no, no, no, no, no.
Where is a chair that needs to be discussed?
Now, these are the early days
because this is year six of this somehow, right?
Incredible.
And I feel like we are a little more aligned.
This is what's happened as the years have gone on.
We've gotten a little more in sync.
And just to illustrate this,
Mike, if you could bring up that little map, that diagram.
So, there we go.
This is what you're looking at right now.
This is an overhead of the Haunted Mansion,
like a schematic,
and the yellow line is where we were after year four.
Now, if you could show us where we ended up after year five.
We're still making progress.
Yes.
We didn't go backwards.
Yeah.
The hat box ghost got re-edited
as part of the diamond celebration.
Oh, that is one of my triggers.
It's like Steve had a birthday.
Scott hates when we say diamond celebration.
Diamond celebration drives me insane.
The assumption that I know what the diamond celebration is
is that it's a diamond celebration.
It's a diamond celebration.
I know what the diamond celebration was.
Well, because the Mad Tea Party,
they had a special diamond celebration playlist
where they would play like a different Blink-182 song.
Yeah, they had two Pitbull songs on that playlist.
And hey, look, it's our sixth year,
which they call the little diamond celebration.
We all know that.
Is that true?
No, it's not at all.
Oh, okay.
Oh, baby.
I'm lying for comedic effect.
I don't know.
That's just how few diamonds I've bought.
Little or big.
But so, for the listener,
that little jump in the yellow line,
that probably represents about six feet
in attraction ride track.
And that is because last year was entirely about
the Hatbox Ghost.
And there definitely was a ton about the Hatbox Ghost.
And I agree.
We all signed off on this.
And I think it's become a friendlier, more empathetic.
I think brotherhood is formed between us
as this has gone on.
That said, I think tonight,
there is an opportunity to make a little bit of headway.
Wouldn't you say?
There's an opportunity.
There's some dramatic tension, certainly,
because I don't wanna get too far past that caretaker.
But I'm an entertainer at heart,
and I want the people to feel like
they got their money's worth.
But I got a lot to say about that fall.
The fall?
You mean like going backwards down the hill?
Well, I learned some stuff about the fall this year
that we need to discuss.
Okay.
Well, I hear you.
Look, I'm excited.
I'm excited for all this.
This will be great.
We'll see where we land.
Listeners, get a guess ready in your mind.
You've got the map there.
Just physically, just mark it off mentally.
I know where I'd like to be.
And it's not the exit, okay?
It isn't.
Not the exit of the ride or the exit of the building.
I'm excited for this.
So, that said, there is some business
that needs to be attended to
before we can even get to this fall.
Right, we need to discuss how Mike said
he wants the hat box ghosts that's going into Florida
to look like Jared Leto.
Mm-hmm.
I wanted it to be different.
And I'm just trying to help.
I mean, that's a whole,
I could talk about the hat box ghosts
where they're putting it in Florida.
Okay, yep, that's fine.
Yes. Oh, whoa.
I was gonna say that for a few years from now.
Well, I'll allow it.
It's, you know, that's the other thing.
Because there is so much Haunted Mansion news
and there's a few of them around the world,
you do end up with every one of these years
the need to do like,
Haunted Mansion news and views.
Yeah, that's true.
Things do happen every year.
They do happen.
But I'm like, whatever you were talking about.
No, no, I feel free.
Next month it is going in Disney World, I believe.
Right after Halloween.
Always time this stuff perfectly.
And you don't like where they are putting it?
No one likes where they're putting it.
No.
Oh, you like it?
No, I don't like it.
No, it's at the hallway, right?
Yeah, it's way before-
And it's too busy.
It's too busy.
Before Leota summons the ghosts.
Yeah.
It's like, he's coming in like the doorway down the hall
way before the ghosts materialize.
This is getting this interesting abstract
like reaction from the eye that's always like, oh.
Some people didn't know.
Some people may need a minute to process this.
I'm hearing about this for the first time.
If you need to take,
if you need to excuse yourself and go to the lobby
and make a few calls, now you know.
Feel free, because I understand that's heavy news to hear.
But they're, yeah, I don't know.
It's weird.
People are arguing about why, like there's not,
the electrical isn't right to put it in the attic,
like right after the attic.
What is the problem?
What is there?
An electrical issue?
There's not an outlet near-
There's not a Disney company.
There's not an outlet near.
They're missing an outlet.
And if they ran an extension cord, it would look ugly.
Oh, he's gotta be grounded.
He's gotta be plugged right in the wall.
He can't use an extension cord.
Oh, you're right.
Too much power to blow out the, oh, sure.
Yeah, it's gotta be plugged in the shoe.
Well, they should have thought of that years ago.
Anyway, here's what we need to address
is that we've already broken from tradition
by having other people around for this
and by not doing like a cold open
because typically as we've done this series,
the fact that there's that year gap
between all of the episodes,
and I think it'll be interesting to listen back
when you're like, wow, an entire decade,
how many we think it's gonna be at this point,
that you'll be able to listen to all that in a row
and hopefully in a seamless fashion.
And some of that run where it's on Zoom,
so there's a lot of delays and a lot of sad sacri
about how we're on Zoom.
But besides that, hopefully it all kind of flows together.
And part of the seamless stitching of these episodes
is that we've done these little like assignments.
Like next year, the episode will start
and we'll all do this and we'll all like say something.
I don't know if that's a character's name.
I think last time it was the amount of weeks
until Avatar Way of Water came out.
James made it, six weeks later,
we all fell in love with everybody, the Metkaina.
Yeah, that's right, yes.
Agreed with applause.
But what started happening was my co-hosts
were not doing the assignment.
All you had to do was go back and listen
to what are we gonna yell at the top of next year,
a pretty small assignment.
And that broke down some of the trust
that I think is built up
during this somewhat combative series.
So the assignment for next year became something
that was a little more complicated
and it had a little more stakes.
I don't know if I should say the assignment
or if I should say the,
I mean, I won't say the assignment.
I will say that if you guys didn't achieve
what we agreed on that you would achieve,
that we would never talk about the hitchhiking ghosts.
The hitchhiking ghosts are pulled
if you don't do the little assignment.
And so, I ask you now.
Um, gentlemen, can I see, first of all, your stickers.
Step one was a sticker.
Was it technically a sticker?
It had to be a sticker?
I don't remember a sticker.
Oh wait, maybe not a sticker.
I think what it had to be was a hoodie
and I'll cut some slack
because we're dressed like the Munsters.
I'll cut some slack on this.
We didn't plan to dress like the Munsters last year.
The Munsters not part of the plan last year.
So I will say, here's what I will agree to.
Any amount of any of the plan being done by either of you
puts the hitchhiking ghosts back on the table.
All right.
But I noticed, Mike, that you're wearing something.
There's a hoodie under, oh my God.
Whoa!
Oh my God!
It says Pyakin.
Pyacon!
The mighty Pyacon!
The leader of the great Tulkun!
You're not the leader, the wisest, I think.
I think he was the most, what?
The deepest of the Tulkun.
That's right.
Mike, I can't, and you snuck it in there.
Here you are getting dressed like Herman Munster
and it was, I didn't even notice.
I hid this from them.
So I'm not, you're not the only one with secrets.
I've got a few.
Jason, I turn to you.
Gosh, I've just been so busy lately with the move
and I don't wanna let everyone down.
You know, I love our listeners
and they mean so much to me.
And you're an entertainer in art.
So that it's good, I follow the fucking assignment.
Whoa!
What does that say?
Also Pyacon?
Pyacon!
A double Pyacon!
It's a Feliz Navidad miracle.
Oh my gosh.
Wow, wow you guys.
I'm so impressed.
I like, and here I've been wondering like,
is the whole thing here gonna be the gear up
to where then it does it because it got lost in the shuffle,
got lost in putting the live show together.
And then, oh wait, and I forgot,
part of the assignment was it was a reveal
of your favorite character from Avatar Wavewater
in blue ink and sure enough, blue from both of you.
Great job.
However, second part of the assignment,
and I do notice, Jason,
there is a box already on the stage.
I get to open it even.
Wow.
What's in the box?
What's in the fucking box?
Wow.
The assignment was, in honor of the hat box ghost,
to get a box of any kind and to put a hat in it
that would surprise me.
I did say that a Phillies hat wouldn't count
because I know you have those.
They're playing right now.
Do you need to check a score?
He's playing right now currently.
Five to three.
What is it?
Phillies.
Wow. Thank you.
Five to three.
Yay, Phillies.
Go Phillies.
And let's keep that support for Jason's team
and for Jason because he has brought me,
and I'm very surprised to see, a propeller beanie.
Wow.
You got, this does feel like Christmas to me.
Your unwrapping presents.
I'm so happy.
I guess what?
I just thought of a new rule though.
You need to put it on, Eddie Monster.
I'm gonna do the best I can
because I've already tried it on
and I have too big of a head.
Usually I'm up for adults.
Wow.
I'm so happy.
I'm your adults.
Wow.
Oh my gosh.
Spin it around.
Wow, you spin it.
Can you help?
Yay!
He got it.
This has turned into what I was like.
I just need to be ready
in case it's the greatest disappointment
and it needs thews most anger for me,
and then one of the audiences mad and boos me,
but instead it's such a victory unlessENS
you have not achieved the final step of the point.
Well, it doesn't seem like I have a box
anywhere around here.
No, not like, not on a table like Jason has.
Does it, does it, does it seem like that?
Are you gonna propose to me?
Then it would be the perfect night.
I'm gonna propose, I don't have a hat,
but I am going to propose.
I'll let you do the honors.
It is the tiniest little chest.
And the like three people who were like,
oh, so they're gonna talk about the haunted mansion.
They're like, why are they over on the little chest?
Where the hell does this go?
Do I know how, oh, well.
It is, and inside is the tiniest little hat.
So glad we did this.
It is a little cloth-ish hat that says weird on it.
Weird on it?
To what does that refer?
That is a hat for my little Ninja Turtles.
In that, please do not let me pocket this.
Do not let me accidentally throw it in the audience.
I know how much these are important to you.
This hat is, Michelangelo has been wearing this hat
for about a year.
In the current set of my hat,
he's having a little house party
with Mondo Gecko in the sewer.
And Mondo Gecko is break dancing
and Michelangelo is holding like a boombox.
With this hat on.
Wow.
That's what's happening.
Encouraging weirdness.
Wait, actually, I know it's gonna come right off,
but can you put the hat on as well?
Wow.
Yeah.
Right on that Herman flat top.
That's perfect.
Oh my gosh.
You guys, delightful.
I'm so glad.
I do have to give credit.
Gene helped me out and got this hat
because the hat I ordered kept getting pushed back
and pushed back and it was a bucket hat
with a propeller on it.
I know, I know.
I'm disappointed too.
Wow, wow.
Not a bucket head, like the guitar player bucket head.
Yeah, yeah.
That would have surprised me too.
So this is a Burbank Halloween store,
this is not returnable purchase.
Yeah.
Now leave in our new apartment.
I've discovered that over the course of getting us
all Munster's costumes and various things,
yeah, not a lot of return policies out there.
No.
Nor would they want anything.
We're all gonna be sweating into these implements.
Is everything, are we like,
are we dripping paint at this point?
Yeah, it's disgusting.
Please just scream if you're too alarmed
by our appearance at some point.
Guys, that was so great.
Can I tell you what I would have done
had you not done this?
The plan- Spanked our little bottoms?
Yeah.
Yeah, Scott, was it spank our little bottoms?
No, I would never wanna spank your little bottoms.
That's not the kind of thing I'd like to do.
These guys are crazy.
Spin that propeller again, Jason.
Just the thought of it is-
He's so annoyed.
I'm not used to it.
Who would be?
Who wears one on a daily basis enough?
My plan was, I was gonna,
I don't wanna lose the hitchhiking ghosts either,
and I was gonna make a little sacrifice,
and if Jason didn't fulfill the plan,
I was gonna say, guess what, we're making a trade.
Brian Setzer will no longer be mentioned on the show.
Oh, we dodged them.
Yeah, well that would have caused the bootleg.
It's not happening.
And Mike, I didn't think it would come to this,
but I had to bring out the big guns.
If you had not succeeded in the plan, Green Day, gone.
Green Day and Smashing Pumpkins
just announced an arena tour for next year.
Stadium tour, stadium tour, you're right.
Not a sphere tour?
Not yet.
In which case, I may be there.
All right, well that is the end
of what typically is supposed to have been
a minute and a half intro of these episodes.
So what has happened now, I would say,
we've eaten into enough of the time,
now we're looking at about an hour left.
We've basically guaranteed that we will not get anywhere
in all of that nonsense.
This surely will be the least productive
of the Haunted Mansion.
I'm not sure.
And the fact that you guys are here too.
I'm glad they're here, but I'm just saying,
who knows what could happen?
Maybe we just speed through it
and we end the ride tonight.
That's right.
We don't want that.
Is there anyone who'd like to vocalize wanting it?
Yay, thank you, all right.
And it's Fred.
Easy filler, easy.
Easy filler.
Extra horse.
So now this having been dealt with,
let's talk about the ride.
We're in the ride, let's get into the ride.
Yes.
Because this is an exciting part
because when you get away from the Hapbox Ghost,
with the very first thing when you turn
is that you enter the sequence, the graveyard.
We are in the graveyard, the big finale,
the most complicated, full of different characters
and scenes and gags part.
There's so much to talk about here.
We've got a lot to deal with tonight.
That said, Jason, I almost feel like you should be deputized
to set the pace, to be the pace car.
And I also feel like you maybe have some thoughts
you were saying about the very first thing.
So we've kind of, we've turned, right?
We've gotten a view of that graveyard.
And we're up on the second level.
This is like a, this visual to talk about for a minute.
This is like the, maybe only beaten by the Mara room
in Indiana Jones in terms of it's multi-layered
and it seems to go on forever.
And it's a big dramatic beat where you're like,
wow, we're gonna be there for a while.
I can't wait.
Let's get into it.
Yeah, sure.
Just one thing.
Before that?
Well, yeah, before that, a little epilogue
on the Hapbox Ghost.
I got a hold of the Jason Sorrell coffee table book
about Haunted Mansion.
Because I finally broke down and bought it
after years of taking out the Burbank library's coffee.
You never bought the book?
You don't have the book?
In all the years of basically reading it on a podcast.
You never gave the man some money?
I did.
I bought it now.
Cause, and I said.
Wait, can I, did you buy it
because the book was checked out?
No, no, the book is still available.
The book is still available.
Head there after this.
I'd have to break in at this hour, but you understand?
Yeah, worth it.
So that was in 2004 printing.
And we talked about how the Hapbox Ghost
only had one page in that edition.
And I got a hold of the newest edition,
which is dated 2015.
And now the Hapbox Ghost has one page dedicated to himself.
Is there any new information?
Yeah, not really.
There's a picture of that guy Ray Spencer.
Is that his name that we talked about last year?
Remember?
He's the, he's the, he's the circus man.
He's in the toy store at California Adventure.
Oh yes, yeah, yeah, I remember that.
There's a picture of him in there.
So you're the writer.
Is he in a fun hat in that too?
Oh no, just slacks and a button up.
All right, so the book is unchanged,
is what you're telling us.
Pretty much, there's little bits and pieces here
and there it seems like,
but not much more about the Hapbox Ghost.
Thank God, boy, hey, it keeps working out tonight.
Things keep, things keep coming up grandpa.
Hey.
Okay, so that means we get to,
let's talk about going in reverse, right?
You tell me, we get to, we spin in reverse
and we go down the hill into the graveyard.
You are essentially falling out of the attic.
This is what I didn't know until recently.
Yeah, I kinda didn't either.
I guess really what you,
cause like, it's like you're being killed
and you're falling backwards into the graveyard.
That's some interpretations, yes.
Or you could be falling, you're saying you could be alive,
falling backwards out a window
and maybe upon impact you die.
Oh, and it goes so slowly
because everything's flashing before you.
Right.
What in reality would be just one or two seconds
of horror is stretched out to 10 seconds or so.
Right, what's interesting about it
is I find that part of the ride so relaxing.
It's kind of like a reset,
gives you a break from all the activity
and lights and stuff.
Well, and it's like, it's like you're in a hospital bed
and it like starts going down.
Famously comfortable.
Yeah, like, yeah, pretty good.
But now that I'm hearing what like it might be simulating,
it's kind of, I don't know, it's weird.
I feel like it should be, here's what I'm saying,
it should be a jerky, violent motion
when you're falling out the window.
The thing should like whip around
and then you'd like do like a drop like pirates
but you're backwards in the omnimover.
I'm just saying they fucked up.
Huh?
They're like.
It's an unclear death.
The exact supposed to be dead.
Well, there was something apparently
that would have spelled this moment out
a little more clearly, although this is very speculative
and this is from doombuggies.com.
I now will read in front of an audience.
Part of a website.
As a printed out part of a website.
Here we go, that's what you came here and paid for.
And then Grandpa Munster read me a website.
That's my favorite show.
And six years of this, you're saying.
And Daniel Roebuck was in the Tam O'Shanter.
Yeah, and we all got excited about it.
Huh?
Very not very good.
We're sorry.
Lock them up, lock them up, put them away.
All right, it's the idea of that
that part is supposed to be dying
has been maybe written off as revisionist history.
Maybe not the Imagineers intention,
but a haunted mansion enthusiast named Hunter Adamson
shared a story with doombuggies.
He swears it's from a reliable source.
I once heard from an old Disney manager
that part of the original plan for the haunted mansion
was that as you leaned backwards to descend to the graveyard
there would have been a Pepper's Ghost type figure
shoveling dirt as if to be burying the occupants
of the doom buggy in the cemetery alive.
So that would be like in the ceiling essentially.
Jason is a big guy.
I don't smile like this.
You sit, Jason does.
I'm just imagining someone hosing a thing of caramel cord
and then going on this ride and it's like,
oh wow, we're getting buried alive.
It's that famous Disney touch.
Walt's like introducing the ride on,
or not ABC, whatever channel it was on.
And then NBC.
NBC.
And then you'll go and you'll be buried alive.
It's very strange.
It doesn't open up like what else you could do there
if they're gonna make it so personal and so much your death.
If the next step of that was more Pepper's Ghost
but not too many because the idea could be
that there's just one Grantskeeper and nobody else there
because you were having a sparsely attended funeral.
Or it's like if you're actually dying
everybody's really happy about it.
You're about to go to a big party.
Which on one end I guess is like, it's a nice,
it's comforting in a way because you go like,
oh, there'll be an afterlife in the party
in the afterlife, excuse me.
Or everyone's thrilled that I'm dead.
Well, it'd be great if there were a bunch of revelers
all celebrating above your grave.
And then you wonder aloud,
is this because they're celebrating my life?
And one of them says, no, we're happy you're dead.
You're going to hell.
You know what?
They should have kept then,
you should be on your back for that whole section.
They should have kept you that way.
And then you go like the whole ride like this.
Like looking to your side and you're like, oh shit.
And then you have to figure out how to get out lying
on your back.
Oh yeah, okay, so then they have to build a door on it
and it has to close on you.
And you have to bang your way out at the end.
So coffin challenge, we've just reinvented
the coffin challenge.
Always my problem with doom buggies, no lid.
That Bob Gur didn't know what he was doing.
So I'm very interested, the Pepper's ghost was going to be,
had to be in the ceiling then,
or I guess maybe to one of the sides
because it couldn't be on the left
when you're going down the Disneyland.
They have the scrim, you can see the scrim
when you're up top of all the ghosts flying upwards.
Right, so in the distance you can see all the ghosts flying.
But you couldn't put the Pepper's ghost, I don't know.
I'm interested in the geography of this.
I was there with my family recently
and through trying to get on doom buggies,
it ended up where I was in one with my brother
and Jane and my dad were in one.
And so of course me and my brother
were totally silent the whole time.
And I think I leaned over at one point and went like,
that one's name is Bickwick.
Because of course I did.
But Jane and my dad were so excited when they got out there
like that part when you go backwards,
you see the side of the house.
I'd never noticed that before.
And honestly, I had to go back and look it up.
I hadn't really noticed either that you can see the side
of the mansion in here.
But did either of them talk about Bickwick?
No, I can't imagine.
That's the only way to ride.
Next time everybody start whispering stuff to each other,
whoever you're with, next time we go.
Well, there you go.
So we didn't get to actually be buried alive.
You don't go on your back.
You comfortably sit for the rest of it.
You know what?
You get an appearance from the Raven,
one of the many Raven appearances.
And this is really good.
Yeah.
I really, the Raven,
I forget the Raven's there almost every time.
So it gets you when it calls.
I'm not scared, I just go, yeah.
The Raven's there, that's nice.
You do the move when like an Everclear song
is on at a restaurant.
Listeners don't get to see it usually.
Okay.
My answer's a miracle point.
Oh, yeah.
It's like you're in the lobby of a courtyard
by Marriott with Mike.
Bruh, Everclear's cover of Brown Eyed Girl.
They wrote a new intro for it.
The other thing when you're going backwards,
next to the Raven, Scary Trees, your favorite song.
Oh, God.
I know.
Big shout out for Scary Trees.
Yeah.
Hang on now.
Let's not support them too much.
They don't bother me too much
because they don't talk.
We're not in that Wizard of Oz, you know.
Hey, what are you doing?
If they, no dialogue for that.
As long as they never,
that's a plus up I don't ever want.
Is for them to talk?
Yeah, yeah.
No, keep them silent.
What if they did the E.T. effect?
And you, can I give your name at the start of the ride?
And then the trees were like,
Scat.
Friend.
Person.
The afterlife is just me and you.
I'm gonna be there throwing apples at you.
Yeah, you should see,
cause yeah, if you were going to the afterlife,
it shouldn't be trees, it should be like little devils.
Oh, they're right.
Or little angels, I guess.
Depending.
I guess you could, yeah, you could,
that would be a plus up is where you would flip them out.
Sometimes like cars, sometimes you win,
sometimes you lose.
Sometimes on a mansion, you get a little devil,
sometimes you get little angels.
Wow, it decides for you?
Yeah, it's random.
Wow.
Yeah, it's like the end of Ray Dator Springs racers.
That's what I said.
Sometimes you lose.
Sometimes you get the one you didn't want.
Would you prefer if they replaced the trees
with little devils or little angels?
Maybe for the oddity of it, sure.
But then, you know, maybe not,
because at some point in the nearish future,
I'll be taking my son on there.
And I don't know if I want.
I think I want the motive, like,
we've chosen hell for you.
Yeah, that's a little intense, I guess.
Okay, but what if-
Next guy's heaven, next guy's a better kid, he gets heaven.
What if the little devils are hot stuff, the little devil,
and the angel is the biblically accurate angel,
which is like the floating eye and the tentacles,
and it says, be not afraid.
Because then it's,
then it's like a good, it's a lesson.
It's historically accurate.
I mean, the angel part, I guess, hot stuff.
Hot stuff's just fun, it's just fun to see him.
Yeah.
Well, they got a branding deal to work out, I guess.
I don't know who owns hot stuff.
That's amazing, is that something I can ask the audience?
Who owns hot stuff? Who owns the hot stuff devil?
Yeah, who owns Harvey Comics at this point?
That's a good question.
They got hot stuff, they got Baby Huey, Casper, Richie,
you know? Dreamworks.
Dreamworks? Dreamworks.
Don't lie to me, huh?
That's right, they did all those like,
cartoons that we all remember.
Also, what's on your shoulders?
I got a Ghost Mickey from Tokyo Disneyland.
Whoa!
Oh, nice!
And a Jelatoni as a pumpkin from Hong Kong Disneyland.
Wow, a Jelatoni and a Ghost Mickey on his shoulders.
Great job, I'm glad we could shout out another costumer.
Yeah, what was that?
Yeah!
Big round of applause, dude.
Wow, yeah, wow.
Oh, everybody's nervous, we didn't know Jelatoni
was in the building.
Oh.
Fellas, hide the ladies.
Jelatoni's here.
By that, you mean Dr. Lily Hotten?
Is that her name?
That was her name, yeah.
Oh, okay, great.
Jelatoni's gonna go find those Lily Hotten dolls.
Give them away, give them away in the packages.
Do we move on?
Are we off of the downhill?
This is the first time.
I don't know, trees, I mean, okay, yeah.
Let's go over trees we talked about,
we talked about going on your back.
Generally being backwards, yes.
How do you feel about being backwards?
It's cool, it's nice that the ride can do it for me.
Because this is, I really think this is,
we've taken this for granted after all these years.
I bet this blew people's mind when they went on this first,
that this vehicle could do things.
Because in the same way that, oh my God,
the trackless risers, oh wow, look what this can do.
I'm sure people were like, holy shit,
this thing turns around and flips me on my back.
Going backwards with elevation, with an incline.
Yes, two things, two.
It's two things, so.
And it has like, you know, a decent amount of wrap around
so you can do some awkward team making out.
Well this is.
That came up in the first year with me.
This is the most romantic part of the ride.
The downhill, oh yeah, because it kind of like,
clunks you back, and oh that's true.
This is like romantic comedy city here.
If you are not, like you better be prepared
when you do this, if you know what's happening.
Like you better not go on with your crush
if you're not prepared.
Okay?
Yeah, you better not go on with your brother
or your boyfriend's dad.
You gotta know what's coming.
Will that new, will Sydney Sweeney and Glen Powell,
who the guy I know, will they go on this ride?
Well you think they're a couple, but watch out.
So they're gonna go on the Haunted Mansion?
They're gonna go on the Haunted Mansion
and maybe they'll get stuck on the decline.
Oh, getting stuck on the decline with your crush?
Get outta here, oh my God.
He's so stressful.
Oh wait, I thought you were saying it was a good thing.
Oh no, I would, not good at all.
Then you're gonna kiss, ew.
No, thank you.
Let's use this time wisely and figure out our itinerary
for the rest of the day.
Oh, I think my Disneyland app still works.
Let me get it out, see if those dining reservations
are available.
Oh, not yet, I better check over and over again.
Until the ride works.
Turning the other way as far as I can.
Can I pull this bar off me entirely?
Oh, I think the ride's starting.
Did they say the ride's starting?
Oh no, I must've misheard.
So.
I'll ask this gravedigger for help.
Excuse me, good sir.
Yeah, so is there a more romantic motion
on a ride vehicle in the history of rides than this?
Just gently moving?
Clunk.
I'm not saying it's perfect, I'm just saying
of all the ride systems, is there one that sort of
forces you sort of in a position?
What's that?
The Mater Swaying Mater is one.
Oh, you can slide.
You barely have extra room.
You toss and turn.
I think that's a good number two.
The Old Matterhorn.
Oh yeah, you're right, yes.
Lap straddle, yeah.
There you go.
Wait, let's demonstrate in case they don't know.
Here, let's do a little.
Woo!
Aw.
Oh.
Woo!
We should ride separate, I think.
Party of one, please.
Party of one, yeah.
You'll enjoy the ride better.
So yeah, that'll keep Matterhorn, but Matterhorn.
Matterhorn is more like erotic.
Ha!
And not ha!
No, hold on.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Explain eroticism to us.
That's a, okay.
The Matterhorn, it's all about like vibration
and aggressiveness and it's like,
that's like just having aggressive sexual intercourse.
Fun in Mansion is it swings you around,
you lower, that's romantic.
Really seems like you're trying to get us
to recognize you as a sexual being right now.
Thank you for recognizing me as a sexual being.
So.
Well, I mean, in terms of romantic,
there's literally a Little Mermaid ride
where you very slowly go by the kiss the girl scene.
How romantic?
That's a pretty romantic song.
Well, it's the same ride vehicle
and there are similar moves in it,
but I just, it doesn't do it for me.
There is a Caribbean crab singing at a teenager.
Yeah.
Keep in mind that part.
You know what it is?
There's too many robots around there.
On a mansion, you're just seeing that raven.
Oh, there's some privacy.
It's more chaste.
And it's dark, it's dark in there too.
That the kiss the girl scene is very well lit.
So you're not getting that mood.
People can see, the little turtles can see, they'll see.
That might be for someone a little bolder,
but for my preference,
I prefer the backwards on a mansion
is for a romantic movement.
Okay, so most sweeping movements,
most romantic ride there is,
part of a ride that there is,
except that in the dead center of it, there's a,
car!
If you can ignore that, you're a romance.
He's just cheering me on.
So.
It's not true love to me!
Car!
You're a sexual being!
I love you!
Car!
Okay, okay.
I think we're moving on,
but just to like-
Can you say something?
Just, I just get, the romance is just too much.
I'm getting flustered.
I wanna, just before we move to another part of the ride,
there's one more bit of business.
I wanted to talk about some ride before we backtrack into
this because there is something else that was a lingering
thing from last year's episode,
because between last year's episode and this year,
a big, something happened in Haunted Mansion World,
Haunted Mansion the movie came out.
Yeah.
How about everyone cheer as much as you liked it?
Yeah!
Okay, huh.
Mixed, interesting mix.
Well, another thing that was mixed were our guesses
as to how many skulls out of 10 we would give this film.
We didn't, it was just a guess, just based on rumors.
We hadn't even seen a poster.
There was no real way to know,
but we were like, let's guess for next year.
Here were our guesses.
Mike thought he would like the movie 6.5 skulls out of 10.
I guessed 3.5.
My rationale being it is a product being released
in this year by the Walt Disney Company.
Uh, Jason, 8 skulls out of 10.
8 skulls.
Um, would we all like to say what we officially give the movie
out of 10 skulls?
Yeah.
Um.
First.
Yeah.
I haven't gotten around to it yet.
I know, I know.
I know.
Also no, Mike.
I'm after Yellowstone.
I will watch it.
There's a lot going on.
Uh huh.
It's just that you have all that,
literally anything else to do.
Yeah, it's true as well.
I had a little evening nap
after the Phillies lost last night.
And I-
Wait, hold, hold.
An evening?
Isn't that just going to bed?
Uh, no, I woke up for a couple hours.
Then we went for a few hours.
What time were we talking?
What time?
Well, it was a 2 of 5 game local time.
So it was probably about,
so I think I slept from like five to eight.
Or five to eight thirty.
Wow.
That's a long, that's a long, God.
I went, my kid's not even taking naps anymore.
I would kill for that long of a nap
in my three year old who lives in my house.
Yeah.
And I just found out through my watch
that they lost again tonight.
So, I know.
Sounds like-
They got more chances, they got more chances.
It's okay.
Oh boy, you're going to make it through
the rest of this one, you're going to be okay?
Yeah, we'll see.
At least we don't have a second show or anything.
Yeah.
Um, let me, here's,
I know I lied a little bit.
I've seen some of the movie.
I've seen the first three seconds of the movie.
And I saw it because someone alerted me
that at the beginning of the movie,
there's Disney does, Disney Plus has the warnings
and it's PG-13 and this scene is made,
contains such and such.
There's literally, this movie has so much product placement
that literally there's a warning on Disney Plus
that is warning, this film contains product placements.
Wow.
That is unheard of in the history of movies.
I have never heard of that.
Well, keep in mind, they had to go through
the governing body of themselves, Disney.
Like this didn't pass through some FDA outside body.
They were just like, God, even for us, this is,
this is a lot.
That's the type of warning you get printed on a sign
at Staples Copy and Print Center.
Literal dialogue from the film.
This is, if I could just really quick
and I credit the screen rant for this information.
If you wouldn't mind me reading to you
some of the product placements that occur
in Haunted Mansion 2023.
Most of them I don't have in context.
I just have the products themselves.
Here we go.
U-Haul, BMW, Dell, Pentax camera,
Fujifilm, Tito's vodka, Budweiser, Jose Cuervo, Fritos.
Those ones we know are all real
because that's who has the liquor licenses
in the Disney parks.
It's a general partnership there.
Crocs, Zillow, Yelp, Benihana, Chevrolet, Apple Watch,
Black Panther, the movie.
Marvel Comics, collector's edition, Monopoly.
Costco, Canon, Burger King, Zatarain's,
New Orleans style Creole seasoning.
Zatarans.
Zatarans, thank you.
I had a feeling, should have looked it up.
Yankee Candle, which is purchased via subscription
on Amazon.
There's a part where Tiffany Haddish wants a ghost
to write a message, quote,
using this pen and pad I bought from CBS.
And finally, the emotional crux of the film occurs
during a dramatic monologue about how
Lakeith Stanfield's wife died on the way to Baskin Robbins.
I think maybe all of us guessed many too many skulls.
Wow.
I've read that list a few times,
and every time just makes me wanna watch it more.
It also makes me go like, oh, that company's still around.
Okay.
Dell computers hanging in there, all right.
Well, the where if you try to watch it,
because it's dark, it's a dark film,
and I don't mean like the themes.
I mean, it is so hard to see.
What's happening?
Disney, all just colored, all our eye photos have it.
We'll do it for you.
Give me a couple bucks up right in the movie.
It's so weird.
Anyway, that's my weird,
I wanted to get a little of that out
because the haunt cast season will not be going
too much longer.
We got a couple more episodes on the pod,
but we aren't doing an episode about the movie
because we don't wanna be sad.
And we all know, everyone agrees it is much more important
to talk about Harrison Ford and Calista Flockhart's
Halloween.
Hey!
Yes, great.
Everyone agrees.
The Reddit agrees.
Our Reddit can't wait for it.
Hey, our pretty-
Good news.
Every minute closer to it, we get.
Good news, foolish mortals.
It's already in the cast.
Okay, back to the ride, to the caretaker.
Can we see it still in the caretaker, Mike?
Let's see our pal.
He is the shaky-knee guy.
He is holding a lantern.
He's got a trusty dog and a trusty shovel.
He's great.
It's a moment, Mike, of intimacy.
You get so close to this character,
you sense emotion.
This is no cold distance, you know?
Not like all those presidents you sit really far away from
and all the presidents who aren't feeling anything
in particular.
This guy's scared and you can tell.
Yeah, he's scared because he just discovered
that you were in the middle of intimacy.
Look at that face.
That's the face you would make.
This guy is great.
I mean, I feel like in some ways he's sort of
like not as celebrated as some of the other characters
in the ride because he's not a ghost.
But he's iconic.
Yeah.
You can see us.
Let's celebrate a non-ghost.
Celebrate him.
Let's show them we can do it.
Everyone here, round of applause for this robot.
Lit by regular light as opposed to black light,
a lot of the others lit differently.
One of the few living things in the mansion.
That's true.
Like, yeah, he's organic matter.
Yeah.
I can't see through him.
Right.
The dog is malnourished and I don't care for that.
Yeah, I gotta feed the dog more.
Yeah, that has nothing to do with anything.
He doesn't look like that because he's scared.
Something happened.
So you can at least, you can surmise from just
the picture here that he's a bad owner.
Unless, what if they're meeting
for the first time right now?
No, no.
That's his dog.
That's what I've always felt, but since I like this guy,
I don't wanna go throwing accusations at him.
I don't wanna take him to PETA.
Jason, what do you think that's his dog?
I think it's his dog.
They seem acquainted.
He's a bad owner then, two out of three say.
Yeah, cause he's not looking at the dog.
So like if the dog was just a random dog,
he would be looking down like, ah, like he'd be scared.
And he would be saying the same thing.
I, he would be like, where's your owner?
They're taking such bad care of you.
I mean, I feel like he's a little distracted
by the graveyard jamboree.
Yeah, that would probably take my attention over.
Yeah, but he's not looking toward the graveyard jamboree.
He's looking toward you.
He's not noticing the graveyard jamboree.
He's not, I've always taken this as, at least he's seen.
So I take that face as he is looking
at a thousand ghosts at once.
Yeah, I feel like his jaw is like jabbering.
Like it's scared, like, ah, ah, ah, ah.
He's like, what was that?
What was that?
He's either just seeing the ghost for the first time
or it's just like, he looks, he looks a little rough, right?
He looks a little like shit.
So maybe he sees the ghost every night
and he's still not used to it.
Yeah, he is look, he's, I think he's seeing you as a ghost.
That's what I think.
But he's not looking toward the big party.
I think he's like, oh my God, who goes there?
It's a ghost people and that they're necking
and my dog needs food, but I keep forgetting.
That's not her letterman jacket.
It must be his.
She must have put it on.
You think it's at you, like, like that you were
so horrifying as a ghost.
I believe, I think so.
Cause why wouldn't he be pointing the other way?
He's blocked off from seeing the actual graveyard.
This to me ties into your kind of paranoid,
everyone's looking at me, runner, everybody's,
everyone at City Walk will notice me
throwing the mini monster away.
I'm in a haunted mansion and there's many ghosts around,
but you are the scariest one of all.
Well, the room for one, the further they say it,
room for one more.
And yeah, everywhere I go, I'm a star.
And yes, want to hug me, especially Orlando.
Orlando, many be wanting to hug me.
In Mike's defense, there's a lot bigger security corridor
now, so they might be checking him out.
Wait, what?
What does that mean?
Like there's a lot more fences and presumably cameras
and metal detectors at City Walk, at City Walk, Hollywood.
We went back to City Walk.
They might be like, what is that guy being weird
with the drake?
Should we keep an eye on him?
Where are there more security fences?
The metal detectors are for like going into the park.
Yeah, I'm just saying there's more of a presence
than I feel like when we did that City Walk saga.
We need to, we've gotten reports of people throwing
mini monsters away.
We need to put three milkshake detectors outside the store.
We're gonna pat these people down,
force them to finish it in the store.
Shove those bobas down.
We need to train 10 milkshake sniffing dogs.
And they need to be patrolling at all points.
The dogs need to know that you can buy glass at City Walk,
but you cannot carry it 20 feet into the theme park
you're probably going to.
Teach them to bark at that.
Let me say something else about this guy, Caretaker.
He, I mean, I feel like always iconic
probably like lived his toys or in artwork,
but I think he really, his iconic status really got sealed.
I want to say it was last year that Lowe's made him available
in a take-home version.
Do we have a still of that?
There we go.
Lowe's or wish.com?
Can we see the next still, Mike?
What is this one looking at?
Presumably he's going to be on like on your front lawn.
So he's looking at local teens drag racing.
Oh yeah, Jay Walkers.
Jay Walkers?
He's a guest at Jay Walkers.
He's sort of like a nosy neighbor at this point.
He's just sort of like,
he knows everyone's business in the neighborhood.
He's mad about the 15 year olds
are not even in costume and it's 8.30.
Come on, it's too late for this.
You should just put him in like a window at your house
with like drapes like this.
So people will be,
no matter what they're doing on the street,
if they catch a view of him, they will be like, ah!
There's a peeping Tom.
He could always be watching your moments of intimacy.
That's true.
Bring him home.
You could do, you know, you could do a lot with him,
just not even in Halloween.
Like you could maybe put him in a Hawaiian shirt
and like his glasses, like put him on the beach
and his glasses like tip down his nose.
And like, as people walk by,
he's sort of like checking them out.
And he can't believe what he's seeing,
how hot everyone is.
You could, it's very, it's, it's bug eyes and white hair.
And I think that in non-Halloween season,
you could easily restyle this guy to be Rodney Dangerfield.
Put him in a Hawaiian shirt.
Yeah.
And you know, you put him in your yard
and people ask what it is.
It's Rodney Dangerfield for back to school season.
Oh yeah.
There's so many, I wonder if the hat comes off.
It'd be nice.
You could, well, or everything,
like could you switch clothes with him?
Um, I, I mean, presumably it's removable somehow.
Yeah. Let's see the full wardrobe.
We got a brown jacket and a green scarf.
Yeah, the jacket's a little long, but I like the jacket.
I like the jacket.
I think this guy's going to be a little,
he's not quite the size of the real one.
So he's going to be a little smaller than you.
You're going to, it's going to be a squeeze for you, Mike.
Okay.
He's got big pants on though.
He hasn't been to the tailor.
It has not come with a dog figure.
Louis is not selling a sickly looking dog option.
That's a clue that it's his dog.
But you could put a mini next to him.
No, it is. It's a clue.
What is the clue?
It's a clue they're not selling the dog with him
because it would not be his dog.
It would be a separate dog.
Oh, so you're saying Louis is really concerned about Canon.
Well, I'm saying that Louis knows that he's doing a bad job.
So they just want to sweep it under the rug.
They're not going to want the dog, right?
No, of course not.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
we're not going to sell any of these if we.
The president of Louis had a meeting about this.
We're not selling a groundskeeper
that treats his dog poorly.
So either we don't sell it or remove the dog.
And that's why you got CEO of the year.
That's right.
Mike, can you.
The man who stands up for his beliefs.
Can you go back to the ride picture?
Which one?
The real.
The real Silas.
I guess the question I have that I'm sure we've all been
wondering though is, is the caretaker daddy?
I mean, I don't know.
He seems not threatening.
He could be nice, but he seems confident in his job.
Well, daddy seems to say you're attracted to the
groundskeeper or whatever.
Is that when you say daddy.
Well, that's what I would.
Yeah, no, I wasn't saying.
Can he get it is what you're asking.
It's hard to tell.
He's so covered up.
I got to see that pod.
He dressed.
Switch clothes with him.
I think like, literally like maybe the pants, like maybe if
he just went to a tailor and got them a little bit hemmed.
I do think like this is an outfit I would wear.
So he is dressed pretty well.
Like you would think like he'd be all like much more like
ragged and like his clothes would be torn asunder because
he's just, he's out there and he's just takes
for care of himself.
But he looks pretty good.
I will give you that.
I don't know that he's my type of guy.
Let's poll the audience.
Who thinks that the caretaker is daddy?
That's not nothing.
Well, is Pickwick daddy?
Yep.
Pickwick brings the party with him.
Doesn't he?
Which character on the Haunted Mansion is everyone
most attracted to?
I mean, the organist can play an instrument.
That is always attractive.
That's a good question.
I mean, Hapox has the charisma.
I know that's a little bit, that's like.
Those dual guys are pretty dashing.
Yeah.
Constance might chop my head off.
Figures crossed.
If you're into a certain thing,
Constance is probably the answer.
Ultimate Finn-doming.
Murdering your husband.
All right, well, I think that's my job for the evening.
Should be getting to bed.
That's it.
Take two or three hour naps with you.
This liquid death makes me crazy.
Canned water.
Let's put some other.
What did he say about canned water?
It made him crazy.
It made him crazy, yeah.
Let's throw some other characters into the possibility
mill of who is daddy, I guess.
Which is the Weird Little Band.
Can we see the Weird Little Band?
Give it up for the Weird Little Band.
Our next.
And I say that because I've seen this referred to
as the Phantom Five, but I've also seen the singing busts
referred to as the Phantom Five.
And it's not even, it's like half and half.
No one can decide which is which.
So I don't know.
As with a lot of this lore, it's like good lore,
but it's also like pretty fuzzy, right?
Yeah.
Like, you know, nobody quite knows what they're called.
I don't know.
But we know, well, you know, and I'm scanning them
pretty fast, I don't think we got any daddies in this bunch.
Unfortunately.
That's why they took up music.
They had to offer something else to the world.
Yeah, they seem.
If I can take a step back,
cause you brought up confusing lore.
Did you guys see all the names for the caretaker?
Sure.
Yes.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It's backtrack.
Fine.
Get back.
Let's go back.
Re-wind.
Get back on your back.
Yeah.
I already, it's funny.
Like I will tell you where I was thinking maybe
optimistically we get is singing busts.
I'm watching that dream dissipate.
It is floating away.
So names, names.
Silas Crump.
This is another one.
Everybody's Crump.
Everyone's right is Crump.
Alastair Crump.
And these guys, this little band,
they're all named Crump.
Everyone in this thing is Crump.
Who are the two guys shooting at each other?
It's Aloysius Crump and Foggin Bottom Crump.
I don't think I like the lore.
This is what I've learned after six years.
Crump, Crump, Crump.
Christmas, Christmas, Christmas with the Crumps.
It would have, that's what I'm saying.
It would have made the Eddie Murphy movie
a little more dynamic if the Crumps showed up.
I think that fellow being dynamic.
They all farted each other.
They all make up one of them.
What's more dynamic than that?
Okay.
But also there's some special
where Phyllis Diller calls him Clyde.
Ken, we're all over the map.
There's a model from, I believe the 70s
where he is referred to as a grave robber.
Oh, that adds something to it, doesn't it?
Oh, I didn't see that.
Well, let's, I guess, yeah, he's got the shovel.
So he's obviously digging.
It's either, is he doing it virtuously
or is he doing it for his own nefarious deeds?
I think it's virtuously because he doesn't have a sack.
If he was gonna grave rob,
you would need a sack to take the stuff, you know?
Not if, not if he's gonna dig him up
and then do something with it.
No, no, no, no, no.
And then put them back.
There's no need to be body.
No.
Jason said grave robber, not grave fucker.
Yeah.
Grave robber's fun.
The other one, no.
There's a number of comic book short stories
with conflicting, like they hire a younger caretaker
and then he gets his old job back.
I can't believe I thought we were out of this.
That was, I was like, there was no pushback.
There were no comic stories.
I thought we were out.
What was I thinking?
That's why this guy's the best in the biz.
Hey.
Yeah.
Woo.
Spin it, spin it, spin it.
It's so much higher than you think it is.
We have, guys, we gotta talk about something.
We have to, we have to.
We have time to talk about the Phantom Five.
We do.
Okay.
And you know what else I think we have time to do
is to play my favorite little part of Grimgarden Ghosts.
There's a little video and I think like to the extent
that anyone wants to.
I feel like the monsters.
Well, yeah, at one Grimgarden time, they had 30 tracks
and they recorded 42.
So, you're gonna have to go through all of those.
Yes, definitely.
Yes, I'm just saying it's my favorite part
and I feel like maybe the monsters should dance to this song.
Can you put on the song?
Oh, we're gonna do a little dance?
Yeah, yeah, we're gonna do a little Grimgarden dance.
Hold on.
Oh my God, it's not working.
Yeah, there we go.
There we go, there we go.
There we go.
You can just spin the propeller around.
Woo.
Oh yeah, that's it.
I just wanted a quick hit of that.
Great.
That's.
Woo.
Oh, the theater does stuff.
Wow, hey.
Woo.
I just got bold.
Thank you for that.
That's my favorite iteration of Grimgarden Ghost.
I have notes about Grimgarden Ghost.
These are also clearly going out the door.
That's how much these things expand.
Well, it's a fine place to start up next year.
Well, we're not done yet.
Go back to the Phantom Five.
Let's talk about them.
I mean, my question about them is,
did they, were they musicians in our world?
Or like, were they a band first
and they died altogether in a bus accident or something?
Did they die and was this a day the music died?
Yeah, it's the day the music died.
The musicians.
They were all on one plane.
I think, yeah.
They were on an airplane getting ready
for their Loot Bagpipe and Ovo show.
Big tour.
Yeah, they were on a big tour.
And yeah, I mean, I guess it brings up the question
that can ghosts learn?
And that's why he's the best.
It's pretty heavy.
We can all sit and think about it.
You think when the moon rises,
when the clock strikes midnight,
they like get memento disease and forget everything?
Every day?
Or they forget the afterlife and then they-
Or it's because learning is so vague.
You learn little things all day, every day.
Well, right.
I hope you learn.
Yeah, can you learn a skill if you're a ghost
or is it like Groundhog Day?
Although he learns.
That's exactly, yes.
He does learn.
He becomes incredible musician.
He remembers.
He remembers everything.
Yeah, I think it's that.
I think you get to Groundhog Day.
It's a Groundhog Day that you have no hope of escaping.
There's no rom-com ending for your Groundhog Day.
So you better learn every instrument.
Because ghosts, yeah, ghosts seem tortured.
Because they're stuck, they have unfinished business.
But if you could occupy your time learning new skills,
I have so much stuff.
You can watch Yellowstone season one through whatever it is.
Five, six?
So you're saying the afterlife is good
because you get to get caught up on your shows.
Yeah.
Knock out the curriculum of ITT tech.
The world is your oyster at that point.
Yeah.
The afterworld is your community college.
Air conditioning repair and private investigator.
There's time for it all.
These guys are proof.
I don't know, that's possible they couldn't play Lick.
And now, and all it took was 900 years.
Yeah.
And now they can play one song over and over again.
I like that long horn.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's funny looking.
Yeah, I think there's the specific here
that a lot of the music was played backwards.
That's a way that it's weird and ghostly.
Like they transcribed it and ran it backwards.
It's got this weird little sucking effect,
a lot of the melodies.
I think it's not a bagpipe, it's an oboe in reverse.
Because I guess bagpipes are tough to play.
I think even finding a session bagpipe player
is a very tough thing.
In the 60s, let alone now.
I don't know the market today.
Some of the stuff is played out of tune on purpose.
Unsettling, sure.
Proper tune age, that's the land of the living musicians.
It's all creaky around here.
Yeah, step wrong.
You also, I think maybe my favorite musical
little stingers or section in any of the Grim Grinning Ghosts
versions in the ride,
is probably when a little trumpet comes in.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da.
And that's fun, that's good, thank you.
I'll learn it better in the afterlife.
But I learned who played the music on the thing.
A lot of the musicians you're hearing
are all these Benny Goodman kind of guys.
But the guy who plays that little trumpet part,
his name is Cappy Lewis.
And he made an album called Get Happy with Cappy.
Cappy!
I definitely got happy looking at Cappy.
Look at that watch he's wearing.
Wow, you don't get a watch like this
being a mediocre trumpet player.
Say that.
This is great, I love he's wearing
almost like a bowling shirt.
Like a red bowling shirt.
This feels very Jason-esque too, I feel like.
I mean look, we'll start next year with an hour on Cappy
and his various endeavors.
We can go back to simple assignments.
Next year, as much as I loved the boxes
and what you're wearing, maybe next year
we go back to a simple shout out of Cappy.
Cappy!
We come up with our favorite song of his
and then we learn that he was nicknamed
Cappy the Killer after bodies were found in his yard.
If you were a musician, a male musician in the 60s,
chances are you were a murderer.
That's just how it is.
Well, I don't know exactly what else we have time for.
I don't know, I mean, there was the whole,
like they announced like changes to the Haunted Mansion Q.
There's a get like.
I wasn't sure if you pulled something up or not
and then the audience response was like.
People seem upset by that.
There's a gift shop coming next year too.
So I could be, the gift shop of course
is outside of the confines of the ride.
Literally we're looking at the exit of the ride
so that is not something we will need to discuss, yes?
We have to.
Well, eventually.
Just let me try, let me try please.
So I kind of wanted to propose next year
we take a break from the graveyard
and we go right to the new queue and the gift shop
because it's gonna be so fresh.
It's like.
Thinking outside the box.
It's gonna be so.
And it's gonna be fun to like sort of take a quick break
from the whole way we've been doing it.
Who knows what new feature on the Disney Play app
will be integrated in this gift shop.
That it'll over eat your phone in all sorts of new ways.
What kind of spirit jerseys will they sell?
Can I hide in a cape for a year?
Oh, trust me, I've tried.
I, well, okay, look, you guys, you know,
you filled the assignment.
I was delighted by your fulfilling of the assignment
so I guess whatever we wanna do next year.
But let me just say this.
And this is like, you know, I'm looking at a clock
that's winding down.
I know we're ticking down here
and we got another show to do.
So, and I had no fantasy that tonight would be the end
of the entire thing.
Of course not, I know that.
I'm no fool.
But I, you know, just imagine for a second
while we have an audience here,
just hypothetical, imagine if we could all be together
for the moment where we finally finished this series.
Wouldn't that be cool to like, shall share that together?
Sure, yeah.
Yes, we can totally agree on that.
But I, you know, that's just a thing to imagine.
That's just kind of a thing to like brainstorm
because like we're ticking down, right?
And you know, it's not like you could possibly finish
the rest of the ride in just, I don't know,
exactly 26 seconds, right?
Unless.
No.
Mike, could you play that video?
What?
Just click on the video, see what's there.
Scott sent me a video and said, don't watch it.
Yeah, just watch it now.
Here we go.
Okay, all right.
Oh, it's one of his misbehave videos.
Five singing bus perform the iconic song
Grim Grinning Ghost.
Then we weave through a series of comical
rave-mode scenes involving many spirits
set behind a number of scrims.
There's a tea party, the headed guy, a Viking lady,
all kinds of shit.
The ghost host returns to warn us of hitchhiking ghosts.
I can't even understand what he's saying.
What funny names.
In a series of mirrors, the ghosts appear to follow us home.
I seem to be getting through it.
Climb off our doom bunnies and step onto a moving ramp
where we see a small ghostly bride who tells us
to hurry back.
The ramp leads to the exit and that's the haunted mansion.
Wow.
I knew we could, I knew we could.
The guy from the Oscars held up the envelope
and it said haunted mansion is done.
That means it's official.
We got to do it together, guys.
Nice try, champ.
That video didn't even include the phrase
Ned Nubber Uncle Theodore.
You know what?
That video was very nice.
Yeah, I thought so.
I liked the effort.
Went over pretty well, yeah.
And it's official and binding.
And what I think is nice about it is actually
it sets perfectly up next time for us to talk
about the new gift shop and the new queue.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
You're saying that by exiting I have actually reset it
which makes it more justified to go back
so what we'll just do is we'll do the gift shop
then we'll go to the queue and then yeah,
we'll go through and see what we missed.
Yeah, because we barely touched on the various types
of audio recording and playback, analog and digital.
So yeah, so this is perfect.
Thank you for that nice little video.
Thank you so much.
Let's have a round of applause for the nice little video.
That's perfect, that's perfect.
Okay, glad you enjoyed it.
Yeah, it was nice.
That's why you guys are the worst.
All right, that's our show.
You survived Onkest of Fright.
Ladies and gentlemen, wow.
Happy Halloween.
Thank you so much for coming.
Thanks for dressing up.
Thanks to everybody at Dynasty Typewriter.
Hey, happy Halloween and if you're coming
to the second show, feel free to come to the second show
and if you are, hurry back.
Hurry back, happy Halloween.
On the mention it's gone.
I was right, they were wrong.
Amy Qu pitch
conversational recording
forever
dog
this has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott
Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever
dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get
your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.