["The Cemetery Gate Theme"]
Welcome, foolish mortals, to hauntcast the fright, The Cemetery Gate, where today a creature has escaped from Crypt 3.
It climbed over one paywall into another.
I'm Scottle Juice, who of course loves haunts now in the wake of Shacktoberfest, and joined by Frightful Narlson, who has long loved haunts.
Err, I love haunts.
That was actually supposed to be a monster, but it sounded like one of our topics.
Oh yes!
I meant to be like, oh I'm gonna be like a monster, but it just sounded like the guy we're about to talk about.
Get ready, practice that tone.
Yeah, yeah.
As should jagged slash and drain.
Jagged slash and drain checking in.
Very excited for this one.
This is a trick of the trick or treat season, you know?
This is a little trick.
Sure, yes.
Where we got to pull our little...
It's a trick, a little trick for the listeners, but a little treat for us.
It's absolutely a treat for us.
Here's what happened if you were not on Crypt 3.
There was a poll per usual, a number of topics that came from you, the listeners.
There was one that we were especially excited about and rooting for, and that is not what went in the poll.
So we immediately moved it over.
And let's just say it, a little bit more business to go over, but the topic is Harrison Ford and Calista Flockhart's Halloween costumes.
This is catnip for us.
I don't know if this is hyperbole, but I texted you guys right away,
Hey, you know, we're still digging into the suggestions and everything, but I think we got one of the best Club 3 suggestions ever.
Oh, yeah.
And then we throw it out into the wild and it comes in fourth.
It just dies on the vine.
So we had to take matters into our own hands.
Another thing that happened is that via the comments, I saw people going, I sense a little Mike mischief.
I feel like Mike is, and because we've kind of established that if you're doing, if you're on the next tier of our Patreon,
we encourage you to do it.
We have some fun over there, but we'll throw out the poll.
Here's the topics for the month.
And often there will be kind of a long chaotic title, which usually involves several celebrities being mentioned.
There's there's it's kind of a mealy.
There's a whole like premise.
You got to get your head around.
So I think people thought it was you for that reason.
Right.
It's usually like, oh, it's the clip from the 1975 when Andy Griffith rode on a Tilt-A-Whirl at the special that was on ABC.
And the special was called like Tilt-A-Whirls.
It was a 1974 made for TV movie about the Flash.
And the Flash was played by Mickey Rooney.
And that's that.
And that whole sentence, I said that will be in the poll.
Yeah. We have to post it like that.
Right. Right.
Which will be next to just like, you know, a ladder like the teacups.
For. But but in this case, in correct, this was, I think, mass agreement on all of our parts.
Yeah. It doesn't matter who wants to say it.
We all want to say it. Right.
We're all excited.
And then there was a second stage of the texting when we were each choosing our individual because it's it's the most votes.
It's the incumbent. And then whatever gets the most hearts within reason.
Yeah. And then we all pick one.
And then we each pick one from the runners up.
And I ironically was standing in the Grand Californian Hotel lobby and remembered texting like, are you picking this?
Well, not necessarily. Are you are you going to pick?
Well, I want to see. Somebody had to put their neck out.
You did it. Ultimately, you grabbed the breast ring.
Yeah. And and Mike picked one that that didn't win the rare the Disney haunts they did at Hong Kong Disneyland would seem fascinating.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I'd like to get to that one.
Yeah. It looks great. I know I wanted to pick a winner this time.
I wanted to feel the victory, but it didn't happen.
So now I'm going to go far the other way. I'm not going to do that ever again.
I'm not going to try to pick a winner like that. I'm going to pick what my heart says.
Be yourself. One of them is going to resonate. Absolutely.
Now, it's funny. You say ironically, I was in the Grand Californian as if to say, like, ironically, we were dealing with theme park business.
And here I was in a theme park environment.
But of course, in a way, there's nothing ironic about it because this has nothing to do with theme parks.
Oh, yeah. That's what it does have to do with the season.
It has to do with theming.
So apologies to the seven militant listeners who haven't realized that we don't always do episodes about theme parks.
I'm sorry. If this is what it takes for you to figure it out, I've got news for you for the last four years.
Harrison. Harrison. We frequently.
It's not even about theme parks.
The Harrison voice is definitely. It's called Podcast the Ride, not Podcast the Costume.
They're not doing theme parks again.
We're not. Well, how about this photo before we get into the meat of it?
Of Cindy Crawford and her husband, Randy Gerber, dressed as Sharon Gregg Allman in 2014.
That's a good. That's like a good duo costume.
Yeah, Jane found this one and sent it to me immediately.
They were famously married to Gregg Allman. Of course, we all know.
We all remember. But and that's supposed to help the cause that there's more Randy Gerber.
I will say this. George and Randy were at the Sphere the other day as well together.
Yeah. Seeing you to Randy's favorite band.
Not when you were there. Not when I was there. No.
But Randy Gerber's favorite band is you two. Tell me more.
This guy's so interesting. Believe it or not.
You never hear that. His favorite songs probably with or without you.
Can you believe that? Whoa, whoa. God, this guy's deep.
Yeah. Do they do they share a one hundred dollar parking space if they can stack their two motorcycles?
Depends on how much cargo they got out of those cycles.
They drove their motorcycles from the agave fields. Right to the Sphere.
Oh, yeah. They were they were picking the they drove the points out of the tire.
They drove their motorcycle on the Sphere. They parked it at the top of the Sphere.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, they drove it up.
Only only JD's JD's VIP's get to park at the tippy top.
That's right. OK. Credit to the suggestor of this.
Matthew Comiggy's sorry if I butchered your last name.
Club 3 suggestion for October.
You go over all of the Harrison Ford Calista Flockhart Halloween pair costumes over the years, perhaps rate them very well.
At first, I thought it might be too slim a topic, but a quick Google search was a deluge of images.
Yeah. First of all, you say too slim a topic.
That is that is the PTR bad signal. Yeah.
Suddenly we are sprinting to the top. Yeah.
So thank you, Matthew. Absolutely.
Much praise from us. And now let's let's fully dive in.
Yes, we've known about these for a while. Surely we've referenced them over the years.
I feel like this is like it's not the most current because as we I'm sure you all looked into it,
there is not like too recent of an iteration of this.
Perhaps the covid era slowed down their Halloween socializing as it did for many people.
So we're dying for a new one of these.
But I feel like this was an Internet fascination a number of years ago because there was a there was a run there.
They had a run early 2010s where that was this couple.
This great Hollywood couple is killing the Halloween costume game.
Yeah, for sure. I feel like I'm trying to other famous couples like a lot of couples do it.
But it's so something so funny, I guess, about Harrison himself doing the costume.
So I feel like that's why it's extra extra notable.
Yes, because there's something extra funny about grumpy old Harrison Ford dressing silly.
I think yes, I knew that some of this would be the psychology of why this is funny and why it is so joyful.
And I think, yeah, absolutely. He's just he's such a curmudgeon.
His I love his talk show appearances very much.
And frankly, I wish more people just fully put themselves in the way that they are out there.
Yeah, the way that he does.
They're just willing to be such an over it grump because he's so funny.
But he is silly on the talk show appearances, too. He is like a mix of grumpy and silly.
Yeah. Yeah.
There is a costumed appearance where he's on Jimmy Kimmel Live right before Force Awakens comes out.
And Jimmy Kimmel is dressed as Princess Leia and Harrison Ford is dressed as a hot dog.
A hot dog costume with a dog snout.
With a little snout. Yeah.
And it's great. It's great to see him in the spirit.
And it's there's just there's a there's a mismatch going on.
I feel like where it's it's like exclusively the silliest costumes.
None of these are cool. There's a there's a cool isn't it?
And maybe no Halloween costume is truly cool. Right.
But these aren't even in the ballpark. These are completely like look how silly grandpa looks.
Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
It is like it's basically like oh look at the dog is wearing a Halloween costume.
He doesn't like it. Now I think he does like it.
But that's the perception at least. Yes. Yeah.
I sense a little smile in some of these.
We're gathering all our information from paparazzi photos except for when he when he did it on television.
But I think another thing I mean there's there's the grandpa nature and how we'd all love to see our grandpa.
I have a very like lovably curmudgeon father-in-law and who his persona reminds me sometimes of of Harrison Ford.
Like that's the other grout. But that's how he is.
And he's happy to you know that's that's the role he plays.
Right. I don't think he'd be caught dead in a costume.
I think curmudgeon makes you think maybe the costumes are not in the picture.
So it's such a delight to see him going for it.
Being so silly. And then another thing besides just the type when you remove his celebrity
and his history then when you put that that in who he is and what we know him for when is Harrison Ford ever looked silly in anything in one of his movies.
This doesn't happen. Good question. He only looks dashing and cool.
Can you think of any of the origin of a of looking goofy. That's a good point.
He's in Anchorman 2 for one scene but he doesn't look silly.
No he's an old news man. Yeah. But he doesn't look silly.
He doesn't look silly. He transforms into a werewolf or something but that's not really he that it's just a different face by that.
Right. He's got a cool cowboy hat and American graffiti. He's kind of a jerk in that but that's not uncool.
He's got a he's wearing a cool hat and what's the Indiana Jones.
Oh yeah. A number of those movies. Oh yeah. He wore this cool hat.
He he's playing it pretty straight. I've only ever seen bits and pieces of this movie.
It's like the Today Show kind of it's like oh yeah.
This is like a hallucination this movie at this point. What is this movie called.
Is it called Morning Glory or is that a different movie.
That might be right. It's him and Rachel McAdams.
But he doesn't look silly. He's a news man right. He's not wearing anything silly.
No I don't think so. Unless there's one part.
Is the movie called Morning Glory. That's what I want to know.
Oh there's a very weird part in it where the Ty Burrell character like activates a button on his desk that closes the door.
And this is a few years before that came out. Oh wow really. Is the way really. About Lauer. Yeah.
There's a button. Is it for that purpose or does it. Whoa whoa. I thought you were making a joke.
Whoa really. That's true. I. So this is just like an inside secret about the button.
I feel like it is. Now this is probably the movie I've fallen asleep watching.
Morning Glory is the name of the movie by the way. I was correct.
I have never seen it all the way through because I kept dozing it off.
Because it's not particularly compelling. You don't say.
But he doesn't look silly in that movie. He looks handsome and smart I assume.
Maybe he's a bit of a blowhard but that's. But yeah. Unless he at some point wore a silly costume as Matt Lauer did.
Matt Lauer is one of the only other celebrities I associate with silly costumes.
And I'm right. He's not the only one now because I don't want to think about those.
Right. He's as disgraced as Paul McVee. Ty Burrell's character that I've just learned about.
But there is a button. Jesus. That's one of the inside.
There's a thing where his door closes really slowly and he's like leering.
When it was inside like people knew about it for years. It was a little. Yeah.
That happens with everything. Anytime you hear something bad you go a bunch of people knew about this for 25 years.
And it makes its way into things. And then the thing can go public and everybody can pretend they didn't know.
Or say I do actually. It doesn't seem right to say. Yeah. I didn't want to say.
They said I should have known. I should have known. I should have. Everybody like the classy thing to do is to write a song about it.
Yes. I've had Joel in his ignoring a lot of his other pals. He's like get ready to song about all of them.
Yeah. Not enough notes on the scale. I had this idea for a theme album.
It's entirely songs about my disgraced friends. I did that because I got 20. I could do a double album.
Anyways. No I don't know. Well that's a question listener. Go into the movies or television. I don't know what's going on on Shrinking.
I don't know if this man is looking silly anywhere that I'm forgetting. But even like does he know he'll wear a disguise in the Indiana Jones movies.
That's true. Like what does he does he like dresses a Nazi at some point and maybe last crusade.
Yeah. He steals a uniform. Yeah. But he doesn't look. It's not silly.
You know what never happens is that there's never a part where Indiana Jones has to like who's Kate Capshaw's character.
He doesn't have to like. Well I got to pretend to be like a showgirl with. I got to be in the show.
Or try to dance or something. Yeah. Silly. He never ends up looking like Carmen Miranda or anything. Right. Right.
Which could have been. And again I also I never saw a Dial of Destiny so I don't know.
I hope and pray that there's an extended Carmen Miranda. I hope so too. That would be great.
He is funny and he would be funny dressing silly in movies. Sure. But he's got. A lot of funny snake bits.
When he gets. When he gets scared of snakes. Oh. Like those are often played for laughs. Yeah that's true.
Well but being funny is different than looking. I'm talking pure. Oh foolish.
He never. You know what doesn't happen is him dressing like a big snake to make the snakes think that he is their queen.
Yeah. Like and to leave him alone. Yes. Yes. Yes. I'm your queen. Brass brass.
And then like one of the snakes falls. One of the snakes falls in love with him. No no I can't.
OK just one little kiss. OK. And the kid bites him. That feels good. And then like the snake priest comes up.
I'm in love. The snake bit me with its love venom. Snake priest comes up with a little collar.
I'm going to stay here. Snake priest. That's just the pattern on the scales. It just looks like a collar.
Man and wife. I do. I do. I do. I rattle rattle.
That would have made Dial of Destiny a much better movie. I haven't seen it either.
It's his translation. You may kiss the bride. Then they do and then like ahhh. He clamps onto his tongue. Get it off short round.
Now that's a punch up. That's a punch up session. Oh yes. I love it. If they could add that in post. In post. Yeah yeah.
In post two years after the movie is done. How mad were they you think?
As the incredible rise of short round and the Oscar season and that they're like shit why didn't we put them in there?
Yeah. As it comes out and kind of disappoints. Yes.
Because everybody was saying that online and I feel like they didn't anticipate that as being maybe a fun thing.
In a movie industry that's entirely like fan service and cameo they missed the one that would have been like just molten lava.
Just sitting there. Is that a good thing molten lava? I don't know. It would have made the movie as hot as lava.
Well there's always another one maybe. Yeah I know. Maybe they have to to redeem it. They said last but they didn't know this was going to go bad.
So there's that. He doesn't like seeing him dress silly is great. I mean I can talk a little. I think we can bring Calista into it a little bit.
Sure. But should we also just like you want to just like pick one and start. Yeah. Just so we don't go too far without talking about it. I agree.
Throw a dart. Pick whatever one. I don't think we have to go in order. I think I know roughly what years a lot of these were. Okay good yeah.
But I don't know if that matters for the context. Like now you remember Obama was in office. So this maybe put them in this kind of thing.
Well Jason will say how many years from 9-11 the photo was. Yeah yeah yeah. You reverse. You do the math from 9-11.
Like maybe they had just shaken it off. Spirits were high. It had been eight years by this point.
Married by New Mexico Governor Bill Richardson. That is fascinating. That is yeah. I saw that.
He was a candidate against Obama and Hillary in 2008. Yeah right. Didn't work out. But he did get to in New Mexico while he was filming Cowboys and Aliens.
He got to perform this crucial wedding ceremony of a great couple. They've been together for so long. They have.
And I think some of the fun of the costumes also is like oh that's right they're together. Yes. You kind of forget.
I forgot for sure until a couple years ago. I was like oh probably they're not together anymore. No they are.
And they usually seem happy in photos together. They do. They seem like they're having a nice time.
I think it's going great. I think they're in love. I think as grumpy as he is. It's because maybe the grumpiness is because he has to go do press tours and be with a lot of people that aren't his wife.
That's true yeah. He's a wife guy. He's a wife. Wait hang on. Let's not throw that out. What? What?
That's maybe a somewhat of a tainted phrase. Okay fine. Host Try Guy. He ruined being a wife guy for everybody.
No no. You just edited yourself from a Try Guy gate. I'm not going to say it. People are waiting. How long ago was that? Has that been a year?
God I think it has yeah. Wow. Oh boy time flies. We're at the one year anniversary of Try Gate. Yeah.
So anyways. But here as I said we can pick off more about them but somebody just name a costume. What's one that you... The P. The big P's. The big P's.
Calista was like a hippie in this and then Harrison was... Harrison had a big like a green like a pea costume. What do you call it? A pea pod. He's a big pod.
He's a big pod. This one is a solid candidate for favorite. Yeah this is because he's got a painted green face. A big big like cumbersome ish costume of like peas around him.
And yeah he's got sunglasses on and a baseball hat on. He looks like he's maybe unhappy with all of this on. And this is one of the perfect examples of dog wearing a costume that the dog is not enjoying wearing.
And I don't know that he's not. Your feet could shake his way out of it. It looks like that. That's what it seems from an outside observer.
I would... I like anything. I like if he's happy. I like if he's unhappy. I like any range here. I love that he has painted his face green to match. Yes. And put on a hat and I feel like green sunglasses.
We had a lot of shades of green going. Kind of a good 70 something guy sweater and then just like rubber gloves. Just like kitchen gloves. This one epitomizes it I think because it's so homemade, homespun.
They are not... I think this is another aspect that I love is that they don't feel curated. It doesn't feel like... And then we got our stylist to make us some fantastic elevated cut. This feels like he went to Target and grabbed whatever and put it on.
Heidi Klum very famously goes and has some elaborate... She dresses like... I don't know if this is right but like Mystique. The Jennifer Lawrence Mystique where she's sort of nude. But obviously this is a major undertaking to body paint and do all this thing.
She fully with makeup and contouring turned into Ned Fulmer the wife guide try guy. People thought it was him. People thought it was Ned. You're in public but you're disgraced. Oh wait it's Heidi Klum.
A lot of people have been going though as sexy Ned for Halloween from the try guys. That's true. It's a controversial costume given what he got into. Maybe it's kids getting embraced. It's creative though.
So yeah this is... And then I like that... I think I would like if the costumes were a pair. I like if they go together. But in this case a peep pod and a hippie. Love it. Love that they don't have anything to do with each other.
Yeah I like when they do contrasting costumes. They each get to shine. Yeah they each get to shine. The peep pod... I got a couple pictures of it. It is missing one of my favorite features which is often he's got a bottle of wine or two or bottle in a solo cup.
And that is not present in this one. Yes. Well this is a daytime. That might be why. There's some children present. I don't know the timeline. I don't know if this is their... I think they have an adopted son together. Maybe it's a friend. I don't know.
But that might explain the... Although of course I would love if he was just fully swigging from a full bottle of wine on the street at 5pm. Well I think when he's got a couple they're going to a party. Yes I would imagine. Like they're going somewhere.
But this is just pure trick or treat. And he's in the spirit. And I mean do these... I guess in a way these fit together because maybe a hippie would be into healthy living. I mean I think eating well. Sure. Yeah. You would hope that's the case. But maybe I mean... Abstractly they fit together. I think maybe that's already more thought than they put into it. I could be wrong. But it's possible.
It's cute. They're having a lot of fun. And then... Oh yes. Can we just say hippie is funny because I feel like that's like I've seen that costume growing up a lot. Even though like what is our generation have anything to do with hippies?
Yeah I don't know. I remember thinking hippie. I may have dressed as a hippie on some like... I'm sure. Every history day or something. Beads or something. But hippies were so around. Well there was a big revival in the 90s. I guess that's what it was. Of like the smiley faces and the bottoms and tie dye. Woodstock was back. I guess that is part of it. Woodstock was back.
So it was sort of like the reinvention of the hippie. And then kids were dressing like hippies. I bet most of our listeners know of a kid who dressed like a hippie or they themselves dressed as a hippie. But why? Why? I don't know. I don't mind it becoming like a cartoon of what it was. Especially because so much genuine hippie stuff is like extremely trying. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Full on like yeah man. We're not... We're cool.
Well like the movies. You know some of the movies of that. Like there's a lot of movies that don't escape the hippie era that aren't like actually interesting to watch. You had to be there I think. And Reese I think I... Was this on the best show? It was occurring to me that like the Woodstock lineup. There's a lot of crap in the Woodstock lineup. I'm not throwing the whole thing. There's incredible music there and great music in that movie. But so then you're looking at like the ones that aren't in the movie. And like what's this one though?
Well it was a few days right? I guess they had to pad out the schedule. But there were people when I was looking at the lineup there were people who weren't even supposed to be on the... They were just there attending. And it was maybe like John Sebastian and then like shit the bands are late get up there. So some of the better acts were just like fuck stall. Like they didn't even plan on having some of the better bands there. So I was like can you give them points? I guess you gotta give them points for like improvising like that.
Yeah. I have a guitar John. But anyway great. And then I just like to imagine the struggle like as this night went on. Out of these bobbing peas.
Calista. There's a... I can't... There is no fly in this thing. There's just a bobbing pea.
I gotta go to the bathroom. I need assistance though. Do I need to take the whole thing off? Do we rip the pea off? What's the protocol? Give me a jug. Give me an empty jug. No Harrison you can't do that. This isn't like your old carpentry days. You just go in the car and you would pee in the middle of a construction site. That's not how this works.
We're at a famous producer, Brian Grazer's house. You can't piss in a jug at Brian Grazer. Where does Grazer keep his jugs? Brian I need a jug. You gotta jug a juice. You gotta jug room.
Don't drink out of this jug later. Remove it from the jug room. He's got an authenticity because he was a blue collar guy working with his hands. He didn't make it till later in life. We've all heard the lore. He was a carpenter for people. He sold weed to people. That was what he was doing. So yeah he would piss in a jug.
He worked with yes. That's what I'm saying. I'm just justifying the joke. He doesn't need it. Not like us sus elites with our fancy porcelain that we recall. This is a guy. This was a dude who was out there. He didn't have anything delivered to him on a silver platter.
I'm not a dealer you gotta hang out with for a while. I'm in and out. I don't even want to use the bathroom. I got the jug. I got the jug. I got the jug. That's all I need is a jug. I don't need chit chat. I just need jugs.
Yeah so there was a hole to do with a big costume like that. It was probably a discussion. Logistics surely became an issue. They're bouncing back and forth as I walk. I'm going to be bruised on my chest. Throwing my balance off. There's no gravity to these things Kalista. Can we tape them down? What if I cut them off? I'll just cut the peas off.
Nobody will be able to tell what you are. You need the peas. I don't know how to be her. You'll look like an unripe banana Harrison if you cut the peas off. That's a viable costume. That's fine. That's pretty good. A rotten banana. We've improvised. Costume change in the middle of the night. That's okay. People will be impressed. More than one. Brian Grazer will be knocked on his ass when he sees my new costume.
And then later Brian Grazer. Wait what are you supposed to be? I'm an unripe banana. Obviously motherfucker. He punches him. Get off my plane. Get off your house. Get off your porch. Leave the bottles and let's go. Great. Fun.
Now the relationship, the two, that's also a nice thing. It's a Hollywood relationship that's gone for a long time. They seem to have met at the 2002 Golden Globes and this is the magic of the Golden Globes in action.
Where movie and TV people get to meet and mix it up and merge and maybe form a forever bond. Unlike those Oscars that callously silo the performing arts. Only the Golden Globes and People's Choice allow movie and TV people to meet and mingle.
Yeah. Ali McBeal gets together with Han Solo. I don't know why he was there. Star of Witness. Jack Ryan you could also say. He was a Jack Ryan. That's right. And Jack Ryan also. He didn't have to dress up like a statue. He pretended to be a gargoyle to sneak off a building or something. No silly costumes.
Jack Ryan. He goes over to Ben Affleck, the then current Jack Ryan. I was like can you give me some advice? Do you know what Ali McBeal is? Oh you would ask Ben Affleck because she's a younger Jack Ryan?
Do you know about? They say it's on something called VDDs. How do I get my hands on one of those? DVDs? Sure. Probably. Do you think there will be a Spider-Verse Jack Ryan movie with Chris Inskey, Ben Affleck and Harrison? With the pointing? They're all pointing at each other?
It's like Attorneys General. Not Jack Ryan's. No. Jack Ryan. Don't mispluralize it all the time. I'm always correcting people. It's Jack Ryan. Enter the Jack Ryan verse so they all get together. The sum of all Ryan's. The sum of all Ryan's.
What do we do Jack 3? Well I think that's my impression of Chris Inskey post 2019. I'm not sure. There's lots of way here. That's good. Yeah. That's a debut on the show of Chris Inskey.
Didn't know what. This is how I've always talked. I just wanted to shine a light on some good news. Hell of a Reed Richards voice. Watch the Office. I sounded like this then. What does that actually sound like? What am I actually doing? When I do Roy Zinski, what does that sound like?
Yeah. I don't know. It did sound like something. Will Ferrell's Janet Reno? Yeah. Welcome to John Krasinski's dance party. I really like dancing to that song. To dance to it again. Play it again. I'd love to do an Office reunion. I just did Office Ladies the other day. I had a blast.
Okay so here's another fun fact. Their first date apparently, James Marsden was a third wheel. Really? Came along with them on their first date. That's interesting. Maybe also some attempts to. No I think that came through her. Maybe he was on Ally McBeal or something. That's a good question. Where is that connection? Which one of them? I don't know. I'm not sure. Who knows. Who knows where these people meet? Probably at Brian Grazer's house. Probably all at Brian Grazer's house. How many times do you think that this couple will be together?
I think that this couple was in the presence of Jimmy Buffett. They must have been at the same party. God all the time. Many many. Yeah constantly. Constantly. They probably didn't even talk to each other because they had just like, well you need to socialize with people you don't always see. Yeah for sure. Jimmy thank God you're here. It's always good to see. I hate these things. Nice to see a friendly face. A real man. Somebody I can actually talk to. Yeah. Especially because Jimmy and Frank were best friends. And there was that whole, there was that video.
That's right from the Indiana Jones. Was that a, was that shown on tour? Where Indiana Jones actually played by Harrison Ford interacts with Jimmy Buffett. Harrison Ford shot footage for Jimmy Buffett's tour from around the time. Which is.
Yeah he's like outside of the five movies. He shot something for Young Indiana Jones Adventure.
And he shot something for the Jimmy Buffett tour. I'm sure there's a few things we're missing but that's pretty limited. Think about what they had to do to get him to come back as Han Solo. Like what was that? How easy did they have to make it? Here's the amount of money. We will kill you. This will not be a whole movie for you. That's a good transition for what I have to say next. So much had to be offered to him to get him to come. And then like hey could you come do Jimmy Buffett. Yes. Yes. For Jimmy anything.
No that's not even work. You know he loves Jimmy Buffett. I wouldn't be shocked. We said because Biden tweeted about Jimmy Buffett dying and I was like it's not hard to believe that like that would be Biden's favorite musician of all time. And it's not hard to believe it would be Harrison's either. Yeah. I'm not saying it is. I'm just saying would you go yeah that makes sense. The main mode that I picture Biden in is sorrow you know because he's had his personal difficulties and he's overseeing a very tough time. Yeah.
President various. So I feel like my main image of Biden and he's also and he's old and tired. So I mean image of Biden is like solemnly closing his eyes and just kind of like just feeling just feeling. And I imagine him doing that. Like on that day do you think he listened to
Cheeseburger in Paradise. Just close. He could have picked a sadder Jimmy Buffett song but I'd like to think that he was trying to. I don't think he knows them though. I genuinely think a lot of people who are very mournful of his death do not know any songs past the three.
Do you think they don't know a pirate looks authority or son of a son of a sailor. Possibly sailor. Maybe. Well I guess that one. Those are sort of famous ish for the crowd.
Seems like a song from carrying me from that seems like a song from the time before he was like a cartoon character. Yeah those are like more legitimately kind of a singer song writer. He was like he wasn't wearing lays and flip flops all the time.
That was before like the 90s sort of cemented him as the restaurateur and like exactly what his brand was. Yes for sure.
Like a Gordon Lightfoot. Gordon Lightfoot then did not go on to open a chain of casual restaurants. Lightfoots. Lightfoots.
You know it's real light food. Sundown cafes. Is that a song. Yeah that's right.
I apologize if I'm wrong. Yes it is. No that's it. Yeah. It's yeah. So all that stuff pre sort of more cartoonish Jimmy Buffett.
But this happened you know this happens to a lot of people where like you hear a new Rolling Stones song and you go yeah that's that's them.
Something's off though like it doesn't in the context of 2023. Yeah. It also sounds weird because like some of his old songs have a bunch of food in them.
But like it sounds better. Sure. It sounds more. The production is more. It sounds more yeah. We talked about it when I talked about Olivia Rodrigo's Guts.
We talked about how. Have you finished the album now? My. My. Oh you've had this for so many weeks. I know I forgot. I forgot I'm sorry.
Oh the list is piling up. Yellowstone. Oh shit. Rodrigo Guts. Made it to the new vocal album though.
So that jumps. I thought you were cool. My shit. You're telling me you finished the vocal album. Oh I'm old. No I just revealed it. I'm too old. I'm an old man.
If vocal takes priority that's the sign. Although I'm listening to this K-pop group 50 50. There's a song I really like by 50 50.
Oh I don't know 50 50. Look them up. 50 50. I think everyone here would enjoy 50 50. OK. OK. This song specifically. To be clear because they're cool and you're cool.
Oh well yeah for sure I'm cool and they're cool but yeah it's just a good pop song that I really like from them.
Let's do a different. Unless you had somewhere. Oh yeah. Transition wise you say Force Awakens. So my question was Harrison Ford had his leg crushed on the set of Force Awakens.
That's what happened. It wasn't just like he didn't just hurt him so his leg was crushed. His leg was. By the door. The door of the Millennium Falcon fell on Harrison Ford's leg breaking it.
I didn't know this was a crush. Crushed. My God. JJ Abrams rushed over. This is the story he tells to try to help and pull it up. It was too heavy. JJ broke his back doing it.
What. Yes. Wait. He revealed this later years later that he because he didn't want to like he said he didn't want to like steal focus or something. Sure.
He needed to wear a back brace the rest of Force Awakens because he had broke like a vertebrae trying to lift the impossibly heavy Millennium Falcon like I think it was the I don't know for sure.
I think it was the door like the thing that comes down and you walk up the ramp on it. Let me say this. There's a lot of people and all this theme park stuff is about living your Star Wars story.
Yeah. But only JJ Abrams got to rescue Han Solo. Well try to rescue. For real. Yeah. Or try his attempt. That's true.
It's just dawning on me now that it's like OK. One of your stars gets her leg broken.
There the director breaks some part of their back a vertebrae or something that feels like oh this production is cursed.
Yeah. Well like remember he got hurt on Dial of Destiny 2. He had to delay it. Yeah. Yeah. Like delay it months as well.
I shouldn't say I don't know if it was. Now that I'm saying that I don't know if it was the door or the ramp that comes down or if it was just a door on the actual ship. I'm not sure.
I always picture it as the ramp. But I think it was during Chewie were home like they were about to and everybody's like people's hearts are well like people are tearing up because this is the moment and it's them and they're gonna and then all right.
Take one action.
Chewie.
My leg my seventy five year old leg is snapped in half.
I mean there's footage of it somewhere that is not character.
Mayhew still alive still in the suit at that point. Peter maybe trying to help. Peter is not in good shape at that point.
I can't imagine. And then and it's just limited visibility. Yeah. It could only be JJ.
I think for sure Millennium Falcons I don't think it was on that like he remembers on the ship he's hauling Raptors or whatever they call it. Remember Rathars. Rath Tars I think.
You know what I'm talking about Force Awakens. There's like the big things on the ship and like some of the parts of it maybe have disappeared from my brain.
Yeah.
So I was wondering OK what costume was he wearing when he was recovering from this injury in 2014.
You're putting the timeline next to.
Because it took months.
Very good.
So here is the costume in 2014. He and Kalista are dressed as like 80s rockers.
Hair metal.
Rockers.
See this is a good this might be up there with best matching couples costume.
It's a good one. Yeah this is now this is one where they are together they are both in the same mode even their pants match. It's zebra stripe leather for both of them.
He's in a big red trench coat and like let all the half glove the fingerless gloves and she's got a lot of jewelry on.
Yes I think.
She's got a big smile he's got a little smirk. They seem like they're having a good time.
They are both definitely having fun here.
Yes I think he's on the end of the recovery he might have even been back to work at this point because in July he was still like this.
Oh.
Oh wow he's got a big mechanism there.
Yeah.
You actually put this on the real time so in July he's having a tough time down some stairs.
But by Halloween it's like to the doctors like this needs to get fixed.
I know you've got to get back to Star Wars.
I don't give a shit about Star Wars.
Yeah.
I'm not missing Halloween.
Halloween time is coming.
It looks like.
We picked up the glam costume. We're going to be motley crew.
It's called crew. You can't be crew alone.
So one person is in a crew.
He gives like a big like president speech like in Air Force One or something.
He's not.
Smashes his hand against the x-rays.
I don't accept this.
Fix me.
In August he is castless.
So it says he's still recovering at that point so maybe he was feeling pretty good by.
You're just Googling you're you on Getty images like Harrison Ford 2014.
He is very well documented from the paparazzi and the like tabloid press.
So you can get a kind of timeline of his recovery.
So that does help here.
I guess I really should have done it with Dial of Destiny 2 because he got hurt as well.
Well but then it doesn't result in a Halloween costume.
So who cares.
That's true. You're right.
It doesn't matter.
Real I think so.
I think the true best work of his career in the last two decades.
Yeah it's true.
Similarly I was looking at a timeline that was on People Magazine and that was helpful
for finding out things like James Marsden and Bill Richardson and yet the timeline included
no Halloween costumes.
What kind of rag is this People Magazine where they leave out the most important part of the
relationship.
I know that is very important.
Yearly Halloween costumes.
This is where this is who they actually are.
This is where their spirit lives.
Look how happy they are as glam rockers.
Let's name another one.
Okay let's stick with where they are in the same mode and I will bring up this one where
they are both nerds.
Yes the nerd costume.
I really like the nerds.
So yeah both just you know real classic giant glasses.
Horn rim.
I think this is one of her best.
She's you know it's taped up in the middle.
This is like the nerds that we knew from cartoons in the early 90s.
Yes and her glasses are like really big.
His is actually closer to normal.
I feel like those are just his glasses.
He's like I gotta wear my own glasses I can't fucking see.
You're doing a costume with glasses this time.
Who has glasses?
You watch movies?
Who's a glasses character?
He's not wearing any there's no tape on his glasses either.
No.
And she has tape.
I dare they were expensive.
These rims are important.
I'm not putting tape on them.
He's a nerd or no nerd.
These are a gift from Brian Grazer.
These frames.
He this one it has the things I like.
He's got a bottle of wine.
He's got an orange solo cup.
Couple of them he has an orange solo cup.
I wonder if it's the same pack.
Great we're partying.
I only just get it for Halloween.
Red solo cup.
Do you think he knows the song red solo cup by Toby Keith?
Maybe.
I think he does.
Because it's like a country fried song.
Yeah I think he likes it.
It's chill.
I like it too.
I like the red solo cup a lot.
I think you're saying he likes it because you like it.
I'd like to think he likes things I like.
Yeah I like him and I would like him to like things I like.
You know what holds up?
Third eye blind.
I jammed out to them every day on Air Force One.
Do you like his name tag that appears to say Timmy?
Yeah I do.
I do like that.
We got a name here.
I actually I forgot I was going through like screenshots on my desktop.
I forgot that I pulled this from an article that just very very stiffly.
So one of these British tabloids is like who's Timmy?
The actor seemed in great spirits as he attended the party dressed up as an old man.
Apparently named Timmy.
I saw that too.
I saw a couple say they were old people.
But the wigs are very clearly brunette wigs.
They're not really white or anything.
You're right if anything this ages him down.
Yes.
Yeah he looks youthful.
He looks less gray than...
He looks like a youthful nerd.
He looks like a nerd of 53.
Every costume should be its own movie starring the two of them.
A thousand percent.
Every movie just no budget script doesn't even have to be very good but just use the same
costume and like they're two nerds and they're getting in the hijinks.
They have a May December romance going on but it works they seem happy.
Sure yeah.
He's a nerd.
Hello I'm here for the...
I'm here for the computer job.
My name is Timmy.
I've got my model planes in the car that I've constructed.
Here's my resume.
This just says E equals MC squared on it.
You Timmy are a nerd.
Oh this has dogged me my whole life.
Geez.
Oh jellikers.
But will Timmy ever find love?
Yes I'm here for the job as well.
Oh wow.
Slow mo dream weaver.
Yeah they like they they both drop their calculators at the same time.
They're trying oh is this yours?
No this is mine.
Oh excuse me uh my calculations were oh I lost what I had been computing.
Oh I forgot all the numbers what are you doing?
He works at the computer job she works at the book factory.
You like books?
Yes I guess you could say.
Yeah all of these.
Calculators like they both that all the numbers come loose and then they both have threes and
they put the they're like bumbling they lost their glasses too and then they bump and put
their threes together and oh yeah.
Oh wow this is a beautiful love story.
And then the finale they both dance with the dancing baby screen.
Oh the dancing baby is in this too.
Oh sure you expect to see from Ali McBeal.
From Ali McBeal.
To come along with with that.
Yes yeah sure.
That's they just put glasses on it and that's their baby.
Yeah sure same same cgi.
Two nerds and a little nerd.
This Thanksgiving.
Has Calista worked a lot lately?
She had a show on CBS it was a drama.
That's a while ago.
Is it a while ago?
That's when Rob Lowe I want to say.
There's an Ali McBeal reunion talks or new Ali McBeal talks.
Oh yes because we need to know more about what's going on at the firm.
Of course.
We've been wondering what's up at the firm and it really doesn't matter if they get all the
actors back I want to know the firm story.
That's right.
I think I was finishing middle school when like Ali McBeal was at its height
and I really I didn't watch it but I saw all the commercials and like I feel like a couple
people I thought were cool in school were they were like oh I know they're really in the Ali
McBeal must be a cool show.
I didn't know it's where this was.
It's a cool show for adults.
I thought maybe you were going to say I've watched every Ali McBeal.
No I've watched maybe one.
I could see you have been being an Ali McBeal kid.
I remember who's in it from Ghostbusters 2.
Peter McNigle.
Yeah.
Jan Krakowski.
And then Donnie Jr. eventually.
And seemingly constant musicians.
Non-stop.
A lot of musicians performing on Ali McBeal.
And he sang on Ali McBeal as well.
Our DJ did.
I believe so.
I wonder what did he sing.
I don't know was it from the Futurist?
Was it from his album?
I'm not sure.
He was doing standards right like in the early 2000s.
That's why the lady is up.
Was he doing an album or you mean on the show?
Well I think he had an album.
No the Futurist is an album but it is original songs that I've talked about before where it
says not an album I like but I appreciate that there's a lot of effort going on.
You may have noticed I didn't engage you on the Futurist.
I know you tried.
I know you tried to get me to go away.
Jason what do we got?
But Jason said stuff that felt like he didn't know what he was talking about.
I don't know.
So I had to guide him lay in.
I had to let him know.
I kind of remember him doing like Seth MacFarlane swing albums or something.
I don't think there's an album of that.
No no he doesn't have.
He just has the Futurist.
Is it just some appearances?
Maybe he sang a big band song somewhere but I don't that's not what he put out.
That's not what he released.
You should play the Futurist back to back with that Sinatra album.
He sang.
The concept album where he talks about the future.
He sang with Sting a couple years ago at I believe Sting's birthday party I think.
But he sang a police song.
And it caused a wave of sleepiness that echoed across the globe.
Every people who weren't even there had incredible night's sleep.
I want to like the police more than I do.
I like the police fine.
Solo Sting gets points.
Well no that's rough.
Yeah.
So Timmy gets points I feel due to being named.
There's a full character there.
An entire universe you can imagine.
But what else we got?
Here let's why don't we stay in.
Well no that might be the last one where they match.
What I'm looking at now is kind of a sequel to Nerd.
For her Calista is a seemingly a mad scientist with crazy teeth.
Oh yeah.
Who has perhaps been in some kind of accident in the lab.
That's how I read this costume.
Is that fair?
Yeah.
The potion blew up and her hair is messy.
Sure sure.
It's like that kind of nutty professor kind of thing.
Yeah.
Thought she had the cure for cancer but all but all she had was a tag on her face.
And as for him this is what what is he like.
He put on a Lakers jersey and sunglasses.
And like a chain.
Yeah.
So he's like he's a Lakers fan.
Who's the number what number is on the jersey actually?
24 I think it's Kobe.
Okay all right so he's either a fan hopefully he's not being Kobe.
I don't think so.
Well he has not done anything problematic to indicate this.
That's good.
So I don't know.
This one seems a little lazier on his part.
It definitely does yeah yeah yeah.
You know also he's wearing a hat and sunglasses so I don't think that's being Kobe.
Because Kobe couldn't wear those things to play.
He's just a basketball player.
Maybe.
So you know all right let's let's just say I don't think anybody's as excited about this one.
But it's fine it's fine.
There's no lasers in the bunch.
It's fine.
But you know I like to see her I like to see more range.
See what else she can do.
Yeah.
Because I think the other nerd was superior Mrs. Timmy.
Absolutely yeah.
So then let's let's see how we like.
Here's a good like nothing to do with each other.
We got none and I guess Miss Piggy.
I think this is not just a pig this is Miss Piggy.
I think because due to the the feather boa and a tutu and there's I think kind of a glam nature.
I'm going to say that's that's Miss Piggy.
And then none's up there for him.
And it also feels like the closest that when you look at him looking very serious in a nun habit.
Here's where you can imagine that there's some mood that like in the fugitive he
passed through a church.
Oh yeah.
What can I throw on.
I don't I don't believe so.
He's dressed as a priest in a movie maybe.
Am I wrong.
Maybe I'm right maybe making that up.
I think he.
God again I can't remember.
Witness.
Does he put the Amish outfit on.
We've been dancing around that the whole time.
That's the silliest costume.
Even still here wait I'm looking at it.
It's not you could go a lot more.
This is not the Halloween store costume of I think he's they're still trying to make him look
hot as an Amish detective and he's protecting a witness.
Yeah right.
That is called witness.
I should know that sounds right.
You seem more confident than me.
But he doesn't put like a beard on.
He's not like chewing a big stalk.
Right.
So you know and there's a few where I think he's he's looking at it is one where he's like
barrel chested is you know the shirts way open.
I think he's a hot Amish guy.
So there's no like Lincoln beard.
So I can't I don't know if even by default and due to the it's certainly his silliest hat.
Yes.
And so maybe by default it's the silliest he's looked in a movie but still not that silly.
Not that silly.
He almost he looks like Indy honestly in a couple of his films.
Yep he's a cool Amish guy.
Back to none.
Yeah.
A thing I like about it is he's wearing like joke shop the glasses that look like aviators
but they had the big fake like really made up eyes.
Oh my god I was looking at a couple's photo where that's gone where he's not wearing that.
Thank you for reminding of this.
Yeah you're right he must have lost those at some point in the night.
It's the like I'm not asleep glasses.
Yeah and this is one where of course he's got the two bottles of wine as a good party guest.
Yep yep yep yep.
Okay I know to bring a nice bottle of wine now.
And it fits with the religious theme.
Yes oh that's true.
This wine could be used to be turned into Christ's blood.
Yeah maybe she's just stocking up at the religious supply store.
This is also if we're talking about a movie this is the one where Harrison is definitely the
like the most well cast.
This makes the most sense is him playing a nun in a movie because he'd be sort of stern no nonsense.
He's obviously an older guy like he is perfectly cast as a nun in my mind if you're putting
together a movie like this.
Sure.
There's kind of a gender erasure that comes from the hat because all you've got is the face.
So he keeps his head down.
If he's in a big line of nuns all walking somewhere is there still anywhere where there's
like a lot of nuns together?
I'm sure there are.
There has to be.
In my head like the kind of you know like where my parents go there's like one nun per church.
Okay.
I don't know when I've never maybe in my life seen 30 nuns all walking somewhere.
Where was the sound of music?
Well it's in a fake but yes.
Yeah but maybe in I guess in the real sound of music.
I don't know.
Yeah there's got to be like 30 nuns hanging out.
Where I grew up there was a retirement home for nuns.
Okay sure.
Next to Newman College.
The nun house.
Or a VH1 reality show.
Yeah.
What am I gonna do?
They think I killed my wife.
You're gonna have to witness protection program in the nun house.
This is kind of now we're getting very derivative of his other.
It's a derivative of both fugitive and witness but he's good at what he's good at.
Can be a sequel to any one of those.
Sequel witnesses.
Witnesses.
Parentheses nun house.
Witnesses nun house.
Turns into a party movie though halfway through.
Yeah yeah.
Oh yeah yeah.
This nun house is more of a nut house.
The case is resolved so then they party to celebrate.
He gets Frank to license Margaritaville officially.
Yeah.
Frank's producing the movie.
You think we could get.
We have an idea where all the nuns are partying to Margaritaville.
I think I can handle that.
Sister Mary barfs on me.
A thing I want to give Calista some credit.
Please.
Because she does a thing that I like a lot about Halloween costumes.
I think I like both extremes.
I like the picture perfect costumes but I also like the homemade like
it's not 100% exact but it's all the signifiers you know.
What you can find to represent kind of a difficult concept to represent.
And I think that's part of the fun of Halloween is like you piece it together.
And it's maybe not like 100% like camera ready but it communicates the idea and it
looks fun and funny you know.
So she's got the pig nose and ears.
She's got the feather boa.
She's got a pink like sweatsuit on and it's like yeah that's pretty all pretty simple
but it communicates what you're trying to do you know.
It's not too sweaty.
There's a certain point if you put too much money into these things.
I don't think any of these costumes cost either of them more than $100.
Absolutely.
I have never seen them do anything.
They could afford better.
I like think so.
That money should be going into the planes.
That money is for plane fuel.
That's right.
Another thing he has injured himself doing.
He crashed an old World War II plane I think onto the golf course in Santa Monica.
Any landing you can walk away from right?
Yes that is true.
There was a period where he got hurt a lot.
I think he hasn't been hurt luckily in a few years two years.
This nun's habit is too long.
I slipped.
I crushed my leg.
Thankfully JJ Abrams was at the party.
Pulled it up.
He broke his back again for me.
Twice.
This man loves me.
His first JJ Abrams movie that he wrote regarding Henry stars Harrison Ford.
Does he have a silly costume regarding Henry?
Let's look it up.
Oh my god look.
Oh it's right there.
He's dressed as a big grapefruit.
Oh wow.
It's in the poster too.
I think there is going to be one that the listeners are like guys duh.
There's something famous.
Yeah we're missing.
Yeah.
Where it's not coming to me.
He is going to be.
First of all I think it's fascinating that he signed onto a Marvel like multiple Marvel
movies recently to replace William Hurt.
Oh he's the president now?
Maybe something like that.
But he's all going to be a Hulk.
Harrison Ford is going to be a red Hulk.
Yes and he didn't know this.
He doesn't know anything.
There was an interview.
And I love it.
Maybe you're going to maybe turn into the red Hulk.
And he's just like what are you?
Maybe he doesn't even say anything.
Just stares at the interviewer and he's just like I don't know.
They told me I can shoot it all in my backyard over three days.
It's five million dollars for three days of work in my backyard at a green screen.
His lack of interest in Marvel is the one thing that gives me hope that we could be friends.
Well he doesn't care about Star Wars either.
I think he and I do probably have similar levels of caring about Star Wars.
Yeah yeah.
It is great casting for Thunderbolt Ross.
That's who he is right?
If he's the red Hulk.
That's who he's playing yeah.
Because Liam Hurt died who was Thunderbolt Ross before.
So he is replacing.
But yes that's going to be I guess what I'm saying is unless we're missing something big
it will be funny to see a big gloopy CGI red Hulk with Harrison Ford's 83 year old face on it.
That is funny.
I'm worried.
I'm worried it's going to be bad or I might like it.
Well I think I'm going to like it.
I think I like that he has a straight.
I like that you only have to know about these pictures to see him silly.
Yeah.
I think we like $80 silly Harrison Ford.
Are we going to like $80 million silly Harrison Ford?
But you have to remember it's going to be a rushed production no fault of the CGI artist.
But Marvel will change it like two weeks before it comes out and make it look weirder for some reason.
Oh sure.
Oh yes so there's going to be those frames that look horrible.
Yeah so it will look goofy and I'm sure in some shots.
Okay well I like that.
So that will be maybe his silliest on screen appearance.
So we have a project where it's confirmed that he's in.
Yeah he's in the Captain America 4.
He's in the new.
Is that next year?
I don't I used to know this the answer to these questions I do not.
There's too many.
It's used to get like an evenly paced kind of like.
Yeah I knew.
A softball from the batting cage every 10 seconds and now it's just firing a mega.
I'm behind.
I fell ow stop pummeling me.
We go to every one opening night and I'm behind I haven't seen Guardians yet.
I haven't seen Quantumania yet.
I haven't started yet.
Loki season two has started.
I know that.
A couple episodes in.
I think Secret Wars has been delayed to 2028 I believe.
Oh man.
Which is the finale of this saga.
I don't know but I think it's probably next year.
He's in it for sure.
Okay.
But he's going to be in more too.
They're you know they're they're struggling a little right now.
Maybe a little oversaturated.
A little.
Shot in the arm they need maybe is Harrison Ford Red Oak.
It's a blast of gamma radiation.
Everyone says you know what I'm a little tired of superheroes but you know what.
This guy sleepwalking through this performance is what I needed.
A body scan machine never saying a single line is the Red Hulk.
They bring it up all gingerly like there are these tools that we have.
It's gotten a bad reputation but AI and what it allows us to do is to capture.
Yes do it.
Sounds good.
Whatever you want.
Yep.
All right.
Yeah.
Whatever.
I'm just saying.
What are all the syllables I need to say?
What do you need for me?
I'm just saying.
We have them.
Actually we fully built the model already.
We were worried you were going to say no.
No.
Sign off.
Go for it.
I'm getting on my plane.
We borrowed it from Lucasfilm.
You've got all of your stuff on file.
You are putting dots on my face.
And that's what he won't stand for.
Like the gumdrops.
Too silly.
Too silly to have dots.
I've seen those photos from Dial of Destiny because they de-aged him.
He has the dots.
Oh he has the dots.
That's silly.
That's the silliest he's ever looked on camera.
Yeah.
Oh what a fool.
I'm just saying you know.
You're going back to this point.
I'm saying Levin and Mathau had a whole other stage of their career
in the night.
Grumpy old man.
Sure.
Shot in the arm.
Okay and you're saying that Red Hulk is grumpy old Hulk.
Sometimes you can teach an old dog new tricks.
Red Hulk is looking for love in his 80s.
Maybe.
Okay the only way this works is if there's another.
Just follow the same formula you just said.
There's also a Purple Hulk.
They are both old.
They are too old to fight.
They are maybe they're strong and they're certainly big but they don't really.
It's more about them like sitting around and checking out another an old Hulk lady who
pezzes by.
Galista wants to do it.
She can.
Well I was going to say.
Look at that orange.
Art imitating life.
Another new entrant to the Marvel Universe.
Newish.
Julia Louis Dreyfus.
That's right.
She is in there.
On camera.
You know.
You think she's going to fall in love with.
General Thunderbolt Ross.
But I want him to be the Hulk when he falls in love.
Not General Ross.
He can be the Red Hulk.
She can fall in love.
She actually hates General Ross.
Completely butts heads.
Right.
I don't ever want to see this guy again.
But the Hulk.
That's different.
That's a different story.
Yeah.
But a May December romance with a 90s hot television star.
Red Hot.
You know very funny.
Hot Sizzle.
The cover of Entertainment Weekly.
Multiple times.
Jason's standing up and waving his arms around.
He's so excited about this.
You're just referring to the fact that she's ever been on the cover of Entertainment Weekly in her life.
Well what I'm saying.
She's hot.
Art imitating life.
Calista.
Julia.
You know.
I think you have a severe crush on Julia Louis Dreyfus that's coming out here.
Hot.
Hot hot hot.
I mean who doesn't I suppose to some degree.
She's beautiful.
Yeah.
But I like this idea that Julia Louis Dreyfus.
Who's been on Entertainment Weekly.
She's been.
Do you want to answer if this actress is hot right now or not.
She was on the cover of Entertainment Weekly.
Okay.
When?
1996.
Fronted.
She's.
Okay.
Seinfeld.
I know.
You don't have to say her.
I'm aware that Julia Louis Dreyfus is a popular actress.
He's going to list the credits.
What?
The NBC show.
I think the list is done after Seinfeld.
The NBC show in real time.
New Adventures of Old Christine.
I remember that.
Veep.
Oh I forgot about Veep.
You're right.
She does have a career.
What about the Tony Soprano?
What Gannolfini movie she was in.
Remember they fall in love.
Yeah.
I still.
You don't remember.
What are we arguing now.
So you see she can be in love in a movie.
This dream is.
I don't know what the argument is.
I think a mismatch romance.
A romantic comedy is just what the Marvel Universe needs to get back on track.
I agree with this.
All right.
I agree with that too.
Yeah.
I can't dispute that.
Break genres.
They always say that they are like this is a little more of a this and then they don't.
Yes.
Full rom-com.
No action.
The action is boring.
I agree.
I can't follow the action.
Now I sound like a grumpy old man.
The action puts me to sleep.
I don't know what I'm looking at.
That's what my mom says too.
But a nice bit of.
I do.
Genuinely though.
This isn't even recent.
I said this in 2012.
Yeah.
I thought the action was boring.
I think some of the action is good and some of the action is boring.
Yes.
There's a certain point where you just can't make heads or tails.
Well, some of the VFX staff has unionized so maybe it'll be a little smoother.
Maybe there'll be less last minute change.
I think it's 20% of the VFX staff.
Yeah.
But we'll see what it does to the silliness of the look of the Red Hulk.
I don't know.
I miss the silliness though.
Silliness is something.
The bland aesthetic they go for is nothing.
Now, oh, I hate to.
We have so much.
What if they decide there's just no time and they got to make them like old school
Lou Ferrigno style and we got to paint Harrison.
Could you imagine?
Then we have the best.
I'm now I'm back.
I'm back in the Marvel universe.
Now I think I solved the issue.
Yes.
Paint him.
Practical effects are back.
Oh, please.
And then just like a big like make him wear whatever Violet Beauregard wore.
He's just in a big puffy.
Well, that's even more than I thought.
I was just picturing Ferrigno with the pants ripped pants and naked.
Otherwise, that's Ferrigno.
Ferrigno is big.
That's true.
Harrison Ford's kind of the slider at this point.
Okay.
You got to puff them up.
So put them in a paint a suit red.
Great.
Harrison knows where to find the costumes.
He knows where the deals are.
I'm the Red Hulk.
Watch out.
Go to the sun.
The sun Valley, Idaho target.
Great.
Great coupons.
Harrison times are tough.
Use the app.
We know your ability to make a costume, so we're going to trust you to make your own
Red Hulk costume.
We're pay.
We are.
Now we have already agreed to pay you $25 million.
Can some of that money go to the costume?
Use as much or as little.
I'm sorry, but that's going to have to include your costume fees.
All right.
I'm going during circle week in the app and I am pocketing the difference.
I'm buying granola bars, too.
Those are for me.
I'm not sharing them with the crew.
Oh, this is my birthday month, too.
So I get one purchase.
That's 5% off.
I'm pocketing that.
You're not getting that one.
Well, that'll bring the people back.
I would absolutely bring me back.
Okay.
So let's here.
Let's make good.
We said them all.
And then there's the hot dog.
I mean, the hot dog was on Kimmel and I really like in the clip when Kimmel is fishing for
force awakens spoilers and his response is woof, woof.
Woof, woof.
That's great.
That's very good.
And then he's pretty sincere.
He's like, I just want them to see the movie.
I don't want to give anything away.
Just go to the theater.
This is the way it used to be.
There wasn't the whole weird spoiler market and that's great.
But so now we have all our competitors.
They're probably all on all of our desktops in some form and we were asked by Matthew
to rate them somehow.
It might take too long to do a full ranking, but is there some way to determine the best or
to say, I mean, we already said the nerd, but is there one that we want to fully see as a movie
that we haven't gotten to?
I mean, I say follow your heart.
Do you guys just want to name a favorite?
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, we can do a little more of this ranking on Twitter as well or on X.
I really, I think my favorite actually is the hair metal.
Oh.
Actually.
I love the P that's silly, but I like that they're all there together.
They have a unified theme.
It lets you imagine what it would have been like if he was in the film Rock of Ages.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
If Tom Cruise said no.
Yes.
And that's a movie I would want an 80 year old Harrison Ford doing like poison.
Here I go again on my own.
Is that what he said?
What is Tom Cruise singing?
Yeah, I think he does sing that.
Made up my mind.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, it's a couple though.
He sings a couple of the old.
She's my cherry pie.
Sweet cherry pie.
I was promised real cherry pie if I sing it.
Yeah.
Where's my pie?
Stacy Jacks' agent.
That's right.
That's the character.
In case people don't know,
Stacy Jacks is the character from Rock of Ages that is played by Tom Cruise.
Yeah.
In case they don't know.
Isn't Alec Baldwin his agent or something?
Or is the manager of the club?
He's the manager of the club.
I forget.
Yeah.
I didn't know Baldwin does a number.
Not sure.
I don't know.
Hope so.
But yeah, that's for me.
I would like to see Harrison Ford sing in a movie.
And I would like to see him like in the debaucherous 80s.
I don't know that I want to see him having sex a lot.
It's in his age now trashing a hotel room.
But that yeah.
Like it's party.
I like that.
And then a really slow pickup of a chair.
Yeah.
Knocking over the ice pocket.
He will get.
Damn it.
You got to watch out because he will kick an amp over on stage and it'll crush his leg.
Break it.
Ah.
JJ.
Where is JJ?
Do you got a favorite, Jason?
I think it's the nun and Miss Piggy.
Yeah.
I like the contrast.
I like that these costumes look like an assistant went to a Hollywood toy and costume,
which is like a 20 year round prop and like Halloween kind of junkie shop on Hollywood
Boulevard.
But if you just need like X, Y, Z for like, oh, I need a fake arm or I need a big fake tree branch.
They have it.
You know, it's a little grungy, but they're really nice there.
You need a big fake tree branch lately.
I don't know.
It's just trying to think of what you could need.
I was thinking of Halloween decorations.
People have scary trees.
I know you want the scary tree in your, but you want the, we established that you want
the like 5,000 pound Chinese scary tree.
Into an apartment building.
So I don't have a backyard.
If it had been a house, you definitely would have purchased the custom, the $20,000.
Where the shipping was likely three times the cost of the tree because it needs to get to
Southern California from like Shenzhen province.
Yes.
And the, and when it arrived, like, like if you're like, oh, I actually, maybe it'd be
better if we rotated it a little to the right.
All right.
Let's hire 25 men.
Oh yeah.
The installation, the installer costs more than the item.
We can do your job.
I know good men, strong men, but it's going to take six months at minimum.
Yeah, I'm with you.
I'm well, I'm glad nobody said it.
I'm going P pod.
It's definitely P pod.
Yeah.
Love P pod.
And then I'm imagining the movie where like, it's a, it's like a sixties flashback movie
and Calista is a, is a hippie and takes some psychedelics and imagines and is maybe having
an awakening as being a health food nut and liking being a vegetarian and maybe what
solidifies this is a, is a big handsome P pod coming to life and showing her the way.
Come, I will show you.
And there has, then this is it.
And then he's, this is the stupidest shit I've ever said.
He sings this thing.
You see, he's performs a song that's about vegetarian awakening and this song is,
is called the says the dawning of the age of asparagus.
Some real food rocks.
Asparagus.
That's good.
They missed out on that one.
I just produced a perfect food rocks with no foresight.
Or kitchen cabaret.
Yeah.
And fifth dimension wouldn't go forward.
They wouldn't sign up on it.
There's a lot of members.
And then there's a disgusting sex scene between the P and the.
Ah, rub my P. Not that P lower, the lower, the fifth from the top.
That's where that's the erogenous P.
Yeah.
No, it's the anatomy is different on a P than it is on a human.
So don't you know how to fuck a P?
We're here at Access Hollywood.
So Harrison, tell us about your newest project.
You're wearing a peep pod, but there's nine songs level nudity and sex scenes.
I get fucked as a P. Don't you want, I've answered you already.
Okay.
Well, hey, fire up your AMCA list to see Harrison Ward get fucked as a P.
I don't like spoilers, but in this case, I'll tell you.
Six ways to Sunday as a P.
All right.
Where else do we go?
I don't know.
Get the hell out of this.
Thank you, Matthew.
Imagine everything that you just heard.
Now just picture a quote around all of it for the last hour or so.
And then just attribute it to Matthew Kamegis.
Thank you.
You caused it and you all survived.
Haunt cast the freight, the cemetery gate, hunt cast the freight.
Merch is available in our T public store.
We'll get one more booness episode on our RIP tier Crypt 3.
There you will hear the rightful actual poll winner Tower of Terror, the movie
with Steve Gutenberg.
But here we took the reins, grabbed the whip ourselves.
That was the other.
Wait here.
Here's a little thought exercise on the way out.
Combining Harrison Ford and Halloween costumes.
Imagine his real cost.
If you wanted to be Indiana Jones, if you wanted to be Han Solo,
the off-brand Halloween costume names of Harrison Ford's iconic characters.
Can we do this?
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
Oh.
Like, you know, it's not Han Solo.
It's like Astral Vest-Wearer.
Interstellar vest enthusiast.
Instead of Indiana Jones, it's just Professor Adventure.
That's good.
I like Professor Adventure.
I think a lot of the movies could just be serious guy.
Mean man.
All business.
This is my other idea for Indiana Jones is being non BDSM whip enthusiast.
That's great.
Yeah.
So if you're selling bootleg costumes out there, there's some free ideas for you.
Airplane president.
Plane demander.