I want to dive right in. I want to talk about the poll. The thing about the polls that I think
is great is the audience gets to vote with their heart, you know, and just put out in the world what episode they want and whatever they want is correct. And there's no right or wrong. There's no right or wrong answer. Except for this time. There was a right answer here in the Crypt 3 poll. The right answer was Harrison Ford and Callista Flockhart's Halloween costumes. Now I don't want, you know, and it's not a good note maybe to start with,
but I wanted to get this right out of the way. We're excited to talk about Tower of Terror the movie. We will talk about Tower of Terror the movie. That being said, the right answer was right there. And it only came in fourth? I have to say I'm shocked.
I had been tracking and it was number three. What knocked it out of three?
I'm not sure. I think maybe Spirit Halloween still snuck up there. I mean, while we're naming things, the nightmare experiment will be the run or that'll be the incumbent next Halloween. So we'll revisit that.
Really fascinating. It's very interesting. If you don't know it, and we didn't dive in, so I don't really know it, but it seems like Hong Kong Disneyland tried to do this in 2016. They tried to do maybe the only true Disney attempt at a horror nights that had actually scary and upsetting stuff, all of which is maybe more upsetting than usual because it involved Disney characters being entrapped and tortured seemingly.
So fascinating. But if we want that, that's going to have to be next Halloween. For now, I mean, Harrison and Calista. Look, I also we revealed a little bit recently about how a certain type of topic is usually Mike's pick. And so I saw people saying, I see Mike's trying to get his nonsense in there with Harrison and Calista. Let me tell you, listener, this was all of our pick. We were all abuzz about Harrison and Calista.
This was this was no one person's pick. This was everyone's pick. And, you know, it can't always align the way you want it here on Crypt 3, but over on the cemetery gate where we choose Harrison and Calista coming soon.
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I think that's right. I think it has to be right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, it's where, you know, hey, the audience controls here, but we control the other place. And I like I think it's really nice to I enjoy getting to promote a an audience suggested topic. And yeah, and that one I'll tip my hat a little. I'll give away my opinion a little. It's a little bit of nonsense. But also every year when I see the pictures, I smile.
Like I'm always looking forward to like, what are they doing this year?
Uh huh. Yes.
A little bit of nonsense. Be a whole lot of nonsense. But that's what
I don't know. This is a substantial topic, I think will deep dive into their career into their marriage. See how it's doing today, how it survived post pandemic. I think there's I think it's rich. There's a lot to talk about. And I'm sure very theme park related.
Yeah, very, very much so.
But we did we did, of course, land at something theme park related. And I mean, sorry, you know, it's based on a film, a sort of a film.
Shot in a theme park, parts of it.
Parts of it.
I mean, kind of.
Little parts of it.
For November, back to regular suggestions, regular topics, not only topics which will go up against the strange Animal Kingdom show Kite Tales.
But for now, let's dive in. A number of people suggested this.
So this is how you know there was there was all there was, you know, mass agreement on this.
Among them, Dylan Lee, Six Fogs, Great Adventure, nice name.
And then I think Z.H. might have been the main and first one who said quite simply Tower of Terror, the Steve Guttenberg movie.
And here we are now.
Yeah.
We all watched this film.
We did.
I think as far as I know, I didn't know.
I didn't ask.
We don't watch it together.
Mm hmm.
We did not.
No, we didn't have a party for it.
No, we didn't.
We watched presumably the same single bootleg copy that is uploaded to YouTube.
Yeah.
Now this I think that this is purchasable as a DVD or even perhaps VHS.
I seem to recall it existing as physical media, but you cannot find this on Disney Plus today.
Yeah.
This is certified.
I think now probably YouTube is you're in our best bet.
Yeah.
Jane has DVD and it's somewhere.
We don't know where it is right now.
Okay.
Owner of the DVD.
Books are still or books and movies are still in moving box like we haven't filled up the bookcases yet.
Well, you got to get Tower of Terror the movie out and on a shelf.
When guests come over, they're going to be wondering do you where's your physical copy of Tower of Terror from 1997.
Blue Ray players not hooked up yet.
It's a mess of cables on top of the.
4K, Blue Ray.
U.K.
Yeah.
Oh, it's going to sparkle in that Blue Ray.
Why are you wasting your time?
This is a film.
This is a film from October 1997 was the release.
This was a movie for ABC's Wonderful World of Disney.
And I was like in what order do we go?
Exactly.
Is there context?
Do we discuss the casting a little bit?
But as soon as I have now said ABC's Wonderful World of Disney and that's where this premiered that tells us something very important about this movie.
Right. Of course.
And how it was presented on television.
So why, you know, why not cut to the chase what we all want and with no further explanation.
Here's what we want.
Give it to me.
Give me that hit.
Hello, I'm Michael Eisner.
Music and sound plays such an important role in setting the mood both in filmmaking and in our daily lives.
That's so true.
That's why I do some of my best thinking in elevators.
There's a safe and quiet.
They always have such a nice and right use of it.
Wow.
Once again, a bright idea has come to me in an elevator.
The next time I think I'll take the stairs.
Welcome to the Wonderful World.
Oh, Michael.
Michael wandered into that 10 second clip of Tower of Terror promotional footage that has been used.
Over.
Seemingly the majority of our lives.
Yes, we have how many times have we seen this and in revisiting old specials and looking at resort TV, it's the fits like there's the shaft and there's like the wheel creaking and then the shaft, the car flying down.
And then the the numbers that take you all the way up to 13 was spinning and spinning around.
Yeah.
And we see this footage even if the rest of what it's accompanying is shot on cheap video.
Yes.
Still, we look at this like nice film footage like really nicely directed and lit footage that was in all the TV ads, which also and I'm maybe taking this from a listener.
Somebody pointed out how this intro and the ads for Tower of Terror always made you feel like so wait, you go to this thing and you stand in an elevator.
You do not have a seat or a seat belt or a restraint or even a pole to hold.
You were just they're just going to drop me in an elevator.
I might hit the ceiling.
I might collapse and keel over.
Yeah, kid told me that's what it was.
I think some kid told me that's what happens on it.
It looked very scary and very cool, but I was fully prepared like well, we're going to do this cool thing and we might die.
I don't know why all these people are laughing, but I guess it's what this is the way I'd like to go out.
I'm a child.
Sure.
Huh?
Or I mean, if you believe the story that you're told at the beginning of the ride, a story which is reprised in the film and the basis of the film, then you might believe that this is not the way to death, but rather to eternal life.
Yeah.
If a weird creepy limbo, but like that's maybe if something happened to you up there, then maybe you get decades more and you're locked in age wise, then you get to be the Sally Shine of the fifth dimension or whatever it is.
Wouldn't be the worst thing in the world.
Hey, walking around a beautiful hotel, a lot of those plants still holding up just going, it's raining, it's pouring over and over again.
Big band music playing.
Oh boy.
Big band music.
On a creaky old turntable.
I was going to say that the beginning of this film, they play that the one song from the 30s.
I wrote that down, yes.
The film starts with the big band equivalent of like one of the three Vietnam War rock songs.
Oh, that's true.
That's the Fortunate Son of the 30s.
That's how we know that it's the 30s.
The song is Sing Sing Sing and that's how you know we're in the past, baby.
Sing Sing Sing is playing or Fortunate Son.
Or it's a candy bar commercial from the 90s.
Oh, that's true.
Something like that.
Something with some creepy early CGI Snickers bars or something.
Yes.
Or like a swing dancing Gap Khakis ad.
Very possible too.
Could be in there.
I think that's probably it too.
I guess that's mostly West Side Story, but I feel like there was a sword at generations of Gap ads.
Eisner also uses a joke that's in the movie.
Like I'll take the stairs?
I'll take the stairs, yeah.
That's almost like one of the only, what else do you got?
I guess that's true, but it is funny that he uses the same joke.
That is the main bullet point in the press kit that they gave everyone.
Like, okay, when you're doing interviews, work in I'll take the stairs.
The press kit for this movie?
Well, for the movie, for the ride, for any, like, okay, everyone.
This will work.
This will kill.
Seeing Eisner also with the listener can't see unless you look up the clip.
And you have to also to find that it's like within, it's not in the main YouTube version of that.
You got to go fishing a little bit, which is great.
There's like, there's no shortage of hellos.
And that one wasn't in one of your montages?
No.
So often do I run into ones that aren't in the, they did so many of these.
At this point, I don't think I even, because I, and I updated it and added more.
And even with the second one, I don't think I got even half in there.
It's crazy.
And there used to be a YouTube channel that like was compiling them all, but I think it disappeared.
I think it went into ghostly limbo.
So I don't know what happened.
But you get to see, you only have one shot basically of Eisner reacting to free falling to his death.
And this is, this has long been a setup for hammy acting, I'd say, is like making people like the Regis's of the world.
Oh, yeah.
Ride the Tower of Terror.
And Regis is broad, silly, bug-eyed.
Yes, but it's something.
Eisner is just, he's just giving, it is the, it's just no reaction.
It's just his like resting face.
It's like if you just saw him at a coffee shop, just kind of, you know, not thinking about anything.
This is, it's how you would look falling to his demise.
Yeah, it's an interesting choice as we probably assume they didn't have a ton of time with him.
So maybe, you know, two takes each and, okay, great, Michael, that was great.
And we'll tilt the camera.
So like we'll tilt the.
Now we still, this again, we don't have like total confirmation on this Eisner Soren situation.
But as you just said, I, of course, they didn't have a lot of time with him for a lot of these things.
Yeah.
And it remains my biggest question.
It's like, why is he waiting through all these flybys?
Unless he is just relaxing.
Yeah, it's true.
Like getting crunk at the Arnold Palmer La Quinta course.
I don't think he's a big drinker, but I don't know why I think that.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Well, now we know he's not a big golfer.
He's not a big golfer.
He gets tired of golf.
So we know he's a big shower.
Now we know that about his office from the recent Eiger.
Well, of course.
Yeah, he loves the double.
Did he love the double shower?
No, Eiger loved the double shower.
He said he lived for the double shower days.
Eisner could have been a quadruple shower guy.
We don't know.
We don't have the information.
After every meeting, he took a shower.
He loved to be so fresh for each meeting.
After every shoot, they took it out of him.
A speakerphone on a cart into the shower room.
Sampling the different Mickey's Kitchen foods on his desk.
All right, I got to take a shower after each one.
He personally approved every brownie.
To make a soup. I got it on my forearm.
It's going to be a long day.
Bring me a peanut butter and jelly pizza.
Can I get something with gummy worms on it?
Michael, you have to approve this new plush pile we're thinking about putting in each Disney store.
All right, but I got to take a shower first.
It's going to be 45 minutes.
I got to get a steam worked up in there.
And then he comes out and he knows it.
I have just one shower is all it takes.
And he's like, I think it's got to be more of a cone.
You need a 35 degree. Otherwise, it's going to be too imposing.
He does his best thinking in the shower.
So yeah, he comes out and he goes, it's Tigger. It's Eeyore.
It's Mickey, then Minnie, and then it's all the Aristocats.
And that's the topper. That's the big thing.
All the Aristocats are on top of the plush pile.
Michael, you did it again. Back to the shower.
Someone bring me a worms and dirt for the love of God.
Yeah, yeah, he did it all.
It's got to be what it was like.
Yeah, like got the ideas out of his pores.
So we start off strong and we're there.
And then because this also this comes in the Renaissance of Eisner intros,
because this is the return of Wonderful World of Disney.
It's when they start airing it on ABC, because you forget a lot of those were aired on NBC, I believe.
Or maybe I think I don't recall if there's any CBS in there.
But now they own ABC. We're bringing back the landmark franchise.
They thank God they didn't think of a new host.
Thank God it's still Eisner because a lot like five years have passed.
I hate to to rail it, but not completely.
Have you guys seen that Byron Allen is thinking of buying ABC?
I've seen I've definitely heard swirls of they're trying to sell these networks.
And then the website deadline has an article about Byron Allen every single day.
So Byron Allen context for listeners.
Byron Allen may need context.
All right. Byron Allen does a show that we've talked about on here.
I think a little bit called Comics Unleashed.
But just in addition to that, he's like a very low key media mogul, made a huge fortune and now seems to be in position to bid on ABC.
My God, he might just own all of ABC.
He is a I believe a Malibu mega estate neighbor of Eisner.
Yes.
He's another where the compound is ridiculous.
Right.
I hadn't heard this ABC thing.
There was a profile of him a few years ago about his giant house and just how many shows he's produced for daytime TV and cable.
We knew him.
I feel like the thing we knew him for was that show Comics Unleashed, which is like a roundtable show.
And he would set up the most softball like, hey, Mike, I heard you had a story about Byron Allen story.
Like I heard you had read a Byron Allen article recently.
Well, yeah.
Well, the Norm MacDonald version is we John Love what's on the show and Byron Allen would set up people up for the material.
So he just turns to John and he goes, John, so I understand you're getting older.
Like that's the transition.
The vaguest set up.
Anyway, yeah, he just quietly is by Allen on his 10 billion dollar offer for ABC and other Disney networks.
Capital's not an issue.
But by Bob, you're not ready to pursue the sale supposedly.
But Byron says that the 10 billion Disney TV asset offers fully financed.
He's got the money.
My God.
So he's in the mix.
And he said, I'm the prettiest girl of the dance.
There you go.
And regulators would block big tech and private equity.
So it's got to be me.
I just give it to him.
Does he then start doing?
Well, I mean, I don't know if they're going to start if they're going to bring back Wonderful World at Disney, but then it could be Byron Allen.
Hey, that'd be fine.
I love that.
Yeah.
I don't want this to be sold to like a like a giant conglomerate or something or some tech company.
Yes.
So it's all to Byron Allen.
ABC is about heart.
It's a little upstart network.
You don't want to see some big company owning it.
No.
How weird would that be?
No, it's bad.
I want all my favorites to be like in a little cottage of content.
That's right.
So well, that's exciting.
We'll monitor that.
But this was in this era of so the show is back.
A Wonderful World of Disney.
And we and so they're making an effort to this was I think in the first few months.
And I remember this era.
I was excited by this era because we're getting a bunch of great new Disney films, all of which have some novelty to them.
Some of which are like reprisals of old IP, you know, mixed in with like they just showed Toy Story or whatever.
But I was trying to remember some of these.
And it's the first one of this era was a movie called Toothless where Kirsty Alley is the Tooth Fairy.
There was a movie called Angels in the End Zone.
Remember there was another Angels in the Outfield where Christopher Lloyd came back and my high school classmate David Gallagher was in it.
Little disgust.
I think at this point, my date with the president's daughter was in this era.
If you remember that one, that is kind of a charming that is that's Wilfred Dell from World.
Who is it was funny enough in that that I'm like, I don't know how he didn't become kind of a low budget romcom lead.
Sure. In the wake of it.
The next week after Tower of Terror, they showed the brandy Whitney Houston Cinderella.
That's what I was going to ask.
That was right after this.
OK, that's the same run.
Yeah, because I remember that.
I remember the renew marketing push.
Like I was certainly the hook line and sinker for the refresh wonderful Disney.
Looking back, I in my head, I'd mush together the ride opening and this movie.
But it's three years later.
No, it was after the fact.
After the fact. Yes.
The audiences in Florida have become accustomed to this property and they've taken many rides on the Twilight Zone Tower of Terror, leading notably to the movie Tower of Terror.
Something was missing along the way.
Well, that I got like that was like, OK, that's like comic book logic.
Like the Wolverines and every issue of the X-Men, but the X-Men aren't in every issue of Wolf.
He has his own adventure.
You worked that out when you were a kid.
I worked it out when I was a kid.
It's like, oh, there's a Rod Serling in this Wolverine is the prototype.
There's no Twilight Zone stuff.
It's just the original story of the ride.
I get that I liked and I loved the ride.
I feel like, yeah, I loved it, too.
I love the ride. I've been on the ride.
I love the ride.
So I was excited for a movie based on the ride.
I feel like they were able to double dip, like get people who hadn't been there like, oh, look, it's yeah, that's right.
Yeah, we should we should go check that out.
And then people who had been there like, oh, it's like it's the ride.
It's the building.
So you're describing people said watching TV and saying, look, that's that ride.
We should go.
Look, a lot of people didn't have Internet.
So we had to get our kicks wherever we could.
You know, from the television.
That so that implies that you watch this at the time.
Yeah. As I did this and I think the brandy Cinderella, which is on Disney Plus.
And we watched a couple of years ago and we're like, yeah, that was pretty good.
And this I also was like, this held up pretty this is a pretty competently made movie.
This is kind of like it is. Yes.
It is a solid movie.
But I'm sure there's holes. I'm sure there's holes.
Don't you almost wish that it wasn't, though?
I 100. Look, I have no nostalgia for this.
I didn't know existed when it was out and watching it.
Now I go, this is too like fine.
The movies. Yes, for its it is it is in tribute to the people who made it.
Yes, it is fine. Yeah.
But now, yeah, like what do you do?
What do we do?
We just we just show we describe the plot of a fine movie, I guess is what we did.
The guy who made Are You Afraid of the Dark made this, which is a show I really liked as a kid.
And I could feel the Are You Afraid of the Dark in this.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Light thrills, light thrills, mild ookiness, little messages, little hearts, the big kind of like, oh, is he going to do the right thing?
No, yes, he is.
Turns, turns, good little turns. Yeah.
That actually worked for me. Yeah.
The turns. Yes. I didn't see them coming.
Did you see this when it was out, when it was aired?
I think my history with this being a theme park fan and then seeing it pop up on YouTube,
I have given it a go and gotten lost kind of in the first half hour because while it ultimately ended up working fine for me,
there's a while there where it's like this is the most daytime horror movie.
Oh, I know.
Of every seat. It's just like it's sort of like aesthetic-less for a while.
And I just got, it just lost me in that realm.
But here now that I had to watch it, it's my job to watch it.
I made it to the end and I'm like, okay, you know what?
It started picking up a little mojo.
It became, it started to feel like a light horror movie.
Some aesthetics entered the picture, some darkness and some creepiness.
When Gutenberg is not doing the heavy lifting, the movie gets better.
Yes, yeah. That's what I would say.
I mean, let's, yeah, maybe it's the time to talk about that.
Steve Gutenberg is the star of the film and it's the thing that probably from a distance makes you think, well, this must be a hokey film, right?
Is that sort of how, now I'm questioning why do I feel that way?
Steve Gutenberg kind of has this jokiness about him.
And where does it come from? Is it his name? Is there something that he's especially bad in that, is it this?
Why does Gutenberg feel like a joke?
I can tell you where it starts for me. It's the Stonecutter song on The Simpsons.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
And I knew that they were making fun of him.
The Illuminati organization does all of these things.
Who keeps the metric system down?
But then elsewhere in the song is who makes Steve Gutenberg a star?
And it's all bad stuff.
Yes, yeah, yeah. It's all terribly evil or just suspicious.
So I was like, at the time I went, OK, got it. Steve Gutenberg sucks.
But is that it? Is that just, I mean, this is a feeling I have all the time now where there's somebody just like, guess who's starring in every movie and show?
And I'm like, but why?
Well, yeah.
I mean, this is a very common thing now.
That person is not necessarily always like a malicious presence.
No.
Sometimes it's just like, well, this guy's a little like bland, a little nothing.
Yeah.
And then they just like strike gold with the agents of the world and now they're in prime position.
And then they won't be in like a year after it all comes out and is boring and bad.
As a kid, in the same way that I would mush together Billy Joel and Bruce Springsteen just because they were so ubiquitous at like where I grew up and family parties and.
All right. I will accept this as if it's not insane. Yes. OK.
Well, OK.
But in.
How old were you?
Like in my single digits.
Like I'm saying people playing these at like weddings or christening.
Hearing the songs.
Yeah. Hearing the songs.
Not the men. OK.
Not the men.
Why does that think that's weirder?
I think the songs aren't alike at all.
Yeah. But when you're a kid, you don't necessarily.
No, I'll forgive the kid.
No.
Again, I just mean to say they're like the wallpaper.
They were kind of.
You weren't actively paying attention.
Sure.
Yes. I wasn't paying attention.
In that same way, I would mush together Billy Crystal and Steve Gutenberg.
Interesting.
Because they both kind of had the same like kind of funny way about them.
And in a lot like.
I would say Albert Brooks, Steve Gutenberg.
And when I was younger, maybe I was a little confused by.
OK. OK.
Yeah. Yeah. Because none of the movies are for you exactly.
Right. So you haven't had the cause to really sit and investigate.
I might have known the difference by the time or Steve Gutenberg landed with me more because he was in the Olsen Twins film.
It takes two. Oh, yeah.
And to my kid sister, I would see most of the Olsen Twins content.
Kirstie Alley aforementioned an acceptable film.
Fine.
Sure. I've never seen it.
I know reason to, but it satisfied what it needed to then.
I think that would be like a teacher is hung over or teacher doesn't feel well, but it's still that like that in school.
Any Olsen Twins thing.
Sure. Because it's like I don't even have to check this to know this is fine to show a lot of them have songs.
So music teachers would often be like, we're watching.
We're watching this today.
You know, you want to hear perfect two part harmony and listen to the Olsen Twins.
Yeah. Yeah.
Do what they do.
It takes two.
I just remember that the plot of it, that it is the parent trap, but with real twins and not optical illusions.
Oh, oh, the same thing.
So what if we get we oh my gosh, this is our excuse to do the parent.
We don't have to do any comping.
We have the twins already.
We have to do it.
Is it?
There's a good chance that many Olsen Twins movies are that they have that plot.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They might have done.
I mean, I'm sure I don't know every episode of so little time.
I don't know the full filmography, but I imagine that they used their lookalike abilities to do a lot of fun mix them ups.
Yeah. Yeah.
So so Gutenberg. Yes.
And now I don't again.
There's that Simpsons thing.
But I'm like, what am I?
What have I seen where Gutenberg like sucks?
I don't feel that way in Three Men and a Baby.
Yeah.
Those are fine.
He's fine in that.
Yeah.
He's fine in this also.
I'm just saying once the characters show up, it gets moving a little bit because they're more they're like horror, you know, archetype broad quick hit kind of character.
So you're like more interested in what a crazy voiced ghost guy is doing.
I think it's the weakness of the whole thing.
Listeners, if you don't know, this is we said that it starts with the one song from the 30s and it starts with an effect, an entire scene in the 30s as just as the ride begins.
But after that, it becomes entirely modern day.
And the modern day, I think, is the struggle.
Don't you almost want to see?
I was like, either I want to see an entire 30s movie or I want or I want there to be 30s.
And then we pick it up in like the 50s.
And like Sam Spade guy is solving the mystery of what.
So we're still in a time period because the 90s are very dull and play a very dull.
Yeah.
Is the new haunted.
Have you seen the new Haunted Mansion?
I know it did just streaming.
Is it modern day?
I think so.
Yeah, I believe so.
This is a big problem.
It's like all this stuff.
And this is like they have like we need it to be like people aren't going to understand if it's in the past.
And it's like people like the aesthetic of the old past.
It's creepier.
It can be weirder.
It feels more otherworldly.
Now, I don't think any kid is like bothered by.
No, because you get to enter this whole world like some dumb executive like brain thing where it's like, well, we need to have some sort of like adult from the 90s who's struggling with something.
And we have to deal with him for 30, 40 minutes.
And then we can get to like the old timey ghost stuff.
And you're like, no, we just.
Well, there is so much 90s specifics in here.
One, the weekly world news.
Oh, yeah.
Of it.
Oh, yes.
The crazy tabloids we all see.
The name of Steve Gutenberg's character.
Yes.
Is it Bucky?
It's no.
It's Buzzy Crocker.
Buzzy.
OK.
Buzzy Crocker.
Just so we don't end up in a run of like now let's explain the entire plot in a row.
Buzzy Crocker is a writer for the National Inquisitor.
And when we meet him, he seems as far as we can tell, he's the king of nonsense.
How could you believe that kind of stories?
But they get the tabloids flying and he seems like a little like Buzzy seems a little scuzzy.
Yeah, he's cynical.
He just wants to make money.
And we find that he's faking it essentially.
He's faking most of what he does.
He's a liar.
But yes, Jason, that's true.
It's very like that's very of its era.
And like people now I think you just know what it is.
Like, oh, yeah.
So they started making all these newspapers and made up stuff to buy.
But at the time you'd get like I remember being with my mom or grandma at the grocery store and like, what?
You expect us to believe this?
Like almost akin to like or like a 90s not understanding like, you know, wrestling isn't real.
Yes, it's more complicated.
And that's a weird and also a movie's are real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why are we applying that logic?
Also the 90s, the real newspaper newsroom is the most hectic place on earth.
Oh, yeah.
It's just constantly firing people handing papers to take a phone calls.
And yeah, there's there's not a still moment in it.
Yes. And the people there are deadly serious.
Unlike. Yeah, this is the news.
Yeah. Get real.
Yes. Well, there's that because his girlfriend.
Correct.
Works at the ex-girlfriend that when this when we meet them is from the legitimate news from the Los Angeles banner, I believe.
And then we come to find that he used to be a legitimate journalist.
He was not about faking everything and chasing sensationalized stuff.
And he kind of maybe pines to to go back to that.
What he what happened was that he fell for some fake news.
He was handed a tape.
I'm good. They don't really resolve who gave him a T.
He was he wrote he wistfully recalls a story he wrote mobster mayor.
And it was a video of the mayor taking a bribe from the mob.
But the video was a fake.
Right. And now I wonder that leaves me with questions about this.
This is not in an AI deep fake era where actors dressed up as the mayor and as a bugsy esque mobster.
Hey, I get there is a bag of cash for you right here.
I don't know. I don't know how he fell for this.
I don't know. He really should have double checked.
Yeah, I feel like newspapers of that caliber, especially back then, really went to great lengths to authenticate weird videotapes.
Yeah, yeah. So I don't know.
I don't remember who despite growing up here and I remember who the mayor was at that time, maybe an easily fakeable mayor.
If the if the mayor had a mustache or a big silly hair, then maybe if you know, like you could this is New York, but you could fake an Ed Koch from behind.
Oh, that's really. Yeah. Yeah.
You really think you should see the face, though.
Buzzy. Come on, Buzzy.
You should see the face of the mayor.
Well, he might have maybe he got too eager and like we got because he had he needed to make his career.
So it's like, get it. Who cares? It's vetted. Somebody gave me this. Who was it? I don't know.
A guy. He was nice. Yeah.
So I don't know. But it destroyed his career.
And now he's a tabloid shady guy, although it seems like that's going.
He's doing better. Fine, too. Yeah, I know.
And you don't have like all the integrity ish. You can just like run around and do a little.
It's not that. Little dress up shoots with your niece.
It is also funny that it's like treated sort of like as very serious thing that he's doing.
That's like unethical, where it's like most people knew that like Wolf Boy wasn't real.
So when they put Wolf Boy on the cover of these, like people like really upset with him.
And it's like he could be doing worse things with his life.
Oh, you also get a snippet of another 90s go to where like the actor is hired to play a doctor.
And there's a gag where he's going to saw off an alien head.
But Kirsten Dunst is in the end. The actor is very actor.
Like very actor for like 90s.
Like, did you believe my performance?
Like, you know, that sort of like when it breaks and now everybody's an actor.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, you know, this is presented to us as the Steve Gutenberg movie.
But it's interesting because we're that that is the first mention of Kirsten Dunst, the second lead of it, who really the career at this point of Kirsten Dunst.
Like it's like she was a big star already, I feel like, in making this.
And because interview with the Vampire had already happened, which I just saw for the first time.
It was really entertaining. I really enjoyed it.
She's nominated for Golden Globe already.
And then right after this, she has like she goes like straight to a ton of big old movies, which is sort of hasn't stopped since.
So it's almost like the only lull in Kirsten Dunst's career is this film.
This is the one. This is the valley.
And not to say because, look, it's still it's a job and it's a Disney movie.
Her only Disney movie hasn't done anything.
Hasn't done a Marvel or anything.
But here's what I having just watched interview the Vampire and that she is like doing this great performance against these giant stars.
And I was adding up like everything she did before this before Tower of Terror.
And then I made a list. This is this is a list of the actors who she had worked with.
And these aren't just people who are in the movie.
Also, she had scenes with everybody I'm going to mention.
This is all before the age of 15 when she shoots Tower of Terror.
Tom Hanks, Tom Cruise, Brad Pitt, Robin Williams, George Clooney, Woody Allen and Mia Farrow, Winona Ryder, Susan Sarandon, Kirk Douglas, Nick Nolte.
And months before shooting Tower of Terror, Dustin Hoffman and Robert De Niro in Wag the Dog.
Wow. That that is at 50.
She has exclusively worked with the biggest stars of the century.
That's so bonkers.
That is when you have that all together.
Bring it on. It's just a few years after this.
Yeah. Then she enters this like really good comedy run and then Spider-Man soon after.
I remember being very excited seeing Dick in theaters because there were so many comedy people.
I'm like just a weird 12 or 13 year old just going like it's got Bruce McCullough and Will Ferrell.
I feel like it was heavily promoted in Entertainment Weekly as well.
It was pretty.
I remember you in Entertainment Weekly.
I was in Entertainment Weekly.
Were you as well? EW? Were you an EW kid?
I would look at it at the library sometimes.
Sounds like a no.
Me too. Until I demanded a subscription then yes I would also look at it at the library.
Let's go to the library mom. Straight to like well how's Legends of the Fall doing on the box office?
Well they started doing comic book coverage at some point around 99 or 2000.
And it's like alright we hit the big time and now the big time is like haunted house.
Like you can't escape comic book stuff. It's just the chains we've forged in life.
It's going to destroy the movie industry.
So we have you guys to blame. If you'd kept your mouth shut back then.
No no I was just rooting around in dirty bins in smoke-filled holiday and ballrooms.
Anyway I guess I'm saying that like at this I think maybe she just like had a pocket she needed to fill.
A job came up. Let's do it. But I think already at 15 with that list of credits I think that being in this kind of slow moving Disney light horror movie with Steve Guttenberg.
This is beneath Kirsten Dunst I think. I mean she does an admirable job.
Sure. I mean maybe there was a strategic reason. They were like well Disney we got to get you in at Disney.
I don't know. I'm not sure what the reasoning was but yes when you put them all together like that this definitely seems to be an outlier.
It's like skippable in a Wikipedia.
Yeah. It's a TV movie.
It also.
Yes. Well hey maybe it came with a hole. She had a hole in her schedule. Maybe it came with a trip to Disney World for the family.
Possibly.
Well that's at the time when they used to do stuff like that.
Yeah that's true.
When Disney was nice to the people in their movies. Not like you think about what we gave you and now you want more. You greedy pig.
Speaking of which.
Yeah.
Tower of Terror the movie. The new iteration of this that has been discussed is that I guess is still in the works in theory.
Is it?
I'm trying to tell. It's not not in the works. It hasn't been killed off entirely.
They killed the Taika Star Wars finally I think. He collected his two million dollars to do nothing and then they've canceled it finally.
So he's attached to Tower of Terror.
Yeah I don't think I realized that till this morning.
So I'm just saying.
So are you saying that a Taika attachment means next to nothing?
I'm just perhaps I'm saying that it might not come to fruition.
I think this man when he enters a room he hunkers down and you have my focus. You have my full attention sir. Phones down. Phones off.
Sure.
I will not be Instagramming. I will not be checking emails about the 35 other things I'm attached to that are all the biggest properties in the history of the earth.
Two words.
That I got all of them.
Two words. Stretch Armstrong. Okay.
You write the dollar sign after stretch Armstrongs.
Turn the S's into dollar signs.
Oh yeah.
Anyways they're trying to make more of this but we don't have a lot of details about that. We don't know if it's the same characters. We don't know if.
Is it Buzzy Crocker?
Are we back to Buzzy Crocker?
Yes I don't know.
I'm guessing no but I don't know for sure.
Buzzy Crocker is aggregating like the top ten gardening tools you can get on Amazon. Like he's making those lists.
But now he's getting replaced by AI. Now AI just writes all those articles.
So where is Buzzy? What's Buzzy to do?
What's Buzzy doing?
Does he have to reinvestigate? Or maybe it's a different tower.
It's a retelling of the story I think. So it's not.
We modernize it. It's not. Okay. Okay.
And Jared Leto is Buzzy Crocker.
Because Disney loves him. I mean that's just what they would do.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
He's in every movie that there is.
Yeah. Yeah. And he's going. He's deep diving for his part as Buzzy Crocker by doing what Buzzy Crocker would do and sending Jizz to people in the mail.
Yeah. Yeah. He's sending Jizz for sure.
It's very Buzzy.
That's what Buzzy would do in 2023.
So that's kind of the. So okay. So Christian Dunst is the niece who helps him out with these little charades.
And that's what seems to be happening again with the Tower of Terror.
Because in this world, the Tower of Terror seems to be a big story, one that everybody remembers.
And it's on the Hollywood skyline. But nobody's been there in a long time.
Like nobody's really hanging out in this place.
But it's the same characters as you see in the ride.
It's the same group of five who get stuck in the limbo.
And the little girl, Shirley Temple equivalent, Sally Shine.
We learned that in this universe, this is one of the most notorious deaths ever that has made her a legend ever since.
This is like day the music died. Everybody knows the Sally Shine tale.
So what's my overall point? I don't remember.
This is the it's the universe where this is a big deal.
This is JFK. This is moon landing or whatever.
And but then Buzzy gets a lead that is about like maybe we don't know what actually happened that night.
Right. Yes. So yeah, you would have to think it's like hearing that there was like a conspiracy with the JFK assassination.
It's that level of big deal, which I don't know why Buzzy's getting the scoop.
I feel like it would be a bigger deal, like although, you know, really it's RFK goes on Joe Rogan to talk about that.
Now, RFK Jr. goes on to talk about a JFK conspiracy.
So maybe it is is Buzzy similar to a Joe Rogan now.
Everybody would. I mean, like, you know, Trump would have been talking about the Sally Shine.
Exactly. So yeah, maybe with Sally Shine.
We can't trust them. Yeah.
Yeah. So I like the sister Alex Jones would be Abigail.
Everyone had their eyes on Sally Shine. They should have been watching Abigail.
She was the snake in the grass. OK.
Trump definitely would have been a big Sally Shine movie fan, though, because as we know, Trump loves Sunset Boulevard.
He loves old Hollywood. So enchanting, magical, delight.
The oh, the step, the tapping. Oh, the tapping.
The tapping is it takes you to another world.
We stopped at a gas station when we were out on the campaign trail.
And there at the cash register by the candy bars, there was box of DVDs and they had 20 Sally Shine movies for ten dollars.
And I said, I'm getting this and we're watching them on the plane.
And I love a good deal and 20 movies for 10 bucks.
It's the best deal I ever got. Yep.
And he would quietly, like while the movie was on, turn to a staff and go like, isn't this great?
Isn't this wonderful?
Sir, things are escalating with Putin. I think we should.
This is only the sixth, the sixth Sally Shine movie of the day.
She's got a big lollipop. Don't bother me to wear it.
Movie 11. Look at, she's got a bigger lollipop now.
In this one, she dances with a big tuna.
Giant tuna, the biggest you've ever seen. I got a bigger one.
Look at the ringlets. They're so adorable.
The red tried to get Ivanka to do the ringlets.
So this old lady approaches. Why does this happen?
I honestly, I know the old lady's there.
It reminded me of Titanic in a way, but I don't remember.
She wants to tell, she says I was there I believe.
Or she at least conveys that.
She knows, oh wait a minute, yes.
She knows that there was foul play with the elevator.
She says no one will believe me.
No one will believe me. She says she had read all of Buzzy's stories about the supernatural and aliens and stuff.
And she's like, you write about this stuff. You'll believe me.
Which is eventually I think kind of revealed to be a ruse.
She's fooling us, she's fooling everyone.
Of course it absolutely is a ruse.
It's a classic are you afraid of the dark tactic.
Spoiler alert.
This is the woman who did it. She made the accident happen.
Another are you afraid of the dark tactic.
If you think about it a lot, it's very unsettling.
As a kid I was like this is really intense.
It's an are you afraid of the dark where it's like one piece of information that was omitted has caused something awful to happen.
And now you'll live with regret for the rest of your life.
I'm trying to think of an example. I can't think of one off the top of my head.
But it feels very are you afraid of the dark where if only you knew that this is what the person thought or said.
And then decades go by and life decisions are made based on missing information.
And it's like if you only knew one little thing then everything would have been different.
But in the end.
I'm not a source of anxiety.
Are you saying that you were as a kid were just worried they were going to be...
I know everything because if I miss something I might send me down this other path.
If I don't say goodbye to them now, them or me could die without having said see ya.
I mean that's that's that would be a bummer.
That's just needless to say. But it wouldn't be quite as bad as like causing the death of a bunch of people.
Yeah. Other people get caught up in this. Yeah.
Nothing to do with maybe this is a good time to talk about the the people who we're dealing with.
Sally Shine has been mentioned.
Her nanny, Emmaline Partridge, she is blamed for what happened that she put a this nanny.
This Hollywood 30s caretaker somehow could put a curse on the girl and the elevator,
which caused it to whatever to free fall and they're locked in limbo.
Whatever you consider black magic, they say a couple of times.
Wow. OK. This nanny did black magic and that's Emmaline Partridge.
So and now we recognize them from the ride.
It's all I what I was trying to remember is I mean I watched the pre-ride video again.
None of these names are said. They're just kind of archetypes you get from afar.
And I don't know if Imagineering had the names and then they gifted the names to the makers of the film
or if the film invented the if all of the mythology of the five characters from the ride was invented by DJ McHale.
I do. Do we know? Do you know? Hmm. I don't think I know.
So maybe we're getting all these names from this.
But now when you go on the Tower of Terror, Florida and France only, you can, you know,
if you have if you're with somebody who is nervous, a partner, a family member,
nervous about the upcoming drops, you can distract them by saying, I know all of these characters names.
It's Caroline Crossan and Gilbert London and Sally Shine and Emmaline Partridge and Dewey Todd.
Maybe that will confuse them enough to put them in these.
Yeah, at least they know the put a name to their face. Yeah, yeah.
We don't like going on rides and not knowing every single thing that can be known.
Well, that's nothing can be a mystery. So now it isn't with this. Great.
The other thing about the Guardians Tower is you know all the names. You know, I'm coming in.
You don't have to learn all that, except for me, who's never seen the movies.
But they say their names. They do say their name with like light up signs. So that that does.
That does. Tanelier Tavon. Tanelier Tavon.
Caroline Crossan is the glamorous actress singer, boyfriend actor Gilbert London,
and then a bellhop named Dewey Todd.
I guess all I could think of with Dewey Todd was Jason.
Do you feel like this is a part that you would like to play if you were?
Tread lightly. Yeah, no, I well, I could not get over with the Dewey Todd thing.
The Dewey Todd thing. Then eventually we meet the caretaker of the hotel.
Yes. Who is just keeping it from falling down and paying the taxes.
And it says it's his grandson. Which leads us to believe that like, was Dewey Todd married?
Dewey Todd. He had a child. Yes, he would have had to. Yeah, Dewey Todd.
You think a bellhop can't be married? Yeah, what do you mean?
You don't think a bellhop fucks? He was kind of, I couldn't place his age.
I guess adult, but he was very like, all shucks. Yeah, could be 20, could be 70, I don't know.
Yeah. Oh, imagine looking down the end of your bed there and seeing a little bellhop hat popping up and down.
And he's got the bell too. You have the bell. All finished.
You have the bell. Let me know if you need anything else. The lady has the bell, yeah.
Yes, what do you need? How can I help? Ding ding. Dewey Todd here at your service. What do you need? Where do you want me to go?
You just hit it faster when you want him to go faster. Just point to a body part and I'll be there. Ding ding ding ding ding.
Then you slow it down. Efficient service as always from me, Dewey Todd. Tips the cap.
There's no mention of Dewey Todd is solely obsessed with proving he's not a doofus to his father, who is the owner of the hotel.
Seemingly. Yeah. Sure, I remember that. Everything what you just said. Yes, the father. Of course I do.
When they're at the party at the end. That and proving to the people that he was stuck in limbo with, like, I didn't do this. This wasn't me. I didn't fuck up.
And I fuck. And I fuck. Also, I'm pretty sure, I think my, we were trying to conceive, I don't know if it happened.
I'm left in the limbo and I don't know if I had a kid or after that a grand kid. I left a widow and a new child.
Well, that's true hell. That's amazing. He has such a chipper attitude. Yeah, really. Given that.
But yes, the connection here becomes, okay, like, so nobody knows what's going on at this hotel, but there is somebody working there, just kind of a caretaker.
And that's Dewey Todd's grandson. The grand, somehow the grandson of the bellhop ended up owning the hotel or not owning it, but he's there.
He could own it, I think is what, right? He could. Yeah.
I think, spoiler, it is what happens. But that's the character who he has got another name, but they only call him Q.
Yes. The quartermaster. Q, where is he? What's the guy's name? Michael McShane. There it is. I got it.
Yes. Now here's Michael McShane. You were, Jason, before we started recording, you listed some of this man's credits.
British Hose Line. British Hose Line. My, like him, or my favorite role of his guys is Professor Keen Bean from the Richie Rich movie.
Oh, yeah. From part one, Not Christmas Wish with David Gallagher.
I don't know if he's in Chris, I don't think he is, but I could be wrong. He's in a lot of stuff.
He's a guy who just pops up in things, especially in the 90s. Yeah. And like I have a lot of affection for him when I see him.
So when he popped up in this, I went, hey, Keen Bean. Keen Bean. And he's also, he's on, he's FDR on Seinfeld.
Franklin Delano Romanowski. Oh, right. Okay. Kramer and Newman's friend. Oh, yeah. They're playing risk, I believe, against him. Yeah.
And he's got, he just pops up in a lot of things. Office space. Office space, yes. He's the hypnotherapist who has a heart attack.
And then Ron Livingston is stuck in the like vibing state. Yes. So he's in a lot of stuff. Wait a minute.
In Rich, I thought this was right, but I didn't want to vocalize it. In Richie Rich's Christmas Wish, Professor Keen Bean is played by Eugene Levy.
Wow, really? What do you mean? Like they cast way up. Yeah, that's not what usually happens.
For no offense to McShane, but you know, like Levy's a star. How does that part? Yeah, how do they? Plus up.
Well, is everybody else, like who else is in it? Apparently Marla Maples. Really? Trump's ex. Oh, I know exactly who Marla Maples is.
Tiffany's mom. That's weird. As Mrs. Van Doe. Mr. Van Doe is Richard Fancy. Oh, that's Mr. Lipman. Wow, another Seinfeld.
Who plays Cadbury in Richie Rich's Christmas Wish? The Butler. The Butler. Keen Curtis might be the same.
Is it the same guy? Wait, no, I don't think it is. That's the guy, because the guy from Jumanji plays Cadbury in Richie Rich.
From Kirsten Dunst in Jumanji. Yeah. I'm wondering if they did a total recast of everybody.
Like, so they failed to lock everybody down for Christmas Wish? I guess. Straight to video a few years later?
I don't think anyone recurred unless Leslie Ann Warren was in the, I don't remember who his parents were.
There's a really funny, so Professor Keen Bean is like Richie Rich's Q from James Bond. He's like the inventor and he gives Richie Rich all these weapons basically.
Oh yes, which come into play. I remember that being one of those movies where I'm loving the first hour as a kid and then it just becomes this scary, it becomes about blasting lasers at the Mount Rushmore being built of the riches.
Yeah, and it's very stressful. I've said this before, that I liked the Lassie movie from the 90s because there was no climax at all.
Because I remember going, here comes the scare, here comes the intense part, and then the movie just ended and I went, oh good, everything's fine.
Okay, great. Richie Rich, yeah, I remember going, when they're showing the mansion and he's got the McDonald's in there.
I think if anyone has positive feelings about the movie, it is entirely from the McDonald's scene.
Yeah, there's a McDonald's in the mansion.
And there's a roller coaster. We only like roller coaster and McDonald's.
I mean those were the only things I liked as a kid. Not going on roller coasters, seeing them. Too scared to go on them.
There's a joke, I mean I laughed at this and he's in the room, the professor's room and he's showing off all this stuff.
And the professor gives him a bulletproof outfit or some crazy shit.
And then he yells at one of his assistants, his child assistant, she's just shooting a machine gun at this suit.
I'm like, what is this movie? I don't remember this.
That was like a go-to I feel like when you had a Q type character.
Oh sure, yeah.
This is bulletproof and they unload a machine gun in it.
It's like, see I'm not lying.
But this was a child's movie.
Oh yeah, sure. Blank check too I feel like.
Unloaded a machine gun at some point.
Well no, no, just in terms of stressful. Blank check the movie, not the podcast.
Similar to Richie Rich where it's like at a certain point I'm like, man this kid is having a lot of fun.
And then the bad guy, I'm like, is he gonna kill that kid?
Yeah, there's real danger, yes. And the FBI is involved.
All these era movies, like Dennis the Menace, I just remember the last.
Oh yeah, Christopher Lloyd is genuinely really scary.
He does not play that fun.
And he's like, yeah, like killing.
Gonna cut ya!
He's gonna kill Dennis the Menace at the end of the last 30 minutes and I'm like, I do not like this. This is scaring me.
See, this is one of my favorite movies from when we were kids, Camp Nowhere.
The stakes are very low of like, oh no, we might have to go home early this summer.
That's not as scary.
It's not as scary.
And I was less scared I'd say by animated peril.
Beast has fallen to his death, I don't care. I know it's all pretend.
But real actors.
And then like, you know, and just, you know, really what it was with Christopher Lloyd and that was like too unshaven.
I was so uncomfortable with his amount of shaving.
I hear ya.
Either clean shaven or not. Full beard, the in-between scared me as a kid.
I think his teeth and his unshavenness is unkempt. He was unkempt.
Yeah.
And not in a fun Doc Brown way, who is also unkempt but not in the same way.
Yes, or a fun, who's the taxi character?
Jim Magnatowski.
Yeah, yeah.
He was also unkempt in a different way.
Yes, but unkempt for kids, we don't like unkempt for kids.
Not unkempt for kids.
No one comes around.
Faster, very, Kempt.
These Hollywood sickos are putting on Kempts in front of our kids.
Right. Sebastian Jackal, very Kempt.
Yes, yeah. He cleans up nice.
Christopher Lloyd can be very Kempt when he wants to be.
Absolutely.
They put that coat on the hanger between takes, you know.
Yeah, they have the steamer.
Yes, get all the hair off, all the dust.
Okay, so now, Buzzy.
I had the least feel like explaining the plot of the movie.
No, I know, and we're like so early.
We're so early in it, too.
Well, we could blast, you know, whatever.
Okay, so we're poking around this hotel and Buzzy assumes he's just going to do his old stuff.
He's going to dress up his niece and take fake photos.
It's a strange relationship in general.
Yeah, I know.
There's something uncomfortable about it.
Here, put this on. We'll lie to them all.
Yeah.
But then he's hiring actresses to be the ghosts in his little fake photo play.
And then this mysterious actress shows up named Claire Poulet.
Yeah.
And she has kind of a strange air about her.
And if you're smart at all, you're like ghost, ghost, ghost.
She doesn't, she's not loved this era or time.
And she's lit different.
And this is a ghost.
This is a ghost.
Yeah, she's in an old dress.
It's Melora Harden later of The Office.
And previously of the weird pilot that I love, Shangri-La Plaza, the musical about a strip mall.
I know I mentioned it on the show because then I was interviewed for an article about it.
Oh, wow.
So that proves that I mentioned it on the show.
That article exists somewhere.
Oh, Melora Harden, I didn't, I.
She's in The Rocketeer.
Oh, right.
Yes.
And I either I knew or I forgot the trivia that she was supposed to be Jennifer in Back to the Future.
Oh.
Was cast even.
You have the part.
Let's even take some promotional photos.
And great.
Well, we're going to get filming all of our scenes with Eric Stoltz.
So we'll see you in six weeks.
We'll be ready for you then.
Then things change.
They don't work out and they have to call her and say, we have recast and we have this new actor.
He is shorter and we don't we just frankly don't believe a short man and a tall woman and she was recast.
Yep.
Jason thoughts.
I don't care for it.
Sympathies to Michael J.
Fox, I guess.
Yeah.
Will listener, would anyone believe a tall girl and a short guy?
What a strange.
This was before Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman.
Which I feel like maybe a long way into making that like, OK, great.
As America, we're comfortable with it.
Seeing such a normal, acceptable couple.
Two normal folks.
A non-strange couple.
Two normal folks being together with a little height difference.
And everything was fine from then on out.
America's sweethearts.
But not Back to the Future.
So anyway, she shows up.
She's kind of the conduit to the all of the ghosts beginning to appear.
And as soon as she shows up, weird stuff starts happening.
Green lights and a headless butler who sits up.
And now, OK, we're starting to cook here a little bit.
And then it leads to this really unsettling thing where the elevator doors open and there's pure flame behind them.
And then that nanny who we're at the moment suspecting is there or just no is the bad guy.
She's saying, you're a bad girl.
You're a bad, bad girl.
As the flames of hell appear behind Kirsten Dunst.
That's genuinely upsetting.
Yeah.
But then once they actually talk to the ghosts, they realize they don't know the whole story.
There's a lot.
There's very quick acceptance of ghosts.
There's ghosts here.
OK, well, let's have a conversation with them.
Not a ton of like, Jesus Christ, like crying for a while and like, no, it's OK.
We're ghosts like dealing with like everything we thought we knew about the earth is.
Well, yeah, dealing with that and then just being like, oh, so that opens up a world to like my whole family.
Like I can talk to them maybe in some ways and they're somewhere else.
And what do I think about religion now?
Like there needs to be many, many scenes of Steve Gutenberg coming to all of these realizations.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
And yeah, yeah, pure, pure weeping, breaking, breaking down, not even speaking English anymore.
He feels so insane.
The interstellar scene of Matthew McConaughey crying, like seeing his daughter or something with Steve Gutenberg in the Tower of Terror movie.
And perhaps going to the top of the tower and ending his own life.
Right.
Possibly.
I mean, so you could you blame him so freaked out as he by everything he's discovered.
This would be very overwhelming all at once.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To deal with.
Do what you got to do, Steve.
But instead he's just kind of like, well, I could prove that there's ghosts.
And I the whole time I was real.
I was like, what am I lacking in Gutenberg?
He's not bad.
But much like Eisner earlier, there is just not the presence.
There's no you really just in a movie like this, you really lean on where you know there's not going to be a lot of effects to make the spooky stuff happen.
They don't have the biggest budget for that.
So really, you just need an actor who you know is going to be really compelling making faces and going.
And he's just not at all.
He I don't feel like he's ever scared.
He seems like maybe five percent concerned at times.
Yes, he's really there.
He's even the whole kind of movie.
Yeah.
Like Eddie Murphy Haunted Mansion doesn't work, but you could tell that they're teasing it.
The trailer was just basically there's a teaser that was just like him going.
Well, at least there's the Eddie Murphy will be interesting to look at as he screams and is scared.
Yes.
And there's Steve Gutenberg just frankly is not the I even these movies are not as good as the Don Knotts, the Ghost of Mr.
Chicken movie.
I'm going to take your word for that.
But yes, it's an old of you.
You've heard of this movie, though.
I think so.
Don Knotts is like a very believe it or not, a timid kind of guy.
And he has to spend the night in a haunted house.
And boy, imagine Don Knotts selling being scared.
He did it all the time.
These guys aren't doing anything close to that.
Gutenberg is just, yeah, goes OK.
Don Knotts made a meal out of being alone, being scared.
He looked like a living like the Haunted Mansion ghost that pop up with like locked in ghoulish like, whoa, that's just what Don Knotts looked like all the time.
That's true.
So it was a natural thing for him.
Perma scared animatronic.
Do you think they based the shaky need groundskeeper on Don Knotts?
I kind of looks like Don Knotts, doesn't he?
I think Don Knotts influenced scared characters for decades.
And I feel like is there any better scared guy on TV than him?
I can't think of one off the top of my head of somebody who like watching be scared or nervous.
His whole character was as I maybe talked about on this show before he developed a character called like Nervous Man before Andy Griffith show.
OK.
So like he came in with like I'm the perfect guy to be nervous.
So like that's how that's how he made his career basically.
So but I'm just like, do you have any influence on you?
Either of you in that way?
He is perpetually nervous.
I'm sure he did because we watched the end of Griffith show all the time was a child and he was my favorite kid.
Like what kid wouldn't like him the best, I guess, if all made nervousness acceptable.
Right.
It's a lot of care.
I mean, Jim neighbors certainly was influential, but not as much as Don Knotts.
Don Knotts, I don't think.
But Don Knotts Haunted Mansion from the old days would have been awesome, I bet.
Well, they should have cranked it out.
They should have gotten that movie going.
Absolutely.
He was already in like Disney stuff.
That movie should have come out in 1971.
Yes.
Starring Dean Jones and who was the one actress they liked?
Suzanne, Suzanne Bouchette.
Yes, Suzanne Bouchette's in there.
Yeah.
And Don Knotts.
Film it in the ride.
And it's still bad, but it's better than this stuff.
Yeah.
There's something to it.
Yes.
There's an aesthetic we like.
I'd say so.
You know what I was comparing this movie to the whole time was the recent film before this
came out, Casper.
Casper, I think a movie that works pretty well and that kind of sticks with everybody.
And that's like a haunted, that's a guy and a younger girl in a haunted house.
And that's modern and we don't care that it's modern.
The modernness doesn't bother because it's all kind of a magical reality.
It's in the worlds.
Yeah.
And when you compare Pullman to Pullman just has like, he's like kind of an odd, ticky
David Lynch actor.
He's a weird actor.
So you plop him in a family movie and that's going to round him out a little, but he'll
naturally bring odd tickiness to it.
Yes.
And that's where I think Gutenberg is not the right.
They needed somebody with like a little darkness for this to work a little better.
Yes.
And I think with a recast, I think this might end up closer to the lane of like a Hocus
Pocus that we, you know, what's not bad is that Tower of Terror.
I watched that every Halloween.
I think you get maybe like, and I don't know who did the cinematographer.
You get like a different cinematographer.
The day has to be, it should just all be at night also.
Never day.
Yes.
Different cinematographer all night and then kind of a weirder leading guy.
Yeah.
Cause Kirsten Dunst and in Casper, Christina Ricci.
Both good.
Both.
Yeah.
Really fun.
I couldn't figure out who.
I was trying to think who's, who's gettable in this era who's a little creepy and maybe
he, I think this is too far.
Although, Hey, look, I would never complain about seeing this person.
Crispin Glover.
Crispin Glover is the dad.
Oh my God.
Put him in a family movie.
He's good.
It legit good in like Mike, the movie where a little Bow Wow finds the magic shoes so
he could play basketball and he's an evil orphanage owner in it.
But that's scary.
I guess maybe he can't be like the dad.
He's pretty scary.
He's too, yes.
You know, the only time he works for family movies, I guess, is he's still a villain.
Yeah.
He's good for sure.
But yeah, that's like 97.
But he wasn't scary in Back to the Future.
Other than just being genuinely, generally.
Yeah.
He's very unnerving.
Uh huh.
But I feel like that might be too unnerving for your lead guy because Pullman is the perfect
example of like kind of weird guy.
But I still as a kid liked him.
Yes.
I was still like, oh good.
It's Bill Pullman.
I feel, I feel good about this.
But yeah, is there another TV guy?
I'm trying to think of anyone was like Brent Spiner.
Oh my God, please.
Brent Spiner.
Jonathan Frakes.
Frakes.
Frakes though is too little too smooth.
I think you want a little bit more of like a dark darkness in there.
Frakes is such a.
So there's an investigation to be done at the Tower of Terror.
He's a little too.
Hi, I'm Mike Laughlin.
Sure.
That's close.
You've just been in also a villain part, but Flintstones.
He works in a family movie, but then you can like, you know, he's the dad in Inside Out.
And that's, there's no malice or weird.
Actually, I think that that might be right.
He's got like a, you know, a clean, trustworthy face.
Uh, and I, yeah, he can be a dad in a Disney TV movie.
That's not a bad idea at all.
That's not bad.
Yeah.
But then he would just be, there'd be something odd about it.
More so just Gutenberg is just too, too vanilla.
Yeah, I think, yeah, I think that's, I get why they were like, he's a friendly family,
friendly guy, but yeah, for this movie.
But you know who had it out for him at ABC?
Bobby Iger.
For Gutenberg?
No, for McLaughlin.
Iger canceled Twin Peaks.
Oh.
So you think he, you think based on that, that he was, he specifically had about the ass?
He was in that weird thing.
No, no, no, not on my, yeah, maybe they, well, Iger was there.
Yeah, maybe they had him.
Maybe he was, they were about to shoot and he said, pull him.
I'll call Gutenberg.
I know him.
I have one last suggestion for this.
Eisner plays the dad.
It was right there.
It was there the whole time.
He'd be, he'd be a little odd.
Hello, I'm Buzzy Crocker.
My name's Buzzy Crocker.
I work for the Inquisitor.
You may know me from my article about Wolf Boy.
Now I'm here to investigate the matter of a different kind.
Go.
Take some photos of my niece.
For the periodical I work for.
Don't cut her head off.
Oh my God.
You're a bunch of ghosts.
Ghosts are real.
You know, again, again, you know, I come back to like, if he was the golfer, how brief is that?
What does that give us?
What does that actually do for us?
But as opposed to imagining if he is the star, if he had to take six weeks to play a character named Buzzy.
All right, when's lunch?
I have to do all of my CEO work.
Did he?
We're losing light.
We're going to do half an hour.
Okay, that'll be half an hour.
Shit, shit, shit.
Okay.
And I don't remember my lines.
Where are my lines with?
What do I say to Sally in the next scene?
I swear.
Give me an earpiece.
Or no, he does the Godfather Marlon Brando.
We're like, write the lines on a PA shirt and I'll read them off of that.
Put them on a billboard outside the window.
I'll just, I'll do it one take.
Did he, do you think Michael Eisner, he started, I think he felt like he was the star.
I think he felt like he had to do, and maybe this isn't in one of his books, he felt like he had to do those intros to give it a Disney of another face, a warm face, friendly guy, like Walt did.
But then at a certain point, did he regret that choice and then just felt like he had to keep doing these intros?
Because it seems like he was cranky when he was doing them.
So it wasn't, I think he liked it on some level, but I wonder if he regretted the precedent.
Just in terms of like how many they're going to need.
Because that's what you're saying.
There's so many, more than I even imagined.
And what's the minimum time this could all take, you know?
One hour?
Yeah, I'd say so.
If they're like lit, ready to go, then maybe they could do it pretty fast.
Right.
But, you know, some of them are in weird, some of them he has to be in Florida for or somewhere weird.
They had to build a little set and light it.
You know, there was a little lighting gag to make it look like he was on the elevator.
Right. And Iger abandons this immediately.
Like he doesn't, he never did one of these.
No.
As far as I know.
It's why we should have known back then.
Unwillingness to host.
We should have known.
Don't trust this guy.
That has to be number one if you're the Disney CEO.
Yeah, it's got to be you.
And if Tim Cook buys Disney, he's going to have to do these intros again.
That's the only way I will accept it.
The only way he regains our trust.
You know, I don't know if I can see myself buying another of his products unless he hosts the show.
Or unless my current ones break and then I have to and will buy the products.
Well, that's a good point.
Due to their wretched monthly warranties.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Constantly.
Due to them wearing down very readily.
Okay.
I mean, really, we should have just amended this.
We should also have taken matters into our hands and just added, you know, listeners suggested Tower of Terror, the movie with Steve Guttenberg, we should have just added intro.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We've only done that.
Yes.
But whatever.
We're fitting that within this broader episode.
Ghosts are sitting around.
We soon realize that Abigail, the old lady who gave Buzzy the tip, is Sally Shine's sister.
And we realize that she's been in a sanitarium for a long time.
A real movie sanitarium where you're going across the lawn and there's like 10 people of various Ilks all speaking to unseen people or doing somersaults.
Or walking upside down.
Yeah, not how you would portray it.
You would not portray it like this these days.
I think.
At least they get the lawn.
The lawn's nice.
The lawn is nice.
The grass is nice.
And the actual reporter does some actual investigation.
Yeah, Neopiepels comes through and does what Buzzy cannot do.
And finds in the lid of a steamer trunk a bunch of scrawled on Sally Shine like headshots and a doll with a head ripped off.
My favorite way to quickly communicate that she's mad at Sally Shine was like a black and white photo with the word bad scrawled on it in like jagged red lettering.
She makes me frown.
Yeah, it's very broad strokes.
But at the same time, I didn't see it at the time.
I didn't know in the moment it was going to be her.
And the nanny is so loving.
She would never.
The ghosts are, there's no divisions between the ghosts.
The ghosts all love each other.
Honestly, their limbo hell doesn't seem that bad.
You got a hotel to wander around.
Like we were saying earlier, like it's, you know, old creepy records to play.
They're all buddies.
Aside from Dewey not getting to see his family.
I missed this fact also.
This is a bizarre tiny Wikipedia fact that Dewey Todd appears in other media also made by director DJ McKay.
Right.
Because DJ McKay wrote a book or a book series with many young adult book series with many entries called the Pendragon series.
Yes.
And Dewey Todd appears in The Neverwar.
So for those of you out there who are craving more Dewey Todd from this film, check out The Neverwar.
OK.
If you're Dewey Todd, fix doesn't require seeing him.
If you're just reading about him in his essence, does it?
For November Club 3, if you want Jason to read The Neverwar and report back to us, please vote for it.
Jason, Jason, the reader is always open to reading whatever long story.
No, I'm a slow reader.
Make sure you specify it's Jason only reading it and he's giving us a book report.
Jason reads The Neverwar while Mike and Scott proceed with their lives.
Uh-huh.
Viable option.
So I'm not saying it's happening, it's just if the listeners want it.
They have to pick it, yeah.
They have to pick The Neverwar for Jason.
Oh no.
You're allowed to throw an idea just for me.
Jason's making a big scared face just like Steve Gutenberg's not doing.
If you can pitch something that I forced for just me to do, then you can do it right now.
The forum is yours.
I mean, let's sit here for a while and think about it.
You have to read one of those.
Did you have like the stories of love?
You had one of those Barnes and Noble, like all the Lovecraft stories.
H.P. Lovecraft, yeah, yeah.
You had to read that cover to cover.
Which we need to, so we got to pick one of those.
So it's either you want Jason War, The Neverwar, or I have to read H.P. Lovecraft.
Thousands of pages of the driest, slowest.
I suppose you punished me more there, but to me The Neverwar by the Are You Afraid.
Well, it's still, look, it's their poll.
So I guess they can do it if they want.
If they want to hear, then we'll have to be a six and a half hour episode in which we mostly don't participate.
Right.
We just sit here and drift in and out of sleep while Mike reads a Lovecraft synopsis.
I just list to you the longitude and latitude of where the characters were at in the Mountains of Madness or whatever.
Oh, yeah.
Which is what is by far most of it.
The agonies.
Explaining exactly where they were in this fake scenario, in this made up scenario.
The ghosts all, by the way, the ghosts in order to free their spirits, they need to get to the party.
They never got to go to the party.
So they tell us that that only by going to the party do we set our spirits free.
We've tried the stairs, but we can't get past 11.
So they need to make it to the Tip Top Club.
The Tip Top Club.
The party is heaven.
Yeah, I guess so.
The party in this is heaven.
Yeah.
And dying in an elevator is hell.
Exactly.
So the party seems fun.
And I guess this is maybe to me proving the existence of the Christianity in general.
So you didn't believe in Christian God until watching Tower of Terror, the movie.
And now it makes sense to me.
I didn't understand heaven until it was a 40s party.
Well, then another good assignment.
Mike reads the Bible.
All of it?
Which one?
Oh, no.
Okay.
So we'll record that.
There just won't be any Club 3s for the next 14 months.
You've got to wait for that one.
Something maybe to get us off of seeing the plot, which, boy, am I tired of doing.
We haven't talked about this.
When it cuts to the tower, to the tower itself, we see some shots that are clearly of the ride.
It can only be the ride in Florida was the only one that existed at that time.
I don't believe anything else in the movie is filmed in the ride.
I saw something that said there was some lobby shots.
Maybe.
But even that, wouldn't you?
I'm just thinking of claustrophobia.
It's small, yes.
And I think maybe you're better off just like, you can make a new set where then you've got room to light it.
I mean, certainly all the grounds of the hotel.
And also, if you're going and filming in the lobby, now we're bringing at least to at least Gutenberg Dunst.
And maybe we're having to bring ghosts.
Now we're finding all these actors for a whole Florida shoot as opposed to, my guess, what they did is get one camera guy, perhaps already on the property, perhaps a cameraman for the Mickey Mouse Club or whatever.
Can you just go film 10 shots of the Tower of Dare?
Do one that tilts over and do some nights.
Yeah, you know what?
We're going to need some night ones.
So 10 shots, please send them to us.
And that is all of our Florida shoots.
Yeah, I mean, maybe it's just like strategic shots of the lobby somehow.
I don't know.
Maybe this is also wrong.
It could be like establishing.
I just don't think they brought those actors to Florida.
That would have cost them money.
That would have cost them to end up in park tickets.
I saw really tight shots in front of the gates with a car.
And I was like, did they build the gate and they can't make this shot any wider?
I think you also see it's a back lot.
You never tilt up.
It's all. Everything is framed for a movie about a tower.
Boy, do we not see much of that tower unless the tower doesn't have the actors in the shot.
Yes, I think everything is oddly.
Everything's clipped.
Uh huh.
Yeah, yeah.
That's a lot.
You know, it's how I can only imagine how low the budget of this was.
That's how you do it.
And I like that they use the real tower.
They didn't do some CGI crap and make, you know, you got to give this movie this.
It looks like the ride because they pointed a camera at the ride.
This has been a big issue with a bunch of other ride movies.
Just make it look like the ride.
What are you doing?
Yes. So that they actually did that, which is usually not happening in this.
Uh, sadly, I don't know why I had to look it up just now, but I really wish they had just shot it all there.
And it was in 1999 because then they could have gone next door to the rock and roller coaster.
Or at least sort of it's been a big guitar.
You could have dressed up to look like something else.
You'd be like, well, the guitar store is next door or something like you could have explained it away for some reason.
This is like, I mean, I'm almost like I feel like I got my eyes out the door.
I'd like to just end talking about this for as long as we want.
It begs the question. Rock and roller coaster, the movie.
Yeah, of course.
So that I guess it just has to still it's still Therosmith and they're they're acting.
Getting to see made in the 90s, every step of that getting to see like arriving at the session,
maybe the moment where they all hired Ileana Douglas.
We feel good about this. Just don't cramp our rock and roll lifestyle.
As soon as this becomes us having to go, go to this appointment, that meeting, then that then then that's not rock and roll, baby.
Wow. Yes.
So I want to know how they met.
I think that, yeah, I think you have to probably combine it has to maybe be an Aerosmith origin story in some ways, too.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Because the recording Walk This Way in the session, which doesn't make any sense.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because it's the open in 1999 and it's not a new version of what they have rerecorded Walk This Way.
Walk This Way, Aerosmith version.
Yes.
Steven's version.
A young Scooter Braun stole the copy to the original.
Well, if you go a step further from the rock and roller coaster, you get to the Fairfax market with the big hot dogs.
So this is really talk about that movie, too.
Yeah, that potential movie.
Jason is Jason is vetoed Rock and Roller Coaster.
He wants big hot dog.
The big hot dogs for years.
They've had big hot dogs there.
Do they still have them?
Yeah.
OK. Well, hopefully that won't go away either.
Well, we don't know Rock and Roller Coaster still around.
Yeah.
Sure.
No talk yet of it going away.
Sorry. The other moment, I think you want to see like the first gig and where like nobody's there, but there's one guy nodding along.
Right.
And like he really keeps their spirits alive and he comes up and meets them after.
And, you know, I just want you to know that concert meant the world to me and just whatever.
You know, if you're doubting that you made a connection here, you really just consider me your fan so that that becomes the origin of you know how we feel about our fans.
Oh, good.
That's really where that feel like.
Then he walks away and then Stevens, you know, Joe, that guy gave me a really good feeling.
I guess you could say I have a good feeling about our fans.
Wow. That's perfect because that's a great Han Solo moment.
Yeah, yes.
Uh huh.
This is what Iger likes.
So he's going to want to.
Yeah, let's put that together too.
How about the scene where Stephen walks this way?
The first time he walks this way.
And then they think, oh, Eureka.
They say Eureka.
And they say Eureka a lot during the movie.
Well, and they can have a little interlude in this movie with the next door neighbor for Rockin' Rollercoaster, Lightning McQueen's Racing Academy.
Well, we're jumping arrows here.
I know, but it's.
We're talking and you're over there looking something up.
What's it going to be?
I was confirming that the name in my head, Lightning McQueen's Racing Academy, a place I've never been to.
Did you just say Lightning McQueen?
Lightning McQueen, which would be a good name for like a treat or the porn parody.
Or when he comes.
Ka-chow. Ka-chow. Ka-chow. Ka-chow.
You can get that in Fairfax Market too.
There's lots of different little stands.
Lightning McQueen donut.
Yeah.
Yeah, so yeah, that would.
I think that would have been a more exciting movie to talk about.
Did you see Stephen Taylor broke his larynx?
His vocal cords are gnarled.
You can break a larynx?
He's twisted and bleeding and then it was revealed he broke his larynx.
So now he's like as month, the tour has to be like postponed.
It's never going to happen for him.
I guess it's never going to happen.
So.
And along with this, his character is being assailed.
Well, that's another story.
This, I refuse to look at this man and think that he ever did anything wrong.
Stephen Tyler did something wrong, illegal, unethical.
One of our great song smiths about underage sex.
Yes, that's right.
Stephen Tyler, a great man.
A good man.
Let's all be on the record as much as possible.
What are we, what are we, oh.
I mean like, alright, the old lady did, the old lady starts like doing a hex.
Yeah, they all.
I like this because we've been walking through empty courtyards a lot.
And now like, oh, now we're surrounded by candles and old lady's a witch and she's casting a spell.
Here we go.
We're doing okay here.
There's not a lot of speediness in like once they figure it out, they just kind of go about their business and they just let her like get all set up and go about her business.
Yeah, it's.
Because Buzzy, the real reporter is X is like, come on, Buzzy, we got to write this story.
And that.
Right.
Side track.
Everything gets, you know, delayed.
They, you know, you got to go deal with the real ghost stuff.
The actual story of the Tower of Terror doesn't quite make sense as a Twilight Zone morality play.
Yes.
But it is in the vein of like, well, the universe is doing this to these people because of some reason.
That's sort of, that's the Twilight Zone generally is like the universe is punishing some somebody for something.
Like a way that they are.
Yeah.
But in this case, it's like a little girl and a nanny who we've now learned is nice.
Right. So they have to make up the actual, I guess, more practical reasons why this has happened.
And it's a witch.
It's a witch.
Well, I guess it was a witch again.
Like per usual here on the Twilight Zone.
The true twist is that Sally Shine's sister did all the black magic.
Abigail did all the black magic.
But in a twist of fate, the party everyone was going to was a surprise party for her.
Yes.
Well, that's somehow 300 Hollywood stars and band members were all gathered for a party for the Tip Top Club for another little girl.
Yeah. The Tip Top Club was apparently a Chuck E. Cheese of its day for kids parties.
They made the best martinis and adrenochrome shakes around.
I was going to say on that note, it was getting to a point in this movie where I realized that a bunch of bad shit is going down.
Basically, what we've here's what's been uncovered in this movie that a Hollywood tower is a secret hub of satanic rituals and child abuse.
Yeah.
And only one man can stop it and his name is Q.
Very good point.
This whole like I don't know why QAnon has taken all its cues from what's that movie White Squall?
That's where the phrase comes from. That has nothing to do where they say this phrase that in the trailer it's not even in the movie.
Right.
So I think that it was all actually everything they need to know is has been in Tower of Terror 97 the whole time.
QAnon should adopt the new they should adopt the tagline of the movie, which is hotel guests check in but they don't check out.
That should be on signs of Trump rallies from now on.
A little more.
HGCI, BTD, CAO.
Okay.
A little more cumbersome than next time take the stairs.
You know for simplicity.
Yeah.
That is some well next time take the stairs could apply to like you know if you can't find if you go to a pizza restaurant you can't find an underground sex cabal in the basement maybe you didn't look hard enough for the stairs.
Next time take the stairs.
Yeah.
You'll find Tom Hanks and Oprah in there.
You'll find all everybody Kristen Dunst made movies with in the 90s all together getting Adrena Chromat at kids.
Yeah.
Luckily this is behind the paywall or if it was main feed I think it would actually this would trickle down.
To the real trickle over to the real QB poll.
Like they'd hear this.
Yeah.
This is new podcast I've been checking out and they're really on the level.
Although maybe that's a good idea.
First of all they defended Steven Tyler and then secondly.
Yeah.
I'm really on board with everything they're saying.
I.
OK.
So anyway I don't know.
So there's a satanic spell and then the only as we're getting towards the end I'm like the only thing they're like it's this kept for a movie called Tower of Terror.
It's a little dopey and there's not a lot of action in it but then right towards the end they get in like the two cars are stuck up there and you got to hear it hang on.
You got to cross from ear to ear.
Trust me.
And you do get some like scary elevators.
So they fit it in budgetarily.
They did it and this stuff is all this is not an unacceptable run as the climax of Tower of Terror the movie.
Yeah.
And they do start the service elevator like in the ride comes into play a bunch.
They do say service elevator.
Yes.
So that was a good call back.
Well I mean that actually.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
So yeah you get that you get a little.
Yeah you that that is your I'm trying to think like what what before it's seeing this what would I want from a Tower of Terror movie and it would be like a lot of elevator play.
Love in an elevator.
What if you just moved Aerosmith to Tower of Terror and called it love in an elevator.
Like if they're wanting to kick them out.
Yeah yeah yeah.
So rock and roller coaster be themes.
But you move Aerosmith to Tower of Terror.
I think this would be so well received.
I think I think Disney fans worldwide would cheer.
Finally our hated Twilight Zone property is out of there and more more there's more Aerosmith.
What if they deserve.
What if it's just everything is the same as Guardians except it's the Aerosmith in those cages and the start on the video screen.
Well then you'd be more invested because you don't want Aerosmith to be locked up forever.
No they are the people of crime.
What what have these men done.
But he was without sin cast the first stone.
Oh Tannaly or Tavon.
It's also Tannaly or Tavon collecting Aerosmith as well.
Last I find.
And Rock and Raccoon is breaking them up.
I gotta break the bad boys of Boston out of these cages.
Come on.
So yeah.
They're gonna miss a record and say they're gonna miss their concert across town unless we just make it all one ride is what you're saying.
One ride is what you should.
Then you get to the.
OK we're out of the gantry lift.
Now hurry now get in a limo go.
I'm their new manager.
They fired Ileana Douglas.
Now it's me.
Rock it.
They're making an appearance on one of Lady Gaga's jazz standards records.
Steven's got a solo recording for his new country music career.
Oh God.
He's feuding with Joe again.
And he's releasing the album Red White and You.
Not a joke.
That's all right.
So that's right.
So now you.
I mean we didn't need to tell you that.
Tourists in the line you knew about Red White and you.
We just want to remind you know in case anybody was.
The sexy robot from Just Push Play the cover of Just Push Play also will be featured on this ride.
We all know her.
Well we gotta learn her name.
Yeah.
I wonder if she has a name.
That's a good question.
We'll find that out before we put the proposal together for this.
We have to.
We're hurt.
We must find it out before the world's last Aerosmith fan who isn't you dies.
Clock is ticking.
Well look I think we're pretty much there.
The power of forgiveness slows down the elevator and the ghosts are.
The ghosts all get to come down the elevator and then immediately go back up the elevator.
Yes.
To heaven which is the tip top club.
They get to all it took was a jazz concert and then they all disappear.
Disappear with their loved ones.
Also all the humans do take the stairs but no one is winded.
They walked out.
The most believable part for you.
Yeah.
You wanted a five minute scene of everybody catching their breath.
Yeah yeah.
Ah shit.
God.
Should have just done the elevator again.
Geez.
Just full five minute shot of huffing and puffing.
Yeah.
Is there even water?
I just need some water real quick.
Oh God.
Yeah that would have been more realistic.
They wanted the night.
This movie is like a tight 90ish minutes.
So maybe that was cut.
I got to say one of my favorite parts about it.
I was so happy when I saw 90 minutes.
I said yes.
90 minutes.
90 minutes for this thing.
Now assuredly any Tower of Terror.
The rule of movies now is movies are long.
Always.
That is the rule.
So we can assume that Tower of Terror with Scarlett Johansson if made will be.
220?
Yeah probably.
I think so.
But how else are you going to.
You can't get it done today.
And the fools in 97 somehow wrapped it up quick.
But you got to jam a lot in.
And especially if that film as we're pitching includes Sarah Smith.
Sarah Smith includes.
I mean I think it's maybe.
My thought.
What I want out of that movie is that you explore the full Towerverse.
Because all the towers go to different Limbo's.
They're all across the world.
So why not get Rocket in there.
Why not get Harrison Hightower in there.
Of course.
Yes they can all meet in elevator.
They all like wander the globe in elevator Limbo.
And assume that there's no one else in it.
Right.
Until they meet.
There's only.
There's what.
What's the amount of.
Six people.
Ghosts in elevator Limbo.
And then Guardians of the Galaxy who are not ghosts.
But they're in a they're in real world Limbo.
Right.
Yes.
That makes sense.
So let's get them all again.
All the elevator the full universe of elevator.
Well Tyka I'm sure he's hard at work on his typewriter now.
Typing away for the script for Tower of Terror.
When this guy comes.
When he sits down he buckles down.
Full attention.
Here we go Tyka.
Bring the magic.
Because you got to get it on the page.
Because you can't just get to the set and make it all up as you go.
You're not going to find it on the set.
You need to have this all worked out.
You can't just rely on.
Improv.
Make a mubs.
First thing back when the new writers contract.
You know Seth Meyers came back pretty quick.
Tyka booted up final draft.
To do that Tower of Terror script.
Back to the page thing that he reveres.
That he cares about.
Well you know it's the most.
Some people find the blank page terrifying.
But it's also very optimistic.
It's a world of possibility.
Who's this character?
Who's this guy?
Willy Wonka of screenwriting.
Another property that Tyka has.
True.
He does. He does.
That is a real thing I think.
But he's not doing the new.
No because the Paddington guy is doing the new.
Wonka.
No it's an entire other.
It's a different Wonka?
I think so.
Really?
Another Wonka?
What element of Wonka does Tyka have?
Unless I was told this in a way.
No no no.
Here.
This was said years ago.
Right before the pandemic.
This news caused the pandemic.
Tyka went to TV2 to reimagine Charlie and the Chocolate Factory for two Netflix original
series.
So we're just going to want to start with two.
Usually the way TV shows go is just do two at the same time.
So that's going to be the best for you I think.
We don't want to make you wait.
So let's get up to.
We'll do one is two seasons and one is three.
We'll pre-renews those.
So that's five.
Get going.
And I know you got to leave and get working on Tower of Terror and your Star Wars.
Probably a Jurassic World or two.
But get those in.
Get those drafts in when you can.
I think that is the Roald Dahl estate has a Netflix deal.
Yes I think that's right.
Because of the Wes Anderson stuff?
No I think they were just plumbing like going through the Roald Dahl books.
So is that separate than the Wonka like young Wonka movie that's coming out?
I think so.
Yes because that's Warner Brothers.
That's Warner Brothers.
Okay.
So maybe there's competing Wonka properties now which is funny but also not that unsurprising
in this day and age.
Yeah.
And also as we know Tyka has a first look deal with Everywhere.
So they actually can't.
I've tried I've pitched my own shows that are complete or like here's an idea that I
had that I alone thought of and I want to do it.
And what I've gotten from every network is can we give it to Tyka?
Is that just a quick question?
You mind if Tyka does it?
Wasn't he?
Did I send that there was a story and then I saw it was from like 2019 or very start
of 2020 that he was going to do Flash Gordon at Disney?
Yeah that sounds right.
I think that's another two million dollar check cashed and not.
That was the only I tried to look into it more and it was just one deadline story.
I think there was some talk of it.
Tyka's process is going to he sits down his computer like we said he types into Google
movies he writes down 10 movies then he drives to movie studios and says the names of the
movies to the executives and they say here's two million dollars.
It's a good one.
I mean look it's good work if you can get it.
I would like to.
Just looking people dead in the eye and going three women and a baby.
All right.
Can you validate my parking sir?
Okay we'll get I'll get working on the check though validation and thank you.
Please don't.
No need to ever actually make it done.
Well you survived.
I guess the three.
Three is a good one to be behind multiple paywalls I'd say.
Sure.
Your bravery saved the haunt cast.
Well done freedom frighters.
Oh good.
Yeah.
Nice of Halloween intimacy.
But we now send you to come up with some regular November topics as we are off to do some
research about a few beloved wonderful classic Halloween costumes.
I want to drop a quick bomb.
I found the schedule for my high school band trip.
My mom found it not knowing.
Oh not knowing even about talking about that on the episode.
And I was like first of all I went right to the page of the Pleasure Island and I'll put we'll
talk about this more later and I'll post some photos of it.
I was like where is it.
Where's the Pleasure Island Club because I didn't know.
Remember I said I didn't know which one it was.
It doesn't say it just says dance party at Pleasure Island in the morning.
But here's the piece of information that I did not remember that I think is amazing.
We marched in band in front of the Spectro Magic parade.
Wow.
What.
You were an opening act.
We opened for Spectro Magic at the Magic Kingdom.
Wow.
Oh boy.
And I don't remember I didn't remember that detail.
So I just wanted everyone in the club three to know that I've opened for Spectro Magic.
Damn.
Well that should be your new credit.
If we're trying to like you know interest people in the show.
Right.
What have the hosts done though.
Why should I listen.
And that's when I was like I'm going to be the opening act for Spectro Magic.
That's right.
I will.
I will list that.
In that stage.
2002.
The doll face Spectro Men.
They were really nice.
Yeah.
We were actually really nice.
We were on the show on Tender Earth guys.
Wow.
And they said keep at it gang.
Andatique.
And that meant a lot.
You could be where we are someday.
You'll have opening acts someday.
You could have a doll face one day.