Club Three.
Welcome to Club Three where your cartoon friends go to die.
I'm Scott joined by Mike and Jason and just imagine big inflatable versions of all of us
lunging, lunging of our own might straight into lamp posts and ripping our faces open.
Occasionally I first.
Yeah.
I was not prepared for how gruesome this episode would be.
If you kind of view it as these are the characters and this is something that's happening to them,
it really puts a really almost like a metal light on what's happening.
Of course it's balloons.
It's but if you just you know if you if you backed or if you were if you were a you know
a three-year-old and you saw some of this happening.
Oh god.
Potentially scarring for literally scarring for the characters mentally scarring for anyone
witnessing it.
It's like and I've said this before because I like this is such a big deal that I watched
Hellraiser in the last few years because it was so scary to me as a kid.
I keep talking about this like an annoying guy who's just read like his first book of
poetry or something.
Yeah we're in like eight time or nine time.
Yeah yeah yeah.
But that's the like the skin tearing is what this reminded me of from Hellraiser.
So like when one of the balloons goes down because it gets caught on something and then
like it's balloon whatever it what is the what is the material a balloon is made of.
Do we know do we look into this.
I'm not sure.
I think it used to be rubber.
I don't think it is anymore.
Mylar is like a smaller balloon I assume but yes when it gets ripped I'm like oh my god
it's like Hellraiser it's like the skin is ripping off and the body horror is coming
true.
At least though you're you're spared in that there is nothing but just air and and white
reverse of flaps inside.
If you add blood to any of these scenarios now it's the most horrifying stuff.
Blood or like a skeletal system or like muscles.
Yeah if any of the balloons had muscles then we're really in trouble.
Yeah oh yeah.
You're seeing half of Barney's screaming face.
Someone getting whipped in the face by like a tendon.
Like it would be like that attack.
Attack on Titan character you know I'm talking about.
Yeah yeah the big ones.
When he's got like the big muscle face.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah potential for grimness.
We'll see how scary these actually are as we dive in.
It's an interesting poll this month also because ultimately kite disasters lost to balloon
disasters.
Kite tails was in the running and it didn't make it.
It was number three even but it's another thing where facsimiles of characters
severely injure themselves in front of a mass audience.
So something was in the air I guess or something I guess a lot of it wasn't the characters.
The characters are not in the air anymore.
From the beginning they were they were pretty upfront about like these are designed they
have to come down somehow you know.
So once they started crashing and people like these things keep crashing they're like oh
we're so sorry that they have to.
That's part of it.
The crashing though clearly is like the heart of the show.
It's like why you watch or why anyone remembers.
We'll talk about how to maybe hit kites down the road.
If really you could like figure out a really like specific way to satisfy this hitch.
It's like would it be satisfying to watch like the rainy day cavalcade where all the
characters walk down Main Street but a couple of them break their leg while you're going.
Is that sort of the fun of this?
Yes.
Goofy steps weird on a crack and he breaks his leg.
Like it depends on how I think you need some I think you got to exaggerate it a little
more.
It's funny though it's funny.
The leg break can maybe you don't even catch it you know.
Yeah that's true but yeah it's not they're not going to have like a really like severe
thing with a parade to stop.
It'll be funny but yeah a couple characters get severely hurt.
Yes.
In a funny way.
Well there I did watch compilation and it was just called parade fails and a lot of
it it wasn't just the balloons they included a lot of like Disney like this float stall
the dragon catches on fire.
Yeah right.
And they did show a clip from Fantasmic where like all the characters on the riverboat.
Dopey loses his footing goes through the railing lands on Goofy and then lands on the floor
and Goofy shakes it off and keeps his streamer going and then another.
Never stop streaming always be streaming.
Loses his job.
Another costume character goes and checks on Dopey and it's just like.
I guess the human that there are humans inside.
Yeah I guess we could have like drone carried characters breaking their legs that'd be a
little less.
There was that patent remember we saw that a couple years ago like for drones carrying
like big puppets down Main Street.
Wow.
Oh yeah.
Remember that.
Yeah I think the current regulations a lot of what I have seen the drones have to be
far away.
You know you can't fly drones over people's heads.
You can't fly drones too close to people so that's why the night time show at Harry Potter
and Hollywood they can launch from where the worlds and like Disneyland Paris I think has
a big.
Let them fly over people's heads.
Let them fly over.
I want a big puppet that wears down Main Street and then can break its leg and we won't
feel bad about the human being inside.
Jack Skellington will break his leg on Main Street every night.
It'd be a good leg to break it's long and yeah you notice it you definitely know I think
he'd bounce back quickly too.
Yeah.
So that's what I want.
The the runner up not kite tails but heading into next month the Fox breaking the magician's
code and mass magician specials.
Pretty excited about this.
Yeah.
Suggestion and now it's just a matter of next month is December.
I feel like we need some holiday ideas.
So let's do this.
Submit your holiday ideas or your whatever ideas.
It tends to work when we kind of grab bag it and just whatever you're feeling out there.
If there's a ton of like unbelievable Christmas ideas maybe we'll hold mass magician until
a more secular time.
Oh yeah.
But but if not we'll throw them in.
I don't know.
We'll just see what happens.
Put your ideas in the comments but with your likes and we'll see where things go.
That was I feel like it's been a long time coming one way or another the mass magician.
Sure.
Yes.
I'm excited about that.
I got opinions about that.
I watched those.
You like it comes out a lot comes up a lot.
I'll just preview.
I felt very guilty watching those specials.
Wow.
Yeah.
You're breaking the code.
I'm breaking the code.
Yeah.
I'm piece of shit.
And you're supporting that odd guy inside.
I remember the reveal of him just feeling like deflating to use the term of the opposite
like and who is he?
Some strange man.
It was just a strange man.
We all forget his name now.
Because we were all like is it Copperfield?
Is it Lance Burton?
Could it be?
Of course not.
Not one of the three we know never mind.
I love that Fox era of programming.
We've talked about Beyond Belief Fact or Fiction hosted by the great John and the Frakes but
also like Alien Autopsy shows.
Animals doing animals attack.
Yes.
There was a whole vibe to those shows that was intriguing and like trashy as well.
I watched Who Wants to Marry a Multi-Millionaire Live.
Oh wow.
With Rick Rockwell, semi real estate magnate and star of Return of the Killer.
Not star actor in Return of the Killer Tomatoes.
Darva Conger.
I ate up all this.
When you had no friends in high school the Fox network were your friends.
Darva Conger was your friend.
That was an era.
That was a time.
It really was.
Yeah.
But let's dig into this and let me read an excellent little suggestion word for word
from Eric Scanlon.
Thank you for submitting this.
Next one.
Macy's Thanksgiving Day Parade Balloon Disasters.
Kermit, Barney, Mighty Mouse all dead.
Good work Eric.
Love it.
It's a little bit of the tone.
Okay.
I have some like dry beginning of Macy's Parade kind of history.
But just to do like kind of a streaming show style hard cold open.
Let me just dig in.
Let me just go straight to one of these and you guys might have some of these clips too.
But I'm just going to start at this one.
I think the height of Macy's Parade Disasters.
This here is Sonic the Hedgehog.
Two time balloon.
64 foot tall Sonic the Hedgehog was swept into a street lamp at 58th and Broadway.
As the balloon began deflating it pulled the...
All right.
Well it stopped there but that's fine.
You know it doesn't really work as audio.
Then that is I forgot that's the one you were alluding to Jason.
Yeah that's I first.
That's I first into a street lamp.
I think knocked part of the street lamp off.
Some people lightly injured.
No one in a coma.
No one in a coma from this incident.
Not this one no.
Yeah not this one.
Yeah there's great amateur video.
It's got the big amateur video stamp at the bottom.
Just imagine you're in the closest apartment or office
and this happens with you have the best view on Earth of Sonic the Hedgehog ripping his eye open.
It's a boy it said just on a basic level.
I mean the balloons are always exciting to see but then every step of it seeing like
you know right here's the beginning of the puncture and here's like the you know the
tear of the I don't know what we're going to keep wanting to refer to the materials.
I don't know the materials but like seeing it start to give and stretch
and then that moment you can frame by frame this and it's so satisfying seeing this first
weird flaps form and there's something so fascinating about seeing an iconic character
just punctured in the eye.
It's nuts.
Yeah polyurethane is what the polyurethane thing.
Okay great we're going to need to know that.
Yeah for sure.
How often it is that the faces too is really I mean I guess it makes sense.
That's what you would line up with.
Yeah.
Boy is it just like and it's crazy in some of them where it almost feels like this weird
moth to flame like they're being drawn to like they're staring right at the lamp post
and going what is it?
Yeah.
Is that good for me?
Should it be on me?
Yeah there's a Rudolph I think because you see it at smaller cities too like
I saw Richmond Virginia and Davenport Iowa and then when they get Macy's parade there's
a dozen balloons or more but when it's a smaller city they like get one big balloon
and it's a whole thing and Rudolph very slowly hits a stoplight and it seems like he's squeezing
under it and then it just gets him in the face.
Yeah yeah is it in the nose?
I've seen that one.
I think it's in the nose.
That's fascinating that plays out so slowly and that's a good one I recall as all of them
are and as we will hear I mean there's not video of everything we're going to refer to
but it's one of the best aspects for sure is hearing audience of adults and children
because you hear the children like puncture through the audio of it hearing a big group
all cheering for thinking that maybe they'll make it and then being so upset when they don't make it.
It's a Hindenburg that you're allowed to enjoy more because nobody's getting in most cases
nobody's getting hurt.
I was gonna say we were talking about muscles and all this stuff oh imagine they were screaming
but there is screaming like some of them have amazing soundtracks of the audience like fully
following.
But there's some like there's a compilation I have where like there's a guy's like yeah
like so excited about it and I swear one guy yells like and man we were here we were here
for a bat once when one of them caves in.
Yes like blows up and like there's like a bro energy to the clip of guys like celebrating.
This is some toxic this is some limp break stuff you know that's hot the toxic masculinity yeah
yeah exactly yes no yeah the toxic masculinity just really feeds these Macy's you know we all
have to examine yeah yeah we were all complicit we didn't realize it yeah yeah what was happening
pop culturally to lead to the cheering of these balloons being destroyed.
So there's that one and there's other 90s ones that I'll bring up but just now with now that
we've gotten a quick hit of one did you guys look at all into the early days 20s and 30s
because the disasters on this parade began real quick right out of the gate this kind of thing
was happening because no matter the decade or the year wind has always been very prominent in
New York City in late November sure yes that is not something that's that's that's nothing new
with the times and there's really no balloons are ultimately not the most advanced technology
I'm sure they're made better now I'm sure there's some you know a digital component to the design
of them but ultimately you got a big dumb thing with 40 people with ropes all just trying to it's
like it's like sailboats it's like trying to cross the Atlantic oh and someone told me once like the
you know the the people handling these balloons are like rigorously trained and then some of them
go down to universal Florida because they do a brand at Macy's day parade with balloons
around Christmas time and those are real handlers like this is that's a train it's not you're saying
it's not like volunteers just like having fun it's not from lack of trying but there's only so much
regular people can do balloons and wind never really change yeah yes well and especially just
because it's like when they started doing it they really didn't have it maybe down pat as far as how
to do things right sure yeah so well in the pain you know I feel like the the 20s and 30s are a
wild era of like nobody knew how to do anything and yeah yeah so there's like I don't know let's
fucking try it I don't know so uh I mean the beginning of it all right so uh Macy's Thanksgiving
parade starts in 1924 balloons are introduced in 1927 and to your kind of fuck-it point Mike
the reason the balloons came into the picture is because in the first few years
they did not have balloons they had live zoo animals and I when I see that all right they
started in 27 I was like oh what happened in 26 and unfortunately well fortunate ultimately
fortunately yeah nothing happened I think it was just that seeing a bunch of live animals scared
kids citywide so no more of that so how do we have a big fun component that works for kids
balloons and it was not too long until stuff started happening with the balloons I don't
think they like I don't think there were that many to begin with and they weren't really
big IP yet obviously because there wasn't that much big IP at the time 1931 Felix the cat is
the first like major uh character Mickey and Donald were not too long after that's the Disney's part
of it really early on but at the very beginning they sort of had to make up their own characters
one of which I was disturbed to see is called terrible Turk oh my god I didn't see this yeah
I don't know I feel that terrible turn I don't know why we're mad at the Turks oh my god um
which is just kind of a big rotund guy with a big mustache um and but then also there were
pre Felix the cat there were like characters from comics but the this is a little bit real
test of Jason's old timiness uh or either of you're both you might know some old timey it's not a
Felix thing maybe you're talking about but maybe it's a different well I'm referring to okay in
1930 here's the here's the balloons they had in 1930 Joe Jinx don't know what that is yeah Barney
Google I know I've heard of Barney Google you've heard of Barney Google that is an old comic strip
thing debuted in 1919 um from Barney Google and Snuffy Smith yeah yeah I know yeah we know these
guys yeah yeah yeah yeah these guys they got some cats and jammer kids oh yeah yeah oh you're right
you're oh you know what predating that you're right cats and jammer kids in 1829 uh-huh did these guys
do king features snap these guys up they might be in the family I'll look it up um the and then
the one that really jumped out at me boob mcnut I don't know boob mcnut boob mcnut uh was it from
ran from 1918 to 1934 by mcnaught syndicate different syndicate this is a comic strip by
rube goldberg what yeah I didn't know he did stuff that wasn't devices that's wild
flab trapsions yeah he did a con he did boob mcnut he did boob rube goldberg did boob mcnut
boob mcnut started as a series of one-shot gags which usually ended with boob being tortured to
death for his innocently destructive ways my god rube and then it was about him like meeting uh
pearl and making her pearl mcnut but then they soon got divorced pearl mcnut this is a very we
got looking at that depressing sounding well then so then a new character named professor
lucifer gorgonzola butts b-u-t-t-z this was the mcu of s not as barney google and snuffy smith
are in the king features syndicate family damn nice damn wow the place that's the only show in
town the best syndicate to be in it's the number one syndicate uh wait a minute oh you know actually
and they still boob mcnut started with oh oddly started with king features syndicate and ma'am
maybe now today is with no syndicate oh wow i'm not sure they lost the boob mcnut they lost boob
so it's a dark day for us at king we lost boob um so that's that that's the kind of general tenor
of the characters that we're dealing with at this time and this is a story that is attributed to
felix the cat but i think the story i think that's not right i've also seen that it's just
the cat because maybe they weren't doing licensed characters yet so in one of these years might have
been 30 or 31 i don't know um basically this was the plan that macy's had in the early days right
what do we do with the balloons after do we need to develop some kind of deflating uh uh you know
procedure um no here's what we'll do it's we only got five of them right we got five balloons let's
just like give them a little extra helium boost just a little little bit of extra power then we
let them fly and they land somewhere they'll go somewhere and in somewhere presumably in the
greater new york uh you know upstate or new jersey area and somebody will find them and if you find
our balloons and return them to your nearest macy's we'll give you a hundred bucks in macy bucks
and at the time for if you convert it that's 1600 dollars today so that's nothing to sneeze at
that's a lot of you're getting a ton of clothes or bed sets or whatever yeah go check the bird
sanctuary something usually land there i want those macy bucks i gotta buy my lady a mink stole
oh it's my only shot she's gonna divorce me like pearl mcnut so that seems fine right just let them
go that doesn't seem like that will lead to widespread disaster immediately uh well you'd
be wrong to say that because the cat early on um okay so the the cat was just let loose into the
sky and then the first person to encounter the cat was a pilot who suddenly had not one but two
balloons on his tail and he's like is this a mistake he might have not known about the reward
he maybe is just like do i need to help do i need to be a war hero right now so he has like rope
and he unfurls the rope and he tries to lasso the cat and for a while he has the cat lassoed and
like what do i do now where do i even not even know it is for the macy's parade he doesn't know
what the hell's happening um and then the cat gets away oh well didn't get it um uh and then
suddenly the cat shows up in somebody's backyard in west norwood new jersey 27 miles away a lady
looks out the window and sees a silk and rubber cat like oh what's this is that for the macy's
parade what's going on oh no it's going into a telephone wire boom explode probably like
city's power nagdi is just on fire and imagine the materials back then imagine that on fire
imagine the material you could imagine just asbestos actually is that fireproof it's just made of the
film from the end of inglorious bastards that just these super flammable film thank god the
cat didn't float into an old movie theater hundreds could have died there unless it was
nazis and then it was good that they died yes there was no one was smart enough like why didn't we
just use black paint why did we have to use that blank film just the way you look at anything any
materials that are used like anything over 50 years ago we're like i'm surprised they didn't
use like the joker gas chemicals from the first batman movie to fill up the balloons
and then when they leaked everyone just started going nuts it's fine as long as nobody goes near
it yeah don't know if the balloons spring a leak everyone around it will lose their minds but and
yeah as long as it doesn't happen they'll be all right the city will be full of rabid maniacs yes
it will turn children into essentially like hyena people for the rest of their lives but as long as
that doesn't happen look if we end up with a bunch of fish with clownish smiles we sell the fish
you know monetize the rot as they say they're curios then sell them to that ripley and his new
believe it or not museum yeah so because of all this there's some bad pr cat caught on fire in
new jersey a plane tried to lasso it and macy's was like we're gonna get ahead of it this year
listen but they put out a press release or some kind listen up pilots there we will not the the
we're not retiring the program you get your macy's bucks if you find a balloon but it doesn't count
if you're a pilot and you lasso the bullet that's got to be on the ground you pilots don't get your
head started so um they get this word out there and they hope that all pilots are made aware of
this news this does not work at all there's no internet how do you make every pilot aware of
don't go after our balloons so immediately a 21 year old female pilot annette gibson
sees a different cat much taller cat named tom cat and it's like oh hey but i think maybe does
know about the reward so like oh i'm going for it and just fly straight into it maybe i can wrap
the balloon around the plane and then return it to the ground this is a pilot trainee at this point
she's just like learning for fun she's 21 all right straight into the balloon uh plane immediately
goes into a tailspin people are watching people are gasping in horror down it goes luckily during
the tailspin she's with her like trainer and they're able to trade seats as they fall and he he pulls
it up gets them out they shake loose tom cat and uh and nothing happens um she goes on to become a
major pile open like a big like a female pilot you know uh uh event or school or something i
think new Amelia Earhart um this is also like batman 80 the 89 movie where batman has to take
the balloons and gets them in the bat wing remember he collects the balloons all right and takes them
up in the air and lets them go up there wow well there's batman's in a bad example you can do it
if you have bat technology but if you're somewhere if you're a regular pilot who's just learning
he's a trained pilot yeah he is brought down by a big like long gun if you remember joker has a
long gun in that but he's after he gets rid of the balloons macy's was ready to do that they
were gonna like if any of these dirty pilots try to steal our but so anyway and they still don't
after that they still don't cancel the plan and they're still just like um balloons washing up
on riverbanks including one where uh georgie the drum major landed in long island where he was
mobbed and torn to bits 82 people tried to claim the reward money oh my god everybody's ripping
up georgie get him tear his eyes up georgie the pupil get me a fine bounty of macy's books
i want to buy some pendleton flannel shirts i need to buy some more work shirts good ones
yes so this is the starting point we aren't even a decade out and this is what's happening
with macy's uh and so they almost it almost like you think it was getting crazy in the 90s when all
these balloons are exploding but they had they had nowhere to go but down insanity wise um and then
weirdly like okay so after they stop releasing the balloons into the air for cash rewards
things kind of calm down a bit um but then we get into one if you you guys probably looked at some
like list of calls or photo slideshows of this kind of thing and there's one that that eric our
listener referred to which is mighty mouse which is kind of a like um it's a powerful almost like
war image of like mighty mouse holding one arm up like almost like help me please not so mighty
anymore for black and white from behind it's a it's a powerful image yeah starring image it's
yeah and he's because who's more powerful than mighty mouse no one at that time no week like that
it's haunting heroes can fall yeah um i'm bad that's the five for fighting song that superman song
plays in my head yeah yeah um so i don't know what year this was but this is another hero
one where this isn't a full deflate but it's superman and he like he made it through the parade
but the like triumphant arms out pose of superman didn't really work out like he's deflated at the
arms so they're just limp it looks like he's like about to take a dive in a pool yeah yeah which i
guess is not the worst most disturbing image but it's certainly not the heroic arms out flying
through the sky in such a no no yeah well and if you get the full like i mean look at it from the
side because it's it's so limp they have such yeah curvature i mean he looks like he's being
carried like he was just shot in the chest and now somebody's like wow let's get oh yeah like doomsday
has just killed him maybe yeah being carried his corpse is being carried by doomsday yeah new york
is hosting superman's funeral today this is getting to the we've been recording for just under a half
hour now and enough has been i feel like i watched so many compilations and so many video clips and
i was like i didn't see kermit like i didn't see super like there's so i didn't see kermit i know i
want to represent all the ones eric mentioned and kermit i don't really recall i might have seen
kermit in print there's a very robust macy's fandom site bless these fandom sites always good
stuff on there um the i saw in 1987 kermit the frog's right arm was ripped by a tree
yeah the pictures i've saw kermit are yeah i didn't see okay he's like i mean just look it up kermit
balloon disaster and his his head is just has no air in it oh no so it really looks like he's
melt like kermit is melted by a giant candle or something okay obviously the 90s you know there
there is so much television so much cable news and broadcast news the 90s ones are pretty well
kermit documented yes kermit at the end of uh of last crusade uh his face is melted off
oh he picked the wrong cup he picked the wrong cup he was foolhardy he's being carried by a bunch of
people in green they're all in kermit suits so he's like all his minions are like below him
does feel like some weird like you know death of a great leader or something everybody's everybody's
in a cult and they lost their their number one uh did you guys see the popeye thing that happened
it's not quite a it's not quite a disaster um but jason did you see this popeye no popeye so it was
like a rainy day okay the way popeyes cap was set up it was a perfect rain collector oh no so
popeyes cap was just collecting rain and then he took like a hard right turn and just like a like
a tidal wave hit a bunch of people oh i'm not sure if anyone was hurt because it is pretty like a lot
of water from a high up like uh altitude but oh no that was not that was not a regular disaster
but it's a different type of accident wow that's an innovative a new type of disaster right yeah
you didn't know was possible kermit is especially upsetting because he looks like he's doubled over
in pain yes like his appendix burster he's just vomiting i mean obviously vomiting kermit we we
was well documented from conan but yeah and he just looks like the the bones have been taking out
taken out of his head yeah yeah yeah he's been removed the bone his skull is not in there anymore
yeah what would have to happen to yeah you would say like for your face to have no nothing in it
right what disturbing accident that's like something yeah that would be i don't know if
there's a movie where like a villain takes the skull out of your head but that would be a scary
situation it's a good one yeah is it too is it too upset i was gonna say like that's like you can't
put that in like a marvel it's got to be for everybody no no no that's that's too upset and
it doesn't happen in hellraiser as far as i know there were sequels there's sequels i have not seen
although yeah some of it's too gross so maybe it actually did happen i didn't realize it
when you turned away yeah it's hellraiser had a skull sucking machine it's possible yeah
goes out right through the ear um here's here's what i'm gonna uh what i i mentioned this fandom
and they they have a list of incidents and accidents that is so overwhelming that you
couldn't possibly get through them all and i don't think a lot of these were even notable enough to
be like a thing and a lot of these didn't make it before the cameras that's a lot of the right
the tragedy is that you know well you know uh the the quick money wasn't in good enough shape
to even like be on the broadcast so many of these are not but as i was going through these here's
what i'm gonna i'm gonna read a number of these and just i'm gonna leave out the the term balloon
where possible so that we can just imagine this happening to the character oh cool themselves
yeah 1983 mickey mouse's arm was accidentally torn off he later exploded
betty boops moon was deflated during the march or moon okay um poor betty this is just a
confounding one the leaves on bugs bunny's carrot were ripped off by trees
uh-huh um humpty dumpty had his left hand and left leg deflated by a tree branch near the start of
the root that kind of that just sounds to me like a that's a bad that's a clunky first draft of
humpty dumpty right right this isn't quite it it's tiny that up this is a economy of words
uh bart simpson's t-shirt was ripped open by a lamppost
he definitely had a cow man uh um the unexpected wind demons caused woody woodpecker's left hand
to get torn by a tree and then uh 2002 cheesusaurus rex's right arm was shredded
the cheesusaurus rex wow i missed that one too i love that that was in there what a good yeah what
a good balloon i don't think we've talked about cheesusaurus rex somehow in all of the
ip and uh childhood relics jason what do you think about cheesusaurus rex what um brand was was he
for the tv dinners or was he for crackers craft yeah he was craft seems like you don't have much
knowledge about cheesusaurus rex well deep dive and you're a podcast the right host
well because i was i we were talking talking about rex talking about macy's tell me five things you
like about him uh cheese uh noodles okay all right story checks out cheesy okay he's delicious
no we're talking about balloons and rex my my brain immediately went to the uh we're back
dinosaur story oh well yeah i saw him too let's talk about we're back this this is one of the in
in one of those years i forgot i feel like there were a number of these accidents in one unlucky
year maybe it was all in the same stretch of time yes the character rex from we're back a
dinosaur's tale dinosaur story story i think it wasn't tale it was story i believe it was story
i think that's right um the character rex as voiced by john goodman and and i have a clip of this too
again you know you never know uh how good any of these clips are just to listen to but uh why not
give it a go well you know and to remind you guys of what happened here let's get a little taste of
rex
that's another one where it does it feels like he's doing it to himself in a way yeah yeah he
feels like kind of like a like a dumb cat or something who's like sniffing
where he's sniffing and then before you know it yeah well it's just a blank stare what's this
oh boy that is that his entire that entire snout tears up but that's a lot more that's a lot more
insta damage is done than sonic for sure yes there's yeah some of it's slow mo that that one the
rex one is i think would be extra disturbing as a kid because like some of them are just like
there's a tear in the side and it's kind of a slow deflate and as a kid you could kind of like
be like okay but no no rex is hurt badly yeah there's no way around it there's no way around
it there's also like the footage is so interesting because there's so many different like fan not fan
footage but it's a you know home video footage essentially so it feels like an old like disaster
like there's some like very like i don't know like you're watching archival footage of some sort of
like the hidden bird or something you're being pieced together from like we only have a couple
angles and thankfully somebody was here is a brutal film you know it's not like modern disasters
where we have like all these different cameras on it and footage it's pretty high quality there are
three angles of sonic seemingly one of these compilations does a little like side by side
yeah so you can pick your but none of them are as good as the one in the in the window yeah that's
true um it at times like that with when things like this happen to rex you just have to be thankful
that it was a character who no one has any affection for oh yeah if that had happened to
a more beloved yeah dinosaur like cheesusaurus rex like she's yeah the country would have never
yeah his accident was in 2002 and luckily it was only an arm getting shredded because
new york is shaky in 2002 i don't i think maybe morale wise you throw in the towel if all of
cheesusaurus explodes juliani and cheesusaurus rex together a lot of juliani in these clips
like you see it's like wow i forgot he had so much hair in the 90s yeah yeah he looks so healthy and
normal he was that he's quoted there's a new york times article about when there was kind of
a an epidemic of these things happening if this is something that could be corrected in the future
we'll find out what happened it's not bad i don't know i don't think we know enough to answer that
yet anytime there's an injury like this it makes you feel very very bad an injury well that might
have been one because there's what we don't need to dwell on this there was one where there was a
bad there yeah yeah so which you know is less so you meant the balloon less fun and and uh funny
nutcracker i don't know the hat there was a really oh cat in the hat was the bad one um
there are some generic ones like a nutcracker pops okay with the funniest is a candy cane and
it's just a strip blows up it blows up it deflates it's so funny it deflates so quickly in midair
that might be the one where like bros are like yeah you know we'll know when he's hurt you aren't
losing a beloved there's no smile on the candy cane right right right yeah so that that helps
you're you don't feel like you're watching a soul right right a soul escape a body as opposed to
um here's one from that article uh this might have been cat in the hat year um listen to this
this gripping description from new york times uh there was high drama as the balloon handlers and
the police tried to control the airborne chaos as the pink panther lurched about while simultaneously
imploding a police inspector shouted somebody give me a knife quick an officer quickly handed
him a five inch long knife and he punched a hole through the feline's tail a move that almost
immediately stabilized the balloon so it was good but i love that these scenarios now involve
now involve police officers saying yeah i gotta stab the panther hey uh did anyone ask that cop
we had a five inch knife on this person or they just let that slide i got a five inch i got nine
inch i got two inch what do you need i got every inch from one to twelve oh okay officer dommer
has lots of knives all right awesome well their non-union union will cover this uh right quick
you know the pink pan that was the pink panther yeah yeah mm-hmm i had to stab his tail um and i
think the same article deals with oh wait you know actually just sorry before we move on from
we're back i do want to say you don't want it to happen to any of the dinosaurs but thank god that
it was rex as voiced by john goodman and not vorb as voiced by jay Leno oh right right anything
had happened to vorb again morale i don't think we'd be able to we would have said no to the topic
like yeah we would have eric you expect us to you expect us to go on mike and discuss the the airborne
death of vorb no taste for taste to dig in on vorb vorb is an alien evidently an alien how
do we never i mean i was just we're back i started a list because like hoopla or toby have all of
the stuff i missed and then like you've presented a whole new one oh who's punching your library
card and they have a really weird collection of movies um but they have you know cool world
cat stone dance oh one of them has we're back a dinosaur story and i was like i didn't dig in
all of it i could have i could have see what i missed you know we've all been missing jay leno
is vorb the alien who's in the dinosaur movie yeah yes what's the plot of we're back well that's what
he just said um well presumably some dinosaurs are back back to the law they come back in the present
day i assume i think because i i believe you know what i read that them being dinosaurs in the parade
nodded to the plot of the film in which they try to blend in by disguising themselves as balloons
in the that's the balloon that's the poster yeah they are balloons in the poster that that one year
the year with rex also had a bethoven balloon and easy the atlantic olympics six olympic yes and it
was like i think 94 so it was like two years out and they were already hyping isi oh yeah well i
like isi yeah i like isi too that summer i was at bush there was an easy wild mouse roller coaster
bush gardens really a themed roller coaster themed isi just with some cardboard like this
particle burr cutouts of isi i just say i'm sure it got quickly re-themed by 95 roller coaster yeah
it was it seems i'm getting an auto fill in for wild isi it was a wild mouse called wild isi yeah
boy this is wild boy you think you've heard every obscurity and then you hear about wild isi wild isi
yeah it's weird also they did the they did a balloon of richard jewel too two years out just
spreading awareness of the characters we're gonna learn about in 96 yeah get ready some twists and
turns coming with this uh this security guard character um okay so uh vorb episode coming but
for now um let's talk about i think i mean i i guarantee we've talked about this and we've watched
the clip presumably on on an earlier second gate about this broader topic uh but we can't not spend
a little time talking about barney yeah it's time to discuss barney i am sure that we played the
clip and we talked about day in the park with barney um but i'm never going to turn down the
opportunity to play it again because this has the best crowd response oh yeah this is wild and he
dies in agony yes it is the most so painful it's the most exaggerated you get full body
um it's maybe the funniest character that it could happen to yeah because older millennials we had a
blood lust for barney experiencing pain and dying we hated barney we wanted barney dead so yeah yeah
you were offended by that
he is just the audience is like oh shocked and horrified it is like a hindu park level reaction
he's yeah he's like he goes a wildly swinging into the right side of the street he's got the
hole cut into his side and then he's done he's gone he's almost in two there's just back skin
keeping him together at that point and that is my favorite vocal uh iteration or you know
interjection which is oh oh no so good and the crowd they all yell because they think he's going
to like collapse on them initially like he's heading our way so they all and then yeah and
then sliced down the middle and then within two minutes he's just he is on the floor and then you
guys gotta see this i've never seen this this great like ap photograph of a helicopter angle
where he's just flattened on the ground he looks like he got shot with 200 bullets like a big
purple tarp it looks like he jumped off of a building yeah flat like a cartoon character
which was beauty killed the bees oh that's depressing poor barney so crazy and then okay
well all right here let me read some quotes from here's some newspaper quotes from uh when when
this happened the crash of barney the purple dinosaur beloved by preschoolers and loathed by
some parents was heart-stopping for those at the end of its ropes everything turned purple said
an onlooker barney attacked us said still stunned isabella faciano of hoboken after it fell police
officers rushed to puncture it with knives and relieved the tage again all right get your knives
do you have your seven inch yes the big day do you think like cops in new york are like kind of
excited for macy's because like they're like maybe we get to like stab up a couple balloons today
i forgot thanksgiving was coming next week so i primed a bunch of knives
just getting them sharp in case we need them yeah they get to like the fancy their fanciest knives
out from like a qvc knife show like just like long like pirate looking knives and stuff like
fancy knives there's a 40 for the set but it's 50 knives so that's a good bargain that's a good deal
i cut through 20 balloons in one morning with this thing the guy at the store told me um yeah i think
so i think i mean like you know to be to be able to do a bunch of stabbing and be cheered as a hero
yeah yeah and to yeah and to stab such beloved characters truly what is needed right now more
than anything is for you to stab barney repeatedly yeah best day of that guy's life
what what occurs to me also again if i'm like stepping back and putting the characters into
this and imagining the characters doing this oh yeah in all of these cases um i was thinking of
a term that i realized i've been saying wrong forever and maybe i'm saying wrong now but uh
here's here's what flashed to me is hara kiri this is like the oh the samurai harry kiri i think
that's wrong is what i learned oh um as i was sure i think that maybe also uh whatever it is
because i've disgraced myself with all these mispronunciations there you go take this sword
you know what you gotta do um uh it's almost especially the barney i think you could regard
it i just imagine that like because it is you know it's the samurai just like gutting themselves
that they're on sort and if you imagine like that that's what but like that this is barney like i
know i know what you think of me it's time to commit a ritual suicide on a public stage
this is what you did to me all of your mockery your s.l uh sketch with charles barkley this is
what it made me feel just is this what you want i will restore honor to my lineage what is this
for you baby bup what is the revenge me riff is rift the one with the saxophone the hard squad
that was badass barney just carry on your legacy just imagining the barney deflating
and riffs on the side playing the saxophone too playing baker street
turn turn
yeah you're going out on a high you're going out on your terms barn you're gonna live forever the
video clip of this the same with with rex from we're back imagine him just like oh yeah like
i've heard the snickers all morning i know i don't know i don't know if you like me i know you're you
all we're just biden time till you see bethoven i know i'm destined to be the least beloved john
goodman animated character that biker from that not good simpsons is going to be more popular than
me here's what's happening old rex now you're not gonna have old rex to kick her out anymore
yeah there would be somebody really should just like narrate like what they're thinking
characters are thinking as they like plunge themselves into a telephone pole
yeah we now cut to joe dimaggio and tress mcneal standing by in case a character needs to have an
honorable death it's like i know who you're who you mean but did you say joe dimaggio
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
what's what's in sonic said why does why is sonic suicidal in 1883 well he you know sonic i think
he's just goes too fast he's just not him off a cliff a million times and he that's just part of
him so like like he thought it was a ring over there or something he thought it was like one of
the big rings or i'm invincible yeah i got you think i'm scared of a light pole he saw it he
thought he saw a chili dog stand which is of course a very common thing that sonic liked in
the cartoons but not in the games he didn't seem to care about chili dogs in the games oh interesting
but in the cartoons and i think in the comic books he liked chili dogs this is how that what
in the parade is how weird teeth sonic ended his life oh yeah yeah i saw the comments
i'm so sorry my brain just jumped to something and i had to look it up does anyone want to guess
the budget and box office if we're back which was the thanksgiving release for 1993 so happy 30 years
100 happy 30th the weekend box office is that where we're getting no overall budget and box
i was just on wikipedia well it didn't cost that much to get leno because uh oh wait maybe it did
he doesn't spend the tonight show money yeah like now is that right now vorb cough it up now for vorb
pay me fucking eight mil bitch does it was helen kushnik still negotiating for him at that point
well he probably had to record it oh this might have been booked pre-tonight show yeah yeah so
listen you cocksucker
just stop sucking each other's dicks long enough to sign a check for eight million dollars to your
to the the only guy in america who can play vorb hang up hang this should have been in late
shift then if that's what happened who got you the vorb money i got you the vorb money
got you the fucking alien money jay okay you so you ungrateful prick the only reason you have
tonight show money you can't spend is that i bet you'll be milking your vorb money for 10 years
i got you a little prick i got you a 20 fucking year contract to play vorb in all the fucking
sequels jay have you seen what they're planning for land before time there's going to be 15
we're backs minimum um i moved the game these numbers are surprising in that the level of
uh budget of 20 million box office 9.3 million that is brutal in 93 when there's not the internet
like jeez yeah now i gotta see what else came out kushnik oh kushnik was boy that's
at that point she knew the writing was on the wall yelling at the producers for making a bad movie
be fucking good man was good good you fucking assholes that book said best seller
if you'd made a vorb balloon maybe people would have seen the goddamn flick where was vorb on the
fucking posters okay jay's name should have been on the fucking posters with vorb up front
what do you mean ray of pearlman gets top billing above jay taxi was 20 fucking years ago
so cheers excuse me cheers i'm getting all fucking worked up here her husband was on taxi john
goodman's on the way out mark my words he won't be doing jack shit 30 years from now
julia child's not bringing in the ticket buyers walter krank is not putting him in seats it's
vorb and jay that is an incredible line now this is like short oh my god wow the great the great
broadcasters are all uh i want three times child or jay walks um fuck i mean this is this is i
think all some like peak culture uh what what a time um and unfortunately after this era after
some very serious accidents occur these do uh dissipate they do start regulating these things
a little bit more it doesn't mean that stuff doesn't happen i think in the mid-2000s there
was a big return of wind and a big return of these accidents occurring i didn't i couldn't
find the footage of this right and look very hard but there was like there was one it was like a keith
herring balloon i don't know if it was like that that style of character like a big heart or
something and it briefly took out the broadcast booth and like ended the nbc broadcast for a minute
um maybe the balloon was trying to kill matt lauer maybe it was uh maybe
it was an attempted murder suicide for good i i have answered my own question here are some of
the other movies family movies in theaters in november 93 doubtfire three musketeers mrs doubtfire
adam's family values and the nightmare before christmas oh my god wow i kind of see why people
were hitting up we're back yeah you know they were doing the oliver platt three musketeers
yeah yeah gathering the whole family this family of musketeers no keep for southerland cool running
is the beveling hill lilies wow that's the same weekend remains of the day enjoy a lot club may
have pulled some we're back we're back or remains of the day you know for the book the bit.ly file
you should have been in the fucking three musketeers okay you should have been one of the
fucking musketeers get oliver platt out of there put jay in he's porthos now he's honorable you
get rod stewart brian adams and uh sting and you don't call jay he would have nailed that
let him do some jokes in the middle of the song stay should be in the fucking joy luck club i don't
give a shit what it's what do you mean that he's not an asian woman that he can't be a star of jay
love club joy love club that should have been the jay love god damn it
fucking pricks remains of the jay
is a nazi collaborator too remains of the jay good really good helen you've done it again helen
you're hired back
you know so unfortunately you know we don't get these every year but it doesn't mean that we
don't have a little bit of balloon fun i don't remember what year this was and i don't really
remember it occurred but this is like faint in my memory as like an internet thing maybe like 10
years or so ago there was like a nighttime inflating event where at the same time they
were inflating uncle sam and spider-man and they were being inflated right next to each other and
you wouldn't necessarily call this a disaster might be the opposite this might have been yes of course
the best day of both of their lives and here is a photo if you'd like to anyone if you want to take
a stab at describing what you're seeing right now i'm gonna let jason say it and i want him to put
it in the most blunt way he can uh spider-man's kind of going to town on uncle sam's feet no no
i'd say he's up a little further than the town all right but i don't know if it's on the feet
he's in a different neighborhood he's heading for the butthole he's having heading for brown town
i want you to put yourself in a place like jason from 2015 how would he describe this in a way
oh um spider-man is tossing uncle sam's salad all right that's better yeah that's more sorry
it's more classic sorry before i was a broadcaster you're so much more professional
you know black box improv theaters you know todry mind um yeah well if look if i you know i'm not so
comfortable saying certain terms but i will revive a phrase that we've said on the show yeah a
previous second game i will say that spider-man is eating ash
through the pants though at least it's through he's doing it through uncle sam's pants i mean
unless yeah i don't know if he's got some sort of contraption unless he sees his super strength
yeah to tear tear the pants yeah red white and blue shorts open
it's close i mean it's close to the human centipede also it's really fully there was a third
it was on the end there uh connected to spider-man you know what really makes it just subtle detail
is that spider-man's arms are on the ground oh that is crazy position yeah yeah looking forward
to this all day yes his arms on the ground means that he's been looking forward to this all day
the arms indicate it is night so at 8 a.m spider-man woke up and thought today's the day
today's the day i eat uncle sam out hey aunt may i got a big day planned today oh peter why are you
so excited well i can't tell you but i just feel like there's a new uncle in my life
and i'm very excited about him my spidey senses are tingling and i hope uncle sam i was
sorry his uncle's senses will be tingling too i hope you remember take a long shower right before
we met up
well where else to go from here i mean i said any any final details or any any like
hopes for balloon explosions in the future yeah i think obviously they're getting they're getting
a little better about all like they learn a little more each year obviously there's been
recent balloon disasters but it's like i almost wish they could do it in like more of like the
desert and they could really be lawless with like a parade like they could do a big balloon
parade in the desert they could really go wild as far as letting these things loose yeah where all
the characters can explode and nobody gets hurt and they can all suck and fuck happy thanksgiving
everyone yeah you're doing more a little more adjacent 2015 that jason's comfortable with in
the year 2023 with his filth but yes i think that the the lawless desert would be better for
for disaster and for uh uh coital interactions between the balloons uh uh maybe it's maybe
there's like a kind of a secondary once macy's is done the balloons go to unwind in the desert
in a different parade and that's where they can like you know let it all hang out let it all hang
out and if one wants to blow up they can if one wants to fillet another balloon they can
if jesus restores who am i gonna who am i gonna choose here um if he wants to i'm sorry if he
wants to take the quick bunny to completion which equals him blowing up from the top of his top hat
that then they in the desert it's okay yeah yeah i just had a couple notes i've got about
the nutcracker one is noticeable because it starts it's notable because it starts to falter
and then balloon handler runs up and tries to help and it immediately bonks him in the head like it
knocks oh no that's our ass over no and then uh kong breaking out of the chains yeah no i don't
want your help uh i forgot i i wrote down a cracker too yeah a generic nutcracker just getting
like owned by a generic nutcracker is yeah it's very funny and then i wrote down a superman balloon
i've heard you'll believe a man can fly but a man can die you wrote that i wrote that down
and i forgot i wrote that down that was the catchphrase for the chris for reeves uh movie
yeah you'll believe a man can fly of course yeah and now he's dead and now he's dead
uh doomsday and wind are his weaknesses yeah did you as a kid as kids i was like i got excited
when a character i liked was in the parade oh yeah i would get very excited but it is funny now
looking back that how many of these characters were already 40 years old the pink panther like
i liked the pink panther but in hindsight what did i like about the pink panther what yeah why
opening of the peters one of the peter sellers movies i saw or the cartoon that like was kind
of strange yeah i did it like like just on in syndication forever yeah but like i it's funny
that they were already doing like it was already like tuned lagoon during these parades where you
were like huh why make kids like them yeah so like king feature i wonder because how many king
feature syndicate balloons overall were were featured in general and then how many of them
went down this is where they make their money it's mostly balloons i looked up like dagwood
balloon and it doesn't seem like there was ever a dagwood yeah there was a dagwood different
balloon but it looks like it was not for the macy's parade um i'm looking up uh who is going to be new
this year and um you know let's just i'll throw this list out of the of the newbies and i hope
they all have long runs but if any of them explode this year is there a way that you'd like to see
them explode yeah um beagle scout snoopy there was a lot of snoopy had a lot of accidents through
the year but this seems like a new snoopy uh beagle scout snoopy uh leo netflix's leo um
it's a samler smigol vehicle um i don't remember uh uh the pillsbury doughboy really is new is new
i feel like he's been he's been around maybe it's a yeah he was he has been in the but he but he's
this is like a new version of him i think uh he's got a fresh look
okay how um i don't know it is a new pillsbury he's been in it before but it's a new i mean
i hate to see you know it'd be a good one to see explode oh well you'd really want his voice too
yeah like you really want that kind of calling yeah voice they warned me about this but i
didn't believe them i said you could poke my tummy but not with a sharp object on the street
you cops with your knives just poke me with your fingers your knives why am i flying behind the
nypd giant knife float uh i'm trying to look at there's a new design for him he looks about
the same i was wondering if they like made the pillsbury doughboy hot or something but
i don't think so i think this looks like maybe what you were wondering if they made him hot
well that's what they do to some of these characters they try to make them hot
not the doughboy luckily though yeah if you get him shredded then he's got no belly to poke yeah
no he they should not give pillsbury doughboy abs if that's what you're saying i do not want this guy
going to the gym i don't want any crossfit for the pillsbury dope although now that i say it uh
maybe i i don't know oh my god somebody drew it like he has i was getting curious wow i don't know
he looks he looks okay you like him like this i don't know uh you know what i i say i say line
him up with spider-man and just just see where things go oh my god oh my god well they're both
they're both in the same shape at least yeah so that's like a match up automatically by muscly
pillsbury i don't know to pop down by muscly pop and fresh the least doughy doughboy jason you like
this you like him looking like this i don't know well you like it too you guys like this you're
both wearing all yeah let's just say it throw me around you know would you buy more daddy
more yeah would you buy more pillsbury products if he was hotter like this
um you know seems like the answer is yes i mean maybe if he makes me um all right let's get let's
let's get out of here uh uh yeah i think you survived uh you survived club three uh
i'm shredded
well you want to give me here give me a good uh your your bravery saved the podcast well done
freedom fighters your bravery saved the planet what the podcast and it is it's well done freedom
fighters feel my bicep now how well done do you want to be how well done i have crescent rolls
in the oven my calf feels like a hard crescent roll now give it a feel why not jason you would
want a calf to feel like a hard crescent roll my crescent rolls are burned to a crisp like my
cat my hard rock calves jason hard rock calves you heard me you want me to say it again fucking
say it again and see what happens did you not hear me because my calves are crushing your fucking
skull can't speak anymore can you huh businessmen on wall street pay me thousands of dollars to
crush their skull with my rock hard calves my heart crescent calves it's a side business
nothing says 11 like my heart crescent calves suggestions in the comments uh christmas or non
throw them in there do it or the do it or if you want to want hard crescent calves around your
throat