["Frightful Narlson Theme Song"]
Welcome, foolish mortals, to the final haunt cast, The Fright, The Cemetery Gate.
Let's take these names out for one last spin.
I, for the last time, am Scottlejuice, joined by Frightful Narlson.
Hello.
Sad to see it go.
And Jagged Slash and Drain.
I'm here too.
Whoa!
That voice dropped.
The hidden voice.
That haunted doll jumped on the mic and ran away.
Oh no, and he dropped his phone.
And dropped his phone, oh!
He pulled his phone out of your lap.
That haunted doll is so impolite.
Didn't even say excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yeah, this is the final cemetery gate.
There's a little extra treat at the end of the week on the main feed, but Halloween may be over, but we're keeping it going here.
Especially because I think maybe we have experienced the ultimate haunted attraction of the LA area, of the country, of the world, and we're going to talk about it with...
I took a stab at one, but feel free to give me your own.
Give me your own, but I will for now say the best ghost in haunt casting, Evil Anderscombe.
Yay!
I love it.
It's really good.
Great.
If it works for you, it works for us.
Evil, thanks for joining us.
Are you just calling me Evil the whole two and a half, three and a half hours?
Not Evil.
I really committed to it.
Long after you've forgotten.
So glad you're here.
Oh my god.
And well, I don't...
There's much to address here before we get to the main topic.
And I don't know, I mean, maybe we should start with the thing that is not haunt cast oriented, but you reminded us right before we started recording.
And we were like, yes, my god, how have we not cut into the regularly scheduled programming to talk about it?
Do you want to just break the news in case people haven't heard the news?
Let me give you the honor.
I mean, it happened yesterday, right around 5 p.m. ish.
Was it only yesterday?
Wow.
Only yesterday. Is it only yesterday?
I think it happened a few days ago.
I think it happened Friday because there was a appropriate follow up tweet Saturday.
Oh, yes.
During the day that made me exclaim like, oh my god, and Jane's like, what's wrong?
And I'm like, okay, sit down.
I got to start over.
I had to like when I saw the news, I had to like sit down and like put my head in my hands for like a full 30 seconds.
Breathe, breathe.
Um, I guess the only thing to say is that February of next year, David Copperfield will make the moon disappear.
Wow.
And we've all been informed and we have no say in it.
No.
Yeah, yes.
Doesn't someone need to sign off on this?
This affects every nation.
Yeah.
The whole world.
Tides are affected.
Oh my god.
The second it happens, everything's going to go swirling around.
All the water will splatter up in the sky.
He not thought this through.
He announced it with a video of him standing.
You don't know where he is.
And voices are just being like, he made this disappear.
He made Statue of Liberty disappear.
The Statue of Liberty has disappeared.
Um.
As if, wait, is the ad implying that like the news was talking about it like they didn't know what happened?
Yeah.
I mean, they did at the time, they did treat those specials as news specials.
The news people would be shocked that the Statue of Liberty had disappeared.
And then it zooms out slowly and reveals that he is on the surface of the moon.
Oh, so headline one.
He's been to the moon.
He's definitely actually been on the moon.
What has he been doing with his time and money?
He's been spending his time and money.
We found out 30 years out from his previous big special.
He's like, now's the time with what's going on in the world.
I must.
This is also it is a Mr. Show sketch.
Yeah.
Blow up the moon.
It is really.
It feels totally exactly like it.
Yeah.
We can and must.
Blow up the moon.
And then, and then the additional announcement, very 90s throwback.
He called into the Today Show or he's on a video call with the Today Show.
You watch this?
Yeah.
Talking to, of all people, Carson Daly.
And he's in front of the MGM Grand.
And he's like, yes, I'm going to blow up the moon.
Because does anyone know that just the justification.
He said make the moon disappear.
That's the Mr. Show sketch.
How is he making it disappear?
Well, by blowing it up.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah, we don't know.
We don't know his tactics.
I don't have the text of the justification.
Of the children of the world?
Yes.
Kind of thing.
Wait, can you pull it up?
I don't have my phone in my pocket.
I have it.
It's been blowing up the thread that is mostly about the sphere otherwise.
Hold on.
We're all a buzz.
While we're looking it up, I will share something from the Sphere Facebook group I'm in.
Bono recently sang with Lady Gaga at the Sphere.
Oh, yes.
And they did a snippet of Shallow from the movie that she was in.
And someone was like, man, can you imagine if Bono starred in that instead of Bradley Cooper?
And then there's a couple reaction like faces that you can put on Facebook and people just had the like, like laughing so hard you're crying face.
They just clicked that.
So I don't think that the comment was maybe well received.
Would have gotten that Oscar, I think.
That would have overcome it.
You would have played that grueling part.
What's the name of the character?
Oh, God. Let me look it up.
Carton Myrtle?
Is it Carton Myrtle?
It's pretty close.
I knew it.
Carton Myrtle.
This is the phrase.
So he's doing it for the charity Save the Children, which is not the QAnon affiliated Save the Children.
This did exist before.
And also that this charity is constantly been like QAnon, please stop using the phrase Save the Children.
You're distracting from our charity Save the Children, who do save children.
But the quote is, by making the moon disappear, the magician will show that no challenge is impossible to overcome.
Quote, if one person can make the moon disappear from the sky, imagine how together we can make poverty, hunger and danger disappear for children on Earth.
What?
Wait a minute.
I mean, it sounds nice.
However, some of those are kind of abstract concept.
Danger?
Fully danger is going to be gone for all children on Earth.
Danger is also like there's light sockets in your house.
Danger is not necessarily, you know, a wide, it doesn't have to do with like nations warring.
I'm picturing like a cane toads scenario, like in Australia where they introduced cane toads and then they had no natural predators.
So what if March 1st we wake up and children all over the world have no more danger at all?
They're just like immortal.
The moon is gone and children are thriving worldwide.
They cannot be killed by anything.
Yeah.
I wake up to find my toddler son saying, look, daddy, and he takes a steak knife and runs it along his own forehead and he doesn't bleed.
Ouch. Thank you.
This is a Stephen King novel being ready to happen.
Fear is the mind killer.
Pain is for cowards.
It feels very Epcot Millennials celebration of like all the big puppets and they're all, everyone's singing in gibberish.
But it's like it's we combined all languages of the world.
So it's no language in every way.
It's like, what are you talking about?
So how do we go?
How do we watch this?
We're still waiting.
And again, this is breaking.
So we don't know details.
We don't know where it's going to be.
We don't know how you can attend.
And we were asking questions and then Jason said there's a whole rigmarole apparently.
I feel like what I saw.
And again, it's crazy that we've all gotten different bits and pieces.
But I swear on the day show there like there will be a contest.
You will enter a contest and the winners will have their names drawn and they will get to watch this.
That's it?
At the MGM Grand.
Oh it is at the MGM Grand?
I think it's happening.
Yeah, I think there's.
Wait, really?
I think it's happening there.
Doesn't the theater though feel too.
No, I think they're building something outside.
I think maybe they're building stands.
Wet Republic.
You'll be aware.
So you can do the VIP.
You can watch it from a Jacuzzi.
But I am not a hundred percent.
I think it's yet to be revealed.
If I'm at the Cosmo, does the moon disappear?
Or do I.
You have to see it from the MGM Grand?
I have to see it from exactly where David wants me to sit.
Does that imply that how he's able to pull this off?
That if I'm just down the stairs, if I'm up on top of the Trump Hotel, that the moon does not disappear for me.
I've been on the roof of a hotel in Rovinja, Croatia.
Is the moonshine on me or is it David Copperfield taking it from me there as well?
Well, you need to be the test.
You need to go back to Croatia if you don't win the sweepstakes.
Guys, I've been to Croatia.
Do you think this is a reaction to the success of the Sphere?
Do you think he's trying?
Sphere is all the talk of Las Vegas.
My question is, is the Sphere involved in this in some way?
Will it be like the build up to the David Copperfield weekend?
Will it be a Copperfield thing in the Sphere?
How does he feel about Dolan?
He probably is upset that he...
Oh, sorry.
I was going to say one thing Dolan and Copperfield probably have in common, probably, allegedly,
took the Lolita Express, allegedly, probably, with Harvey Weinstein.
I think they at least both would have gotten the invite.
They would have been on the short list.
They don't know Harvey Weinstein, probably, allegedly.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Copperfield should have done a magic trick to atone, to apologize for.
How can I via a trick say I'm sorry for knowing Harvey Weinstein?
His little trick called.
Copperfield has probably been on the Lolita like starship to the moon.
Like a spacecraft.
Why would he think he's making the moon disappear?
No moon.
No evidence.
Cover the tracks.
Make the tracks disappear.
Little St. James, there's a moon base for it.
I think in the dying embers of Twitter, I feel like I should have said this,
but I swear I saw someone defend like Eric Adams or someone not worth defending.
Like was in the Little Black Book, the Rolodex.
That had dozens and dozens of names.
And someone went, Hey, everyone was in that little black book.
And it's like.
OK, the book is different than the flight.
The book is different than the flight.
I just want to make that clear.
And you need to make that clear because.
Because Jimmy Buffett is in the book.
Everyone was in the book.
Jason, they're right.
And I'm in the book.
Oh, right.
Eva Anderson is in the book.
I forgot.
The other Eva Anderson.
David Copperfield.
Right.
So we don't.
Wait a minute.
He's Jesus.
He said, I don't really.
There's a longer article.
I'm trying to find where it's happening.
It says the MGM Grand headliner, but that doesn't necessarily mean I don't know where it's going to be.
But he the quote Copperfield, my secrets are on the moon.
Remember that?
He said this.
I'm scared of that.
I think he did an illusion where he wrote something on the moon.
Oh, you're right.
Next paragraph.
Yep.
To remind some of Copperfield's techniques that were etched into nickel plates as part of Arch Mission Foundation's lunar library crash landed on the moon in April 2019.
So he.
Remember that.
Nickel plating that contains how he does his tricks and maybe some other things from his personal life that he wanted not to be on earth anymore.
Jason, you're right.
Wow.
He's put evidence on the moon and now he's going to make it disappear.
And how do you think I know?
Well, I guess it's time for me to disappear.
Oh, wow.
Oh my God.
So great.
Yes.
Well, we vow to clearly it's not in our control to say that we will be there.
That will be the official reporters on the ground.
But rest assured, we will us and presumably Jason Warner will do anything in our power to be there, to be as close to the action as we can.
We could.
I mean, if we don't like we should show up and see if we get in, even if we don't win a contest.
You check your way into this.
That's what I'm thinking.
Check your way into the disappeared moon.
Walk with confidence.
Yeah.
I wonder how like people aren't going to flock to Las Vegas for this.
I don't think like I'm not no offense to David, but it's not exactly like.
The sphere.
Or that race that happened.
The F1 race.
The F1 that's ruining everyone's lives in Vegas right now.
It's such a pain in the ass walking around there.
It's such a pain in the ass.
Even more than it already is a pain in the ass to walk around Las Vegas.
The blocking the view from the sidewalks and the foot bridges is so funny.
We made so many when we went to Vegas just a couple of weeks ago, we made so many mistakes going places and then it's like, no F1 is blocking.
Yeah.
Like it's really a shitty situation.
It would be cost less for us to go to see the moon disappear than it would was to meet Martin Ravenhill.
That's true.
Also, but F1, they have been slashing prices because I was getting MGM like get exclusive seats at the Bellagio and this and that to get starting at $12,000.
And it said must buy hotel room.
So that did not include your hotel.
Oh my God.
Places have already been slashing prices because I think some Vegas news channel was already saying there are flights into Vegas with no tickets sold that weekend.
Really?
Because the high rollers are like, I am staying away.
This sounds like hell.
When is this happening?
November.
At some point in November or December.
Right at the beginning.
It's soon.
It's very soon.
I can give you guys just the feeling of it.
I'm closing my eyes imagining it.
And then so then that for like three hours.
Yeah, it's something like 80 laps.
I think 80 or 90 laps.
It goes past the fountains and stuff.
It goes past the fountains which are blocked by Grand Sands right now.
Oh my God.
So you won't be able to, yeah.
Well, okay, so there's going to be a lot of like, you know, black fabric that blocks stuff around the Vegas area.
Do we think that Copperfield is going to buy this wholesale and string it up in the sky and maybe that's how the moon will disappear?
I don't know how David Copperfield does his tricks.
If he's been thinking about this for 30 years, it better be not just some black fabric in front of your face.
I feel like it'll be better than that.
I don't know what he's going to do.
I hope so.
But in person it's got to be.
It's also such a rare opportunity.
Apparently he has not done one of these since 2001.
Tornado of fire.
It invoked moon effects.
That's a meaningless phrase.
He thinks about the moon a lot.
Wow.
He lives with an extraterrestrial.
Oh my God.
Will he be involved in it?
Is he Dick Tracy?
Oh yeah.
Oh wow.
Will a moon maid be part of the scheme?
Oh my God.
Well, we're really going to follow every step of this and then of course keep reporting on the new beautiful world where there is no more poverty and hunger and danger, at least for children.
I assume he's got to do one thing at a time.
First, disappear the moon.
Second, make it disappear for children.
Then hopefully for us.
But I'll wait for children again.
Is it a Logan's Run scenario?
Yeah, yeah.
There might be an age cap at first.
If you become an adult, like, oh, it's like Hunger Games for you.
It's like Purge for you.
Danger.
Release the danger.
It's fair.
Look, I want no danger for my kid.
And if Copperfield's the man to do it, then I thank him.
Okay.
Well, that's very exciting.
Hopefully some more stuff to come in February.
Here now, not in October, actually.
I think it's coming out November 1st.
But we've finished kind of the official Halloween season.
And I was curious, Evil.
Probably the last one.
No.
I had to recur it one more time.
I feel like you've presumably done some, like, off the beaten path and strange things in this season of Haunts.
Is there anything you want to name check or mention about your October 2023?
Well, first of all, I just want to say one of the best Haunts I went to, I went to last night when recording.
It was the last night of the LA County High School for the Arts.
Double Haunt night where it's a Haunt at the high school cost $25 entirely, like, designed by and starring high schoolers.
Teens.
But it was so great.
Like this year, one of them was called The Mine and it was like an 1800s mine, like, disaster.
There were teenagers in the line being like, can you help me find my son?
And then you get in and they had built into the high school like a multiple room adventure where there was a Wendigo that was making people into cannibals.
And then there was another one with like a carnival that had like Siamese twins and like a crazy ventriloquist and kids on stilts in this like deranged carnival.
There was like all these crazy effects and sound design.
Really, really cool.
Every year they do it.
Guys, check out the Laksa Haunt.
Wow.
That's my new number one.
What part of town is that?
It's like just east of downtown.
It's inside Cal State LA is like where their campus is.
And it's cheap and like incredible.
It's just like their kids are so good.
There's something I very specifically want to talk about because it's a show I took you guys to.
Delusion.
We went to the Blue Blade years ago.
And I just want to say that this year, the show's in Pomona.
I went with a group of people, including Jason Walliner.
And the VIP ticket for Delusion this year was a hundred, I think it was either $130 or $160.
Either way, it was like a lot of money.
So it's basically a 45 minute show.
And what is it, by the way, the thing that like ties any Delusion together?
Like is it's different shows and themes?
There's a mythology about like, well, this one was supposed to be the culmination of all the Delusions where it's like the history of all the Delusions.
So there's monsters from previous Delusions.
They were using monsters.
Okay.
But the thing that was super crazy was that, how to explain, we were up in an attic.
They had taken one of our party away and they're like, I'm kidnapping her and you'll get her later.
And usually they usually kidnap like a character, one of you at some point.
And then it's like that person gets to have their own side adventure and then comes back to your group.
That happened to me once. I got put on a gurney like in this Delusion and then I joined back up with the group.
They took away one of our friends.
Then we got chased around by this crab monster from the previous Delusion.
And the crab monster knocked over a piece of furniture that was very heavy and that like fell very close to me.
Like I pulled my hands away at the right moment, but it would have been quite bad if this thing had hit me.
And so then we, the crab monster was like, and like, clearly no one knew it had hit something.
How do I acknowledge this in crab language?
Yeah, because he's like an upside down crab man.
But then we ran out, we ran, we went through multiple rooms.
We end the show, we have the narration of like, and now the show is over and we go out into like the outside.
And this producer comes up and it's like, did the furniture hit anyone?
And I'm like, no, but our friend is still missing.
And then this producer goes, oh no.
And like gets on her mic, she's like, we figured out where that girl was from.
And this member of our group had been in a closet, just a dark closet the whole time and never, no one ever came and got her.
And she missed the end of the show.
She missed the 30 minutes of the show.
Wow.
And just heard the murmurs of what everybody else was doing.
Just heard other people going through Delusion.
Wow.
And probably at least for a while was like, wow, they're really committing to this.
I guess that not only am I kidnapped, I got to do it for a long time.
Exactly.
But then by minute 20, probably.
Playing wordle on your phone.
At least I got my phone on me.
I can check my sites.
So I needed to talk about that because I don't think Delusion should be losing people in closets if the price point is that high, is my point.
Losing adults.
Because you're supposed to like find her, right?
Somebody's supposed to like lead you to her and then you rescue her, I assume.
Or we go to another room and she's back out or you find her in the next room.
I think maybe the knocking over the furniture might have thrown everything out like into chaos because that clearly was not supposed to happen.
Because I did go, have you guys ever lost someone before?
And the producer goes like, no.
And I went, has the furniture fell over before?
And she goes, no, you're special.
Wow.
Whoa.
You didn't even know the half how special you were.
I also did not offer a refund to the person that was in the closet.
Really?
She paid that much money to be in a closet.
They just said she could come back to Pomona and do it again.
So that's all I want to say about Delusion, a show I took you guys to.
Just for future reference, that did happen.
Is this the show with Manny Manners, the little puppet boy?
Yes, Manny Manners was back and you couldn't hear him very well.
He was like.
Jason's voice at the start of the show.
Oh yeah.
Oh, is that Manny Manners?
Yeah.
Anyway, that's all I had to say that publicly at the end of the season to be like, shame on Delusion.
Yeah, yeah.
It does come up as it'll be the shorthand sometimes, especially in these haunt guest episodes for something that's very immersive and cool.
And I think Delusion, Delusion is cool.
But now I guess it has to be the shorthand for when it dulcer laws.
The Lolli County High School of the Arts Haunt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So they get the name check as the ultimate from now on.
I'm glad you didn't get locked in there.
I'm glad you were not stuck in a closet so that you could join us for this and join us for the event that we got to attend.
Jason didn't make this one, but Mike.
I didn't make it, but I'm so curious to hear about your experiences because I did find some ride throughs.
Oh, wow.
Go to Haunt Chronicle's Attractions 360 and Sharp Productions.
They hit up all the haunts and there's so many attractions in Southern California and around the country.
This was a very funny one to watch a quote unquote ride through.
Yeah, yeah.
I also feel like it's very important, Jason.
I was thinking about this, that one of us did not go.
Yeah.
Because I was thinking about, I'm going to quote, I just want to read something really quickly.
Let's just pull out a very thick book.
I'm reading from the HP Lovecraft's Great Tales of Terror.
Oh.
Because I was trying to figure out what to say about this haunt before we get into it.
And this to quote the Call of Cthulhu.
The most merciful thing in the world, I think, is the inability of the human mind to correlate all its contents.
The sciences, each straining in its own direction, have hitherto harmed us little.
But someday the piecing together of dissociated knowledge will open up such terrifying vices of reality
and of our frightful position therein that we shall either go mad from the revelation
or flee from the deadly light into the peace and safety of a new dark age.
Because I do think what we're about to talk about is enough to drive one mad.
Yeah.
And the fact that we need to have a neutral party to make sure that we haven't completely like...
Like a mediator.
We're not a mediator, I'm an observer.
Yeah, just to know that what we saw was not the way the world is.
Yes, things are still happening on the outside.
That phone book size compilation was what I was trying to get people to vote to make Mike read.
It is so weird.
Oh, right. Yeah, nobody bit on that really, no.
Mike, do you not like racism?
No, no.
And then I found the YA genre book that the director of the Tower of Terror movie wrote.
I found it at the Burbank Library and discovered it is 336 pages.
Whoa.
So also kind of long.
So that's what you would like to have to read for the next couple...
I ended up reading and thankfully neither person bit on either of that.
Well, there's always next month.
Oh, yeah, sure.
What we're talking about today, the haunted car wash, and thank you for that proper prologue.
That was beautiful.
Haunted, the haunted car wash.
I mean, this is a genre that exists and these happen I think throughout the country,
but we went to one specifically in Anaheim.
Some of the backstory here, if you aren't on Club 3,
this I think grew our interest and awareness of this grew out of one of the first Club 3 episodes
where the listeners requested that Eva get to talk about whatever she wanted.
You wisely show us themed car washes and alerted us to a fantastic area
that caused me to go to Campbell, California and have one of the best days of my life legitimately.
And it certainly kept the world of themed car washes on my mind and hopefully some of the listeners as well.
So it's a bit of a sequel because during that episode, I think there was the discovery that there is the,
like theme parks, there is the horror and haunt equivalent of the themed car wash.
There are overlays for car washes.
Yeah, they do holiday overlays.
Christmas, I don't know. They should. I would love it.
The foam could be snow.
That's true.
Halloween is what we know about.
There are haunted car washes, but I didn't know where they were and how close to us they were.
And I was so delighted when you said several weeks ago, pretty close,
Anaheim in the backyard of Disneyland and jumped on it.
So excited to do it.
It's part of the one that we did.
I think the haunted car wash, which straddles a couple of car wash brands.
This is one in Anaheim and there's one in Lakewood, I believe.
So that's what we checked out a few nights ago.
And where to begin?
I mean, like, should we discuss our expectations?
Did anybody have an idea of what you thought it might be?
I will say my one thing. Every time I saw the trailer for this, I was like,
so I assume that they're just using the car wash as a tunnel
and that you do not get your car washed at the haunted car wash because it only costs $50.
And so just hiding people in the tunnel of the car wash and them bothering you
while you go through it, especially if you're on the rails,
then that seems like a great ride vehicle for you to get scared.
That was always my impression of like, this must be what the haunted car wash is.
They turn it all off and then it's just, it's a different thing that they can do.
It's a tunnel of love or fear, if you will. Right?
Yes.
That's what I was like, assuming we would be going to.
Yeah, yeah. And that the experience would take place in this kind of cave or tunnel-like environment,
like a re-themed situation.
I think we quickly discovered that the experience spills out in front of the building.
Yes.
And honestly, the experience begins, you know, probably a block and a half away
because you immediately encounter a lot of traffic, a ton of cars.
A backup.
Yes, a big backup around the block.
And this is the big question I had driving up was like,
will this be a thing where they're like, oh, thanks for doing it.
We appreciate it. Wow. So people came and did this and I'm so glad that you could.
The opposite. It was so crowded.
This is one of the most successful endeavors I've witnessed recently.
When I drove up, I was like, oh, is there an in-and-out around here?
Like that's the line of traffic.
Exactly.
That's what it reminds you of if you've ever been to the West Coast staple.
We all had to park separately and get into Scott's car,
which was parked in a parking lot that was in the middle of kind of like the corner where the line was winding around.
Yes, I somehow ended up exactly boxed in into a tiny strip mall parking lot
because I was like, OK, we can all get in one car and consolidate so we don't have to do separate tickets for this.
So I just on Street View was like, well, probably this little Caesar's parking lot will be a fine place to meet.
And then discovered that it was completely boxed in by very much traffic.
Yet somehow I snuck in there. I was the only I don't know.
I turned left over to it.
So I ended up kind of like skipping some of that line.
People were probably mad at me because they thought I was.
But I'm like, no, I'm not.
Later, I will be going to the haunted car.
I'm going to the boxed in Little Caesar's.
I want a hot and ready five dollar pizza for dinner.
I'm going to eat it in my car by myself.
Let me get the pizza.
You joke. But Little Caesar's has really upped their game rates.
Really? I haven't done it.
What do you mean?
I had a reaction.
I now live by a little close to a Little Caesar's.
Really?
Yeah. I'll tell you.
Tell me where your address is in there.
No, I'm not.
There are a number of them in the Southland, of course, and in the San Fernando Valley, especially.
And, you know, moving so many times we were tired and like, let's get a Little Caesar's.
And we're like, this is really good dinner.
How many times did you get a Little Caesar's in a month?
During the move, I think we went like three times in a month, two or three times.
Is it still five dollar hot and ready? Is that the deal?
It's like six.
And they only keep pepperonis hot and ready.
Cheese, you have to wait for.
So cheese is hot and ready?
Why wouldn't they have cheese and pepperoni?
At least at this location.
The other thing is my mom had heard me talk about it a lot and she gave us some gift cards without scoring.
And we discovered the app does not have gift card abilities yet.
You have to go inside.
So do you order?
Just wait. Sorry to cut ahead in the question line.
Yeah, it's OK.
You continue to frequent this place despite them not taking coupons and the biggest pizza genre not being hot or ready.
I'm ready, but we always call the head to begin with.
OK, so you weren't actually going in there unannounced and doing a hot and ready.
You were ordering ahead of time.
It was just Jane noticed.
I think once she tried to go in and pick it up and they're like, oh, only the pepperoni is hot and ready.
You have to wait a couple of minutes for the cheese.
So they were making your pizza hot and ready for just you.
They had a Little Ceasar's Day in my high school that has Simon game where you play Simon.
And if you got up to a certain level, you got free crazy bread.
Really?
And then if it went very hard, like it got very hard and you could get up to like a hot and ready pizza for free.
The game was free and we realized my best friend in high school and I realized very early that you could get to crazy bread pretty easily.
And we did it every day until they took the Simon game out of the little.
Because we could just go in there and each get a free crazy bread and walk out with it.
Wow.
We didn't have to pay any money.
That's wild.
It wasn't even with an order.
No, you're just one hundred and stealing crazy bread from Little Caesar's.
I am wondering if modern day teenagers are like the teenagers when we were teenagers and would go to a place and either use a freebie coupon or just order fries or just order coffee and just post up for two hours.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I think they are.
I think so.
Yes.
Mel's Diner.
We respect these businesses and chains and we give them the money they deserve.
That's our generation.
I don't know that some of these businesses have stuck around.
Some of the funniest stuff during lockdown was like this terrible diner has to close because of lockdown measures.
And it's like the reviews are like food is so expensive and it tastes like shit.
No, lockdown.
They don't even give me anything when I play Simon really good.
Interestingly, though, one thing that was created in lockdown haunted car wash.
Yes.
That's good context to mention, which I kind of forgot because there's nothing I guess when you think about it inherently pandemicy about it.
But I guess when you like, yeah, OK, when you think about it as like a sealed environment.
Yeah.
Or it's like an equivalent of some of the drive through Christmas drive through dinosaurs.
And I found all of them extremely depressing.
Yes.
When I when I said I was doing this, I remember telling friend of the show Andrew Grissom and he was like, did you ever think in the year when in 2020, did you flash to years later in twenty twenty three that you would be attending a drive through haunt in a car wash?
I thought, yeah, boy, when you think about it that and that I'd be like excited about it.
But I think this is one of the things that has maybe transcended the genre of pandemic drive through experience.
If the lion's any indication on a Thursday night.
Yes. Yeah.
Oh, I shudder on a Friday or a Saturday.
And the later you get, the more expensive.
If you ever want to do one of these, try to hit it like as soon as it gets dark or cheaper.
I wonder, though, if it sort of grew from its origin, because, you know, pandemic year, they might not have been as aggressive in certain areas as they were in twenty twenty three.
If you know what I'm saying.
Yes.
Well, yes, we will.
This is a tease.
There are certain things that could not have been done in twenty twenty that would have gotten to would have ended the business, would have gone viral.
This is so exciting.
This is are I think the answers to questions I have.
But I've been biting my tongue so hard.
I'm like, oh, I can't ask this question yet because I want to give anything away.
You know what I was thinking, too, because, you know, Scott is starting to, you know, like a like a flower.
He's sort of opening up now.
Like a black flower with lots of thorns that bleed.
He is kind of opening up.
And this is the second time this month that he's done something.
But I thought this would be a perfect this would have been a perfect time.
Maybe next year we get you in the haunted car wash because this is a good, I feel like, first haunt because you get to be in sort of a comfortable place.
Is it?
Yeah, well, he's going to have to assess.
Yeah.
We'll ask you at the end if you feel that way.
That's a good way to frame this.
Can we sell you on if you want to do this?
Or should we?
Yes, we'll see at the end.
We'll see at the end.
Nay, should we?
So, so yeah, I was immediately distressed that the place that I had picked like, hey, friends, you know what?
We can all meet in this one parking lot and that should be fine.
It was the opposite of fine.
It was completely surrounded on all sides.
We had to pivot and go to the most hoppin' bowling alley I've ever seen in my life.
Oh, this bowling alley rules.
I was salivating just thinking I should show you a flower.
Oh, god, I wish we could have hung out longer.
Do you remember the name of the lounge?
I didn't take pictures.
It was cool.
It was a cool name. It was a cool sign.
This is like the real Anaheim, I think.
It's like 80 years old or something.
Those are the best bars and lounges.
Yes.
Bowling alleys are so cool.
It was a super like double bowling alley.
You had bowling alleys on both sides of the bowling alley.
That's great.
Was there like 60 lanes?
Yeah, and a cocktail bar.
Oh, my god.
That was rad.
One of my favorite places in LA is Chateau Lanes in Koreatown.
Incredible.
It's so many lanes, a snack bar, a big arcade, a bar that has never updated.
The wall is mostly stonework that was very popular, I don't know, mid-60s.
Yeah, definitely.
And it's just stuck around.
The stuff that gets like stripped out when everybody does like their Property Brothers
like landifying of houses.
It's a crime that things like that get yanked out of.
Chateau Lanes is awesome.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I had a photo of it somewhere.
So anyways, that didn't work.
But then it led us to this bowling alley where I'd like to go back to at some point in time.
And then we had to go back over, get in my car, in that parking lot.
And then we're like, well, now can we kind of cut?
Now can we kind of get ahead in the line?
And I tried to pull out and the guys directed me.
And then I'm like, I am going to this.
I have a ticket and he's like, I'm not even done with the sentence.
And the guy directing traffic, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You go back. You go back.
You back up. You go back.
And so now I have to find another spot to like to cut.
And I didn't mean to be cutting.
I didn't know I was getting in a cut position.
Yeah.
Well, that, I mean, the first time I was trying to cut.
I get right.
First time I wasn't trying to cut.
Second time I was third time.
I just, I need to get out for, you know, anyway, no matter what to go live my life.
But yes, I'm going to the, but I was so stressed out in that, like trying to get somebody and we're judging what cars like.
We get mad at us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What seems like a slightly weaker car that will let me in?
Yeah. As if the cars were from the movie Cars and we were judging them by who had the most muscle.
They would have the personality.
I said the Escalade.
No, we can't cut in front of the Escalade.
Absolutely not.
So we cut in right behind the Escalade and then the Escalade was in front of us for what transpired.
Oh my God.
And then we realized the Escalade was just full of little children.
And that there was a mermaid mom who loves mermaids.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
She had a mermaid license plate and mermaid stickers.
Oh boy.
Wait, wait, Jason, I know you're heading for something.
Sorry.
A mermaid mom leads to another point.
This is in the period of time where we were sort of caught in traffic and waiting for things to get a little more exciting.
There wasn't much to do or much to look at.
But a couple things caught our eye.
One was this license plate that we're trying to parse.
It's like MRD and MD and is it a doctor?
And we knew mom, but what is the rest?
And then the frame around it had further, it was like my other car is a shell or something.
So like, oh wait, that means mermaid.
Okay.
So it's a mermaid thing.
And then Mike, the most matter of fact, the most like earnest you could have possibly been, you said, oh, okay, so it must be like a Jimmy Buffett fan.
And then conversation kept going.
And like much like on the show, I said, whoa, whoa, whoa, back up.
So because a mom has a license plate that refers to mermaids, the only possibility is that this is a Jimmy Buffett fan.
Well, she's a fan of the ocean and she's a fan of like that type of like iconography, I assume.
I was going to say there's some mermaid iconography in the Parrothead.
Of course.
Extending universe.
Okay.
But now let me as a parrot head lay person, as a Parrothead lay person, I only know some of this from what you guys talk about.
I don't know any what the mermaid songs are.
None of them are famous.
And I maintain that 90 percent of Jimmy Buffett fans know the three famous songs and that is all.
Even if even people who would say I'm a hardcore.
Six who know the six songs they know probably.
I think you're underestimating them.
They know six ish.
They know.
Okay.
And I'm a light fan like Joe Biden knows three and then a expanded fan knows six.
Yes, exactly.
Okay.
But I that just seemed so then that like well there's no other media certainly with mermaids.
What other famous mermaid movie or anything is there that maybe the mom is referencing?
I couldn't think of any.
The other thing and I'll get back to where you were going, Jason.
We had not much to look at when we were kind of in that stall there.
So we're talking about mermaid mom and then there was the sign next to us that was for the detailing part of the business.
Oh, yes.
Now there was an accent that we kind of missed because it was framed as a line and it was not so clearly an accent.
So we realized this is this is a last name.
But we're just looking at the letters P E N A S and just the only way we could say it out loud.
P P NOS P NOS.
P NOS.
I just said penis.
Penis detailing.
Yeah.
Okay.
So we're thinking about penis.
We're thinking about mermaid moms.
Yeah.
Anyway, back to what you were saying.
What I was going to say, the aggressive guy directing traffic.
I think two of the big sources of anxiety for all those drive thru attractions that we did a few years ago.
One is the actors or employees just wandering around moving cars and, you know, seasonal hires or a few week hires.
That was very stressful.
Like driving car very slowly and there's people walking around you.
I think the even bigger piece of stress was the people directing traffic who aren't pros at doing that.
They were like learning on the job and he's getting to them.
Yes.
And they're right.
They're right to be aggravated by this.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, I was because I watched the same guy try to kick other cutters out of line.
I was I was glad that there was somebody laying down the street.
There's no they didn't build a lane for this.
No.
On the actual street.
No, no one anticipated the incredible part.
The beetle like popularity of the car was the right turn lane is completely consumed by this line.
Someone just wanted to get their five dollar pepperoni hot and ready.
And they did it.
And they could.
And they can't for a month.
Yeah.
And somebody came thinking there would be cheese ready and there wasn't.
There was no cheese.
Pepperoni.
The only applies to pepperoni.
Yeah.
So we do we do get in line eventually and realizing a weird in it.
This is going to take a while.
It's moving very slowly.
Once we finally get to one of the stressed out youngsters, scanning tickets and such, there's a really quick rundown of the policies and just, you know, turn your lights off and directed us to the radio station that you that goes along with the thing.
And then really quick tossed off unlock your doors if you want them to come in lock them if you don't.
OK, so as if that's not something that is blown.
Jason has made a face as if he just like got as stressed out as if that were he was actually in the moment.
I think the answer is Jason.
Well, I didn't know if that was a thing that you could customize.
Yes, because I was watching video of them getting people's cars.
Yeah.
And I'm like, I think for safety, I if I go through regular car wash, I make sure it's in the parking lot.
I make sure it's in the correct gear.
They tell you I locked the doors.
I make sure the windows are up.
So, yeah, the unlocked doors.
I had a lot of questions about the line leading into the car wash.
Yeah, you're not in the actual car yet.
Watch is.
But how do you think we went?
What do you think happened?
Yeah.
I think you likely unlock the doors and maybe a window or two down as you were maybe as you were going.
I'll put it down.
Let me just put this thought into your mind.
Yeah.
Each door can have a separate unlock or lock function.
Can I ask where Scott?
I assume you're driving.
Yes.
Where were you guys?
I was in the back with the baby seat.
No baby in it.
No, you're right.
Thank God.
We did not take a baby to this.
And he was in the passenger seat.
And you were in the passenger seat.
Yes.
OK.
And I've ridden in your car with the baby seat.
You gave us a ride back after the dynasty shows.
You're familiar with the seat.
I'm familiar with the seat, which adds a very funny complication to the unlocked doors and
what comes after the unlocked doors.
Do you want to guess who locked who?
I guess that Scott locked the door.
I think Eva unlocked the back door quickly and bike put the window down.
What about the door?
Was it locked or unlocked?
I'm going to say unlocked for the sake of being a Fee Park journalist.
Nailed it.
You did nail it.
You nailed my rationale as well.
Yeah.
Look, you're right.
I am blossoming into the thorny rose who loves haunts.
However, people coming into my car, this is an entire other level.
I am taking baby steps.
I don't think Jason should have been driving, but I do think he should have been in the back seat of the car.
Because this would have been a really deep end as far as haunts.
Yeah, it would have been a deep end.
And I would have flocked all the doors.
Yes.
And I don't think there's anything wrong with it.
I don't think there's anything.
We recorded a lot of this and I filmed a lot of videos of it.
And my voice is edgy.
I watched them all back.
I am right into precarious.
No, no, no.
That's what I say at every haunt.
And that's what I was saying at this.
I understand fun peer pressure, but I'm sorry.
I don't want these people going.
It's my car, damn it.
You guys speculating about people being in the tunnel, whether the car wash is on or off, to be revealed.
Flash me back to doing the dinosaur themed car wash.
And I was like, all right, got to be very careful.
Got to get on track correctly.
You got to make sure I'm in the right gear.
I mean, I have an automatic car, but they tell you like, oh, put in neutral sometimes.
You were sort of it was unclear whether you were going to do this in general.
But as soon as the idea came up, you said, not driving real fast.
No, I you would have run over someone.
That was my fear.
I drive through Six Flags or drive through Trick or Treat.
I'm like, I am going to my foot is going to slip.
I'm going to plow into class twisted.
If you were like in Don Knotts level nervousness mode, it would be very easy to accidentally drive over someone's foot.
Yeah. It really was shockingly easier than I even thought it would be.
And can we talk about just what exactly the second we got into line, like inside the car wash line with scare actors, what happened that something went wrong?
Something was wrong.
Yes. So the delay where we're just talking about what we can see around us,
that's partially because we were there for a while and we realized we're past the ticket point and we're not in the street anymore.
We're sitting there and like no cars are coming out.
We haven't seen one car come up because we're trying to figure out do they wash the cars or not?
Right. And we have nothing to support evidence on either side because no cars coming out wet or dry.
But we are seeing managers having very tense conversations.
A lot of movement among sort of non-cloth like non-costumed people.
Non-psycho clowns.
But then also we are seeing psycho clowns go and examine what's happening.
Casually.
Yeah. Casually is the word.
Or like their posture is certainly not in scare mode.
They are also going to see if they can help or they can do something or they're waiting for something to happen.
And then we're seeing this multiple people back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
There's a security guard that's wandering who I believe has a gun.
We noticed that.
Yeah, I was going to say a gun was in play at the haunted car.
We are now in the scare zone.
We've entered the scare zone and now we are, everything is broken down.
But they also are not quite scaring us yet because we're still too close to the street.
Too close to the sidewalk, yeah.
So we're not really getting our entertainment other than the radio station that I have tuned to,
which is pretty much like scary drones, but then sometimes like a big shriek or spike.
Like it's a lot of just like, vroom, vroom, jing!
And then suddenly a giant one.
Like a knife sound effect.
Which did was, I liked that.
I liked that.
And then it was a little staticky because it's like a local broadcast radio station.
That was effectively creepy and gave it a tone.
That is a radio station they told you to tune to?
Yeah, that was a sign.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it sounds like it was like in film school when you would have to go to the quote unquote equipment cage
and get like sound effect CDs.
Yes.
And it was just, it was like, okay, that's a screaming band.
That's the Wilhelm scream.
Yep.
That's a spooky wind.
That's a Frankenstein.
But it's just played on a loop on this radio station.
Yes.
Yes, yeah.
It's more like a drive-in movie.
Okay.
But I thought this was, I think this was Trent Reznor level sound immersion.
I thought this was done expertly.
Yeah.
And I've plopped into it.
Sphere quality.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes, sphere audio quality.
I feel like eventually one car somehow exits and we get in one car enough that we're in the scare zone.
Yeah.
There was not a problem despite, you were reading a lot into things.
At one point you referred to like several of the employees have joined arms.
They are, I feel like you were flashing to like somebody died in there.
Were you actually thinking about that?
That like, did it happen?
Did somebody's foot get run over?
It doesn't seem.
It's not plausible.
With what we know now, that seems like it might happen every night.
Right.
Yeah, yeah.
It seems like.
I don't think I thought anyone was dead because I think there would have been a lot more like
traffic.
There would have been more people running and a lot of like panic.
Okay, question two.
Did you see an ambulance at all?
No.
I've been at enough theme parks.
I have seen an ambulance pull up or stretcher go by.
Kind of puts, makes you, I feel like at a Six Flags or like Hershey, like people, if someone gets heat stroke or someone like falls, they are usually security is like, oh, we have to call 911.
We have to call or at least the local, you know, nurses on staff have to come and check on a person.
I don't know that this infrastructure is necessarily there at the haunted car wash.
Do you think that they have a nurse on staff at the car wash?
No, I don't.
But I think in an emergency, they would just call 911 and an ambulance and a fire truck would legally show up.
And then they'd have to get in the line though.
And they'd get in the line!
We're trying.
Who do we owe?
We can't get past the escalator.
Claw, claw, claw.
No, sir, we're trying to get to the woman that passed out.
We're not a themed vehicle.
We are actual ambulance.
And it's like taking the fibulators off the shelf.
Anyway, everything's fine.
No one was crushed.
It's not in our hour.
We were stuck in this zone for almost, I think, 45 minutes.
That was most of the time was looking at all these people trying to figure out what was going on.
Yeah.
But we eventually get into the territory where we are starting to get scared.
And you see, you know, really this whole thing, this should be called the haunted car wash line.
Yes.
Really what is being haunted much more so than the car wash itself is the line of cars while you wait to get into the car wash.
So it's like there's two rows of cars and characters are marching back and forth and kind of stalking and like running their heads across creepy and maybe clawing.
And then and like maybe lunging at a car with like a big axe and you think they're going to smash the window, but they pull it back right onto.
And this is this is a creepy scene.
It's a creepy scene up ahead of you.
Even before they're at your car, there's there's fog going.
There's scary lights.
There's definitely like they are.
They've established some kind of like zombie apocalypse vibes at school.
So, you know, when you're in an in and out and they have a couple of employees that are just like a little bit ahead of the line versus actually the box, that's sort of what's happening here.
There's a couple of clowns that are like they're all clowns, by the way.
So we have to say yes, I did pick that up from the writer.
There are various forms of clowns.
And do you do you have the text of the sign that said like tunnel of terror?
I think you said this on a video that it says tunnel of terror, but then terrors crossed out and it says wasteland.
Okay.
It's a tunnel of wasteland.
So why would they're so different?
Kind of a lateral move.
Why are they correcting terror?
It's a terror out of it.
Is populated by clowns.
By clowns.
Yes.
We were in the time we had to wait.
We were discussing what is the story of this and the story that I had maybe in my head, I was thinking this is going to be like a zombie thing.
And then once we actually saw the characters it became clear this is clowns.
There are not zombies.
It's entirely clowns.
But the surroundings are not like dark fun house style.
There's no theming beyond the clowns.
No.
Yeah.
The theme is some clowns and a sign that says terror, tunnel of wasteland.
Tunnel of wasteland.
So we inch forward bit by bit.
It'll go ahead one car at a time.
And something I learned about my car is that every time you inch forward and then stop it again or put it into park, then everything unlocks.
And thus I have to like quickly lock the door and I'm like, oh, my gosh, I'm going to be a big star.
So we're going to have to do that.
I'm going to be a big star.
And then it's going to be like a big star.
Or put it into park, then everything unlocks.
And thus I have to like quickly lock, lock, lock.
And you might get concerned that, well, if they're going to check your door and see that it's locked and then they're not going to go in our doors, which are unlocked.
Then they're not going to go in our doors, which are unlocked.
But then I just said well, then that is up to the individual clown.
It is up to them to check every door handle themselves.
Individuals are allowed to make decisions.
It's why all parents can lock some doors and not all.
So I found my and I had to show you how to make sure.
No, you pull it back that way.
Yes. Make sure yours is unlocked.
You do whatever you want.
And I was wrong because they thoroughly checked all the doors.
They did. They knew that maybe one door could be locked and one door could be open.
That first moment where they rattle because they started with mine.
Yeah. And that is a very unsettling moment.
And I'm glad that it worked.
I'm glad they didn't like pound and demand and points like no, no, no.
I did have agency in this.
Yeah. And I will say we they put the most aggressive clown up front.
Someone I showed a video to somebody of that clown and they said he was a terrifier.
Oh, yeah. Like art the of course.
He's like art the clown from last year's argument.
Art the clown from the argument.
And they really like no other clown matched his commitment to this.
Well, he the first thing that happened was he got he opened your door.
Yes. Leaned over you and was like, yeah.
So he literally invade your personal space.
We saw him doing this to the Escalade full of children.
He was just like sitting in there.
He would open the trunk and just get in the trunk with the kids.
Yeah. And the kids didn't seem that bothered.
They were excited. They're moving all around.
Yes. As more than multiple clout.
That was that felt like you're watching a car get torn apart.
Yes. There might have been three clowns getting into that one.
Yeah. And the kids are just like, no problem.
The kids did not care.
What I'm so afraid of.
A ton of kids are fine with.
But yes, the aggressive art the clown.
He got you first.
He got me. He opens the door.
He like gets in there.
He like invades my personal space pretty good.
And it becomes very clear to me very fast that this art the clown guy smells really bad.
He stinks.
This clown stinks.
And not like he's been doing the job for like eight hours and his body is just.
This is a body odor stink.
That's what I'm thinking.
Unless it was an outfit that hadn't been washed, which I think I compared this to the.
When Sacha Baron Cohen plays Borat, he's never washed that suit.
Oh, right.
So he wants to keep people.
So I was wondering, I don't know.
I like either this gentleman just maybe needed to put on deodorant or he's doing something to fuck with people.
I don't know the answer to it, but I immediately kind of pivot on my keep the door open.
Well, the smell was really bothering me.
I would say like out of every like maybe 12 times someone opened our door or did something to our car.
Yeah.
It was like 75 percent art the clown.
Yes.
He moved so fast he was back up and he's back again.
And like the other clowns, we got like one interaction with them and they were like 25 percent of the like aggressiveness of this art guy.
But then art would be back after they were back.
You would assume, well, art is he's done this car.
Now he's going to another car.
He's going to do his thing.
No arts back.
He's open.
Open my door again.
He came in my door.
He came over.
He leaned over the baby.
The child is called a baby seat.
I think that's why.
Yeah, yeah.
Child.
This also really disturbed me.
He wasn't there, but that seat is so much a part of my son's life and family.
Seeing a scary smelly clown just even near that seat.
That is pretty startling.
Really upset me.
I think the person is, I think I did have an anger.
I mean, this would have bothered me no matter what.
I think it would have bothered Jason too.
But it's not about it being my car.
I think that did just bug.
Like this is my item in the world.
And it's scary clowns all over it.
You're like, no, and you lock the trunk.
Well, I locked the trunk because my laptop was back there.
Once I saw that it was a possibility that the car ahead of us, they just popped in the trunk and then sat in it.
And I pictured them doing that exact same sit right onto my laptop.
And there are some people, some clowns of larger carriage who are working this job.
And my laptop would not stand a chance against some of the people who might sit down.
Did you tell me you have 61 unfinished screenplays on that laptop?
Yes, over 200 things that I've started.
A novel.
Anytime I try to explain like a Dropbox, I cloud.
He just like zones out and walks away.
He doesn't listen to cloud back.
I mean, I started like 13 versions of an update on Pepe Le Pew.
And every one of them could be gone.
The world will never get to see any of what could be my Star Wars.
You would have had to post like on Instagram, like help art.
The clown stole my laptop.
Yeah, get it back.
Yeah.
But hopefully one of my oldest friends or my oldest friends would go and actually talk to the clown and get it back.
If you don't know the ghoul we're talking about, whatever, this is an inside joke for you know, you know, you know, you know, the horrible man, you know, the world is broken.
It must have really, by the way, must have really bugged him to have to post on social media like that.
This guy does not like attention.
He likes to sit and do his work.
That's why he's a writer.
Yeah.
I got to say, watching video recaps of this experience, it felt like, do you guys know that Tim Robinson sketched the Pointer Brothers?
Yes.
I think it's on his characters, Netflix episode of the characters.
And so it's a bunch of people going to watch some entertainment.
It might be at a conference or something.
And like Tim Robinson and Connor Romali and another guy just come out and start pointing at audience members.
And a guy in the audience goes, that can't be what this is.
That is how I felt watching videos of this.
I was like, that can't be what this is.
When I realized what was the car wash in the background, the clowns in the line, I was like, oh no.
Why have the Tim Robinson flash when I was worried about my laptop back there.
I was thinking about Chunky.
Oh yeah, Chunky.
That's my laptop.
You had all summer.
Figure out what you do.
There's one thing though, because it wasn't all that it was, because a certain scare actor, I feel like, because we were in that scare line.
I would say 45 minutes.
I feel like that's the downtime we were in the scare line ish.
30 minutes.
I know because you had to pee, Mike, and you kept talking about it.
Yeah, I was stupid and didn't pee before we started.
And then that like breakdown.
That's why I had my eye on it so hard.
But it did make me feel like because of the long wait that Art the Clown felt the need to escalate things.
Art the Clown proceeded to do something that redefined what I understood about haunts in general.
And I think in this moment made the haunt for me.
Yes.
Yeah, let you know what is possible.
But made me satisfied with the experience.
Killed me too, yeah.
In an unexpected way that made me both disgusted and not delighted, but impressed.
Jason, can you guess what we might be saying?
Well, I have a guess based on a Dr. Clown clip I saw.
Okay.
But does, was it poop based?
Thank God, no.
No, no, no, no, no. Oh boy.
I mean you're in the realm of...
Correct.
But not that gross.
Just tell me because I have other things I've viewed.
Let me say a couple, let me do the first step.
Because I forgot that there were a couple iterations.
You knew that bodily things could be possible when a clown reached up their nose.
Well, that's this, right?
Is that this? Wait, wait, okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
He just did a gesture and yes.
The very first thing was reaching up into his nose.
That's right.
And then pulling out the contents and then making like a cross on my windshield.
I missed that.
The clown picked his nose.
Oh, he'd say he did that too?
Yes, he did both things.
That was the first one.
He picked his nose and made a cross on the windshield and right in front of me.
That was where you were sitting.
It was Scott's car which couldn't feel good, but it was right in front of me and very aggressive.
I still had the stench in my nose.
You had just gotten the stench and then you see a cross made of boogers.
Yeah.
And now I'm like, this thing better wash your car.
This entire thing does not end.
That's when I knew it did, I think.
Where you go, well, of course.
That's why you do that.
I was also worried that the cross made of boogers was some kind of weird signal.
Like these people are down for this.
He didn't balk at my smell.
He didn't throw up.
That means I can throw up on him.
But then he walked over to my window, tapped on the window, stuck his tongue out from the clown mask and licked the dirty car.
Wow.
Licked the window of the dirty car while we all watched.
A clown licked my car.
The unwashed.
A dirty, unwashed clown.
I forgot to say that part.
I was also hoping for a wash because even pre-clown booger, my car was dirty.
I was like, that would be a nice perk of this thing.
If I get an actual car wash, I need a car wash.
My car is specifically pretty dirty.
I've never seen something so vile in real life as the tongue of the art clown wiping across the dirty window.
This is beyond what I...
I said, man, I wish Jason was here.
But I was like, we need to be able to explain this to somebody.
We know we're not insane.
We all three produce the same memory.
He's a decorated survivor.
Scott, once we recorded a bunch of episodes back to back or something, we were working on something,
and I had a can of La Croix without thinking we were just talking and put it down on your roof.
And you're like, oh, can you put that on the ground or put it somewhere else?
I don't want water.
And I'm like, oh my God, I'm so sorry I wasn't even thinking.
It was nice of you to leave out all the profanities that I actually said.
That fucking can of piece of shit.
You called me a little pig.
You basically didn't hear Baldwin voicemail at me.
Do whatever you want.
Because I left a can of like your little pig soda, coconut La Croix on your roof for a second.
So I can't imagine.
I got very reasonable cross wearing like, oh, sorry, I wasn't thinking.
We recorded so long.
But a clown licking your window and picking up the filth.
And Eva, you say again, you have paid for like, oh, I'm going to crawl up to your house.
It is $80 because they're like a commando who thinks World War II is still going on.
You are disgusted by it.
It must have been so gross.
It felt spontaneous.
I felt like he was like, I've been doing I've been bothering these people for too long.
I've come back to this car too many times.
I've reached the level where I needed up the game before they go in.
Gigi Allen of haunt of scare act.
And none of the other clowns are behaving this way.
Wow.
Only art.
The clown was licking cars.
I don't want to correct you.
I think that it might have not been art.
I think that because I'm looking at a video, I think this is the video.
This is this is like this is like a bald.
No, that was that was.
That's you.
I thought this whole time you were referring to the the triple faced clown.
No, no, no, we're talking about the white, the white.
The triple faced clown.
I'll get to it.
The triple faced man did something along these lines, too.
So, you know, there's other gross outs.
You know, when I have it, why don't I play the moment?
We can hear how this actually played out, not see it because we didn't we
nobody had a camera in prime position.
But I can only admit, Eva, only you have to live with the scar of this
happening next to your head.
Yes.
OK.
Right. You could not drive.
You could drive. You could run over a guy.
You don't know.
I'm impressed with the lack of safety.
He's looking at your car.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Um, that conveys it.
I got so, so petulant.
So, no, my car even with the light of mine for one second.
And then like, yeah, you wake up the next morning.
You're like, oh, no, what have I done?
A little perspective on it goes a long way.
And then he came into the car.
Now he's over the car seat.
Ten seconds later, he's deep into the he's on the end.
This was I think he was scaring you.
I think I think like I think there's clowns on either side of you in this moment.
I become in that door, too.
He just had he was overstaying his welcome.
Yeah, much.
He was.
But he was moving around so fast.
Like, I feel he was giving everyone this kind of attention.
He was on.
Well, this is this is interesting that I, you know, because I actually was picturing
triple faced clown because I think he was I think he was pretty solid, too.
He did some great stuff, too.
And which here, why don't I play the moment of that?
And this I do have framed pretty nicely.
I didn't know I'd be in such a good position for it.
Here is the highlight of triple faced clown.
Yeah, that's right.
He just spit on the car.
Really?
Once you've even licked and snotted on the spit is like no problem.
Is it reciprocal?
Like that guy had your car in his exactly.
Yes.
Yeah.
My window was like in his body, essentially.
My dirty window.
They should have saved arts antics for like right before you went in because I did think,
holy shit, I didn't realize they could do this.
Now, what are we in for?
But nothing really.
But instead, it was like it was an early climax, unfortunately.
Yes.
And almost none of the performers were into it as much as that guy.
Just a car getting licked is imagery that I can't really.
Just a car getting licked is imagery that I can't really unsee in any context.
Just the mere fact and the phrase lick my car has been in my head since.
And I was thinking how two things.
One, just like listener, try it in a moment of anger and like especially in like a road rage incident.
See what happens if you say, hey, I'll lick my car to see what happens.
Does it diffuse the fight?
Does it escalate it?
Because it's so strange.
Or does it make the person you're fighting with go, sorry, what?
Or lick their car.
Or do they actually do it and lick your car?
It makes me think of in high school, in college, there was a guy who went on dates with a couple of my friends.
And the things people said about him was that during making out, he would grab a woman's head and erotically lick their forehead.
And that's what I felt like they flashed you when Art licked the car.
Like licking something that you're not supposed to lick.
Yeah, yeah.
It's really something.
I also thought.
What a move.
Yeah, yeah.
That was his move.
What a trademark.
Multiple people said it.
He's like, yeah, that's his.
That guy's move, his thing is that he licks a car.
Yeah.
Before he goes into your house and has sex with you, he licks your car.
I also thought the other thing about the phrase that occurred to me is that like, I don't know if they still do this,
but that whole weird practice of censoring the movies for cable with the bizarre phrases that are not profanities.
Car licker.
Hey, listen, car.
Yeah, it's kind of a good euphemism for suck my dick.
Like, why don't you lick my car?
For years, you know, I had only seen the cable cut of Mallrats.
For a long time, I thought Jason Lee's catchphrase was, holy snot, because he says, holy shit, so many times.
And every time they use the same edit of, holy snot.
Which an holy shit doesn't read as a catchphrase, but holy snot, absolutely.
Yeah, it does.
I was like, well, that's catchphrase.
And then I bought it on DVD because it was one of those $5 DVDs, $10 DVDs forever.
And I'm like, I want more money.
And that's it.
I thought.
What was the thing's dick conversation when it was censored?
What's that?
Remember he has a conversation with Stan Lee about like the superhero dick?
Oh, that's a great question.
I do not remember.
What could that have been?
Yeah, just gibberish, I guess.
It would be a fun thing to go back and watch the edit of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, put the ad on stream.
Put the TV cuts on stream.
Yeah, yeah, they should activate the other audio modes.
Yeah, yeah, please.
I miss those.
Anyway, so yeah, I agree.
At that point, I think we were all buzzing.
That was a cosmic horror for me.
Like, if this is true, what else is true?
If this guy can lick a car, what else can happen to us tonight?
Are we going to die tonight?
Like, I really wasn't.
Put anything on the table.
Another thing that happened post-car lick was the discussion of, you know, when I got
home, Aaron said, like, did he, like, put, like, a condom on it or something?
Was there any protection?
Like, I don't think, yeah, yeah.
No.
Dental dam on your sedan.
Dental dam on your car wash lick.
And, Mike, you said something similar, and you skipped to some, like, is there some,
like, wax or something that he would, and I think that's a reasonable question maybe
in some other setting, except that I think that this is, like, this is seasonal hires
in Anaheim, that's something that a magician might do.
It was a petulant car lick, too.
It seemed like he just decided to do it because we weren't giving him the reaction he wanted.
Wait, that's a question, because only you saw it.
Was there, like, yeah, was it angry?
Was there an attempted sensuality to it?
It was like, it was like, you're doing it very, like, fraudulent.
Because it was like, you know, there's a whole, like, face in front of the face, and he's
sticking his tongue out of it, it's like.
Oh, so not that much can get out.
It's as much as he can get through the mouth hole.
Yeah, because it's sticking his tongue out as far as he could get it to get it to the car.
Did you notice that he, like, spit after that, or did he swallow whatever was on his mouth from the window?
He's in the mask.
He kind of walked away so we didn't see, yeah, I didn't see him spitting.
What if he went into my car right after?
What if he spit it into my car?
It's possible.
You're okay to spit your car into your car.
You've got to de-louse your car.
Even the whole time you're thinking, like, well, even I get an exterior car wash, they're not going to vacuum.
They're not going to.
Well, you know what? At the end of it, there were a big row of vacuums and there was nobody in that.
Like, technically I could have stopped and vacuumed and we were all like, no, thanks.
No.
Not stopping for vacuuming.
What if car liquor comes back?
So, should we get to the actual, the second, the turn?
Yeah.
Well, I want to say this real quick.
First of all, well, okay, they're walking up and down and all these cars are like in park or they're idling or something.
They're just inhaling exhausts.
Oh, yeah.
All night.
Yeah.
And this wouldn't be the only time when they make performers inhale, like, probably toxic things.
So, for all you know, that car, he could have inhaled so much that he could have thought, like, he could have been hallucinating.
He could have thought that car was the love of his life.
His good lady wife.
Finally, yeah.
Hello, dear.
Or a big turkey.
Rebecca.
Oh, yeah.
Big turkey.
Glass of water in the desert.
Yeah.
He's like just minutes from dying from his breathing smoke or whatever, like, asphyxiating.
And he's like, yes, it's Cynthia.
My sweet love.
Can I lick you one last time?
You know, I know a couple, a few couples at this point who met working at theme parks.
Is it possible there was a love story where like, well, the doctor clown and the cheerleader clown, you know, we met working at the horn of car wash.
Didn't you see two clowns with like their arms around each other when the breakdown was happening?
We saw someone touching someone's waist.
Wasn't that the manager?
Oh, yeah.
I'm a fan.
Maybe married to somebody who worked or like touching someone at work.
I mean, look, on set romances, rehearsal, romance happens.
Well, I hope that if Art fell in love with my car, that he didn't write down the license plate and isn't scouring the Burbank area.
Breaking the garage.
I mean, season.
Apple key under your bumper.
Apple key tag.
I'll see you soon, my love.
This won't be our final lick.
So there's a so can I jump ahead?
Much have we got a line.
But the funny thing is like you get up to the end of the long line and then you're just at the place where you buy a car wash and there's the manager there in a manager outfit.
No clown. Nothing.
Regular guy just hopping in.
Okay, let's button button button.
Okay, is that okay?
Gold wash.
Go send you know the value of the you're getting a twelve dollar car wash as part of a fifty dollar of a fifty dollar experience.
Yes.
But that answered the question.
Indeed.
It does wash your car and I got so excited since it had been licked and boogered and I was like if they're washing the car, they could have thrown blood on the car.
They could have done like a lot more shit if they really wanted.
Yes.
Could have put shit on the car or dirt.
Yeah.
And then getting washed anyway.
Why do they just like a little lick?
Because they only can find one guy in Anaheim or two.
I guess the spitter was not.
That's not as bad.
I would spit on a car.
I'd spit on a car in a second.
I would not lick a car though.
If they could have thrown a bucket of blood on the car, that could be really fun if you're going to wash it anyway.
That's kind of what I was expecting.
No, just the little lick.
Which hurt him more.
I don't want to accuse you guys of erasing my trauma.
But you're right that like the spit isn't as aggro because he didn't touch my car with his mouth.
But on my end, being that close to watching spit dribble on again one of my belongings.
And I know that it was going to be washed.
I had a feeling it was going to be washed soon, but I didn't quite know.
And I mean, we're only three days out from this as we record this.
You better believe I've looked at that spot every single time I've gotten in and out of my car and just thought about that spit being there.
I still see it.
It's still real to me.
Oh, wow.
I get it.
That makes sense.
But so, but thank God we are getting a wash.
Yeah.
And you were talking about the manager.
They didn't figure out any sort of mechanism to just open up the like, whatever you call those things, the gate thing with the whatever the things that move up when you put the money into the car.
Yeah, they didn't just like, oh, we'll pull them up and then we're just going to have it on auto.
Whatever. Yeah.
No, the manager had to keep going back and forth between two kiosks.
And punching in some sort of a free coupon, like free coupon to get them to open and for the car wash to actually work.
And he was not in character.
He just seemed like this is the shittiest job I could possibly have back and forth, back and forth, back and forth.
I saw that in a video clip.
There was just a guy in a blue polo in black slacks.
Yeah, that's the clown.
That's right.
Yes.
And he's like, oh, this is very funny.
They're pulling up to the care zone and like there's a creepy cheerleader clown and rubbing a baby doll on the front of the hood and going car wash.
And then I'm like, oh, that's creepy.
And then I like kind of look and I'm like, I think they have a sponge because it's the dragon or it's like a stuffed animal.
But just the person going car wash, car wash.
I remember the only words a clown said was he opened Mike's door.
I went to a point and went, do you like clowns?
Yes.
There was a guy and then yes, he said, do you like clowns?
I go, yes.
And he just like there was a good beat, which I thought was a pretty good like comedy beat for him.
And he just slammed the door.
And then he went, oh, and he closed the door.
Like he didn't. I didn't answer correctly.
I didn't say no.
And then he would be like, well, I'm a clown.
And then, but no, I said yes.
And then he's closed the door.
So that's like when you sense that they're not following you because they want a reaction more than they.
He wants to scream.
Yeah.
So I ruined his fun, I think.
Another thing we haven't mentioned is that they would say if this is the fun we would have gotten if I kept my door open as the driver that they would have reached in and honked the horn.
There was a lot of that going on all over the place.
And then some people were not dragged out.
I don't think it took, but people were definitely outside of the car.
They were definitely trying to get people to come out.
And you seem to draw the line there, Eva.
I feel like Mike might have.
You might have gotten out of the car.
I would have gotten out of the car.
Yeah.
And then right after our car wash was paid for in a non-horror way, right after that was the point where a clown just fully got into the car and then drove one stop with him and then got out.
That was cool.
Erin's question about that was like, what if they could kidnap that guy?
They could just take off.
Yeah.
But I guess that's what, you know, he did it in the safe zone.
It's like between lots of line and the car wash.
Yes.
The funniest clip I saw, well, after you finish, I will explain the most funny clip.
But a very funny clip I saw, there was a clown in like a just seraphine and they were like mad doing a car and they weren't making any noise.
They were just getting closer and closer and they were right up against the car and they put their hand on the windshield.
They had a massive sponge and just started wrapping the car.
That's so funny.
Car wash related humor.
Yeah.
We didn't get any of that.
There was no sponge or anything.
Basically, it just hit us that, okay, we are just getting fully a regular car wash.
And it was, they didn't like theme it spooky.
It was the regular signs and the signs telling you the rules to put it in neutral and make sure the windows are up, basic stuff.
Regular got not a clown telling you that information.
So then we're just cruising.
Now we're just on the little ride and the colors are not even particularly horror.
Sure, it's flashing green and red, but also blue and purple.
And these are not necessarily Halloween colors.
This is just regular stuff by this point.
And I think it lures us into a false sense of security.
So that probably halfway through when somebody jumps out and waves a big skull stick or something at Mike, it was a real shock because we were not sure with car wash running.
Are there going to be people in the car wash?
A clown in between the two big brushes getting hit by foam scaring us.
Yeah, because we had said before, well, like, well, they can't be like in the thing because it's really dangerous.
Like a big mechanism there.
And it's like coming down like somebody could get hurt.
There were like five of them in the thing.
There were there were a lot more than I thought.
They found a lot of pockets.
That makes me anxious when workers are like between the brushes.
Oh, yeah.
Or like you see places sometimes where it's just like, yeah, just do my job.
OK, I'll do a little squeegee.
And then the brush comes back down.
They're doing those.
And so to see clowns doing that, they're just doing their job.
This is what on the attraction 360 you can see this.
OK, so a normal car, it's like you get blast with soap, the brush come down, then it rinses.
So in this video, a clown steps in on the rinse and without thinking, opens the passenger door.
The door gets wet and you can they don't say anything, but you tell they kind of make the movement of like, oh, shit.
They close it real quick.
They forgot where they were.
No, no, no.
Now that would have and that has nothing to do with like that.
You can't put that in the category of Scott doesn't like Hans or Scott's afraid to get it.
Scott's a no launch queen.
I don't want to put a car wash filling up my door.
That is I get money back if that happens.
That's like when you're getting in your car and it's like pouring rain and try to close it real quick and your hand slips.
You're like, oh, shit.
And a bunch of water gets on the inside of the door.
You're like, well, the dry, but it's inconvenient right now.
And then you take all that and make it that a clown did it.
There's a scary clown.
Oh, my God. Blowing around in the hot air area.
It's moving in a car wash.
It's a moving platform.
So to have a human being approach that platform in between two dangerous things coming from the ceiling spinning, pretty insane.
And in addition, like just inhaling what I assume are very toxic chemicals after maybe not toxic, but just soap and weird fumes, weird car soap.
Well, what do you OK, let's choose a path on this avenue.
Do we think that this is a car wash where actually we use materials that are safe and we've thought about this and we wouldn't put anyone in harm's way?
Or is the answer? Get out of here.
Why are you why are you asking these questions?
Don't think about it. Do you want to have a haunted car wash or not?
What do you do?
You have any sense? I don't want to throw the people who do this thing under the bus.
Do you have an answer? I don't.
OK, I would say you have do you have a hunch?
Is it just cause is it just like fucking we're doing it?
I have a hunch because of just the way that it was set up like they never when we're waiting in line said, OK, now you come to this point and put your car in park and turn it off.
And then the actors come.
So immediately once the cars are like, as far as anyone knows, somebody just has their foot on the brake.
The cars may be in drive and you have a bunch of human beings coming up to it, going into the cars, scaring people.
All bets are off.
Whoever put this together is actually not thinking that hard about safety.
So that's why I believe that they may have just said, fuck it, throw some humans in there.
Tunnel of Wasteland is a rogue nation.
You enter the tunnel of wasteland as a prison planet.
Yeah, anything goes.
You just try to escape.
There's only one thing you can do.
I. Yeah, then we your new mission.
The acolytes are scattered around the globe at the tunnel, the wasteland.
I'm a little wasteland tunnel of waste.
So, I mean, it would it gave us all quite a start that we were not safe in here.
And there was one I completely forgot about.
We were at the end and I was just focusing on like, you know, lining up and wait, does the green is a green yet?
Do I go? And then somebody got somebody slammed right against that.
And it is very effective that they're just an inch from you.
And I don't know.
And the music, you know what?
I also I was making fun of the music at first and then I forgot because it went away for a while that it had like jump scares and stabs.
So the music was hitting me again.
I have to say, by the end of this, I was pretty sold on the whole thing.
Maybe this comes from me that I have not done a lot of other haunts.
Perhaps that I perhaps I'm grading this and checked over fest too high.
I don't think so.
I was I was so delighted by both of these things.
Getting my car licked.
I who knew that this was a possibility on this earth.
It's getting his car licked.
It's getting his car licked today.
If you say it with any affect, it immediately seems double entendre.
What are you doing tonight?
Going down to Anaheim, getting my car licked.
Nice.
Cool.
It's right by the Disneyland.
Just 50 bucks.
Reasonable price.
There's I've said this phrase.
I said it about Meow Wolf and I've said about like after you do a few of these, you do want to get and I'm of course I'm on the mild side of this.
You want to get a little fucked up.
You want a little something to fuck you up.
And like you're looking for that in an unexpected way.
And this did it.
Getting your car licked.
This car licking and the snot.
I even think the snot because you were obviously saw the licking more closely than I did.
But the snot is really what got me because it was right in front of my face.
Yeah.
And I couldn't unseal.
It was just sitting.
The snot was sitting there the whole time.
Right in front of me.
So we all got one.
We all got a different bodily horror done to the bit of car in front of us.
Just like Eva got a horror at Delusion.
Nazi actor character menacing me.
The heightening of that is that a crab monster nearly shattered multiple bones in your hand with a giant table.
Yes.
What a season it's been for you.
Raise the stakes.
Wow.
Yeah.
I mean I kind of get it.
And it's let's say a thing we say a lot.
Moments of intimacy.
That's right.
These are this is parts of people gave parts of their bodies.
People gave their DNA to this experience and put it an inch away from my face.
This is like if Optimus Prime kind of reached through the screen and said he was proud of me but he also smelled because he's been fighting a lot and there's like oil smell and like he's obviously like he's been through it.
So it's very similar to that.
Your bravery saved the planet.
I will now lick the windshield of Evac.
His tongue has motor oil all over it.
I'm sorry we didn't get the video of the tongue but we did get.
We got the audio reaction.
So I'll post that.
I think there's a lot of pictures and supplementary material to post here.
But any closing thoughts about this experience.
Wait a minute.
I mean the only person who can really do closing thoughts or really make a judgment call here is the person who wasn't there.
Jason wait was the first name.
Jagged Slash and Train.
If we decided to do this again next year where do you land.
I will be a passenger I will not drive.
Okay.
But I will come.
Will you unlock your door?
I kind of want to see.
I kind of want to see how I'm feeling in the moment.
Maybe unlock the door but window up.
I will rent a car that doesn't have a door on your side.
That the door has been removed.
How will that do with the car wash?
Yeah wait.
Now he's getting splashed.
You heard what I said.
He's getting souped.
It's not my car I rented it.
So you're checking boxes.
You're on the website checking it.
Why don't they have an option for three doors only.
The back right door is removed.
You have two doors and you have four doors.
How do I remove a door?
It's like that story that Tom Lennon told on a podcast once where he rented a car in his 20s.
And he paid for the extra insurance and they just fucking destroyed the car.
By the end you will do that for the haunted car wash.
I paid the extra enterprise.
Well that might be also on our Club 3 episode I learned the joys of washing a rental car.
And I think and then on this one I learned the horrors of having one of your belongings get licked and spit on.
So maybe I will and maybe this is how it works.
Jason comes he can decide the in the moment whether he wants to unlock the door or not.
But we rent a car.
My laptop is staying at home.
Because the MacBook Pro may as well be made out of a single sheet of glass.
It will just shatter if you look at it cross.
What's the funniest car we could realistically get our hands on and drive through?
Dodge Charger?
Like the fucking bullet car.
That's funny. That's pretty good.
Yeah that's pretty good.
Great.
Any notes for next time?
Would there be a next time? Would you do this again?
Is there something you want out of the next time?
Some friends of mine live in South LA and I told them this story and they said oh yeah we drove past in South LA.
There was a car wash that just had a sign that said haunted car wash.
And the guys were like oh yeah we went to one of these in Anaheim so we decided to do it.
So my friend and his husband just drove through and just two ghouls just got in the car and rode with them.
The whole time?
The entire process?
The two guys that worked at the car wash just got in the car.
What?
And they were like woo.
And so I would like to see next year is it tunnel of wasteland?
I mean driving down to Anaheim is a lot but I guess now I have to do this until I die.
Every year. That's one of your days in October.
We could do Lakewood next year.
Let's do Lakewood.
Let's do Long Beach and then we could combine it with Shacktoberfest.
Oh there you go.
Because Lakewood is Long Beach.
Because I would like to do that one again. I think you'd enjoy that.
Let's say, let's set it in stone. I'm back on all this.
I really, if I have Halloween bluffs, this has honestly been my favorite Halloween season since I was a child.
Wow.
It really feels like it's been bad. I think pandemic hurt it.
I was starting to think like am I not going to be in a costume at a party ever again?
I don't like these haunts and is it all over for me?
It's really come back and I thank Shack first and foremost.
Shack did.
But I thank Eva second only to Shack for alerting us to this area and for coming down to Anaheim and for joining us for this.
Eva Landerskum, you survived haunt cast The Fright.
Thank you.
At this point also, I was doing some math. I like to keep abreast of your stats.
And at this point you've now done eight paywalled episodes.
Oh my god.
Two of them are about Dick Tracy and two of them are about car washes.
Incredible numbers.
The best stats anybody has on the show.
So thank you as always for joining us and let's exit through the crypt shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
I would like to plug. I am doing an immersive.
Me talking shit about immersive.
I'm putting on an immersive show in November at the end of November, at the beginning of December in Koreatown, Los Angeles.
If you want to purchase tickets are available now.
The website is the shape of the night dot com.
That's the shape of the night dot com.
It's I'm putting on with a couple other really amazing immersive creators.
It's going to be about dreams and nightmares.
There's it's got a it's got a it's got a you got a free drink with your ticket.
It's going to be really fun.
And not to tip it too much, but how much licking is involved.
Oh man, I mean, Scott, you're bringing your car, right?
I'm not sure now.
If Scott's car is not there, I'm not going.
But yeah, it's not a haunt. It's something else.
It's creepy, but it's also like dreamy.
And I just would love any local fans come check it out.
Yeah, I well, yes, having been to the last one of these years, you've done one since the one a few years ago.
Yeah, I've been one of these before.
Eva puts on great shows and this is, you know, you've if you've heard her on the show with like, yeah, come see something experience Eva put together.
It's you know, it's going to be great.
I'll be there. We should all go. Let's figure it out.
So thank you, Eva.
As for us this Friday on the main feed, you will hear the final haunt cast of the year, the live show that we did at Dynasty Typewriter with our pal Anthony Geo.
So you'll get that on the main feed and then we will go back to normal haunt cast season.
Unfortunately, it's over because I've had a lot of fun this time.
But on the main feed, when we switch back to normal, a fun returning guest, somebody who hasn't been on a long time, think you will like that.
And if you enjoyed all this and you want to hear some stuff going on on Club 3 where this whole themed car wash business started, you can always upgrade to our VIP tier Club 3 where next month, I think, is Macy's Thanksgiving Parade Balloon Disasters.
Looking forward to that one. Very excited about that particular victory.
And one more thing before we go, I'm going to take it back to Eva because something that has come up that we haven't put in the poll, but that people have mentioned and it requires your permission and participation.
Obviously, great results from Eva does whatever she wants.
If you are free and not busy to join us for to put into the poll and Eva does whatever she wants round two.
Lick.
Oh no.
We didn't take a break. Eva's hallucinating.
She thinks the microphone is the love of her life.
Or a giant turkey leg.
Or a hot and ready pizza.
Hot and ready pizza.
Yes, of course.