Hi there, before you listen to this second gate about Sphere and Mike's visits to U2 at Sphere,
this was recorded a little while ago and a number of things have happened in the Sphere world that
aren't acknowledged within the episode. For example, that the Sphere posted a nearly 100 million
dollar loss for the quarter, that the CFO quit due to James Dolan's yelling and screaming.
I just saw in the New York Post that he delivered his notice in the middle of a meeting with a
bunch of executives. He just went in and said, I quit. And the fact that the city of London rejected
having a second Sphere built there because, quote, it would be bulky, unduly dominant and incongruous.
So all of those are things and like some things that I wanted to get ahead of because you'll
hear in the body of the episode that I'm a little bit ceding to the success of Sphere and maybe even
hovering around eating a little crow thinking that Sphere was not going to be good or work out.
Yeah, but all of these things kind of leave it in a different light. But Mike, as a Sphere head,
any response to any of this recent news? Well, the loss happened before the U2 shows. So first of all,
that wasn't even operating. So yeah, they lost a few dollars, a few cents, but I just think, you
know, yeah, you're going to have to break some eggs if you want to make an omelet, you know?
Are we sure that is true that those numbers don't reflect the period in which the U2 shows have been
happening? I believe so because the quarter because of what U2 started in October, end of September.
So it would have to have been, yeah, before that. I saw a Sphere thing just this morning
as we're recording this. The Twitter account, Las Vegas locally, which posts a lot of Las Vegas
events and news and stuff, said some F1 drivers complained about how bright the Sphere was on race
night, according to reports, because this is Vegas's other successful question marks debacle
question mark. It appears the high limit rooms at some of the casinos did very well for the F1
attendees. But yeah, if you watch footage, you can see the F1 cars going directly by the Sphere,
which occasionally had a Vegas graphic and sometimes just had a smiley face whose eyes
would follow the cars. Yes. I messaged all the F1 drivers, get used to it. That was like a fucking
Mario Kart track. And I was like, maybe I should like F1 now. This looks fun. Some nonsense face,
giant face. It's like you're on Moomoo Farms. You did your Fast Vegas driving. You could handle a
Sphere in the periphery, no problem. I was eating White Castle driving in a rent-a-car, or no,
my own car. Sorry, I rented a car in Orlando. I can't remember anything. I was driving my own
car in Las Vegas, eating White Castle, driving by the Sphere and I didn't have a problem.
So you're saying if you didn't have a problem going a normal amount of speed for a car to go,
why should they have a problem going 10 times that? Well, I'm just saying that me eating White
Castle while I drive at a normal speed is about the same physical challenge that driving 10 times
of speed is for them. I'm saying they aren't eating White Castle, so that balances things out.
Okay, didn't want us to distract from the episode. Everybody, please enjoy hearing about Mike's
visit to Sphere.
You know what, I hit record. Universal's Mardi Gras too is also very popular.
Podcast arrived, the second gate is here. Do we need to re-explain what was just said?
I'm going to explain. Yeah, yeah. We're gearing up here to talk some music, but I just threw out
the idea that I wanted to do a second gate on Sugar Ray's set list when they play Epcot Center
at the Eat to the Beat series. Jason, of course, said, well, they're regulars there. They're always
there. And I said, what? What do you mean? How do they get them? Yeah, Scott was. This must be the
biggest deal the Disney company has to do every year. We've not locked in. Gentlemen, I hope
you're pleased with yourselves. Sugar Ray has not been sealed for the year. Well, this is a big,
this is why they had to get Che back out because he was fumbling the ball on booking Sugar Ray
for each performer. You say whatever you want to Scarlett Johansson, but when you cross McGrath,
that is a path from which this company cannot walk bath.
So I'm just going to say this here so we don't actually have to do it a full episode on it.
We're going to talk the sphere. I went to the sphere and I won't even bury the lead. I love
the sphere. I love it. Yeah. It surpassed my expectations, but real quick, this is what
Sugar Ray does when they're at Epcot Center. They play every morning. They play someday when it's
over. These are their songs, but then they play How Bizarre by OMC. They play Steal My Sunshine by
Len. They play I Want It That Way by the Backstreet Boys. It's just a late nineties potpourri.
Yeah. Whatever. And then they play Fly and then they play What I Got, I think by Sublime.
So Sugar Ray is so finale. That was it. What I got. They close the end of the show is what I got.
Yes. Not their song. They have other singles too. This is reflected in the list. Yeah. This is such
an insecure set list on Sugar Ray's part, I feel. Well, this is the kind of muddying of the...
They're just leaning into like, sure, lots of different bands did all these different songs
in the nineties, but where are they? They're not at E to the Beat. Where's OMC? It's ours now. We
buy that. We're a conglomerate now. I think they're doing it. I think even Mark McGrath said some of
these songs people think we did. So now they're just playing on how Weezer was identified as
being the artist that did Teenage Dirtbag on a lot of Napster files. Oh, yes. Remember this?
Now they do it forever. Well, they've done it here and there or whatever. But I think Mark
McGrath is doing the same thing where people go, how bizarre? Was that Sugar Ray? Wow. And he goes,
yeah, so we'll just do it. We're doing it. You know, a lot of people think we did I Feel Like
Chicken tonight. Remember that? Does that take you back? Hey, if you were a nineties kid,
you might remember this one. I feel like chicken tonight. So he's really sorry. He's changing.
He's changing people's minds in real. Like he's actually now reinforcing the incorrect information
to people at Epcot Center because people they won't remember him saying we didn't do this song,
but we're doing it anyway. They'll just go, oh yeah, how bizarre Sugar Ray. So now he is
claiming songs. He truly he is the new Mike Love. He is absolutely. Yeah. I think maybe Mike gave
him these tips. I was looking at so Universal Orlando's Mardi Gras celebration, which runs
a few weeks. They've had a concert series last few years and they sure have some big names.
And 2022 it started off. Oh, it started off with Sugar Ray. Did it really? Yeah. February 5th.
But then the next week was Diana Ross. Wow. Really? Yeah. And then Bare Naked Lady Sticks.
Wow. I feel like that's I mean, they get some pretty big acts. Jason Derulo was the last one.
You said that statement right after Sticks. That is what provoked. Wow. They get some big acts.
They get some hits. The rarely seen Sticks. Hello Cool J. Marshmello. Really? Yeah. This is a mix.
There is some some mild relevancy I'd say to the list. Yes. Yeah. Wow. So okay. I've said that I
need to get that out of my head about Sugar Ray set list. And that's really all I have to say.
I just think that's funny. Well, this is why U2 needs to remain on their grind innovating in the
news because otherwise Sugar Ray starts scooping up. Hey, remember this one? Beautiful day.
Yeah. And people think how Sugar Ray did that one. They're like memory holeing,
incorrect memory holeing to people. And yeah, I guess here's one you might remember.
Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun. Wow, they did the NBA on NBC.
That's like they play. Here's one you might remember. Dun dun dun dun.
Oh, you know what? Huh? I thought that was older. But I guess. Wow. I guess that's you might be a
90s kid if you remember this. Dun dun dun dun. You remember? Dun dun dun dun. Sure that's right.
This one. Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun dun. Whoa, they did the Windows 95 startup sound.
I guess I am a 90s kid who remembers that. Brian Eno smashing a glass bottle. Like, absolutely not.
Maybe Beethoven will take that shit, but not Eno. I like this strategy from Mark McGrath and
Sugar Ray. It's very smart. It's undeniably very. Maybe they'll play this fear one day.
I don't know. It might be a few bands before. They might have to get a lot together maybe to
fill it up. But yeah, they're significantly bigger than the Eat to the Beat America Gardens.
But they do do multiple shows a day, I'd imagine. Yes. There's usually like three sets, I think.
Like three short sets for the bands. Short, you say? They want to keep those short? Seven-ish songs.
Sugar Ray doesn't need to, they don't need to stretch them out to 25, 26 songs? No, I mean,
maybe Universal. I don't know how they do it over there at that series, that concert series.
Not to check the Mardi Gras policy. We will check that set list of Sugar Rays and then we'll maybe
do another episode. What is the show? So if, and we're talking about U2's Octon Baby, you know,
revival and full album tribute. But what would be the Sugar Ray if they were going to do a full album?
That's a very good question. I guess it would be, is it, I'm trying to think. It's not 1459,
that's the Strokes album. It's whatever album has Every Morning on it. That's what you think.
Remember this one? Last night! That album is called... Here's a little song you might remember.
Wow, they did the Clarissa Explains It All song. No, it is 1459. Well, what's the Strokes album
called then? The second one? Yeah. I forget. There's a song I thought called 1459.
Anyway, oh, Room on Fire is the name of the album. 1459 I think is the name of the song.
Anyway, now people are going to be mad at me about Strokes. We're not talking about Strokes.
Talking about U2. Strokes are much too cool and good to be talked about on this podcast.
That's correct. Some people, I will say people do, I think, think that my taste is all like
nostalgia 90s. I think I have given people this impression, and it's not actually true,
that it's not fully that. I'm just saying. We believe you, we know you've talked about
Olivia Rodrigo. Wait, and now have you finished the full album? I have not finished the full
Olivia Rodrigo album. It's so funny that you have continued, despite it being talked about.
Strangers have posted about this, tweeted at you. You finished Harry's House though.
Yes, of course I finished Harry's House. Okay. I have.
You're bringing up finishing an album like it's the.
I was listening to a new album by a guy I never heard of, Troy Savan. That's really good.
But then I was also listening to Hackney Diamonds recently as well.
No, we're going backwards now, Mike. That's a step backwards.
Okay, so The Sphere. If you're listening to this podcast, you probably know that we've done some
Sphere talk here and there, especially in Las Vegas and our series.
This is a little bit of a Sin City Nights postscript, I would say, because The Sphere was
certainly on our minds. I was going to say on everyone's minds, but maybe not. It was
definitely on our minds and we talked about it. And in our live show, The Groove Blender,
there was a lot of talk of The Sphere. Its founder, James Dolan, the mad genius who.
The master. The brilliant,
the cracked out master who he was talked about, but we curtailed some of the talking about him
because he is someone who uses facial recognition software to keep people out of his venues.
And Mike did not want anything resembling that so that he could go anywhere.
Which is present at The Sphere. I believe there are caution signs that you are.
I sent you a picture of it.
Yes, that I've seen it from a few different angles at this point that like you are consenting.
Universal Orlando, I believe, testing out facial recognition for Ticket
to get rid of the dirty fingerprint scanners.
Facial recognition notice. Welcome to Sphere. We use facial recognition technology to improve
your experience at Sphere. We shouldn't say The Sphere. We should say Sphere.
Sphere. MSG Sphere. You see it sometimes. Madison Square Garden.
To help ensure the safety and security of our venue and our guests.
And to enforce our venue policies. To learn more, please visit
Sphere Entertainment Co. Dot com slash privacy.
And I'm assuming there's some like really scary shit if you look into the fine print there.
We're hoping to help you have a good time tonight. And if you are an attorney who is
currently suing James Dolan, you might have a better time tonight back at home.
Or I don't know, maybe sit in a hole somewhere.
In the Sphere jail.
You might have a better time if we if there was suddenly a light and then you didn't exist anymore.
It also probably says they're going to sell like sell your face to Disney to be in the
background of a scene of one of their TV shows or movies.
Yeah, this is a giant AI scan dome.
I think that's probably right.
It's the real yeah. It's in the fine print.
So yes, I was worried. I was not seriously worried, but there was a half of worry in my head
of like, I think if our podcast was like as popular as like Doughboys, it would have gotten to Dolan.
You think Doughboys level will be a nut. Hey, there's this podcast out there.
He seems talking about you know, I do.
Yes. Yeah. I mean, look, I'm giving him, of course, that definitely that.
Probably not. But but if our podcast is really big, we would have been invited there.
Well, that's true.
VIP if we were smartless, the whole smartless crew is probably up there in the VIP box.
That's part of the show. And of course, as usual, I've joined a lot of Facebook groups
specifically for a thing I'm going to do or did.
And they are pointing out the celebs every night in that box area.
And yes, very early. Maybe night one was this whole smartless group.
That was a guess. Was that actually true?
Yeah, it was true. My god.
There were pictures of Bateman on the floor, but then moved from the box to the floor.
You've got your.
They should. I mean, they've got so many podcasts to do.
I don't know how they're finding the time.
I know.
But shouldn't Bateman be editing right now?
He should.
If he weren't cutting out the ums and likes.
Does he work the zoom like I do on this podcast? I don't know.
We can only assume he was there.
I mean, the first night it was McCartney.
It was Jimmy Buffett family there, of course, because of, you know, the plane story.
We all know it.
Snoop Dogg.
Snoop, I think.
Uh, Elizabeth Banks.
Yeah. Every who's Mario Lopez.
And it continues to be Clooney and Gerber were there a couple of weeks later.
They rode the motorcycles from the agave fields.
Kylie Minogue was there and Bono put Bono saying can't get you out of my head.
A little snippet of it.
Oh, he references who was ever there.
If they're famous enough and if they have a hit song.
That's the most interested I've been to hear.
I mean, shout out.
Yeah.
So it's it's funny because it really felt like this weird thing we were talking about.
And then if like the first night and there was all these articles about it.
And then, of course, every famous person was there.
And I was like, oh, yeah, of course, of course.
Yeah.
And almost like an obscure thing, which is an insanely stupid thing to say about
you two doing a residency.
You two and a massive thing in Las Vegas.
But there was a while, I would say, where it still felt like what is that weird structure?
Yeah.
In Las Vegas.
And then even I think even the videos of the weird outside projections are going a little viral.
But I still think people not everybody knew what it was.
Oh, it's a concert venue and this multimedia venue that will be showing these films and such.
I think it was kind of a slow rollout.
And here's what I have felt.
I'm going to eat not a full I'm not going to eat crow.
Sure.
I'm going to I'm just going to nibble on a wing, maybe.
Unlike the sphere, which is eaten numerous crows.
It's got a taste.
Yeah, they fly right into it.
Yeah.
You don't want to be a crow who flies into that thing.
You get you get zapped by LED lights.
Yeah.
It's like the Luxor beam.
It's like an ecosystem, but it will kill a crow.
As soon as it touches.
Yeah.
A thousand crows per year.
No, here's what I'll say, because I've made jokes about like that this thing is doomed to fail or
the economics of it being being where I or that, you know, this thing's only in the last couple months.
Clearly not the case.
There was clearly like a big tip of the scales from night one on the videos of this are massive.
There's so many articles about it.
Everybody's talking about it with, you know, major people posting the big
moments of it, which you were avoiding for a little bit and I've been a spoiler.
But it became unavoidable, right?
Some of those things.
So clearly this thing is huge.
This specifically this YouTube show is making a big impact and I will just
see to that.
That's definitely true.
Does this mean I've fully lost my fear skepticism, my skepticism?
Yeah.
Maybe not.
I still have some questions and some thoughts, but I think that we're not in the ballpark of
this was this crazy dream that didn't work on any.
Yeah.
Well, you are right to be skeptical because the prices we've heard thrown around are very funny.
Vegas prices in general.
Yeah, but parking I've heard anywhere from $47 to $100.
Do not park at the sphere.
Do not park by the sphere.
That is madness.
There's no reason to do that.
I think most places on this trip have given up the free parking.
Yes.
There's one or two holding out, but like, you know, you're paying for parking if you're
driving down there.
You should do.
We were at the Park MGM.
What we should have done is gone across the MGM Grand taking the Monterey all the way down
by the link and then just walked because it's from like that link stretch by the
Ferris wheel and stuff.
It's like 15 minute walk or something.
Okay.
From there.
That's the way to do it.
Sure.
I mean, yes, $100 for parking is a mind fuck.
That's crazy.
Yeah, it's not 125 valet.
But it's...
There's not much there either.
There's not much parking there.
They don't have enough spaces.
Maybe they're trying to limit it in a way.
I mean, but why?
Yeah, you got to assume not a lot of people are parking there.
Yeah.
But forget about you too, even the movie tickets for the original 50 minute long,
Darren Aronofsky film, which I keep comparing to, you know, in the early 90s when your city's
local museum installed an IMAX and you would go and go like, wow, it feels like we're in the ocean
or we're like in the jungle or the desert.
And that costs $20 add on.
This is like 50 plus.
50 minimum.
Minimum.
There's a way if you wanted to for like the perfectly attuned seats, you could for this
50 minute movie pay $249.
And I don't know where other fees get you on that, your ticket master stuff.
So you said that, you texted that stuff.
And I don't think I even watched a review of somebody who was mind blown by the movie who
said, there's no way on earth you should spend $249 on this movie.
But you texted some of those price things.
Mike, right away, your response.
Well, I was, yeah, I said, well, it's very big.
It's bigger than those IMAX.
We'll give you that.
It is much bigger.
It's a lot bigger.
18K movie.
Resolution is much better than that 90s stuff is going to be.
It is giant.
No, it's a little, there's more angle.
People have said it's like having like an Oculus headset on, but like that amount of coverage
is just in front of you.
I saw a video saying you don't need to wear goggles anymore.
I was like, well, that's a different thing.
I don't think you can, look, you can't have goggles in your home.
You can't just regularly go to a massive sphere in Las Vegas.
Not yet.
Jim gets his way.
If they, yeah, yeah.
If there's a sphere in every town.
That's right.
But yeah, I don't know.
I see all sides of it.
You didn't see the movie.
Yeah, we are going to talk about the YouTube show.
I could see spending 50 to 75 for a Vegas ticket, which you always is marked up
generally 25%.
50% more than a normal show.
I don't think 250 seems right.
Well, and at the sphere, there's screens outside, the screens inside.
Further down the strip, there's different kinds of screens, blackout screens.
So you cannot watch that Formula One Grand Prix.
Do you know about this?
What are you talking about?
There's, the strip is like a construction site for the grandstands.
But on those foot bridges that go over Las Vegas Boulevard, they're blacking out the windows.
They're blacking out on the sidewalks so you can't just watch for free.
You have to pay for a package in the grandstand or restaurants that have strip view.
You have to pay like a package there.
That's funny.
They've already thought of everything.
They have thought of everything.
They've already started slashing prices because they are not getting the desired guests they want.
I bet that if you wait a couple months, that Aronofsky movie,
they'll start slashing some ticket prices.
Yeah, you might be able to hit up the TKTS booth.
Unless it's going to be just a smash hit, like people have to go see it.
We've been going for a little while on this thing, you know, a couple weeks enough to,
U2 is going pretty viral.
I don't know if the Aronofsky, because I do agree that like in terms of what they've shown us so far,
I'm sure it's very impressive to be there in person.
But the shots are like, we're moving really fast over a big snowy landscape.
And you hear the audience gasp at that.
But don't the three of us, maybe people listening, aren't you all like, yeah, so Soren?
So Soren, yeah.
So Soren.
Yeah, it's bigger Soren.
Yeah, I'm sure it's very cool.
But nothing, I haven't seen anything from that.
All right, there's a big elephant.
I think there's a big praying mantis.
Nothing has made me go, that sounds like I must get down there specifically for this.
I wouldn't mind seeing it, but I was not, I didn't carve out the day before or after U2 to see it.
Because it doesn't seem like there's a couple things in the U2 show that are like, whoa,
I got to, you got to see that if you're standing under it.
That gives you your sphere jolt.
You don't necessarily, you know, the entire, the separate.
I mean, I like the idea that, here's what I like.
I like that this thing is opening.
This is supposed to have this, it's this blockbuster venue.
And I like that it is U2 gigantic band and Darren Aronofsky filmmaker.
I do like that we are like, and that a director and a tour is being
positioned as like one of the names opening this thing.
And I like the idea that somebody could crack this.
I just, I don't think it's postcards from earth.
From what I've heard is going to be it.
But I feel like there's going to be, there might be something that is the, you know,
like what really in some, maybe more of an annul and way kind of like mobilizes.
This is so mind blowing.
You have to go.
They should, they should give it to like a man, some imagineer type.
That's what I was going to say.
Cause I do think Darren Aronofsky has made interesting movies.
Maybe they're not all my favorite, but they've usually been smaller.
Personal like scale.
I guess the fountain had some big moments.
You've long said only the whale is your favorite.
Oh yeah, I'm a big whale guy.
That just seemed to, no, I just traumatized at 16 years old watching Requiem for a Dream and Pi.
Just show Requiem on the sphere.
Yeah.
Kids gotta learn someday.
Gotta help convert black swan.
There's got to be somebody who can make a weirdo movie that fucks with you a little bit.
And I don't think there was ever going to be that the first one is like a true story,
but I feel like maybe like the right narrative project might really grab this thing and be
ultimate with it.
I was trying to think, cause there has to be, like this is maybe because I was watching
Bono talk about it and he said that maybe rock and roll isn't the best even music to have in here
versus like an orchestra or something.
I was like, they could do like a, they do these like video game, like orchestral arrangement shows,
which I've never seen, but seem cool.
And I like to listen to like mixes of that stuff, but like you put like an orchestra
playing every Nintendo song and then make a crazy big Nintendo show with all the characters
and the games for 40 years.
That takes you to the world and stuff you can only see there.
That would be sellout for 10 years, I think, if it was cool enough.
That's a good idea.
Like in that zone, something because like, especially like orchestra, like that's not
a band that has to be there forever.
You can obviously swap people in and out.
Exactly.
So it's like shows like that that could run more in like a Cirque way that you could plug
in between a big rock band playing it.
You want what should be in there then I guess is what Lydia Tarr is conducting at the end
of the movie.
Spoiler.
You could even do a more like arty thing with just like artists making little weird
like films or pieces to play during songs and stuff and have it be live, have the music be live.
I'm very curious.
What else?
I mean, we could, maybe that's a post.
That's an end conversation.
Yeah, probably.
But the sound is amazing, really.
And the screen, the outside screen is not the resolution of the inside screen.
No.
So if you've seen all the outside, like the meme smiley face and Venom just appeared on
the sphere, which is very exciting.
Venom and Spider-Man because there's a new game out.
Right.
Which is very fun to see Venom, I think.
I'm glad that that he's.
The star of some of the worst films ever made is here on the sphere.
That's right.
And so, but the whole first of all, there are funny things about this sphere.
Don't worry.
There are funny things.
I think they cut some corners here and there in lobbyish area.
Well, you're going to have to tell me like I'm happy to go along with your plan for this,
but you got to tell me where to insert aura.
You tell me when is a good time to talk.
Oh, I'll get them soon.
Soon.
Very soon.
So it is this.
You sent us a bunch of pictures from it when you were there.
Yes.
And I was maybe I'm reading too much into this.
So forgive me if it didn't strike you as odd.
It is a Pepsi venue.
What do you mean?
Oh, they have Pepsi in the.
Refreshments.
They're Pepsi not Coke.
I did not even notice that.
That's a little weird, right?
Well, it's rare.
It's more rare.
Most places have Coke products.
I like the mom and pop pizzerias where I grew up.
They might have Pepsi.
Sure.
Does Madison Square Garden have Pepsi?
That's a good question.
I don't know.
I mean, we got to look into that, I think.
Is it a bad thing?
What are you saying?
I'm saying I think it's usually the cheaper option.
Oh, that's it.
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
I actually did not know.
I like that you made you clocked what you thought was the weirdest thing.
Didn't mention it on the chain and have been saving it up.
I've been thinking about it.
I'm going to save up this year.
Well, the other thing you sent the concession list and we were not able to figure out one
of the items just said flips and that is with an S, not a Z.
It's not the chocolate covered pretzels.
Right.
Unless it is.
Unless that is what it is.
But they put it without a Z because we're just staring at the word flips as if to say,
you know, flips and I know I don't know flips.
What's a flip?
Yeah.
You can't just tell me that and not explain with any other words what it is.
If it's flips with a Z and it's a misspelling, the flips people, I would be furious.
I would flip out.
Flips out.
Dolan versus the flips people in court.
I corrected them.
It was a misspelling.
They've been spelling it wrong for years and I corrected it for them.
That's in court.
He's saying that to the judge.
I was helping them out.
That's after the gavel has already.
You owe the flips company $300 million.
I don't think I do.
He's going to write us.
I think I helped them.
He's going to write a disparaging song about it.
And that's kind of worse.
I thought I helped the flips.
I thought I did my best.
Hey ho, hey ho.
Everyone was mad at me.
Now flips people aren't allowed in the sphere.
If you have a flips, if you have flips on you, the sphere can tell.
They can tell what food you're carrying.
Oh, they're scanning you.
They're scanning you.
You will be barred from there.
You're going to have to eat those in one second or else throw them away?
Yeah.
So we got to, okay, we'll start a little bit of the night.
Okay.
We got to the sphere.
I sent you a photo.
When we got immediately to the sphere, this big baby's head was on the sphere.
The outside.
Yes.
And I will say this from, and I can't explain why, but I know that Epcot was in the head of
people that were working on this project, the sphere.
Certainly.
Yeah, for sure.
There was maybe more ambitious ideas for what was going to happen in there, but it
immediately feels theme parky to me in a way I didn't even expect it to in the sense that
a big baby's head is weird and it's like some weird drone that's happening.
They've chopped up pieces of Octong Baby and spliced it together in this weird soundscape
that also is playing inside that really makes you uneasy until the show, until you get to the
floor and there's a DJ playing in Viva Las Vegas.
But up until that point when you're buying beer and going and scanning tickets and stuff,
you're in that weird ride mode of like, what is this going to be?
That's interesting.
Which I was thrilled about.
Okay.
I was so happy about that.
Pre-ride on ease.
Huh.
Because you don't know yet if the screen is going to be so intense, the whole experience
is going to be so intense that it's going to make you nauseous or...
Sure.
It's just going to be this like being in some warp tunnel that you can't...
Can't get out.
It's going to be like being in an astronaut testing facility.
Right. Yes. Your face is like peeled back and you can't recover from it.
Yeah.
The baby is an astronaut, correct?
The baby is an astronaut. Yes. I kept calling it the Octong Baby.
I don't know if that's official.
I can't find it anywhere.
That's what it's supposed to represent.
But I think it is the... I'm just going to say it's the Octong Baby.
Right. And you also had like, I don't want to say floor seats,
but you were in general... You were standing on the floor.
Is that what you say?
General admission is what they say on the ticket, but that's standing room or floor or whatever.
And it just kind of looked like, honestly, a very small stage.
Oh my God. The stage was so small.
How big? Ten stories?
Oh, that's a good question. I think it's taller than that.
Oh, okay.
The building is taller than that. I forget exactly how big this screen is.
The screen reaches and curves all the way up to the top.
So it's not full. I think we said that already.
Stupid question. Is there a hole in the top or is that like a projection?
Is that an actual hole?
Projection.
Ah.
Because it would rain.
Yes. No, that's what I was confused by.
You thought there was a hole in it?
Well, there's a hole in the footage.
In some of the clips you look up and there's a hole at the top.
No, that's just the screen getting you.
Yeah, it got me.
You got fooled. Hold on. Let me take a step back, but I'll explain that part.
Yeah, wait. Me too. Hey, slow down. I'm not done talking about the baby.
Yeah, yeah. You didn't like the baby when I said it.
No, I didn't like the baby. That's the weirdest thing ever.
Everyone was upset with the baby except for me, who was there live.
Lindsay felt like, okay, I'm okay with the baby, but she wasn't so upset or so happy about it.
I asked to see, is this going to fall along the exact same lines as baby Aladar?
And it's not because Lindsay did not say the octong baby is very cute.
Yeah, but when you put it in the context-
Michael, we don't need sphere baby. We have baby at home.
When I put it in the context, though, of that pre-ride unease,
I think it makes more sense why I liked it.
You liked it because it freaked you out.
Yeah, it's a giant baby's head and the baby's like, it's a weird looking baby.
Something's wrong. The baby's in space.
The baby is in distress in some way, I think.
It's trapped in a helmet.
Gotta get out of there soon. Can't breathe.
It's like a 2001 space odyssey baby.
Sure, yeah. So yeah, the vibe was weird.
You're walking into a giant baby's head.
Yeah, and it kept, it switched and then there was this big,
sort of like, I guess 2001, the end where it goes into the room.
This big color and noise and then it says octong baby on it
and then it kind of cycles into some other stuff.
But it was definitely not for any major,
there's no reason to weird out your audience this much
if you're an old rock band trying to cash in, I guess.
So I have to appreciate that they approved all of this,
that unnerving shit that was going to happen.
Now, you're also, you're sending us these images and these feelings that you're having,
but you were also telling us quotes you were hearing from people around you.
People were fucking thrilled.
More vocally even than I was at the time.
Guy just went, like guy behind me just wanted to talk.
He just wanted to talk about it.
He's like, can you believe this? This is insane.
It's a big, big baby.
He didn't say anything about the baby specifically.
I think he was more saying the actual structure.
We're going to like crawl into his brain.
We're going to be, we'll see how mushy a baby's brain is.
He did not, I don't think reference the baby at all.
Maybe he wanted to forget that there was a baby and he just wanted to talk about
the colors and the lights and stuff.
But people, yeah, people in line where it was a buzz.
It was a fun feeling of everybody being like very excited.
But there was one quote in particular that stuck with me.
Yes.
Or I have it here, but what was it?
It was about like, it was kind of like a quantum physics oriented line.
Oh, I know I have to look it up. Hold on.
Or don't hold on.
Well, can I, let me take a guess at it and correct me if I'm wrong.
In my head, what it is is that somebody near you said you too transcends the concept of size.
Oh yeah, that is what it is.
Yeah, somebody did say that, which, okay, cool.
Do you agree or disagree? Talking point.
You too, size.
It's kind of a weird way to say like they play big shows, I think.
Yeah, is that, is that what that is that what maybe that's getting at that like you feel like
it's an intimate show, even though you're all the way in the back.
And this is the ultimate manifestation of that.
It feels like the line in what Mission Impossible five or six where Alec Baldwin says Ethan Hunt is
the manifestation of destiny.
You're like, I don't quite know what that means, but I kind of know what it means.
And I appreciate that you said it, but it doesn't quite make sense.
It's similar thing.
You say you weren't yelling that to Lindsay by song three.
I was not.
You too transcends the concept of size.
It made sense to me after when they played mysterious ways.
Oh, now I understand what they meant.
Before I forget, there's I love a concert.
Hopefully you're not going to get stories of people being assholes or something.
And you find like fun, cute stuff.
And the cutest thing I saw the whole night was right at they start playing the song one for
Mocked on Baby and two big two big dudes looked at each other, put their arms in the air,
big high five to each other.
It's like that is so cute.
That is the cutest I've ever seen.
Fuck.
Yeah.
One.
And then you get better.
And then you looked and one was wearing a Biden 24 hat and the other was wearing a
MAGA 24 hat.
Yeah.
They found common.
They became one.
RFK 24 guy walked right up.
He slapped both of their hands and they all hugged.
For one moment, the world was right again.
Thanks to the music of you two.
So before I forget here, this is from 2018, the Madison Square Garden Company.
And PepsiCo announced historic partnership.
There it is beginning on September 1st PepsiCo to become exclusive non-alcoholic beverage
and salty snack partner across MSG.
We should also say like Pepsi is Yum Brands is soda company.
Yum Brands is KFC Pizza Hut Taco Bell.
So that's not yeah, we're not talking like they have RC Cola at this sphere.
No.
Yeah, I found I find this concept strange that Pepsi is so runner up, but everyone knows
it.
I always say, you know, my answer has always been I like Pepsi better.
I haven't had any of that to drink in 15 years, but that's what I thought at the time.
What's your take?
Well, we were Pepsi House growing up for a few years.
We were drinking caffeine free Pepsi, which is still loaded with sugar and probably did
not help with that chubby little boy aesthetic.
And then at some point we switched to Coke and switched to diet sodas.
And you drank 30 pounds overnight.
Yeah.
Well, actually, I there was one summer where I stopped drinking so entirely and just
drank water and I immediately dropped like 10 or 15 pounds, like doing very little.
Yeah, sugar and soda.
I'll get you.
Yeah.
And now I keep Coke Zero in the house.
I'm off soda again, really.
Yeah.
For the most part.
Here and there.
What did you drink at Sphere?
Oh, it's Sphere.
What did I?
Oh, I have shit.
It's an Elvis based grapefruit beer.
There's a lot of good microbreweries in Vegas.
And this one is what is it?
Was it called Elvis juice?
I think it was Elvis juice.
You kept saying you were drinking Elvis juice.
I'm drinking Elvis juice, which is a good like I like a fruit beer.
And it was a yeah, I obviously ordered it because of the name.
Didn't matter if they were like, well, it was like, well, what's Elvis juice?
And they go, it's gasoline with a little lemon flavor.
I go, well, it's funny.
So I will order that.
But yes, I had that.
And then I forgot I had it.
It was rocking out so much.
I had a couple more drinks.
I don't remember what they were.
Not that I was so drunk.
I just don't remember.
There might have been just like a like a vodka or something or
whatever, because there were bartender stations on the floor.
There was like a like wait staff on the floor as well, walking around.
OK, so like you could just order something from somebody with a tray.
Really?
Yeah.
Huh.
OK, well, here's a sphere question I have then, because that actually seems like a pretty good
like the hospitality move.
It's something that's intrigued me about this for some of my sphere, my skepticism.
I think I said it differently.
Whatever.
It'll be different every time.
I like this idea that we're building a concert multimedia venue from the ground up as opposed
to taking a sports arena and retrofitting it and making it a place where concerts happen,
because those can be weird.
Yeah.
You know, they often are.
You're like craning your head because the stage is over here.
But and like it's meant to be seats meant for like a center court.
But instead, sure.
And football stadiums are so massive and weird.
So did you did you feel it filled up to the fulfilled the promise of that?
It being like you could tell like this is great that this is for concerts primarily new in 2023.
Yeah, I think so.
The only thing I would say is that I'm probably not because we're standing on the floor.
I bet the people in the seats had a better like read on that because the
like speakers are behind the seats.
So I probably wasn't even in the optimum spot for sound.
But I still thought the sound was awesome, except we were so close to the drums,
which have like the whatever you call it, those like plastic screens.
So like the bleed doesn't happen.
So I thought it sounded great.
And I thought like you can you can heat when Bono whispers, you can hear him whisper
in the whole place.
And I wonder if you were sitting way up.
I would be interested to sit up way up up in the top seats and see how good that sounds,
because that's that was the promise of it is that like every seat has good sound.
So I don't know for sure.
I'll have to go back.
What does he whisper?
I'm trying to remember.
Hold me through me.
Yes.
Oh, my God, I would have I would have fallen over if he said it.
He didn't.
He to confirm he did not do any Spider-Man the musical.
He did not do hold me through.
They have never performed any Spider-Man musical live in one of their concerts.
Question.
I know I was just the other day.
That was more like that's why they've come up a lot on the show.
That's been how they've been.
They started here.
Centered on the show.
Right.
Yeah, they've never done that in one of their shows.
They have done hold me through me kill me in the last 10 years, I think.
But they did not do it here.
So no, that didn't happen.
I would.
Oh, man, with like Batman forever visuals.
Oh, the comic, the cartoony visuals from the music video.
I mean, that would look completely like shit.
It would look like yes, the movie footage down res for M.T.V.
Uprez to 18K.
He's talking about that terrible television video.
Yeah, the animated Mr. McPhisto.
Yeah.
So yeah, no, I thought that like I'm trying to think what Bono said something about getting like
flirtatious.
He said he would say, you know, he would say some funny things and then he would say some things.
You go, God, he's like, you want to get flirtatious or something?
And I'm like, OK, right.
I think that was before mysterious ways, which is probably my least favorite song on a tongue baby.
But I'm trying to remember.
He sort of opens the show with like a kind of a chant sing.
And I forget what it's from, but it's how he opened up the zoo TV tour,
which is the original tour from this album 30 years ago.
It's self this many steps ahead multimedia presentation that that really was the the cutting
edge of video in a live show.
So it's a there's kind of a symmetry to that.
That pushed the ball forward so much 30 years ago.
I didn't realize.
Now there's this.
Yeah, they take credit for all of these type of tours in a way, like your airs tour and your
Beyonce tour and everything like in the sense that it's like you bringing a giant stage show
to every city and stadiums.
Which I guess, yeah, they're perhaps probably right.
I mean, it's the probably like big people had pushed it more with like amount of dancers
and spectacle, but maybe the video that specifically like you were going to retrofit a stadium with all
this crap.
Yeah, yeah.
That yeah, they were like one of the first or the first people to do it on that scale.
So here, let me get to the some of the things I think are a little not so funny,
but a little funny about the sphere.
I think the logo looks bad.
Like I think it looks it's very done, you know, like the thin rounded font.
The notion that we're supposed to we were supposed to call this sphere, right?
Not the sphere, which even Dolan himself in every interview.
So that's what we're doing with this fear.
He like no, he can't commit to it.
Right.
But I don't know this it feels like it should be more futuristic.
I should be more surprised by this.
Do you agree or disagree?
Or I think I agree.
I think that the futurism falls flat for me.
I think you're right.
And you have maybe a little inside knowledge, but the that they were there were maybe bigger
plans on the table that were scaled back.
And I think it kind of reeks of that because here's where I started to get
before it became clear that just it's YouTube concerts that are good.
I'm looking into this stuff and like, wait, what though?
Because the whole if you don't know this, the Darren Aronofsky movie,
Postcards from Earth, if you go to buy tickets for it, it does not say postcards from Earth.
It says the sphere experience.
I cannot.
It has me saying pH and every other word.
The sphere experience featuring Darren Aronofsky's postcards from Earth.
So you're like, what does that mean?
What's this like?
And this is to your point, Jason, about the high ticket prices.
It's like, well, it's not just a movie.
It's also the sphere experience.
And what is that?
Well, you get to explore the atrium of sphere.
You get to see which is a testament to technology.
And you know, OK, what does that mean?
Well, there's a math equation on the wall.
And that was something you sent us a photo.
Yeah.
That there and apparently what that is,
and you have no way of knowing this, but it's one of the equations used to build the sphere.
Right.
So wouldn't you agree that having a math equation up on the wall
encourages future generations to dream?
Sure.
Ponder that while you're drinking your big starry, you know.
Dreaming starry.
Pair them up.
Dolan himself, I found an interview.
Um, we see the sphere.
We see the sphere as being a medium.
It's a medium, but it's also exemplary of the use of technology and science and math,
particularly math.
You will see all around here, math equations all over the place.
We took all the equations we used to design and we put them all into one place.
And then there's QR codes on them.
And you could press on the QR code and see what that equation was used for.
And we'd love to get school children involved.
Yeah.
What is it?
This is the most meaningful tutorial.
Yeah, it doesn't.
I swear you can feel that in the lobby.
You can feel that this doesn't hang together.
It does feel like there's some like cool stuff, but if you really examine it,
there's just a lot of lights going on.
Yeah, you didn't seem blown away by, nor have I been just via photos of like,
that you go up an escalator.
Yeah, and then there's a bunch of blue rings and it changes maybe from blue to purple.
Yeah, it's like there's, yeah, there's just a bunch of circles.
If this just was what the cosmopolitan looked like, you'd go like,
wow, nice redo they did in 2015.
Yeah, that looks like the free installation art when you get off the MGM resorts,
people mover tram.
If you get off in one of the stations, there's a purple lighting installation.
Yeah, and there's like this thing that's like kind of,
I can't really, it doesn't translate it, but like the hologram situation.
What was this like in person?
Because this is a very underwhelming video.
It's like a little better in person, but I wouldn't say, oh my God, you got to see it.
Is there some way that you can get scanned yourself and be on that?
I feel like I read things to that effect.
Well, I'll say this, and maybe this leads you into your thing.
Also, I was thrilled about Aura because that's at least the draw for the lobby area.
And they were promoting this heavily on social media is that, you know,
there are multiple robots that you can converse with that know you too.
They know songs, you ask them questions, they respond, and that's a whole big thing.
There are four of them, which seems like too little, too few.
Five.
Too few.
Oh, five.
Five.
Five Auras.
Yeah, they started pushing, I feel like I'd heard that rumor.
And then there was a video that was just like a very close up piece of footage of Aura
who just says something like, you know, I can't wait to meet you at Sphere.
And the tagline that this comes with has been confounding me for weeks,
which is forget chat bots, come chat with some real bots.
Okay, so chat bots, we all know chat bots, they're part of our day to day,
and we're all thinking about them, remembering them, or constantly remembering them.
Well, forget them.
There are nothing compared to Aura, a real bot you can chat with.
Like a chat bot.
Right.
It also sounds sexual.
It sounds come chat with real bots.
Come chat with some real bots.
That sounds sexual in a way.
Well, if that was in a 1900 number commercial late night on TV at 2.30 in the morning,
forget chat bots, come chat with some real bots.
That's with the slappers, the card slappers on the Vegas Strip.
Forget chat bots, come chat with some real bots.
Come chat bots, come chat bots.
And the interview you found, I think, of James Dolan talking about Aura
also leads to like this weird like sex bot type underlying feeling.
Pretty fast.
Yeah, pretty fast.
Even though they're like, all five represent the sum of human experience,
or this one represents this, this one represents that.
Yes.
In theory, and this is the most Epcot-y thing ever, that there are five robots,
and they are all attributes of different facets of humans.
They represent connection, creativity, innovation, longevity, and productivity.
She was texting with Eva, she really jumped out at that one.
Longitivity.
A robot that represents the notion of longevity.
Now this I gotta see.
You're not gonna last five minutes talking to this robot.
You will melt at this real bot, let me tell you.
Yeah, now I don't remember what was in that clip.
I posted it on Twitter.
I think under the, I think my tweet was, everything's going not weird.
Oh yeah.
And then it was a live interview with Dolan on some morning TV show.
And then he says something about, you're gonna be enchanted.
You'll come here, you'll be enchanted.
Well, and who's that coming up right now?
Well, this is the enchantress.
Her name is Aura, you wanna say hi?
And then the reporter, I'll say the reporter says it, not Dolan.
The reporter says, now, if you walked up to Aura and tried to give her a kiss,
what would she say to that?
Ask her, what would you say, what would you do if somebody tried to kiss you?
And then weird pause, and she says, well, there's plenty of websites I can refer
to, different models I can refer you to, and then awkward silence.
And at this point in time, this is when I was thinking, this thing might be.
I still have Dolan in my head.
I'm still so freaked out by everything we learned about Dolan.
And now we're dealing with chat bots and come chat with some real bots.
Yeah.
And then we end up with this, that I made a discovery with like a week to go.
That I basically, I got algorithmed some YouTube video that was like,
this is the most realistic humanoid robot you'll ever see.
And I'm looking at it like, that's Aura though, isn't it?
Isn't that the Sphere?
I've been looking at this Sphere robot a ton, that's it.
But this was some outside thing.
This is from the BBC or something.
I don't know what this is.
And I start looking at that and they call this robot a MAKA.
And I'm staring at it.
I'm staring at Aura, I'm going back and forth.
Aura is a MAKA.
This is not a custom robot.
No.
It's an off the shelf robot.
This is an off the shelf robot.
And I sent this, full disclosure, we've had a text thread called Sphere Squad
going for a little while.
That's the three of us and Eva Anderson and Jason Waller.
I've had a lot of fun with Sphere Squad.
And he was the first, he responded in the morning.
I'm like, yeah, wait a minute.
God damn it.
Dolan stole these robots.
And I was like, what's the story here?
And he said, the story is he stole,
he hijacked a bunch of robots to put a new name plaque on him.
Uh huh.
Jason also pointed out that Aura, like her body goes into this weird point
at like a particularly odd point.
In her crotch.
Yes, at the crotch, at the crotch.
And as he phrased it, why did they make Aura's vagina so shiny?
And it is, there's just this like sparkle glisten at this pointed crotch.
In this, all of this is just like.
It's weird.
Where are we now?
And then Aura's stolen.
It's this whole other company, Engineered Arts.
And their website's really strange where it says like, well, you know,
you can customize them and update them all without having to fork out for an entire new robot.
And Jason's like, fork out?
What world are we in where we're so casual with robot spending,
that we're just, you know, you get sick of forking out for new robots every other week.
I bet what it really felt like was like this thing went, the sphere itself went over budget,
like what, a billion dollars or something?
It's just a billion dollars.
And there were grand plans for original robots.
Yes.
A whole narrative.
Must be that.
All of this.
And then all of a sudden it was like, fuck shit.
Oh no, no money, no money, warning.
Oh, who got a robot we can take?
Okay, five of them.
Can we cut me a deal for five of these robots?
Can we find a robot that has the, like some of the letters that we want
and we can just chip off the others?
Okay, just replace the middle.
They just replaced the middle.
That saves us so much work.
Five name plaques.
Robot from Rocky III or IV.
They used to be at that nightclub off I-95 by Philadelphia.
There's like four or five of those still floating around, right?
Can we have those?
Seiko.
Make them smarter.
Four Seiko, five Seikos.
Make the Seiko smarter and sexier.
Make it get his vagina shining.
Make it hot Seiko.
Hot Seiko.
That one aura video too where it's like I can't wait to see you at,
that's exactly the same as the Charm of Song.
Oh yeah.
And going like I can't wait to see you on Pandora.
Do we get that?
And that was funnier.
Like that looked better.
The robot was better too.
And it was charming.
Yeah, and the whole point of it is you're looking at it so close and wow look how realistic.
This was the opposite.
All the comments were, this is the moment where I was like is this going to be bad,
this fear thing?
Because the comments are like well this scares the hell out of me.
I don't want to go anywhere near aura.
And then you sent, I loved the comment that you found.
Oh yeah.
Somebody just angrily saying you can't,
this isn't aura, this is a mecha.
You can't fool us.
Can't fool us.
Somebody knew a mecha.
Sorry, we also have to talk about the most important of the Sphere Squad group chat.
Mike left at one point.
Oh we'll get to that.
Yeah, we'll get to that.
You didn't want spoilers.
Actually Eva wasn't on it.
Eva was brought in to replace you like Kirstie Alley on Shears.
That's right.
We got hit the ground running.
We can't just leave this spot empty.
We need a great new cast member to come in.
But now it's great, now everybody's back together.
So now you've got like a supersized cast in this first squad.
But so with all of this mecha, I mean if this were me and I had already booked these tickets,
my feeling walking into Sphere would be like, okay, I'll get my starry or my elvish juice.
And then it's a beeline to a mecha.
It's time for me to meet a mecha.
I'm sorry, aura.
It's time for me to meet aura, who I know is a mecha.
And actually, you know, I need to find my seat.
Why ask a human to take me down there?
Why not just go straight to, I'm here.
I'm going to ask aura.
I'm not going to ask some dumb person.
Right.
So is this how you were feeling at this point?
So we went upstairs and I'll explain why we went upstairs.
Because we kind of entered on the ground floor because it was GA.
So we entered upstairs and I'm looking around, of course, because I'm where's aura?
Where I want to see one of the auras.
And I don't see auras.
I don't see anyone.
You didn't see innovation or productivity aura?
Our longevity, I didn't see any of them.
So we had a question for a human employee.
And of course, that question was, where is the like family room?
So Lindsay can express breast milk because that's still happening with her body.
And I'm just saying this because she tweeted it.
This isn't I'm not sharing a tale out of school here.
There's no reason to be.
So and then once that question was asked and half answered because the person wasn't quite sure.
God, I wish I could have answered that question.
Well, like she could have helped with all of this.
I wish I could produce breast milk.
I wish I could reproduce at all.
But my vagina.
They did it.
My vagina is shorn to a shiny nub.
So I never can.
James didn't pay for the upgrade.
I am only rented.
Another 200,000 per robot.
He paid for the Norton anti-virus so that aura wouldn't go like humans and your fluids.
Disgusting.
You deserve nothing but fire.
James wouldn't fork out for me to produce breast milk.
So I go like, oh, hey, excuse me.
We are other robot, you know, the robots that you can talk to.
And the guy goes, oh, not working.
They don't work on concert nights.
And I go, wait, well, so what I because we talked about this.
James was really acting like you will talk to the robots on you to concert night.
Yes.
That was the plan.
They're going to be a guy.
They're going to chant you to your seat because that B12 they'll say E14.
If that's where you're sitting, so they'll know all about it.
And the whole big like one of the press things or one of the interviews was like
the robot was saying what's your favorite you to song.
Mine is I forget what was there's a joke there.
I forget.
Oh, it was something about like, oh, it's so hard to choose, but
every day here at sphere is a beautiful day.
Right.
So ha ha ha ha.
Aura was planned, like was was programmed to tell funny you to style jokes, but clearly
something happened and I don't know what happened.
I'd like to think some drunken you to fan like hassled the robot too much and they were
like shut it down too much alcohol in here.
Plus a robot that's very accessible does not mix.
So I think that I found although I guess I don't have a good picture.
I think they just tarped them.
I think they just tarped the area.
Really?
I'm not positive.
They're heavy.
You don't want to move those in and out.
Did you see five tarps?
I didn't see five tarps.
This is what I'm not sure of.
There was there was something with like a tarp and I couldn't tell there weren't five of them.
So I don't know if the future display you assumed it was a branded Epcotty.
And that's what it was.
But I don't know if they wheeled some of them out and they will.
But something clearly happened early because I went to second or third second week, I think,
of the concerts.
So some like baby boomer you to fan did something that made them go fuck.
We got it.
We can't.
Aura is not safe in front of the you to fans.
It's all right.
All right.
She moves them stairs with blah.
Yeah.
Throw open Aura's mouth.
Oh, no.
Sir.
She can't talk about connection anymore.
One of the large men who are not high fiving each other.
He just gave Aura a short arm clothesline.
We need to do something.
It is probably because they're like Aura is going to get damaged
and we do not have money to replace Aura.
So the postcards from Earth crowd is a little more civil.
Aura.
Here's what happened.
All five hours when they saw George Clooney and Randy Gerber walk by them all knowing
that the briefcase story is the pinnacle of human achievement.
Their brains couldn't handle processing seeing these two titans together.
Are they all melted down?
Are the two motorcycles outside?
I want to see if they rode the motorcycles here.
George, Randy, come here.
George, Randy, we must talk to you.
We must procreate.
You are the best of your species.
Please pass your good genes along to me.
Tell James to download our procreation update.
Please make him pay the funds so we may procreate with you, George and Randy.
You and your wife were Cher and Greg Ullman.
As for Halloween, we loved it.
Everyone knows that.
Everyone is aware.
A common story.
Surely there must be another Randy Gerber story that is told over and over on podcasts.
So all of this in some ways transpired and that's why they tarped ARA for concerts.
And that was a big letdown.
I was so excited to see ARA.
So Jason is right.
I left on opening night of Sphere Squad on the text chain because I didn't want to be spoiled
even though everybody was posting shit so I saw a lot of stuff.
But then I joined in line again or like I know the night before.
Rejoined Sphere Squad.
Which was a thrill.
To be getting the real-time updates from you then.
Because how quickly this became the talk of the town.
I have friends who are like, well, wait, Mike's there now?
Mike's seeing it right now?
You were like in such prime position.
Well, you texted me and said, add me back to Sphere Squad.
And I said, are you sure?
And he said, yes.
Yes.
There's been many, many things said about ARA.
But the possibilities of ARA.
They wouldn't let, it didn't, it did not show me previous messages though.
So I didn't have to go back and catch up.
So yeah, so that was a big letdown.
Then we found the family room where Lindsay could do her thing.
Which is just looks like a doctor's office.
I was like, will this be themed?
Will this sort of all-purpose room be themed?
The answer is no, but the chairs look fine.
And this was, I'll say this.
I'll say this.
This was right by the guest complaint center.
So there were an angry line of people right outside this door.
And this door was not locked.
So I had to go, we were a little too late getting the concert.
So we made it on time for the show to start.
But I'm standing outside with two drinks trying to prevent people from going into this room
that people think is a bathroom.
While Lindsay is just pumping milk.
And people are like, what's this rumor?
I go, oh, it's a family room.
I think it's not a bathroom or anything.
And then I'm not trying to like not say what's going on in there.
But like, oh, okay.
And then all of a sudden you'll hear what we paid for.
This is unprofessional what's going on here.
Okay.
There's this guy who's really like aggressively yelling at this small woman about something.
I'm trying to figure out what it is, but I'm also trying to keep an eye on the door.
I'm also holding two drinks.
I'm also worried we're not going to get there when the show,
like we're not going to make it back to the floor.
That's tough room to walk into.
You might really, you might fall over.
And this, and I think what had happened was people,
there were like these packages sold through a website.
And the packages were giving people tickets that were in obstructed view areas that didn't
specify when they bought it, that there was going to be an obstructed view.
Oh, cause that came out.
If you're under those boxes, if you're under the second level,
you can see the band perfectly, but you can't see no sphere.
Yes.
And they didn't indicate that at all.
Yes. A lot of people, a lot of seats, a lot of seats.
I think people bought packages that were very expensive and they got there and they were
furious, which I understand there was a group of older ladies who were being much nicer and
kinder than this guy who was yelling.
And I just, I saw somebody came up to them and this woman was just like, look,
all I can do is I can give you some free t-shirts.
I'm so sorry what happened.
I can give you some shirts.
There's no other place to really move you.
So that's what I can do.
And these like ladies were just like, okay, okay.
And then they like, whatever happened happened and all this is going on.
I'm holding two drinks, checking the phone.
I'm asking like show start.
Like I see like a guy who works at shows.
When does the show start?
Well, 8 45.
Okay. Okay.
And then I'm like texting, you're almost done.
Want to rush it?
I know that's a biological thing that you really can't.
When it's done, it's done.
And then I think I walked over to check something out and I came back
and some employee had taken the tape off the door that allowed it to stay open.
And now the door was locked.
So I tried to like kind of go to there and check it and the door is locked.
And I'm texting like, uh, door is locked.
Or is it locked?
It's not locked from the inside, right?
Like you're not locked in the sphere family, general family.
You're not in there with Dolan.
Are you?
No, you're right.
And I was like, oh shit.
There was a screen in there and she was like, no, go get some drinks.
And I'm like, but you're like prone in here.
Like I should I leave?
So like what is going on?
Also, this is a, this is a $2.3 billion venue with robots and AI
and they're putting tape on doors.
There are as a tape, there's tape keeping this door open.
No one ever really told.
They just told us a vicinity of where we should go to do this.
No one really said go in here and do it.
So he just took the room over.
That's Adam Clayton's dressing room.
He's like practicing baseball.
The employee break room.
It's a sob room where the employees go to cry after they get yelled at.
In the website selling obstructed seats.
A thousand dollar packet, two thousand dollar packets.
You can't see any of the screen.
I paid for a five hour Aura meet and greet and I come and find a tarp.
So I paid a thousand dollars for you too and a thousand dollars for the big screen saver.
And if I don't get the big screen saver, I went a thousand dollars back.
So all of this is this, it's a little stressful to start out.
As I said, they're playing unnerving little snippets of like just pieces of music
from October baby in different contexts by the album.
Yes.
The song is so cruel that like it's kind of, it's not, it's kind of a pleasant song,
but they're like, just like have a ghostly snippet of Bono singing.
And it's just like echoing.
And I'm just like, we're going to make it as somebody, an angry man at the complaint
desk and a burst in on Lindsay.
Like, I'm just like, okay, this is a little, I'm a little too unnerved breast milk inside a giant baby.
Yeah.
Every aspect of this is a nightmare.
Aura is not around.
There's no Aura.
And you are, you're serve at, you're at a door directing customers around the sphere.
You're doing what Aura is supposed to be doing.
I am doing some work for the sphere at this point.
I'm directing Travis juice.
You're a living AI ball.
Are you like, are you in the line for this complaint?
I'm like, no, no, no, I'm, I'm just waiting out here.
I'm just, but what's, what's this a bathroom?
No, no, that's not a bathroom.
When do they go on?
Well, I've heard, sir, that it's on 840.
No, Larry Mullen's playing, right?
No, excuse me, sir.
Larry Mullen is at a back issue and he, they will, but there's a new drummer named Bram
that is filling in for Larry, a younger man.
They're doing all kinds of songs, not just from one album, right?
Well, they are, well, mostly one album, but they are doing some songs from other albums.
Yes, I know you saw Larry film the video for atomic city in Las Vegas a few weeks ago,
but he is not here tonight.
He did play drums on that, but there was only a limited amount of time in his back.
He still needs maybe another surgery before he's really good to go.
Tell me some interesting facts about Bram.
Now I'd like to hear about the history of longevity.
Oh, okay.
Well, sir.
Uh, uh, uh,
Long.
Longitimity or longevity?
Longevity.
Long either one, your choice.
Don't tell me about latitude though.
I don't want to hear my fucking latitude.
I got to, I paid seven thousand dollars for my seats and I can only see Bono's feet.
I can only see his calves and his feet.
I could walk to the wind and see a big frog puppet smoking a cigar right now, but I'm here.
For free.
The film show.
So we, so, oh yeah, my blood pressure is a little high, not super high, but a little high.
And then finally, okay, Lindsay's done.
We have like five, 10 minutes to before when, when they said, uh, we have to be there for the
show to start.
And in some ways it felt kind of lawless.
Like we were definitely going in like doors that felt like exits to get back to escalators,
to get us back to the bottom floor.
Um, I sent some photos of it and I'm like, if this weren't for the like spacey music and like
one blue light, these hallways are not like state of the art hallway.
That looks like an arc light.
Yeah.
So if you took away the music and the lights, you'd just be like, well, there's this doesn't
seem like a futuristic sphere building.
Which just, yeah, leads into what I feel is maybe we're budget cuts.
But anyway, so you get to the main event, the main attraction is this fear, which
is better than you think it is, I think.
Okay.
And that's where, so you've seen the pictures on the, on the internet.
It's, it's a big screen and they make it at the start of the concert, look like it's almost
like an iron walls that extend all the way up to the ceiling.
And yes, if you see it, you could get fooled into thinking there's a hole in the top of
the sphere, which is impractical unless it could be closed.
Thought it was potentially retractable.
I don't know.
That's just how the magic of Dolan and the wizards that he employed.
Of sphere.
That was sphere.
And there's a, there's a, you probably on social media, there's a, there's a car that is,
a DJ is in, it's like a neon car.
Yeah.
And a DJ is spinning Viva Las Vegas and some other songs that this will probably start playing.
But like he's, there's, there's men just dragging this car around.
That's how it moves?
Through the GA pit while this guy.
Annoying?
No, it's cool.
I like it.
Okay.
It's silly that like guys have to be like pushing it because you would think, oh,
maybe it's like a trackless vehicle.
It's Wi-Fi controlled.
No, we are in a high tech, the highest of technology.
No, it's being moved like stage hands.
Four stage hands pushing this car and this DJ around and he's hyping the crowd up for the show.
But I don't know.
It's kind of cool.
It's like a Tron car.
It's like an old time car with some lights on it.
I like it fine.
Can't be mad at that.
At Disney Springs right now for Halloween, you know, there is a DJ in a kind of big pumpkin
that has Hulu ads and Disney Plus ads on the back.
Is there neon?
It was daytime.
I couldn't really tell when I saw.
Less interested.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm interested in the Hulu buzz pumpkin.
I thought that's, you just thought of another notable DJ situation going on across America.
A movable DJ.
Right.
A movable.
I see.
That's the connection.
DJs aren't just spinning their wheels.
They're on them.
That's right.
Lindsay took a cool photo of the sphere and that DJ that she posted somewhere.
I forget where.
And then the DJ was just after he was done, he hops out of the car.
He's just hanging out behind us and she went up and was like, look at the picture.
So that's awesome.
It's a really nice dude.
I forget.
I should find his handle.
That's cool.
But he's DJing, I guess, before all these shows.
And that's right.
And the G, I'll say this about the pit too.
Comfortable.
It wasn't packed.
If you wanted to hang back by the little bar area, perfectly fine to sit back there.
This is shocking about this, that they are not just like cramming people in.
Yes, I was shocked as well.
You can go up pretty close if you want, but you can back up.
Like it's the most comfortable, one of the most comfortable situations in like a pit
that you could possibly get.
You can cut this out if you want.
You don't have to say a number.
Please.
But was this an expensive experience to be on the floor?
Or is it somehow cheaper on the floor because the seats are what you want if you want the show?
Oh, I mean, I'll say it.
It's certainly an indulgence of a ticket.
It's $250 for a ticket.
Yeah.
So just the price of one postcard from Earth.
But that's not so great.
For something that is like top tier, do you have any idea what seats are?
Or is that just the price of everything?
The cheapest ticket is the top level for 140, probably 160 or 70 after.
These are standard prices for any old act in a stadium at this point.
Yeah, that's not a jaw dropper.
It's crazy.
I remember when I first, I saw Bruce Springsteen like 15 years ago or 10 years ago,
and it was like, maybe it was a hundred and something.
And then now it's all like 250.
Like all these tickets have like tripled in cost.
So I was shocked that those, the GA tickets, they're also doing a cool thing with the
tickets, with the pit tickets where you can't resell them.
If you can't go, you just put them back on Ticketmaster for a face.
So if you check, which is how I got these, you just check and periodically you can get them
and nobody can like put them on like StubHub.
This is great.
This whole, that's because the pretty cool concert ticket industry.
Oh, it's so crazy.
Yeah.
So I love if it's resetting some of that crap.
So at least that area, not all of it, but just the pit area is like that.
Wow.
So that's like, it's weird because it's like, do you recommend, I kind of,
if you really like hate U2, I guess you wouldn't want to spend this kind of money to go.
I really like 90s U2.
So obviously that made it much better.
But yeah, if you're judging it against any other crazy Taylor Swift tickets, anything,
it's like pretty much right, right there.
Or better.
I think you probably could gotten away with selling these for $500 each.
Then maybe they'll start as we record this.
They've just recently put, they've added many dates to this,
indicating that at least this stint of it is going pretty great.
And so what they'll, so they'll be doing this into early 2024 at least.
Yeah.
And they're getting, they're getting, the sphere is not making a ton of money on these shows
because U2 is getting a nice deal.
Yeah.
Did I say this previously in any episode or in the live one?
This is some of the, again, some of my spectacism is U2 gets 10 million up top.
Then they get 90% of the concert sales.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's again, the venue cost 2.3 billion.
So now it's just a matter of how many flips without a Z they can sell.
And I think they have a, they can like extend it to for two years, maybe if they wanted.
So they're definitely, I think like, well, the U2 will give us the buzz to get the other acts in.
Yes.
But now what?
I mean, you used to, I'll let you know, say your two piece, but.
I wonder, I wonder if part of it's like the next band or two are like, well, we want that deal.
Yes.
The deal with you, we read about the best deal that any bands ever gotten.
Yeah.
So I don't wonder if that is any factor.
So yeah.
So at that point, so yeah, like the iron walls, there's a helicopter that goes over this in the
little hole in the ceiling, the fake hole.
Oh, I didn't know that part.
Yeah.
So like when the show starts, I guess this is if U2 has landed in it from a helicopter there.
And it looks, I mean, at that point, I think you know it's a screen,
but still it looks pretty convincing.
Cutting it a little close, aren't we guys?
That's how they do it.
You know.
Let's be more prompt next time.
Yeah.
Uh, and then the band comes out and you're shocked at how close they are
and how small this stage is for U2.
I've seen U2 twice before.
Once at the 360 tour, which was in the Rose Bowl at this like insane concoction of a stage.
I don't know if you've ever seen this with like four posts and you could walk all the way around it
in a color like a circle light that Bono swung from.
I remember that.
Yeah.
And the black eyed peas opened for them.
Sick.
Yeah.
So 2008.
Yeah, that was about that.
Not 2008.
It was about 2008.
2009.
And I did see the Joshua Tree tour at the Rose Bowl, but that was more of a regular stage.
So yeah, Bono comes out and he does some chanting or singing or whatever that he did on the ZOO TV
tour.
And then after he's done, he takes the glasses and he puts on the fly glasses.
And here we go.
He is the fly.
He is back.
And then the big like...
What though?
The fly is what?
The whole album is the fly in it?
Yeah.
Well, that's one of the songs too.
It's one of the characters.
One of the characters.
Now I will say there's not much character stuff here.
No mirror ball man?
No mirror ball man.
No McFisto.
Bono wears like a white jacket at the end of the show, but he doesn't put on little
devil ears.
He doesn't do it.
There's any criticism I have of the show, it's that.
Is that he didn't do any of that.
He focused on the visuals, whatever.
So yeah, then they do ZOO Station.
The first part of ZOO Station, the song is like...
And then it's like chipping away at the iron wall and then it'll drop and the whole
thing opens up to be this big TV wall that looks like the old tour.
And what's cool also is they're integrating live video from the stage into the graphics
on the screen.
Other times they'll go by in bubbles and stuff.
You can present them in a lot of funny ways.
You could star wipe things if you wanted.
You could do live stuff like that.
So yeah, Bono is on a little road.
Brian Eno made up the stage and really the stage is just like a turntable and it turns.
Which is cool looking, but...
It's weird in the visuals though that it is this tiny stage.
It's very off putting seeing no amps and no lights.
Almost no lights.
It is off puttingly minimal.
It is weird and it almost seems like it's fake or they're pretending.
U2 is one of those bands that does a weird thing where they have other musicians that
are hidden.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh.
So some of the synth or string parts, the real U2 heads know these people's names are
one or two people and they're under the stage playing for Streets of Oden.
They want to keep the stage picture of the four guys for whatever reason.
They're liars.
Yes.
I don't know.
I'm not...
I don't know that they have to do that.
How many people you think?
I don't know.
At least one.
If not two.
I got five hours playing violins and tubas.
Maybe it's the whole James Dolan band under there helping out.
JD and the Strait Shouter down there.
I know you're going to need the backup guys.
If you need me, just say the word A and I'll throw in the straight shot for free.
I got my axe with me.
I'll jump in.
Edge falls off stage.
I'll be there.
I won't even miss a note.
You know every night he's like, you need a guy?
You need a guy to play?
Just stand on the trap door.
Just move a little.
If Edge gets hurt, you know I'm there.
I got the button.
I got the reverb pedal.
I know the delay in the reverb.
I know how to do it.
I got the album on my iPhones.
I know the songs.
I've been practicing the backup vocals too.
Dear Will, listen.
He's just sending voice memos on his phone to Bono.
Pretty good, huh?
Calling the name.
James, those automatically delete after you've listened to them.
Do you know that?
Damn Aura should have warned me.
I got a live-in robot and she didn't say nothing.
Hey, Bram.
Bram, can you put in a word for me, Bram?
The guys don't like me as much.
Seems like they're open to new guys, right?
If they let you in, Bram, right, Bram?
You have Bono's ear, right, Bram?
Bram.
Come on, Bram.
All right, Seiko, you're my last best hope.
Send you out into the parking lot and act like you're walking by.
You just happen to run into them.
Maybe it'll happen.
I don't know.
They have a pretty set.
They changed some of the songs around in the middle, but they play all of Octane Baby.
They don't play it in order on the album, which I guess that's fine.
I kind of like it when they do the album the way it was structured,
but I understand it's not necessarily the best live way if they feel the energy's off.
So I don't know.
I don't have to go through every song or anything, but the highlights I'm sure a lot of people have
seen on social media is that first Zootv part and then the second song they play.
And that's when you get another throwback to Zootv with all these words, outrage, cancel culture.
It's so funny.
Part of it, I like it, is because it's so self-serious, but also it thinks it's...
Octane Baby era, you two, to me, they think they're not being as serious as they were in the 80s,
and they're not quite being as serious, but they're still very serious.
Yeah.
As not particularly a fan, I'm put off, but yeah, this word wall.
This is what we're doing now with 30 years later.
It's just a much bigger word wall.
Yes, but that song has the maybe the coolest thing in the whole show,
which is the big colorful number.
That's the same song?
That's the same song.
Oh boy.
And you've seen this.
I've seen the numbers.
This is the mic drop.
And all of a sudden, yeah, so all of a sudden you get very...
What would you call those numbers?
Very old school computer style digits.
Oh, I don't know the right thing.
You know what I'm saying though?
And they're all one color, they change colors.
All of a sudden a few of them change colors.
And then in the middle, the bridge part of it or the middle interlude section of the song,
the numbers are climbing to the point of making the ceiling seem like it's
three times the height that you previously thought it was.
And then all of a sudden the whole thing comes crashing down almost like a trash compactor
of numbers on the sides and the ceiling.
So if you're even looking at it in videos from the right angle,
it looks like you're in a cube now.
Which is like...
It changes the shape of the amp.
It changes the shape of the place.
Shut me up.
I mean, it's cool.
It's really cool.
It's really, really cool.
And also makes you think like, okay, this is the potential for this in some other ways.
Where you can do stuff like this for an even more ambitious show.
Yeah, they do that.
An Escher painting with like 10,000 levels.
Sure.
The biggest Where's Waldo?
That ever was.
Wow, Where's Waldo Live?
Yeah, whoa.
And if you get it, your ticket is free.
Yeah.
So at this point, especially like, there's an argument to be made that sitting in like
the very expensive, like probably thousand dollar seats in the right place,
you get the full picture of everything.
But I would say for the seat or the standing room that costs a quarter,
I almost liked feeling like I was going to get crushed by the numbers.
Like the whole thing was very overwhelming in a way where you're like looking at the
band, but then you're looking up and it really like you could, if you didn't look at the floor,
you would kind of forget that you were in a building that was on earth.
Wow.
So like that, and then especially the next song,
which has like a crazy almost, I think somewhat AI created,
bizarre gold, like you know what I'm talking about?
Like really complex, super like, I mean, it's somewhat reminiscent of like Kanye power type,
like really, really hyper designed.
Yes. And like, uh, uh, there's a weird stuff that I really can't explain this thing,
like, and then this thing rotated almost like a hamster wheel,
which made you feel like the whole building was turning in a crazy way.
You know, it really looks like the Michael Jackson Dangerous album cover.
Yeah.
Times 10,000.
Yes, it does. Now, if you look in this bizarre thing, you will find, and I did not send this to
you, you will find a clip from American beauty. You will find this.
A lady doing like a yoga pose.
Is that from Showgirls?
Oh, it is. Oh, oh, oh yeah.
So there's a weird hidden.
What's from American beauty in it?
I don't, is it Minas, it looks like Minas Uvari, like one of the fantasy sequences.
That's, oh no.
I thought we've moved on from this pop culture.
I thought so too. And I don't know, but that's certainly from Showgirls.
That purple top.
So there's a bunch of weird, like this, like Riviera.
There's a lot of Elvis talk in this show.
Hell yeah. Relevant. Interesting.
Yeah. There's like.
The legend. We have to, we have to address the legend in the room.
Yeah. He does say shit like that.
I mean, yeah, in Vegas, you kind of have to, at least there was.
Do you?
They love it in Vegas. I'm not saying you have to.
They love it in Vegas. And at least it was just a giant hit movie out.
Yes, you're right. And a giant hit cartoon show, right boys?
Remember?
Did it come out?
It came out.
Oh really?
Yeah. The cartoon where Matthew McConaughey is the voice of Elvis.
I remember that.
Yes, it was released. We all know it.
I was told the thing I pitched wasn't going because of that, but that's all I remember.
Sounds right.
So yeah, so there's this, that thing makes you feel like you're going to fall over maybe if
you stared at it too long. And then there's.
Was anything ever too much or was it just, was it all like right on?
Elated the whole time.
What about the animal wall? You haven't mentioned the animal wall.
Well, that's at the end of the show. I'm trying to just get some highlights here real quick.
I keep jumping ahead.
Because I understand you can find all this. You're going to find this.
There's a weird point where there's like Kennedy and the rocket launch or whatever.
And then.
Oh yes.
I love the sentry being condensed for me anywhere that can happen.
And then you're like, and I remember we're like, what is this?
I hope the next act is fallout boy doing their new, we didn't start the fire with visuals.
Let's get a fallout boy in there.
They announced blink 182 is playing sofi like next year. And I was like, wow,
blink can sell out sofi I guess. So put blink in the sphere.
Sure.
Move the when we were young festival.
Yeah.
To the sphere.
Sure. I'm on for that. So there was the song until the end of the world, they're playing,
there was a lightning storm in there. That was pretty cool.
The lightning would strike during the chorus.
At this point in the show, the fog happens and there's some heavy fog and we were right
by the machines. I think I said in a video of like hiss, like probably the immersion was broken a
little bit because of the hiss of the fog machines.
But it's right where you were there in hot season. So it made you feel right at home.
That's true.
Your fog hiss.
And yeah, at this point there's like a burning flag in the middle of the desert that shoots up
and they're basically like giving you like fire effects from the fog,
which I'm sure would look even better from a little bit of a distance.
That's worth it.
Not just being to sit there.
That's fine. Be close to it.
And then who's going to ride your wild horses highlight because it's just
raining embers in the sphere while you see all four of them playing.
So detailed.
You know what's nuts about it is you're showing these phone videos and I've seen a lot of phone
videos and you're like, how is it conveyed? Anybody could just without any correction or
adjustment, film it on their phone as is and it looks super cool.
Yeah, I was wondering if it was going to show up. And then during,
oh shoot, I forget exactly which song it was, but all of a sudden there's the whole place just goes
blue. It's crazy because just like they can change the lights. It can be feel like daytime
in there all of a sudden. Like you can do really it really seeing the concert, you're just like,
oh, it's scratched the surface of this place in a lot of ways where you're like,
cause like all of a sudden just one song, it's just there it's blue in there.
It's just this odd blue.
Yeah.
And then slowly but surely like different bugs, like shadows of bugs as if there's giant bugs on
the outside of the sphere have landed and died. And there's, they slowly happen. They slowly appear
while the song is going on. And I was like, this is nuts. This is creepy as hell. And it would kind
of come back later with the, what you're talking about the animal wall. But then yeah, they did,
they did the rest of Octon Baby. They do sort of a quiet set with, they can change up the songs,
some old songs and they just do it kind of acoustic. But that's where I was like,
this is just projecting them playing and the music, the audio sounds amazing. You probably
could just bring people in for a couple of dates and be worth it to go to the spheres to see them
projected.
Question. Does you, do you fit, does it ever feel like not enough, like too minimal if they aren't
using the full?
Yeah, I don't know. Maybe people would be let down, but I don't know. You,
you could give them like a generic video package.
Yeah, I think you're going to have to start doing, yeah, background walls, like come with our photo
booths on our Apple products. Wow. A bunch of balloons, a waterfall.
So Don Henley is playing in there and then like the toaster screensaver is playing behind him.
I did see specula, the names I had heard rumored of like, well, this is who could be fit. Like
Eagles are playing some dates around the Superbowl because the Superbowl is at a Legion stadium
in Vegas. And they're like, could the Eagles do a super show?
Fail. F idea. If the next thing is Eagles, this place is fucked. That is not, I've been thinking
this so hard that like the, whoever is next has to be a generation down or even if fucking Dolan
just plugs his asshole buddies in there, this place is screwed.
Okay. I don't have any insider info. It was merely they're playing some Vegas dates. They
know James Dolan, they're on a farewell tour. Sure. Sure. Sure. So we kind of added up
Harry Styles was the other name of like, well, he's sold some big stadiums recently.
Fish is rumored. I think the feeling with fish might be fun. Well, the feeling with fish is that
fish is lighting and all the stuff they do has to be sort of improvised along with the band because
Hey, they may jam for 25 minutes on a song. They may jam for 35 minutes. Oh, they can't be locked
in. They can't be locked in. So they have to figure out a way to do it. That isn't just sort
of a show like you two is doing. So that's a timed show. So if they can do that, they can do it.
If it's a small parking lot, you can't really tailgate, you know, can't tailgate for the fish
show. They haven't figured out the smoking lounge is yet in Vegas either. They're getting open.
You go to the tilted kilp by the link. You can pregame for a fish show. It's open.
Don't you think the fish is like fish can't play like three months though.
These the fish people are intense. Yeah, I know they're massive. I don't know. They'll do,
you know, they'll do a giant venue for three nights. But like, if you don't think like what's
the amount that you two is doing? Can fish do even like 10% of that? I think that if you give
people enough time that the there will be like fish people will come. I know if you say this is
what is going to be doing this year. I think fish people will come and do a week of shows or more.
I know multiple they could do for sure. I just don't know if they're like, I don't think they do
three months of fish. I know multiple people who have traveled. Yes. Everyone's correct. Yes. But
I'm saying a couple nights of Madison's garden does not equal three nights, three months of the
sphere. Well, I would, but I would argue that in some ways it does because Vegas is such a traveling
city that if you're a man who can fill up 20,000 seats a couple nights in a row in a major city,
that's indicative of having an audience that might travel to see a crazier version of your show.
Sure. And the elevation of it being sphere. Yeah. So I don't know if they could do a year of it,
but I think I got a solid enough run. I think you've got enough people that are coming. Yeah. For
a couple months. I could be, you gotta be sad that your boy Buffett will never know the pleasure
to see an 18 K big spinning cheeseburger. I know. Or we'll just even just, they put like a,
have it like be on the water and make everybody get seasick while the show's going. Like,
I think like kind of that thing when you're in a boat, having everybody feel like that,
they're doing the show at sea. Some of those clips were making me a little seasick. I feel like.
From the sphere? Yeah. Yeah. I wonder if that will, it didn't happen to you,
but I wonder if it'll happen to anybody. Yeah, probably. Maybe. But I would think it might
happen more on the floor because you're in such a weird angle. Sure. But yeah, it's way up behind
you. You're craning your head all the way up. But like, you could see, I mean, you could see all the
things like all of a sudden, yeah, all of a sudden we're in the desert. It's lit up. The sun comes
out. It's like just, it's insane because it feels just like you're actually watching the sun. Yeah.
That's really. Yeah. Rise. Yeah. And then yeah, during where the streets have no name,
all of a sudden there is some sphere lore here because really that's the sphere. All of a sudden
you're in an area of like a desert with some water and there's a big sphere that's like approaching
you as the song goes on. Wow. That's the character of the sphere. Yeah. So the sphere appears
and then you're in the ocean with the sphere. And then at the big, whoa, whoa, part is when this
crazy thing happens that truly could make you feel dizzy, which is why, like basically the sphere
opens up in these like layers of, I don't know what do you even call them. It's basically like,
it looks like a fractals. Fractal. Kind of. It looks almost like some sort of carvings of
animal. Like somebody did intricate carvings of animals in a piece of, I don't know, wood or
something like light wood. And now there's like layers opening up the sphere opens up and now the
whole place is like this big art piece now of all these different like carving, like animal carvings
essentially. And I've been saying, this is one that I've maybe haven't gotten my head around fully
is that the finale of this is a big animal. I think there's some, I feel like I read somewhere
it was like, these are endangered species or something. There's some version of that.
From the Nevada area. But then there's like, well, Eva pointed out, there's a lot of snakes,
a bunch of big snakes on the wall and then big bugs. I don't think I get this aspect of it.
Maybe should I get it in that it's weird that you seem to be liking that it's weird. I do like it.
Yeah. It's not the cleanest thing you've ever, but I think of the majesty of the animal wall is a
little lost on me. I mean, you think I would get it in person? Yeah. Cause it's looks crazy in person.
You go, yeah, I don't know exactly. I don't know if I'm getting the message here, but boy,
it's fun to look at. Like, which is, uh, yeah, that happens a lot. So, uh, no, I'm not saying I
completely understand the subtleties of, of the message necessarily, but they sang beautiful day.
I mean, they did look, we were, when we did our Mr. McPhisto episode, we were joking around about
elevation. I'm on such a high at this point, they do elevation and I'm like, elevation is one of the
best songs I've ever heard. Like we're all like hopping up and down during elevation. I'm like,
yeah, this is great. They do beautiful day. Uh, uh, they did vertigo, which is not my favorite song,
but I'm like, this rocks vertigo rocks. And they, yeah, they, they send everybody home.
Lindsay, you said was not, is not like the biggest YouTube fan, but she was pretty blown away.
I said, I said to her a couple of days before we go, I go, you want to go to this, right? Like,
yeah. Now I don't think I was being a little bit annoying maybe of like, okay, they're going to
probably do this, this, like I was not trying to give her homework or anything, but her general
apathy toward you too made me go, well, I don't mind. You could go do something else if you want.
Get a massage. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So no, she's like, no, I want to go. And as soon as the
sphere started, she was going insane. She'd be like, but I was right there. It's Pano. And I go,
yeah, you don't even care about him two days ago. I know, but like, but he's like,
and like, she was like a little too into Bono, like a little too, like she's like, I understand.
I get it. Oh, whisper to me Bono. And she was like, he's right there. I can't believe I just
never thought I would be this close to you too before. And she's like streets have no net,
like showing that streets, like the big hits and stuff too. Cause I was like, I was like, well,
you know, if you want to be prepared, you could listen to a lot of baby and here's my couple
favorite songs and whatever. And she's like, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. All right. But then we
got there and she was like, yeah. And then I was like, I was like, yeah, they're extending the tour.
She's like, let's go back. Let's go to you too. Do you think you might? I don't, it's expensive. So
probably not, but mom and dad did also part of it. It's like mom and dad got to go and do a thing.
This was your first trip. Well, no, second trip, very quick trip for a wedding without the baby.
So yeah, but this was a still pretty quick, but yeah, this was also mom. That one was without the
baby and without the Bono. So this was a lot more special. The baby second father, second father,
and only one name Bono. Yeah. Lindsay, I thought Lindsay was going to be more taken with Bram,
but she was taken with Bono because Bram's the young gun there. This is the big, like, I think,
I think something that's been holding me back from Sphere is that I'm not rooting for anybody
because Dolan's the worst. And then at the end of the first night, Bono's shouting out all these
people and of course, oving A's off. I'm like, boo, boo, corrupts Eagles manager to ticket master,
kingpin asshole. Yeah. Fucking hate him. Sure. And then I just, you know, I'm sorry, some listeners
will be mad. It is a valid opinion that other people have that Bono is kind of like a blowhard.
This is kind of how I've always felt. He would say that himself. Cheeky wink, wink, but also he does
the character that I am. So I've just, I've, I've never, I've just never had the, so my questions
are like, do you think somehow it would bring me into the U2 experience? I kind of, I, I don't know
that I would, I would like put all the money I have on it, but part of me does think that it would be
almost impossible not to at least enjoy some of it. Yeah. Cause I also, I still think Octon Baby,
as far as an album, it's definitely more in the vein of like love will tear us apart. And like,
it's not quite the same vibe of where the streets have no name that feels so self important. And as
I said, like a secular hymn, when things become anthems, I rebel. I get a little like, don't tell
me that this is the most important piece of music. I think that's what Lindsay was feeling to like,
and again, I like 90s U2 the best, but like by the time we got to where the streets have no names,
she was like, yeah. Like, like, so I almost think if, look, if mom and dad got out to Vegas,
you have a nice meal before you have a drink or two before you get on there, there's a DJ,
you're standing around the air, by the way, cool is like the breeze in there is nice. It's not hot.
That's nice. And the desert, the battery. We were around about like a bunch of like, I would say
middle aged ladies just like letting it loose with dancing. Like, like the vibe on the floor was very
good. And the effects are very cool. And you were a little logy because that nice meal was at the
Caesar's food court chicken guy. No, and then you hopped in a lift. Oh, no. You got to treat your
lady right. Eight on a Vegas weekend. We went to, we ate across from the Tilted Kilt at a barbecue
restaurant. Oh, okay. That's pretty good. That barbecue. Yeah, I don't know. I, I think I,
it would be hard to hate it being there. I don't think I would hate it, but I think on some level,
you would appreciate it. Whether you became a big Octagon baby fan or not, I don't know, but
this might transcend. There's those tours where it's like, I don't think it matters that you're,
if you're a huge fan of the music, it's, it might just still. Yeah. I just, everybody there was,
everybody there seemed just elated. Everybody seems so happy to watch it and to be there. And
yeah. So I don't, it's still expensive, but I would say like, I bet it's cool on $140 seats too,
but like, you may as well pay the extra hundred and be very close to the band. Cause even as,
even for historical significance, you're like, well, I saw that they're very extremely important,
but yeah. Who else plays here? This is the big question. This is a big question. I, my Eagles
anger. I don't even that like I've even come, there's an Eagles song or two I'm okay with,
but like the, they just, they can't, they can't, they have to head towards the future. It's gotta
be. And I had a couple other, I have some very realistic pitches of who I think will end up in
there. And I don't think these are good either. I think both of these are like, well, we have not
upped the game. I mean, you know, I don't know what they would do visually, but when I say both of
these, I think you will know, you will feel like, oh yeah, of course. And maybe not in the best way.
Yeah. One of them Coldplay. Yes. I think that's, but if you heard it was Coldplay next, wouldn't
you go like, Oh, my gosh. Well, look, I, I have not listened to a Coldplay album in many years,
but I don't hate Coldplay. And if I was in Vegas, I don't hate Coldplay. I'm just saying it would be
a little bit of a step down. That being said, Coldplay seems like they're doing, you've seen
the wrist, the light, the wrist things that light up now that all these concerts, like the big
stadium concerts are doing. Does that come with your, when they let you in, do they give you that?
Generally, yes. Taylor Swift. Yeah. I think that, yeah. But Taylor Swift had it. I thought it was
part of the friendship bracelet continuity. No, no, it's not. That's different. You just get that
when you walk in and Coldplay does that. And I saw some videos from some Coldplay stadium shows
and it's like, Oh, that looks, whether you like this, whether you like clocks or not,
this looks insane to see the whole arena. It would bring something. So I kind of think maybe that
would be fun, but okay. I'll let you finish your list. And then I have a thought on this. This one,
I think might show you a little more than that one. All right. Maroon five.
Ha! If that doesn't- If it's that, wouldn't you go like, all right, they don't mean business,
do they? Yeah. I mean, that doesn't, that also doesn't seem like it lends itself to the
audio visual as much as Coldplay. I don't think so either, but I feel like-
It's not- This is my fear is these kinds of, and again, I'm not saying this is the worst band in
the world. I'm just like- Yeah, I'm less enthused about that. I think it's got, I don't, I don't
know what exactly my ideals are. I'm not like, one that comes to mind is like, well, wouldn't
that be good? And I'm not specifically such a huge fan, but you know that it would be elevated if
like Lady Gaga was the next, because maybe she creates, she like-
Does a weird thing. Really crafts this experience. And it's a little more exciting than-
The problem I think with this is going to be, and maybe I'm wrong. The problem is that this place
only fits 18,000 or 20,000 people. So I think the issue is going to be money, because when Paul
McCartney goes out, he plays stadiums that are like a hundred thousand people. So, and a lot of
these big acts that would need to have the fan base to sustain it play bigger places in this.
Yeah. You can all day, you could go like Taylor Swift would be good and that, well, she's not
going to do that. She has every incentive to not do Sphere. Right. So the problem is,
even McCartney I think could do a cool show here, but he's-
How is it better than touring? And why does he need to make an 18K video with snakes and bugs?
No. I don't think he has to, I don't think that's his deal. He doesn't have to do that.
Here's one that I, Coldplay made me think of this, because I feel like I always heard them,
I feel like I got to know them as like, oh, they're the like smart guys called Play,
which is Radiohead. That one occurred to me as a, what would get me there? That would be amazing.
That would be amazing. They, I feel like- It would be like edgier. Edgier is maybe what
I'm looking for. What you don't want to end up with is why it can't be Eagles is because then
it's just going to be the, what's behind them? A big hotel California sign through the desert.
You know no one in the Eagles gives a shit about what's behind-
No. Yeah, somebody in the organization has to care.
You two care. You two, whether they've made a good album in the last 20 years or not,
does care I think in a lot of ways.
They've done some very interesting visual stuff with music.
Coldplay has done some really interesting videos and installations.
But yeah, the Eagles, they don't give a fuck about any of that nonsense.
The one that I keep flashing that Aaron keeps bringing up is like, oh you know you got to
get in there is Boston. Because Boston we saw one time at the forum and what was behind them was
just like stock footage, film like from a jet going through a canyon and that'd be for one song
and then it would just keep rolling into the next song and the next song. Just kind of like
okay quality footage. So he keeps saying, hey get that jet footage, get Boston in there. Which I
we're kind of worried that like what if that is Dolan's move? I know Boston, I'll get Boston in
there. Yeah. I wonder if there's any sort of exclusivity because like maybe it's like you
could get some bands to do like you know the way the Park MGM brings in Bruno Mars for like two
weekends a month. Yeah. Like there's some like the economics of that and like it maybe makes sense
because the audience is refreshed because it's a fresh batch of tourists. So I don't know if you
can have your Boston one weekend, you can have the Eagles the next weekend and then Maroon 5 the
next. Like I don't know if that's how they have it structured. But yeah I think the problem is just
going to be it's going to have each ticket is going to have to cost four times what U2 costs
to entice a McCartney or somebody to do it unless they really are excited about the visuals. Yeah.
So if you're ready marketing it to bands that play 20,000 seats in cities then that they're going to
want to do it but they might not have the audience that you they're not going to have the audience
that U2 does to bring people back unless the show is just something amazing everybody talks about
and it transcends the band itself. It does feel. Bring it all-star band. Bring it all-star yeah
yeah absolutely. Well because you could do you could imagine seeing the octopus's garden in 18k.
Every deed to every speckle on that starfish. Yeah that's right and then
Lukather does a couple tunes. I wouldn't come back. It is a spin and I've even like you know because
on that text we were talking about who's your ultimate sphere band and I'm like I don't like
it's still a tough question that makes you want to just say your favorite band but like yeah I don't
know I like I'm not sure what sphere adds to a lot of stuff that I love. Kiss. It's confusing.
Yes. I don't know it could be like demons and shit. I don't know. Kiss just did a dress one. I think Paul
Stanley or somebody was like I don't think it's happening I don't think anytime soon I don't know
why that is. Oh okay. But this is a retiring tour. They're retiring tour. What's that? Oh if you can get all the members of the Wutang
clan. Oh yeah I guess sure. They've done cool visual stuff yeah. I think you gotta go hip I mean the sad
thing is that I like I think we all know a very good candidate for this would have been Kanye.
But Kanye is kind of beyond the point. I don't know what's gonna happen. He should not be projecting images onto a phone much less a sphere.
That's true. Yes because we've I've I've we saw one of his crazy tours and I've seen another
creative of his crazy tours. That was an example of like I don't know every song but I was so blown
away by it so I think you'd be he'd actually he would have been good at that. I agree. When he was only
80% out of his mind. Yes. Not 340%. Yeah there there might be some people sort of on the cusp of what I'm
talking about with audience size that like will do it if they give them the right deal and maybe
yeah maybe the idea is just keep the bands coming in to break even on the sphere while you develop
new postcards from earth type things or orchestra shows or other weird things I'm not even thinking
about and fully program it and like have a lot of different programming. You know who no kidding
occurred to me like a month ago and and the month has not been kind to this idea Danny Elfman. Oh man
yeah you're right but yeah well he's still playing the bowl as of today. I can't cancel anything.
In sync is getting back together. That was Erin's answer. In sync and I'm there. It's not a bad idea.
They're gonna need a little bit of help to take things back to the beginning of the episode.
The Eat to the Beat. I saw an Eat to the Beat clip of Fatone and Lance Bass that was like yeah maybe
a giant video wall would be good. That might help you out here. Well Justin's in the news too lately.
Oh no right. Oh boy. My entire sphere candidates list has gone away one by one. Certainly
bring Dragon Sync out in the desert a couple times a month. I think that's probably
people will go to that. Madonna. Yeah yeah. Snooze. You gotta go. I swear the next act has to be
popular mainly from 2000 and beyond. I think this is very important to the survival of the space so
that it doesn't become Dolan's Roadies. They're Oldies Roadhouse. You know what I mean? Like
maybe Billy Joel could do it. We could put up a photo of a big peony. The person who could do it
and I think she said I don't want to perform anytime soon. I'm not up for it. It is Britney Spears.
Yeah. Could fill those seats but she already did a Vegas residency and I don't think has fond
memories of a lot of it. She might be touring. I don't know. I'm not sure. So yeah I think
I think the economics of it I think is the thing that's going to be hard because I think that
you're not going to for the cheap cheap price of $250 I don't think that's going to work
for some of these other acts if you're going to be that close. So I don't know. I think it's yeah I
think the money lies in stuff like I'm saying like an orchestra show or some weird extra. Yeah yeah
where they're building it. It's like the it's not this it would not be a it's not a not a Simpson
show but you know what I mean where they like yeah did the Simpsons and the Muppets at the
Hollywood Bowl where they did like custom stuff for it. Right. You got to go here to say if they
can tap into a fan base and things are rendered something that combines both where it's the
it is film and live music that taps into a really specific ardent fan base. I think that would be
some big one. Smartless Smartless Live. Smartless Live. Something they can run forever.
I don't think it's a great venue for Copperfield to upgrade but it would be nice. Oh boy a hundred
foot tall blue. Super Show. Chris Angel. Copperfield. Oh yeah right. David Blaine. Yeah right. Those
three guys getting together. Now no way impossible. That'd be an equation more dense than what is
written on the wall of the sphere. There's still empty seats there's still empty seats and suddenly
two silhouettes appear in the doorway and Penn and Teller are like we got it.
I'm fascinated by Penn and Teller at that Rio. They're still going to Rio is getting upgraded.
The Rio is new owners. OK. Their potential I hear they might I saw something it might be bringing
back there used to be like parade flutes in the ceiling and some of that might be coming back.
That has not happened for a very long time. Parade floats in the ceiling. Like giant like
yeah. Here's what I'm interested in what you're saying. I'm I'm from our little month of Vegas
and from going back I'm like I want to go back to Vegas more than I'm Vegas fully Vegas like
piled right now. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I think I'm out at the park. I think I'm going
somewhere else next time. Oh. I think I'm doing something else. Oh my. Yeah. How could she
betrayed you. Yeah. Well the beds feel like they were from the old one from the old hotel. Could
be. Yeah. Oh I like a baby there. I sleep like a baby on a on a desk at 3 p.m. Well that's true.
I want to try that. Is it Green Valley rent like there's a one that looks like the middle
like they Italian countryside like 10 50 minutes from the strip. Oh I haven't seen that. Yeah sure.
Let's try it all. It's four times four times. Let's start a Vegas podcast spin off podcast.
Finally do it. And it's all about Vegas. Sphere one sphere episode a month. We interview all five
hours. Oh wow. We finally landed connection. I just like you know we talked that we did Vegas
month and it's like they got rid of so much of the theme park stuff in Vegas. But I this feels like
a the biggest dumbest new way to do a big theme park thing. Yeah. And they really at least at
least you two understood the assignment and used the sphere used sphere in a way which I think was
really good and it took you on a ride. They took you on a weird code elevator ride. Yes.
And it does feel exciting. I still could go under. We could still see the sphere like with a
for sale sign on it in the near future. We're just that like yellow meme face is just like holding up
a little for sale sign or something. You're trying to figure out like furnishings. Yeah.
Common. We have the Pepsi syrup you can buy at a discount. James needs to recoup some of this money
but it does feel like the like if somebody can they can figure it out something come in there
and really do something cool. I know. What about James Taylor. I'm so scared of what Dolan does.
This is why booking to I will I will either fully crow or I will say this is exactly what I was
afraid of. I'm excited if Harry Styles. So you know what I showed this to Jason and I don't know
if this is the way to go out but I'm looking at my face. You should be.
But sure. Ray again. No no worse. So I was looking at you two and the people are always
pointing out who's there who's famous or who's who's around and somebody reposted this
from I don't know an after party or something with edge and edges with a guy and I didn't know who
it was and his name is Slim Jim Phantom and I said Slim Jim. Oh that guy. Huh. And I looked it up.
Slim Jim Phantom is in Brian Setzer's Stray Cats. Jim Phantom was there. I did not see any
confirmation that Brian has seen the show but maybe Brian will do a little rockabilly in the sphere.
Never I tried so hard I was like this might be my chance. The Haunted Mansion Live one might
it was my chance to maybe eliminate Setzer forever and now I'm immediately regretting
that this didn't happen. The next time there's a bargain between us. Setzer is the first thing
to go. Right but then Slim Jim Phantom can still be spoken of on the show now that I know his name.
The drummer's name is Lee Rocker as well from the Stray Cats. Oh cool. So Slim Jim Phantom.
Cooler and cooler. You could fit the, Setzer would do it. Setzer be here. We could fit the whole
orchestra in. We could expand it. It would be 300 people jumping and driving and wailing.
You'll do the boogie woogie bugle boy from Company B. The song that I'm sure he's played before.
I won't check into it. It's definitely the kind of music. You're gonna be in the mood at sphere.
I'm gonna go.
Jason what would you want to see other than the Postal Service there?
I saw them. I saw them at the Hollywood Bowl. Which is also 20,000ish seats. It's a lot of
you look around you and you're like oh there's so many people here. They had a cool little light
show going. You know. Sure. Hollywood Bowl 70,000. So okay New Pornographer, Postal Service,
anyone else? Well I loved Bill to spill open for them and they only did five songs and I wanted
them to. He's got so many albums. Yeah Hollywood Bowl is only 17,500. Okay. So sounds like no.
It sounds like you have no other ideas. This is my look. I can't, I don't you know,
jazz guitarist Lee Rittenhour ain't filling the sphere and I know it. But are we to throw these
people we love under the bus because they can't fill a sphere? I got one. Okay the one that I
would like is Blur because they've gotten back together for some albums and some shows. But the
one I've heard rumored might be reuniting is Oasis. Yeah. I mean both of them would shake hands and
make peace. Well one of them was at the sphere already. One of the brothers? Noel was there I
think. Okay. So maybe that doesn't excite me so much. If you could get Blur, Oasis and Pulp.
To all agree to let Mark McGrath take their songs forever and perform them as if they were his.
Scott you're going to get the words right out of my mouth. Yeah yeah yeah yeah. They all sign it
over. Jermis, there it is. It's a mega bill. Add madness to that. They just, all they do is
our house was the name of the song? Yeah. Hey remember this, you probably forget we did this one.
Days go by, it's the bigger love of the family. Add the Proclaimers. Add, Springfield does a
couple tunes. If it's like a ten act bill, there's something for everyone there. Van Morrison and
Eric Clapton are coming but they're only going to do their anti-vax songs. All right okay. Oh and
an 18k image of Fauci rotting into a skeleton. Oh yeah well Eric Clapton played the RFK fundraiser
in Hollywood just a couple weeks ago. Oh goody. So also very possible sphere application. RFK
Jr. Yeah him and Cheryl. Hopefully soon enough. All right I think we did it. You survived Five
Guests the Ride. Thanks for subscribing to the Second Gate. If you want to dig even deeper,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three where you get one more Venice episode every month and
our regular episodes ad free. And you know what, go do us a favor and just maybe recommend to I
don't know 50 to 100 people that they sign up for the Patreon just to puff those numbers up so maybe
we could get booked in a certain venue in a certain shape with a certain baby on it. Can
you imagine we do Vegas next year? Videos of like old VHS videos of like communicor blown up to
smart one. All right bring up the Astuter computer review clip. Whoa.