Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate, thankfully avoiding a third full humiliating
month of neglecting to cover Al Roker's butternut squash tart.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson grimacing at the thought that a single day would have
passed longer where we don't discuss this tart.
I was just thinking about how I deserve to be punished more.
I mean, we, I guess all three of us, but I like, I want to take it out on myself too.
I want to take this.
You think you deserve to be punished more.
Yeah.
More.
Huh?
For what, per se?
Does anything come to mind?
For not getting to it.
Oh, just for, oh, I thought like maybe for things in general.
Well, I guess there are things that you've certainly just have just a general guilt,
but no, I'm sorry.
I mean, specifically for this, for the neglect.
This is, well, I don't know.
I don't, I don't wish the same thing.
I hope there's no more punishments coming your way anytime soon.
I don't, don't do that to yourself.
Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Yeah.
I mean, I was ready to discuss it the last time we were down, but then I didn't end
up beating anything there.
So it's probably for the best we didn't.
But the menu has changed.
Yes.
So it changes all the time.
Avocado toast is gone.
It's gone.
It's long gone.
Oats left behind in 2019.
You know, is that right?
I thought they had it still.
Is there not overnight oats?
I feel like I didn't see it.
I definitely didn't see Al's avocado toast.
No.
Well, that shifted as I was saying to Al's butternut squash tart, which is the new thing
from a couple months ago.
And again, if that had gone any longer, I think the listeners would have started to
notice and started to complain and revolt.
But we're here doing it now.
We're talking about the Today Cafe, which is the Today Show themed restaurant in Universal
Orlando.
And look, we've just, you know, we're back from Orlando and we're filled with like a,
it's December here.
It's a Santa's bag full of goodies of the rides and attractions and experiences, really
keyword experience that now we can talk about that we haven't been able to for a long time.
And folks, it's here.
The one you've been begging for, the one you've been asking for.
We're finally doing the Today's Cafe.
I'm sorry.
The overnight oats are still there, but the acai bowl appears to be missing in action.
Oh, jeez.
Possibly replaced with tropical chia pudding.
Okay.
These are, well, this gives you, I think, a flavor of the kind of things they have.
You know, these, you know, earthy, balanced, good for you recipes that certainly are real
and well crafted by the artisans who work in this theme park.
Doesn't it feel like overnight oats especially feels like the fakest.
Like what you picture it is versus the container that it is taken out of and put in the microwave.
Yeah, it's, they, it's a, everything sounds classy.
Everything sounds curated and handcrafted.
Yeah.
But I, there's very few quick service places in any theme park where things are truly handcrafted,
like handcrafted in front of you.
I suppose pastries and certain things are made in big bulk amounts.
But I saw the chef without Roker touring the facility at opening.
Well, you know, again, all restaurants have that, like that stretch of time where people
are watching and paying attention.
So they have to be decent impressions of restaurants and then time passes and things kind of fade,
which is a, I imagine a theme that we will be exploring in the, the city walk Orlando
saga, multiverse of madness.
Spoilers.
It's really, you might like, when were these restaurants good?
You might want to chart that opening and then look like a month out and how long ago in
the past was that we will see, you know, speaking of that, it is okay.
So, you know, we're going to be covering that NBC sports grill, which is at city walk Orlando
there.
And then you've got, of course the, so there's an NBC property and restaurant, you know,
the, the, the spirit of the sports casters and sports enterprise.
And then you got Jimmy Fallon up the road and obviously the recreation of 30 rock.
That's the biggest scale nod to the corporate overlords.
And then you've got this.
So in the, in kind of a same little loop, if you want to like really keep that NBC spirit
alive in the most, in the vaguest way, all three probably places where you can get things
that say NBC or you can get like a, I bet all these places have something just called
like NBC pie.
Does that reflect, does it like, is it based on, do anybody who works there come up with
the pie recipe?
I don't know.
But if you know, if you're loyal to a brand, then a universal's got the way for you to
celebrate that.
Yeah, no, it's, it's really, I mean, I, maybe this is for the end, but like, what, like
what else, what else would you want from NBC?
Like the NBC property, what other, if you're a fan of the network, I mean, is there famous
NBC stuff?
Do you want like Brandon Tartakov walk around characters?
Like what, like this is, I guess, probably the optimum way right now that an average
tourist would experience the IP of NBC.
I suppose.
Yeah, well, that's obviously what I want.
I want to, you know, like, like a cigarette, you know, machine or whatever, but then you
actually get to it and there's kind of like a no, no, no.
And it's Brandon Tartakov with the cast to say by the bell, all saying think twice before
you do that.
Yeah.
The greatest thing they ever aired.
Yeah, I think enough has been enough.
I think it's time to bring cigarette machines back to it.
Even if they're fake out cigarette machines, they're fake out.
Even if you pull on it and it tells you it's just like your favorite embassy, NBC property
telling you.
Right. Right.
Yes. No, no.
The cast of manifest is here to tell you about the dangerous smoking.
Which I'm saying that has shifted to that.
That's one of those shows that's secretly a massive hit for Netflix.
I think.
Sure. Sure.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
What's what's happening?
What?
You absolute fool.
He found you.
I mean, how did he find us in a different location?
It's the minute.
There's no way for him to know the minutes are.
I found us.
Hey, oh, well, yeah.
Being really nice.
Thank you so much.
They're better.
Yes.
Hello. I guess I should help you with the mic.
Well, you know what?
I didn't plan for I didn't know you were coming minutes.
Oh, my God. The Minotaur who recently visited us to dynasty typewriter is back has rudely
interrupted the today cafe.
But ultimately, I put this on Mike, I would say.
I like you like you. You have to know.
You're the reason this is coming.
I assume so. But let's hear him out here later.
OK, you know what I'll do?
Maybe Minotaur, why don't you take my microphone and I'll go grab that one
on a stand that's set up in the corner here.
Here, here, here. Come switch to mine. OK.
All right. One second. We get some.
All right. Well, yeah, I don't want you to podcast uncomfortably.
Oh, it's going to get it's going to get uncomfortable.
My God. What have I done?
At the level for our level.
And you think you do. OK.
OK, OK. Minotaur levels.
I have to audio engineer my own yelling at my scolding.
I mean, my God, can we do it while we're going live?
I might have to restart and restart. Oh, my God.
I think you're a you're a you're a bad son, but you're a fine engineer.
You'll figure this out. What this is about.
I know it was actually at food.
We like to take a day and we have to talk about it.
But we have to address this.
This is important.
We have to address our sudden. This is important.
But you have to blame Mike for what's happening.
Because you know, well, I do for most things.
Minotaur, do you want a bottle of water while you're getting settled?
That is really polite. I would love a bottle of water.
Thank you. Hold on.
I got to restart and I got to restart. Hold on.
It's done. You hit stop.
Minotaur's really settled in here.
Yeah, you got a water. You're all good to go.
Aggressive. Yeah.
That's aggressive posture.
I just say I just say don't pop the peas.
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Minotaur is a very thirsty job.
Generally, you're you're you got a bellow.
It's a bellowing job.
I can only imagine. Yeah.
Is this is busy right bellowing distance from the microphone?
I think it's OK. I can hear from over here.
How does that sound? Oh, it sounds fine now.
Yeah. Bellow right in your face.
Oh, that's that's a little too hot.
I guess I'll lower in case you want to have that room.
I mean, that's that's probably what you should be doing,
because I think I have a feeling why you're here.
Yeah. Why you've showed up by by surprise.
Does this have anything to do with what happened
the last time we saw you at our live show?
Yeah, I thought I came to your show.
I had a great time.
Lovely time at the Dines and Typewriter, a beautiful venue, by the way.
Thank you. Well, we agree. Yeah.
No, no, no. Yeah. Really, really comfortable. Good snacks.
Did you get some of the popcorn back?
Yeah. Some sour gummy worms.
That's a really good snack.
Some like peanut butter M&M's is great.
You know, an orthodox topic.
It's kind of, you know, kind of like nice, fun treats like they would have it.
The Today Cafe.
I know, but I guess we have to put that aside for the time being.
OK, so I think I know what's happening.
And to catch the listener up on what's been going on
a little while back, Mike
would would not face the Minotaur in an escape room experience.
You had to tap out of this thing.
And that led to the Minotaur appearing in one of our recent
live shows where he put you to the test.
He made you face one of your biggest fears,
which is the fear of missing out on on great deals.
Yes. Or something that's a limited time release that might go away.
Which I will come open to interpretation.
I let you. Yes. Pick what would work for you.
Yes. And yet and yet.
Yeah. Once a specific was offered.
Yeah. Once you were given.
And look, this all played out on stage as it did.
And you were a champion that night.
Public record. Yeah.
You were told to delete one of the many, many, many home screen
notifications that are on your phone.
That's true. At all times.
And you picked one.
You had one in the chamber ready to go.
You volunteer and sacrifice something called Deal Vibes.
Yes. At Deal Vibes. Yes.
A name that's kept you up at night ever since Minotaur.
Yes. Well, I want to read a little.
I want to read an X that came across my bow.
I don't even have X. I quit X. OK.
You had to go back on it because of all this crap.
People were people were DMing me on Instagram.
And I had to get on X because I was going to go full threats.
And all I had to decide.
Somebody told me to go on X.
And I read this from Michael Carlson at Fat Carlson spelled P.H.
Replying to podcast, right?
Do you guys plug your show and all this stuff? Yeah.
And he's he writes, I refollowed to spit in the face of the Minotaur.
I will not be bullied.
I will defeat it in person.
Oh, ho, ho.
And then you refollowed Deal Vibes. Yeah.
And now we're in person.
That's true. Yeah. It's right here.
What up, dog? OK.
Well, look, when I said I would defeat in a person,
I assumed it would lead to another episode where I went to the Minotaur
to escape room, which I learned is real.
Oh, he's he's living.
But he's thinking about your escape room.
I mean, it's not about the escape room anymore.
Now you're in it. First of all, let me just say this.
I realized weeks, days.
I don't even really remember.
I realized what I was doing.
I deal vibes is so important to my phone ecosystem.
Yes. And I said, there's no fucking way I can unfollow this.
I'm following this again.
Well, this is my question.
I'll wait a little bit more context really quick.
The you unfollow you.
You volunteered unfollowing.
You always said was home screen. Yes.
Acations. Yes. You took that off.
And then as an extra brave boy bonus, you said, and I will unfollow it as well.
Right. You got a big round of applause.
Yeah. Minotaur called you the bravest boy he's ever known.
Yes. Yes. It was a victorious moment.
I gave you paternal approval, an intimate moment of paternal approval.
That's right. Yes.
And I appreciated that.
His biggest desire.
I appreciated that. But then I was I was thinking about it and I was like,
who is this Minotaur?
I don't even I'm just a man on a stage trying to do a little show,
make the people laugh, make the nice people laugh.
I just because I had an anxiety attack, I didn't face the Minotaur once.
And I said, you know what? Who is he to tell me who and what to do?
And I said, I can't.
And then I refollowed deal vibes.
And yeah, I almost immediately was clued in that the new expansion pack
for Disney's Lorcan was now available for like five minutes.
I got a booster box because I refollowed and it justified all of my decisions.
Now I have that kind of box.
Lorcan, a flood born booster box.
That's pretty amazing.
Twenty four packs. This is hard to get, folks.
You're to your to your tip in him a little bit.
I know I have a question.
How soon did you refile?
Because there were two weeks between us recording the live show.
Yeah. And then we put out the episode and I want to shout out listener
Ethan Dickinson.
Thanks for getting on the crime tip line.
Well, he's now listening to the show.
Ethan, you're out.
If you're on the Patreon, you're going to be blocked.
If you're on X, you'll be blocked from our accounts.
Personal Minotaur.
You're calling out Ethan. Yeah, there were two.
And you get one free trip to the labyrinth.
If you ever want to come to my labyrinth, you can come and check out the labyrinth.
It's really cool.
Well, it's got a lot of like justice based puzzles.
OK, it's going to be great.
Are you going to like eat them or kill them at the end?
Yes. If I do catch you, I will eat you or kill you.
That's kind of my job there.
I guard the treasure.
But there is treasure there, Ethan.
So you could you could be treasure if you're a brave boy.
Yeah. Hey, look, Ethan, I mean, you're much more loyal to the Minotaur than me.
So I think this is where he picked a side.
Yeah, he picked a side. I get it.
And there's something that I want to know from what Ethan found out.
There were exactly two weeks to the day between.
Yeah. Recorded it.
And when he discovered that you were still following deal vibes.
Yeah. How soon after the show did you spit in the Minotaur's face?
Don't I think it was like four or five days.
I think I made it four or five days.
And then I think it pops up a little better.
I wondered if you even like like the night of we're in the venue and decided
and look at you know what happened while I was sitting backstage
eating peanut butter and you would do that secretly on your phone during the show.
You know what happened is I think that X then started showing me deal
vibes as well, because what happens is it doesn't always go to just who you're
following. Oftentimes it clicks over to the for you tab,
which then shows you an algorithm of what you actually might want to see.
So I think I was getting deal vibes and I was just I would I got the FOMO.
I got the deal vibes FOMO.
But that's what you're over.
No, I understand that. I went back on my word.
But really, who was the Minotaur to tell me what to do?
Well, OK. Well, first of all, who are you to sit there and back out on a deal
that you made and you hugged on?
I mean, if Jason would have made a deal like that, he wouldn't have reneged on it
at all. He would have stayed in.
I told I would have never done something like that.
I would have never renamed to know it kept me up at night if I refollowed.
Just like the person who mentioned me and some other of our accounts
in a post and acts and they were like, hey,
you should deal with five pounds of her serum.
Oh, yeah, that's right. We were just fine.
That we were just tagged on a deal vibes,
you know, which could be a good way to suss out like how much of a real problem
we're dealing with, because you're right. OK.
Yeah. Did you get the chocolate, by the way?
The syrup syrup, the syrup? Yeah.
No, no, I don't think I have the room for five to ten pounds of Hershey's syrup.
It is. It's over seven pounds over seven hours.
She's chocolate syrup for under ten dollars.
Too low and ten was too high.
Are you a Hershey's on the on the Sunday guy?
Do you like it? Even at home for a home ice cream?
Do you do it? I usually have something for a home ice cream.
I love to do a Hershey's syrup and then you stir it really fast. Yeah.
I don't mind if it melts a little like it's getting ice cream soup quickly.
You know, you don't just like feast on the on the bones of those who betrayed you.
You you like it just a bit like a like like any of us.
No, but you should try bone ice cream if you've never made bone.
You can home make it. It just takes milk and ice and everything into the bones
of your enemies. Oh, sure.
So it's like a bone broth, honestly, like it's almost like when you're making
bone broth at home, which, you know, is very popular these days.
And it takes a while.
But you instead of using it to make some sort of a broth,
it's like salt straw would have a bone broth ice cream.
I think you could probably get one seasonally.
I'm yeah, I'm betting Jason would bet five real.
I bet it would be good. I'm going to be good. Yeah.
Yeah. But it was Jason's honorable man is what I'm saying.
Well, here let me I hate to bring out contract law into this conversation.
But let me just read a little mighty minutes.
Are you going to use words? Let's just read.
Let's just read. I deal with riddles all the time as well.
Occasionally in a lab or they'll be a riddle.
So I'll listen to this to this contract riddle.
He is sovereign citizen Carlson going off again.
Listen, this is a corporate finance institute dot com, a website
we all know very well.
It says in contract law, duress is used as a form of defense to a crime
where the defendant uses threats to force the plaintiff to commit a crime
that is against their wishes.
A party who is forced into an act or contract under duress
can rescind the contract, rendering it null and void.
Well, can I counter with that? All right.
Were you under duress just because I'm a minotaur?
No, this is how I talk and this is how I look.
And all of a sudden, if I'm asking to do something, it's duress.
Well, I would say that the way you were intimidating me on stage
by charging the stage, we didn't we have to approve everyone.
I charge everywhere I go.
I charge the movies. I charge the grocery store.
I charge. That's how I do.
So you can't you cannot you're incapable of not you're capable of not charging.
I'm not. How did I come in here?
You charged it.
But it's very intimidating.
We heard a little charge. What was that?
Yeah. And he showed up.
After we took a little break because some nice people were walking
through the alleyway.
Yeah. I was really messed up that intro.
Using a residential.
There was an energy.
There was an energy going on here that I couldn't put my finger on.
It was weird. And then the people the dogs walked by.
And then I was like, wait a minute.
And then I said, no, no, no, start recording again.
Yeah. There was a weird, weird energy.
Not that I thought it was a minute.
It's hard approaching necessarily.
Just something was off.
It's got say something was off.
I was like, I never yelled at your rest.
Yeah. That's what I was not doing.
I was just nonchalantly hiding behind a fence outside of the recording studio.
And these people just stopped.
They were underdressed by me being there.
Just a bit of tar with horns and large sound.
And I charged up to the fence.
I believe you could not charge.
I believe you have the ability not to charge.
I believe that you could be slower in your light to not charge.
There's also I think that, you know, there's like a range of intonation
and how something sounds in your head versus how it comes off in reality.
How you presented yourself to us during the show.
What ended up being duress might have been very calm on your scale,
similar to how there's a story I'm trying to remember.
One of us, I can't remember, was used this phrase in a text message.
Counterpoint, you were wrong.
Yeah. Yeah.
Also sounded like a like a very like kind of an angry,
especially angry, sharp threat.
But once Pestered to say it out loud, it was said more like,
look, counterpoint, you were wrong.
I thought it was very clear communication.
That sounds like some of that clear text counterpoint comma.
Was there a comma there?
No, it was a colon.
It's a colon. Yeah.
Looks like the title of the show. Yeah.
So that's like that's like something you would text
and you would you'd be shocked if anybody took that as like that seemed
like like an angry thing.
Exactly. No, I'm just I'm just being a minute.
I'm just doing minute things.
I don't know what your big deal is.
I mean, no one's blaming you for just doing minute.
It's just tests and feats and riddles.
It's just how ideal it's ideal and intimidation in loud voices
and getting in a person's face.
I have been whispering the whole time in my mind.
Well, there you go.
Come off now.
Whispering, because that's I'm trying not to wake up the neighborhood.
Your whisper is a little loud.
It's a little loud. Yeah, I'm not.
But I'm not. Hey, over here, I'm not mad at you about that.
Other chairs might be. I don't know.
They might say they're under duress right now.
I'm a bit. Yes, I do feel like I'm a bit under duress right now.
All right. Well, let me bring it down.
I'm going to give you a paternal feeling, intimate paternal
disappointment. OK.
Michael Carlson.
You are a bad little boy.
You follow deal vibes when you said you would keep off of it.
And for that, I am sad.
You are not brave.
Hmm. Look, a knife.
It cuts like a knife, but it's like, unfortunately, it's a minotaur.
But not Optimus Prime. But.
You did stand up to a minotaur,
one of the scariest beasts there is.
And you told him that you would defeat him
and you would spit in his face.
And as a minotaur, I respect that.
You charged onto Twitter and you charged right up to me.
And for that, you are a brave little boy.
Oh, my God. Whoa.
All the way back around.
Wow. Geez.
Yes, you're even to me, which I would count as a victory, honestly.
Yeah, I think maybe we landed at like a spot of peace.
I guess the question, though, is how do we feel about Mike
continuing to follow deal vibes at this point?
Is this his own business?
You've got kind of a respect for him, given what he's how he's behaved lately.
Well, I told him he'd face his greatest fear, which would be to miss out.
And he didn't face that fear.
I feel like that's a fear for him to conquer in the future.
However, he did conquer the fear of a minotaur, which is pretty good.
You know, I think that
I don't know, or I can't believe you got a conic couch for real.
Those are impossible to find.
And then there are the new expansion.
They're flood.
It's called Floodborne.
That's the new title for the Larkana.
Without you, do you collect Arkana or do you actually play it?
I haven't played it yet, but I do collect it.
It's a game to play, right? That's right. Yeah.
And you haven't played it. Never.
Hmm. This is convicting you now.
Now you don't know what to do.
But it's a collectible card game.
Yes, I know.
But it's like we don't collect magic cards and not play magic.
Some people do. That's foolish.
That's baloney.
Some people do. No way.
It's true. Toys.
He doesn't take out of the box.
You chose to play with.
Yeah, I understand. I get that.
Like there was more in the box, but it's a card game.
It's not it's not baseball cards.
I would like to play it.
Hopefully I will play it soon.
Would you would you ever play your old man?
Wait, are you calling me?
Are you calling yourself my old man?
I mean, I'm kind of everybody's old man.
I'm an ageless creature of math.
So all of our lineage ultimately goes back to this minotaur.
You've been around for thousands of years.
We're related to you.
So I'm guessing I'll have to curate.
Like I'll have to create a deck because you don't have any more kind of card.
I would have to create a deck for you.
I've been wanting to play.
Well, yeah, you're not following the lives.
Oh, now that he's on a.
He's jumping the air now.
Well, and you're going to want to, you know,
because I started thinking about what am I missing out on?
Not following deal vibes myself.
And, you know, this is the kind of thing that's on the table for Mike.
And it could be for you as well.
Minotaur, you could get deals on lightning McQueen Crocs.
You can get a deal on a grimace from McDonald's Crocs.
You could get a deal on Will Ferrell elf cries.
Yeah, a lot of Crocs in there.
What's the deal like on those grimace Crocs?
Because I've been thinking those are new.
I don't think there's a deal.
I don't think there's a deal on those.
I think those are just sort of like telling you this is a limited edition.
Just letting you know that they exist.
I think so. Yeah, I can't.
I actually can't tell you that one.
Elf Crocs. And again, this is in the past listeners as you're hearing it.
Fifteen or five, sorry, fifty nine ninety nine with code save fifteen.
But you get I think the links to I'm not going to say the link out loud.
You kind of got to follow deal.
Right. Get it.
I mean, I'm not specifically against deal vibes necessarily.
No, no. Just that you said you had quit it.
You did that. That was the real issue.
We should say also, I think we're kind of getting to be
a little bit friendly with deal vibes as a result of all this,
because they got tagged in all everything that was going on.
And they, you know, they were tagged in Mike issuing a grave
threat about spitting in the face of the Minotaur.
Yeah. So they're seeing all this, whoever deal vibes is.
And they posted this may be my first even good publicity is bad publicity moment.
And then a picture of Thor that says, I have no idea what's going on.
And I tried to explain what we're a podcast about theme parks
and a Minotaur made one of our hosts, Mike, delete one of his many home screen
notifications, and he chose you deal vibes, but immediately
we followed you to get more deals on meatballs.
And now the Minotaur is mad.
But I guess that's not up to date anymore.
It seems like now what's happened is so deal vibes.
If you're listening, if you are on like a fair trade.
Yeah, we fight.
If we all follow deal vibes together, he should be paying for our Patreon.
I agree. Yeah, we're helping spread his deal.
I have gotten texts and messages from people in the wake of all this saying,
I started following deal vibes and I got some good stuff.
Do you know? Do you know what anybody called out as something that they got from deal
vibes? Oh, I should. I should look.
Some of there was some like really maybe a cheap couch on target
that somebody tweeted at me. They got like a brutally cheap.
Maybe like it was a glitch like it wouldn't last for like one move, but it's, you know,
you sit on it. No, I think it was just like somebody made an error
writing the price into the target website and they bought it for like 50 bucks or something.
Come on. I think I mean, I saw a deal for 100 feet of
perforated bubble wrap for only thirteen dollars, which is a forty nine dollar value.
Seems pretty good. You never have bubble wrap when you need it.
You just move, you know, you can see it and then it's lingers around
and then I throw it out and then the next day or two, of course, I need it.
That'd be fun to charge on.
Imagine charging on 100 feet of bubble wrap.
My my hooves just hitting it just so satisfying.
I feel that good on fingers. I can only imagine on hooves.
Oh, you could.
Ian, a friend of the show, Ian Riccobani,
you texted me Saturday, November 4th, not for nothing.
I got a fucking steal on the new Mario via QVC due to deal vibes, by the way.
Mario wonder how much was it for?
I think it was thirty dollars.
Thirty dollars. Pretty good.
Oh, sure. Here, let me also let me also just add a little more
please context for what's going on here.
In my mind, I said, let me follow deal vibes and follow when the show comes out
and then follow it a week later and forgot.
Wow. You knew you were going to get caught.
Well, I thought I didn't know I was going to get caught.
But I thought to myself, well, I could follow deal vibes surely for a few days
that unfollow when the show comes out, if anyone wants to search and snitch on me.
And look, things get in the way you forget sometimes.
So somewhere in the run of being a parent to a very young child,
doing three separate gates worth of theme park podcast content.
And again, having 200 home screen notifications
flooding into your phone at all times.
You forgot to do an unfollow.
I forgot to unfollow again as well to avoid this nasty business from even happening.
And look where we are.
Oh, I feel like I could put this to bed.
I think we just have one game of Arcana to the death.
All right, fine.
But you did hear that last part, right, though, to the death.
Yeah. Well, I mean, I generally deal things to the death.
If you got my labyrinth, I'll either kill you or you get the treasure.
And the treasure does. If you do get the treasure, you end up dying.
I perish.
Will you make bone broth ice cream out of me if I lose?
Oh, absolutely. You have great bones.
Do you think so? You got tall bones.
You think tall bones?
You can make a meteorite flavorful.
You think tall means flavorful?
It's like when you make a new like a noodles, you know, you really got to like
spread the, you know, like you got to like really knead the bread and spread it out.
Same thing with bones, like short little bones.
They're like they're like compact and they're still full of marrow.
Your long bones have stretched out.
So it's kind of the marrow is kind of kneaded in.
Do you think that sort of how like things that I do that keep me kind of youthful
in spirit also help keep my bones fresh?
Like like when I'm listening to young person's music and stuff,
like which I do often.
What's the young person's music?
Do you like Steely DeHaan?
No, no, no, no, no.
Like Olivia Rodrigo's guts.
Olivia Rodrigo's guts, which he listens to for a long time.
He listens to the second half finally.
But now he has heard the full album.
I've heard the full album since she's like 20.
She's a young person and I'm listening to music as if I'm just sort of a peer of hers.
So so would you think that's a fear of hanging out with Olivia at a party?
It's just a kind of a cool friend who looks like a tiny bit older, but barely barely.
You didn't even know.
You're very young.
Shred the boards.
We're all but performers on a stage.
You know, right?
Who's this character that entered?
Who's this character that entered the show?
I just let you love the theater.
It's just me.
You're saying that because Mike is a fellow performer with Olivia Rodrigo.
Yeah, they were camaraderie.
So you're saying that anyone who does anything on a stage should be able to get along.
Like I should be best friends with Jim Brewer because we're all that.
That's true. You have all the same values.
Yeah, you have the same beliefs.
We think all the same things.
Yeah, by the way, I don't like Jim Brewer.
Not for his current steps.
Current stuff is kind of interesting.
But for his old stuff, when he plays Goat Boy, that's kind of.
Oh, yeah.
It's kind of not cool to like play a hoover creature when you're not hoovered.
It's kind of like problematic.
It's just like, I don't know.
It's like we're not jokes.
Like we exist, you know, and I.
Yeah, we get it.
We got it.
I get it.
Yeah, I know. But don't don't cut him a break just for that.
You know, he should be, you know, and he is where he is now.
He's in right wing country as he should.
If you see any if you see any or hear any like minotaur comedy on a podcast,
you should pounce and make sure it never happens again.
I'll charge right at it.
It's not happening in my book.
Don't ever participate in it.
You guys first.
It's like I heard like, oh, there's like a minotaur thing that happened on the podcast.
And I go back and listen.
And I, you know, I go back to the backlog.
I only you know, I've been I only listen like the big right episodes.
But oh, yeah, yeah.
A lot of people do that.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I'm not going to go in like what is like, you know, like David Copperfield.
All I did listen to that particular one.
That's like not the one I normally wouldn't listen to.
Oh, yeah. Well, that's the hovers.
And then we lure you into kind of the more niche topics, which, you know, to that end.
And I don't mean to cut any of this off, but we do.
Look, we you picked a hell of a one to walk into.
We've been looking forward to doing the today cafe a lot.
And at some point, we're going to have to get back to the business of covering the
restaurant based on the Today show.
Oh, that sounds great. Where's it at?
That's it. That's in.
It's in Universal Florida, like the original.
They don't have it here. They don't have it in Hollywood.
So you'd have to go to Florida for that.
But then you were saying you were kind of only like like big rides and stuff.
I mean, does it does today cafe feel to like niche to you or something?
I mean, it's like the biggest television show in the history of television.
Like, really, if you think about it.
You know, it's long running.
Yeah. Quite a while.
And the building is notable as it used to host the Beverly Hills Boulangerie,
which was a lot of getting back in this
20, 30, 30 years.
It was an opening day.
It was Blanchery.
But the first restaurant when you walk in any park is pretty common.
It's kind of generic.
They're going to get people hungry for breakfast. Sure.
But this is kind of a step up because it's
now that it's kind of some cool NBC synergy in effect.
I guess my question is, do you want to like we owe the listener
getting back to the today cafe?
They've all been begging and pleading.
Yeah, probably.
Tweeting at us angrily that we aren't.
If we really I really did plan to like come in here
like Gore Mike with my horns and leave, I wasn't going to take a lot of your time.
I really swear to God, I was like really planning on just a quick murder and gone.
But oh, wow. But now you've decided, you know,
be proud of him for a second.
I thought maybe we were going to like fight a little bit.
It's still good.
Yeah, I was originally going to do like a punch challenge
where we take turns punching each other.
OK, that doesn't seem as fun, honestly.
Well, how about this?
When I let's talk a little about the today cafe.
Sure. Minutes are feel free to hang out and participate.
Yeah, absolutely. You're a guest on the show at this point.
I feel friendly enough with you.
Hang out. Talk about today.
Cafe, we got a lot of great Al Roker stuff to talk about. Yeah.
And then if you guys want to fight it out a little bit while I do the plugs
at the end, maybe then that's up to you guys.
By the way, is one of the few people that got through by labyrinth.
He made it. That's how he got the job. That was his treasure.
That was what he that was the test that he had to pass to be like a guy
who's on television forever.
They killed so many local weathermen trying to figure out who,
you know, could take over the today show.
And Al Roker just went right through.
He's smart. You know, think about a labyrinth.
You just see the end and you go around and get lost. Right.
And then Minotaur comes kills you.
He went right up and over the walls.
So he just scaled it, which is probably you're probably like waiting for.
Why don't more people do that? That's the smart way to do it.
But like cheating is like part of how you get out of a labyrinth.
So yeah, yeah.
You know, vibes just I got an alert.
Twelve pack of Monster Energy Java Nitro Cold Brew.
Only six dollars after sub and save coupon on page at Amazon.
Jason, what do you think of that?
Um, Monster Energy Java usually patronize the monster brand.
I'm not a big energy drink guy.
But what if you added the coffee to it?
Yeah, I'm interested in the coffee.
Wait, is that the kind of thing you would drink? No.
Then why do you need to know that or see that?
Well, just because they're going to they're going to really like
cast the net very wide when it comes to deals.
So I'm just I'm bound to like something.
The fact that you also sorry to cut you off, Minotaur.
But the fact that you you not only refollowed,
you also turned to the home screen notifications back.
The entire premise of the thing went away in four days.
I forgot what the specific premise was.
It will. It was only home screen notification.
No, I know now. I remember now.
But you that's two steps.
You have to remember to go back and turn on a little green dial on your phone.
Well, that's the thing.
You're not going to get the deals unless you do it.
This is the trick. This is what people don't know.
And I shouldn't even reveal it because then I'm going to lose out on in
the next expansion pack for Lorcan, because they're not getting the alerts
directly sent to their home screen.
And you might miss out.
They might be sold out of limited edition Marvel
and Lucky Charms collab Loki Charms.
Imagine if you had to go through life, not having a box of Loki Charms.
Yeah. Which are mischievously delicious.
That's exclusive to Walmart.com, I think.
So you knew that?
Yeah, I knew about Loki Charms.
Oh, my God. You pulled that out.
But that's a Walmart exclusive.
I haven't even opened my box of Carmella Creeper yet.
I finished the Monster Mash.
You have a Carmella Creeper button open?
Carmella Creeper.
Oh, that's going to be like a collector's edition, I think.
Yeah. Oh, maybe.
I don't. Yeah.
We're not going to get into collecting cereal boxes.
Is that a hobby now?
People do it. I don't.
I don't do it.
So people do it somewhere.
Mustang. Oh, we'll see.
Well, I'm sure people are going to start some collections of today's show mugs,
because that's one of the things they have today.
Oh, yeah. They have the very kind of mug that the hosts of the show drink.
And the whole thing, we weren't even into the premise whatsoever.
It's kind of a recreation of Studio One A, where the show comes from.
So if you ever wanted to visit where they where the magic happens,
where Savannah and Hoda and Al entertain and wake up America each morn.
That's what you get to do right
towards the entrance of the park at Universal Orlando.
So what today's show is like, what's the iconic thing is the big glass
window wall, right? That's the is that the thing of the state is that
recreated in this cafe?
It's not giant.
I'll tell you that.
And I know you'd be looking for giant especially, but I'll pull.
I'll throw it to what Jason said.
You brought up the what it was originally Beverly Hills, Boulangerie.
And I saw pictures of that establishment and I thought it was very closed off
and a little like not as warm as it could be, not as vibrant as it can.
And they and I would say that the today show
can't the today cafe, not the today show cafe.
I know I keep wanting to say that.
I know. I know.
Well, here, you raise a hoof to make sure next time we do it, to make sure.
Don't let us say the wrong thing.
You've got to respect the cafe today.
Cafe. Well, it's respect.
The rhyme is really what it is.
Hey, look, there's very few.
The Beverly Hills, Boulangerie just opened with the rest of the park.
Today Cafe opened with the taping of Al Roker was down there during a remote.
He went down the receiving line of all your favorite universal friends.
Oh, I've been trying to find the video of Jimmy Fallon doing this.
I know we talked about that on the page.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
A big high five line, because I'm pretty sure he must have high fived
the bunny from Hopp, who's voiced by Russell Brand.
Something everybody wants to be seen.
Wait, what year was this open?
What year is that line in there?
This this is twenty nineteen twenty nine.
This day cafe is new.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
I guess we could have gone there last time we were there,
but we only did it.
We were just in Orlando.
Oh, I did. After we said that's when you were there.
Yeah. First, and I was just kind of waiting, eating my clip bar.
I brought from elsewhere.
So all right.
So your today cafe tip is eat somewhere else and use their chairs.
Well, I mean, I'm saying that's what I did.
But this time I made up for I bought it as you do with 1030
a.m. cannoli and wolf that down.
You were we've been having more meals together recently, I think, with traveling
and prepping for the travel.
I think I've seen you get dessert at every single one of them.
I don't think I've seen you.
Well, how reporter has to do the legwork?
We had a vacation.
Yeah, no, but I'm thinking of the.
Oh, full restaurant.
But watching you eat just like a fruit compote waffle is your lunch.
Not long ago.
Oh, yeah.
It was a place with waffle in the name.
Yes. You got to try the waffle.
It's like, oh, fresh strawberries.
That would be nice.
Can I ask you about your morning cannoli?
You get a coffee with it.
Did you dip the cannoli in the coffee?
Like I'd already had coffee that day.
Oh, yeah, that's that's I would do a morning cannoli now dipping the coffee
and like some of the cream inside the cannoli would get in the car.
That sounds good.
That sounds like a nice.
Well, that's solid.
And having that with the penguins from Madagascar, Al Rooker
and a full of minions.
You know, lovely.
Wow. Wow. Wow. All our favorites. Yeah.
I did. I did somewhat of a high five line.
I was in Universal Studios, Osaka every once in a while.
I get to travel. Oh, yeah.
And I have my travel bag because I was going to be in Osaka for a little bit.
I have my travel bag in in the in the locker.
They have lockers at the front down Universal City Walk, kind of like right
when you go to the entrance.
And I found one in the back back corner because I had everything in there.
I was very nervous about losing it.
And I was leaving the park because I had to catch a train.
And I pulled my bag out and I and I hear this music and it's like
celebrate good times come on and a line.
I'm not joking. 30 Minions walked around the corner.
The 30 like in a costume.
And they were and they were very much walking like they were like not on shift.
They were walking, not like minions.
And then because they thought they were alone at this point of the park.
Then they saw me and they had to start acting like minions.
And I was just into it. So I started high fiving them.
And they just didn't stop coming in. I high fived every minion. Wow.
It was an incredible experience.
What a dream. Magic. I'll never forget.
That is awesome. It's so cool. Wow.
And the loopiness of that, you're on the other side of the way.
I mean, I assume your base is kind of more I don't know where you live exactly.
Kind of the California area. The labyrinth.
I live in the labyrinth. Right. Right.
Yeah. There's probably this labyrinthian parts that can take you like burrow
under the world. Sure. Yeah.
You've got to pop out of many different places in the labyrinth.
Yeah, that's right. That's nice. That makes travel pretty easy.
It takes a while. It's so convenient.
You know, know where you're going, but not everybody does.
Sure. Sure. Just get a real fast charge going.
That means that you have been to or at least maybe just
you must have might have had to charge right through it.
But CityWalk, Osaka.
Yes, I did go to CityWalk, Osaka.
You're a rare person, rare or rare being, I guess,
we've had on the show who's been to CityWalk, Osaka.
I don't want to skip ahead because we still have to deal with Orlando.
We've got our work cut out for us Orlando wise.
Anything interesting in notable you noticed in CityWalk, Japan?
Who's been to CityWalk, Osaka? CityWalk, Osaka?
No, never. No one here has.
So there is a store at the very beginning of it.
And I don't know what's around. I went in 2019.
There's a store that's like like America Cowboy Store.
Like I think it's called Western America or something like that.
And you walk in and it's like it's all American
kitschy stuff and cowboy things and American flags.
They sell like it's like a cowboy store.
And they have like an arcade, like shoot them up game.
And like you draw a pilgrim gate. And it was really amazing.
But then then what's almost more surreal besides that, it's just like
seeing a bubblegum shrimp in Osaka seems.
They still.
So if we ever were to do the CityWalk, Japan Saga, we would have.
We have once again be back.
Yes, if when when when when when I go, we're going to have to.
We will once again have to handle Bubba Gump.
There's the third time, maybe more depending on.
I don't know where else we're going to go.
There's also a TGI Fridays.
I believe so. I mean, I think there's a conventional everything.
There's a few conventional restaurants.
Yeah. TGI Fridays, a Bubba Gump.
And I got Tokyo Dome City as a bubblegum and TGI.
Does it really? I thought so.
I'm not sure.
I got to go back and look at look at my photos and see.
But yeah, you know what?
I think that Universal Japan still has this restaurant,
Beverly Hills Boulangerie, I think because it was just one of their like
they probably recreated the kind of generic
Hollywood Beverly Hills like opening area. Yeah.
So I think they have and probably the Today Show means nothing to them.
So they don't have a cafe.
But you might have passed right by that
that Beverly Hills Boulangerie, the thing we've been talking about.
Wow. That that would be incredible.
I just didn't even know like two ships in the night.
Something we didn't know about or care about until cultural days ago.
Dangerous clammy club sandwiches on the other side of the world.
To our Japanese brothers and sisters.
Well, what's some other stuff about this place?
Well, all right. So you had a canola.
How did you feel about that canola?
I thought it was good. Yeah.
I thought it was pretty solid.
Jane really like the breakfast sandwich on everything.
Croissant.
Oh, no. Oh, go ahead.
It's actually smashed avocado, devine, tomatoes, which
devine tomato. I looked it up.
It's just roasted tomatoes on everything.
Bagel seasoning, croissant served with side of fruit.
She did that without the sausage, but she had high marks for that.
I'm going to confuse you a little here
because do you remember what that was called by any chance?
Was it just like, oh, that was just breakfast sandwich.
Everything, croissant.
Here's a weird thing that they do at this place.
And maybe this this almost in a way mirrors the kind of bizarre politics
and infighting that we know about from the Today Show over the years.
You started saying that sandwich recipe.
I'm like, that sounds familiar because I looked that up
because I watched a segment from a couple of years ago
where that was called Savannah's Dream Croissant Sandwich.
And now it's just called breakfast.
Croissant sandwich.
Yeah. What happened?
Why was Savannah Guthrie stripped of her sandwich title?
Which is very odd because she's kind of I would say the rock of the Today Show.
Like I used to catch 20, 30 minutes of the Day Show when I was getting ready
for my old job.
And I was like, oh, I like Savannah Guthrie.
She's like personable and normal.
And has weathered all the storms of the Today Show.
Her and Al Roker and later in the day, Hoda and Kathy Lee.
Kathy Lee, I believe, is retired at this point.
I don't think she's there. Not there anymore.
Not there.
I know that. And Jenna Bush.
Jenna is there.
Not in a Bush.
George W. Bush's daughter.
Her daughter. Yeah, the party girl.
She's not partying anymore.
I know. She's grown up.
Yeah, grown up.
And she's got some things to say about international events, unfortunately.
Oh, no, no, no.
And she's going to be honest.
You get away with more of that.
She just went by Jenna Hager.
Why does she have to like you still carry the book?
I mean, I get it. It's how she got the job.
But it's also like, you don't have to, you know, yeah.
Like day to day.
I've seen is so great anymore.
Yeah, yeah.
Although as time goes by, we all forget.
We start forgiving the bushes.
Everyone pretends being happy with their performances on the third hour
of the Today show.
I like I'm sort of endeared, though, weirdly, to Jenna Bush from her pre
Hager went because she is in there's all these.
Have I ever talked to the show before about the the videos that they made
for the White House dog, Barney, the Bush dog, Barney?
Oh, maybe they made every year.
This is the kind of thing that's like this is fucking toast and Trump era.
No, I'm not making little dog videos.
But every year they made a different thing where George W.
Bush had to like act with his dog and like got big responsibility.
Barney, we got to clear out all we got to get this tree going.
I get that tinsel up.
And she, Jenna was the worst actor in the entire thing.
My leaps and bounds like, yes, Barney,
oh, you are excited for another classic holiday around the White House.
And she's looking every which way.
She does not know how to be on camera. Just screaming.
I can't believe that she is a daily television personality from her beginning.
I mean, she has come a long way, although I wish she I wish she was still as like
funny and cruddy as she was in the Barney holiday video.
Well, they do.
Well, first off, today's show is like what?
Four hours of broad. Four hours. Yeah.
So like occasionally, like we learned recently about, you know,
Copperfield based events.
And it's like, oh, Carson Daly pops in.
It does hosting on the today show.
That's true. You seem very shocked by that.
I feel like you had never heard that Carson Daly was a host.
I knew they kept him like on contract, but it didn't dawn on me when he is.
I had seen him host other NBC stuff after his show ended.
But he didn't dawn on me. Yeah. Yeah.
Boys, he's on the news right now.
Is he permanent New Year's? Right?
I'm not sure the status of the permanent
ness of his hosting duties. I'm not sure of any. Yeah.
Is anyone?
Well, but I mean, there's Seacrest.
There's the Andy Cohen.
There's I don't know who's permanent and who's not.
I don't know. I think he's been on New Year's.
I'm not sure. We haven't seen the contracts.
I can't speak to how permanent is.
Carson Daly's rocket New Year's Eve.
No, it's still Dick Clark's rocket.
Dick Clark has it in his ironclad contract that it's still called
Dick Clark's rocket New Year's Eve.
Wow. For some stupid reason.
A Minotaur level of like seeing these things through, following the letter
of the law, you feel like Dick Clark would, you know, charge back up.
Here, if you ever saw that name come off the right.
If you're in Hades right now, talk to my dad, Zeus.
He will get you back on the show. He can get you back.
Dick Clark will have a bowlhead, but he could get you back.
There will be his hand goes right through Hollywood Forever Cemetery lawn.
As soon as they get rid of that name, he's coming fucking back.
That'd be the baby, the biggest ratings you've ever seen.
We'd finally be excited about New Year's.
Oh, zombie Dick Clark introducing Megan Trainor.
Olivia Rodriguez, Rodrigo, Rodrigo, he knows that he might has.
You didn't stop at the first half of her last name.
Did you know that young people are back on in sync?
In sync is now popular among young people again.
Well, they reunite and they have a song.
The Trolls Trolls Trolls Trolls did hot ones around hot ones.
I was I was I saw a group of kids all like 15, 16, 17, and they were
they had windows down. They were blasting an in sync song.
And they were just like, they're like, this is like a classic one.
Yeah, like one of the tearing up my heart.
OK, you're one of those like ones.
I think I've been much stranger if they were blasting the new one, the trolls.
Yeah. They're troll soundtrack fans.
Well, it's like us when we were young, cool high schoolers
and we had the windows down with a CD of Sean on up.
The big Sean on our revival.
We are part of the revivals in the 90s, 2000s.
Did you did you eat or drink anything at the Today Cafe?
I had a coffee. Well, how was it?
Exclusive, exclusive roast of coffee.
How was that was the roast of the dark light?
I felt like it was a medium roast.
I didn't feel like it was.
Yeah. Yeah.
But I mean, they put a lot of creamer in there, so it's kind of just, you know,
we've got to pre-made so you don't you don't take your coffee black.
No, I do. I do.
Or she don't.
Is that an insult against my man and my manhood?
You know, I drink it however you want.
You know, the caramel drops or whatever the hell you put it in.
Oh, karma. I don't have caramel drops, but I do.
Yeah, I could drink it black, though.
OK, OK. I could do it.
We don't all drink our coffee, have our base goods
with like a squeeze of of ocular jelly.
Oh, I just I just I just chew the beans and I greased up all ocular jelly.
But I used to just put it in there.
You know, however you want, but you know, that's why I have it.
Now, sure, there's the there's the food, which is all kind of like
the sandwiches are all like New York seems like the idea here.
The Carnegie platter and the big apple cheese platter,
the bulls and the bears platter is because of the sketch.
Why or is it because of bull market?
I think it's a market.
I believe it's a market thing.
Yeah. OK.
And I know I go to the Today show for all my financial suggestions.
You know, Kramer's off, you know, because he's pretty sharp.
Yeah. In the rare event.
The Kramer host a New Year's Eve event.
Do we know? Oh, just yelling about.
Yeah. The CNBC New Year's.
Well, he was one of those people hiding in the Bernie Sanders talking in the primaries.
I think Jim Kramer and no, he was one of the guys scared.
He was about to get his head lopped off.
Yeah, that's right.
Glad he's OK. Yeah. Yeah.
This is so embarrassing because of, you know, who I am,
but I actually could never tell there's been a bull in a bear market.
Which one's good? Which one's bad?
You're not. I don't think we're the people to ask.
I don't know. I know the answer.
I think if you know how to play them, they're both advantageous.
Well, that's true. That's right.
He's right about that.
Bull is good bulls when everything's going up.
The rise bear is when everything's going down.
It's bearing down. Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah. Yeah. I like that.
I think that's cool.
Well, because you're sort of bull like you're there.
And I'm half bull, not like bullish bull.
I'm bullish, which is what they say about the market.
It's bullish or bearish. It's right. Yeah.
And I'm you know, I've been bullish on the episode, I think, since you
I mean, as much I like, I'm glad I thought it was going to be a packed one.
But now that I've heard, you know, like they were kind of talking about,
like the coffee was fine, the cannoli was fine.
It's almost like maybe this kind of was one where there was some room to
to chat with a mentor for a little bit.
Oh, I'm sure.
But I know people want to hear about the Today Show Cafe.
So start at night. 2019.
Yes. Yeah, you're right.
Well, let's make sure we get our facts.
Yeah. Well, it opened in May.
Opening ceremony with Al Roker.
I mean, like the thing that we got to give a little love to before we
we wind it down, unless anybody had big.
I did. You guys have like special guests are going to come into the garage.
Well, we're crowded out now by what's happened.
Well, like Randy Runyon's great grandson
happens to be around the corner.
And I'm waiting for him to show up because he's going to put on his great
grandfather's choco outfit and run in here.
But I guess I don't know, maybe we're a little too packed.
Oh, we don't have time for it.
Young Sheldon was hanging out in his car and I texted him.
I was like, hey, man, it's getting too packed. This one.
You know, man, you know, but you just meet me in an outburger.
I'll be there soon.
I just got canceled, though. He must be so bummed.
Young Sheldon got canceled. Yeah. Yeah.
The show, the show, not.
Oh, I know.
He's great. He's a great guy.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Young Sheldon is fine. The show is canceled.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The old the old kind of guy. Yeah.
Yeah. I but here's let's talk for a second.
The thing I mentioned at the beginning, which is so a couple of months ago,
Minotaur, they introduced as I was saying, they kind of shift these hosts
around. They like are at Savannah has an everything croissant one day
and then her name's not on it the next day.
It's like they're trying to keep these hosts on their toes.
When she in this very segment brought up to Al, don't you have an avocado toast?
He said kind of rushing through it like, oh, I think they took that off
for one or two years ago.
And so like, what is this?
Why are they hiring and retiring hosts in terms of sandwich ownership?
Good question.
Al has a different item, but she doesn't.
Yeah. Yeah. She wasn't given the opportunity.
No, it was originally opened with like the marketing of like.
And a lot of these are Al Roker's recipes because he's written a lot of cookbooks
over the years. OK.
A more healthy.
He did keto for a while. Right.
Lost a bunch of weight doing that.
So I think there are some healthier things on the menu.
It is funny. They led with that marketing of like it's Al.
Al's recipes and it's healthy.
There are a lot of sweets on the menu.
Yeah, it's so much. Yeah.
Confetti cake.
Where there's big macarons on top.
You do want some sweets with your coffee.
You're at a theme park. You're having fun.
I believe they used to.
I almost got it.
I think last time I was there, they had like, oh, a chicken biscuit sliders.
I was like, oh, that sounds good.
And then it said that's that grilled chicken.
Oh, grill. Oh, grill.
I was like, oh, I'm not a grill of the chicken at the bar.
It's usually pretty gross.
Very can I say something about grilled chicken, though, in general?
Because I feel like health wise, if we could have just gotten away
from chicken nuggets and gotten more towards pieces of grilled chicken,
I feel like maybe we like I don't always want to fried things.
Really, what I'm saying, you go to a state fair, you go to any
almost any fast food restaurant, you're not often even given the option
to not have like a fried piece of chicken.
If we just had grilled chicken on the menu,
you could even have like little tenders and you could dip
the grilled chicken in some sauce and you get your flavor that way.
I just feel like it's usually underseasoned or dried out.
Oh, but that's correct.
I also think your premise is strange.
I was at a restaurant last night where there was the full gamut of options.
Was it a fast food?
Food? Fast food restaurant was not a fast.
Oh, you're talking about.
Oh, I'm talking about. Yeah.
Food isn't going to.
Why are you going to fast food for grilled chicken?
Because I want once in a while, if you need to eat something late or or quick,
you know, you don't necessarily want the worst thing you could possibly eat.
Don't you think you'd be immediately complaining about how crappy the grill
would be bad, but the sauce would make it taste better
because the sauces are always very good. That's true.
I want to sauce counteract the healthiness of the to some degree it does.
But at least the fried, we should not get in the fried stuff.
OK, but I think the fried stuff easier to make in big portions
and usually more consistent.
I tried the blackened chicken sandwich of Popeyes and it was nasty.
Yeah, your point is like think about a fried thing.
It's frozen.
The it's easier to do.
I understand. Inside it is juicy.
Even if it's on a heat lamp.
Well, it's easier to do, but also because it's easy.
Well, it's easier to do.
And it also tastes better when it's bad.
Yeah. Yeah. That's also an issue with it.
I'm just saying once in a while, if I'm like trying to get something quick,
it would be nice to McDonald's.
They don't McDonald's even have like an option for a grilled chicken sandwich.
You can't even get a grilled chicken.
There you go. But it all is bad.
All of the fast food is well, I would eat the whole thing.
But I know for you guys, you wouldn't want to eat it with even a little bit
of pink in there and you'd have a teenager make it be bad.
Well, you like it with.
Yeah. No, your way of chicken preparation is like feathered, beaked alive,
feathered, beaked alive.
That's your one of my victims that I bite that guy's head off with the chicken
inside of it. And then the chicken double up.
Yeah. Chicken is in your stomach alive for at least an hour.
Making for a streaming and agony.
The juices. Yeah.
Before you can listen to hear the juices destroying it, your stomach acid
destroying the chicken and then you get and you I assume you get some sort of
like arousal from hearing the chicken dying.
All right. No, hold on.
I don't talk about my sexual dispersal.
Well, you're an evil creature, obviously, like you're getting off.
You're getting off on your Minotaur.
You're getting on, Mike, everyone.
And you know, we're probably ending this episode.
Maybe we won't be trimming anything out conveniently.
You're getting your fucking rocks off hearing a chicken scream.
You won't even recognize us as sexual creatures, but you're King
Shearing. Well, I'm OK with certain boundaries, but yeah.
You won't do Jason eats chicken McNuggets.
He gets his rocks off, too.
It's the same fucking thing.
That's not on Mike.
Bring up that Jason gets aroused when eating chicken McNuggets.
That actually is the time the dipping sauce is still a lot of the heavy left.
Yeah, you mean some special hard made.
Erotic. They come in a little too.
Yeah. There's Mambo and sweet and spicy jam right now.
They will charge you extra for that.
What do you think about that?
What do you think about Mambo and sweet and spicy?
Mambo is very good.
I didn't try the sweet and spicy jam because I heard it's just jam.
But I like the sweet and spicy jam more than the Mambo.
I do. I don't think it's a great execution of Mambo.
Mambo is the regional DC sauce on a lot of stuff.
Is that right? Yeah, I'm not familiar with it.
I don't know anything that's like an analog to a but let me tell you about sweet and spicy jam.
You get a sausage, egg and cheese McGriddle.
Yeah, take that sweet and spicy jam.
You put it on top of there a little bit sweet with the with the spice, that sausage patty.
It is a good, good breakfast.
That sounds good. It sounds good. Yeah.
Or even just a sweet and spicy jam on a plain hash brown, that crunch
and the sweet and spicy jam.
I highly recommend it.
Yeah, I hear that.
I'm going to snap my man.
I know you're a big fast food guy.
I remember for the one time a year I go to McDonald's.
And then I regret it immediately.
You love the YouTube channels where it's someone eating the new fast
food items in their cars.
Oh, God.
Are you watching? It doesn't sound sad.
Are you watching my new guy, Luke Foods?
No, I watch.
Because I'm into my this is a new guy, Luke Foods, and he just tried
Indian food for the first time a couple of weeks ago and it was going viral.
You saw Luke Foods. OK.
Oh, I saw the Indian food, the guy in the shirt and tie.
And he was really sweet.
He's just very nice.
He was in Nintendo Land the other day yesterday.
Oh, wow. He's really making the thing of it.
Yeah. What did he think of that food?
I haven't watched it, actually. Yeah. I just saw he was there.
She's if I go to Nintendo Land first time, what's the number one thing
I should eat besides toad?
I'm going to eat some some some food from home before you get there.
Yeah, far from.
I like the little cake that looks like the green like hills.
You tell us. Yeah, that's pretty.
Yeah, a little tear. Yeah.
And there's a little flag that goes in.
Yeah, dessert.
But then you would be shocked by the level of rigor,
more role of like what it takes to get a cute little dessert.
Yeah, you have to have a reservation.
Stool cafe.
Unless that's not the case anymore.
I don't know. Yeah.
It was when I was there in November.
It's still like insane there.
There's still the ad hoc website set up with the reservation.
I thought that was a mistake.
It was the shadiest website that a theme park has sent me to,
and that includes Go Dotcom.
I live in a labyrinth and I'm scared to go to Nintendo Land.
I'm like worried I'm going to be stuck in a line and I'm going to be like,
oh, this is where I'm too much of a home.
You know what I mean? Yeah, I hear you.
Yeah, even the other lot.
Yeah, you live in a labyrinth.
And yet I think that the the Genie Plus lightning lane situation,
Mike can found you not to mention as much as me.
New brand new ride.
They could have engineered it any way they want to.
Apparently doesn't fit Minotaur sized people.
Ah, yes.
On a video game where Donkey Kong and Bowser
Bowser can be in a cart.
It's unbelievable that the Minotaur couldn't fit in there.
And unlock incredible powers with their size and heft.
You can get you can get going so fast if you're one of them.
You can get going on acceleration.
No, yeah, but they're not there.
They wouldn't even be allowed.
Wario would be turned away.
Listen, I can understand like the Harry Potter ride
being not Minotaur sized people, but like, but
but the life of pets.
Come on. What are you doing?
That's a that's a flippin dark ride.
You can't fit on that.
They could have made that any way they want to.
Could have done it. Yeah.
One mile an hour.
You know, feels like they just have it against Minotaur's
and people the size of Minotaur's, to be honest.
Like they literally could do it any way they want to.
That's how they chose.
Sorry, I'm out of my hobby horse.
Oh, I understand what you mean.
Yeah, this is your area.
Our guests get to express any theme park opinions they have.
And I'm glad you're here.
And then you have a bunch that you've been to Osaka.
One thing that I think you'd be but that ride was wouldn't really do it for you.
Because part of the novelty is like you see yourself on a screen
and it's like you're a little animal.
You're a little puppy, but you're already half right.
I don't want to get anything wrong.
Oh, yeah.
So just filling in that extra half wouldn't be that fun for you.
I'd be OK because I would be one third ball, one third human, one third puppy.
I think that's kind of cute.
I think that'd be kind of fun.
And then you get adopted at the end.
Oh, really? Yeah.
That's what happens.
Thanks for selling me on a ride.
I can't go. Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was trying to tell you.
Keep stepping in it.
I tell you, let me go back to what I was saying a little while ago,
which is that they they they trade these hosts in and out in a very cruel fashion.
But sometimes they throw them a bone and Al and Al Roker gets to rise back
to the top and have a new item.
Now, I don't know if anybody in our group tried Al Roker's butternut squash tart.
So I can't really speak to that.
I'm going on a little bit of a tangent here
because I'm going to show a video from when he debuted Al's butternut squash tart.
They sent Al down to Orlando to talk about not just the tart.
I guess they thought the tart wouldn't fill an entire segment.
So they decided that maybe he should talk about some other stuff
like the Minion attractions that are are pretty new down there.
The whole Minion land and the Minion Cafe.
And he talks a little bit about the Minion Cafe.
And I found Al Roker's thoughts on this a little bit more interesting than his tart.
Minion brains when they when they bring it out, it looks it looks grim,
but it tastes fantastic.
There's a lot of yellow.
OK, it is this.
Al had the soup that that looks like Minion brains.
And now I heard that and thought, well, that maybe that's something that they have.
But then I looked up the actual name of the item.
This is just called Otto's Noodle Bowl.
Yeah, this is not called Minion.
I actually remember seeing it.
Yeah, I saw this. OK, it's just a bowl that looks like a minion, right?
It does a regular soup. Yes, this is a visual clarity.
You're correct that like it comes in a clear bowl.
And the yellow is provided not by the bowl itself, but by the noodles,
which are bright yellow.
And then you kind of like turn it and dump it onto your plate
and mix it with the other ingredients.
But I don't think the intention here was for it to be Minion brain soup,
which makes it all the more strange when the host kind of grimace
and then he says, sounds grim, but tastes great.
That was because I had a difference.
I had the green tomato soup, which I think is just tomato soup.
But it doesn't look like a brain or a liver.
And I know there was pork belly in it.
There was Minions, pork belly, some little red flavor.
And a tomato soup.
It was surprisingly good.
And then it came with a little pimento cheese, grilled cheese.
It was delicious.
Yeah, that sounds like, you know, I, you know, just like we're going to end up
like pining for the other restaurant instead of the one we're supposed
to be talking about. Yeah. As Al did, I thought Al was more fascinating
talking about Minion Cafe.
We haven't even gotten into these tots.
I'm excited to hear about the tots.
By the way, I also like that clip how he was actively trying to ferment
a fight between butternut squash and pumpkin spice.
Oh, yes. At the very top of that.
Yeah, there's a constraint because his thing is butternut squash.
And he says, like, well, unlike, you know, all that pumpkin spice,
who likes pumpkin spice and kind of gets nothing either way.
He doesn't get like a boo. Yeah, I'm kind of like, I don't know.
I don't think anyone knows what they're doing exactly with the hatred
of pumpkin spice. Oh, yeah.
Is it? It's just one of those things people have started doing.
And do they mean it?
Is it just like a fun game for everybody to participate in?
I did is I like the people in that restaurant
and confused by it and have no opinion either way.
Hmm. I it feels like it's just maybe it's so everywhere now
than that people are annoyed by it.
I think the ubiquity.
But is it also just is it like does it have something to do with like
like you're so you're like soft as well as it like one of those Minotaur slams?
Well, it's like it's so fully a full hearty.
Yeah, I don't know. I'm not sure.
I think it feels very like I'm not sure what people can identify
what's going on here exactly, other than like I see it too much.
I would listen.
I would pumpkin spice the neck of my enemy and then like, great.
Get your rocks off that way.
Actually, I had a pumpkin filled ravioli the other day.
It was some red sauce. It was great.
It's like a little sweet.
Oh, yeah. And it's a sweetness.
It's not too overpowering.
It doesn't feel like you're having a sore.
So you can mix it with something savory.
I think it's fine. Yeah.
I've been I've been eating the
Dunkin branded goldfish pumpkin spice goldfish.
Oh, wow. Really?
Hold on a second.
Hold on. Different things fighting.
I've been really into the the sweet goldfish lately.
So I got the elf one.
I got the 20th anniversary maple spice.
You're leaving me in the dust here.
So yeah, goldfish, the official goldfish cracker crackers.
They have a cookie.
They have a sweet one.
They have a cookie line.
Yeah. Oh, the goldfish, the same like crispy, like a cheesy one.
Is it like, no, it's like a like a thinner crispy butter cookie.
Oh, but the same size is like a size of goldfish.
Oh, wow. OK.
You know what I had that was kind of an interesting combo recently was
that Campbell's is doing a chunky ghost pepper chicken noodle,
which sounds like kind of a weird.
Wait, I'm sorry. I didn't mean I did. I say that I had that.
I didn't. That was just something that I saw on deal vibes.
Yeah, that's an exclusive deal. It looks good.
I actually missed that one.
The heads up on what's happening.
Progressive or whatever that soup cans of ones.
They are making spicy soups and they are so spicy.
Wow. Really? Really?
It's a real spicy like the chicken tortilla soup and like a spicy chicken noodle.
So I guess Campbell's is getting the games, too.
So interesting.
Like I was like, OK, whatever.
They're going to sell spicy stuff at the grocery store.
Right. It killed me.
Wow. Oh, my God.
And this is you we're talking about.
You were like you were like down on your back for a little bit.
Yeah, I'm somewhat of a heat seeker myself.
So I don't want to start any more rivalries.
If you start stealing people's catchphrases, catchphrase from what?
This is other podcast as there's a whole.
This is the first time I've ever listened to because I got tagged to this.
Oh, you know, not only did we bring you to X, you got you've never listened
to a podcast at all. Wow. Wow.
This is like the radio, but it's like you download it or it's on an app.
It's yeah. Yeah, you got it.
It is like the radio. Yeah.
Check it out a lot. It is a little confusing.
Just be be a little careful about the kinds of things like
if you're passionate about like a hot salad, right?
The podcast forum, I think that area is kind of covered by this other guy.
OK, OK, I won't I won't touch you guys.
I mean, I don't have many food opinions.
You know, I like I go to the restaurants.
I'm like, you know, the McDonald's like I said, I'll tell you what,
the spicy jam, I'd give it like if I was bringing like one to five
little forks.
Oh, it's like fire.
Careful, folks, two times.
Make it like make it like pitchforks or something.
Yeah, that's good. Yeah, that's good.
Yeah. We held that you're in that conception, the devil.
I'll read it for to have battle axes.
Yeah. So eight blades and nine blades total on my battle.
That's not bad. That's not bad.
You could also you could make it out of like six six six.
That might kind of like get you away from the.
You're thinking of like a demon thing.
I'm more from like the Greek thing, not like the William Blake.
Right. Christian. Right.
I'm more of like a Greek Zeus's son, I think.
I said sounds right.
It was a long time ago. Yeah, it seems all right.
Like he made love to a boy.
You haven't done you don't know your own.
And you haven't done like an ancestry on yourself.
So you don't know exactly what you are.
I don't know. I don't know.
Is there a Christian Minotaur? I'm looking it up.
I'm sure we've been like appropriated by certain religions.
Great. It says what religion is the Minotaur and it's Greek.
It is Greek mythology. Yeah, that makes sense.
No, my favorite religion, Greek Greek is the religion.
I was your Mount Rushmore of religious
Greek Roman Persian.
American. Yeah, American number one.
Well, then let me let me let me tie it all together with food opinions.
You haven't done this yourself and they aren't, you know,
you just high five minions while they went by.
If you had to take a guess
and follow Al's error and crack open a minion skull and eat the innards inside,
if you would you have a good do you think that would taste good?
Any any thoughts?
Honest, my first thought, maybe just because we were talking about,
I honestly think the brains would be a little pumpkin spice flavored,
a little like cinnamon.
What did you know?
So we broke down what pumpkin spice actually is.
It's not anything to do with pumpkin.
Have you heard this? No, I forget.
Somebody broke it down.
It's like it's like it's like cinnamon, cardamom, nutmeg, nutmeg.
And it's a specific mix.
What you put into the pie. Yes.
Yeah, exactly.
So the pumpkin itself is not necessarily like part.
If that's why it's pumpkin spice, not pumpkin.
It's the spice of a pumpkin.
The spice of a pumpkin pie.
Yeah. Wow.
Like it's like it's the brain, the brains of a minion.
But should be pumpkin pie spice then.
I have had some pumpkin pie lattes I've been seeing on coffee shops
and you since a little sweeter.
But I'm saying if it's called pumpkin spice
and it's really just the spice you put in a pumpkin pie,
the pie part really should really be in the title.
You're correct.
But I think that does make me now I start leaning that that's sweet.
Yeah, I'm avoiding that.
Because I think a pumpkin ravioli or a pumpkin bread,
you would get similar spice profiles.
So there's room for savoriness in the general description.
Wouldn't a minion taste like a banana because they eat so many bananas?
I just think they have good bones.
They'd be a good bone ice cream.
OK, so probably with at some point, there's so much banana
that some of that banana is going to filter down to the bone.
And then you've got a natural flavor that, like, say the bones of a Mike
might not inherently have long bones, long, youthful,
as long as he can his forked tongue.
Oh, he's licking his tongue.
He's licking, licking with his tongue.
One time, I actually can lick his.
Wow. Oh, that's cool.
That's a dream.
Is he ever wanted to lick tongue, bro?
Somebody else's?
No, no, no. Your own.
That's right.
So I got to ask this with one of my biggest regrets.
Talk about universal socket.
I don't want to keep bringing up.
I'm not doing it to brag.
It just happens to be a lot of minion stuff over there.
I regret not getting there was a minion burger that was a perfectly yellow bun.
Oh, yeah. With a little eyeball in the center of it.
And I'm sure the hamburger was just kind of normal.
I'm sure the bread wasn't flavored, but it looked beautiful.
Like, it's so cool.
Like, I really like that.
Like, I had the I had some mochi ice cream at the Tokyo Disney
Sea that looked like the little little green guys.
Oh, yes. That was great.
Yeah. That was also really good.
That was tough.
And for some reason, maybe I trust that kind of thing to be done
better in the Japanese parks.
And well, there's stuff like that in Mario.
I feel like that's like I don't think I don't want I don't want any color on my
my burger bun. That's what I'm I have.
Have you guys had a good iteration of that?
No.
Only if it's like steered, like if they see her like an image or something.
Oh, that's fine. Yeah.
But not that would I want to eat the black bun at Burger King.
Yeah. Oh, that's right.
They've done that. Yeah.
Yeah. Wow.
Well, it's that dye that probably turns your poop neon blue.
It's right. You know what I'm saying, buddy?
Lully. Yeah.
It's happened because I had the black slurpee like 20 years ago.
Yeah. And I shit neon blue.
Oh, yeah.
There's a few blue poops laying around the labyrinth right now.
OK. All right.
I hear you.
I hear you. Oh, no.
Well, any any closing thoughts on on today, Cafe?
I know you haven't been in it.
Does this all make you excited to go?
I would definitely.
I mean, it seems it seems like let me ask is it's if today's show stuff taken away,
is it a serviceable good cafe for like a coffee and a serviceable?
Yeah. Yeah. It's a lot of variety.
And it was fine.
As I said, it is a more pleasant environment, I think, than the previous
establishment was.
It's right at the front of the park.
So it's convenient.
I feel like I think park habits wise, I feel like I'm really trying to get a coffee
before I get into the park wherever I am, because I think it's going to be more of a hassle.
And, you know, if like in Orlando, I'm in a hotel where I know that's going to be a quick
Starbucks there, I don't I'd like my coffee to kick in before I am in the park.
But are you guys that way?
Are you willing to have your your morning jolts in the park itself?
I'm willing.
But I do think it's nice to do it on the way.
I mean, the best is if you can, if you're going to Disneyland, for instance,
your mobile order is you're like walking down downtown Disney for that Starbucks there.
And you grab it.
That is a nice thing to walk in with a little cup.
I like to get like a deal on like a 12 pack of Java Monster Energy.
Well, yeah, I think that on the drive down to the train right over, you drink all 12 on
the way down. And then you're ready.
Sure. Coffee's not bad or else you're going to be hoofing it to that
parking garage restaurant.
That's right. I've always up in it everywhere I go.
You know, it started tense, but I feel like things worked out.
And now I'm so happy to say Minotaur, you survived podcast, the ride, the second gate.
I'm so glad you could join us.
Wow. That's amazing.
It's like this labyrinth of a podcast that you talk about
was actually a lot more fun than mine.
I didn't feel like I was going to die at all once.
It's a little easier than the one you preside over.
I'd say, you know what?
Let's let's give you the opportunity to exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything that you Minotaur would like to plug?
Sure. Yeah, yeah, of course. Of course. Come to my labyrinth.
There is great treasure and reward at the end of it.
If you could solve my riddles and puzzles and survive me trying to kill you. Sure.
Also, gosh, I just saw this Indiegogo.
There's a great filmmaker named Matt Mazzotti, who has an Indiegogo.
He's trying to raise some money for a short film starring Mike Mitchell
from some other podcast called the Doughboys.
That's the Minotaur. That's so crazy.
You bring that up. That's what I was alluding to with the fork scores and everything.
That's the podcast that that guy is on. Mike Mitchell.
I just read on his Wikipedia. I didn't even know what it was.
I was just being polite.
That's this whole other podcast. It's good.
I mean, we're way more popular. Don't tell him.
We're pockets are insanely more popular than Doughboys, but still a good one.
A good pocket.
Because theme parks are much more universal than food.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. No.
Very old-fashioned and broad. Sure. I'll take it.
But Indiegogo for a short called Big Brothers.
Matt Mazzotti, look it up if you can't donate.
If you can, you try to raise some money for this film.
So check that out. Wow. Wow. Hey.
And you know, Matt Mazzotti, it's funny you just happen to catch that.
And a good man.
And I think he's going to make a good film and he's going to be good to the crew on that.
This is a guy who's good to the crews.
I know you can expect. You're a Minotaur of the people.
Sure. Yeah.
You treat you treat people right before you start cracking their necks open.
And chopping their heads off.
Will there be some sort of new like what sauce would Matt Mazzotti lay out for the
crew like crafty section, do you think?
There's be lots of sweet and spicy.
That's what I'm asking. OK, well, there'll be some spicy.
Got the mongo.
Mambo. Mambo sauce.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mambo. See, we're not in D.C.
You know what? I have a few packs of Mambo sauce right.
East Coast Brothers and Sisters. All right.
Sure. We're fine.
We're fine with Mambo.
How do you guys do you want to like
a rattle a little bit? It's really up to you.
It's an audio podcast is a problem.
We don't really have three cameras.
Should I maybe can?
It's going to sound like Foley, which we've all learned.
The mentor.
I'm a big foley.
Do you hear the scrapes listeners?
Foley.
He's charging.
Oh, no, no, no.
The second game. If you want to dig even deeper.
Turn on your VIP manager.
Club three where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular
episodes ad free.
Please. I thought you guys ended up in a good place.
Spare our co-host Mike.
I'm more than likely killing him.
Oh, he's getting his rocks off while he's doing it.
I can tell. He's clearly aroused.
Mike was right.