attraction music
It's official. Christmas is better than magic.
It's been officially determined here on Club 3
via the last Club 3 poll. I'm Scott Garen, you're my Carlson Jason shirt.
Hello.
Magic sucks.
We can finally say it.
We're saying it now. We're saying Merry Christmas and we're saying
Magic is shitty magic.
Um...
No magic is better than the birth of the baby Jesus.
As many miracles, don't be true magic.
Yeah, if you didn't notice or don't recall,
the Club 3 poll, we realized there was something interesting happening.
There were some Christmas topics and several magic topics.
So why not pair them together?
The magic of Christmas versus the magic of magic.
And the magic of Christmas ultimately won with today's topic,
Jimmy Buffett's Christmas Island.
Um...
Chris Angel's magic with the stars got trounced,
coming in hot as a nominee.
And yet I think maybe...
I just think there was a need and a desire to celebrate Jimmy.
As you hear this, we have just passed the...
Not just the first Christmas, minus Jimmy Buffett,
but also his birthday.
His birthday was Christmas.
A fact that comes up in some of his Christmas music.
The song Working and Playing.
Which is not a Christmas song, I should say.
I'm blanking because I screwed up.
Do we have to listen to it on this then?
If it references that fact?
We sure could.
It's a newer one in the last 10 years, I believe.
Because I believe the show we saw was the Working and Playing Tour.
That is correct.
The one I was at?
The one you were at.
I believe it was Working and Playing.
That was sort of the title of the tour.
I didn't hold on to the premise of the tour.
The title and theme of the tour.
Of being working and playing.
I believe it's the first line in the song.
It wasn't by choice that I was born on Christmas.
I believe that's the lyric.
And then something about floating on...
What a heavenly sound.
I can't even say the word.
He does a Christmas-ismus rhyme.
Did he play it live on the Working and Playing Tour?
I think he did. I think he had to do it.
It's the name of the tour.
I gotta do it if it's the name of the tour.
We should look up the setlist for that night and see.
Oh yeah.
I've been looking at the setlist.
Not for Jimmy.
Just for lots of bands.
It's fun to see a show 20 years ago
that you saw and find that the setlist is available
and you can remember parts of it
and then you forgot totally parts of it.
Oh certainly.
In this case, with me, forgot all of it.
The whole thing.
He did Cheeseburger in Paradise.
You know, Finns Happen.
Seems right.
Did he play Margaritaville?
I believe he did.
I have a faint memory that he played Margaritaville.
Well Jason looks that up.
In terms of magic, Fox's Masked Magician special
is held on as the runner-up.
So that will need to defend its title
one more time.
The Fighting Masked Magicians.
Can they make it in January?
We will see.
But we need four new ideas to go against it.
No theme. Whatever you want.
I do have one more little Club 3 assignment.
Should I say that now?
Or do you have the setlist, Jason?
I believe October 22, 2015.
Does that sound right?
I think that's right.
Setlist.fm
And I'll remind you, you don't have to read the entire thing.
Oh, okay.
Well, obviously you started with Rag Top Day.
And then off to see the Lizard.
Working and playing number 3.
There you go.
So that does answer the question.
So we don't have to continue.
What was the encore, perhaps?
That's fine. Cut to the end.
Let's ask what the stretch was.
It just says, oldest surfer on the beach.
Yeah, I know that.
Scarlet Begonias, which is a
Grateful Dead cover.
And Brown Eyed Girl was Van Moris' cover.
I remember he did his cover of Brown Eyed Girl.
I do remember that.
And of course he did Southern Cross.
And he did the Back Where I Come From.
In what world is of course
He did Southern Cross a relatable statement
to even all the people in this room.
Well, he always does.
Of course Southern Cross.
I say that because he always does Southern Cross.
What's Southern Cross?
The song Southern Cross.
I know it's a song.
This is the fastest to me being
It's a Crosby, Stills, Nash cover.
I've seen
live videos.
And he inevitably does that.
And he also does Back Where I Come From.
The Kenny Chessy song written by Mac McAnally.
Of course.
Future Country Bears contributor.
Mac.
Look, I know some people know
that's a guy in the band.
Some people listening are not
Buffett experts.
Every single person
listening is a Jimmy Buffett
band and set list expert.
If this was the main feed I'd say absolutely
you're right. But no, I think everybody
I'm actually shocked this won.
Quite frankly, I know people have affection
for the plane and everything, but I'm like
wow, really?
I am a little bit too and I think I do
attribute this to that it was the year of
his passing. I think everybody
felt like we needed to
end because this is the final
episode of 2023.
You're getting it here on Club 3. So what better
way I guess to end
than with the tributes to one of the greats
who we lost this year.
That being said
I'm not sure if people would have voted for it if they knew
just how much Buffett was coming
in the upcoming series
City Walk Orlando Saga
Multiverse of Madness, which brings me to
my next point before we fully
dive into Buffett.
I didn't talk this over with you guys, but just see
if you agree with this plan as I say it.
You know that next year, 2024
will be the year of the City Walk
Orlando Saga Multiverse of Madness.
We are currently consulting
with the Sector Keeper.
We've had many dense
prayer sessions and
workshops to try to figure out
exactly what our journey will entail
and how this is going to work for all of us.
But we've
had the question
what do we do with Club 3?
Club 3 has not existed
for a daily saga
yet. So this is the first time
we've previously used
the second gate, but
not Club 3. So I guess
in addition to just give us your regular
topics for January, separately
I want to know
what do you want Club 3
as far as the City Walk
Orlando Saga goes?
Do we do the most
deep, obscure
insane thing,
a never built thing, a closed thing?
How obscure do we go?
Or do you
the elite Club 3 members
take one of the biggest things that there is?
Whatever that is.
It's a weird scale we're dealing with here
as far as City Walk.
Let's find out what you consider
a big one, or what is the
deepest possible dive we
could do. Do we think this is a fair
question to ask? Just ask our audience
at this point. What do you want?
Well, I'm going to put my
thumb on the scale a little for January.
I want to talk
about that mass magician. I want to talk
about those shows that haunted me.
I've tried twice. So, I think
there is a clamoring for it, but this is
a democracy.
In February, though, you could also vote for
Masked Magician. Maybe you want a nice break
in the middle of this saga.
And we'll warp to a different
universe.
You're saying that there's a possibility that
Club 3 doesn't want to be
part of the saga. That they actually want to
step outside of it. Or I would say even if
there's an outdoor mall that's in the
LA area that you like
and you want to send us there for a mini
saga, so we could do that too.
This is true. We haven't said much about, and I don't want
to say much about what multiverse
refers to exactly, but it does
open up possibilities of
other places that we could
be sent. So, that's a
very good think outside the box.
Something completely, you could
pull us out of Orlando. We might all
need a break by then from Cityhawk,
Orlando. I mean, there's plenty of places
that are pretty close to here that we've mentioned.
Just think about it. That's all I'll say.
Does it have to be close to here?
I guess it doesn't. I suppose it doesn't.
It helps us to go there, but I think people
wish it was like Times Square, I don't think.
Well, they can send us to go read about things
in Times Square. They can send us
across the world if they want. I think we've all
been to Times Square a number of
times. Various years,
various configurations.
That's true.
So, if you want the topic in that
month to be Times Square,
then it could be that.
Basically, possibilities are endless,
but just, you know, in addition to general
topics, I'm sorry to give you so much homework.
I know that it's a holiday break,
but we do need to, we do need
a path forward on this.
We want to figure out in advance. So, if there's things
people are excited about in Cityhawk,
Orlando, we'll do a poll way ahead of time
and figure out what we're doing. We still don't know exactly
what month it's going to happen, but we do.
This is a crucial piece, I think, in figuring
out the puzzle that is going to be
this daily saga.
So, please give us your ideas
for regular stuff and for Cityhawk
stuff or wherever you want to send us.
Vote with your likes. Put that all in the comments.
And with that, now we can
officially move on to JB.
Jimmy Buffett Christmas.
He was, can I say other people who were born
on Christmas? Ryan Seacrest,
Karl Rove, great Americans.
Only the best.
Yes.
It's like, oh, that's good.
And it's Karl Rove,
who was the one who was like, and my
birthday is separate, okay?
So, there's gifts on Christmas
and then there's great gifts
from my birthday. What's funny, you bring
this up, this is a thing Jimmy brought up while he
was alive, obviously, that he didn't
like it when people would like try to combine
a gift for him. Yeah.
And he could smell that a mile away when he was a kid.
Because I imagine that would happen.
I think that happens to you if your
birthday is December 20th.
I think anywhere in the vicinity, that's
the trouble you're getting. My dad's
is November 29th, my mom's
is December 15th.
So, I've tried to make a point of
like, sending
a gift or sending flowers
or something on their actual birthday.
So, I didn't do the like, and here's the
extra present on Christmas morning.
Yeah.
He was talking about his mother, apparently, too,
was very insistent that the family give
him two gifts. He said more, he was talking
about how this didn't sit well with him, but he said,
more importantly, it did not sit well with my mother
who made it known. In no uncertain terms
to the aunts, uncles, and cousins of the Buffett
clan strung out along the Gulf
Coast that she expected two
presents for her bouncing baby
boy. One for his birthday
and one for Christmas.
Wow. So, laid down the law.
Not as easy going as her son
would turn out to be. Right. Or at least
the character. Yes. Yeah, yeah.
In reality, yes. He was
this friendship's over.
One gift
and we're done. It's hard because I want to talk about
more, I guess I really do want to kind of just
focus on the Christmas Island because, again, there is a
lot of Buffett coming. I have
a lot of recent Buffett thoughts, but I don't
think that they belong here. I think this is
Christmas time. I mean, something could
I mean, you're right, that's
good to God, but does anything feel like it
needs to be said in this, the
year of his terrible
Oh, of his passing?
I don't know, just sort of general.
I forget who said it, but like
there was a somebody said it in the
band, like, you know what? Or no, Jimmy said it to
the band, like, let the party
continue. So I'm like, oh, it
seems like the Coral Reifers
are going to go out without
him. So
this is an interesting topic in general we've talked about
lately and a lot of things have popped
up lately is the what happens
after a very successful
lucrative band
or musician dies?
How will in a state
continue to make money?
Yes, and especially
how do
very popular bands
that wrap it up or pass away
that are of the boomer
generation make sure
that they keep their mitts
on the marketplace and don't ever
give up or pass the baton to
anyone else even post their death.
How do we make sure there are no
new stars and it keeps going
our great grandchildren? There's no
bands. You're not allowed to have
bands. I don't care if you're
Kiss or the Democratic Party, no bands.
Yeah, so I mean it's interesting
I look when I go see the Coral Reifers
without him, maybe
it might be fun if it's the same
environment. I think everyone
in the audience would, our audience
who as we established, knows
every single member of the Coral Reifers.
Of course, yes. The club three only.
The club three people who know, yes.
Yeah, I mean if Mack
frontstead. I don't think
I don't know, Mack can sing, Mack's done his own
concerts, but I feel like you're going to get a different singer.
You can't get somebody to do an impression
of him, but I feel like maybe you do rotating singers.
Scott and I saw the revolution without Prince
after Prince died, but that was sort of
just that one like stretch of tribute
shows. I think that would have been not
a great thing to do.
Well, I guess it was his passing, but it was also
way after they had ever played with him.
So there's also the emotion of just
that they're back together and maybe this is a good
excuse. I think the immediate
let's try to keep going
could be tough. There's something
odd about that. Or maybe this is
the time. Maybe you do it, I think you do it
now and you don't do it forever.
Sure, yeah.
Well, if it's a two-hander
if all the band backing it up
and it's Mack and
Jimmy collaborator Alan Jackson
Alan Jackson is like retiring though soon.
He's like in his late 60s, I think.
The club three knows that
Mike. Everyone knows what
Alan Jackson's up to.
Alan Jackson, I believe is on some sort of a retirement tour.
I could be wrong. He, of course,
wrote It's Five O'Clock Somewhere.
Right. But
Jimmy's on that song and it is
a big hit and maybe a lot of people
know that song better than not Margaritaville,
but almost every other song he's got maybe
other than Cheeseburger. I think Jimmy's first
charting song. Something like that.
Yeah, it was a big hit.
Jimmy does that in concert. So, no, I don't think
Alan, I'm not against it. I like
Alan Jackson. I could list the songs I like
of Alan Jackson's, but I don't think he's
the guy to keep the band
going for another 10 years.
He's got his own hits. He's got a bunch of them.
Yeah, I know. So I'm just saying
we need a young person.
We need a young person who plays the guitar.
You need a dead in company. You need a
mayor. Yeah, or you just need like
a podcaster who maybe
is seasoned as far as his actual
age is concerned. Comfortable on stage.
He's youthful. Yeah, cool.
You wouldn't be able to, you would never guess
what age he is. You wouldn't guess.
And we won't today
either. 18, 19? Sorry,
I know I wasn't supposed to guess, but you, sorry,
you just, you look 18. You got a backwards
cap. You look 18. You get
carded for those hard seltzers
that taste like candy. Those bomb
pop seltzers.
So yeah, a guy
like that maybe you want, maybe somebody
an unknown perhaps. Cause I don't
know, but you can't get the Adam Lambert
Queen thing, which they've been doing this now for so
long and that's pretty popular, but
I don't know. I don't always
You can't copy that formula.
You know, you don't want somebody who's well
known for their great singing.
You want somebody maybe from
another medium who could surprise
people with his breadth of talent.
Exactly.
And would that person be willing to
keep up Jimmy's image
and shave a bald spot
into his own head?
Only that person can answer.
Whoever that is, I would be comfortable with
whoever you're talking about. Yes, I think that's what they
would have to do. Would he be comfortable performing on
stage barefoot?
Yeah, yes.
So front of the paywall.
There was some hesitancy
there. Yeah, I just I've
been walking like when I walk outside,
I feel like my feet get messed up.
Whoever this is, his feet
might get messed up a little bit. So I
feel like it's better to have shoes. But again,
if you're on the, he had like a rug
out on the stage. That's a comfortable
place. Yeah, one of those padded
like, you stand
at the sink, you get a little pad.
Well, there must be, there's probably
a way to develop kind of like
invisible insoles
that pad your feet,
but also blend into your skin
tone so that it looks like you're
barefoot without you having to actually
be. And I know that's not something that
the 70 year old performer needed,
but maybe the
close to 40 year old, again, just
guessing ages. Yeah, the person. Some
practical calluses on
the insoles. Right. Yeah.
And the person could slip in his own, like
say like, hey, we're doing one of mine tonight
too.
And like that would be like a good way to get
out there. Huck up apps.
So just really
quick to explain this is from this is a McGruff
album. I made some stuff in
style of McGruff. Yeah, I've tried
to explain to somebody who doesn't know the podcast
what that is. And they go, okay.
McGruff? Oh,
okay. Interesting.
What year is it? What year is it?
I don't think I've ever, podcast or no, I don't think I've
ever been a part of anything that didn't require
a full four sentences of
onboarding before you can enjoy the
this is, yes,
my body of work and all of ours.
Eventually, you
develop the phrase, hey, don't worry about
it. What's up with you?
How are you doing, brother? How are you?
How are you?
Been to the movies lately?
How about the weather? So yeah, so that I was thinking about that
because yeah, I am
very interested to see how every
major act tackles
this issue of how do we stay alive forever?
Well, we had a good old, you know,
we got to get to Christmas. We can't get
in this whole tangent, but we
were delighted to discover that Griffin Newman
was a man on the ground for
a historical event, which was the
final Kiss concert at
which it would be determined how
will Kiss move forward
post their actually
being there at the concerts
and how headlines described
it was Kiss announces a hologram
Kiss that will take kind of
like what ABBA's been doing
and how Griffin described
it actually playing out was
the band left and then
a movie started playing with CGI
Kiss and there was no explanation of what
it was and the audience was confused
and Kiss's
decades long touring
career ended on a note of absolute
confusion.
I mean, it's so much more clear with a press release
and wait, he said also
that then they put it then like boom
put up a big QR code. So
Kiss's touring career ended with
a QR code and then you scan the QR code and
it says look check back in one hour
just enough time
to be inconvenient for like
you forget or it takes you a while
to get home or whatever. Yeah.
And then that tells you, okay
it's gonna be like a hologram and ILM
made a new Kiss. So, okay, so it's
like they're young again. Well
not exactly because they aren't bringing back the
two older original members.
No, no, yeah. It's the two new ones
as holograms. They're out. Those guys
are, I forget which ones have been out. Chris
Peter and Chris and Ace
Fraley. Dead Dust. Not even in hologram form
can they ever return. Anyway
basically this sounds to me like
a bit of a clusterfuck
but of course, but I'm also a fan
of clusterfucks. I never saw
flesh and blood Kiss
but maybe I'm more likely to see
confusing hologram Kiss. Did you know Kiss? Yeah.
Yeah. It very much seemed like the
response to it was like Moe
at the Bachelor auction on The Simpsons
when he stretched across stage and the whole
audience looked so
mad at him. And he just keeps walking.
Yeah. He doesn't bother to stop and
get bids. Yeah, a little bit. Yeah. I think
so. Anyway, so that exists as
that's an option. I think people have been very
moved by the ABBA version Kiss. I think people
have been confused by.
Yeah. Buffett.
I don't know. Is the key, are they gonna have
to, are they gonna have
to get Jimmy's friend, Frank Marshall,
to use some of the
de-aging technology
deployed on the
film that I have not
I haven't even made it
past the first half hour in two
sittings, the film
Nina Jones and the Tile of Destiny. Oh, I know.
I haven't tried yet. Oh, boy. Yeah,
I gotta try. Anyway, are we
gonna have to do that to Jimmy maybe? They got
the tech for Erason. Yeah.
I think that's probably
gonna happen. You know what? Frank maybe
goes out with them for a year
because Frank plays the guitar. You know what?
That actually. Oh, wait a minute.
That's interesting how I apologize
that you said Alan and there was some hemming and
hawing. And now you say Frank
Marshall becomes the new Jimmy.
I think that's the better one.
Yeah. But physically the
type. I
if Alan's in town, he can come out and do
his song and wave. That's how
you do it. Yeah, he's in the family. Yeah.
But, ooh,
all right. You got me. Yeah.
And this is me, somebody who's been
confounded
by Frank Marshall
and Buffett related information. Now that
I get it, I would absolutely go to
that concert.
I think everybody in Club 3 would.
Maybe even Main Feed.
Yeah.
Now, it is sad the way
things played out with Jimmy because
at the time of his death, he was due
to release his 32nd studio album,
Equal Strain on All Parts.
That's right. Buffett got the idea
for the album title from his grandfather's
description of a nap.
But did
that come out or is it going to?
The full album? I believe the full album is out.
Yeah, I think I listened to it. Yeah. Great.
That's got my like gummy
kicked in. The whole album or just
the first step? I think so.
So you didn't scrub through. So this one
you didn't just do the first half and then stop.
Look, I realized that I finished the
Olivia Rodrigo album, but I
set in on a thing that's not coming out yet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. In S.O.P. you didn't get, but you got
great cheers in person for
it. That's true. So yeah,
Club 3, I will let Club 3 know
I listened to the whole thing. Wow.
Wow. It's good. It's good.
There's some good stuff on the second half. I believe when Prist
for what you liked, you said
Track 10. Yeah, I couldn't
remember the name of it. The song is called
Pretty as I'm Pretty. I do remember that now.
Yeah, this
is all out. This has that Paul McCartney
song My Gummy Just Kicked In
where he plays bass on it.
Oh, relatable.
Relatable, didn't he? Bubbles up.
I like the song Bubbles Up better than My
Gummy Just Kicked In, I will say that.
Like My Dog has like a little
music video that just came out.
Paul is on
God, we've got to get to
Paul is on that song and then he's
also on a Rolling Stones
Hackney Diamonds song,
neither of which, if you listen,
you go, okay,
both of them. I'm like, I don't know.
It's like him chomping the carrots on
the Beach Boys vegetables. Right.
You wouldn't know unless you read it. Yeah.
So I was like, I don't know, maybe they had him
for an hour. I don't know. But yes,
Jimmy finished the album or got
finished his a lot of his stuff before
he passed away. And that's his, yeah,
final album unless they do some.
So what's the last song in the album?
What then serves as his final statement
to our world? Moe's Ambique,
Him and Emmylou Harris.
So that's not so bad.
Country royalty.
But I wonder if he has a full vault like Prince
or something of many, many unreleased albums.
I'm not sure. I didn't know
that Jimmy was on this Willie Nelson
live song
called Roll Me Up
and Smoke Me When I Die.
Yeah, he did that with Snoop Dogg at the Hollywood Bowl.
Oh, cool. Yeah, it was fun.
I saw a video of it. I wasn't there.
Yeah, that's good. Oh, and he also
was on a cover from the same live album
of On the Road Again.
OK. Damn. I bet that's
interesting as hell.
A lot of interesting takes
on that little ditty.
OK, so, oh, you know
what, I didn't do the official credit for who
suggested this. This is just simply from
Matt. In memoriam of
Jimmy Buffett, you should do an episode
of his Christmas album, Christmas Island.
Plus, his birthday is on Christmas Day.
So there's that. Very popular
suggestion.
So this one's for you,
Matt, and we can dive in here.
I'm going to
say this about going forward.
First of all, I don't want to speak ill
of the dead. Of course. Secondly,
and this isn't really speaking ill,
as with many Christmas
albums, you get a lot of
covers. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. We got a lot of covers
here. And the
covers, by and large, correct
me if I'm wrong, and
play ones that are interesting
and notable. I feel like some of the covers
are a little less notable
and essential
than original Christmas
songs.
Yeah, you were saying like
the definitive versions of some of these
classic Christmas songs.
I just think, you know, Christmas albums
have a lot of padding.
And I shouldn't
maybe, for my
own self-care,
maybe I shouldn't be advocating for a longer
episode. But I would, I'm
going to vote for a little
bit. We don't have to talk about all of
them, because some of them just kind of are covers.
But I would like to pull into this,
and you probably
want to do this as well, some discussion of his
second Christmas album, Tis the
Sea Sun. Tis the Sea Sun, which
has a couple songs I really do like.
Yes. Okay. Right. So let's... And he
looks like he's jacked on the cover.
Like the Photoshop of him,
which I think, and maybe that's insulting.
What is it when you're standing
on it, is it like wakeboarding?
What's the name of that? Yeah, that's a good question.
Yeah, it's like standing on a board.
No paddle boarding? Okay.
And he's got like a dog photoshopped on it with him,
I think. Yeah. Wait,
wakeboarding, I guess, is if you're stiff,
you're like pulled, you're still being pulled.
But if you're being towed, that's wakeboarding.
So yeah, paddle boarding might be right.
But so,
anyway, with
that, I don't
want to dictate how you do it. This is
your rodeo, Mike, and
whatever you want to do.
Yeah, so
let me pull up some of the credits
here. I learned just also just
looking around that Jingle Bells
was written by a guy named James Lord Pierpont,
who was an American songwriter,
arranger, organist, and a confederate soldier.
Well, I don't like that, but
I like that name, Pierpont.
Yeah. It's one of my favorite spots
to hang all day with a
fisher pole. I feel like he could have used that
somewhere.
Like, owed to James Pierpont.
Pierpont. And then it was like about,
like, it was really just about singing, like,
like a nickname for him,
Jimmy James. They call
me James Pierpont.
I'm always putting my feet in the water.
So,
so, yeah.
Confederates, wow.
Jingle Bells canceled? I'll say this.
I canceled it. Yeah, Jingle Bells is canceled now.
A good collection.
These are like the Christmas
Carols, by and large, that I like.
The ones on this album? Yeah, on the album.
I especially like
I'll Be Home for Christmas, of course,
originally written during World
War II. Sure.
It was kind of a very sad
song of soldiers pining to be home.
Irving Berlin, is that right?
Bing Crosby did the
big cover. Oh, sorry, Irving Berlin is
White Christmas, I'm sorry.
So, yeah,
so, there's
stuff on here that I do really like
and then there's stuff on here that I think is
less good. None of who you just said
wrote I'll Be Home for Christmas.
No, no. Bing. No, no, I'm wrong.
I'll Be Home for Christmas was, of course, written by
Buck Ram.
Yes, yes. No, White, I'm
thinking of White Christmas, that's Irving Berlin. I'll Be Home
for Christmas, Bing Crosby
was
in the top ten on the charts
with it and then it shows up
in Meet Me in St. Louis,
Judy Garland sings it. Well, I do
know that White
Christmas stuff because, of course, I
worked and did tech for a Katherine
Crosby, Bing Crosby's Widows
show, which I brought up here and
there before. So that was the, I should
remember that. It's embarrassing that I
attributed that. Audience, raise your hand
if you've ever heard of Katherine Crosby
before Mike Carlson
bringing that name up.
What was your awareness of Katherine
Crosby? His second wife.
Look, the mother of
Mary, who was on Dallas,
you know that.
I don't reference, but I know I
know other Dallas people. She shot
JR. That's who shot JR?
Okay. Yeah, how about it?
I have her phone number.
So where I grew up in Woodland Hills,
sometimes I'd see Charlene Tilden
at the mall. Well. How about
that? This is for the Club 3 heads, really.
An audience of one person
half-gassed
out of all of the thousands of listeners.
Yeah, Mike.
He's in this room. He also has a
microphone.
So I will say
Mella Kalikimaka is maybe
the perfect Christmas song for Jimmy
to do. And that, I think, you
could say that sort of should
be in your rotation of essential
Christmas song versions or whatever you want
to call it. I guess that's why it
appears on both albums.
Both albums because
it's the perfect song for him
to do because like very
island flavored. For people on the internet
like, oh my god, Mella Kalikimaka
too. It's bad. Score
guys.
They're very excited
about him doing two
two different recorded versions.
I'm not sure what was wrong with the first one
that he needed to re-record it.
He added like a ukulele
guy. Ukulele star.
Is it Jake Shima
Bunkura? Shima Bukura.
Shima Bukura, sorry. Yes.
So he is doing like kind of a duet
there. So I guess that's why you're doing it.
Like Willie obviously recorded, Willie
Nelson recorded a million on the road again
I'm sure with many different people.
Like I am kind of fascinated by that
because I was like, why would you, like Frank
Snatchard doing duets, the
Bono song and with Jimmy
Buffett as well. Like going
in there and like re-recording your songs feels
like such a slog to me.
No way. Writing new
ones. That's the slog. Let's do
it again. Mella Kalikimaka.
And you have to write this one.
So yeah.
So like Christmas Island I think is a fun
song. His Jingle Bells is
not my favorite version
of Jingle Bells. Which I think
a lot of this is going to devolve into
sort of a discussion of what you like.
Like I liked as a kid.
Because like I liked Jingle Bell
fine but I loved Jingle Bell Rock.
That was my preferred.
I always would lump those two together
and be like, yeah Jingle Bells is fine.
I can sing it. But Jingle Bell Rock
to me was like, that's really fun.
This is a fun song. Rock and roll.
Rock and roll, yeah. You know I was a little kid
who loved rock and roll. Rock and roll
kid. It's like when the music teacher
would get a bunch of sheet music
Beatles songs.
Like a little rock and roll.
Not just you know. Oh like the teacher would show
oh you know what I know new stuff.
You know too. Which is like when our music class
in 1995.
Yeah in 1995. Hey we're singing
Blackbird.
We're not just singing
like American songbook songs or
what we'd sing. We had
like in second or third grade we sang
Hero by Mariah Carey in class.
Which was a very new song.
Or maybe later.
Maybe fourth grade. Let me do a sir.
Cause I am not alone in that.
I think one of Jane's school
choir sang this. And I
definitely encountered other people who
sang this. Did you
ever in a music class sing Ease On
Down the Road from The Wiz?
No. No. But I was really
in a lot of music classes. Okay.
Did you? Yeah. You did.
The whole chorus of White
Cat's singing Ease On Down the Road.
Yeah. How about it?
Yeah. Yeah. That's interesting.
He has a
song. So he wrote the song A Sailor's Christmas.
Which is kind of
melancholy sort of in the same
I feel like vein as a son
of a sailor. Son of a son.
Son of a sailor. Yeah. This is that mode
that he has of just kind of like
wistful. Contemplative.
Yeah. And I'm like snooze.
You don't like those. Yeah. Really?
I want to hear lists of
drinks and
lyrics about conch shells. Yeah.
I mean I like the party stuff I think better too.
But I like some of the stuff. I was
in fact disappointed by
because you hear the album title Christmas
Island. Oh cool.
Is it like him imagine? Is it like
Scatman's World
where he's imagining a whole island
that is decked out
Christmas and then you remember oh no there's just that kind of
boring song on Christmas
Island. So I felt disappointed
by that. That he's not like
architecting a world
where like a volcano shoots egg
nog. He gets. And palm
trees have coconuts that are
candied peppermint striped and when you open
them up they're full of egg nog.
Yeah. No that I think he should
have made an album more along those lines.
But he does in Sailor's Christmas he mentioned
like he mentions the realm of King
Neptune which I like.
You get little treats. Okay.
But it's not a big treat meal. It's not a big
like Christmas celebration of
full nonsense. He has a song
on the. But it's not like is that
like. But is
is that good old Santa
no it's King Neptune.
Yeah no. He confuses him because they both have white beards.
No he doesn't yeah. No that
would be more fun like yeah
Santa. Santa fought King Neptune.
They
have their hands around each other's necks.
The ownership of Christmas.
Santa got stabbed in the back
with a trident.
But his healing
his North Pole powers brought
him back. Santa's
fat came in handy.
Watch out Lord Darkin
on Zero Two.
Yeah no it's not
if only we could have produced an album for him.
This is my wish.
One song that gets a little close.
We'll get there. Yes yeah yeah yeah.
But yes it is sort of just like a sad
like another like sad Christmas
song about like somebody being away
from home and what it
is like being on the ocean
being on the water. It's just a sad
time. Well it paints a picture of like
imagine if it was Christmas. A time
when you're supposed to be with the ones you love
and instead you're just out in the
middle of an ocean and you've got
stockings in your tiny
boat and Christmas lights in your tiny
boat and you're wearing
a Santa hat and a Christmas shirt
but you're all alone.
That's kind of the picture it
draws up which is the
album cover of Christmas Island.
But that's not lonely at all. He's happy as hell.
I love it.
I gotta do Christmas solo more often.
Give everybody one
extra day to come up with two
extra presents for me. Christmas
and birthday separate. It really ruins
sort of the sadness of the
sea life. You see how happy
he is being in the tiniest boat you can
imagine celebrating Christmas
alone.
I wish the boat was smaller.
Well you know what I was saying
before I saw the album cover
I was just thinking of the
Corona commercial that is
aired for 30 years.
Where someone is
whistling Oh Christmas tree, Oh Christmas tree
and they walk out of a little shack
and they flick on the
Christmas lights on the palm tree.
That's one of those perennials
that's just in there forever along with
he does exist
I do exist.
And Folger's
incest commercial.
I just
read an article about that.
I think I read the same.
There was an oral history where the
brother and sister are a little too
familiar.
I think they did pull that though.
They should air it.
It might have gotten pulled eventually.
It aired for a while.
And the Hershey kisses
that ring like bells. That one's never going
away. I like that one.
They should do more of that.
But you know what they should do is not
have them be Christmas and just be commercials Jason
and I were in.
They should just have those run forever.
Christmas is a great time to remember what
the best insurance on the market is
and what the best
streamer is.
Streaming packages is.
They end up in little Christmas presents
called healthcare for all the
actors. Wendy's always has a
chicken sandwich. Come on.
And Hulu
is always a great deal.
I don't know what
they cut by now and I don't know who owns
them at this point. But no matter what
they're always celebrating the Hulu
days. And before that Hulu
we and happy Hulu days.
So OK. I mean this. OK.
I want to play a little
bit and this is I'm wondering how
where Scott falls on this.
If he likes this or not because
I actually hadn't I've listened to his album
but I really didn't even clock this
for like last year when I listened to this
or whatever or I wasn't just not paying attention
because he does a version of up on the housetop
that is a very
in character
like song. OK. Did you listen to this at all?
I did. Wait I'm trying to replace
well I'll just play it. I'll play it. I think it struck me
as being kind of a genre in a way.
Yes absolutely and it's a little bit
out of his. It makes sense.
Christmas is for sure.
Share that
way with me. Don't cut me off man.
That's cool dude.
So he's doing like a
surfer guy.
See my head lips.
Little dick tail. Yeah.
But I'm also wondering if he's doing a little beach
boys.
You know what it struck me
as actually is more it's kind of like the cars.
Little like
a little new wave. Yeah.
He also sounds like Tom Petty
though. Yeah.
I'm wondering what he was going for.
This is obviously a surf rock
song.
Surfer
stoner music.
Like Tom Petty man.
But it sounds like he could
be trying to do a beach boys
ish voice but I'm not sure.
It's a different voice for sure.
Yeah it's not his normal.
It's a take.
Does this have a bunch of he like prattles
on and on at the end of this.
This stoner guy voice.
Can we hear some of that. Yeah at the end.
Yeah. It should be
hold on it'll be a little imprecise.
I kind of like this.
This is more in the style music
I guess. Yeah. Besides maybe the
character.
Sounds like 90's Costello.
Yeah.
This is five songs in by the way on the track list.
Nourley.
OK.
So he's got yes.
He's doing his SNL audition reel.
Yeah. So I was like oh yeah I guess
and then probably bigger Buffet heads
will like find something that where he does
more of a character or something.
But I was like OK that's.
Bigger Buffet heads. Yes.
There are there exist.
They exist. I don't know as much about him
as I do pre Stephen Page leaving
Bearnic and Ladies.
Where I have like a lot of more
more B sides.
I know a little more history from the band.
I think it's though that it's possible that you know the most
about Jimmy Buffett of anyone below
fifty five years old.
There's a chance that's
possible.
So yeah. So so he had done
yeah the first Christmas Island Jingle Bells
Sailor's Christmas. Then he does Happy Christmas
which is
John Lennon War is Over.
If you want it. I feel like
that's an OK version of it.
I feel like you had that on the background.
You might go like oh yeah that's that's fine.
Do I want it on for five minutes
thirty five seconds.
I'll say I don't know.
I think it was because I worked in the container store
for a few years and they had
like this Christmas loop
that would play a lot and they would play that
John Lennon song all the time.
And I do like it but I think I heard
it too much in the same way
that I heard for like for the longest
time by Billy Joel during regular
regular seasons.
And I'm just like I don't want to hear this song
ever again maybe. Sure.
But it's like a fine song.
I still like I want like Wonderful Christmas
Time better. I don't we don't have to put John
and Paul against each other but
Christmas time I think is on
the other Jimmy Buffett
are correct.
This by the way
Christmas Island comes out in nineteen ninety six.
Yes. And then he
doesn't do the other one for like ten years.
Yeah it's a fair relatively
recent. Yeah. Twenty sixteen.
Oh yeah. Twenty
years. We went twenty years.
How did the world manage without more. But I do
think maybe it's part of it's like you're taking
a shot and can you add
one of your songs to
the list. To the like primaries.
Yeah. Always played.
It's tough. It's tough to penetrate.
You can certainly make Christmas music
but how do you. Right. Become
and the dream obviously is to become
Mariah Carey. Right.
But I don't think anybody's getting in there
as big as Mariah ever again.
In terms of like that song is
such a pillar it feels like it
it's up there with the ones from the
30s. Feels like it was written by James Pierpont.
It feels that classic at this point.
The new James Pierpont
Mariah Carey.
Right. What are the other
like last Christmas.
Yeah. Yeah. Christmas wrapping.
It's primary now. Yeah. I feel like
it's primary.
Fairy tale of New York
in some circles. Sure.
Yeah. It's not
primary but I may have spoken
before about the new edition Christmas
EP. This is my favorite Christmas music.
Six songs not all original
but mostly original and then the covers are
not that famous of covers.
They aren't doing any winter wonderland
sleigh ride. These are
they're all like I think it's some
of the best new edition songs
regardless of the Christmas
this is the best. Look check this one out
on Spotify. Highly recommend.
That's cool. Should be primary.
Can I so can I just
confirm for Christmas Island
the original Jimmy's songs
are Christmas Island
and the Sailor's Christmas. Is that
it? No.
There's one more. Oh. Ho ho ho
in a bottle of rum. Ho ho ho
in a bottle of rum. Why don't we talk about a ho ho ho
in a bottle of rum. Yeah you want to play a little of it here?
This to me seems like the closest
thing to satisfying
what you want silly
Jimmy Christmas to be. Right right right right.
Good. Oh Merry Christmas Alabama
I think he has the credit on to him.
Yes he does yes.
This is some nice
Mario Kart
Peach level whistles.
Original Mario Kart.
Beep beep boo boo beep beep boo boo.
Santa's
dressed out as the holiday
season draws near.
He's been doing
the same job now going on
two thousand years.
He started right after
Christ is what he's saying.
Right. And chimney
scars cover his buns.
Christ is born
in year two Santa starts his
workshop. Is that right?
The Christmas bus is more work than fun.
Aww.
He needs a vacation from bad
decorations and
snow. Santa does?
Even Santa? Yeah.
Oh December 26
he's going to Cali town.
Beaches and palm trees
appear night and day in his
dreams. He's going to have to
buy a new wardrobe for that.
This is the funniest line.
A break from his wife.
The elves and that damn reindeer team.
That damn reindeer.
He doesn't like his wife. He hates the reindeer.
Santa's run off to the Caribbean.
I guess he's on his own getting to the Caribbean.
Reindeer not helping him.
Ho ho ho and a bottle
of rum. I mean this is great.
This is really good. I like
these like images.
Santa and the old timey bathing suit
are like the tank top and swim
trunks. Yeah. I think that's
fun when Santa gets cut loose a little.
Santa in shorts. You're not
sold because of the lyrics.
Oh yeah.
I got some trouble coming up.
Yeah here we go.
Just for the weekend
he'd like to be Peter Pan.
Excuse me? Yeah that's a weird line.
Get out of his long johns
and dance with the sword.
Dance with the sword in the sand.
Dance with the sword in the sand like Peter Pan.
Peter Pan?
Oh I'm like pirates. Oh yeah I guess.
Yeah he's always singing about pirates.
Peter Pan has a place in Buffett type
imagery. Yeah.
Is that what all the
parrots think they're doing is being
little like Peter Pans?
Like pirates? Like never growing up.
Is that the idea?
I don't know. I don't think
so. I think
they're just like being
like maybe even I guess pirate
just in general is a thing because he
mentions pirates. I'm confused by
this. Santa wants to be Peter
Pan. Santa a two thousand year
old at least man by the premise
of the song
wants to he's sick of his
work and he wants he doesn't
want to grow up he wants to be a little kid
again. But Santa's day
to day is like drinking hot chocolate
and marshmallows and
like no this toy
should be this toy should be able to flip
around this this toy should make
a little poop this dolly.
Like he's still he's kind of pretty
I know he's got a lot of work
to do but he's got as much of like an
adolescent adulthood as anybody.
Why does he need to be like Peter Pan?
Is there a common yeah like
okay because because now
Santa especially in the last couple decades
obviously with manufacturing happening
with toys is the
idea is Santa day to day
working in the toy shop
with the elves or is
that just a Christmas season thing
or does he work all year
like doing all his Christmas
business for the one night?
It's actually gotten easier they
just want Roblox gift cards.
But is he
purchasing Roblox or are the elves making
the Roblox gift cards?
I had this exact question in
while watching the film Santa Claus
2 which I'd never seen
I was like okay so
they make all of these kind of old style
like you know dollies and
the rocking horses
but then if a kid wants a Nintendo
Switch did they just get
that from Nintendo or do Santa
and elves have to because it's a
Christmas present did they have to
make their own version of a Nintendo
Switch? Right. It's a great
question and one that I had as a child
I believe too because
all the old time
Santa stuff is based on old school
toys that feel much more
He started again in Christ's time
so he began
talk about adapting as a business
man he started in a pre
electronic time
there was an electricity even
when Santa began so now
he's got to like figure out
microchips and keep up with imagine
being Santa and now I got to make video games
now I got to go from 8 bit
to 16 bit and then every
generational jump after that
Is he developing? Yeah
I think there needs to be
kind of a
revision of the Santa
lore maybe
because kids are going to
be confused our kids are going to be confused I think
when they fully grasp this
Your alerts
Deal vibes
When's he edited the grocery list?
You get a ding for that
I have a shared
list too sometimes I get updates
Yeah I guess I do get lists
More hot cocoa
More nog
So yeah so
I guess in this Jimmy version he's
talking about Santa's day to day I assume
is very stressful and he's
shouting at elves
shouting at Mrs Claus
I cannot wait I cannot
wait to be in the Caribbean
I want to go and be
play Peter Pan in the sand
I want to be a little boy forever
Mrs Claus Always stop me you tell me
that wanting to be like a little boy
is a creepy thing
and for the last time no I don't
want kids I don't want
that type of reliving my
childhood I want to be the Peter
Pan
What do you mean the elves
They're like my lost boys
I hate them they're no fun at all
The only thing worse than them
is that damn reindeer team
You better believe I'm getting on a
plane to the Caribbean with one
seat they're not invited
you're not invited
When we're flying over the Pacific sometimes I just wish
the magic would wear off
and we all plunge into the water
To an ocean
brave at least for a
minute when I'm splashing around
I'll be happy I can climb under
Dasher's corpse and float
to safety
There's none of those cursed
Christmas lights in the black unforgiving
Pacific
No red no green
Just brutal
waves crashing
I don't think Jimmy's thinking maybe fully about
what he's painting picture he's painting
of a man difficult Santa
this almost Scrooge like Santa
The jolliest man supposedly that loves
bringing cheer to children
That's the character he's got to play
Johnny Carson was very dark
behind closed, you know Dark Side
All the great public figures do
Santa of course among them
No exception Santa
But yeah you're right that gets the closest
to like fun nonsense
because you want that
Is the last song
besides a hidden track
A Visit from St. Nicholas
Is the song Merry Christmas
Alabama parentheses
Never far from whom is that
sad too
Or is that more jaunty
Yeah it's kind of sad I mean it feels
It feels sad I guess if we want to
analyze the lyrics
But it's definitely not one of his
party songs
Not like Merry Christmas Alabama
Let's have enchiladas
Which could be another
song if he wanted to make another
Christmas album posthumously
Maybe that's part of the living forever
It's like just use AI
With his voice and then
Have people write new songs
And have the AI sing it
Maybe this is a good time to
Say again the covers
Are fine but I don't know
I don't want to hear him doing the sad John Lennon
I want like
I do want the party silly
Jimmy Christmas
And I took the liberty
Of in four minutes
Time writing
What I desire
And this I also though tried to
Keep it in like where it's not that
Silly this to me feels like plausibly
Something that he would have
Written
If he like just maybe put a little
More in the realm of the bottle
Of rum so let me
This is just a chorus
And I don't have musical backing
Or anything but just you know imagine some
Steel drum and some acoustic
With this okay
Alright
Leave Santa a
Margarita
Cause milk is such a bore
Getting past a big dairy
Glass sounds like such a chore
Why not give him
A salted rim with a splash of
Triple sec but Santa
Don't over do it
Or you'll get in a sleigh wreck
Hey Santa I'm Margarita
And everybody comes in you know
Just repeat it or do more I don't know
Loosely the same
Yeah I think if you pitched
It to him in one of these songwriting sessions
You bet great got it
You turn this way and he turns back
And he's recorded the whole song already
I did it
It's in stores already actually
Getting back on the battle board
Had to tweak the you'll be in a wreck
Live we can't talk about drunk driving
So I just changed to you're a wreck
Good point Jason good note
He says but don't over do it
He says it's warning
It's kind of a drunk driving warning
But also Jimmy I would leave you know
You know your own rules
But also Parrotheads when you get in those cars on the way home
My liability is gone
When I leave the stage my liability
Is no longer valid
Rod Sherr encourage to the
Then you won't have your own tail
To gate on but
Bring a blanket
Yeah there you go
Jason your
Question about Merry Christmas Alabama
Yes he says like Merry Christmas
To my saints and guardian angels
Who protect me as I roam
All the faces in the places that we're home
It's like that's not
It's a little yeah
Not the most fun thing
Do you picture a better
Merry Christmas Alabama
Like well let me ask you this Jason
You I think do really like
The sad Buffet you like the
I like it okay I like he went to Paris
Yeah
Yeah I don't know
Do I wish it was like
Sweet home Alabama
But then it was like
Merry Christmas
Sweet home Alabama
Merry Christmas Alabama
Alabama
I like that you worked that out
Yeah I was trying to figure out if the math worked
Yeah yeah so you do actually
Like the party Buffet better
You do like party Buffet better
I think party Buffet is
Preferable for most people
Like run can we run
Rudolph? Yes of course
That's a pretty jaunty song
No we're going back
We've been bopping around
We've been bopping
Oh boy alright nevermind
Yeah no it's uh
We have to hear this
You know you're the mastermind
Run run
Rudolph Vixen can't be
Far behind
That's what I thought too
It's a little
More Ryan Censor
I wonder if you want to hear the
Why is he so insistent on the
The Ryan Censor
Surely has done many versions of Run Run
This is absolutely
He might be doing it right now
On the other side of town
Yeah that's possible
We gotta get to him
He's in the Capitol Records building
You guys ever trick me into like
We're going to Knott's Merry Farm
Okay great I'll drive
Oh well thank you I'd love a break for a drive
Guess what wrong we're going to
Ryan Censor fuck you
I'll crawl
I'll force that door open and fly out
Sorry Scott it's time for you to get
In the mood
Da da da da da da da da
I still don't know if that's something they would play
Or do play
Look at setlist.fm
Jason find the last
Brian Censor show and see what the
Setlist he did was cause I would like to know
Is he with the orchestra now? I know he's
You know he's gotta be cooking
That's a good idea and while Jason does that maybe we can move on
To Tis the Sea Sun
Tis the Sea Sun I'm comfortable with that
Yes yes
Oh wait actually you know what I will go
Will you play I forgot the hidden track
Is him doing Tis the Night Before Christmas
Can you just go to around
I miss these hidden tracks
The fun thing about CDs
You might actually get tricked
Like it keeps playing and then oh what's this
What's this my wondering eyes
Should appear
So you get to hear him do this
But go to around 617
Jimmy convinced that this is a
This is a one take
Oh I think I know what you're talking about
And he whistled and shouted
And called them by name
Now Dasher now Dancer now Prancer and Vixen
On Comet on Cupid
On Donner and Blitzen
To the top of the porch to the top of the wall
Now dash away dash away
Dash away all
As dry leaves have before of the water
When they meet
But again he was already
I just do what sorry and he's already out on the pedal
I'm done
I finished it
Should we get Jimmy back for one
I'm sorry I looked out the window and he is
Riding on a dolphin
He's already half a mile away
I'm surfing on two turtles
On my feet
I'm water skiing with two turtles
Don't worry they're smiling they're happy
I'm doing it I asked them
They're my best friends
Cheeseburger and paradise
So that's the
That's Jimmy's first Christmas album
And 21st studio album all told
Now we move to the 29th
Studio album
Tis the Zee Sun
20 years later he had more Christmas to do
More Melickaliki Maka to do
And he's on a wakeboard paddle board
He's ripped
His muscles look so big
His arms look huge
He's wearing a Santa
Onesie kind of a look
It's a Santa shirt with short sleeves
Well you know what it's a little bit like
This would be maybe all the way sleeveless
But it's getting close to Santa with muscles
It is close to Santa with muscles
Kogan style
I guess maybe I like this in general
For some reason
I think I like
Buff Santas
Not in an attracted to way
In a I think it's cute way
I think for all the things I won't put on the cute list
I think buff Santas are cute
It's something adorable
I like buff Santas
I don't know that I would even consider them cute
I think it's such a large swath of Santas
That I don't know that I could give it a full blanket cute
I'll just Google
Buff Santa stuff
Buff
Well you know it's like
I am looking at some of the funniest pictures
I've ever seen
Look at this
I know translate to the listener
This is a really angry
Probably AI Santa who's really ripped
Who's going like
He's so upset
He looks upset like he just ate
Like three meat parts
And then there's a weird
Mangled
Tim Burton candy cane
In front of him that he looks disgusted by
What is this picture?
This is a t-shirt I can buy on
Redbubble
That's interesting
It is AI
Look up the movie Santa's Slay
Which I believe is the name of a
Movie starring pro wrestler
Goldberg
Where he's like an evil Santa but he's Jack Santa
I like this but I don't think it's cute
Because he's mad
But this seems like fun
This is from 2005
Santa's Slay
These are some very funny prosthetics and beards
So yeah I'm pro Buff Santa
Maybe that's an episode for next year
Buff Santa next year
Let's put a pin in that
So that's
A pretty big pin
To get through those muscles
Santa's Slay
Is he flanked
Sidekick wise by
SCTV's Dave Thomas
That's who I think I'm looking at in this picture
Maybe that's right
I have actually seen a lot of this
But maybe in 2006
So I can't remember
I'm sorry on the poster
Brett Ratner presents
He didn't direct it but he
Produced it
Or just like brought it
Somewhere
Boy we never stop finding out about crap
Robert Culp
Many time
Columbo villain
Who's Saul
Rubenek
Shit shit he's a
What is he in? I know this guy
Let me keep going Chris Catan
And our leader
This strike year Fran Drescher
Appears in this film
Saul Rubenek
You've seen him he's in a bunch of stuff
And now it just went back to Yo Ho Ho
And a bottle of rum for some reason on my computer
While I was looking him up
He's in
A lot of things and I can't think of a single one
He's Kivas Faho
Kivas Faho on Star Trek Next Gen
Well that's true
Kivas Faho
You're looking at a picture of him right?
Yeah so you don't recognize him?
No automatically no
Oh I probably know him as Detective Saul
I know him as Detective Saul Panzer
In the Golden Spiders and Nero Wolf mystery
That's it
He's
Yeah he's in Buster's Scrugs
I forget where
He's just in a lot of stuff
Well
I like his name
Speaking of
While we're looking up things
Did you ever figure out the set list
Or we lost that thread?
Well yeah it's complicated
Because most of his
Recent set lists in the last few months
Have been him performing with
A show called
Brian Setzer's Rockabilly Riot
And those are mostly
Straight Gats
That's covers
Some Hoogie Carmichael in his orchestra covers
This sounds the same
This sounds no different
Than what it usually is
Well I'm saying it's not really orchestra
It's not really the big band
He's not doing in the mood is what you're saying
No he's doing Rock This Town
He's doing Fishnet Stockings
The Straight Gats song
So glad I don't know more
Straight Gats songs
Really thankful this holiday season
That's what I'm thankful for
Rockabilly Riot
George on my mind
That's another Hoogie Carmichael
Oh yeah I see that now
On the road again
Okay
Tis the Sea Sun
Here's what I'll say off the bat
I think I like Tis the
Season better than Christmas Island
I think I might too
I don't know what it is about it
But I think there's more
I think there's more things on here
Especially there's an original song I really like
Called Santa Stole Thanksgiving
I think that's the big ticket item
Which is the big yes I think that's the best of all of these
Of all these songs
And it is real fun
But let's give a little wonderful
Wonderful Christmas time I've realized is controversial
And I'm just blown away
Some people do not, Lindsay does not like
Wonderful Christmas time
Lindsay's an anti yeah
I have good friends who are anti
And sometimes you will get to a list
Of the worst Christmas songs ever
And it's on there
Sometimes you'll see it at number one
The whole list I'm anticipating
But what's the big dog going to be
Excuse me
Get out of here with that
Maybe a minute too long
I guess so
I'm giving people a little bone here
It's really delightful
Synths he's having a lot of fun noodling with those
Synths and you take the synths
And you take them away and you replace them with steel drums
And I am less of a fan
It is not
My favorite version of
Wonderful Christmas time
Getting ready for you to do like a
And I think it's pretty good
Just
I mean there's a little synth
That is a little unusual for Jimmy
I'm a synth snob I don't know
I understand but I'm just saying for him
That is a noise that is not on a lot of Jimmy songs
So I'm giving them some credit for at least
Retaining some magic
Give me a big
5% of the magic whatever
But they've slowed it down
Which I would not necessarily have done
That might not be my
I'm a big synth guy
I'm not a big organ guy
That's boring
And that's enough
Synths he's having
A wonderful
Christmas time
Okay
It's okay
I'm not going to listen to that over
Again we were sort of talking before about
Could it go in the
Could it be one of the versions you listen to
And I don't think that would put that in there
He does Jingle Bell Rock
Which of course I talked about this
I do the original Jingle Bells
He does Jingle Bell Rock on here
My favorite
Now this is pretty just straight ahead
That's the full regular
That's how you do it you bring the Jingle Bells in there
Jingle Bell Jingle Bell
Jingle Bell Rock
That's it
Whoever oh who's singing it doesn't even matter
That's just a timeless song
I love my preferred version
My preferred version is Hall & Oates
With the music video where G.E. Smith
Is grandma
The family comes over
I think it's a video they're mortified by
Because it's very hammy
Shot in a day quick
But then you think it's an old granny
But then
She rips off for
Shawl and there's a guitar underneath
Just in time to play the solo
Check it out if you're a G. Smith fan
Which again this is club 3
So I assume most people
Are specific to this
Saturday Night Live band
Okay so he does
All I Want for Christmas is My Two Front Teeth
A song I've never
Liked
Jason what do you think?
It wasn't even my favorite when I was in the
Business of losing teeth
The business
It is a business
A few years
You're like wiggling it
You're giving me like hard rolls
This is almost
Bite into this and it'll take it out
Bite into some Italian
That was kind of a Jimmy Line you pulled off the top of your head too there
What?
I didn't even like it when I was in the business
I didn't even like it
That was a good turn of freight
And then the next song
Is called
Driving the Pig
I'm baffled by this song
And this is a confusing one
Can we get some Driving the Pig
Yeah yeah here we go
Driving the Pig
Some familiar instruments
Hold on
This is sort of like the Billie Jean lead up
Where you really get into the rhythm of it
This is a genre song
Whatever you call this genre song
Christmas in the Caribbean
On the island named for snakes
Songlines took me to Culebra
For a perfect Yuletide break
I had gone there for the fishing
But when I stepped off of the plane
There was an airy celebration
I couldn't quite explain
I had gone there for the fishing
But when I stepped off of the plane
There was an airy celebration
I couldn't quite explain
Driving
Driving the pig tonight
It's a smoking revelation
And a pork pie ecstasy
Steering wheel is turning toward
These possibilities
Little Jesus stole my birthday
And my savings
I got you high
We got to a stagistics to sing
I like this
Come and join us for some ham
Can I stop it?
Can I read the lyrics?
Little Jesus stole our birthday
Christmas babies we got scammed
Does this mean himself?
He's mad at Jesus
Stealing his birthday
Jesus was there first
But the three kings were our saviors
Come and join us for some ham
And then pork pie ecstasy
Is driving the pig
Killing a pig and feasting on the pig
There's some articles
And I think a YouTube
Behind the scenes video
Where someone says what does this mean
I would think
The ham pig
Unless this is some sort of
Sick sacrifice he's talking about
But it seems like
That's what he's getting at
Sometimes he doesn't want to spell it out for you
He wants to leave some mystery
Some of these biblical figures can't have ham, right?
Oh, I guess that's true
Maybe that's a joke
Is that a part of it?
I mean, some of the magic of Jimmy's songwriting
Is that it's not always
Exactly clear what he's saying
Now maybe some again, bigger Buffetheads
Will say always, come on
He said what the meaning of this is
Oldtimemusic.com says
At its core, driving the pig
Celebrates the spirit of freedom
And living the life
On one's own terms
Oh
Okay
So, a lot of Jimmy's songs
Here's what I'll say
I like his voice better
On this album
I like his older voice
There's something like, I don't know if it's maybe the quality of the recording
Of Christmas Island
I don't know if this is more modern recording
But I like the quality of his voice more
It's a little mellower maybe
It's mellower, but it is a little deeper
And I like it, I think maybe that contributes to me
Liking this album better
Than Christmas Island
This one, I'm baffled by it
But I like the genre
I think some of the covers
Selections are good
And I think it's got a little more silliness
In fact, I'm going to advocate for
Skipping the next track, saving it
Because I think that's actually the real
Well that's the
I would say that's the money as far as if you're looking for complete
Jimmy Universe
Nonsense
Maybe that's a closer
Just the title
Gives that away
We get a Mack and Allie
Original
Which
This has some lyrics
It's on the leg
Christmas
Everything I wanted the most
No island or peninsula
Christmas
Another Christmas
So close
As you can put your finger on it
So far my wish is just
Didn't do
I didn't get for Christmas what I wanted
A little more time
With you
I want to fool around
Go to town in the devil
Meaning way
Yeah, Mike you should be out on
That too, this double entendre filth
Yeah, I mean look
It's so, I love his little like
Impish way about him
And his cheeky smiles
So I'll let him get away
There's nothing pervy
Go to town
So he's also, he means on a
On a pork pie
On a ham
That's what he means
Oh, I just by the way
Oh, I can't, yeah, keep moving
I just walked into something there
Really accidentally and I won't even acknowledge it
Past this line
Past this sentence, I got worried too
The word pie was said
Okay, I don't even know how to collect myself
So yeah, Mack
I like this song though, I'll say that
There's nothing
There's nothing that makes you go
When you hear this
What? I just, I did
Well, okay, you're right
Other than the lyric
Go to town in the double meaning way
But I mean it's not, it's fun I guess is really what I'm just trying to say
Well this is, if you're worried
About the state of the country bear jamboree
You can have this kind of
Songwriting and performing
To look forward to
That's it, oh, you know what
Also, if Frank Marshall's unavailable
This requires some help from the
Walt Disney company, but why not get one of those bears
Whichever one, whichever bear
Is the most like
Buffet, make a copy of it
And send that on the road
You replace Jimmy Buffet with a country bear
Which one? Wow
It's hard to name them even after we did that series
Henry is kind of the MC
And he has to wear a lot of hats
But isn't one of them more
One of them has more of like the
The island hat
And the kind of frayed guitar
Which one's that?
Are you talking about newly renamed
Romeo McGraw?
Well he's Elvis in the show
In the Japan show basically
You know what, well Henry's
More Buffet-esque
I'll stick with Henry for now and it's up to them
If they want the raccoon to
Burst out of the hat or not
I heard that they're not
They're not going to be new robots, they're going to be the same robots
I think I was saying
That's good, I don't want
Yeah, no I think that is good, ultimately
I think they were going to
They would just not be the same
You know he's kind of like Jimmy, he's the one in the
Five Bear Rugs with the little hat and the banjo
He's kind of jolly
Like Jimmy
Yeah, what about Shaker?
Shaker maybe?
They're all good choices
Let's be honest, country bear wise
You know what I'm glad is that
They didn't, what happened with the
Country Bears is that they didn't say
Okay this will be the final bear show
Okay, curtain comes down and then they show just a video
Of ILM's
New country bear models
And then they don't explain
What's going on until an hour later and say
Oh now the country bears are just a video basically
There's a QR code
But because it's a dizzy website it never works
And the country bears
Made it themselves
Out of thatch
Oh they have a justification
Oh
It doesn't work at all
You can't make a QR code made out of sticks on your way out
Each person actually gets a
Physical QR code
Rub them together and the smoke will give you a vision
Then they will show you what we're gonna do
Splash some Pago's Bill's Salsa on ends
See if you can figure out what's going on
Rockin' Around the Christmas Tree
Again, a song I always liked a lot
I don't know that we need to play it
Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer
I'll play a little of this, this is of course the version
Or the song you know
Starts a slower
I always did like Rudolph a lot
They did, because Rudolph was in
You're playing the real
And then, what's that?
You're playing the real one to compare contrast you're saying
No this is it, this is the Jimmy one
Oh I thought this was the, oh wow
It fooled me
Rudolph was added later to the Reindeer lore
Correct? I think that's right
But I was gonna say it really worked
Like if Rudolph was like Poochie
It did really work on me
Cause like immediately
I was like Rudolph is the star of this
Like I never cared about any other reindeer
But Rudolph because of this song
They Poochied him
And it was so effective
And I think probably remains effective
I love this
Song, I hate this inch
You know Dasher and Dancer
But if you recall
Like I don't like that
Was it just anticipation
You were like get to the fucking fun part
Get to the start, we're all here for one reason
Rudolph the red nose reindeer
You know what this is like for me
I love
I love LA, but I don't want to hear
That, hey New York City
Really? It's golden
I'm like skip, get to the
I don't like that, all the people dressed like monkeys
Skip, skip, skip
If there's a podcast skip button on that
It's the same format, little slow intro, I don't want to hear it
Right to the Dodger's victory
I love LA
You know as the fireworks are going off
And they're running the bass
Yeah, yeah sure
I want to get right to
The fine work of the Toto gentleman
Steve Lukather and David Bage
Great solos
But if you think about
Timelines I haven't thought about
It was the night before Christmas
Rudolph the red nose reindeer doesn't
Show up until 1949
That is
120 years
Of the reindeer as we know them
And then the boldness
Of putting a new kid on the block
And we all love him more
Yeah, it worked
You know why it's not Pucci
Is that Pucci had no character
And no vulnerability
And conflict, but Rudolph
Co-ops the retcons
The story, and tells you
You know Dash, you know all them right?
Well, they're assholes
And only one of them is nice
And they only come around
Because the nice one
Did something good
Now they just want to kiss his ass
Yes, no they really
Paint them out to be like
Fair weather friends
What have you done for me lately?
Yeah, absolutely
Light up your nose and maybe all
Lead our way tonight
And then we'll see if I like you
Has anyone tried to add a new reindeer
In the last hundred years?
Somebody had there must have been
Yes, all of the other reindeer
A book that has something to do
With Drew Barrymore
I forget what she narrated it
Or I don't know if she wrote it
Maybe, interesting
I think maybe that's a book
And then there was a special
Yes, a 1999 special
With Drew Barrymore
Joey Pants
And apparently Michael Stipe
Wow, okay
So there you go
I don't know if that's
I think people like that
But I don't think that's accepted
As a forever edition
Boy, and look at this
In this special Merry Christmas
After all, performed by
Big Bad Voodoo Daddy
Featuring Drew Barrymore
Wow, so she's the voice
Of Olive
Interesting, so they tried to get
A new reindeer in
But maybe she just didn't take quite as well
I think it's successful within this
But we don't need to adopt that
As permanent lore
Also, another reindeer added
Michael Stipe as Schnitzel
Blitzen's flightless cousin
Oh my god
Michael Stipe is Schnitzel
Schnitzel
And Matt Groening is Arturo
The elf that Schnitzel throws
Olive into
Into, not like
Probably just like
Doesn't go into Schnitzel's body
Is 1999 Man on the Moon?
Yeah
So in that same year
Michael Stipe recorded
That hit song
For the hit movie
And then he was also Schnitzel
Yeah, he did to the score of the film
The song existed before
But there was a new song
The great beyond is that
Yeah, I'm sorry
We had to say it
Yeah, yeah
Sorry, Rudolph the reindeer
He does a whole wind up to it
See, that's Jimmy
They put the controls around
The production is better I guess
I think the production is better
But also some more of my favorites as well
The most famous
Famous reindeer
Of all
Rudolph the red-nosed reindeer
Had a very shiny nose
And if you ever saw it
You would even say glow
That's it
I think I got it
I like it, I think it's good
Alright, let's get to my favorite
Santa's Stole Thanksgiving
This is an original song
And I play this
I do play this every year for sure
This is on my list
For who?
My personal list
Lindsay likes to listen to the same
25 Christmas songs
Over the course of the holiday
And I don't like to do that
As much, I like to find other
Stuff if I'm going to do the holidays
Oh, holy
No
Mostly the religious stuff
And the works of John Pierpont
Mostly
So yeah, this is
Santa's Stole Thanksgiving
It's jaunty
What else would you say about it?
Santa's Stole Thanksgiving
For Christmas
Drug-plammered rock
To the North Pole with his sledge
Whoa
No rooms never saw him coming
The bump and knocks they kept coming
That Thursday in November
Caught gobbled up by December
Santa's Stole Thanksgiving
For Christmas
Why? What was the motive?
It's such a happy holiday
No more laid-back relaxation
It's Black Friday degradation
It's Santa's Stole Thanksgiving
To them all
That didn't rhyme with anything
It was not a great rhyme
Or a rhyme
It's like he's quoting
Fruitcakes where he talks about
Sushi in the mall
Yeah
It was earlier in the 90s
It's really weird to see here now
Imagine it
Sushi in a mall
So this is a song
That at least
It shows me that he's paying
Some attention in like 30 years
Or 20 years of being like very rich
He's noticed that or somebody's mentioned
That Thanksgiving
Now is the time when sales happen
Yeah
Now maybe that's he was 10, 15 years too late on
The like door buster
People trampling each other for TVs
But it is
He's a topical song from him
He usually writes timeless music is what I'm saying
And this is a topical song
And it's clear what he's writing about I would say
We understand what the message is
And it's jaunty
So I like all of that about it
Jason what do you think?
Yeah I like it too
It is
It's that he didn't get to see the big thing this year
For Black Friday
I think a lot of companies
Saying on Thanksgiving
We're not opening
So you're saying you might have had to revise the song?
Well no I'm saying
Sushi in the mall
Eventually became common place
Eventually became the norm
And now half the malls
Three quarters are at the malls
Well his AI will sing a song
That's revised maybe in a decade
About what's happening
Because I
Dick talk we need to ban it
I saw some reports
I don't think the
Crazy like door buster sales
Are even happening as much anymore
And it's not maybe like
Pandemonium as much in the stores
No
That we're online I think has to help mitigate
That has helped
And everybody is trying to get
Move the starting line back a little bit
So you're seeing more places
Just like oh by the way ours starts Monday
Sales start Monday
They go into the following Monday
For Cyber Monday
So now it's spread out over like two months
So yes this is maybe a specific
Moment in time when it was
Truly Friday or midnight Thursday
He had seen a news report
Like you said 15 years prior
Right
I gotta write a song about that
15 years later
Oh yeah remember
I wrote it on my notebook
I wrote it on the husk of a corn
A corn on the cobite
That's where I write my notes
I wrote it in sriracha
Luckily it held
Yeah so that's good
It's good
Then he does the song
Mala Kalikimaka again
But with the ukulele player
Jake Shimabukura
Is how you pronounce it I believe
It's basically the same
He doesn't do much
With it which why would you want to mess with it
It's perfection already
This is weird to do it twice
It is weird to do it twice
But I guess because it's featuring someone else
That's the reason you know you don't have to
You wouldn't just
Keep it at one
Okay what did he do Winter Wonderland
What do we think about
Winter Wonderland in general
I like that song
It's like a
It's like a little bit of a
Satter
Snowflakes this far south
Tell me
Ah
It's Christmas
Come on
Sleigh bells ring
Are you listening
He needed to get in character for the song so he had to do that little
Improv at the top
You know what this one has
Speaking of characters
I think I'm not so
Psyched on this one
He does a little voice
He does
I'm married you say no mon
Yeah
Mr. Snowmon
You're going to find that
Here and there through the Buffett discography
Yeah it seems like it
A little bit of reggae voice
But you know he's
No one's
Adrian Brody making guest appearance
As his character
Oh man
It's one of the finest pieces of media
Adrian Brody's SNL intro
Sean Paul
Doing his character reggae mon
Reggae mon
I got to see a Q&A for
Darjeeling limited one time and he was there
And I just
Stared at him
I'm in the room with the guy who
I'm in the room with reggae mon
I couldn't look at anyone
I just locked
I think he caught me at one point
This guy's probably thinking about me doing that reggae thing
Yes I was
Telepathically like you're understanding each other
I know what you're thinking
Then also at the end he says
Frolic and play the parrot
headway
So we're doing our little
amendments
That's basically what I was scanning for in listening to these albums
When did he change something and he did it
About six times per
Yeah baby it's
Cold outside he does
And he does a little flip of it
He does it the other way
He does it with
Nadira Shakur who's one of his regular
Backup singers I believe
Yes that's right
The audience knows, they know he's in the Coral Reefer band
She was in the group Arrested Development though too
That's impressive
That's really cool
And then he does White Christmas
Which you know
Was written by Irving Berlin
Irving Berlin yeah
I like White Christmas
I do, I like White Christmas yeah
It's a sad one though
You know what here's the thing, have I said this about Christmas before
That the argument I get in it with Lindsay
Not it's an argument
It's not an argument
Shattering your novelty's skull
Glasses against the wall
She's not like Mrs. Claus to me
Your music's coming off, I'm playing Santa
Stole Thanksgiving dammit
I find Christmas time so
Like kind of melancholy and sad
That it's not as much like
I want to be enveloped in it
And that was before Jimmy Buffet
That was before yeah
And Karl Rove
I learned that Karl Rove
Born on Christmas
That's what all the Kissinger Twitter accounts are going to have to turn to
Now it's got
When is Karl Rove still alive
They've probably
Switched to it
I'm going to do one of those
I'm going to make so much Twitter bucks
Doing my death count down
You'll get them
But yeah some of it
I want to be sad on a roller coaster
While tears for fears play
But that's for a couple minutes
Of course it's the killer plays
Christmas is just
It's the end of the year
You're looking back
It feels like the end
It feels like the end to me
And everything makes me feel very sad around the time
The holiday season
So I'm always just like
Too much Christmas
Stuff
But I understand that seems like I'm being a
Grinch about it but I feel like it's kind of like
I have seasonal whatever it's called
Effective disorder
Well that's true
Allergies whatever but I don't know
I think that's common
To some degree but
White Christmas does make me sad
But it is good
There's a song called
The closing of the year
That's from the
1992 feature film Toys
This is a song by
It's in the movie
Toys is one of those bizarre things that ever happened
It's in the movie and I'm like who's the singer
Who am I looking at I can't tell
It's Wendy Melvoin
Wendy and Lisa do this song
And it's everything you're describing
It's about the melancholy and the closing of the year
The heaviness of
The kids choirs in it
And then about half way through
In the music video a magical moment where there's a
Dark and silhouetted figure and then
A light comes on him and it's Seal
In the biggest
Hat you've ever seen
Seal in his giant
Christmas top hat and he
Is the most emotional bridge
It's a weird song that I kind of like but I'm
Also watching it like who on
Earth heard this
And thought yes that is everything I
Feel everything I felt from the movie Toys
It's supposed to be the most emotional
Bleeding out song you've ever heard
But then it's for Toys and then they'll cut to
LL Cool J looking mean cause he's
Like a military guy who wants to build mean
Toys this is a terrible film
But it's a awful movie
No no no there's no guest
Rap but there's something about it
Listeners check it out look at this see if you
Feel the magic I feel when
Seal shows up in the biggest hat you
Ever saw
Wow now I gotta look I gotta
Watch this
I might
People might check this out and say Scott
That is the shittiest piece of shit
Of ever and you'd be you wouldn't be wrong
Yeah well I'll give it a whirl
Maybe it'll be what come in your standards
That'll be next year too we'll do an episode
On that on Seal's big hat
Yeah we're making declarations here
It's really I mean if you like Kiss from a Rose
In the bombast of that song getting to hear him
Go at the closing
Of the year
And he's in the biggest hat
Seal's pretty fun
Uh huh I like Seal yeah
My my
I understand Mike what you're saying
And I feel like I get a little of it
But a lot of the times
I feel like Jane and I
Are much more of like let's
Marathon home our Christmas movies
Oh there's a chill in the air let's make
Coco it's time to decorate the
Tree who's rapping
Today you're rapping okay
You're having a ball I am having a ball I love
Christmas yeah
I don't think there's anything strange about that
No no it's not I'm glad that's your
It's Mike over here and his melancholy
And that's what he's bringing to the table yeah I'm sorry
I'm not saying I'm not trying to be a grinch
But I just that's the way I
Feel often do you like New
Year's Eve do you like New Year's time
I do like New Year's yes I don't like
New Year's Eve I like New Year's Eve I feel a lot of pressure for it to be fun
I love the first week in January
I feel good
The first week almost every first week in January
I feel good I feel like
Like I'm born
Born anew yeah yeah
Is that personally
Because the city of LA is like
Quiet and deserted
Well there's something when my parents
When my parents lived
In Chicago and I would come back
I would feel so good getting off like the plane
In LA like probably
Either first week in January just at the end of December
And it was probably partly
Because like everyone's gone
And again I'm just like it feels the years
Fresh it feels like here we go
Okay okay you know
But I'm not I if I'm
Hanging out with you at Christmas time I'm not going to be a downer
I can still party I can still hang
You can still go invite Mike to your Christmas parties
While you're young and cool yeah
And he won't complain about the songs
And try to get different songs in the list
Well I might do that but I would do it in a fun way
Where you think I'm cool because I am suggesting cool stuff
Who's that guy who took over my phone and is putting his own music on?
He's cool I know that
He's cool
He's cool he's trying to ask are you 17? 16?
How old are you?
Wow he found little Jimmy Dickens Christmas songs
Yeah hell yeah
Jason and I were listening to little Jimmy in the car yesterday
What's that?
Little Jimmy we've talked about little Jimmy Dickens
I was probably so annoyed by the name I didn't remember it
The club three people
No
We haven't even gotten into
The club doesn't even know little Jimmy Dickens
I found little Jimmy Dickens
Letter to Santa song here
We can play that at the end
We're still learning about Kerwin Frost
GQ calls him our
Influencers favorite influencer
Kerwin Frost who designed the new
Sorry the new Mcnugget putties
He designed the new Mcnugget putties
I didn't know there was new Mcnugget putties
The new starting yesterday
The new starting yesterday Monday
We have two in the house already
Jason has one there are new six new
Mcnugget putties you can get at McDonald's
Designed by a guy named Kerwin Frost
Kerwin Frost who I had never heard of until this
Happened and I will
Let the listeners know that hopefully
Maybe it'll be gone by then but there's a chase
A secret gold Mcnugget
That you can also get because these are blind boxes
There's a chase
To get the secret Mcnugget
Well that's what they call a chase is when you
Don't necessarily know what the design of the
Blind box character
It's like a fairy
Scott's never heard of chase
Scott doesn't know little Jimmy Dinkins
Scott doesn't know Mack Mcenally
He told you he did a
Thing at like the CMA awards or something
A couple years ago he just died like
Within the last ten years but he did a bit with
What like Brad Paisley where he played
Little Justin Bieber on the
CMAs and he's like 90
He looks like
Young old Benjamin Button
Benjamin Button towards the end of the movie
Or beginning of the movie
He gets younger
There's a chase for the little Jimmy Dinkins
Mcnugget buddy
Memorial
Let's get to the last one
Twelve days of Christmas
Alright and you're like twelve days of Christmas
I know
Fertrusion of Pear Tree I know
This sounds boring
On the day of Christmas my true love gave to me
A purple parrot in a palm tree
What?
On the second day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
On the third day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Three fin hats
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
Guess what y'all
It's the twelve days of Christmas
Parrot head version
On the fourth day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Four Hawaiian yukes
Three fin hats
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
On the fifth day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Five cheeseburgers
Four Hawaiian yukes
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
On the sixth day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Six macadamia tarpics
Five cheeseburgers
Four Hawaiian yukes
Three fin hats
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
On the eleventh day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Four lulu cookbooks
Ten tiki torches
Nine pairs of flip flops
Eight vintage eight tracks
Seven Vegas tickets
Six mac guitar picks
Five cheeseburgers
Four Hawaiian yukes
Three fin hats
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
On the twelfth day of Christmas
My true love gave to me
Twelve lanchard cloggers
Eleven lulu cookbooks
Ten tiki torches
Nine pairs of flip flops
Eight vintage eight tracks
Seven Vegas tickets
Six mac guitar picks
Five cheeseburgers
Four Hawaiian yukes
Three fin hats
Two tattoos
And a purple parrot in a palm tree
Which one wouldn't fit?
He want, no, he wanted you to put it, give a tattoo to his body.
He took me a couple times here, two fin hats.
I thought he was saying two thin hats.
And I was like, what could that be?
Thin hats.
Like a paper hat?
Oh, fins, like that, okay, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so that, yes, he does, he does fulfill like the promise of the, the Buffett verse in there.
Which I guess is, yeah, that's the, that's the top song.
And you can also, listeners, you can also watch a music video of that
where they got everybody at all the shows to sing along to it.
So if you want a visual representation of all of those things and to see all the people who Jimmy touched
and all the people who purchased this album.
Whatever you do, don't drink twelve lanchard cloggers and get behind the wheel of a mid-sized sedan.
Yeah, so I want to say like, if people feel like we haven't done a good tri-
I don't know why I'm setting us up to fail later, but if they feel like we haven't done a great tribute,
it is coming soon, hopefully.
That wasn't it.
That wasn't the tribute.
There's more.
There's more coming.
And I am impressed that so much of the audience is into him.
And I like that.
That every single Club 3 subscriber knows who Mack McAnally is.
Yeah, sometimes we say stuff on the show and I go, oh, did anyone like that?
Does anyone- people like the story.
I think they like the bit on the show with the story of the plane.
But it's hard to know sometimes of what we're talking about.
It's like people actually have affection for that.
So I'm glad that we know the audience is there for an insane amount of Buffett coming soon.
Hours and hours.
There were some comments in the Patreon that indicated some beleaguerment with the amount of Buffett.
But one of those comments I know, I saw shut down with a classic catchphrase, counterpoint, you were wrong.
Yes.
Beep, beep, beep.
They think it's a little money every time someone says it.
And I have to like, I can't pretend that I think a lot of this music is great music,
but I am delighted by hearing it, talking about it.
Yeah.
I'm glad that, you know, we don't have to leave Jimmy in 2023 and we won't.
Believe us, we won't.
We will not.
And now playing us out with a song called Letter to Santa.
Oh, wait, well, you know-
Oh, I'm so sorry.
First, you survived podcast The Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to Club 3.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
There's always that mildly snarky Transformers line, although that is from the most emotional moment in theme park history.
True.
So there's always emotion in there.
But truly, this closes out the second year that we have done Club 3.
That's true, you're right.
And we thank you so much for subscribing to it.
You guys especially make it so this podcast is viable for us to do.
This year, you kept us afloat in a double strike year, a truly-
Yeah.
A double strike year, and you of course eased our pain in the year of Mr. Buffett's demise.
So in all sincerity, we can't thank you enough for subscribing and truly you guys here, everybody here makes this thing work and keeps this podcast going.
So let me give that sincere-
No, you're right.
That is nice and true.
Message.
Thank you so much.
It's great.
Thank you, everyone, I say.
God bless us.
God bless everyone.
God bless us all.
God bless, but then that's a back on us.
God bless you, everyone.
And now your final reward for the year is some- what is it again?
It's called Letter to Sand.
I've never heard it before.
It's by little Jimmy Dickens.
And I-
Now you get to- your present is a bunch of Christmas songs by an old man followed by another Christmas song by a much even older man.
Dear Santa Claus, I sure thank you for all the gifts.
He sounds like a good character.
And after I thought it over, Santa, I decided to write.
And thank you for all the toys.
I immediately do like it, yeah.
And especially the bike.
My little brother John and my sister Sue and my-
Like Mickey Rooney and the Simpsons.
And tell you thank you too.
Oh yeah, Santa.
There's something else I want to say.
Is it quick?
Please don't get mad at me.
Cause I gave my toys away.
You know my friend Jerry who lives across the railroad track?
Jerry?
He doesn't even have a mom or dad.
Just a little brother Jack.
I went to see them.
I went over there.
Yeah, oh my god.
The other song I like is called Take an Old Cold Tater and Wait.
About how he didn't grow as a child because he was always eating cold taters.
We'll play that next year.
Because of coldness?
Old cold taters.
Is it that it was only taters?
Do you want to keep this going so I can play the song?
I forgot to say once again, regular ideas, submit them.
City Walk Saga ideas, submit them.
Regular, don't, not, Jimmy Dinkins.
You can talk while you're playing it.
Give me a holiday present and don't say Jimmy Dinkins.
Dickins.
Look how much my brain doesn't want to, it's bouncing it back real time.
I say Dinkins.
Here we go, this is the good stuff.
The only armor I have is my head to keep them out of my brain.
Take a tater and wait.
There you go.