Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain live notes, large steel orders, an inside reference
made canon, and just the right amount of bananas to be funny.
All this plus Evan Susser and Van Robichaud return to talk about their work developing
Universal Studios' new ride, Illumination's VillainCon Minion Blast.
On today's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks where today we finally interrogate
the bastards who dared replace Shrek 4D.
I'm Scott Gardner, barely keeping it together in front of these fools, but at least we're
here, we're here with a purpose for them.
Mike Carlson, what do you think?
I'm here, I'm clenching my fists, just I want to hit somebody.
We trapped them, we've been all nice leading up to this, but now we get to let it all out.
Jason Sheridan.
I can't even look at them.
Even though I very much enjoyed this new attraction.
It doesn't matter.
An American classic went away for it.
I guess I'll give an actual introduction.
We can go backwards and make you guys villains again if you want.
But genuinely, been looking forward to this episode for a long time.
You know what?
I feel like a lot of guests on this show, people we have on the show are funny friends,
people from the world of comedy, but I think there's a kind of guest we'd like to have
more which is the people who actually work on the attractions who put these things together.
And today, these guest categories have finally merged and we're so excited to have you guys
together.
They wrote for Brooklyn Nine-Nine, they wrote the feature film Fist Fight, and most importantly
today, writers of Illumination's villain con minion blast, Evan Susser and Van Roba show.
Hello, folks.
Hey, how's it going?
Good to be here.
It's all smooth since you became a quiet storm show.
We're in a theme park celebrities these days.
You gotta regulate the energy.
I was a little nervous you guys would be honest about the Shrek 4D of it all, but I do want
to say I consider this all delayed revenge against Shrek 4D for taking out Alfred Hitchcock.
Amen, bro.
So you as a child, or I don't know when it happened, a teen, I forget when the change
occurred.
You were like waiting, somebody needs to take a shot and that's gotta be me.
But anyway, go on.
Okay, sure.
I know we didn't just talk about it.
That was a last year thing, right?
So I don't know the timeline.
Well congratulations, you slayed the beast.
The Alfred Hitchcock experience had a great rear window section where they had little
screens.
Yes.
You could look through binoculars.
From across the way, the optimal place to do it was raised up on the second level.
I'm a big fan of that, very formative in my mind.
Like a perv simulation where you could be a pervert like Alfred was.
I was a very excited seven or eight year old trying to find the murderer and I'm like that's
just a lady undressing, where is the crime?
I've gotta keep sweeping.
You were upset.
No interest in that.
I was just gonna say it's exciting to be here in all the time that we were working on the
ride, thinking about how is it going to be enjoyed by the podcast The Ride Crew?
All of the things that you guys discuss each week.
I was imagining waking up at night saying, oh no, what are they gonna say?
How are they gonna say, how are they gonna bless it up?
Are we blessing it up how they wanted it to be blessed up?
Do they want to burn it to the ground for insurance money, a premise they haven't said
in many years?
No seriously, I think that it was a true thrill and it's exciting to be talking about it with
you guys.
Yeah, jeez.
I've really been looking forward to it for a long time, to finally triangulate all this
and to get down there and experience it.
We weren't immediately on the ball, but this hasn't been open for too long.
This opened in August.
We did a soft opening in August and then it's been open now for a few months.
It's great, you guys are pretty good, pretty on the ball as far as getting down there,
organizing a whole Orlando trip just to do it.
I myself have not been since it's open.
I was there pre-open when it was up and running, but not open to the public yet.
But I've never ridden it with a live audience or anything like that.
So you guys are ahead of me.
I think they're loving it.
I sensed good vibes.
No one was revolting or putting their guns down and looking at their phone.
I felt a lot of engagement.
Yeah, I mean there's so much to ask you guys about.
I don't like, should we just go back to the beginning, which I guess in this case is that
you've been, you've done stuff with illumination for a long time now.
So you've been in their world and in Minion World specifically.
Was that the beginning?
I know there's been shorts, there's been ads, I forget your entire Union filmography.
Our illumination experience has started with working on a Minions short called Minions
Scouts.
It's available on Netflix under the Minions and More Volume 1 compilation.
Which weirdly has Shrek 4D on it too, just to pad it out.
It's one of the and mores, sure.
And then we did some commercials for them featuring the Minions.
We worked on an aborted Super Bowl halftime commercial for Minions 2, The Rise of Gru,
that did not come to fruition.
No fault of ours, I hope.
And then we got an email about, it was kind of not specific, and said, oh they have people
at illumination have another thing, would you be interested in talking?
And assuming, oh maybe it's another short, maybe it's a commercial, didn't know.
And then we heard Theme Park Ride and our eyes lit up because it seemed exciting.
And initially, Van, maybe you will, my kind of understanding was that we were being brought
on specifically just to do kind of the pre-show video that you would watch.
And through kind of elbowing our way in, we managed to ride this thing all the way through
and become a part of both the entire ride and also the Minion Cafe and the whole thing.
Which was a really fun experience as far as people who grew up going to Theme Parks.
Yeah, both big fans, not even just people we've had on the show because we know you.
You're both a big theme park people and Van like an old Epcot head, I feel.
And universal, clearly.
No, yeah, I jumped at the opportunity.
Look, I'm going to back up a little bit just to give the real behind the scenes and tell
just the shortest version of the real story, so to speak.
Oh wow.
Evan's lies.
Evan and I, we've been a long time writing team, but a few years ago, we started to have
interests that diverged a little bit and we actually decided that we were going to go
our separate ways and start working on projects separately.
And we sent out an email to a lot of our contacts and people we'd been working with on projects
to explain this all to them, explain it was very amicable and that there were a few things
we're going to still work on together.
But moving forward, you kind of got to pick one or the other sort of a situation.
And the next day, one of the people we sent that email to was a person from Illumination
who emailed back about this project and very clearly had not read the emails from us saying
we were no longer working together.
Just a slight correction.
I don't think it was an email back, but it was an email basically sent the next day to
us, seemingly maybe inspired by the email, but clearly not read.
Inspired by seeing your names in an inbox.
And so we looked at each other and at the time it was, I think, proposed as like an
eight week job.
So then even before having the initial phone call, we had a discussion of like, well.
They were being very mysterious about what it even was.
And we were, and in the past we'd had good experiences.
And we said, ah, you know what, why not?
And also just to kind of, I think, prove to ourselves that it was amicable and that we
could get along.
We were like, why don't we just, you know, why not?
I believe the phrasing was one last heist.
Right.
Exactly.
And then we said, sure, let's let's have the initial thing.
And then when it was a theme park route and then so, yes, it extended in a very funny.
And so now we've been working together on theme park rides and illumination projects
for three and a half years.
Oh my God.
So your day.
So your breakup lasted for less than a day.
Yeah, pretty much.
Wow.
We are, we are a hybrid team now and we do do solo work as well, which is actually a
difficult situation to get yourself into.
You really can only do it by accident.
Yes.
So any themed entertainment, it's, it's come to your duo.
I think we're pretty locked in for real.
You know what?
I don't know.
I don't even want to commit to that.
You know, I think that's that.
I think that's really just how it comes.
I think Van really impressed some of the people at Universal.
No, but I, it was a very funny way to, to come into the project.
I'll say that.
Yeah.
Wow.
Okay.
You immediately and then, and then enter a mysterious foggy world.
You don't know what you're dealing with.
You don't know what your deal is on the project.
Yeah.
And then, okay, so it's eight weeks initially and you think you're doing pre-show and what
do you know at that point?
Is Ride Premise established?
So at that point, I think that they had come in and from like the highest level, there
had been some agreement as far as what the attraction would be.
I think the, Van, maybe you remember some of these details better.
The idea, I think it was already that it was going to be VillainCon, that it was going
to be a convention and that you would be competing to join the Vicious Six, which all remained.
But beyond that, there was a lot of stuff that was not locked in.
Like the number of physical rooms that would be able to be spaces in the ride had been
locked down.
Basically the track layout.
Okay.
So it was still a bit of a mess, but then exactly what was happening in the specific
rooms that you would move through, that was still up in the air.
Which sort of characters were the character who was the primary character within that
space was somewhat locked in, but still flexible.
Like the idea of like it's roughly this amount, because you're dealing with the Vicious Six,
which is like a villain super group that comes from, that's from Minions 2, correct?
Yes.
And maybe there's the vague notion of like each one of them has a space, but you don't
know that breakdown or order.
Which also at the time, Minions 2 Rise of Gru had not come out yet.
So we saw the movie in advance, which also sometimes made this a little tricky because
understandably, you know, Illumination, these movies are very valuable.
And so they would occasionally give us like two hour windows where we could watch the
movie and then we would have to like frantically write notes because the idea is that you want
to be referencing things that these characters are doing.
Understand the characters, be able to write in their voice, but like had only been given
access to the movie one time for two hours and couldn't go back and reference anything.
And how rough of a state also.
No, it was pretty.
It was a delayed because of the pandemic movie.
So I think it was, I think every time we saw it had been finished, but it was being.
Oh, but you couldn't scrub back and forth.
No, right.
Exactly.
But was it remote?
You were watching it remotely?
But with the sort of like thrown together during the pandemic to remotely screen things,
barely functional systems, everyone in Hollywood ran off.
Oh, we did a similar thing.
We did a similar thing when we watched Jay and Silent Bob's reboot during the pandemic.
Equally.
Similar box office.
Yeah.
We, you mean I kind of avoided that particular zoom in.
Scott popped in for a second maybe.
And I was dismayed to find that I had not cleared the movie entirely.
Right.
There were still 10 minutes to go when I showed up.
Can I ask when you guys came on board, were they already set on the moving walkway element
and the shooter element?
Yes, there was, I believe, Finn.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was.
You were always going to be on a walkway.
The walkway was locked in.
And the blaster.
And the blaster element.
The like functionality of the blaster and the design of the blaster was not locked in.
And there were lots of discussions about that, that we were involved in.
Something that happened, which I think is what resulted in us being so involved was
early on there were just these all hands meetings every week with every department for the ride.
And we were at those meetings.
Yes.
And it would be interesting sometimes these meetings, because I think, you know, it's
a big project and you kind of don't know what's going to be most urgent.
So sometimes we would be on this meeting and it'd be like, okay, today we're talking all
about the pre-show video.
And it would, Van and I would be talking, you know, listening, you know, be very engaged.
And other times it would be like, okay, we need to talk about how much steel is being
ordered.
And we were just on these calls.
And through that process, we started to learn and get ideas.
About the steel.
But also there would be, there would be meetings about, you know, the blasters and how they
would be designed.
There was a whole discussion of that, you know, you want people to be holding onto the
blaster and not, you know, swinging them wildly.
So that was where it came from to have it designed to have two buttons on the blaster
so that there would be a reason to hold it with both hands.
And all of that kind of stuff, we started to kind of be exposed to every element of
theme park ride design, which was a very cool, you know, experience.
But also sometimes I found myself, you know, shaking my head, I do not know what is being
discussed.
I have no idea.
When you're also watching probably the triangulation of like, that there's illumination involved
and then universal functional people.
And that's something I always wonder about these things is like, is it just everybody
kind of like stepping forward and checking with each other about what's feasible constantly
and everybody like slowly moves towards the finish line because it's like, hey, yeah,
how do you write for spaces that aren't fully figured out?
Yeah, I mean, that was a complicated part of the project was it was a constantly moving
target, but you had to, no pun intended, about constantly moving.
But we did have to keep like revising it in sort of in all directions, like moving closer
and closer to what is the actual premise of these things going to be.
But then there would be like, you know, curveballs thrown where it's like there's actually another
section of the line now.
Or you know, this last room is good.
This room's gonna have two walls instead of one wall that are gonna have stuff on it.
And so suddenly you got to fill up.
So suddenly you've got to like, like redefine what would move around.
Maybe the space would be better for this character if it's gonna have two walls and things like
that.
Huh.
Because that was the thing that happened was so there were these spaces that were kind
of defined, but there was a sort of like a horse trading of what character would go in
what space to best suit the concept elements for that character.
Wow.
Like how long did it take where you were comfortable just like, I'm gonna take a big swing here.
Like how many meetings before you were like, it was, I wish I could find, I should have
looked up the email because there was, I think a few months in we took a big swing.
All right, Gru dies.
That's how it's.
Kevin kills Gru, okay.
Who's Kevin?
One of them.
Kevin the minion.
Oh, I gotta cut that one.
Kevin might have to cut that one.
Oh my goodness.
I think we just lost our job.
Just go straight to Van.
But there were, there was a point where I think we got comfortable with the level of
that was being both expected and allowed from us.
And we kind of started reshaping some big parts of the ride.
The entire part of the premise that Villain Con is being held in Orlando at Universal
Studios came from us.
Oh wow.
Oh wait, because okay, so Villain Con, I'm no expert in these movies at all, but Villain
Con came from the first minions, correct?
But that is also a period piece.
That's a period piece.
So that is in the 60s.
And it's being held, I believe it actually may be in Orlando or Florida.
Yeah, it's in Florida.
Okay.
I think it's in Florida, maybe not specifically Orlando.
It's set in the 60s.
And so that's 1960s Villain Con you see then.
Because that's pre-Gru.
That's pre the rise of Gru's rise.
So is Villain Con a place that the minions are going to like hunt out possible villains?
They're looking for a new boss.
Yes, and so they go there and that's where they meet Scarlet Overkill who becomes their
boss in the film for.
But Sandra Bullock?
Sandra Bullock.
Yes, okay, yeah, yeah.
So Villain Con exists, but now you have still more logic to work out and that you have to
get it up to 2023.
So I thought that the idea of, you know, people will hold conventions at the hotels, at the
theme parks and things like that.
And so I thought the idea that maybe the convention itself is being held at the theme park secretly
would add an extra element of fun for the young riders of the ride to feel like they're
really immersed in the experience and like double immersed.
Not only is it like there's a whole make believe inside, but you're like already in it when
you're at the park deciding to go.
Sure, sure.
And then, yes, so it is, I guess that's an important thing to note that Universal Studios
exists in the world of the ride.
You are transporting to a fully other world because there's jokes right away in the pre-show
about that and a funny thing, if I name check things, if everyone take credit, please, if
I bring something up, but they're pretty like good hit at Universal, a joke about how, wait,
oh, God, what is it?
It's about the parking.
It's a universal Orlando just got a lot more evil, which considering how much they pay
for parking is really saying something.
Yes, that was a joke that we wrote and which was funny, though, we wrote the joke and I'm
here looking at, you know, living in Hollywood and how much they charge for city walk parking.
Yeah, yeah.
And I looked up how much they charge for it in Orlando.
It's actually much cheaper.
I was curious.
A number I bought a bottle of water like at the cafe and I'm like, wow, very reasonable
down here in the park.
The joke was still worked.
Yeah.
Yes.
Because paying for parking when you're going to a theme park, I know they all do it, but
it feels ridiculous to have to do.
Yeah.
Hotels even now.
If the joke doesn't apply now, it will certainly apply in seven years.
But yeah, that we were like unsure how they would feel about that, but they actually they
like that at Universal and they were in for it.
And look, I am cool at Universal.
I'm all in favor for taking credit for a lot of things and I think we should continue to
keep doing that throughout this whole thing.
But I should say that it was a very collaborative process and a lot of people on all sides.
Universal Illumination had a lot of great ideas and people, it's not even like, it's
not like every funny thing that's in the thing came from us.
Everyone contributed all sorts of ideas.
I can't clarify anything you don't like about the ride.
Didn't come from me, may have come from everyone.
Right.
And they were also very open to like Van was saying, like, well, if you guys have any,
you know, ideas about how like, you know, the mechanical engineering should be done,
you know, feel free to chime in.
And I did.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, I'm very involved in the app design.
Uh huh.
Yeah, the app is very detailed.
Like for one thing, I'll pay a compliment, it works.
Not always guarantee with theme park theme park based apps.
But I was reading like some theme park blog coverage of like, well, here's different things
you can get and here's different settings you can do and customize.
And I'm like, wow, I didn't even barely scratch the surface with the app integration.
Yeah, there was a lot of that a lot of time was spent kind of trying to figure out exactly
what the amount of depth of customization would be in the app and balancing that with
the ability to just go on the ride and play it without even really having the app.
Oh, sure.
And that was a tough balance to hit.
But I feel like there is a there's a deepness in the app if you get in there and try and
change the settings.
And Evan, I also wrote all of the copy in the app as well.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Geez.
I have a question and not to be presumptuous until you had to do your podcast.
Should we explain what the ride is?
Yeah.
Yes, possibly.
Probably.
We've hinted at it to some extent.
But OK, so this is now and now it's like a quiz to make sure I understood.
If you would like.
Sure, absolutely.
Sure.
So the ride is that you are attending VillanCon to join the Vicious Six and VillanCon is kind
of like a Comic Con like event.
You wait in line, but except instead of comic book fans and vendors, it's all villains.
And so the Vicious Six, which is an editorial supergroup, is looking for their next member
and you get in line like you would if you were going to Comic Con, a convention.
very funny videos where it's kind of VNC, which is a villain news channel.
They're doing.
I'm going to step in because Evan is really just butchering.
He's flailing.
He said very funny.
He should have said extremely funny.
First of all, incredibly rewatchably perfectly funny.
But so, yes, so the the in the ride itself that you get on is a moving walkway blaster
attraction.
But there's a lot of fun leading up to that, which is based on the premise, you are at
VillanCon and you are in line for a specific experience that is being held at VillanCon.
And if you've ever been to Comic Con or any of these big conventions, it's all about lines,
which made it a great way to theme theme park because most of your ride, because most of
your time in a theme park ride is spent in a line.
And so you're really on the ride as soon as you're in the line, because part of the experience
of being at any convention and being at VillanCon is standing in those darn long lines.
Sure.
Yes.
But to make that experience a little more bearable, there are televisions throughout
that are playing a special VillanCon edition of the VNC, which is the Villain Network Channel,
which is sort of like CNN for villains.
It's from the Despicable Me universe.
Sure, sure.
And we were able to get the announcer voice actor who was the VillanCon network, like
newsman in the 1960s in the Minions film back.
Oh yes.
Who's very 60s style.
I mean, will we style him up to 70s-ish?
Yes, yes.
And he kind of sets the premise for you.
Oh wait, does he?
Oh, so the look changed.
You like, you used the...
Well no, in the 60s he is in the first Minions movie, he's in the 60s.
In the second movie you see him again, he's in a 70s look and we went with the 70s look.
Oh I see, okay.
Move him forward a little bit.
But he does also set off in the premise, he sets up that villains have come from around
the world and throughout time and they show some villains traveling through a time machine,
which does help address, we talked about this a little bit off air, that this is designed
to function canonically so that it can have taken place within the world of the films
and there is a time machine added so that villains who perhaps didn't contemporaneously
exist within the films can be featured within the villain con attraction.
Gosh, yes, because Minions, the first Minions is a prequel that goes way, way back, we're
dealing with dinosaurs and all that.
It goes back to the beginning of time essentially.
Yes, yeah.
So we have a long timeline to deal with.
So you figured out, because we were talking about how timeline is an issue in many, especially
recent theme park additions in areas, so you thought this through, what is the way to justify...
I'll be honest with you, the folks at Illumination were very concerned about making sure the
timeline was able to, at least if you squinted, match up and work.
Sure, sure.
Do you feel like you've now planted seeds for future Minions projects by adding to the
sort of canon in a way?
I can't really get into any detail on that, but actually the answer is yes.
Okay, great.
I did have the thought having just a few months ago watched Minions Rise of Gru and then doing
this ride going like, wow, the Vicious 6 looks great.
They've aged really nicely.
Yes, yes.
Probably villain technology.
They may have traveled by time machine.
So anyway, to continue with the ride description, you make your way through several versions
of the line.
We call it the queue, that's the internal...
That's what you say.
Yes.
Terminologies.
And you make it to, I believe, is it Q5?
I believe that's right.
Which is when you are able to walk out onto the VillainCon show floor.
But this implies, not to get into weeds, I guess, but you know the area.
Those are all coded in some way.
So we're like...
You're right in Q1, Q2.
And so in Q5, you get a little bit of free roaming ability.
You're walking around inside of a space that is built out to kind of look like you're seeing
booths at a convention.
So there are various vendors of villainous goods and services.
There's a malicious motors, which is sort of where villains get their getaway vehicles
and evil cars and whatnot from.
There's the Diabolique Boutique, which is sort of a fashion house for villains where
you might get your supervillainous costume made.
There is...
What is the pet store?
What is that?
That's called the...
Do I have...
Corrupt Companions, I believe.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
I remember that.
And that's your evil pet foods and whatnot.
Right, right.
Yeah, great.
Giant gator.
Yes, giant alligator.
Yeah, really good feature there.
And so just to pause on the explanation and just get into some more Evan and I, the most
important part.
I think that was my favorite part of the ride was...
We did work on a lot of the placemaking line stuff.
And so those booths, both concepting what some of them were, but then also the physical
objects that are in them.
Malicious Motors has a bunch of license plates up on the wall that say, like, too evil for
you kind of type things.
And we wrote all of the license plates and things like that.
And again, there were other people pitched on these things as well.
I'm flipping through a couple of things I grabbed pictures of.
And there's in the pet area, cans of corrupt delights, fiendishly flavorful.
And then it's different at bat food, scorpion food, vulture food.
Yeah.
So the process with a lot of that is we would get sent...
Our department at Universal would mock up a label.
And then that would get sent to us to revise the copy on, sometimes pitch a new, maybe
instead of bat food, it's this type of thing.
And so there was a ton of collaboration between us and the different departments at Universal
working on this stuff.
And Malicious Motors has a car console, a steering wheel, and buttons and gauges.
And that got sent back to us with somewhat generic what the gauges said.
And we changed them to be things like oil slick and more specific things.
So there's a lot of interesting places where there's quote unquote writing that you might
not expect on a ride.
What a dream to get to just fill out specifics.
And really specific assignments.
I think one of the biggest things like that is, and this is a...
You could not go on the attraction three times and not see it, but there is a map of the
VillainCon floor.
They have every...
Which is all these booths that you don't see, because the premise is that you are going
through this queue, you're going through a small portion of the show floor.
And you see a map that shows a much bigger portion of...
And it's all of the booths that you don't even get to see.
And there's little small things.
I think some of these, I'm saying, didn't necessarily make it, but it's like torture
chamber and just little things labeled like things that you might imagine would be at
a convention.
One I really like, false sense of security room.
That one was tough to get through.
There were some people who could not understand that joke, I think very fairly.
Yes.
I guess it's a good one to look at later.
When you're doing all this and you're writing all these jokes, do you literally...
Was there anything that you were surprised when you actually saw it?
Or was it literally everything like, yes, no, would you get emails that would list yes,
no on all your ideas?
Sometimes yes, but then other times you would get there when we got there like, oh wow,
yeah, some of the stuff did...
You never hear back about it, then it's just there.
So you're leaving this queue, you head in to go and get your blaster.
And there's a little area where there's these blasters that are on a conveyor belt.
To simplify it for people who may not be familiar, blaster is a word we use in the theme park
business because we don't want to say gun.
Things have changed.
Changed since they proposed a Dick Tracy ride where you have a Tommy gun.
Where you have a gun, yeah.
So a blaster which is not a gun.
Not remotely similar.
No.
Everyone gets to pick one up and one of the things that's unique about this ride is that
unlike some similar attractions, the blaster is not attached to a ride vehicle.
There's no cord coming out of it, it's not mounted on anything.
You freely hold it, you pick it up and then you drop it back off.
So when you're on the ride, you can move around 360 degrees up and down and blast any direction.
So how is that calibrated so quickly?
I hadn't actually thought about how that worked until you mentioned it.
While they're on the conveyor belt, charging belt, that is when they get recalibrated and
re-centered to know what direction they're facing with the system.
There are sensors up in the ceiling.
I believe it uses ultra wideband radio, the same thing on iPhones where you can find your
keys now and it'll tell you where you are.
I also believe it's ultra wideband.
And then inside the blaster itself there are accelerometers and things that can get its
own orientation.
And so there are multiple systems getting the orientation of it and they all communicate
back and forth.
And that gives an orientation and position and angle of the blaster to the computers
that are controlling the screens.
For you, Van, was there ever any onboarding of wrapping your head around what all of this
is or is in the first conversation about this, are you like, yes, got it, I understand.
This is all just like, no one told me any of this, I had to figure all of it out.
I was given access to an internal wiki that explained all of this and I just on my own
read all of it.
There were these, to me, incredible diagrams explaining how all of the signals and messages
were sent to each other and where they were queued up within the system.
So it's possible that the typical writer on a thing like this may not dive into, may not
go on stealth missions to see documents that they were not specifically.
It came in handy as we were getting to the last phases of the ride and I myself, being
familiar with the technology, I had a sense of like, what could be changed at this point
and what's completely off the table.
And so we were pitching things like different sounds a blaster could make and things that
I, you know, the color that it showed when you were blasting a certain thing and things
that I knew were tweakable at this point in the process.
Wow.
Evan definitely had a technical knowledge and understanding that I think they were shocked
to discover in a writer.
I had the ride running in my office because I had enough of the existing technology they
were using for the ride already that I was able to run a version of the ride in my office
for Evan and I to like.
What does that mean?
What does that look like?
I brought both the energy and spirit and mind of a child to the process and was able to
just say, oh, wouldn't it be fun if you could blast really big?
Very helpful.
And you know what?
Sometimes that was valuable too.
And sometimes Van would say no, not possible at this point in the process.
You also picked up burgers once.
So you get your blaster and you walk onto a moving conveyor belt.
Sort of like the conveyor belts in an airport except this one can move around corners and
curve.
That's where I suddenly was because I think everybody was probably, you guys especially,
I would imagine, are wrapping your head around how is that going to work?
And once I saw the first corner bend, I'm like, oh, here we go.
All right, I get it.
That works really smoothly.
Can you all stand on spots too?
Can you explain to me how that works?
It's segmented.
It's in like a semi-circ, like crescent shaped segments that overlap.
And so that's how it's able to move.
But it is the same piece?
Like are we getting moved onto a different piece?
No, you're standing on the same piece that they just sort of are able to corner because
they're overlapping and there's a little more underneath and you don't really notice it.
But the floor underneath you slightly changes what piece of floor you're on.
You're illustrating things with your arms, which actually is very helpful.
But I'm going to ask you to do one more, which is what I'm on with the dot,
what do you know the shape of it if you were to take it out of the belt?
Yeah, it's like a half circle but a little bit of a crescent carve out on the straight end of it.
So slice a circle in half, you've got two halves.
But then carve out a little crescent on the inside.
Almost like a macaroni?
Yeah, it was like a macaroni piece.
Those are stacked on each other.
And so you're on that and then you're moving through different themed rooms,
themed to the Vicious Six.
The overall, when you get to that point, what is that within the premise of the convention?
Great, sure. So you're entering the Vicious Six challenge,
which is like a side event they're holding at Comic-Con that they've designed and put on.
See, the Vicious Six in Minions Rise of Gru kick out wild knuckles,
and so now they're down to the Vicious Five, so they need a new member.
In Minions Rise of Gru, you think that Young Gru might be the new member, it doesn't.
It doesn't work out.
So they're still in search of a new member, and so this could be you, the attendee of VillainCon.
And so it's sort of like if you go to Comic-Con and there's an activation for the new Godzilla movie,
and you go into a room and it seems like Godzilla's there or something.
It's that sort of experience being held at VillainCon where there's a sort of a separate
activation being put on by the Vicious Six.
And for them, it's because they're trying to recruit a new member.
They figure, where better than VillainCon, all the most villainous people are gathered.
And so you're being scored on your blaster, you're getting a score,
and that's all for them to judge whether or not you can become the next member of the Vicious Six.
Right. And you guys have worked on a Comic-Con activation as well.
Yes, the Brooklyn Nine-Nine Comic-Con activation.
And also the Detective Pikachu.
Unveiling of Detective Pikachu at Comic-Con New York.
I don't know if I know that. I don't think I knew that.
I believe that Ryan Reynolds was voicing Detective Pikachu.
You planned how to unveil Ryan Reynolds?
Dave Foley.
It was an insane one-day writers' room.
Legends of comedy. And I don't know if they used anyone's ideas.
I think they may not.
They may not.
Okay.
Well, and if we're, I'm sorry, you know, not to step too far off the moving walkway.
But if we're talking convention experience, Van, you've also, you've put together entire
conventions. You're one of the main architects of this ongoing convention called BugCon,
which is devoted to Bug Main, who is a hip hop artist slash cult leader.
And I feel like genuinely, it must, there must have been a lot of crossover between,
because BugCon is a pretty advanced technologically event.
There was a moment.
You essentially are almost doing solo.
That is where I don't think if you,
probably some people listening have been to BugCon.
If you haven't, and I hope there's a future BugCon,
it really is a technological, that you might think more people are involved in putting it
together than you very frazzled with a number of minions, you might say.
Yeah, but it is, I would say 80% me, 20% like a dozen other people.
And there was a moment where I was simultaneously working on VillainCon and BugCon 2022.
Wow.
I did, those projects did overlap.
But yeah, I have kind of become, I think,
entertainment's foremost expert on fake conventions, but that you can also attend.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That are actual experiences.
Real fake conventions.
That are very, that I've like, both very rewarding, both the universal one and BugCon.
Not only that, you've also put rides together as part of these.
At the last BugCon, you specifically-
Yes, we did have Spacey Mountain.
Spacey Mountain.
Which is a terrifying trip through the career of Kevin Spacey.
Which was a, like, it was like a headset based experience.
Yes, it was a roller coaster simulator experience.
With a fully fleshed out track that actually, that moved along, that was perfectly set up.
Yes, you sat in a chair that moved around and encountered big Kevin Spaceys.
Air that blew at you and they were-
More advanced than this minions ride in a lot of ways.
In some ways, in other ways, less advanced.
I mean, I just think-
Well attended.
I just think universal, like, lucky that you would deign to participate and give them any of your knowledge.
Well, thank you, that's a high compliment.
I appreciate it.
Yeah, no, there was a surprising amount of overlap there.
Yeah, and between everything, because, I mean, listeners are picking this up,
but if you don't know Van or haven't heard Van on other podcasts, like,
yeah, your technological experiences, I don't know, how do you, what do you even call it exactly?
Because beyond, like, your app awareness and programming awareness.
I'm a bit of a polymath.
I think is what you mean.
Okay, yeah, I wouldn't have had that term at the ready, no.
So, all right, so you're a polymath.
But yeah, you know, so I went to college to be an engineer
and I quit engineering school the first week and switched to screenwriting.
But I've always had that engineering bug still.
And so it kind of became my hobby.
I kind of describe it as like, you'll hear that there's like an engineer
who dreams of one day writing a book.
I'm like a writer who dreams of one day engineering a complex system.
Which to some extent, you have to feel like this is one of the biggest accomplishments,
I would think.
Yeah, no, it was really thrilling to work on it.
It really ticked all the boxes a thing could tick for me.
When you're, sorry.
Go, no, please.
When you're on now another shooter ride,
are you trying to break down technologically what's happening?
Oh, excuse me, blasting?
A ride where you blast.
You don't hear about mass blasting.
I mean, for better or worse, I think the reason I was well suited for this
is that has not changed for me at all because that was already happening.
You were already breaking that down.
Yeah, I was already like, okay, so on Buzz Lightyear Blaster,
the reason it's attached is it's getting the coordinates of
where it's pointed at by how it's moving and things like that.
Okay, feel free to not answer this or generically answer it,
but I imagine that with you guys and other people in the process at Universal,
there must have been some, let's say, judgment or comparison
to other recent rides of the blasting variety.
You must have been kind of like comparing yourselves against maybe,
let's say, lesser versions of the genre.
There was a very exhausting ride that's somewhat similar,
and we were keen on not having our ride be quite so tiring on your arms
while also feeling like you aren't actually interacting with it,
but I won't go further.
And you want to feel like there's cause and effect,
like there's actual that you weren't just flailing around with no specific,
you didn't understand, which is a big challenge when you are not seated,
when you're holding a weapon.
Is that allowed?
Can I say weapons?
Weapons last.
Okay, just start it.
I'll say weapon.
But like, was there ever anyone trying to back up and say,
let's not do a weapon blaster that says weighty?
There were comparisons to other rides made as like,
we don't want to be like this or that, both because that is a problem,
but also I think out of like not wanting to be compared unfavorably.
Yeah, you want to distinguish yourself and do your own thing.
You don't want what's different about an attraction just to be the IP or characters.
You want it to feel like a different experience.
Sure.
One of the leads on the project had previously worked at Disney
and had worked on Toy Story Midway Mania.
Okay.
So we were all very positive about that one.
Was there ever an idea to not make it just a regular blaster,
like something weird like a sword or something?
No, it was pretty set on it was going to be a blaster throughout the whole process.
The big conversations with it had to do with like,
how much functionality would be on the blaster.
Right.
You know, there was a moment when you would have more ability with the blaster
to be like selecting different weapons and cycling through weapons and things like that,
but there was a concern about giving too much immediate on weapon depth,
excuse me, on blaster depth,
and that making any riders who are not familiar with
video games of that genre and things like that too confused.
And also you want people to be looking at the attraction and not the blaster.
Blasters have these great little screens on them that let you know what projectile you're using
and what your score is, but it's also like this pressure to, from ourselves,
don't use the screen too much because you don't want people staring down at the screen on their blaster,
which we could show whatever we want on,
but we'd like the action to be out in the big world around them where they're built out columns
and kids are already looking down at their screens.
You know what? I'm looking at screens on blasters.
There you go.
I think the blaster, I thought it was very satisfying to hold,
and it is larger than some other blaster based rides, but it is very light.
Yeah, I mean that was definitely a challenge is figuring out what,
because all of the stuff that you put into it can make it heavier,
so making it not too heavy, but also having the functionality that you want.
That's...
Evan wanted a soda dispenser cut for weight.
Dispensing tech was like the soda itself.
And then just to finish the walkthrough of the ride,
you do the Vicious Six challenge, and each member of the Vicious Six,
whether that be Strongholds, Vengeance, or Nunchuck,
they kind of have their own room that they've designed that they have
their own kind of unique way and challenges of how you can earn more points,
cause more destruction.
Concluding in, and this is a little bit of a tip to, you know,
my fandom of wrestling, which Carlson can relate to,
Bell Bottoms tells you a version of Ric Flair is to be the man,
you gotta be the man.
It's to be the best, you gotta be the best.
And as a surprise, all of the iconic villains from the Despicable Me
and Minions franchise, you discover, are also there in competition with you,
whether that is Scarlet Overkill, Brat, El Macho, Vector,
and they come in and it's a fun thing that if you're riding the ride multiple times,
you might have a different version of who you go up against.
Oh, who takes lead in the ride.
Right, okay, so the first time you go through, you might be finishing a battle
with Vector and then El Macho comes in, and then the next time you do it,
it might be Scarlet Overkill.
So that's a little bit of variation and you have a face off against,
iconic villain and you can either win or lose against that iconic villain.
And that battle is happening, it's gotten so intense that it's blasted out into
Universal Orlando and you can see some of the iconic universal landmarks,
which was a really fun, I think, idea that Van and I really liked and pushed for.
Yeah, this was, this seems like the, I don't know if we can give you,
you tell me if it's 100% credit for that idea, but certainly like that it ends at
the practical universal skyline seem like a real victory.
I don't know what the modest way to say yes is.
It took other important stakeholders saying yes, and that's arguably as valuable as our coming
up with the idea for it. And it also took heroic efforts and conversations with universal legal
about the ability to blast at universal properties and objects and what could and could not be
included. Shooting a fart gun at volcano bay.
Well, yeah, cause you get sort of say what's on that skyline. It felt, it was,
it felt validating for me as a fan of universal Orlando and like the grandeur of universal and
like how, because I think for all the, you know, we'll get into a lot of complaints about
city walk Orlando, but I think a real victory is the big lake or the big lagoon, whatever you
want to call it with kind of like the primary icons all there. It's the studio gate for universal
studios proper. It's what's the lighthouse Jason, I cannot remember the Ferros lighthouse based on
one of the wonders of the ancient world. Ferros lighthouse. I keep thinking fanos. It's not that.
No. And then, and then it's not there literally, but the, the volcano bay volcano is there. And
then of course, most importantly, tooth, some chocolate, emporium and the big smokestacks.
So those are all lined up and a fantastic backdrop for a scene and they, you can damage them, right?
I feel like I saw a video with like cracks on the, the universal globe is there.
Certain letters can be shot to unlock something. Whoa. Wow.
Little inside tip. Geez. Yeah.
Just trying to think what word that could apply to the franchise can be spelled with the letters in
universal. And you might get there. I can't, I need to take a minute to figure it out.
There was a cut for time plan for tooth. Some factory to be able to have a sort of a chocolate
explosion. Oh, wow. That was sadly, we just didn't have the like a bandwidth.
When we were told that tooth, some could be included, I really went in on wanting to
explore the tooth of mythology as a part of this ride. Of course, at a certain point was told,
you know, he did pitch replacing the vicious six with Jacques.
Wow. Wow. He did not.
Was there an idea that when you start shooting or excuse me, you start blasting a tooth, some
that Dr. Tooth, some like comes on and goes, please stop.
My home. I'm running a business here.
In fact, there are no people.
In fact, no people at all.
Very good point. Yeah.
As you think about it.
Yeah. All right. If we're going to do that, no people, no, no guests, no executives.
Jason, are you upset at the possibility that your beloved Ferris lighthouse could be damaged in
some way? Well, I mean, I was going to raise more of the objection that if you were going from
right to left, you would see the universal arches before to some. And yes, you see it.
But, you know, I figured if it passed legal, that was acceptable.
Yes, this was.
We did have to take some geographical liberties for layout reasons to preserve the illusion
that you were looking outside of a wall. There's essentially a concern with the parallax effect
as you move past these screens because they are two dimensional screens. But you want to be able
to maintain the depth illusion the entire time. And so the layout and arrangement of objects
on the screen is very carefully done so that it doesn't suddenly feel like what you're looking at
what you're looking at isn't it doesn't have depth in the right way.
And I was the big one bringing up the parallax concern.
Yeah, I was kind of figured it was a parallax.
You call it the parallax concern?
Yeah.
Scott, you mentioned concern about two from being destroyed. The good news is when you get to the
next, which is called the kiss good night, which is a term that I had not heard where Bell Bottom
tells you, hey, you did a good job. You unfortunately, because it hasn't happened yet,
no one's made the vicious six, but you can get back and try again. But you can see behind her
that robots are putting back together all of the damage at the park. So that when you do the ride
again and you discover that it has not all been destroyed, it's built into the story.
What happened that it's being reconstructed. But if you do go outside the building,
I think you'll see a little bit of damage that has been done.
That's fascinating. Wow. Yeah, kiss good night. That's a good bit of terminology that you,
because we've talked about that as like a, I've heard that reference as a Disney thing,
where all the characters wave to you. Yeah, at the end of the night.
But specific rides, there is this desire to like give you one more little moment.
Yes. And I will say when we were down there testing out the ride and riding it over and
over again for two hours, they have an employee that is there. And I saw an employee who had only
been there for two hours, but could say the whole kiss good night word for word, because he heard
it over and over and over. So that was a unique experience. You don't think that when you write
something that someone was going to have to listen to it. I think that the origin of the term is
when John Lester was in charge of the Disney park. Upon exiting every meeting,
you would have to give him a kiss good night. He was really committed. He's the first one in
the morning and he insisted on being the last one to leave. The last one to leave the park.
This is for everyone. Okay, so you just referred to, Evan, you just referred to like
going down there, getting to test. Now here's the, I would like to get into the portion where
you guys make us jealous. Make us jealous of access and cool things. I mean already the
fact that you had a version of this in your office. What is it like, what springs to mind when I say
like some part of the process that you got to do and had early access to that where we would,
you know, nerd-gasm about it. I mean I hope we've covered it already.
That's right. We were getting to do it. So first of all, I was able to enter for a meeting
Universal Hollywood through Walters Gate. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. I mean we've drawn Walters Gate.
We walked through it. So that was my day. Every day was that for me. Yeah, that's good. I'm not
saying it's that good. I'm just saying we have to. That's all I'm saying. A funny thing that
happened early on was to test a version of the ride before it was up and running in my office.
We tested it at Universal City Walk in one of the theaters. Now we're talking. Yeah. Wow.
Wow. It got like, they hooked it all up so that we could use a temporary blaster that was built
out of like pipes. Oh my god. Yeah, that's great. Wow. And so that the levels could be
shown at the actual scale that they were going to be on the ride. Wow. Wow. Oh, so they're not even
necessarily using the entire screen. No. They're like showing exactly what it will be. Exactly.
So each level would be shown in different sizes. Geez. That's cool. That's really cool. And knowing
that like, you know, for anyone who thinks that City Walk is, I don't know, mundane or something,
that there's, you know, magic like that could be happening around any corner. Yeah. Wow. And then
you got, you made it down to Florida. Yes. I was there on there twice. I think Evan was there once.
The first time I got to go when the ride was mid construction. And so the demolition of Shrek
was complete except for a few, you know, like a donkey ear here and there, you know.
Gingerbread bits. And the rooms had kind of been like cordoned off and sketched out and they were
starting to put up some of the giant fake marble columns for one of the rooms. But it was like,
the whole place was kind of half constructed and that was a really cool experience to be inside of
a ride as it was coming together like that. Yeah. And then they took us to the, like basically the
universal R and D lab where they were working on the ride outside of that. And what was very funny
was right next to us, someone was testing a new iteration of the Harry Potter wands.
Oh, wow. Wow. So it was like a fake thing from a movie about how you would imagine this works
where like they're working on it right here and literally right there someone's got magic wands
and they're like pointing in that a bookcase that's lighting up. It's like the Richie Rich scene with
Professor Keen Bean where there's just chaos going on everywhere. It was like that. That's the most
famous version of what you're talking about. Yeah. The ride vehicles for the Velocircoaster.
There was a like section of track that could just go around in a circle that had the ride
vehicle on it that could move just around and around. It wasn't running while I was there,
but it was there to test something. Wow. The Velocircoaster.
So there are a few places where I would like for you guys to hear something and then
never reference it again and please bleep it out of the podcast. That's going on you.
Okay. Well, we could always use the plan that Susser instituted that our bleep is the song
moves like Bert that bleeped a story. The people are still kind of curious. There's been requests
maybe to hear a story, something that happened to you at Sesame Place in full. People behind the
paywall maybe are like, don't we deserve to hear? What do you think of that?
What do you have? You have the second gate is? The second gate and club three a little
further than that. Maybe club four. Okay. So once we do a club four,
you can finally hear the admittedly scarring, unpleasant, probably unsatisfying story.
Should we in keeping in the minion universe though, should the bleep on this one be like
happy or despicable me song? Maybe just a minion exclamation or something like that.
Yeah. So anyway, let's figure that out later and we'll get to the. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, we're on a little writer's room to figure out. You guys are the experts. You can tell.
What is the big new minion phrase that we could? Yeah. So next to us, I kind of snooped around a
little bit and I saw the. Wow. So that is okay. That's pretty good. Interesting. And just to be
clear, the intention here is to, you want us to leave in all of us going like, Oh, wow. Oh,
and then the listeners don't get to find out exactly what that is. Yeah. They're not going
to like this. Oh no, they're not going to like it. Well, they didn't, you know, they loved the
last time we did moves like Bert. Remember everybody was thrilled when I remember that.
Oh, this is deep story. This is different though, cause this is fun. The other two are awful.
This is the first step. Wait. Yeah. Well, that's maybe why the sound has to change.
It's like Bert is only for when it's something deeply, deeply unsettling. Yeah. Yeah. No,
this is great. So it was very exciting to kind of be inside the dream factory, so to speak,
seeing other things. And then I'll say back to the like, where any of like the dream come true. One,
one fun thing, you know, in addition to work on the ride, we eventually started working on
the greater minion land. Oh yeah. That's around there. And when we were down for the trip,
we got an email. Hey, we're gonna have to start this day a little early. Cause we got to do a
taste test at a bake my day of all of the cupcakes and treats that are going to be sold at the park.
Wow. If only you were there to have, you know, the executive chef at universal talking through
every cupcake and treat and all of the different flavor combinations. I mean, you know, I think
that they had really come to lean on van for his technical expertise.
But then we need you. So sir, Mr. Cesar, we noticed this white napkin that's been tucked into your
shirt. This month, for months in a fork and knife. Can you tell us something that you got to taste?
And can we use the same bleeping mechanism, even though we don't need to just here? Tell us with
something that you got to take a bite of a minion cupcake. Oh, whoa. Okay. Okay. Do not let that
through. I'm going to not. Yeah. Yeah. It's that. Don't worry. I, well, yeah. I mean, we can get
into some, some broader, yes, because this is part of there's the, there's the attraction. Yes. But
then there is the broader minion land, which connects a despicable me minion ma'am, which
has been there for a while. And then minion cafe, uh, which you guys also participated in. Yeah. I
think that that was a little, we were not as full time on that project, but they would definitely
come to us for a decoration copy and also a few items on the menu. Do you, yeah. So what made it
through that you, or do you need to look at a menu to know? I would maybe need to look at it,
but again, I mean, all of it was very collaborative. I don't feel the need to go through. I want to see
your initials next to everything. Something that I think we can take credit for that ended up in
the minion cafe, not as a consumable item, but just as a decoration, um, was as part of the
queue, uh, we were trying to figure out ways to, uh, stretch the production budget for the videos,
for the line, uh, to make them not repeat as often. And so we added some static cards that are sort of,
um, the sort of information you would be being told at a comic con. Oh yeah. Yes. You know, where
the, um, what the schedule is and things like that. Oh, all of the implications of panels. Yes.
That are occurring. I wait, the one I have in front of me isn't from the video part, but it's
from the, like the sign iteration of it. But I really liked, uh, mind control masterclass. You
all, you already RSVP'd. But all the, all the video still versions are so funny. And one of those was
a concession stand slide. Um, and for that we were trying to come up with what are some like
fun villainous items that would be available at a concession stand. And one of the things that we
came up with was, um, this, uh, villainous energy drink called manic energy. And, uh,
the artists did a great job designing the can. The can is available as a collectible inside of the
game. Oh, wow. There is a, um, a full size in the minions break room area of the minion cafe.
There's a non-functional, but full sized vending machine that has various items. And there are
cans of manic energy drink in the vending machine. And that's, that was one of the things where I
showed up and I did not know there was going to be a fully realized three-dimensional organic
energy drink that was, came, come to exist. Well, and it's, it's also, it's the most fun experience.
It's the most you thing also given your work with rain with rain energy drink is the official sponsor
of bugcon. Yeah. Yeah. So it's a real, you can really just like see straight through to,
there's a straight line. That vending machine is really fantastic in general that they're like,
I mean, it's like specific products you can read, but the, the, like that there's just a full, uh,
ice cream Sunday in there. The cafe, um, set deck people did a really tremendous job, uh, with a lot
of the fine details like that. The vending machine also has like exactly the right amount of bananas
to be not too many. Um, funny that they're even in there. A really functional amount. It's like,
one joke is that it's all bananas, but how satisfying is that the, the awkward spacing out
of selective rows of bananas and then just a random fart gun in the middle. Yeah. Fart blaster.
Fart blaster. Yeah. Sorry. Um, I, yeah, it is definitely a restaurant worth going into and
poking around details. I feel like you guys, I think there was a moment where you must've,
you were texting me because you were specifically working on the break room sign with a lot of dos
and don'ts. And I saw a little like a peek into the process of like, what are the kinds of jokes
that would be rejected for whatever like danger reason, minion unlike ability reason. Also,
there was a not to put, uh, there was a about the microwave not to put any, uh, any minions in it.
Because can you imagine a child would go home after reading that sign and say, well, they said,
don't put a minion in a microwave, but surely I could put my little kid brother.
And they may have just watched the flash and that would have been a whole thing too. So
I've shown some restraint and not bringing up flash gate. I don't think so much to talk about.
I was going to say that's what I thought, but there's a tease of this and business to go over
with Evan. Yeah, don't worry. We'll find a time to do it. I'll tell the story.
The fourth gate. Oh, that's not a bad combo. Um, you know what though? I'm looking at the sign
that you wrote van or that I assume you guys wrote together and here I'm looking at the don'ts list.
And one of them is don't, this is about the refrigerator. Uh, don't unplug to charge fart
guns. Jason was correct. No need to correct Jason. I think there was a bit of questioning
that's canonically called the fart gun. Yeah. This was a tough balance that had to be struck
working on a property that does explicitly use guns and knives and other violent while trying
to kind of tip toe around that. But, but yes, um, I feel like, I mean, these are all, these ended up
really funny, especially the last one, the last don't being don't replace this list with a joke
list. Um, and then like, I'm pretty sure, um, that's very good. Uh, and then like lots of,
like minions advertising their, uh, services, uh, you know, the one does lawn when one, uh,
one's a DJ, DJ Carl. And then this reminds me also that there is a poster in here that connects back
to the attraction for the cosplay contest. Um, and this really, uh, I mean, you, this manifests
in the line and in your pre-show videos, but also in the store after where there are minions
that are in costume as vicious six members or other despicable me universe villains, uh,
which is some very fun specificity and really good, like figures in the gift shop. The figures in
the gift shop are awesome. Yeah. Yeah. Um, I like seeing the presence of, of Brad of belt is our
bread, which also something we haven't talked about is the, the actual voice talent being part
of basically everybody returned to do the voices and we were lucky enough to be in the recording
session. So all of them amazing and so impressive, but especially for me personally, Trey Parker,
uh, was really wild to see him do his thing. He was super game to do it. He was really excited.
He's a big theme park fan himself. And so the idea of being a voicing a ride in a theme park was
really fun for him. I think that's chances of a South park theme park ride are very slim.
Given the, uh, some of the issues with the IP and, uh, the theme parks in general. Um, and so I think
this was like a big shot for him at, at theme park, uh, Oh man, immortality, immortality.
Yeah. Yeah. So smart. And, you know, I think, you know, obviously his voice talent, but he also
cannot help himself just being creative overall in general. And he was, you know, thinking he was
like, you know, wait, maybe I should do it like this, because I think if I'm yelling at them,
even though it's supposed to be intense, I think that, you know, you don't want to be only intense.
And he was, you know, really thinking about the, you know, guest experience of doing it. Uh,
Wow. Wow. So yeah, he did a lot of questions about, you know, what exactly is happening,
what are people doing? Um, and so that was really cool. Yeah. Yeah. Intimidating on any level. I
mean, what a cool, I can't, like, of course it's everyone who did voices in this really impressive,
but Trey partners, the only one for like personally, I would be just, yeah, there was a concern
that he would be like, who wrote this funny. I was trying to figure out the timing with, um,
the pandemic and everything of like, were there any remote, they were always record, like just
trying to imagine Dolph Lundgren or John Claude Van Damme plug setting up a blue Yeti mic in their
home. So the way these were done, they were remote, but, um, it would be the talent at a
actual, like local recording. Oh, okay. But no, but the director and all the producers and everybody,
they were remote. Yeah. Right. Gotcha. Yeah. Yeah. Um, correct me if one of these people is not in it,
but Taraji P. Henson, Dolph Lundgren, Danny Trejo, Lucy Lalas, John Claude Van Damme all appear in
this, uh, attraction or any of those. One of the names, um, that you said, uh, was not able to
appear in all of their dialogue is reuse. Um, as a result of, uh, but we, but we carefully selected
the reason you won't even be able to, I believe they were having a shoulder or knee surgery.
Okay. Does that narrow it down to somebody who like, I don't know.
Taraji, you just go too hard. Um, I would like to know a little bit about
this project or any other, any interactions with the mysterious voice of the minions, uh, Pierre,
what's the last name? I don't want to bungle a French pronunciation or is it just coffin?
What's the guy's name? Coffeen. Okay. Um, we did not have any personal interactions, uh, with him,
but we write a lot of stuff for the minions specifically for commercials, stuff for the
movies, stuff for this. Um, and the original minion stuff was recorded for this. Um, and what I can
say about the, the, the, the relationship is it's, it's, he is the minions. And so you can
give him stuff one of two ways. You can figure out the minion ease. That's the language, the
minions speak yourself, or you can write it in English and say in minion ease and he'll figure
it out. And it's kind of a balance between writing in those two styles. But you by now
are comfortable with minion ease. Yeah. It's, it's tough to put your finger on exactly how it works
and how it functions, but we can just kind of write it. And also, you know, sometimes he will
make it his own in his own sort of way. But he basically, like, you, you write it
in that way, you send it to him and what we get back and what's in the stuff always is just like,
it's great. Like he's, he's, he's the man. He's the pro at it. There's no concern about like,
well, we, we better be on the zoom on that one. Make sure he gets it. He might fuck up doing the
minion voices. No, no, he does a great job. Okay. What have, what have we missed? Um, any, any other
details you're proud of already? Like favorite parts of the experience? Uh, one thing I think
that, I think that there are, so in the minion cafe, it's, you know, the dining room is kind of
in different sections. And one of them is kind of the break room where the minions who work at the
minion cafe, uh, where they take their break and we have some, uh, fake motivational posters that
are minion. Yes, I like those. Yes. Yeah. Those are some fun to work on and come up with, uh, fun
slogans for, but I think overall the whole experience really was, um, like anything when,
you know, when you write a movie or a television show, it's a real question of like, what is this
going to be like when it, you know, comes to fruition? And I think the whole thing was pretty
wild of like thinking about it theoretically, but even more so being like, well, what is this actually
going to feel like and be like, and overall, I mean, the whole thing is a delight. Yeah. And
being on the ride was a wild experience because, you know, I've written TV shows and films where
I've been on the set and I've also watched the finished product and it was weirdly like having
both of those experiences at once, like being inside a fully like all four walls, no fourth wall
version of a thing that I had imagined. Yeah. Um, so it was a strange feeling to sort of just be
transported inside, uh, literally, um, cause when you're on set, it's a little different because
there you, you, the conceit that it's all fake is there because there you, there's cameras and
there's lights. It's still a process. Maybe there's like a physical item you thought of and like,
wow, there's one of those. Yeah. And then when you're watching the finished product, well,
you're removed from it because that's all on a screen and you're separated from the reality of
it. But with this, I was just inside of these imagined spaces and it was a cool experience.
Oh, and I will say one personal highlight. Uh, so, uh, our, someone who worked on this, uh, Carson,
who you guys believe, so there is a theme park tradition where the names of people who worked on
an attraction are, uh, put hidden somewhere inside the attraction. And there is, you know,
a hall of infamy when you get to the end of this. And he had taken the Liberty as a fan of both
podcasts, the ride and no boys that a commissioner Evan is on the wall. Yeah. Um, and that was, uh,
that was a real highlight and van Vandal is the van representation. Yeah. Yeah. He shows up as
vicious van. Oh yeah. There was some politics. It was the main name. That was the main name of the
the ride and that I would somehow, uh, step on that cause confusion. But going back now to what
I said about, I mean, we couldn't, we probably can't talk about more, but you two now are in,
in the universe. Oh yeah. So they could be characters. No, that when I, when I, uh,
obliquely referenced some sort of possible ride spin-off that was the van Vandal and the commissioner
and ride that would also be film. Yeah. Which ties together, uh, the despicable me universe
and the doughboys universe migration thing now. Yeah. Yeah. Um, and then lost continents going
away for this new expansion. I heard. Yes. I also, and I don't want to correct you, but I don't know
if you know that your name isn't actually, it is the commissioner. Oh, it's a commissioner.
It does not say, Oh yeah, it's even better. Um, wow. You're just breaking his heart. I'm just
stating the commissioner is better. Um, because last names were not going to be allowed. So
commissioner Susser, while that would have been very fun, last names were not going to be allowed.
And then commissioner Evan is not what I would have liked to let you believe it forever. It would
have been better to let you believe it for. Yeah. It's more canonically correct. Yeah. Um, I don't
know how I was the one telling Mitch about that. Mitch didn't know that there was this permanent.
He did. He did. This is me telling him something he'd already heard, but it was in one ear.
Well, maybe the listeners to these shows will have a chance to tell Mitch themselves and it'll be like
the first time he's heard that. No, I have never heard that. Definitely two people have never told
me that. Um, can I ask, did either of you come up with the phrase Agnes's honeymoon soup? No,
actually that was, I think that that was already by the people at minion cafe. Someone came to that
and that was considered a, like almost a North star for all of the, for all of the food items
on the menu. That's the level. I only bring that up because that was my lunch. The very
Oh, and how was it? It was good. Yeah. I liked all the food. At the minion cafe, uh, you know,
we were involved in the names. We've not, we're not involved in any of the, uh, preparation of
the food or anything like that. So I feel like I can somewhat objectively say, I think it's,
if not the best, some of the best food in the park. It seems like reviews. It seemed like what
Jason said. And let's, let's, uh, let's talk about those tots a little bit. You have this,
I like the tots a lot. Yeah. What's the official name of the tots? Does anybody know?
I think it's just minion tots. They're more like crispy outside kind of mashed potato inside.
And the minion faces represent it's kind of like smushed into the potato piece. Well, well, cool.
Yeah. It seems like you got an iconic new snack there. Did you, sorry, did you say anything when
you tried it? Was there anything like, you know, these tots are salted too much or anything. Did
you say anything along those lines? Just, just a little bit of a like plus up. So I can say,
um, for the, uh, there's a lot of, uh, purple evil minion desserts. Yes. I drank the drink. Yeah.
Sure. PX 41. Um, but there's a, uh, some purple, uh, minion cupcakes and things like that.
And there was during the taste testing, some people concerned about the flavor, um, being,
seeming too medicinal because it had that sort of diamond tap grape flavor to it. Yes. And I was a
big defender of diamond tap grape, one of the all time best flavors. Yeah, I hear you. Um, and I said
to me, that's, that's a plus. And they kept that then. Here's my thing is that the flaming
Mo is not medicinal in the way that it was described on the episode of the Simpsons.
And it's still, I think the same kind of like orange flavor thing. And it should be more like
cough medicine or something. I think so. So speaking of the flavors, I have to say the, uh,
the, there's some, uh, dipped popsicles that they sell there and we got to try those. Those are
really good. Um, and the vectors orange popsicle has a great orange flavor. Okay. Okay. Um, and the
banana flavored minion one, they've got a terrific banana flavoring going on on all of the stuff at
the minion land. That is not the like candy banana flavor you're used to. I don't like that
flavor so much. So I know I don't know. I haven't had the universal. Okay. Yeah. I'm like curious.
Banana runs flavor. I don't like people to put them to banana runs. I'm not, I don't like them
personally. I don't like the people. I guess actually it came out, you know what? It really
drives me nuts. And I start to dislike people that don't like banana. I have to admit it here.
Why does it shows up on every podcast and creates discord. You just blow up the banana runs. He
always brings banana, but I like banana runs, but, um, I understand. I guess if you don't like it,
like the other flavors though of runs are okay. Yeah. I just, that banana run flavor is not to me.
What do you think of a banana runs? I like it. Jason. Uh, I like it. Isn't there a whole thing
of like, Oh, that's how bananas used to taste. And that one is exactly. Yeah, right. That's a
common old wise tale common knowledge. Are you in the middle on banana runs? I'm trying to figure
out. No, I like them. Okay. But are you saying that because I'll hate you forever. Are you afraid of
you need to curry Mike's favor in this tense situation? I, uh, my fists are clenched again.
Jason, you're either with me or you're with Mike. Choose, choose your favorite. They do this every
time. Please help. Help. Help. There's always so much pointing in these records. Yeah. Uh, anyway,
I should have tried. I really now, now that you're talking about banana runs, now I'm more excited
about going to try those, but not doing what van is because it's the, it's not a similar, right?
So you will never eat the banana stuff down there. Yes, I guess not. I guess I'll try it,
but just only to get mad just so I can make myself upset closer to run flavor. Um, I have one more
cafe question on the second gate. We just did an episode about the today cafe, which is a nearby
restaurant. And I watched a video where Al Roker was, um, talking about his new butternut squash
tart at the today cafe. But he also talks about the minion cafe a little bit. And he says that
he had a dish that, uh, that was meant to be minion brains. That is something that Al Roker
said on television. I do not know. Can you shine any light into the process? I have no idea what
that is. I think what he's talking about, um, and it is not meant to be minion brains, but it's
the udon noodle soup that is served inside. If you follow it, a lot of steps. If you haven't
heard the second gate episode, and please check that out if you want, if you want more cafe talk,
uh, but it's like, there's like a, uh, it's a translucent, it's a bowl, uh, with a minion
face on it and you kind of turn it over and dump it. Um, and it's yellow noodles. So Al just took
that as his, his brain saw that for interpreted that as minion brains. And then he goes on to say,
uh, kind of grim, but tastes good. It's a tasty dish. He was, he was like upset by, he thought he
was devouring the brain. He thought he was doing Ray Liotta, uh, eating a brain. But, uh, I think
it's a fun, uh, fun accident. Uh, that's true. Yeah. Yeah. It's open to anybody can interpret it.
However, I have another, I have another good little funny story. Well, involving food while
we were there. So, uh, at our lunch, uh, from working, uh, there was some, uh, writing the,
I had to get done for, you know, I think for the ride that I, you know, had to do at our free time
and I was like, okay, I just need somewhere to work inside the park. So, uh, I think with Van,
we went and we just got a quick burger, uh, at this burger place. I'm like, okay, I'll set up
my laptop here and I'm working. I'm trying to focus. I'm like, you know, as far as places and
a park goes, it's just a burger place. It's relatively quiet. And then all of a sudden
a simulated earthquake began because I was in Richter cafe, a themed San Francisco where there
were earthquakes that regularly go off. So I didn't know that about Richter cafe. I've never
been in there. I know that name. You get an alarm and rumble. So it's not, not the best place to get
some work done after all. That's very funny. And some new information to me about Richter cafe.
I've never had the pleasure. How was the burger? It was good. I thought it was good. Yeah. Yeah.
Not as good as making cafe food. No, no, no, no, of course not. Um, I, uh, what else on the way out?
And you've been working with it. You requested a pen over there. I don't mean to start if you're
not ready with whatever you're up to. I've got one thing that I want to do. This is just a fun
little surprise. It's going to involve some bleeping though. Okay. Got it. We've got the
sound effect where I say, yeah, pleasant bleeping or unpleasant bleeping. Pleasant,
pleasant bleeping, but it's because I want to do something groundbreaking on the podcast. Oh my God.
Um, so we cannot say what it is, but, uh, Evan and I are working on another piece of themed
entertainment and, uh, a full, a full physical spacey mountain. I can't, I can't get into the
details of what it is, but I actually have part of a script that is in process, uh, between Evan and
I, and, uh, because I was busy with a bug main concert, I didn't get back to Evan in time with
this work and this is due. And so what I'm going to do right now is I am going to do a little bit
of our work on this piece of themed entertainment live on the podcast. So this is, we're going to be
really quick here, but this is going to be for a piece of themed entertainment somewhere.
And it was given notes were given on it and conversation was had live on the podcast.
Wow. Wow. So here's, here we go. You're hearing the creative process. So some of it,
Evan, uh, you've got these lines, uh, in the intro, uh, for this character.
And I think they're good, but some of them are a little long. Uh, and the windup lines specifically,
I was going to say brevity is probably important. They're too long. I don't know what they are,
but they're way too long. Um, so I think we should do another pass where we just trim down
the length. Okay. Sounds good. That's it. Okay. Oh, okay. We don't get to hear the lines.
Wow. Okay. I got to hear a little bit of the process. So you might be somewhere on this globe
hearing a line and then you might think that was the perfect length for a line to be.
Work that happened just now. You will know that it was tuned up, but that ultimately the length
Evan got there, but Van really caused the length to be perfect by giving the note.
That's correct. Can I ask why you needed the pen?
To figure out what needed to happen. I hadn't read this at all. Oh, so you literally,
that was a live thought you had. During this podcast, I have been working on this and
noting this up and figuring out. What the fuck? Did you tune out when we were talking about
banana runts or something? Yeah, I love banana runs, but I wasn't paying attention. So you just
said something. Yeah. Wow. And so that was a live come up with note. I didn't come in with that
note. That happened on the podcast. Geez. I think it's cool. I guess I don't like that you're kind
of like double dipping that you're on the clock with multiple things. You're here getting a very
generous guest fee and then you're also accepting another salary at the same time. But I guess it's
that double up that lets you accomplish so many things. Contractually, we're allowed to do anything
that's not interfering. And so I think that that meant I had to get that work done while I was here
to really prove that shit. It is allowed contractually because we don't have a contract. So really
anything is allowed. You could do, you guys could do what anything goes. Yeah. You're not even,
it's nice of you both to like participate and talk at all because that's not even something that we
contract. No, no, no. Yeah. Yeah. You could, you could just sit here and not tell us anything.
That's true. But I guess it was more fun that that you talked and told us behind the scenes
information. Can I ask one question? Yeah. How many different behind the scenes bathrooms did
you get to go to in Universal Orlando? Stuff that's not available to the general public.
Two. Two. Anything unusual about them? Eight.
You had two scenes right? Okay. Okay. And did anything like interesting or scandalous happen
in any of the bathrooms that we show? Okay. Okay. Okay. Good. That's good. So we'll lay off on the
bleeps for now. But I, hey, if that kind of winds it down, then I think I can say,
Evan Susser and Van Roche, you survived podcast The Ride. What a blast. Thank you for all of your,
your not only behind the scenes intel, but doing behind the scenes work right in front of us.
Thank you. Yeah. Fascinating to see the process. And Evan, I am going to do a pass on this. I'm
not actually just kicking it back to you. What if he wants to, maybe you want to get your,
get your hands in there. I don't know what we had to bleep from that. I said the name of the
character. Yeah. Yeah. Wait, can you tell us what that is and we'll bleep again? What property you're
dealing with? No, no. Unfortunately not. No. God. Shit. Yeah. All right. Then you're not even. Can
we Google that name figured out? The name is not out there? Oh, interesting. Okay. Wow. This isn't
a name that's out there, Puck. So you, I mean, in a way we don't have to bleep it because it's not.
No, you do. Okay. You do. But we haven't signed any NDAs. Do you need to make us sign an NDA
before, or maybe we just wrap this up before we get out of here before you can make us do that.
And then we can release whatever we want. Can we name a couple of movies real quick? And you say,
yes or no. I'm writing NDA on my knuckles right now. Land before time, right?
Wedding pressures two now done as a ride and not a film. Oh, you got it.
Wow. But we need your help to do the ultimate wedding crash. We can't do it alone this time.
Seems good. Yeah. Getting to crash it. And then you're in like a wedding crash or vehicle using
a wedding crash or on the tram tour and you have to come in and be like, I'm on to you. My private
eye. He looked into you guys. You gotta see he's not doing all the rides at this point. He didn't
do rocket in Florida. Wedding. You know what? Well, tell me where fake nose.
Then he's in. Can be even bigger than the previous wedding crashers as a, like a bar or a club at
old pleasure Island would be a really good idea. It's a wedding every night. You're always crashing
your always crashing a big wedding and it's all just the tropes of a wedding. That's a great,
but there are characters playing. There's going to have to be a few performers, but it's of course,
as the years go on, there'll be fewer and fewer. Yeah. So there'll be like a bride and a groom by
the end. Kind of like a Tony and Tina's. Yes. Oh, which we didn't do this year yet. I wanted to do
Tony and Tina's wedding this year, but we didn't do it. I would love to do Tony and Tina's. They
have, yeah. How do we do? Where do we go? I don't know if it's running right now, but we'll have to
figure that out. There's a nice Peter out. Yeah. So yeah, Tina's performance losing after the dessert
course. All right. I had a good idea. And then, okay, well, we forgot one thing, which is exiting
through the gift shop. Yeah. Is there anything you'd like to. What I want to plug the ride.
Yeah. Go to the minion blast. Oh yeah. That's right. Wait a minute. Wow. For the first time,
one in the same, the plug and the topic. I don't think that's, uh, well, maybe to some extent it's
happened before or people are on plugging something. This is perfect. Wow. Symmetry. Yeah.
Doubling up on any, anything else to throw up at you. I feel like I'm throwing it to you,
Van, because I feel like you've got like 20 things going on at any given time. I'm also pretty busy.
He's got like alternate realities happening at all times. Yeah. You know, you know, or apps or
whatever. Is there anything you need anybody to get in on? Uh, just, uh, just follow me on Instagram
and Twitter at Van the brand. And you could find out what I'm up to and visit my website, van.link.
Great. All right. Great. That's all. Van.link. Um, okay. Well, I suppose that does it. Thank you,
gentlemen. Uh, for us, you can find us on the socials at podcast, the ride merch is available
in our T public store for three bonus episodes every month. Check out podcast, the ride, the
second gate, or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three, all of that at patreon.com
slash podcast, the ride, where we will be airing all of the non bleeped versions. Yeah. Everything
that we've said, Susser's story included. We're just going to put it all as one big audio file.
So for, uh, exclusive, uh, illegal Intel go to our Patreon. Great.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts,
please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.