Forever.
Dog.
The podcast, the ride.
Welcome, people of podcasts.
Podcasts.
Podcaststers.
Podcastians.
Citizens of podcasts.
Does anyone know what they call themselves?
Do I do the whole thing?
What? I'm on?
Someone needs to tell me when I'm on.
Welcome, podcast Terrans.
The biggest thing fighting me, do I do that,
is the opening, was how long
it would go.
I am Centurion Scott Kierner,
joined by Nova Prime,
Jason Sheridan.
What a title.
Head of the Nova Corps and everything.
Yes, you're right in league
with why Nova Prime,
can I find the name and the notes
quickly enough?
Do we know Nova Prime's name?
I don't know Nova Prime's name.
Wait, I don't.
We've got some work to do.
Joined also by, apologies, I have no more
of these terms.
I have no more Zandari in terms to apply to Mike Carlson.
I ran out, I'm sorry Mike.
That's okay, because you're limited to what the information you have
from the ride, the pre-show is.
So it's not like you're dipping deep into the Marvel comics.
You only know the ride.
This is the definition of what I only know
from the rides.
I looked up other Zandarian titles,
but those wouldn't read.
Those require explanations.
You're right, because
the entirety of
my Guardians of the Galaxy experience is the rides.
I still have not seen any of these films.
Oh, interesting.
Have you seen clips of anything?
Have you seen Baby Groot dancing to Mr. Blue Sky
from the opening of Guardians of the Galaxy 2?
I have not actually.
I think you would like that.
I think that's maybe the only thing you would like.
Maybe there's a few other things.
Baby Groot dances while Mr. Blue Sky and the other
Guardians are fighting this big monster.
So it's mostly while Baby Groot dances
and they're fighting in the background.
Why is he Baby Groot by in...
What is the Baby Groot switch?
At the end of Guardians of the Galaxy 1,
Groot sacrifices himself
for the team.
He kind of blows up.
I think they take a piece, Jason,
correct me if I'm wrong, they take a piece of Groot
and plant him.
And he slowly grows.
So a new Groot grows.
With a different character.
At the end of 1, you're like,
I thought we were saying goodbye to a great character,
but now in number 2,
we get to deal with what this is going to be like.
And then he kicks off and he's dancing
so we know we're off to the races.
And then he slowly becomes like
petulant teen Groot.
In the later Avengers movies.
Well thank you both for explaining
to me the events
of probably some very famous
and commonly viewed films.
Films.
I know, I know.
Now Scott has to be babysat
through the events of
very popular movies.
Well I just, you know, might come up in the conversation
here today.
Look, it all sounds
very nice. Do I have any
desire to watch any of these movies?
No, no, Guardians of the Galaxy.
You know, I have long time listeners
know, I'm not a big Marvel person.
If I had to watch any, it might be these,
because Guardians of the Galaxy has produced
some pretty exceptional rides.
And we finally get to talk about it.
This is a big one.
This is long overdue on our part.
We have had since May
2022 to talk about
this and we have not
all been to Orlando to get,
has anyone missed it? I forget when you went before.
I went in November
2021. So I saw
the destruction site.
This past time, it's
like, okay, Guardians is open,
Moana is open.
Which I'm sure we'll get to
in a future episode.
The beautiful
fake rocks and water
fountains and plant life.
But operationally,
a panic attack. I think it was
worse for Jane walking around.
But just observing, like,
okay, half of these people
are just walking through. Half of these
people are stopping dead in their tracks
to take pictures.
Half of them are reading the sun.
It just seemed
a little confusing.
It's certainly some places were close quarters.
Certainly in certain places.
Very close quarters.
I hear you saying there's a lack of understanding.
Is this a thing where you,
do you treat it like a line and do you do every step
of it or do you just move
through at your own pace? Which I think is what you are
interested in.
It was very, the walkways were wide.
With the scooter, I certainly
was able to navigate through
easily enough. It was just,
I think, yeah,
if you went at a slower time of day,
it was probably lovely.
I like getting wet from the spray.
I like getting sprayed.
So here's a preview of
Journey of Water. That is the name
of it. I'm not mixing it up with because we got
Way of Water. Journey of Water? Yeah, I think so.
We'll learn that by the time
we get there. But today, it's
Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind.
I'm so happy
we're doing it finally. This is like
the best of the best that we get to talk
about now that we've finally been
in. Big basics
to talk about before we get
into specifics
and what it is and
story and the order of events.
It is the first
Disney Marvel
ride in Florida.
They finally were able
to get away from the
ironclad but very brief
universal contract that
excludes most of the characters that they love
to make attractions. Which I didn't realize
goes back to 19... It was agreed upon
in 1994.
Wow. So then by the time it
actually gets
built, Marvel is in
bankruptcy reorganization.
Like Marvel is struggling
when it opens
even though
just run of cartoons
in the 90s. Like very
kind of prevalent in the
90s. But I think the work
around is that these characters are not
present in Islands of Adventure.
You have to not be present
on a wall.
You have to not be present and also they can't
say Marvel in the
marketing and signs and stuff.
So they can say Guardians of the Galaxy
but they can't say Marvel's Guardians of the Galaxy.
Right. I think they can say Marvel
in California Adventure
Now. But they can't
do it in Florida.
And it's really funny that the
Guardians of the Galaxy have two
major league rides in Disney
parks because of just
like legally what happened.
Like it's just if you said that well
you know 30 years ago, what
ride, what characters will have like big rides?
You'd be like well certainly there will be
a Fantastic Four ride and
there'll be Avengers and of course...
X-Men. X-Men. Yes. What about the
Guardians of the Galaxy? Oh.
The characters from the year
3000? Yeah. What?
Yeah. I
was wondering that like did you, well your
relationship to these characters in this
were before the movies. I mean I... Very much
its own vibe and different things.
I will be honest. I had not read, there was a
good, something that I think
inspired, for sure inspired the
movies. There was like a
pretty well reviewed run
by Abnet
and Lanning. Yeah.
That I think got
people sort of interested again. It wasn't like
a big comic book, whatever a big comic book
hit is in the year
2010. The 2000s.
They kind of revitalized all these characters.
They had this big annihilation
storyline and it brought
a lot of them to
the forefront and that's a lot of the inspiration
for the movies. Except
there
is a character named Nova.
There's been a couple Novas.
Richard Rider and
Sam Alexander. Those
were not used in the movies
but the Nova core is
used in the movies. Yeah, you know you pick and choose
some of the mythology but I
will say I hadn't read that run
before the movies
came out.
I knew Rocket Raccoon.
I don't know that I remembered the name Drax.
I knew Groot of course
because Groot is a funny thing that he only says I am
Groot. You maybe could name
most of the Guardians of the Galaxy.
Yeah, I don't think I knew
Gamora. In the 90s I don't think as a kid
I could have said Gamora or
Drax. I don't think so.
You were where I am now. Basically, yeah.
Having been on these rides
multiple times. There was a lot of
70s characters.
There was a lot of cosmic Marvel comics
in the 70s. Stuff that wasn't
like in cartoons. I mean maybe
some silver surfer stuff. Rocket was kind of a comedy
character and
So it's funny. It's just funny
that there's two major like this is a crazy
new coaster and this is the Marvel property
that it's based on. Which I'm happy about. I like
the vibe of the movies
a lot. Yeah. Well and not only that
yes. It is inspired
some of Disney
Imagineering's best work of the last
decade. Yeah. But also
in this year
and the year that we are wrapping up
2023, the only bonafide
Disney hit Blockbuster.
In an absolute catastrophe
of a year box office wise
for Disney. The only one
there's only two that are like clearly
wins. One is Guardians of the Galaxy 3
and one is Avatar Way of Water
from last year. Right.
Which Variety just talked about how
Avatar made more money
in 2023
than the new most of the new
2023 movies. Haunted Mansion, Indiana Jones
5.
The Marvels trounced
by the runoff of Avatar from last
year. Yeah. It's interesting seeing
that. The Guardians because the Guardians really
did resonate I think more
like the first up until like Endgame
Marvel was very
much like had the momentum of
like you got to see it all because it's all
going to build to one big thing and like
even if there was a movie that you felt like was maybe less
good or you didn't attach to the characters
it was like well you got to see it because it's going to be
very important at the end. It might have a little connective tissue
it's all going to come together. Right. Right. But then as soon
as Endgame happened I think people were just like
alright well done. I guess we finished
it. So then when they start doing a bunch
of new stuff and then and how dare people
tap out after
22 films and shows.
That's what I said. How dare you
think you've had enough.
But then when they try to launch a ton of new stuff
and maybe probably overextended themselves
then it was like uh oh
we're like starting in a way starting from
scratch I think. And I
don't think they maybe expected it. I think they kind of
were thinking the momentum would carry all of it
through forever. Yeah.
But so that's why I think Guardians is like
well actually that's pointing to like
the audience really likes those characters.
Like that really resonated
with people in a way. It seems somewhat self-contained. It obviously
like attaches to the broader
Marvel narratives but it's like if you
could only watch those and have a good
experience and not feel confused
by well what is that reference and what is
this building to. And made enough of
an impact that director James
Gunn is now in charge
of DC movies. Yeah.
Entirely. Uh huh. Which is going
great. DC averse just
rising and rising straight to
the top. Everybody's happy.
Well yeah there was that video
that trailer video where it's like
alright we're going to start off fresh
with creature commandos.
I was like what?
Well Gunn is going to bring the magic to creature commandos
like he did with the Guardians. You know?
Yeah. You know I guess. Have I said this on the show before
James Gunn months before getting
Guardians. James Gunn did a bunch of trauma
movies and some other like really small
indie type things. Uh huh.
And like months before getting
Guardians judged
a live show Jason and I did.
Oh. That's called the Tournament of Nerds which
I still do it here and there.
He did a couple times. Wow. I think
so. And it was like literally
a couple months before and he was
set to judge again.
And he got Guardians of the Galaxy all
of a sudden. Wow. Cause like
what he says I think he like really like
went all in on this pitch at Marvel
and got it. And he
actually I think had agreed to judge
before he got this. So he was
set to be back and I
and another person were like we gotta get Jason
out on stage in a Rocket
Raccoon outfit. Oh yeah.
We're gonna have the worst smeary
raccoon makeup. Yes. So we were
like fuck. James is gonna be here.
We need to do a bit on stage where Jason
is Rocket Raccoon. We have to pitch Jason
for Rocket. And then
before the show happened James
pulled out. James pulled out went with
Jackson Maine himself.
You know Mr. Silver Linings playbook.
Bradley Cooper. Fucking Bradley
Cooper over to Jason Sheridan.
Just because of name recognition
and awareness Bradley Cooper
was like in front of him all the time. But if Jason
Sheridan had been in front of him once.
That's what we were thinking. I could
have charmed the pants off him.
That's what we were gonna do. Yes. We were gonna try
to do it. So anyway. Did you have a sense of how
because it was pre the voice that we
all know and love to do.
Did you have a sense of your
Rocket?
It would have been pretty close honestly.
It would have been a little more
old timey. But I think
a little gruff New York. I think
I would have tried to do
a universal Hollywood
New York's you know.
Hey.
Hey Mr. Gun. Hey
it's Rocket. You know.
You like these rock and roll tunes. Why don't you go
back a little farther and sing the
old ones. What do you think?
Boogie Woogie Bugle. My Bonnie
lies over the ocean.
You ever thought about a
rocker who likes public domain.
You don't have to
pay for those songs.
Is that nice? Give yourself some scratch.
You think it's far to get to
Terra. You know.
It's a long way to Tipperary
my man. I like that he's like
oh. Like he's a cat like a
Grace Clay or he's an old like at skill comedian.
So like you want a real you want a real lived in
hard boiled New York voice.
Hey Mr. Gunn.
Or if I did a real hard like
Philly dialect
and then that would have made him go like
Philly huh? That reminds
me of that Silver Linings
playbook movie. Oh it just brought him right back.
It was an
inevitability. So I don't know if I've said that
on the show before but I swear Jason
was weeks away from being Rocket Rec.
That's how I say it. That's how I tell it.
Weeks away from bothering
a man. Weeks away from bothering
Mr. Slither
himself. That's right.
Geez. Ships in the night.
Could have been.
Well anyways yeah we've arrived
here. They finally they've planted the Marvel
flag in Florida.
This is a huge
technological leap forward
roller coaster. The very first
ever Omni coaster.
I forgot that they invented
that term. We have advanced
from the Omni mover
which spins and pivots
and allows the audience to look at specific
elements and kind of direct your
field of vision on rides like Haunted
Mansion or Little Mermaid. And now
this can be done on a rolly
coaster. Pretty incredible. What times
we live in. And I don't
want to like jump
too far. We can go through our experience
of this emotionally. But I feel like
I heard this. I saw this.
Sounds cool. Alright spins
you can look at stuff. I watched a video of the
guys testing it outside. Going
on a little like not fully
track of it. Or finish track
of it. Looks cool cool.
Was looking forward to it cool. None
of it prepared me for how great
this was in person.
No I know. I absolutely
completely agree. I completely blew me away once actually doing it.
And I still now I found myself now I've come back
I'm telling people Guardians is great. They're like what's
so great about it. Well it's the individual
car spins so you can like look at stuff and you can rotate around
and nobody's getting it. Nobody everybody's
the same as I was. Just like oh yeah sure
sounds okay. I like you you have
to you have to have been baptized
in the Omni coaster
to have the enthusiasm about the Omni coaster.
I completely agree.
It is like I don't like
yeah it's I was trying to describe it to people
and I felt like I was doing a bad
job. I couldn't articulate exactly
what it was but I was like
I think I said something along the lines of like I've never been
handled like this on a ride.
Yes. I've never been like
in some giant. You still
new technology after new technology
managed to find weird creepy ways
of saying everything you like. That's true.
You find a specific
ones for every new one that comes along.
I've never been finessed. I've never been
caressed. Caressed
like this on a ride.
I've never been taken care of. Finished. I've never been finished like this.
I've never been completed like this.
I was about to say I've never been completed.
I swear. But now I'm a completer.
You kept going
and spoke more normally
about it at some point was like
you know you go on a coaster you expect
certain
ranges of movement
and like high grids you
launch forwards you launch backwards
but then the surprise of the drop
is unusual. It's unusual
but it's still I've been on a thing with a drop.
But this
is so much unusual movement
forward
backwards spinning
in dark net so it's your little
off kilter. And the lights
are adding to that
like you never I mean it's like Space Mountain
where you never really get a
handle on where you are and what's
going on and then you add spinning to that
you add lights that sort of never stop
to that. The project
the lights the star projections
are really good. I mean it's really
new.
The screens are really good
in it. And I
definitely watching videos that was able
to follow like the story
more. Yes.
Coming off it I had no
idea what happened. Even ride
even the gist you
get the gist of it riding. You get
the bear. But I don't think I knew
when you were launched backwards that is
the big bang. You have been sent back
in time to the big bang. That is
not remotely.
But it's a great it's
you know it hits that theme parky thing where you like
you don't need to know any of this.
You're not going to be lost. You're going to enjoy it
no matter what. You land at the same
space as Space
Mountain where like there is
no story. Yeah. Like you could
and then those specifics
and if you learn about it and
you know understand it more it
adds texture to the experience. But like
if this is just if all you if you just go
on this once and get get handled
you're going to have a good time.
If you get handled on this ride you're going to
love it. This
and then I guess I can say this and
Velocicoaster
I haven't been on rides in years
where I just every like
every different like movement in turn I just
go wow wow. Like I'm making
noises like confused
noises that were also delight.
Like I couldn't kind of like whoa
what. OK. What.
Like we did other
new rides that were good good
rides but I wasn't sort of shocked
by them. Oh yeah.
Which is a tough bar for a ride. But
obviously like the greats
are the ones that do
something completely new. Yes.
I guess like the first time we went on like the
trackless ride vehicle for Pooh's Honey
Hut we were like huh what.
Like the first time you're in a new
you're being handled a different way
is very surprising and if it's fun
it's fun it's really fun and I felt
that way on this ride and then on Velocicoaster
at Universal.
Maybe a good new tagline for Walt
Disney World in general. Walt Disney
World will handle it.
Will handle it in a new
or unique way.
Get handled like
you've never been handled before.
That's really
what's going on here. So you're going to love the way
we handle you. We're going to. We guarantee it.
We guarantee it. We guarantee it.
The
what other first
this is the first roller coaster
at Epcot. Right.
First Disney
backwards launch.
Backwards launch which is catching
on I feel like.
I was trying to figure that
out. What is the history
of backwards
launches and because I could not
you hear it's the first Disney one.
Right. OK. So other places have done it.
And you're like where. Like there's not like
a really famous or prominent
backwards launch unless I'm wrong.
I looked up examples but do
you guys in your head have all there's this.
No.
I don't. I'm not really. I mean Hagrid's
has a lot of tricks but I
think the backwards version is you go
backwards. No no I'm just
saying tricks in general. When you go backwards
it's the old edge of
the track.
Oh yeah sure. Yes.
Yeah. And that's what a lot of them are.
Like other. There's a
lot of rides that launch you backwards
and then you're right. Like kind of you
hit it. It's different than Hagrid's but like you hit a
dead end and then you and then go forwards
from there. Like yeah sorry.
But there's not a ton of
backwards launch and then you stay backwards
or backwards for a very long
time. I think they'll run like
and I forget the names of all the Superman but
the Superman at Magic Mountain which is just sort of a
shoot you up and then back down again
but I think they will run that backwards
sometimes. That's called Superman
Escape.
Superman Escape from Krypton. And
I think it's maybe. I think
do they change it? Like it's sometimes
it's backwards and sometimes it's forwards
or the different tracks do different things.
This is something called Full Throttle
at Magic Mountain that launches backwards.
That's not the bar though. It's not the Full Throttle
Lounge. Right. The very
classy Full Throttle Lounge.
There's something called Mr. Freeze Reverse Blast.
I don't know where that
is even.
And then something called
Revolution at Blackpool Pleasure
Beach in England where you get to
they launch you back and you kind
of like stall up at a certain point for a
while and you stare at a different show
building that has a big Wallace and Gromit
on it. Oh that's not
bad. I don't like that.
I mean that's not related but it's just
an added bonus. Right, right, right. But
I mean it is this is
instantly I would say the
most prominent backwards launch.
Yeah. I think so. For sure.
And it kind of in a way it isn't a backwards
launch. It is a regular
launch because the vehicle never
changes direction but your cars
spin. Which lets you
get out of the territory because it's so
like you got to switch tracks basically
if you want to go backwards. Oh yes. For the most
part. Again, listener
correct me if I'm wrong. If you've been on a great backwards
launch let us know. Let us know.
We don't want to neglect it. But yeah
it's kind of you get a backwards launch and then
you spin around
the other way and then keep spin.
It's every type of direction
you could be on a coaster.
The manufacturer of this
ride is the roller coaster
company.
This is like comic books where
I read someone's name
but haven't said it out loud.
Vcoma or Valkoma.
Oh yeah I've seen that name.
Other Disney collaborations
with them include Big Thunder Mountain
Tokyo and Paris, Gadgets
Go Coaster. Oh wow I didn't realize that.
Expedition Everest.
Wow. And
one of my first
launches maybe I've ever
ever did was Rockin
Roller Coaster. Baby's first launch.
That was my first launch too.
Which is a very intense
even still is a very intense
launch.
It was terrifying the first time
I ever did it. I would not
I don't need to do it again.
If a group was doing it I would do it again.
But that's a little bit
above my threshold.
I was pretty shocked the first time I did it.
Fun certainly but like
that's right above my intensity line.
Right. But Slinky
they have figured out how to do
gentle launch. Like Slinky Dog Dash
has some gentle launches.
Yeah. Yes. Very relaxing.
Well this new when you get a new
just smooth ride. It's
so much of it is that.
Just the fact that like if Slinky Dog did all
the same stuff but it like jittered
around a lot. You'd feel
over handled. Yeah.
If Slinky would like turn and point
you at things to show you toys
in Andy's room. Oh sure.
Then yeah. We're going to have to start
spinning on everything I guess after this.
It is kind of hard to go back
once you go on a ride that like it feels
like this state of the art.
I mean it's not really that hard but it's like kind of
where you're like imagining it. Like I am
upset that we don't have a Velocicoaster
or a Cosmic Rewind in California.
Because I think if I went on for the first
time I'd be like I'm going back tomorrow
or next week. Like I have to figure out
how to get on this soon.
Yeah.
I totally agree. It like haunted me.
I was like we only have a couple
more days and they're busy days.
I'm not going to get back on this. It might be
years before I'm back on this and I've been
thinking about it a lot. I think about both
of these coasters a few
times a week since coming back.
We did. One member
of our party was kind of defeated
by this ride. The Celestial
Ison kind of
center. I was wondering if you would
address this. I will address this.
Jane
immediately
the train pulled up to
the offloading
and was like I am going to be sick
and ran to
a trash can.
And I think I
was not that sick but cast
members very
prepared with both
barf bags and little
bottles of water and these
little hand towels which
we found in our luggage.
We sold a little hand towel.
This one was not used.
The one that she dapped her mouth
was thrown in the garbage.
But this one we
just kind of ended up back with us
that I think we found the other day.
So you got a free towel from All Fisky World.
Got a free towel and free little bottles
of water. Now this is what I
like. This is the smart Jason where he
really takes advantage of situations.
You got a free towel from All Fisky World?
The smarter way to take
advantage would be because you had
to endure, Jane had to endure the vomiting
in order to get the towel. The smart
move is to fake the vomiting.
Fake it and get little waters.
Now here was how the
events, we all
got off. She was sick. I sent you
guys onward and I'm like I have
Pepto-Bismol. I'm going to sit with her
and make sure she's okay.
There is a bench at the exit
which is unusual and I was
told that bench was
added later on.
A puking bench. It's a
collector's help bench because what happened
as we were sitting on the bench
I watched the two track
sides. I watched the trains
pull up and I watched a handful of
people also get
off this ride and walk
to the trash can and be
sick. I watched
and I talked to the chaos members.
I was just like, does this happen a lot?
They're like yeah, it happens.
Did you see
you don't have to say specifically, did
you see a large amount of puke being
produced from everybody including Jane or
was it just sort of like a dry heave?
I think there was some dry heave, some spit
and like bit so.
Did anyone throw up a full set
of wings from the Odyssey?
I didn't see
your scotch bonnet pepper went in.
That would have hurt
on the way out. Food
and wine, people are eating and drinking
all morning, all afternoon
and then getting on Cosmic Rewind. I wonder
if it's common for people to throw up a ton
of food or it's just like
that weird sick
feeling. When you're in a car and you're
reading or you're looking at your phone too much
and you're not driving.
I wonder if it's kind of more like that
or you were seeing just tons of puke.
I think it was just a combo
of like we had shared
a fruit and cheese thing
and I think she
had too much dairy
and like a side salad
at the end. Meanwhile
I talked about this on the live show.
That day I had eaten
cold brew Danish
crab legs
crab claws
half a cheese plate.
And I just hopped on
Guardians and hopped right off.
You ate the crab, you were eating it on
the ride as well. I was eating it on the, I was cracking
crab claws as
Congo was playing.
Let's, here cut this if this is too much information
but at some point in this conversation I do
remember you saying to Jane
that you were, you're
worried in general about it because
she mainly ingests
salad, coffee, and weed.
Yeah, that is
that is part of
our food thing. Obviously
in Florida we weren't having
much of that.
You know, just the salad and
coffee. Well coffee can upset your
stomach and too much greens
that's too much, that's a lot of
fiber, you know.
And too much other greens and ooh
now we feel like we're on Cosmic Rewind all the time.
Yeah.
I am Groot.
Well I was, yes
everybody go we got so high we thought we were
Groot. That was a teasing line.
Whoa you were smoking baby Groot man.
He's a little bud.
Oh that's enough, Disney wanted to get into the market
and make joints that look like little
Groots and like you're burning the hair
of Groot. That's right, that would be
great. Yeah, start making that dough.
They need alternate revenue streams
ESPN shit in the bed and all that.
Eiger, your answer is
They're starting that ESPN
betting app too.
You're going to be able to bet on
your phone. Oh goody.
Just start character
themed joints.
I hear ya. Yeah.
Then you can skip all that stuff.
Yeah.
That was kind of like a teasing
line. I think that was more of like
I don't know if this is ideal for your
stomach but she loved the ride.
She had a great time on the ride.
I think her
I think she said what she
did her in was
there was a moon
set piece towards the end.
You're shot around the moon.
And I think she was focusing
on that to try and
steady herself. That was a very dizzying
effect to stare at things.
Your car is going around
it and you're also spinning
like I think it was too much.
I don't blame her at all. You have to
calibrate to what this is
because as the sounds you were
making Mike it is very like
oh huh, oh okay.
You don't have
I certainly didn't have experience
of a similar thing. So you're
figuring out on the fly how do
I not get sick in this?
And it was I think by the
you know I barely survived not getting sick.
She you know she has a bit
more of a gentle stomach and I
occasionally do but often
it's an iron stomach.
It's either
iron or gentle.
Which is not ideal either.
So it'll surprise
you. But yeah so
I think like this ride
I had
never seen so many people come off a roller
coaster and run for the
trash can. And then the
other you know I was taking the
elevators but the design
I was like there are a lot of stairs
up and down after you do
this dizzying ride.
Yes you walk right downstairs
I think out of the exit
area yeah. A space mountain too.
That's true. There's some
guardians yeah if you're on the second level of guardians
at the California
California Adventure one you have to
go down this big set of stairs.
I will say this
I could feel in my
stomach where you
could get sick. I was I didn't feel
like I was going to throw up or even close to it.
But I could feel that like kind of again
being in a car and
looking down your phone and like the motion sickness
of it. I could feel where it would have
happened. Yeah yeah well like what
part of your body could have been activated
but wasn't. You know when I had a bigger
problem which I wrote out
I was fine I just had to like cover my eyes
but we finally towards the end
of the day did
Remy's Red Tattoo adventure
which was mostly very pleasant.
I think we talked it up in our in our episode
with Taryn I think we were very positive
about it but I also think like thinking
back on that episode we were like finding things to
poke at about it and when is it in the timeline
and this and that. I feel like it maybe
maybe I at least underrated
the ride in my head a little and I was
on it thinking like well it's not like a blockbuster
like this it's not like
Guardians but it's a you know
what it is it's a it's a wine ride
it is like it's perfect for World Showcase
it's perfect as like it's it's gentle
it's it's culinary
but there was one part and I don't
remember at some point something
about 3D and screen
curvature and yeah probably
overindulging all day
finally added up into like
okay glasses off looking down
got a tap which doesn't happen to me
a ton but it did on there
sure yeah there's opportunities
that I've got. Also unconventional
movements added in with
3D glasses. Yeah
yeah yeah. This
ride I was I
did keep my
glasses on because I
wanted to be able to see all the like
story beats and I'd seen
a video of Mr. Morrow riding
it. He kept his glasses
on so I was like okay I feel better
but I put my baseball cap
in the well the Dirty
Mesh Pouch. Dirty Mesh
Pouch a cousin of the Dirty Yellow
Strap of course.
And now we welcome to the show the newest
member of the five timer family
Mike Losing His Hat on Guardians
Cosmic Rewind. Mike Losing His Hat. I look I know
it was going to come up here and the discourse
around it is um is really
wild. People can't stop talking about it since
we brought it up. Everybody has very strong
opinions on it.
Every like we said this a couple
weeks ago is that
I left my hat on as
did Griffin who was sitting next to me.
And Mr. Morrow also
in a video had a hat
on. Yes. But I think a tighter
fitted flat brim hat. And
in case you didn't listen
I had a bag of some of stuff
that I was trying to cram into the little
thing in front and I didn't even think to sort of take
off my hat. I don't always wear a hat so
sometimes I forget I'm wearing it. And
what happened is I lost my hat basically
on the launch. And
in the photo we have a photo which I forgot
totally the order of events on this
because I did not this is new information. It's
kind of fascinating that it is like right
at the that somehow
for all this talk of uh you've
lost that and Griffin took his off
the photo was taken at a precise
hat oriented moment. Yes. But I think
one of you is even holding your hat.
Well we're both holding our hats I believe. Griffin
has more of a hold on his which is how
he kept his and I'm holding my brim.
And the hat slipped
out of my hands is my
memory now. I see. On the launch.
Because all of a sudden it moves and I went oh
shit yeah my hat is oh yeah
I'm wearing a hat and then it slipped out of my
hands and that's when I just turned to Griffin and went well
lost my hat. This is the backwards
launch
or? Yes on the backwards launch. That's when they take
the photo. That's the first yeah the photo.
And then yes that
is when I had my interaction with the employee who
was uh couldn't have been
more irritated with me for
just asking a question. Which is where the discourse
which is where I'm a little bit
online people are like well yeah
he should have been rude to you. And I'm like
I didn't yell
at him I didn't say I want my hat
give it let me walk the track. The people
who listen to this show and root against
the hosts.
I'm glad Mike finally
got what was coming to him. I forgot
I don't know and also as Griffin pointed out
like the woman whispered to her you may
want to take off your hat to him
not to me. You know what it wasn't even I wrote
because I remember the the term it was like
you may want to hold on to your hat. Yes. Right right.
Which I keep thinking is like something that would be said
at the beginning of like an old VHS
where like a youth pastor raps.
Yes. You may want to hold
on to your hat. Here we go.
Jesus is the way the only
way.
The person walked
by on on
my side of the train
the roller coaster
car. It is called a train.
I'm not making that up.
But someone did really
quick. No one mentioned the glasses
but they were like careful with that hat.
I feel like. Yeah. Well
so I lost it and then I think I was
very nice. So is there a chance you get
it back. Like how does that work. And that's when
the employees very rude to me
and acted like well somebody told you right that
you should take it off. Kind of.
Not really. I don't want to
is different than take it off. Yeah. It was like
I didn't defy someone who told me
to do that. It's like I'm just asking if it's possible
to get back and how would that work. And that's when
someone's rude to me. But then they were very
not the other chaos. Everybody else was very
nice. Yes. Until
until the listeners. Until yeah until
we saw some of the listeners who were like yeah
asshole should have known better. Yeah I guess.
I don't know. I wasn't
entitled. I listened to every episode
with my finger up ready to wag
at the host. A wag from me.
I forgot I said I think I forgot.
Like I wasn't even. But again you're an old
theme park cast pro. You know
that is how unconventional
the motion of this ride is.
Don't call him old. Be careful man. I mean
you're a young person. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. I am. You're
thank you so much. Yeah. I'm going to edit
it. I'm going to edit the old part out anyway.
So don't worry about it.
I go through and make a pass anytime.
Now here's what I think. If
they really want
if this is like so severe of
a thing. Yeah. That it needs to be said
and not just repeat
like don't put it on the cast members. Don't make
them say it over and over. This should have been
attained in the dialogue
from Centurion Talmeric.
Right. Original character
in this ride as portrayed by Terry Cruz.
Confusingly Terry Cruz
in his pre-show spiel
which I nodded to at the beginning of the episode also
is very firm about no
recording devices allowed.
Right. Which is weird because you
can watch many videos. Everyone
records this ride. Taken by recording devices.
So this the one that they gave to Terry Cruz
is ignored
roundly. Yeah.
But the one that seems like the most important
the biggest like divisive
issue is not addressed by Talmeric.
No. Talmeric doesn't talk about hats.
There should be a lot more hat stuff in the
pre-show. Every character should remind
you to remove your hat. Yeah. Yeah.
And just one more time real quick.
Because I'll steal it
because you know I like the pilfer.
There should be like a
version or the Tom Jones
version of you can leave your hat on
by Randy Newman but you can't leave your hat
on. There should be like a parody of it
to just drill it into your head
that you should you got to take your
hat off. This is crazy. Don't leave
your hat on. Are you crazy?
So they should be addressing it
in multiple ways I find. Yeah.
OK. So that's a plus up. Every
single and we want to see
icons do it. Yes. We want to see
Pratt and Batista have
to do. Right. That's what the dialogue
about. Yeah. Funny Batista
lines in this. He has
a few good ones. He's
pretty funny in these movies. I
feel like we talked about this before. Is Batista
how is
does he have the best filmography
of? Of a
professional wrestler? Of WWE stars?
More than Hulk Hogan and
Santa with Muscles and. Oh yeah.
You got Santa with Muscles. You got Thunder in Paradise.
You got what's that what's the
Suburban Commando. Suburban Commando. Yeah.
Well I think
Batista I will give him credit
for like wanting to do
like a range of things and being
interested like wants to do interesting
things and like isn't too worried
about like losing
in a movie.
I have a tough time
putting the phrase best filmography
on a
filmography that includes Stuber.
I mean. I said
a range of projects. I mean
The Rock has some duds.
Cena's been having
fun recently. I feel like
he's been fun in recently.
But even Batista I watched a video
of him writing this for the first time.
And he was pretty thoughtful
in his like analysis of
it and did seem emotional
like excited to be like I'm in Disney
World now. Like I am a
character in Disney World.
That's what you want people to appreciate
it. That's the main thing if they have
if they've attained the ultimate goal
for some on this Earth.
Yes I want them to appreciate it. Yeah.
Know how crazy it is.
Well got to ride together. Of course
Mr. Marlowe got to ride with Aaron Paul
of Bryan Cranston. That's right.
Which they
seemed pretty excited to do. There was no video
of that. There is no video of that.
I don't believe. But yes you can
video this as much as you want
apparently. I think well I think there's
you can strap a GoPro to your chest
or your head. Oh maybe.
Some of the videos I watched.
Just holding it would be too much. Yeah. Holding
it I don't know if I would trust myself to hold
onto it.
I caught video from a preview
where halfway through
the ride stopped and all the lights
came on so you could kind of see how big
the girders were
and how big the building is. The show building is massive.
It's massive. Yeah.
Yeah I've heard
it's the size of the contemporary.
Oh my god.
That it has the volume to hold four
Spaceship Earths inside it.
Yeah. And there
is
there's a moment when you arrive
in that show build
it's dark so you never get the
fullest sense of it.
But kind of early on there's
enough light that you could sort of see the scope
of where you've just landed and that was a huge
yell of oh my
god to me. Realizing
like oh we haven't even started.
We aren't even in the building yet.
And it's already we've already done backwards
it's already all been very exciting.
We've got a great queue with a fun magic
trick and hang on only
now are we get it and we get to be in this
room for you know what the
two and a half minutes at least.
I also say about there is a lot
of discourse online about the actual show
building itself because you can see it.
It's painted blue
which let's not go away green obviously
what's the name. Is there a name of that blue
that's a blend in the sky. It's like a sky blue
that they try to make it. Blow away
blend away. Blend
away blue let's call it.
I will say this I didn't really bother
me. There was some people saying oh it's too big
and like it's not hidden at all so like you
can see it. But actually I really wasn't
like annoying to me in any weird sight
line way. Not that I care so much about that
but I was thinking oh it's going to be
so jarring. It was being discussed as if
this is like a true blight
on Epcot. And they they preserved
the universe of energy building.
Well part of it yeah.
Is mostly the queue and
the wonders of Xandar. The wonders of Xandar
which is this
I think I mean we certainly
made fun of the Chris Pratko and like
oh I can't wait to get back to
Horizons
or whatever that kind of. Veggie veggie
fruit fruit. Yeah yeah.
Yes.
Which is this the first Disney world
appearance of the idea of someone
being sad. Their child
their drives are gone.
Well here's okay.
About this beat
and we I didn't see it in
person. We kind of I didn't realize it was a thing that you
move you can move fast very quickly. It's the video in the queue
and I think we went by it too quick.
The queue is like an Epcot
world showcase
kind of pavilion about this
other planet. Yes.
Just kind of clever. It is they refer to it
as a other world showcase.
So you are getting a
it's like a little like
it's you know much like the
yeah you're going to Norway and you're going to
learn some stuff about Norway but it's that for
Xandar across the galaxy.
And we can talk about some other
stuff in there. But while we're talking about the
the scene starring the
film separately players.
Right.
I mean
yeah we didn't get to see it in person but rewatching
I think like that is a
criticism that I have is that the
if that's the joke that
he can't wait to go do
all the stuff that he did as a kid
there's no payoff of that joke.
There's no part where somebody's like oh
somebody nudges him and like hey
bad news Star Lord.
There's no like the
other person doesn't exactly like do a double
take of like oh we got
a little bit to talk about we'll be right back.
There's no acknowledgement. If that's the
joke it doesn't work. They don't telegraph
that joke whatsoever.
It's probably because
they wanted to nod to stuff.
But then somebody looked at the copy
and was like we can't
we can't admit
that people might be sad coming to
Epcot. Yes.
Yeah. And we can't acknowledge this thing
that we've let these I
feel like a lot of Epcot stuff got
yanked out without kind of coldly
and without the realization
that people grew up with these things
and cherish these things. Right. And this
is a fun way to acknowledge all that
but they don't want to
acknowledge the other side of it which is
the sadness and
the fact that they do
want to keep trotting out figment
for everything but improving the awful
scourge of a ride that he is the
star of currently. Yes. I think that's
probably what happened
where it was like I'm sure somebody was
like oh yeah and then he'll say oh
but actually the rides aren't here
anymore Star Lord. I have
one note for this.
And this was we were dis Twitter
canceled for this for making fun of this
for daring to make fun of this scene
where all of the actors are not
looking at the same eye line
Chris Pratt keeps looking off at a second
direction almost as if that is where the
teleprompter is and you maybe
kind of feel that Chris Pratt has I don't
know never heard of
any of the things he's mentioning until
the second that he's saying them.
I have one note here that would help
you can't help all that
and none of it is that bad.
We're teased and it doesn't like drive
everybody crazy or anything.
Could you get one more take
where he doesn't say the Vigi
Vigi fruit fruit. That's the
problem. I can't wait to see Horizons
and the and he really slows down
it and the
universe of energy dinosaurs.
He could not he was not keeping those
those words in the right
order in his head. The dinosaur universe
the energy of dinosaur universe
and then
and then he gets to and here
the Vigi Vigi fruit fruit. Who
would ever say it that way with
the that's the strangest grammar.
Nobody says like you're right but
I kind of like it. I can't wait to hear the
it's a small world because it's kind
of funny because like it's almost like what your
grandma would say if you had been to F
got 30 years prior and she's like
what was that song the
Vigi Vigi fruit fruit song.
That was a nice song.
You're right but I think you're giving grandma too
much credit. Grandma would even remember
that much. She'd go like remember the fruit
concert. Well
that's true. The also
you know when it came out online it was in
like full HD red camera
whatever in the
right it's like vertical screens
and it's got a million filters on
it's a little maybe glitchy or
hazy. Yeah the treatment's
kind of interesting. I didn't
even really we just went by
it so fast.
I caught it as we were like leaving the room. I was like
oh that's the thing. We just passed that part.
I did see the little
I didn't make the connection to
I kind of got with I got what they were going
for in the line which is there's
a little model of like
the Xandar capital
and they play clips of Walt
doing the Epcot
movie the Epcot TV
presentation.
Are there Walt clips in the cube?
There are Walt clips. Yeah trying to make the
connection of like oh our home plan
is much like this experimental city
he wanted to build
and I'm like okay yeah that's kind of I kind of
like that. The Easter egg I
really like that I did not pick up
on until I read about it
and then watch the clips.
The electric there's a moment
where the Guardian
ship is going by
the giant celestial
who has taken
the cosmic generator MacGuffin
and the electric guitar
song that's playing is an electric guitar
cover of the original Universe
of Energy song.
I saw that mention and then I was listening
really hard for it and it is hard
to parse.
It's not like the most prominent. I didn't notice it when I
was there. I didn't notice it when I
was there but watching it enough
times I could hear it.
Is it before the launch
or is it? Yeah it's right before
the launch the ship goes by
and he's like what is that noise?
Okay. And Star Lord says
a line about like you can't
yeah you can't destroy
rock and roll. A little like guitar
kind of a waly version
of it. Yeah. Yeah.
I think this wonders of Zandar
construct is pretty
clever and it's a fun
nod to Epcot history and a way to justify
it being
in Epcot.
What I do
find funny is
okay so because there was
when this got announced
there was an energy
the announcement of this ride that was like we're going to do a
Marvel ride and okay but but but but
but but but but it's going to be acknowledge
the history you see and it's
going to be we're going to
edutain as well and it's
going to be kind of like an old Epcot pavilion
you see and and Star Peter Quill
he went to Epcot he was there
he was there so this is going to be fine
don't worry don't worry
it all reminded me of like I was trying to come up with the right
scenario of what it
the tone of it felt like
to me which is like imagine
that like there's a like a parent
who's getting up there in age who has like a
like their house that's their special
house that they want to keep you know I just where I raise
the family and I want to keep it in the family and
you know in the autumn years
the kids go to the parent and say like
we will never the how we
know we know the house is special
to you it's important and we
will never let it go because that's
because the house is who you are
and we promise that we will and as soon as
the death happens like alright flip it sell it for two million
sell it to some company
hey alright let's split that up alright we did it
we ran the money
boat money boat money
but they have to do because
we know we know Epcot
important to you we know that it is
and we would that legacy
we would that's why we edutain
we don't just entertain we edutain
and Peter Quill was there
he went as a boy your mother and I
love each other very much but
but but
this isn't your fault
and a universe of energy going is
not because of you it's not because you
put too much stress on this park okay
and don't ever think that
you're describing
that situation that I said
and then what you're describing is
coddling somebody
during a period of bad news
or during a period
the other one was like if imagine
that like they're going to take
that right near Williamsburg Virginia
they want to like build like a Ross
and a five below yeah and they have to go
meet with the residents and do a dog and pony show
for two years and go like and that's why
we will honor the
that we are going to call it founding
father crossings
so it's going to make us all the
sense here in Williamsburg because we
acknowledge the history
and we celebrate it and look there's
going to be we're going to do it with like big
columns there's columns there just like
Washington Monument had history
so we celebrate history here at founding
father crossings and then it's
just this awful place of the
Costco and like Disney's
America next to the Manassas
battlefield full of bullets and
bones it is exactly
that it is them having to say
like and we know people
died on this ground and that's
why we will honor them and
we will
put a grave satone for figment
in this ride
you can honor figment on your way
into the roller coaster
bring flowers for figment
you can do that every day bring purple flowers
to figments grave
we will never stop that at the security
line the figment
uh uh uh Jane and I
did ride Journey into imagination
and we when we were getting off
we saw the figment photo
spot and they're like oh
well figment will be out in 20 minutes
and we looked around there's no one in line
and I was like I guess the
five hours wait dissipated
pretty quickly that was a day one
and we're like we are running out
we do not want to wait for 20
minutes we are running out of time
oddly proportioned to
figment anyway I don't
I say all that to say like I don't know
that I think it's just funny
that they had to do that
and that people bought it
to some extent and then you get in and
what it is is like it's kind of a fake Epcot
pavilion
and there's this one scene where Chris Pratt
is saying words he doesn't understand
okay we good we good with that
and I don't know what
side I take in this exactly
I guess I take the side that like
isn't it better
for everyone if there's a big ride
in Epcot center that everybody's going
to and doesn't that create
more traffic that goes to the
to the classics and to the old school ones
like Spaceship Earth right living in the land
like isn't that your better way to get
new to get fresh
blood in a different audience to
the you know the old school
vibe of Epcot that remains yeah
well that's a that's the larger Epcot
question that seems to be debated
by I don't know I would
assume it's a small percentage of theme
park goers online
I think most people go there and they
go what's a good ride to go on
it's this one okay who cares
movie we liked okay
yeah yes
well hang on does this tie into a broader
theme does this fit into the vision
that Walt Disney had years ago
having seen the movie I think
the thing that kind of stuck
with me
I haven't watched the third movie
yet I heard there was some animal
experimentation so I'm kind of building it up
I'm kind of bracing myself for that
oh god
high evolutionary it's too
complicated to explain I understand
kind of why it's in there but um
the thing
with
guardians and especially the Peter
Quill character in general
there's a lot about
him being melancholy for Earth
because he had this whole childhood
and then he was abducted you know
and his connection is
all the pop music it's all the pop music
it all starts with the death of his mother
correct yes
and so
he is a character that
occasionally there's some sadness
to and I guess that's all of the
guardians characters are all kind of drawn
together by their
you know hard times in the past
and that got me thinking of like
oh this is another
thing that connects him to
Earth which he very
rarely gets back and now I'm sad
now he's got yeah he gets back
to Earth and this is he gets
what state is Epcot in oh my god
it's so different
and it's not even teaching me anything
about the motor vehicle
industry yes I don't
get to know what new vehicles general
motors has for 1990
my look I'll say this
about it I think you're correct
do I wish that they could
have just kept up all the like
all the different dark rides that were
edutainment and horizon
do I wish horizons was open of course
do I wish they just plused up
like world of motion and made it like
cooler and kept it yes
I do and then added rides around
let me on the record say I
completely agree with you I think like
the Epcot problem is not
doesn't start with guardians cosmic
rewind the Epcot problem starts
with taking out horizons in the
old school and an original journey
maybe primarily
yeah that's that all feels like it
was done in a real short sighted way
yeah and that
guts that completely guts the history
of the park because again we want
a mix of these places to be things you got to
go on as a kid that have been plused up
and kept in good shape and then new
cool crazy stuff
that's just like state of the art so
that's kind of gone at Epcot other
than spaceship Earth and I
living with the land
but that like that's that's sort of your
two things
there that like you went on if you were
a kid in the 80s or 90s and look at the struggle
though to that they wanted to
do the plus up of spaceship Earth and then
it's yes budgetarily
and let me say this
I alright everybody get get your
anger rising okay I know that we
I know that there's all this love
for living with the land but don't you
feel like it could
be kept up a little of course
I'm looking at like literal like all Epcot
big patches of dust in that
thing like I was pointing out like
Epcot is tired of many even old brooms
lying around which is why
I like when they seeing that they do
a holiday overlay
I'm like that's something and again I think people
are mad at me about living
with the land but if you go back a lot of
my argument is like what do we have here we've
taken away the old song
that was good we've taken away the
live uh tour
guides and I think you just do
some past that's like improving
it aesthetically lighting is
better I'm sorry about
like corn kid and bean boy and all
those people but maybe that could all be a little
brighter like does it detract
from the current living with the land
to brighten it and
freshen it by 10% yeah
I mean all the plants look great
they certainly keep those up they better
they're new they're as fresh
as can be I thought the forest scenes
looked really
good this time I will say
I think I've underrated the
beginning of the ride because I was on there
I was trying to like it more I was trying to see what everybody
sees I like the beginning of the ride more
I was however explaining some things to
living with the land newbie Griffin Newman
and he would say things like
what's up with that window up there is that just
like an office like why is that there
said no that's a restaurant that overlooks
the ride
and then I said well that used to be
a revolving restaurant that has not revolved
for many many years
that doesn't sound good does
it there's all these things that are like
oh that used to be that way that used to be
that way here's a theory
that the living with the land
outrage people are clinging
to living with the land so hard these
days because there's not much left
right yeah it's something
I can appreciate that I still appreciate that
or world of motion we're still
around you might be able to get away
with your living with the land slander
in a different in that world
this is all we have how dare you
come I'm not asking for the ride to be
that's the vibe doubt I'm not asking for it to
go away yeah I just
like I think that like
I feel like that like a budget
that would go to like a
a healthy like
a haunted house display
in somebody's front yard
I think that for ten thousand dollars
that's a very expensive house I know
but you know what I'm saying I think for not a lot of
money I think everybody could like kick start
the level of improvement that living with the land
needs here's what I don't want this to
spiral out of control here but I will
say this unless we're going to do a full another living
with the land episode my needs
it's one of those keeps regenerating
I will say this
yes I was checking for
fast path or genie plus on
the boat but I was for acknowledging
I'm sorry I doubted
you it was very important though what I was doing
it was I was trying to optimize
the long getting set up
and it was a big pain in the ass to get it set
up so I was trying to optimize
but I'll say this the first part
even though it's not sort of kept up
it still is the
vibe it still got
the old school vibe
dark ride wise who is
somebody I apologize if this was maybe
this was Kevin Tully somebody was saying
that it feels like the it's like
there's like a natural history museum vibe
yes I which I totally
like it would be better with the song
I agree but
the smell the way it's all set up like
you cannot ever recreate that
so I was like
I like this when it gets to the
lab part and the plants
it's
anticlimactic it's just like
wow
listener quote put a quote around
that and give it to Mike Carlson
take some heat away from me
please it's burning up over here
I believe this though I believe that if the
listeners think about this themselves
they will find it in their heart they don't have to
say it I will take the bullet for this
I will you don't have to admit it
but deep in your hearts you know that the
dark ride portion is the
part worth saving is the good part
the other part is fine it's just that
it's what
is this we're looking at plants and they
say oh you can eat a burrito
that has this bean in it like
wow like I feel like I'm
getting a full body massage right now
what you were the weight you were taking off of
my I'm just saying that the listeners know
I feel like you're taking a bullet for me Mike and I appreciate it
well yeah you don't have to thank me
I'm just saying that if the listener
they might have some affection
for this part of it but obviously the magic is
in the first half of the ride
we gotta kick it right to Jason because you're the only audience
surrogate here in this argument
I like that portion I think it's
very relaxing I think
it's fine theme parks is so stimulating
having a nice boot
ride you're getting what I
find you know I am a
full believer of like
more greenery more water features
it's good for the human brain
and
I think that I think
the ending films and stuff
that's the nostalgia
that people are clinging to
I'm not talking about the films I'm talking about just being
in the lab part where it's
all the things growing in the greenhouse
well we didn't have you know
we didn't have time for the behind the scenes
store seeds
I was back at the
hotel and I found out they were selling
plants little
succulents or little
seedlings from
the ride you could buy at the exit
and I miss that cause I
would have I'm a little plant
boy I got plants on my balcony
I would have totally bought one of those back
I know airports are a little weird about
bring it on a plane that sounds tough
well I think domestically
it's well yeah it's tough to pack
but I know internationally
they're very bunch of like oh don't bring
that apple into Australia
you know
but if they said we're getting rid of the part
where you're watching plants grow
and we're building more sort of
dark ride that will show like
different ways that
people harvest crops there's different
like future ways that we want to showcase
but it's going to be in the style of the old
part first part of the ride
would that not be better?
I don't know cause I feel like
this is one of the few remaining
pavilions that does fulfill the promise
of like
well the fish but
I shouldn't cut you off
I think the fish tank
definitely the fish tanks
you know while there are fish in them
we did see someone working with the fish
that's looking a little
long in the tooth you know
that's what I know
those old sections cause they haven't kept it up
I think what I was going to say sorry
is that like I think you're I see
all this this all makes sense to me it's
original Epcot that is about learning
I think there's a way to preserve that
without it being
so dry
and maybe that finale could have
more of a finale would definitely help
more of a finale but I just like
the climax of the ride is just going
in an open air greenhouse
in a lot of way like the last half of the ride
is mostly just like going by
oh like a strawberry that you're going to be able to
eat in a tart later like with a sign
like it's just not
as engaging as the first part of the ride
which is gives you the Epcot
feeling that you're looking for you're looking for that
dry
old school dark ride
which I chase on a lot we talked about
I think all of the old school
short supply especially
in Epcot I think we got
I'm telling you the solution
is ten thousand dollars and it's not
putting
you know the marvels in it
it's not what I want it's not
what I swear it's like
better lights and then maybe at the end there's
kind of some like flashing lights you go
through I'm not a complicated man
and maybe it's cleaning up some of the dust
in one of those black tunnels
that's all I swear
audience I'm not trying to take this ride away from you
a little bit of set a little bit of
theatricality I think you're asking for
it's a little bit of like
restoring it for the future and polishing
it up to how it probably looked on October 1st
1982 well yeah
I think too there's been so many
advances in plant based
cuisine and like
that food court and that revolving
restaurant it's still all very
like literally meat and
potatoes I'm gonna say this
right now some of
the some of the bad feelings that I
get from the living with the
land experience in general are from that
bottom floor of the land
I completely agree with that too it's awful there it's so
stressful you can feel the stress of everybody
like trying to get on
like Soren is it feels like an airport down there
it's one of the most unpleasant parts
that restaurant has awful signage awful
fonts and when you look at old pictures of how
that pavilion used to be with the
balloons and it was just like
beautifully designed beautiful
colors restaurant used to be
revolving now it truly that
is an airport terminal in front that you get to
stand in while you wait to get on that I agree
yeah and I think I'm the only one who's
watched the awesome planet movie
yeah I have I
could I think I could do a second
gauge I have a lot of thoughts
let's do awesome planet we're gonna do awesome
planet I'd love to do awesome
planet we're gonna do all hey I would look
if we hey I'll cut you a deal
we'll only do awesome planet if we hit symbiosis
is that
that's the previous that's the
movie before the Lion King
about pollution
how we gone this long without doing all
of these land movies
question however the listeners not found us
and burnt us up with torches
real quick I'll say the living with the land I guess
around the holidays they decorate the
greenhouse section
and that seems like I get
it a little more better yes
food and wine they were they had
placards with like this
is in this Mike has thrown
that under the bus Mike has now
vocalized that he doesn't do
anything for you to know that this grape is
used outside yeah it's just
it's not it's just like
at least you know what flip them around
like let me go in that part first
and then let me go back in time and see the
dark ride because that's obviously the more interesting
part of the ride I think you Bill
I think there's some little finale I think Bean Boy's
gotta go and there's just something that ties
it all together that works
for everyone that brings together the
dry and the people who want a little I
yeah I feel like the movie at the end
could be updated you can keep those little
heads in there that every month
the projections
just the screens I feel like
you could update that
and still have those little guys pop
up
keep the guys but brighten them up
more going on better technology we got
better screens I will
I will share my thoughts
on Awesome Planet
I'm afraid Awesome Planet Syndrome
would affect
oh yeah
how about they add robots in
like behind the fruits
and stuff and the robots tell you
like you know this tomato you
can eat it later in the tomato
soup at the pavilion by
I love that animatronics
in the greenhouse would be awesome
yeah yeah yeah it's just something there
to make that part more exciting don't
think that ruins it for anyone I don't
we'll see I don't know if people are more
we saw someone in the lab doing
tests and people like I've heard people
clap when they see
someone in there working and it
is nice to see someone doing
that because there is work done
in there I mean the seas
I think has the most
like scientists
actually doing stuff because you have
to keep those animals alive
yes that's true you know
and healthy okay well if I could
wind us
if I could cosmic rewind us
back to the
to the ride in question today
this ties in I think to the
Epcot
educational thing
and something you mentioned earlier Jason
they
alright
okay let me ask you both this
have either of you watched
the recent behind the attraction
season 2 of Disney
pluses behind the attraction
and there's an episode about Epcot
and have either of you
seen that no I haven't
well first of all I know you've seen some of behind the attraction
it's of course it's this great show
where they get interviews
with some of the greatest minds
and artists of the century
and they use editing to make it look
like they are numbskulls
well there's also sound effects
there's also like a boy
they do use sound effects as well yes
and so the imagineers hatched
yet another brilliant scheme
scratches nose
yes no you're
human beings do do
regular stuff when they're on camera
sometimes thanks for noticing behind the
attraction people but anyway it's this
big like
you know they
it is nice at least on it like it tells you how much
I want to see all this stuff I endure
this show just to see the old footage of these
things and there's good old Epcot footage
I pay tribute to some of the classic rides
but then like the
what they're
in the like looking forward part where they
that's essentially plugging cosmic
rewind and this is more of that
like maybe classic fan coddling
they try to convince you that
where this ride came from was
we need to look
the dinosaur ride is great
right Ellen's energy adventure
is great we all can't agree
on that but it's maybe getting a little
long in the tooth
so is there a better way that we could tell a
story about energy and we
talked to a theoretical physicist
who said you know what I think would be a good
ride is a ride about the big bang
and how the big bang and yeah
how would you use the power of storytelling
to see how the big bang
occurred and
and then ultimately led us to like you know
what would be an interesting way to do it is with
these characters with the guardians of the galaxy
this is bullshit I call
shit on every second of this there is
no way this didn't start with
let's do a guardians ride
they're really trying to help you like let's
pull you in step but no no no
we wanted to do big bang we wanted
to edutain about big bang
I admittedly did not
know it was the big bang launching you
backwards until I read the wikipedia
no man
you didn't know it when you were on it
right I just
figured it was one of many mcu
explosions
sure yes
when you look back glenn close does
talk about the big bang in her
opening spiel so it's there
but it is one of those things you gotta like
go back and think about a little
and that's fine I don't object to
and they're right a big bang being
launched backwards by the big bang
great I just don't buy the
story that like the foundation
of this was a big bang
yes Isan the celestial
wants to destroy some stuff
there's a shit here's what I'll say
because I remember now reading
that there was an idea for a big
bang coaster now okay
was it the TV show the big bang theory
I don't think I don't know that's maybe
owned by different people but
uh I
it's possible there was an idea
floating around for a big bang
ride I guess I believe that
I'll give them this because remember how it seems
very convenient but this whole
backstory where cars
land came out of car land
that there actually was a route
sixty six themed area
in progress and they just hadn't
connected the dots and wait you should talk to Pixar cause
they're making a movie and that all seems
like such crazy coincidence I guess
that is possible but
the idea like you know what we thought
was a good idea instead of it was a
corporate mandate these characters
need to be in the park immediately
they're the only Marvel characters we can use
we need to make some money on rocket plushes
like that part where it's like
this was purely a creative decision
is obviously
stretching it. What's a way we can tell that story
oh hmm a roller coaster
I guess in Epcot I suppose
well only if we make sure the audience
knows that it's because
we're only doing it because the story
mandated that we do it. Yeah
that part yes that feels like
Disney will not
rewriting history I think the reality
also being that
oh Mission Breakout with its randomized
songs was a big hit
what if we did different randomized songs
on this coaster in Florida?
You're right they're absolutely somewhere in there
must have been like this quickie overlay
that we did has been received unbelievably
well so how quickly
can we get something moving that's from
the ground up
that vibe and then feeling. And shocking to
me that they didn't just
re-theme the Tower of Terror
in a lot of ways because of how
I'm glad I'm happy about it but I just
success wise I'm sure
they were even expecting
more people to be upset after the fact
they must have known that somehow
that's a bridge you don't cross
that the studios
one has to stay toilet-tied. I mean
it makes more sense thematically for where
it is just because that's a I think
people like even though Rock and Roller Coaster is next to it
it doesn't really
but it does make much more sense. Hollywood
Old Hollywood, New Hollywood. I know what's Hollywood in
Hollywood Racker
but no one cares about the Hollywood and
California Adventure. Yeah. No one cares about
that part of it. Oh yeah yeah yeah absolutely
I want them to turn that into
anything they want as soon as they want to
versus like it would be weird it would be weirder
in Hollywood Studios. Yeah and then they
did tie it in. I like that they reverse
engineered it and then build Avengers Campus
and now you can go in that
way. When it was odd definitely was
alright it's a Hollywood Street and then into a
corner there's one Marvel ride and then it's next to
Bugs Land
that was all a little strange. Right.
I don't get too sorry to say
bugged out by any of
this and I also think like in terms
of that Epcot coddling stuff
that like
it does feel like it belongs in Epcot
like aesthetically like lead up building
it does not feel like they just plopped a box
that doesn't relate to anything into
a park with a really specific vibe. Yeah.
I think they got it. They did a good job with the
vibe and like
I think Epcot need a new E ticket.
I know Test Track is getting redone
soon which is good because it's the last
time I wrote it a couple years ago.
It's feeling it's a little
rough.
It's a little kind of feeling its age.
I think all the Tron stuff
that they don't call Tron but
I think that
glowing blue always
looks good.
I hadn't done it till I
went straight there on the Epcot day.
I'd never done the Tron version.
I like it. I hear what you're saying.
They probably got to like tweak
the ride mechanism. Yeah there's some bumpiness
but
it's a bummer. I'm glad it's happening
but obviously there's like 10 things on
the Epcot list I would rather have than
Test Track getting redone. Yeah.
I will also say this like the vibe
of Guardians just in the
queue is right.
Like as soon as you walk in there you go
yes I do feel
this makes me feel a certain way.
And there's old Epcot
mainly just
it's new. It's really
like polished and sleek
and clean and there's a lot
of purple. It's all I ask.
I don't need a lot. To me like you know
you can parse what the Epcot vibe is forever.
Ultimately there's a lot of that.
And like
just like sleek futuristic
purple makes me feel enough
like I'm in Epcot 82.
It worked for me. And a substantial
queue as well.
Enough like a lot of stuff in it.
Right when you get in that big
planetarium they call it the
Galaxarium I think. Yeah.
Which has I think a half hour of new
you know designs
and whatever planets
and stuff to look at.
The way they're running it you don't really get
stopped in there for a long time.
You don't really get to stop and look at almost
anything. You got all these like little like
hologram projection kind
of things like the solo ones like here's just
Terry Crews and I don't know what
any of them say or what any of them are and
I may never. It's hard to. I apologize.
Yeah it's hard to catch them.
The great Glenn
Close shows up in this ride
right? Yes.
Yeah. Vin Diesel and
Bradley Cooper do not. Not voicing
their characters. Or not voicing their characters.
Vin Diesel didn't do Mission Break
either. He's been out for a while.
He learned that he's like
he asked the earth, how do they
like me on the helicopter?
Is everybody saying I'm cool?
Yeah sure. Can I look
at the message board? No no no wait wait Vin
don't don't. That's it.
I'm never doing a ride again.
Never doing a ride again. They should have could have just
sent him a blue yeti and
a laptop and he could have done it
and that was. Well why did they need
they could have just used the dialogue.
Oh right. Not like he has to record
new dialogue.
There's only one thing. They have enough
emotions and inflections
from the movie. Yeah so legally there must be
a reason. Yeah he just didn't like negotiate
it. And then yeah no Bradley Cooper
which is very
noticeable. That was all I could
talk about as we were going through some of the pre-shows.
Yeah I didn't care nearly as much as you.
Yeah well Griffin said. I didn't bring it up until
Griffin brought it up. I was like that was not Bradley Cooper
and I was like I agree. Yeah I know. Didn't sound
like him. But he is in California
Adventure because California Adventure and the
marketing there like we took two days
and filmed all this
stuff on the set of Guardians 2.
Will this come up during the press
of Maestro. Will somebody finally
press him on. Where were you.
Why are you not on the why are you on the ride
in California but not on the ride in Florida. I don't know.
I hope so. Yeah. I want to know.
Yeah yeah. Because he has to he had to
get in the booth for it. I understand like. He was
wearing the nose while when they
needed him and the nose was going to
mess up like it was going to like make
him sound nasal. You don't want like
all right here's the plan.
Anywhere. That would have been different.
Yeah. Should he wore. He should have worn the
snoot for when he played Rocket though too
I think. He should have worn Rocket's snoot.
Getting grief about not
doing a ride and weird prosthetic
choices. Like my man
can't win. Yeah. Well
to be fair I mean yes I would say it's not
equal grief for those things. Not equal
grief. No the nose is
weirder. It's a weird choice.
Probably no one would have
noticed if he just had his normal
nose and they just did other makeup.
You know. I think that's right.
Yeah. So
he's not. I do think
there was I was looking at some like message
boards and people like I think they're going to just replace
it later. When they finally get him in the booth
to do Rocket and they're going to replace it. This was a couple
of years ago. Maybe a year ago.
Naive as could be. Somebody posted under
it's not different a year later.
Oh.
Oh my god.
You find out there's no Santa Claus.
They never change rides. Why would they
ever just swap in
like what why would they take
a ride down to change audio
tracks. I don't know they would have to take it down.
I mean you would just remaster the audio track
and put it in. Don't forget they
did record
Vincent Price for Phantom
Manor and then go in and take it away.
Right. That is now it's come back.
Right.
But I that's a bizarre. Why do you do that?
Why do you have one of the last Vincent
Price performances and then throw it in the garbage.
There's a lot of head scratching
decisions over the years.
We should talk about the songs.
Yes. Well I think you got a little
more pre show. Oh yeah.
We haven't really talked about. OK.
Wait. So all right. Here's the name Nova Prime
Irani Real.
Yeah. There we go. There's our carry.
That's from the movies.
Right. Yeah.
But our original guy
is Centurion
Talmeric. And I did
the spiel at the beginning.
People
of Epcot. Epcotters.
Epcotians. Citizens
of Epcot. This has a real like
oh boy I don't think they realize what they were
doing in terms of how this if this is going to
play nonstop every
day for 30 years.
This is kind of odd. It's like fine.
But
again name check. Kevin
Tully from Telethon. He said
I think before I went on it like I don't know what after
he said like did you were people already
doing Haunted Mansion Ghost Host for
that. Were people like saying
the Terry Crews lines along with and they
were not. But I want listener
I wonder if you've experienced this. People are already
throwing this
this odd
dialogue out. I don't know. It's
fun. He's fine. I like him.
I like him too. It's nice to see him in an attraction.
I think he's funny. But I might
date it
in the way that Ellen's Energy
Adventure. A lot of that
is very 90s comedy.
Sure. Between her and
Jamie Lee Curtis.
I think she's in the end. And Bill Nye.
All of whom I
like.
I mean I don't think that strongly
about Ellen either direction but I love
Jamie Lee Curtis and I grew up loving
Bill Nye.
If you like Ellen so much you should get a job
working for her. Oh yeah.
Well I do know somebody who got a
bicep. I mean the crew got
beach cruisers one year.
That's nice.
You put up with it you get beach cruisers.
What's the cost of a beach
cruiser. But then
you get acquainted with a couple things.
It would take two and a half million
years to get to Xandar.
So they're not going to get you to Xandar.
The way you can jump
around in space
is with the cosmic generator.
And there are
jump points. Artificial tunnels
that act as shortcuts linking
distant points in space. And that is
how people. If you have that
you're able to get to Xandar and then back to
Earth very quickly.
So you know
it's about science.
It's about Big Bang. It's about cosmic
generators and jump points. Jump points.
We're teaching. A lot of
kids grow up without ever learning about jump points.
That's right. Yes.
Jump points. I guess that is
from the movie. But yeah.
I guess you could have. A wormhole is
kind of a concept that is a real concept
whether it's been proven
or not. I mean I like that
there's an all new thing.
It's just funny that they're like. It's still
learning. It's still science.
And yes most of it is faking from Xandar.
Of course. It's there.
Look it's Saturday. It could work.
But you do get to use like a little jump
point. And you jump up.
Terry Crews
lets you know you're going to be teleported to a Nova
ship that is hovering up above
Earth. So you get to
right next to the Earth
the space restaurant in Epcot
which we didn't get to do. I know.
There's too much. There's so much
to do when you go back now. No episode
about that. Not yet. But you get
to do a little jump. And
that leads to. So you're
brought into this teleportation room
that's kind of clinical
and a little bit like kind of a
tight room and everybody crowds around the
center. But then the cosmic generator
is going nuts. And then
is that what that is? I don't know. Or it's a separate
ship. Sure why not.
Anyway lights go out.
Power goes down. It's
black for a couple seconds. And then you look
around and you're in a whole other room.
This rules. It's great.
It's really good. I didn't know there was this.
I didn't either. I stayed away from
most of the videos. I saw little clips. But yeah
I stayed away from this. So this was a shock to me.
Yeah. This is now I don't know if they do
it in the same way. But we've spoken
about how apparently the
effect in the Star Trek experience
at the Vegas Hilton was very
impressive. And that there was a lot of like how
did they do that. And I wonder if it's the same
thing. Which in this case is
spoiler is ceiling
going up into the rafters
rather than the walls going up.
Yeah. Should I say ceiling? Yeah. Yeah.
Sorry. Yeah. Like it shoots up.
Yeah. I don't know about that Star Trek
illusion that everybody talks about being so cool.
But yeah this was very
effective. I first I didn't think
oh the walls must be in the ceiling or
anything. Like it's just such a good
illusion. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They did it but it's great. And that
spaceship is quite grand
and a big like space. Disney's real
good at this right now. Again haven't
been to the space restaurant so I haven't seen that.
But that's a big old space
screen. A lot of good space screens. Yeah.
Rise of the Resistance.
It seems like one of the better elements probably
of the dearly departed
Galactic Star Cruiser. Yes.
Love the space screens. Keep
it up everybody. Yes. Great space screens.
Space screen. The
screens on Mission
Breakout too I find very
good where you look and you see the guardians
in the collection. Yeah.
In that giant facility.
That still looks good yeah.
Still looks really good six years later.
And Bean Boy deserves that level
of screen. This is what I let's get
Bean Boy. 18K.
Whatever the sphere is in.
Yeah. Yes.
We know the technology
is this. Let's get Bean Boy
in Sphere. Let's get them on the
Sphere. Sure. Let's get Bean Boy in Tomato
Girl. Absolutely. I got nothing against them.
All these great
the veggie veggie fruit
fruit boys and girls. Let's get them wherever they
deserve to be.
And also it's you know
it's a good thing that this teleportation works
so well because it's you know our
he's not sure he's never transported
Earthlings before but our molecular
structure is very similar to Zandarian
so it's not a big challenge.
So lucky that works out. That's nice.
But then how
quickly does something going wrong?
When do guardians
show up because something went wrong or
do they just show up to say hey?
I think they because something goes wrong. That's the
the chronology.
And now we're having power struggles
on the ship and nobody knows
and there's also
some effects in play with the
cosmic generator because that's in some
tube that's next to where
the guardians all show up.
And it's there
but then it's not there and they wonder what
happened to it and there's a kind of funny line about
like what happened
to it. I don't know maybe it's that big guy outside
the ship and then a very
like okay Marvel
people. Ison this is new. There's no
Ison anywhere else.
Wait no Ison is a celestial.
He's a celestial. In other media?
Yes. Yes. Okay. In a
movie or in where do you see
Is he in the
Eternals? I haven't seen
the Eternals yet. I'm behind on a lot
of my Marvel stuff. Yeah.
I saw the first half hour of the
Eternals before the hardest sleep I've
ever had in my life. Yes.
The Celestials are ones
where it's like they're crazy
giant god
godlike creatures
very
cool. They feel like people crossed with
suns. They're big sun beings.
Yeah very cool Jack Kirby designs
in the comics that in the movies.
These are the Celestials from
very pop party in the comics. In the movies
they're fine. I like these
sun and the ride. I like the designs of
Jack Kirby more than maybe the live
action Celestials.
Ragnarok had the most Kirby
design
There's some good Kirby background
especially background stuff. And there's a
Celestial masks in
Mission Breakout. Mission Breakout
those look pretty good. Those look cool
yeah. As a
not a Marvel fan
some of the disconnect I've had
is like I saw First
Avengers enjoyed it fine but I didn't
necessarily think I would like 30
more movies in this aesthetic
unchanging in any way.
Well that's a yeah I think the
fun as I've said many times probably the fun
of the comics to me is always or
any doing anything that's been around for
decades the fun of it is
having somebody with an interesting point of view
doing their take on it.
So you know you would get
then you end up after decades and decades of
like oh there's like 10 cool
X-Men runs with different art and
different vibe and a different voice
different style. Same with Batman.
There's so many different versions of Batman. So the
thing with the Marvel movies is they've tried so
hard to make them all feel the same
which after so many of them
it's like let them do a different
thing like. Yeah really.
I don't like that. Are any of them am I
wrong if I missed one that's like actually this one
really stands out. Well I think that's why the Guardians
movies stood out because it was
kind of I don't want to say blank
slate characters because there were certainly
interesting material to draw on
but in terms of the movie you had one guy
with a specific voice.
Applying it to these interesting
performers. You feel a little
more James Gunn in those than you do I think
on some of the other movies but I
do think they still all have like this
I don't know if there's actually a sheet that says there's
a mandate but it all feels like well there has to be
seven action sequences in these things
or every eight minutes there has to be
an action sequence and you're like that's
fine sometimes but like
some of these characters you could just
have it be a little talky and then there's like a
big ending or something. It just feels like
there's still there's a very specific
roadmap that everybody has to follow
when making these things and
the TV shows have tried to deviate
to some degree from them. Oh yeah One of Vision
seems different. And that was different yeah
so like maybe they have a little more leeway there but
it's like I think
they're trying to like
keep everything feeling the same which I think is also
kind of an overthink because like well
how will viewers
accept like
the Christian Bale Batman in
a movie with a different
tone or like with
the Ezra Miller Flash like
that's just such different universes and it's like
I think the reality is the audience doesn't care if the movie is cool.
Yeah no one cares. It would be great I love it.
Somebody from one universe showing up in a
totally different one sounds awesome.
Yeah. That's the problem is that when Clooney
spoiler when Clooney Batman
shows up you're like that's not him
that's George Clooney. That has
nothing to do with Joel that is not a bunch of
that's not Joel Schumacher
in this boring 2023
movie. So it is like I wish the movies
I wish people that were making the movies really
got to do what
they wanted. It's like running Edgar
right off of Ant-Man
to me is a very proof
that like they have a different agenda
than like making sure everything
like has its own unique voice and
is cool and like they would
like you could pick any cool
like filmmaker that like really has
a specific voice and I feel like
at the end of the day like Marvel
Studios would be like no we're good.
We don't need you to make a unique
movie for us.
We're more interested in making something that feels like the other
movies. Yeah.
I think the ones like
Guardians or Winter Soldier
or Ragnarok the stuff that
sticks with people is a little
more personality or a little
more character from the directors.
Yes. Yeah.
Endgame and
Infinity War I
think stuck out because you got
like that one it was just
everyone. Well that's
that's Sesame Street
meets the Muppets.
It's scale. Yeah.
So it's like you throw enough
Sesame Street characters meet the Muppet characters
at me and it's done in like
an interesting way. I'm like I'm going to be entertained.
I'm going to enjoy it. Yeah.
If you know if the characters are doing it.
So yeah those are and I assume when Secret
Wars comes out in a couple of years
and you just have like Jackman and Tobey Maguire
hanging out. I wish
I assume that's what the movie will be.
My brain is really that's cool.
I like watching those
characters like I like that. So
yes. But you will never get your dream of Han Solo
hanging out with
Watto or Dexter Jetser.
Yeah no I won't. Unfortunately.
But what you were saying
are like Fantastic Four and X-Men
do have
like their own self-contained
universes their own
Rose Gallery. Yeah.
And that is like if you want to
juice these movies a little
it's like well bring in all this.
You know. Right. Which is like
whatever they're trying.
Yeah. Yeah. Who got cast
as Mr. Fantas...
Pedro Pascal is the word
right now I believe. That's a rumor.
I like him. Sure
yeah. I mean I like
everybody. Yeah.
I love everything.
I love everybody.
So it's just
I would love it if
they could just
really make the movies very different feeling.
Yeah. That would be
cool. But yeah.
But here you know like
so let's see
we're on evacuation
shuttles is what the right
vehicle is sold as. Now we're on
like a ship that's losing power.
So there's red lights. There's
a panic air. You move from
teleportation room or from the ship
rather post teleportation room to the
like evacuation area
slash coaster loading zone
really quickly. That's nice. It's a fun
you pass by a window and go oh there we go
that room looks good. I'm excited to be in there.
There's a real
like space mountain times five
kind of like when we're descending down
into the load zone.
Coaster vehicles look cool. The ride
vehicles themselves besides that they spin and everything.
So cool. Really sharp. A little
like battle worn and just the right amount.
Good color scheme.
Love it. I want to go on it right
now. Yeah. Describing it
like I feel I'm wistful.
I feel wistful. The Zandarian
ship in front of the building.
I like a lot too. Oh yeah. I like that choice
with a plaque from
Nova Prime. Like that's clever.
I didn't see the plaque. That's cool. Okay.
Yeah
and then you're
you load up. You go up that
lift hill is fantastic. I don't know how to describe
what the lift hill is but just with those kind
of like curved brackets
and then screens that are rapid fire
cycling through. That's an exciting buildup.
It's pretty good seeing like
big screens with the guardians.
My friends from the other
ride and no other media.
It's like Rex.
I was trying
to do the math of
when you
are you in the other
building past that
lift hill or is that
at the launch and I believe it is the
launch. I think that you're not in building
to until
the launch. I believe that's right.
Which that's when you look at it from
afar and you see this kind of this weird little tunnel
that connects to you. Yeah. It's kind of
exciting to see the architecture from outside
and like oh wow yeah that's just that's purely a
launch tunnel there. Yeah. Look how much
we haven't even gotten over here yet.
That room
you go through kind of like
a jump point tunnel.
Cool lights there.
It all feels more
to the argument of like
a lot of Marvel things have similar aesthetics.
I do get I fuzz out on
like this explosion versus
this explosion versus this sky
beam versus I
think that jump point tunnel is
cool. I'm seeing how like
the guardians aesthetic is a little more specific
and a little more defined a little more colorful.
Yeah. Very colorful for sure.
Then this really
cool room where you do like a big
horseshoe and that's kind of
the first it's the room that serves
to flip you around.
Where you stay focused on
Ison and the guardians ship
and it's
it doesn't look as good it really doesn't
read and ride videos. Yeah it doesn't.
Because cameras phones and stuff can't like
adjust the exposure correctly
so you can just you can see the screens you can see
the ceiling you can see the track in the room
it's immaculate in there.
It's so cool and you may not even realize
that's what the track is doing and you don't
maybe don't even catch that you're looping around
at that moment.
But then you get some really great
guardians cheese which is
the line no one
can stop rock and roll from existing.
Yeah. And that's
the universe of energy.
That's right. Down in hell.
Which on the ride
I just thought that was like
that just read to me as
copyright free
It's like Bohemian Rhapsody. Rock and roll music.
Yeah yeah. And before
that I believe it's the guardians
theme. Is that
correct Mike? I believe so.
I always get the guardians theme and the Avengers theme
confused. They're pretty close.
Do you think there was ever a time
when they had it in the copy that it was just going to say
rock and roll will never die?
Because I mean I understand why
they're saying existing because you're going back in the past
and you could like. Yeah no death
is the end. That's the opposite. Death is the
end. This is like never
never die. It's such a cooler
thing to say. Well universe
applicable to the entertainment. Universal
has the monopoly on the phrase death
is only the beginning which has
shown up in an
unusually large number of attractions
over there. Which theme park has the
rights to Neil Young's hey hey
my my rock and roll
can never die or will never die. He's very
anti-corporate but he gives it out to theme parks
no problem. Yeah. He was trying to get
a song on this and they were they didn't take it.
What about Neil Young's rock and roller coaster?
How about that? I'd like that.
Oh it's shop Joe sells ponos.
Overstock ponos. Oh yeah it's ponos. It's mostly
is five hundred dollar. Yeah yeah.
Uncompressed music
software. But we don't
have Neil Young.
What we do have is a great
bevy of other
song selections. Rock and roll. No one's
going to stop rock and roll from existing. Then something
then there's a little like everything like
all this momentum is building and then it all sucks
down to nothing. And the kind of
I really like that moment of
I think we went back.
Zoe Saldana line. Yeah.
Yeah and then it's silent for a
second. There's an odd an eerily
still moment before
incredible launch
sequence. It's a similar moment
to Star Tours when you shoot that
I forget which
scene it is. It's the one with Boba Fett
in his ship. Oh yeah. And you shoot
like a thing at the or Boba Fett shoots it at you
and there's like a brief like kind of moment
of silence. And then this like
massive explosion happened
in space with like and you like shake
and it's that cool. You get a little
moment. It's probably a second.
A little moment of silence but that doesn't have
like a blondie song playing
suddenly. Well I hear you.
Yeah it's true because what a great to like
let it all die down so that
some music can blast
at you. I guess right
before the music that launch itself
is incredibly exciting. I look so
terrified on the
it's a really embarrassing ride photo and
I as was
Tron and I get I think
it's I think it's the unfamiliarity. I think my
first time on anything. I
just really and I don't even feel
the panic but I look back and like
that's bad. That's really but it is
the launch is something. That's
that's it's intense. It's not near
Rock and Roller Coaster but it's a hell of a launch
and I hadn't done a backwards launch before.
It's yeah it's really cool. It's not
unpleasant. It didn't make me sick. It didn't make me
too scared after the fact. But
it's it's intense and it's a cool
tunnel you go through. It's a great moment. Do you
think you would be more like
on Rip Ride Rocket which is the vertical
like because because again I would say like
the launch is the ripping the bandaid off for me
at this point still with any coaster.
It's like I am not bothered by the launch.
It just it rattles my brain
immediately and we're ready to go. I'm so much less so.
It's one of those you feel the time
passage how long we've been doing that honestly
the no launch queen feels really
far in the rear view. Yes. And I'm not just
saying that because I'm trying to shake that phrase off.
Sure. It just genuinely isn't something
I it's something that I love that
like due to doing this podcast
it's like everyone you guys
listeners Matt Rogers
everyone helped me together to
get over this thing. And now I get to go on rides
like this and I'm not like because you were in the line
with me. I wasn't like no you're just
shaking trembling and I was really excited to do this ride.
I had zero nerves
whatsoever. That's good. More intense
coasters possibly and I will I forget
if I've said I did not do Velocicoaster
so that is still there's still
some hills I have to climb.
I sat out
Hulk this time. We did Hulk
last time. Oh I did Hulk.
And that's a very intense launch and you
immediately twist
at the top of that hill.
And Hulk will just your brain will rattle
around in your skull on the Hulk.
But you were asking about Rip Ride Rocket.
Yeah I'm just saying that I still
to this day I'm very anxious especially on
like a completely vertical
slow climb.
But I yes it's it's anticipation
still for me that I get
anxious. Well look and I don't you know
I still not very versed in Magic Mountain
or other Six Flags or more coaster based parts.
I think it would I'm so like based in
the Disney Universal ones that I think I would constantly
be like we're not done with
this hill yet. There's no soundtrack.
There's no on board audio.
What is this? What is this?
I'm in coach. I only fly first class.
Yeah.
I'd be a snob
I think. It's also a
mix of emotions when you're like
I was just loaded by a 16
year old. My valuables
are in like an Ikea
bookshelf. I
am trusting no one to steal
them.
But anyway
great launch. Love the
launch. Photos be damned.
Music. Sorry to cut you off
when you touch another music before.
Oh my god. I'm going to
make this declaration. I think
that just the list of songs
the musical selection here I think
all told is a better crop of songs.
Okay. Then
Mission Breakout. It's at least for
me more songs that I
specifically like and listen to regardless
of being on a ride. I think it's a really
kick ass crop.
I yeah I think
I think I agree with that.
Okay. Yeah. Not so controversial.
Let's talk about what we actually had.
Konga.
We got Konga.
I was so excited about
Konga. Okay. First of all launch hitting me. Oh my
god. So I'm screaming at launch. Then
that it is Konga.
Is Konga my favorite
song to listen to on the
list of six. No.
Do I go out of my way
to listen to Konga. Not necessarily.
But for some reason it is really
what I wanted on this.
It really delighted me that you
would hear this 80s Gloria Estefan
song
as the score of a roller coaster. That just seemed
like the most fun
to me. And apologies to Jane.
Jane on the way. Jane said I just
hope it isn't Konga.
I was like what. And she had
her reasons. I'm like okay. But then
it made me like
her spirit is going to make
it so we don't get Konga. No.
And then we got Konga. And I was like
yeah.
I think. I don't think she
feels. I think she
just thinks Konga is a little
overplayed. That's definitely
true. Yeah. But.
I associate it with a lot of
early 90s, late 80s,
Disney parades and specials.
Totally. Sebastian the crab kind of stuff.
It has Disney.
We're dancing at the newly
opened Caribbean beach resort
or whatever.
Kid friendly pop hit.
When they didn't make music specifically
for kids and teens.
They just had to make do with like
the most clean songs that adults liked.
And Gloria Estefan
and Emilio Estefan.
Kind of a long history with
the resort I feel with that stuff.
With appearances in the specials.
There was of course the
bongos cafe at downtown
Disney. For a while.
For a long time. Yes.
Of course the greatest moment in Disney world
history. Mike's performance with his mother.
Which song was that?
That was a one two three. Yeah.
Come on baby say you love me.
So that's a historic
moment. Yeah. Great concert
performance. And then she also
made a little video of her
and her family. They shot a video of her
and her family going on this ride.
And really funny seeing her say
alright today we're going to Xandar.
In the crossover of now
Gloria Estefan being aware of
this Marvel mythology.
And unfortunately they got Tisco
and Furnos. So
Sorry there's no way to even we can't custom
do it. Sorry Gloria.
So anyway
that it was just
it was the one I wanted for whatever
reason. And then it gets you into this
area where the ride it's a
roller coaster that is also
kind of concert. Because
it is so loud. Yeah.
And so disorienting and
fun and such a party.
And I'm like
like pumping
my arms the whole time. I was watching
the kid next to me to make sure I didn't hit him.
Like let me bend over this way just so I
can prop because my impulse was definitely
to like just pump those arms
the whole time. It was so fun. Yeah.
I was laughing a lot on this
and velocity. I was just so
delighted by all the little
tricks and turns
and all sorts of
things. Yes. It feels like yes.
I've never yes you've never been Handel like this
before. And the delight
you can't help but express it. Yeah.
I'm being Handel.
I love how I'm being Handel.
All the list of songs
September by Earth Wind and Fire
Disc of Inferno by The Tramps
Everybody Wants to World the World
by Tears for Fears
One Way or Another by Blondie
I Ran So Far Away by Flogged the Seagulls
and Congo by Miami
Sound Machine. So yeah.
I wanted Tears for Fears.
Sure. Because
I was like that is an interesting vibe
for a coaster.
There's not a lot of music on roller coasters
that are songs that like give me
feelings. That's what I'm talking about. Yeah.
It's moody. It's like I put that on
as kind of when I like want to feel
you know. So that's that is crazy.
That's crazy. And that's especially in the last couple
years I've listened to that song and I go this is like
one of the best constructed songs
ever. Like it's because like that
almost was just on so much when I was a kid that I
didn't even think twice about it. I didn't care
when it was like if it would pop up on VH1
I didn't give it the time of day did it. Yeah.
It's one of those where you need like a little time. You need to discover
it on your own. And you go
oh god this is a great vibe.
It over heels both. Yeah.
The vibes with those songs too.
And you're like if you really listen to it.
So when I heard that that was one of the choices
I go oh god.
Like I imagine I'm fantasizing
about like being at Epcot
like at closing alone on
the ride. Maybe I'm
sad for some reason and like
I'm going on this and listening to
that song like blasted
at me. You want to create a heavy experience
for yourself. Yeah.
And I think that's what I handled into a better headspace.
Yeah that was real. That's really intriguing to me
the idea that I could go on there
and be in like a thrilling
situation but be sad.
And it's making me feel sad.
And kind of a good cathartic maybe sad.
I don't want something really to be wrong.
It's like melancholy more than
or mixed emotion more than
it's not a depressing song but it's
yeah right right. It's just it's moody.
And it's just like what you like you could bring.
It brings out a different feeling in your
self. And I just I'd
like to know what that feels like. Yeah.
Yeah. That'd be if I
if I could request a
song for the second time doing it that would
be my request. Yes. Yes. Yes.
For sure. I have to say I agree
with that. But the one that caught me off guard
watching it and I don't
think I realized it was one of the songs was
I ran so far away
activated a memory of my
mind of driving around in
Grand Theft Auto Vice City. Oh yeah.
Like stealing a car
that comes on one of the radio
stations and that was like
one of the most awesome parts of
the game. Sure. That's one
that I will that's not a song I
actively listen to and that almost feels like
what Jane probably felt about Konga
is like overused obvious I think about
about that song. But then but also
that's very callous of me. If you
if it wasn't so played a ton
and kind of like a go to
this is what 80s music is. Yeah.
It's fucking great. It is really
good. And I agree. I mean watching
some ride throughs I was like
it's yeah it's not my favorite song on here
on its own but matched
with the the ride aesthetics
and kind of the and the peril
and the the the story.
I thought it worked really
well. Vice City another Florida connection.
Oh yeah. Yeah.
It's supposed to be standing for Miami.
So if
they could have put Cortez the Killer by
Neil Young on here that would have maybe
been the best choice.
If you really want like to feel like
you're in a sad haze
a moody haze. But I
understand why they didn't. And you've got
all those Randy
Newman album cuts you want
here. Randy Newman on a roller
coaster. Is that on is he on RIPRIDE
Rocket? Do we know is he on the secret menu?
Maybe. I don't know. Is
he show up a little on
Incredicoaster or
California Screamin? I don't think he has music.
Is he on Music and Incredibles? It's probably
the only Randy Newman you're getting is like
well don't you hear it on
Slinky Dog probably. You get you get the
yeah yeah. Yeah. Yeah you get the
the swinging version of You Got a Friend in Me.
The other the Spinner Ride in
Toy Story Land. It's all the techno
remix of Strange Things Are
Happening to Me whatever it's called. Oh that's all over
Somaraland. Yeah yeah yeah.
Actually a lot of Randy Newman in
the parks if you think about it. Yeah but not
Toy Story Land. Sorry Toy Story Land.
The Little Gary Men.
You're not getting something. What's your
what's your Randy Newman coaster pick?
Oh my god that's a good question because do you
want it to be as sad as possible?
Oh Baltimore
Ain't it hard?
Uh yeah that's a good
question. I've talked about the song Wandering
Boy that makes me cry anytime I hear
it. Oh so maybe it's that.
You need to well you need to like meld
some ride in your head that is
that where you because there's some stuff
that you you clearly want to go through
on a ride. Yeah. So you need Wandering Boy
that leads into your bravery
has saved the planet.
You found this man's boy.
Reunited a family
for me. Family but a son who like
goes like like I don't know he has troubles
and they lose contact with him and then
after this Prime's like you found his son
you found the man's Wandering Boy.
Congratulations
and I go oh my god. So
do you think that's like would that be good
for like Wild Mouse or
more of like more of a
Dumbo kind of ride? What are you thinking? Spinner
more of a spinner. Spinner ride. It is
surprising there is not a firework show
in DCA 1.0
with I Love LA
or other California
numbers. Right they took they got every
California song they could think of
and not him. Mickey's Mix
Magic which I'm surprised I didn't force
a second gate on which I
really do like. 2024.
I don't know are they doing it anymore? I don't know I don't think
so. What is it? It's like a light
show on Main Street where they play like
modernish sounding music with like
different projections on Main Street. In
what park? In Disneyland.
Disneyland. And I've
not noticed it whatsoever.
Gosh it's brutal
out here. And then it would
end I think with We Belong
Together which is Randy Newman from Toy Story 3.
Which is a nice little song.
So that's another
Newman in the Park.
That's the second gate maybe.
Now a close I said that
my number two pick if I could choose
would be Tears for Fears but
it's a close one that
maybe barely nudges out September.
Which seems fantastic song.
Would really and I love
that they're doing the that they do play
it all day. That's the only option
on the 21st night of
September.
That's great. I think that
would I don't know
I mean I just wanted the I wanted the party
vibe. Yeah. Yeah. There's
a time and place for the mood and for the feels
but my first time I
want to party so I think I would have been very
happy with September as well. Yeah I would have been happy
with that too. Yeah. Surprise watching
Ride Throughs Disco Inferno works
pretty well too. It adds the conga
sort of like party vibe.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't think you can go
wrong and then the kid next to me said
he was like conga's the worst one.
Oh wow. What's the best one?
He said one way or another.
Interesting. Yep. That's I mean I
think it'll be fun. This kid was much more comfortable
with the launch than me.
Well that's always what I
look to whenever I'm doing something
that's making me a little anxious and I go there's a
11 year old boy in front of me.
I go surely
you can handle this. Yeah.
Yeah. Well you pay taxes.
You pay rent.
Yeah and I yell at him.
I go I pay taxes. I'm fine.
I'll be fine on this kid.
Some years I owe some. Some years
I get a refund. It's like living in a
roller coaster. Yeah the
approaching Velocicoaster and I was like
it's going to be a little intense and then like
the thing pulls up and I go half
kids under 15
on this. I go it's fine. I'll be
okay. I got to do my best
to make my boy one of those kids
but right now
at almost four it's
not looking great.
He is his
dad's son. So far
but I'm going to see what I can do. Well you never know.
Well Uncle Jason and Mike
take it to Magic Mountain and do a
dozen. Dozen slightly
off coasters.
Alright have
fun with the boys. Uncle Jason and Mike traumatize
him on Twisted Colossus.
You take a seven year old through the sewer of souls
and it really will open them up.
It will make them really
want to do new stuff. Alright that's
for the uncles to do. Dad doesn't get down with that stuff.
Great little graveyard pudding to put his mind at ease.
Hey and then afterwards you're
hanging around deciding if you should
leave or not because there's
a vomit in progress. Apologies.
This was the first time
in 38 years I had ever been to
a theme park with someone who was that
nauseous. It never happened
before. I think it had. I was with some people
who had trouble with Space Mountain one time.
It has happened. Reasonable. Amazing to see
it happen to me. I'm like more afraid of it happening
than it happening. But
we're hanging around in kind of the post room and you get a little
surrender. You still got your classic
rock tree in there. That would have been great on the ride too.
Footloose plays. Surrender would totally work.
That would work great. Is surrender in the
exit part of
Mission Breakout? I don't know.
I feel like it might be but I'm missing
things out. Maybe the area.
And then there's some music we haven't
talked about but you guys told me right before we started
recording that they aren't doing it this year.
Last year there was a holiday
overlay. A Cosmic
Rewind holiday remix.
And they aren't doing it.
Because I guess you were saying they
are not promoting a new Guardians
Holiday Special. I don't know why they
because they still do
the overlay during
Halloween for Mission Breakout.
I don't know. Was it like
poorly received in some way? Was there a reason
that we don't know about why they wouldn't want to do it?
I think this is very cute too.
They made the soundtrack Run Run
Rudolph but they changed the lyric to
Run Run Rocket. I think it sounds
great. Yeah. If you guys listen to it
because I heard it also
incorporates other Christmas melodies
in some way. I didn't
know. I don't know.
I guess I haven't seen
too many people talking about it in
the sense that oh I hate that one. I wish it would do
the regular song. So I'm not
I don't know. I didn't know about
the holiday Christmas
parties at Magic Kingdom.
There's like a crazy overlay
on Space Mountain where they are like
blaring Christmas
music and flashing red and
green lights. I would love
to do that. Very weird in a good way.
We talked about that last year and we saw a couple
of videos and I was like they're doing
what? This looks
kind of dumb and
not like
there's not too much finesse to it. At least
from videos. I like that.
I've seen like a warped Trans-Siberian
Orchestra album.
The record was left out
in the sun and then they played it.
A very unique way to do
an old
I don't want to say shitty but rough coaster
at this point. Which we
got to see with the lights on when we were on People Mover.
Oh that's right. Yes we did a People Mover pass
which then because it was down for a long time
I didn't get to do it which I wanted to do.
I didn't do it either. I didn't see
any fans. We saw no fans.
Well there were no conventional fans but
there were places, yes, well that's
a whole nother. That's stuck.
I didn't mean to start a discourse.
No you did mean to and it's good.
If it were a discourse I'd never bring it up
again. I hate discourses.
Discussions and debates I
like. If we can get a hold of
Tony Baxter. I swear I felt cold
air blowing on me. I think there's
something to it. It's cold in there.
I think there's something to the fan
thing. It's just not fans
in the way that there's a big fan
next to you on the track. But I do think there's
some sort of science to it or
planning. Some sort of aggressive HVAC
system. Yes that's what I
think and we're going to need
to talk to some Imagineer who might
be able to tell us. Well this is going to delay
the Space Mountain episode
even longer. It's needing to get a coherent
answer on this.
Moments in the ride.
It's tough to say because it is just a big
disorienting thing.
But it does like
it's all bad for a podcast right?
Where we're supposed to
verbally go through things
in a way that
makes some sense. But you get off
the thing and you're just like oh in the one
part and the other part. You're kind of
like it feels like you're like a little sideways.
None of this is good to say
out loud. The only one that I could maybe vocalize
is well unfortunately the part that made Jane
sick. Yes it's the moon.
When I've been trying to illustrate to people how cool it is
that you can pick these like pivot
points. It happens with the moon and it happens I think with Earth
too. That
your car perfectly
rotates to like
stare at this central planet
point. Those moments
are so thrilling. I bet it gives you
a little bit of what staring
at the goat on Big Thunder gives you.
But they're doing it on purpose. Oh yeah.
They make you crane your neck for it. Yeah I think that's
right. I'm
very impressed with
however they figured out how to make
things bright but not
show off the building.
Yeah. That kind of inward
light that doesn't let you see the track.
Yeah because yeah you don't necessarily
it's not calling attention to
the fact that you're in a building all that often.
And I believe
I don't know if it's the exact same technology
but going on Space Mountain a couple weeks
ago they have now
projected stars much more
brightly onto the walls.
And there are like little nebula things.
Has it improved lately? Yes.
I haven't been on it in a while. Yeah for sure. Because it was down
for a little while and I think
it was I think I was there actually the day it
opened because I hadn't been on it
in so long. And for sure
the stars are brighter. I saw other people mention this.
And a lot of the projections
are they're not
quality of this Rive Guardians of
course but it was very noticeable
that they're using some
different thing or. The star projections
in this ride are great.
Yeah oh yeah. But I wonder
if they learned something on this
and that's what they're using or who knows.
Yeah maybe. Well it feels like
this ride is going
to influence a lot of rides
going forward. I hope that in redoing
Space Mountains that you
get some of this technology overlaps. I hope that
there's another Omni coaster again.
Mike your theory you just
fully thought this Tokyo
Disneyland fully knew Space
Mountain. You're like it's got to just be this.
I bet. I don't know what else would you. I don't
know because it's such you're on it you're going
oh this is Space Mountain with like
a rock and roll song. Yeah.
This is just Space Mountain with pop music.
So I don't know. Don't discount
Dick Dale. Dick Dale was on
there before. That's true you're right.
I did like that. Dick Dale kicked
the door open. He broke the rock ceiling.
That's true you're right. Yeah.
Michael Giacchino. Yes.
Well that's not. Which I like
that song too but it's not as rock and roll
as Dick Dale. I like I prefer Dick Dale.
I like Dick Dale. I guess you
did it with Dick the Dick Dale song. Yeah.
That's right. Right when I started going on Space
Mountain that was new in the
soundtrack. And of course I did do Space Mountain with the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
So I did rock on
Space Mountain. So it's certainly not
without precedent.
I've gotten to rock at Disneyland.
Although
no it was
that was on California
Screamin. I don't remember. Around the world
I believe. I believe Higher
Ground is on Space Mountain. I think so.
Makes sense. Well let's
get Imagine Dragons in there.
Let's get the Chain
Smokers on Incredicoaster. Some of the
new great rock music that's out there.
Some of the new rockers. With this.
Credo Van Fleet. With this
technology and seeing this ride
as a space ride. How would you not
just use this? Unless they have something cooler.
Which they might.
We need more. I think Omni Coasters
should not be specific
to Guardians in this ride.
If there is an Omni Coaster that
fits better into one of the Disneyland parks
get it in there ASAP. If you can get an Omni Coaster
in Animal Kingdom. That's what I was trying to figure out too.
Throw it anywhere. I want all the
Omni Coasters we can muster up.
I was trying to figure out where. Cause Space
Mountain I guess. They've talked
about redoing it out here. redoing obviously
all of Tomorrowland. We've talked about it many times.
We'll continue. As we've said
on our show. Our Tomorrowland
redo thoughts will bleed into 2024
at this point. Yes. Like Disney we
have pushed our Tomorrowland plans
into the future. We have plans though.
We ran out of budget. We ran out
of budget. That's really a budget thing. The SD
card is full and we don't need
it's not like you can just buy them at CVS
now. We use special ones
handcrafted. Podcast The Right Imagineer
who was in charge of our Tomorrowland
episodes have been they've been fired.
All of them have been fired. They've all
they've all been scooped up by
Doughboy. They've all jumped.
We had to fire them though. Cause they were making
too much money. Yeah.
They were bleeding. So all of our Tomorrowland
researchers. All 10 of them
laid off. Gone. Like the Imagineers
of Animal Kingdom jumping
over to Lost Continent.
So I guess
yeah there's a world like cause at this point
it's like oh it's gonna be
Tron. They're gonna move Tron into Disneyland
and like
I'm more interested in just
Guardians going.
I would take look
this is gonna be crazy maybe
if I haven't said this out loud. I haven't even
allowed myself to think it. Would I
trade our Space Mountain for Guardians
of the Galaxy right now in Disneyland?
And the answer is yes.
I think my answer is also yes.
Demolish Space Mountain. Wow.
I think the only way
there's no way they have room. I know that's Blue
Sky. I understand.
This box is just too big. So Space Mountain
I get it. I know it's probably safe
from what I'm saying. But
it's so close to
the Space Mountain vibe already
just with songs like
yeah give it to me.
Give me this. It's
better ride. Where could
an Omnicoaster
go
on the Disneyland property?
With the size you mean? Yeah.
Let me ask Jason real quick
what he thinks of that controversial statement.
Would you trade?
The devil shows up to your door
and he says you can get rid of
Space Mountain and have Guardians
of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind if you want Jason.
I mean I was of the mind too of like
oh this sucks we can't ride this
again today. Either because of
Virtual Queue or Lightning Lanes.
It sounds like you're gonna join Scott and I on the
devil's side. Jason's
first question probably is like
sorry devil
that's what you're bringing to me. I can't
like end the war.
I can't. Well the devil doesn't want
to end the war. Yeah the devil loves war.
Devil is evil.
I just
want to disappoint these Twitter
people. Unless it's hot stuff the little
devil. But that's not the devil I'm talking
about. I'm talking about Christian devil.
The reality of like
there's already Guardians Ride
at California Adventure. There's
already a Marvel campus.
But I really really
liked this. Join us
Jason. Join us.
Yeah baby.
You want to talk about Disneyland
Tomorrowland.
It was looking a little rough when I first
got out here in 2006.
Let alone in 2023.
The thing is though like
we can't. I mean getting
rid of Space Mountain doesn't. Space Mountain
isn't the problem and it shouldn't suffer. No it's
not. But I agree it would be. I mean yes I
would make this trade. No I love the Space Mountain out here. The Space
Mountain Florida has fucked me up
in recent years. It's rough.
It's like Matterhorn level
rough. Well let me ask
my question was if we can
reverse engineer where is there room on
property and let's take that Disneyland Forward
shit out. Well that's sadly the answer.
It's maybe the only hope but let's say that
gets canceled. City doesn't approve it.
We want an Omni coaster somewhere at Disneyland
where possibly
and let's work backwards.
Let's like. Like where's the
space. Yeah and let's
if we determine that somehow it's in
Frontierland it's got to be an old west Omni coaster.
If it's in Fantasyland I know
there isn't. I know it's not that.
Using
Disneyland Forward I think that's where
you get the space. Either it wraps
around the Disneyland Hotel.
Yeah I'm taking that off. I mean you're right
that's it. I'm taking that off the table. Let's say
that is done. I'll tell you where there's
space. The Toy Story parking lot.
Okay. A huge amount
of space. That's still. Yeah yeah.
Cheating. Cheating. We're mainland
Disneyland only. Mainland Disneyland.
I'm boxing you in.
We have to. We got to. Would you take
a. How about this. You know how there's room
in Frontierland. If you get rid of Frontierland
would you blow up Rivers
of America and all of it to get an
Omni coaster. Well okay what does that look
like. Is that just a big building now where the
river is. I don't know. They could put something nice
on the outside. You're going to have to expand
on what this looks like for me to approve
it. Okay okay okay. Cause like the vibe there
is so good. Don't put a bunch of trees on top of it.
You won't be able to. Really tall trees.
I think I've got it. What's that?
Big stretch of land. You
got Pixar Pier
and Paradise Carpets Park. Oh my goodness.
That's going to be weird too. But now you're
through space. But that's a lift. Now you're getting rid of a
coaster though. Now you're
trading it for a better
coaster though. Better but
Credit Coaster is very good too.
Well but also
then that gets rid of the
vibe. That gets rid of the
hangout of the pier
and the water. And you've gotten rid of Toy Story
Media too. Or you think all that.
I think yeah I think all that.
But the water stays. In terms of
vibe I would rather keep
Grizzly Peak which people are already
speculating that
will become Avatar stuff.
They keep saying experience.
Avatar is going to be so. They keep saying experience.
I think it's going to be a smoking gun.
Sound stages. Using
a sound stage. That's right. It's going to be where
the Tron Arcade was. Well first of all
okay. I think I have an answer. Before we
get all severe over
in the pier. Severe in
before we get severe in the pier.
As I was saying earlier. Hollywood's
gone. That's what I'm saying. Flowing up.
Any Omni- just do Guardians.
Do it there. Forget the Wonder. Do a different
lead in than Wonders of Xandar. I don't care that
there's already a Guardians right. Just put it
there. Whenever the arch. Like whenever you
leave like the area by
Carthay and you go right next to like the Disney Junior
Theater. That's when you can start
destroying things.
They're getting rid of that Beast's
castle walkthrough which I always
forget is there. Oh the library. Which is
really cool. It is a little
like fun thing. Have you ever done it? Do we need to do
like an RIP for that? I kind of think we do.
I haven't been on in a while. I almost want to get down there.
It closes soon. I almost want to
get down there and walk through it. In the animation building.
I forgot about it the last couple years. I
remember stumbling upon it years
ago and going wow this is cool. This is a cool little
thing. Awesome Planet. Beast's library.
Beast's library. When
it was really cool when they had that
and the Toy Story Zoe trope
in there. Oh that was great. What are they
called? Which is in the Academy
Museum now. That's maybe right.
I don't remember seeing that. I thought I heard
that move there. What you can do I think
is you can get rid of all those buildings.
You can get rid of award wieners. You can go
all the way back. Get rid of Monsters Inc.
Award wieners
can move. I would rather
keep award wieners than
Monsters Inc.
Hang on.
There will be
the same quality of hot dog which is
to say C plus hot dog
can be maintained somewhere else
on property. I have
I know I'm not
I am the only one but I have always
had good luck with film strip fries.
So if you can move the hot dogs
and film strip fries.
I'm not with you on film strip fries at all.
I think those are delightful. They're fine.
I'm not against film strip fries.
But I would say that I don't
make them make them available
at the sit down Carthay circle.
Now you can get
that as a $15
side for the table.
Loaded Irish nacho film strip fries.
There was just a little cart that said award
wieners that had one hot dog and
film strip fries. I'll take it.
That's fine. That's mobile. We cleared the area.
Monsters Inc. blow it up of course.
All those sound stages blow it up.
The plan too at a certain point when they had that parking
garage which I think is eventually still the plan
on the other side of harbor and you were going to have all the
security over on the other side of harbor and
have the bridge have the pedestrian bridge.
They were going to move like
the boundaries of California Adventure out
into the Esplanade.
So there would be more room there as well.
So you get rid of those different sound stages.
You get rid of Monsters Inc. You get rid of all those
streets. Then you can get rid of the theater even though
I like the idea that you could have a thing.
But if we need to get space space space for
this crazy coaster.
Get rid of it and then you push out back that way.
And then I think
you could even like do
something crazy and have the like walkway
be like under the
ride
like building like have some sort
of like oh yeah screen
thing where you walk under like you're walking into
like a jump point or something
and you could walk that way through
to like the Mission Breakout and then to
Avengers Campus. You could do something
weird like that where then the show building was maybe
above and theme it somehow.
That would be a little bit extreme but
that's a lot of space I think right there.
I'll say this I'll go so
far as to say re-theme this
to the constantly changing
question mark Avengers
E ticket.
Sure. Yeah. And you can use the multiverse
idea. Fine yes.
Yes put it there just two guardians rides.
I mean yeah the song wise
Avengers doesn't the pop song wise it's not
as fun but still the technology is
amazing and I guess you can have a big
Thanos or you know what really would be
good. You know what really would be good.
It's fantastic for overlay for
this and have Galactus be
the sort of projection character
and have him sort of going around
and then Silver Surfer as well.
And Johnny Storm is a bit of a playboy, a bit of a party boy.
Maybe he's putting on some tunes.
Yeah he absolutely is.
Why he was played by
have Chris Evans replace
the role. Have you ever seen Scott
have you ever seen the clip of the
90s Fantastic Four where Johnny
Storm the Human Torch. No no no
the cartoon where he like kind
of raps. No. You should
see this. I think you would really like this.
Flame on flame on
and on and on and on.
It's really good. You should look it up.
Here's what I want. I want
Herbie the robot from the
old 80s 70s
cartoon whatever it is. You could do a great
cue of going through the Baxter building.
Obviously which is a big laboratory
stuff going on aliens popping
out robots Reeds
Lab Ben Grimm's
again like you know I want to see
where everybody sleeps. Yeah I want to see
where the thing sleeps. I want to see where
Mr.
Mrs. Fantastic conceived
their children Franklin and
Valeria. Valeria.
I want to get handled and I want to see where my friends
sleep. That's correct. So Scott
do you know about Herbie the robot.
No. Okay so I know
about this because Blockbuster had some
video compilations
in the you know VHS days.
There was a Fantastic
Four cartoon but when they made
it they were too concerned
about the human torch inspiring
children to light themselves on
fire. So they replaced
the human torch and the fourth member
of the Fantastic Four was this annoying
little guy named Herbie the robot
or he was named
Herbie and he was a robot
and he did not
really have a power set.
Quite equivalent
to a guy who can generate
flames. Okay okay but
can we get some kind of Herbie the robot
like pop and lock challenge
happening in the parks. Yes we can.
I've sent you the human torch song. I don't know.
I'm saying all these multiverse
things that they're experimenting with
let's get Herbie in there.
Let's get Spiderman
and his amazing friends Iceman
and Firestorm in there.
I've been looking
down if it
seems like I was tuning out because it was Marvel talk. That's not
exactly right. I was just trying to see physical
footprint and if this would work in either
of the areas and I can't quite determine my Google
Maps aren't lining up very well but if
it could and I'm curious if any
listeners are mad about any of this. Would you
listeners would you sacrifice
planned Avengers
e-ticket that never seems to come
and would you sacrifice all
of Hollywood Muppet
Vision, rarely used theater
and or that's Spectro
Magic. Spectro Magic. Yeah and Philhar
Magic. Who can't afford Philhar Magic. I answered my own question.
Blow it up and then
I think yeah I think Hollywood's out for this.
Yeah. That's great. I think that's really good.
That's a fun little
spirit of debate I think
and I don't want to open it up into
a whole other thing but just on the way
out the door
we could solve this later because we have other candidates
in the question I'm about to ask
to discuss down the road. Is
Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind
the best ride in Orlando?
Oh baby.
It's a good question.
I don't think
that would be a controversial
thing to say.
No but you couldn't
I don't think you'd get mad at anybody for saying that.
Pretty
I'm still sticking
with Spider-Man.
Spider-Man is still great.
I 100% knew that would be your answer.
Because I wrote it.
It's still very good. It is good. Yes.
It's good. I was in front of a family
who was like clapping and laughing
the whole time and I'm like
this is still getting me to react.
I think there's no question that Spider-Man
at least in Orlando maybe
all told that it is I think it is
the best
non-coaster thrilling
fair enough. Dark ride style.
And the only thing that would just notch
it up is how great and expansive
and exciting the coaster is.
I will say this.
I do think obviously
the theming is less cool.
The Velocicoaster
handles me in a more
slightly more fun way.
I almost
if I was just
closing my eyes and feeling
the thrill of being moved around
the Velocicoaster
might have the edge.
There's a little trick right at the end of
Velocicoaster that's hooked my breath away.
There's a couple things but especially
the thing you're talking about at the end.
There's just
parts of it where
if I close my eyes. So that's the only reason I'm giving it
pause. I think maybe overall you still say
Cosmic Rewind is the best.
But that's the only reason I'm giving it pause
because there's stuff about
Velocicoaster that I
again I can't stop thinking about.
I just can't stop thinking about the
handling. I just get handled.
I just put on Cortez the Killer
and I sit and listen and think about
these rides and when will I get to do them again?
If you listen to the long song
Cortez the Killer and it reminds you
that you're sad you can't always be
on this roller coaster. I want to always be
riding. ABR.
Always be riding. That's what I want.
Or ABBH.
Always being handled.
I mean look you can get off
Guardians, walk across the park
and board the Skyliner.
Velocicoaster you can get
off and walk to the water taxi
in City Walk
and take a nice little boat ride.
Should that count?
I'm just talking about nice
fun modes of transit
that I would like to do
back to back.
I'm just saying Skyliner
boat. Both very sad
and flying. Things that have nothing to do with the ride.
These are nothing to do with the ride.
I'm just constructing
my perfect little day.
You have a more gentle
definition of handling.
I would say I wouldn't argue
with that statement
but there's a few things
that just slightly give me
pause and maybe when we do Velocicoaster
I will definitively say what I think.
Okay, well I think that is
going to be a 2024
thing. We're getting close to the end of the
year here so that's something to look forward to.
Velocicoaster, the full debate
of what is the best
ride in Orlando which could lead to what is
the best ride on Earth.
On planet Earth. Or Xandar
will determine that I guess next
year but for now you survived
podcast the ride.
Boy, how great does it feel
to just talk about a great
cool ride.
Sometimes is it as funny as
talking about an awful nightmare
or a funny bad thing?
Not necessarily. But it's fun
for us. I think
it takes us right back to how we were getting
handled. This is all about how we're getting
handled. It's an audio handling.
There's different dialogue
at the end of the ride. Oh right!
There's some gopeteista lines.
There's a questioning whether they're heroes
or whether you're heroes or not
because you kind of just sat there.
Similar to the end of Mission Breakout.
Yeah, he says it's honorary,
they joke about that, they say they're
not coming with us. There's a weird
Epcot line that it stands for
every person comes out
tired and I'm like, I don't know
if that one works, but the other ones are pretty
solid.
I didn't know they changed those out actually. Thanks for
reminding me of that.
Exiting that, going
back through that tunnel.
Talk about topping
Space Mountain.
Dark rides kind of through
space that end with a big cool tunnel.
They did it a little better. It's a great
tunnel at the end there. There's a great
hologram
feature.
Also,
I know we're winding it down, but
there's those rides where
that was fantastic
but that was it.
I like Tron. I absolutely like
Tron, but Tron finishes and you're like, okay, that was
it. Mike, that's your
complaint about Journey to the Center of the Earth,
which is valid, you're not wrong.
It's literally a shorter ride.
I like it, but I don't give a knock
at those points.
I think it'd be really hard to feel
that way about Guardians of the Galaxy.
It's a long ride.
The person
who doesn't feel satisfied by it
is a bitter
cynical is a real
Cortez the killer.
I take it back, every person in our
party did come out tired
of Epcot, but Mike
wild away the early morning hours
at Jelly Rolls.
Not everybody
comes out of Epcot tired.
Not every person came out tired.
Hey, you can find us on the socials at Podcast
the Ride. Merch is available on our Tee Public Store
for three bonus episodes every month. Check out
Podcast the Ride, the second gate, or
get one more bonus episode on our VIP
tier club three. You will find all of that
at Patreon.com slash Podcast the Ride
where soon
episodes about
Awesome Planet, Beasts
Library, and a full hypothetical Cortez
the killer
emotional roller coaster.
I think I know where you're going with this Mike.
It's a little long so we'll see if I chop
any of it.
It's like when Brian Austin Green
did music on 90210.
I like this. I
full on like it.
This is much more credible rap music
than I was expecting.
Put it on the right,
put it on the right.
Put it on the right, put it on the right.
Sick!
This has been a Forever Dog
production. Executive produced
by Mike Carlson, Jason
Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Boehme, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to
our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get
your podcasts. Keep up with the
latest ForeverDog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam
and liking our page on Facebook.