Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following year-end holiday special
features appearances by the Toronto Blue Jays,
Dr. Ian Garvin, Captain Crunch, Cat McPhee
and her father-aged husband David Foster,
Danny Aiello as Papa, and our musical stars,
Alan Thicke and the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles.
In dazzling audio and video,
it's a very merry podcast the ride.
["The Ride Theme Song"]
Welcome to a special holiday podcast, The Ride.
It's a podcast about theme parks hosted by
we three kings of boring your partners
when you tell them about the show.
I'm Scott Gardner, there's Mike Carlson.
Yes, people say go off, King, when we start telling them
about, I don't know, Randy Gerber or the new ride system
coming soon to Universal Japan's Donkey Kong land.
How many times have there been those partner conversations
where like, okay, I've wrapped my head around
that you listen to this theme park podcast,
but how come everything you tell me about it
is not about theme parks?
Why are there stories about Randy Gerber?
Who is Randy Gerber?
Well, the show exists in a universe
where everyone on the planet is deeply aware
of Randy Gerber lore.
Yeah, well, that's, I think the partner,
if they're a good partner,
they are at least paying attention
that these topics seem to be off topic
for the premise of the podcast,
if they're paying attention.
Yeah, yeah, but in a way,
it's like it's all usurped it as the topic.
Yeah.
Jason Sheridan, a jolly,
Oh, yeah.
Jolly old elf Jason Sheridan.
I say this, Parsha,
because you are wearing a green stocking cap
just when I turned to.
Yeah, this was actually
when I was doing this Sleepy Time Bear
for the holiday party.
It was in a two pack.
It was a red one and a green one.
Brett, can I get that image I sent you?
Oh, and this is a good time to point out,
this is a video episode.
It's a video episode.
We haven't done this in a while,
a little special thing for everybody
for the end of the year,
a holiday special.
You can find this on the Forever Dog YouTube.
Uh oh.
And Jason, we've just pulled up,
or we've encountered an immediate error.
There's a big queue on it.
Yeah.
That's what Jason wanted to show us.
He wanted to show us that we're approaching a storm.
The truth.
Uh oh, Jason.
Yeah, the storm is coming.
Jason's big reveal at the end of the year
is that he's a queue guy now.
There it is.
Ooh, yay.
This kind of put me over the edge
of buying this sleeping cap package,
this insane looking old man wearing it.
So wait, when you say put you over the edge,
it meant you're like, I have to have it
now that I saw this older man?
We're looking at a very Benny Hill type,
like leery, that's how I read it,
is a like ooh, hummina hummina kind of old man.
But I don't mean to apply the sexual nature to him.
He's really just like,
he's excited about having both red and green stocking caps.
Yeah, so it also looks a lot like,
almost like a pirate,
if it wasn't to have the big ball at the end of it.
It would be very pirate style.
He's the old guy on the pirate ship.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's the...
So you wanted to, you used this guy, Jason,
as your style icon.
Yeah, as my guiding light, as my newer star, if you will.
Beautiful.
Well, there is the first use of the visuals,
which I think will come into play,
and again, go to the Forever Dog YouTube channel
to check this out.
Thought it'd be fun to do at the end of the year,
especially because it's gonna be a very clip-oriented show,
and beyond that,
everybody's dressed in their holiday finest.
That's right, yeah.
Jason's cap has been covered.
I am wearing, I've got a Santa hat,
I've got a light-up Christmas light necklace or something,
which I got from this weird thing I went to with Eva last night.
I can't, okay, Frosty's Christmas bar.
I was saying to her, I will never remember what this is,
despite being at it right now.
It was called Frosty, this is in Hollywood,
it's on Hollywood Boulevard, called Frosty's,
but there's no presence of Frosty in it.
You never meet a Frosty.
You do meet the Grinch, even I met the Grinch,
so I'm still reeling from that this morning.
It seemed like there was a lot of Grinch stuff,
there's a walk-around Grinch,
but also the drinks are named after the Grinch,
so it feels like they wanted to maybe call it something
Grinch-related, because there's so much Grinch stuff,
but they were worried about a lawsuit from the Sears estate.
That might be right, yes, yes.
So it's a little off-brand, maybe tech,
they do say it out loud, but it's more about,
you can't copyright a green fuzzy room,
that's a thing they have, is a green fuzzy hallway.
Oh yeah, that's really Grinch-like.
Yeah, yeah, yes, it's like being inside his,
well not his, I don't know if he's furry on the inside,
it's at least like being in the Grinch's butt crack.
You think, oh, okay, right, in the crack,
you think it's fully Grinch fur.
I guess probably. At least some of it,
or does the fur. Unless it's like he's like a baboon.
Oh yeah, wait, there'd be spots, I guess.
Maybe it's like you're being squeezed
between the Grinch's legs, that's what it's like.
Okay, yeah.
You think the Grinch is baboon,
do you think he has the big red ass, like a baboon?
Well, we do see his butt, I guess,
now that I'm thinking about it,
so I guess he doesn't have a red baboon ass.
Do you see his butt, does he turn around
in the Jim Carrey movie?
You see his little bottom?
Yeah, he's not wearing pants.
He kind of has a little duck tail.
I guess you see a lot of it,
but I can't imagine there's a part in this film
where he like spreads.
Yeah, I don't think you know
what's really going on deep in there.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm so glad I brought this up.
Really glad, yeah, can we add it in me saying seat
instead of ass, because it's Christmas time?
I should have said his little seat.
Okay, yeah, so is there a part in The Grinch
where the Grinch spreads his seat
so you can see his little seat hole?
His potentially. Hole, hole, hole.
I don't think, I don't remember it.
If it was in there, I don't remember it
is what I'm saying.
I wanna point out one more thing about my wardrobe.
I told everybody, let's all dress like a little holiday,
and I was like, do I have a good holiday sweater?
And I think I do, it's like a red and black sweater,
but beyond that what it is is this is an official part,
this is an official employee sweater
of my beloved Fry's Electronics,
which was given to me by listener Eric,
awesome, generous listener who we met in Vegas,
who gave us all this awesome stuff.
Thank you, Eric.
A highlight of the year in general,
meeting so many great folks, people who came out to our,
who traveled to our live shows,
so I wanna thank everybody who did that,
and Eric, it fits great, perfect excuse to wear it.
Mike, you're wearing something
that brings us into the topic.
Yeah, I have my Ninja Turtle Christmas sweatshirt on.
It's got all four of the brothers,
and they have Santa hats on,
and they just look very jolly.
I think I forgot that that's a way to refer to them,
is the brothers.
They're four brothers.
Yeah, wait, yeah they are, I never think about that.
They are part of the same.
They're the same, yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
Are they though?
Do we know, were they just four baby turtles
who were around each other?
I don't remember if there's a specific canon
that says all four of the baby turtles were related,
but they're all raised as brothers.
If people were adopted, they're still brothers.
That's true, okay, okay, yes, absolutely.
Depending on what turtle,
I mean, the original Ninja Turtles figures,
all four of them had different colors, shades of green.
They were all different greens?
Yeah. Interesting.
But not in the movie, they all are sort of the same color.
And then the comic.
So you're saying that when they started to produce
some of these things,
such as a straight to video Christmas special,
maybe it made more sense to just like,
hey, make eight suits and paint them all,
and we will put different masks on them,
and that is how we will accomplish this video.
It's possible some things were practical.
Like, also practical was initially,
turtles were all red bandanas.
They all wore four red bandanas in the comic.
And then I think it was Playmates toys or the cartoon
are like, how kids gonna tell these turtles apart?
And they're like, I don't know,
four different color of bandanas?
And they're like, yeah, right, fine.
So I need, that was not even a full meeting
to figure that out. Probably not.
So I'm just saying, you probably different continuity
has different answers exactly
if they were all four related, technically.
One of my friends of my grandmother many years ago
was really into making ceramics, like as a hobby.
And she gave, she made Ninja Turtle ornaments one year.
And my brother got the red bandana, which is Raphael.
And I got the yellow bandana, which is not real.
But even back then I knew,
you just tell a kindly old lady, thank you.
Was it not even close to orange?
No, it's bright, yeah.
I think it was supposed to be orangeish maybe,
but it's pretty much yellow.
This is a cut one, that's Rembrandt.
Yeah, that's pretty good.
There is somebody who wears the yellow now,
I believe in the comics.
I believe the character's name is Jenica.
And we're gonna cut this out if I'm wrong,
so no one will overhear it.
But also on the original arcade machine,
Michelangelo's bandana was much more yellow
than it was orange.
And it did bother me.
It was very annoying to me as a kid.
So maybe it's a pseudo Michelangelo.
So this lady maybe went to a bowling alley
and saw the Ninja Turtles arcade,
and she was like, what colors are the four brothers?
And she was like, ah, yellow, got it.
So maybe she was right in relation to that.
Yeah, based on physical media,
that's a place she could go.
30 years ago, where was she going to see the turtles?
She doesn't have the internet.
That's true.
And if her film is not in theaters at that moment.
What's she gonna do but go to the local bowling alley
and write down the colors.
Having a Paul Maul and a Tom Collins
and looking up turtles, but dirty turtles arcade cabinets.
Dirty turtles arcade cabinets, yeah.
You're right about Janica, by the way.
Thank God. So no need to.
Because I am behind all my newer turtle comics.
Oh boy.
Well, yeah, well, I think we're all very 90s focused
in our turtle awareness.
The basics, the brothers, as we say.
And what we're doing today.
So we've done this kind of thing for the holidays
here and there, and I always enjoyed doing it.
I think in the first year of the show,
we did kind of a pile of clips from Christmas specials.
We did a live show that was of that nature.
And that's kind of what we're doing here,
but maybe a little bit more guided.
A guided meditation on all things surrounding
and centering on a very special moment.
I think that came up the very first year that we did this.
One of, I think, the best things that ever happened
in a Disney World Christmas special.
We're going to talk about something from the 1990
Walt Disney World Very Merry Christmas Parade,
which is a special performance of Santa Claus
is Coming to Town, led by the Ninja Turtles,
who are all, the brothers are all led in this performance
by the great Alan Thicke.
I'm sure we talked about it in the first year.
Maybe we've covered this nine times.
It's possible, yeah.
I think we proposed this as one of the greatest moments
in Disney World history.
When we discussed Disney World 50.
It is.
And I stand by that.
It got trounced in ultimately the poll
by you tugging yourself with your mom
while Gloria Estefan,
well, from a Gloria Estefan music video.
So that's ultimately number one,
but I don't think it was in there.
They got votes.
Yeah, so yeah, no, it's the most exciting.
Obviously, we're men of a certain age,
as I said on our episode when we were talking
to Trevor Zammet, who runs the Ninja Turtles line at that time.
Men of a certain age.
We were talking to a Turtles person.
Specifically, a formative time in our childhoods
seeing the Ninja Turtles at MGM Studios was insane.
I know, something we still,
we have not actually done an episode about is whatever,
I don't actually know what the show was
at Disney MGM Studios when the Turtles entered
that incredible fold.
When you see that photo, oh my God,
it's Little Mermaid and Eric and the dinosaurs
and whoever else was in that big group, the Muppets.
I mean, it would have been a stellar lineup
without the Ninja Turtles,
and then that just pushes it over the edge.
It's a cascade of nostalgia at that point.
And we did two very recent attractions.
So now it's time to go way back, 23 years.
Yeah, we did it.
We covered things from this decade.
33 years, what am I saying?
Now we're, yeah, now we're back on our shit.
Back to the 90s.
Before we do that though,
we're cozy in our Christmas sweaters and Christmas caps.
I also threw out if you guys wanted to provide
any sort of holiday snack, not to the listeners, obviously.
Although, you know what, let's curate it.
You can get whatever you want at home.
You know, Jason has selected something
and you could go buy this and follow along with us.
So you're experiencing what we're experiencing
clip-wise and taste-wise.
And I believe you brought something
that came up in a second gate recently,
the one, the normal Today Show episode that we did,
Today Cafe.
These are Goldfish, limited edition elf.
It's the 20th anniversary of elf.
Right now these are maple syrup grams.
And the thing is these taste pretty good if you like maple.
But I ate about six of them
and I have not been able to stop smelling maple on my hands.
Oh, so you're saying it permanently stains your hands
with maple.
Yeah, you really gotta scrub your hands.
Well, I did notice, we started recording,
before we started recording,
you reached into the bag and got some snacks
and then were licking your fingers immediately after.
Well, I was trying to get it off.
That was less about savoring the taste
and more about like, I have electronics to operate.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, so we're all screwed then.
All right, you know what, maybe I'll try to,
I'll take mine with my left hand.
Yeah.
I'll leave a clean hand for the laptop.
I don't want this, now I don't want this.
I'm scared now.
You've turned me off to them.
We can take a bathroom break to scrub our little grabbers.
Oh my God, Jason calling our hands our grabbers too.
It's a real creepy Christmas so far.
Please, bus our seats and hands our little grabbers.
Little grabbers.
The way I'd been eating these at home
was I was pouring them into a rocks glass
and then drinking them essentially.
And then I would forget.
Oh, by drinking, I see.
You drank the crack.
You drank the anniversary goldfish dessert crackers.
Baked graham snacks celebrating a classic holiday film.
Wow.
Wait, when did Elf come out?
He said 20 years.
20 years ago, winter 2003.
It was 2003, not 2002?
I don't know.
Oh, wait, let's see.
Oh wait, I think maybe you're right.
Okay, I wanna make sure they were cracked on there.
They're not gonna put our goldfish
limited edition crackers unless it's a 20th anniversary.
We're hallmark cards.
I'm doing it for a 21st.
We're all dead.
Elf is dead to us at 21.
Yeah, who gives a shit?
We love it.
All right, you know what?
I'm gonna pop these.
I'll weigh in on these.
Now that I know the risks of eating them,
I'll do it mid-clip and I'll try to do it away from the mic.
So anyways, we're going to micro-target focus
on this moment from the Disney special.
Do you want my snack?
Oh wait, oh, there's another snack.
I didn't realize.
Oh my God, I'm starting to neglect.
Christmas crunch.
Family size.
So matter of fact.
Captain Crunch's Christmas crunch.
Wow, he's in a scarf.
There's fun holiday shapes.
What do we got there?
We got trees, we got hats.
This is quite festive.
I got bowls here.
We got the whole thing ready to go.
Where can listeners find these particular snacks?
Are they at your local Target or CVS or something
or must they consult Deal Vibes to attract the snacks?
I did not get any Deal Vibes things
that I could quickly get procure.
So I think these are just normally at a Target.
This is a family size.
That was the only option.
If we wanna just rip through this family size box
over the next hour and a half, that's fine.
We can.
It seems like a lot, but I don't know.
Luckily we'll have plastic spoons here
so we don't have to get the Christmas crunch
stained on our little grabbers.
So that's good.
I was okay so far, but the grabbers were not so active,
I would say.
I tried to go for the palm and my palm,
no, I smell a little bit.
I smell a little on the palm.
Yeah.
Might also be the open bag.
Mike, don't forget your maple.
There's gonna be, hold on, hold on.
I'm scared of the maple now
because I feel like dogs in the neighborhood
are gonna chase me.
It's a good thing this is our last one for the year
because if you get mulled right after we record this,
it'll be tougher to keep going.
This is vitamin D milk too,
so we'll be getting rich vitamins, nutritious vitamins.
Do you wanna, camera wise, are you being blocked
by the box and are maybe you comfortably comfortable
being blocked by the box?
I don't know, Brett, am I being blocked
by this Christmas crunch box?
Oh no. Oh no.
We gotta adjust the camera for it.
Ah.
All right, we gotta wind it up.
Our thanks to Brett Bowen at Forever Dog
and everybody at Forever Dog,
especially for getting a video one going here.
Is this all stuff that we leave in?
I was gonna say, he could, we could end up canceling.
Oh, hey, it's Brett everybody, Brett's here.
We could leave it in, we could not leave it in.
See how it plays.
It's up to us, I suppose.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Leave some, cut some.
Well, you know what, distribute your spoons and all.
Well, we'll cut this, we'll come back with some clips.
Wow, we're back, we have our bowls.
These are so much fun.
I'll try to tip it toward the camera.
Look how much fun we're, it's not just the boring
yellowish beige of typical Captain Crunch.
Right, so it's not the normal crunch berries
with blue and purple, it's red and green.
Yeah, yeah.
So this is great, we're doing something the listeners hate,
which is eating on microphone.
Maybe I won't touch it again for a minute.
And we're gonna do some clips,
something else people might hate because it's audio.
We'll make it work for audio too, it'll be fine.
Okay, oh yes, go ahead.
I'm gonna have, I just spooned out one of these goldfish
and the maple is, the smell is insane.
Boy. It is like a Yankee candle.
It is, yeah, it is like a candle store at the mall
during Christmas time.
Rolled away from the mic so you could eat Christmas crunch.
Only condensed into one goldfish
and I would eat it without touching my little grabbers.
Wow, so it smells a little crazy
when you spooned out the fish.
It's like, oh my God.
Did you eat a whole bag of these before?
I haven't finished the first bag yet.
You see, I did a Target pickup
and they duplicated some of the stuff.
So I ended up with like two razors,
two chocolate chip cookies, two elf things.
Whoa, and a partridge in a bear tree.
Two lemme rinse.
Two what?
Oh, lemme rinse.
It's a dishwasher.
You put it in with the soap, the detergent powder,
if you have hard water and it helps not get white stains.
The lemme, it's called lemme rinse?
It's called lemme rinse.
There's a whole line of lemme rinse.
Okay, maybe we need that.
Is there a cute character or anything
or is it just pretty functional?
I know, unfortunately not.
Or at least that I can say.
Well, lemme rinse your band from the show.
You don't qualify for more discussion.
All right, let's get into this moment,
this performance that we like so much.
And by the way, as with many great things
that we talk about and are aware of on the show,
we want to thank Doug Jones
for bringing this to our attention.
We're using the clip of it
that he pulled for Everything is Terrible
and on his channel, Oh My 80s.
So thanks, Doug.
Merry Christmas to ya.
So to set the scene a little bit,
this is from the 1990 Walt Disney World
Very Merry Christmas Parade.
Some of the other things happening
on that particular parade.
Urkel gets a special sneak preview of Splash Mountain.
Jeffrey Katzenberg, a young, on the way up,
Jeffrey Katzenberg introduces a preview
of The Rescuers Down Under.
Lee Greenwood sings a tribute to our Soldiers in the Gulf.
We get a little behind the scenes preview
of the Super Bowl halftime show for that year,
which is being produced by Disney.
They did like a It's a Small World themed halftime show
culminating in a performance by New Kids on the Block.
Do they do the song or do they do their own songs?
I think, all I, you know, I'd have to watch,
we gotta watch it.
This has occurred to me as something we should maybe,
actually listeners have said,
maybe tackling, tackling these Super Bowl halftime shows
that were produced by the Walt Disney Company
might be a fun thing to do for Super Bowl week.
So we'll talk about that.
Now as with many Disney holiday specials,
of course you've got Joan London
and you've got Regis Philbin,
who you think of as the ultimate Disney parade host.
But he's not the host, he's not up in the booth.
He's relegated to like man on the street bits,
really stealing the show, I would say,
to where it's like clear in the near future
they're gonna have to make a change,
make Regis the main guy.
And I feel like nobody else really,
they tried to go down a generation,
Melissa Joan Hart and Ben Savage,
and I think the audience spit it out.
They revolted.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like two maple-y of goldfish grams.
I will not be eating another goldfish.
No, yeah.
The two might be, yeah,
my maple intake for the day is maybe set.
But anyway, why is Regis not hosting this thing?
Well, there's somebody occupying the chair
who's occupied the chair for a couple years
up to that point, and that is Alan Thicke.
Alan Thicke, you probably know best
as the dad Jason Siever, I believe,
on the late 80s ABC sitcom, Growing Pains,
a Canadian performer.
You might also know him as the father of Robin Thicke,
who was on The Masked Singer.
He was on the Disney Christmas special
this very year, in fact.
So there is still a thick presence at Disney.
There's a very thick presence
for the Disney holiday specials to this day.
Yeah, he's saying an altered version
of his popular song is called Duck.
Oh, wait, fuck, I forgot that joke I was gonna make.
Oh, I'm so curious, can we get there?
Blurred lines.
If it's blurred lines.
You were doing a blurred lines joke?
Duck line?
I was gonna say duck lines,
and you're surrounded by all the duck, the ducks.
Duck lines. Duck.
I thought it was better.
You mean like when ducks walk in a line?
Well, like, yeah, so it's like Donald, Daisy,
Huey, Dewey, Louie.
It's not, you weren't going for turd lines,
like a bunch of real ducks in the park,
all left turds on the ground.
Oh, that's good.
He's following with a broom and cleaning them up.
Here's another. That's more thoughtful.
Here's another one that Disney would not allow
a little joke about the theme park's long lines.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Well, they don't hear lines at all.
I hate these long lines.
Yeah, uh-huh.
No, yeah, they wouldn't refer to it.
I think the whole calling them cues is a workaround
for even having to think of them that way.
Sorry, I do have to correct myself.
The company is called Lemme Shine.
I was using the rinse.
Lemme Shine Rinse.
So, you have hard water out there.
Look at the Lemme Shine.
New sponsor, fog it.
You have a coupon code.
Sometimes there's unpaid sponsors.
Coupon code shared in 20 for 20% off.
It goes right to your account.
Every time you use it, I get $20.
I was wondering why you brought it up.
I get it now.
Okay, you just get an extra one when you go to Target.
That's the perk.
Yeah, I just keep getting it.
Two.
My water could be twice as hard and it would work.
So anyway, just a little reminder about Alan Thicke.
And he's like, you know, he's this very like,
kind of like a cheesy, like, you know, cocky,
kind of like born to be on TV kind of fella.
Very dad energy, usually clad in sweaters
and kind of like 80s puffy hair.
Looks a lot like my father at the time.
And he's mainly up in the booth tossing out one liners.
Very dad, I'd say his style is very dad joke.
Right, he's what?
It's a dad vibe.
I think he's maybe around 40 at this time.
Not sure the exact age.
But anyway, there's a break in the broadcast.
They go back to the booth and he is, he's missing.
And unfortunately it's not, Regis doesn't rush in
to fill the empty chair, not yet.
We find out very quickly why he's missing.
Let's go to the first clip, Brett.
Alan Ninja Turtles won to see how this thing kicked off.
And I'm afraid I'm all alone right now.
Alan Thicke has temporarily disappeared,
but I suspect he might reappear,
where we least expect him very, very soon,
because we've got a great show planned
for the remainder of the morning.
In fact, right now I think I hear some familiar dudes
rolling in on Main Street USA.
That's where I would least expect him to be with dudes?
Yeah.
Oh my.
Al Bunga, it looks like the teenage mutant Ninja Turtles
who's joined the party.
See a familiar van.
They're in the party wagon, they're in the turtle van.
Wow.
It looks a little different than I remember it.
Oh, it's decorated for Christmas.
That's snowman on your head.
That's white.
There we go.
People is there too.
April is just minding her hour.
She doesn't get to be part of it.
Right.
Freak out.
I know that like the back of my head.
That's right up there with the like the splash mountain.
Well, you know it is a thrill when you go down.
Zip, zip, zip, zip, zip.
You know, that's got some viral love a couple of years ago
and I just wanna make sure that this one
is getting its proper due.
Oh yeah.
Cause that's, and I need to get it out of my brain
cause it'll be there forever.
You better not shout, don't pout, freak out.
What else to say for people just listening?
I mean, you're getting a lot of martial arts
influenced dancing, a lot of kicks involved.
I think they're doing great.
The suits are a very like pleasant,
cartoony variety of turtle suits, I would say.
It's like, it's the cartoon version.
Yeah, more so.
I mean, there were so many different suits around this time.
They did not, they were not on the same page maybe
with what the turtle should look like in real life.
Obviously the Jim Henson suits from the movie,
first two movies were expensive
and perhaps not worth traveling down to Disney World
and break them and then not be able to use them for.
They're for the movies.
These have to be functional and out on the streets
meeting the folks.
But then there's also the couple different suits
they use for the Coming Out of Our Shells tour,
which are a little better than that,
but also creepier than that.
You also, you have the possibility
that the mouths get stuck.
So if you just decide that you're gonna have mouths
that don't move at all, then maybe you're covered.
Yeah.
There was an auction I saw a few years ago
of the Leonardo costume for the third Turtles movie.
And due to its rotting nature,
the mouth was slowly peeling back
and the teeth would just look to bigger and bigger.
Oh, those teeth, that's always,
that's kind of a choice that has to be made
about physical manifestations of the Turtles.
How toothy do you go?
And they're very toothy if you were to take away the skin
on their beaks, their snoots.
You can see their full big teeth.
I find it impossible to call these snoots.
Turtles have snoots, don't you think?
Guess so.
Look, I struggle with snoot to begin with
as opposed to snout, but you have to have the little nose,
don't you?
I don't know if these are snoots.
More like a nubbin?
A nubbin?
A nubbin.
You know that that works.
I know what it is, I'm just saying.
It's a cute word.
A nub?
The Turtles nub, they smell out of their nub.
T-Change Mutant Ninja Nubbin.
Nubbin, N-U-B-B-I-N-N.
N-U-
I don't think a nubbin is what people call a nose.
I mean, no, I'm saying, but it looks like a little, like,
did a.
Well, when I looked it up, it's nubbin,
additional nipple occurring in mammals.
Third nipple.
All right, now you have some things to answer for.
I used to start it as like a little nub, a little bump.
I think you were trying to discreetly,
you're slipping in your product placements
and you're slipping in.
Slipping in my nipple synonyms.
Third nipples.
And in England, a nubbin is a word
that I won't say in front of.
Oh, okay.
In front of easily bodied out parties.
Oh, nice.
But you look up snoot,
and the definition of snoot is a person's nose.
So that is a pretty wide ranging.
We all have snoot.
That's what it says.
It says, and then here's an example,
a remark that might warrant a good smack in the snoot.
Does anyone here have, we all have snoots,
does anyone here have a nubbin?
Confess to the audience, do you have a nubbin?
Well, I'm not a. One of these sweaters.
I don't have mutant in my name, you know?
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles,
they could have any number of nubbins.
Jason's not answering the question.
He's not answering, actually.
Deflecting, deflecting.
All right, my whole back's covered in nipples.
All right, it's out.
That's for Patreon only.
The other thing to mention visually
is the manner in which Alan is dressed.
Leather jacket, sunglasses, red shirt.
He himself, it's not quite martial arts,
but just kind of a lot of fist pumps,
and points, and looking cool.
In my head, it's always like,
is he trying to be the Terminator?
Is that what it is?
But then I think, I saw it somewhere else point out,
oh, maybe he's trying to look like Michael Knight
from Knight Rider.
Those are the two things I thought.
Okay.
It was Michael Knight, or it was the Terminator.
Yeah, I wanna be the Terminator.
I wanna look like the Terminator, can you help me out?
Give me a little Terminator, give me a little,
give me some term, shorten it,
I'm familiar with that term.
So he looks cool, great new lyrics,
great new rap lyrics.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They've improved on the original.
I think genuinely so, because I have kind of a bone
to pick with this song this year,
because I put on the Beach Boys version
of Santa Claus is Coming to Town with my son in the car,
and just played it, didn't think about it anymore,
then looked back when we were done with the drive,
and he is about to just burst into tears.
Wow, really?
I think what came out of his mouth,
I think it was like, Santa says don't cry,
and then he cried and cried and cried.
Basically, the song is that Santa is watching you,
so don't cry, and we had already communicated to him
that crying is a great way to express yourself
and work through your feelings,
and now a song is telling him that Santa says no, no, no,
it's kind of a bad message.
You better watch out, you better not cry.
Yeah, yeah.
And he's listening very intently, I guess, to the lyrics.
Yes, yeah, more than I.
And absorbing it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
Because these are like instructions.
Yeah, yeah.
He's hearing this for the first,
that is like, that's like a PSA,
that's like the president came on the radio.
Right.
And issued this to him, do not pout.
Listen, three-year-olds, don't ever pout.
He's got like a notepad out, he's like, all right,
here they, okay, let me, I'm gonna take a note to myself
what I'm doing to get my presents this year, all right,
what did the Beach Boys say?
What?
Yeah, his newly favorite band,
that's working out spectacularly for me, by the way.
For him, I don't know if it'll make him so relatable.
Oh, it's apparently making him sob uncontrollably.
Yeah, yeah, that was a bad meeting
of Beach Boys and my son.
Wow.
So, yeah, well, luckily Santa wrote him a letter
and said, it is okay to cry.
Okay.
And you're a good boy and you'll get plenty of presents,
I'm gonna cry talking about this very kind letter
that we got. That Santa sent.
That Santa sent to, like that was Brian Wilson
singing a made-up song that means,
that is not an official statement from Santa Claus,
not my perspective.
Did Santa get that in the mail that night
or was it like later, maybe?
I think it took a few days.
Okay.
I had to find the right stationery.
I'm sorry, what am I saying?
I'm saying he, Santa had to find the right stationery.
Yeah, was he, have you shown him this one?
Cause I feel like if I was a little kid
and really processing,
I don't think I honed in on the phrase,
be good and keep it neat.
Be good and keep it neat.
What does that mean?
It's a little softer, I'd say,
than be good for goodness sake.
Keep it neat's cool.
Yeah, be good for goodness sake
feels like an exasperated mother.
Yeah.
Like be good for goodness sake, oh my God.
And that's the most that the mother is willing to swear.
Right, exactly.
Yeah, no, I think it softens it.
Wait, and what's the, wait, I'm missing one of the lines.
You better watch out, dude, I'm talking about your mood.
They don't say don't cry.
Yeah, that's true.
So it solves my problem.
It's a cool rap, it doesn't say this thing
that made my son cry.
And Alan Thicke's bringing the heat.
Let's see a little bit more.
Santa Claus is coming to town.
Santa Claus is coming, the dude's all around.
Santa Claus is coming, he's back in town.
You better not shout, don't pout, freak out.
You better not cry because Santa Claus is coming to town.
Santa Claus is back in town.
Almost pick him up at don't.
Yeah, he just leans back slightly.
They support, it's like a quarter of a trust fall.
Yeah, April's got her camera out now and she's crouched.
She's like taking a video of them.
Yeah, sometimes they go to her perspective.
Also the camera's doing a lot of like spinning around
and tilted, it's great.
Actually, it's so much.
I think they did it like, they just told every camera,
spin and spin.
It's great, it's energy.
I like the arrangement.
I think it's in keeping with the character
of the theme song of the show.
Doesn't it feel like a completely in the musical,
the sound font, a word I just learned.
It's in the sound font of the theme song.
The high energy, sort of the rapid lyrics.
Then kind of the orchestral.
You're a little bit in James Bond territory.
Like stepping down, yeah, half steps down in the song.
I don't think there's anything, sometimes you will see
these things that miss the character of the property.
I think this is right on the money.
I got no complaints here.
This is on brand.
Well, I mean, growing up it was sort of a mixed bag sometimes
if you would get real world versions that were accurate.
Like Mario, for instance, of course the movie,
which left everybody confused and upset,
a lot of us upset.
Or this was a second gay, right?
Where we talked about Mr. Belvedere's bones.
Which is a little, I love it, but it's a little,
ha ha, oh yes, don't mess around.
I mean, he's playing, Mr. Belvedere was playing King Koopa
in an Ice Capades show.
Hamaraba!
Yeah, which is. Koopa Paratroopa!
Oh right, Luigi had a cannon.
Yeah, they all explode the Koopas.
Yes, now that was more accurate than the movie.
Yes, it was much, much closer.
And closer to the spirit of the eventual movie from this year.
When the hell did that movie come out?
That was this year.
Was it this year?
Yeah, probably.
So yeah, the turtle van looks like the turtle van.
I mean, they never had a turtle van
in the first three movies.
Yeah.
So there was still the iconography from the cartoon
and the comics that I wanted in the movies.
But yeah, we're seeing it here.
Mm-hmm, it's April in the jumpsuit.
She never wore the yellow jumpsuit in the movies either.
That's right, wow, wow.
We didn't get some of that iconic stuff.
This is the truest live action version
of the Ninja Turtles, possibly.
Yeah, April's not wearing the yellow jumpsuit
in the Shells tour either.
Wow, wow.
So this is like one of the only live action.
They got it right.
It's really all about what we're learning in general.
It's all about either shades of yellow
or being careful about shades of yellow
that are not accurate.
Right.
The turtles have to mind their yellows
to be on the money or not.
Yeah, yeah.
Now obviously it takes a leap
by adding Alan Thicke dressed like Michael Knight.
But I think it improves it.
I wish he was in the,
they should have added him to the movies after this too.
I think, well, I've said this on the show before.
I wish that so many movies that we liked when we were kids
had that Land Before Time style 10 sequels.
Yeah, sure.
Because then that gives you room for a Turtles directed,
which maybe we'll talk about things
that were directed to VHS for Turtles.
But Turtles meet up with Alan Thicke in a movie.
There's less pressure on it to perform at the box office.
Just the VHS you could go get at the library.
You keep it cheap and yeah.
Well, and all the money goes to him
and his songwriting royalties.
Yeah, and he could.
That's where you put the paint.
It could be a full musical.
It could have been a full Thicke musical with the Turtles.
This is the type of thing I may be happy about AI creating
in the next 50 years.
If you could put into a prompt Ninja Turtles movie
released in 1993,
starring Alan Thicke with original songs
in the style of Alan Thicke,
and you could pump out something that felt right.
Pretty good argument for AI, I think.
It's not taking a job away from anyone necessarily.
Because how is this ever gonna exist besides?
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
So you're saying it's not the future of entertainment.
It's the future of past entertainment.
Yes.
Like back to the future, but they meet Alan Thicke.
Back to the Future 7 released in 1995
starring Alan Thicke, Michael J. Fox, and Christopher Lloyd.
Wow.
Is he a character or is he just himself?
He's himself.
You know what?
He's Napoleon.
They travel back and they meet Napoleon played by Alan Thicke
and then they have to fix a problem or something.
Whoa, whoa, what's this fancy space carriage we got?
I don't know, what be this devilry?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Can you open my war efforts?
And in the AI you have to specify this movie is bad.
This movie is bad.
Please make a terrible movie.
Make sure it's bad.
1995 Alan Thicke Napoleon raps.
Yeah. For sure.
That's a good movie.
And the AI's like, I'm sorry,
but you're saying that would be bad?
Worse than Bullworth rap.
Yeah.
If we could, maybe that's a fun online X prompt,
which put in your series of words you want
of a directed VHS sequel of a popular movie with,
it doesn't have to be Alan Thicke,
but you can add anyone you want.
Batman Forever 2, more Chase Meridian,
and Neckline goes down 5% more.
Okay.
Not anything risqu. Nothing crazy.
Yeah, yeah, don't go nuts AI.
Don't be dirty here.
Right, yes, that's great.
Yeah, yeah, stuff like that is what we want.
Well, I think that there is a way in this episode
that we can kind of like fuzz together these things
and make it feel like there was more
Alan Thicke Ninja Turtles.
Sure.
Granted, this is via separate pieces,
but I think all told it'll end up feeling
like we got to experience a bunch more of them.
And I'll tell you why.
At this point in the show, you might be wondering,
how is there going to be an entire episode
out of this one performance?
And of course, there is a plan.
We have a plan.
What we're going to do now is figure out
how we got to this point by looking both forward
and backward and viewing, analyzing the separate
discographies of both artists involved
in this great performance, both the Ninja Turtles,
the brothers, as I can't stop calling them now.
They're the four, yeah.
And Alan Thicke.
We're going to view their separate musical bodies of work
and discover how they were able to come together
for this great Christmas moment.
Right.
So we're going to bounce back and forth a little bit.
We've got some turtle clips,
and we've got some Alan Thicke clips.
Full disclosure, this is a PhD thesis
that I have been wanting to deliver for years now.
I think we were close to doing it last year,
but then we had to celebrate Avatar.
It was the way of water season.
It was Felice Navidad.
Yeah, but does anyone even remember
a character name for that movie?
What character?
Made more money in 2023 alone than Disney's other movies
and almost everything else they released.
Okay, so now I have to contain myself.
I have to calm down as I finally get to go into this.
The Alan Thicke discography.
Do you guys feel like you've seen any of what
I'm about to show, or can you not place
any other Alan Thicke musical number?
I know a little bit,
but I really don't actually know a lot.
Okay, great.
I'm so excited to educate you.
Because if you enjoy that,
if you enjoy that Santa Claus performance,
and there's a lack of irony there, I think.
I think there's a sincerity.
There is just diving in.
Alan Thicke is a comedian and a comedic actor
who has musical abilities.
He was a songwriter.
I'll get into that a little bit.
But basically, I think a lot of comedians
feel like they have to like,
okay, I want to sing and stuff,
but I gotta couch that in a little bit.
I have to seem like removed,
or like it's a little bit funny or something.
Not Alan Thicke.
He just dives in full throttle.
I'm a singer-songwriter.
You're gonna love it.
You're gonna be entertained.
I'm gonna dazzle ya.
And I think it's something
that we need a little bit more of.
I think the, it's,
you're seeing the lines get,
ironically, yes, I am heading towards the statement.
I think the lines are getting maybe blurred again
by the fact that Jimmy Fallon this year
has a not comedy Christmas song with Meghan Trainor.
Right, yeah.
But that said, that's not so much to my liking.
My Meghan Trainor thoughts have been said on the show.
I guess my Jimmy Fallon thoughts have been said
before on the show.
But I guess I like it as a,
I'm like, okay, we're heading somewhere good here
with the host of The Tonight Show
is just making not comedy music.
And it's not the socially accepted show tunes track
that Neil Patrick Harris or Seth MacFarlane
do in their spare time. You're right.
That is, except why do we, yes, what are those,
again, these blurred lines.
I hate these blurred lines.
Yeah.
Why do we allow crooning?
Huh, does that, maybe that just harkens back
to like Rat Pack era where that was the deal.
You sang in that style and then you'd be in a sloppy
comedy sketch as well.
Yeah. Yeah.
And look, prompt, the AI prompt,
Jay Leno, 1996 Christmas album of original songs.
Oh man.
Sings baby it's cold outside.
All original songs.
Oh, I thought he was gonna sing it to like
a Studebaker or something.
That can be your AI prompt.
Yeah.
Yeah, well that's, I mean,
my Santa is a Studebaker.
All The Tonight Show's.
It's its own, it's reindeer is its gas tank.
Is that what Jay Leno's singing would sound like?
Yeah, maybe.
That's a hard prompt to do, only AI could do it.
Right, right.
Cracked engine block on Christmas Eve.
Do you think, does any of those cars,
does he have to deal with hard water on any of his cars?
Oh, good question.
Well, you gotta watch out for that mineral buildup.
You know, it's harmless on dishes,
but it leaves unsightly white stains.
Probably applies to a car somewhere.
Well, he should use Lemmy Wash.
Lemmy Shine.
Lemmy Shine, sorry.
You missed it.
Sheridan 20.
I know, I need Lemmy Shine.
Okay, so, you know, that's the thing.
I don't think it does kind of come from this tradition.
He's like a variety show guy.
Did you know, Mike, that he, one of his first jobs
was writing for a Paul Lind special?
I actually did not know that.
I only recently found that out.
Actually, he was on a podcast that you like a lot.
I know the Gilbert Gottfried podcast,
and he talks about some of the things
we're gonna talk about.
I haven't heard that one either.
Yeah, he talks about Paul Lind.
Gilbert has some questions and accusations
of Mr. Lind that are.
Oh, there's been some stories that paint
Paul Lind is a terrible person
on the Gilbert Gottfried podcast.
I won't go into those now.
He's fishing with Alan, Alan gives him nothing.
But I do feel like Alan is, you know,
I don't wanna like lure you away from,
I know Paul Lind is your true love in this area.
Uh-huh, sure.
But I do think that Thicke brings Paul Lindism
into the 80s in a big way.
Yeah.
In terms of this sincerity and like,
is it funny, is it legit good, is it hokey?
How, what is the level on which I'm enjoying this?
All I know is I'm enjoying it a lot.
So a kind of known fact about Alan Thicke
before he was known as a TV performer,
he wrote for Norman Lear shows
and then Mr. Lear just passed away
and he employed him to write some theme songs.
Alan Thicke wrote the theme songs
to different strokes and facts of life.
So that's pretty major pedigree.
Those are iconic songs.
So as he gets this like, the sitcom stardom
from growing pains, he's asked to host things
and you really get the feeling that he,
on day one he's like, well you know I could sing.
I'd love to sing something.
In fact, I'll do you one better.
I'd love to write you something.
Can I write you something?
I wrote facts of life, you know?
So there's all of these things
that have original Alan Thicke songs,
which again, so yeah, do your covers or whatever.
But originality is what we want
because really that's where you get
like the true essence of the person.
And with all that said, I am so excited to share.
Brett, can you pull up?
Oh, I'm excited to ask for you to pull up a clip.
Sweaty and Hot won.
So this is from one of the great events ever televised,
the 1988 Crystal Light National Aerobics Championship.
Alan was the host of an aerobics championship.
This entire event is 80s to the power of 80s.
It's so bonkers.
It's spandex unitards and pink and purple
and turquoise and zebra print.
And the set is like neon trapezoids.
It's so good.
This special is kind of known.
It's like there's viral clips from it in its own fashion.
I recommend watching any of it, all of it.
But this special was the basis of a key and peel sketch
called aerobics meltdown,
where Clint Howard is putting up cue cards
telling these aerobics people
that your wife and child are in the hospital,
but he has to keep doing aerobics,
which is a great sketch.
I actually hadn't seen it really till recently.
But Alan Thicke hosted the thing,
opening monologue with all aerobics-oriented jokes.
Like, you know, the dinosaurs had two basic food groups,
men and women.
I'm sorry, wait, I didn't explain the lead up.
I should have said the lead up first,
why dinosaurs came in the picture.
All right, here's a joke.
Jogging began when the caveman spotted his first dinosaur.
Sprinting began when the dinosaur
spotted his first caveman.
Then the follow-up.
Dinosaurs had two basic food groups, men and women.
Okay.
So you're getting Thicke one-liners,
but then more than halfway into the special,
almost like they were trying to bury it or something,
there is a big musical number
where he's surrounded by aerobics dancers,
and he does this original song, Sweaty and Hot.
["Sweaty and Hot"]
Here's Alan Thicke.
Said my mind was what you wanted
Said turn you on, things going on in my head
I'm like a cool windbreaker.
Top scholar.
And see the great big hunks
The way they've bought it
But what you saw in me
Was something unique
It says it on the internet
But now you've met some new guy at the gym
And you have a giant with a Schwarzenegger neck
Schwarzenegger neck.
He's been getting fresh
Don't you let him ready or not
I'm coming baby I've got some muscle for you
Sweaty and hot
I'm pumping iron
And when I'm done
You're gonna beg me to have some big time fun
Oh darling
I work my body out just for you
I'm gonna work my body out just for you
And he's just kinda like stepping back and forth
while the aerobics people do the heavy lifting.
Yeah, step on a platform.
I know I'm not still 24
Cause if you're keeping
Cause I have had my nights
And I have plenty more
Plenty more
Spectacular
Cardiovascular radio nuts
I'm coming
What are we thinking?
Cardiovascular
Spectacular
Cardiovascular radio nuts
I love the song
If this was available on every karaoke machine
I would never do another song
I'd be sweaty and hot every time
This aerobics love song
But what do you guys think?
I mean his outfit
Let's deconstruct all of it
He's got like a cool windbreaker on
Collar popped
Sleeves rolled up
Gray slacks
And then puffy white sneakers
Yeah
He really reminds me of my friend's dad growing up too
Like it is he really has like
Your dad just got up here and is singing a pop song
Exactly
If my dad at 40 or 41 was just confident and like
Yeah I'll do it
Yeah you know hey the kids will love it
Also fashion being circular
Going in cycles
Cyclical
This is all very cool again
I would love
It would cost thousands of dollars
I love this jacket
Yeah I love that
It's almost like it's not as far as
It's like one step down from vanilla ice
Andrew Dice Clay
Yeah
If it was like big in the shoulders
Although I'd like that too
I'd wear an Andrew Dice Clay jacket
Would I pull it off?
I don't think so
Does Alan pull this off?
I don't know
It's like he shouldn't
But he just charges in with confidence
What's interesting about this performance and this song
Is you're seeing more vulnerability from him
Than I'm used to
Because he's admitting that he's like I'm a thinking man
And I don't have the Schwarzenegger neck
He's saying
And look let me try to clean this up
He's saying he can't bone like a 24 year old anymore
But he still
It's all a metaphor for that
He still has good nights
And a lot of them ahead
And I'll have plenty more
Yeah
But even in his performance I feel there's a vulnerability
Whether he's meaning to do it or not
He looks if you watch the video
He seems like he's like
You can see his bashfulness, his shyness
Yeah
It's not full on cocky
Like he comes off in almost every interview
Where he seems like Will Ferrell's Robert Goulet or something
He is like that
Absolutely
I haven't even warmed up the pipes
God I've been like there's been something
I mean I've been thinking he's a little Troy McClurey
But then that doesn't quite
That doesn't satisfy the smooths
Because he's a little more laid back than Troy
Robert Goulet was not
I don't think it was more like Will Ferrell's Robert Goulet
Than Robert Goulet was
Than actual Robert Goulet?
Yeah I think so
Yeah
And just to confirm
It's been a while since I've seen it
The premise of Growing Pains
Was that the parents were little ex hippies
Little crunchy
And Kirk Cameron was a Republican
No this is family ties
That's family ties
The premise of Growing Pains is
Not something that I know because I don't care
I only care about Alan Thicke's musical numbers
Oh okay great
I literally know nothing
I know it launched Leonardo DiCaprio
He was their cousin Oliver
Let's
Brett can we pull up Sweating Hot 2
In which there's a little like bridge breakdown part
If you thought he was vulnerable before
Here we go
Here we see
He gets real soft
Real soft
I got the cutest little gluteus
Oh my gosh
And for the listener he's like
He's making these coy eyes
He's like bouncing back and forth
I got the cutest little gluteus
I have no concern with is this good or cool
I don't know
He thinks that's cool
I mean I think he thinks it's funny and cool
I think so
And I think he thinks that the songwriting is very clever
Something I think about a lot of what I'll play here
There's like a Christopher Guest sort of thing about it
Or like often he's doing these songs that are like
What Martin Short makes fun of
Yes
Where like it's almost like it doesn't exist in reality so much
These kind of like showbiz hams with these like overly written
How clever my lyrics are
And that's like exactly what he did
Yes but then it's like couched
Because it wouldn't be as
I bet you wouldn't like it nearly as much
If it wasn't couched in the production of the 80s
Oh yeah that's
You know what I think that is like
Yeah this same sensibility in the 60s or whatever
I don't care
There's parts of this that I think are like legit good
We'll hear one later that I'm like
Yes that is completely my musical taste
Alan you have nailed it
Is that one he also just lists off various muscles
Yeah what did he miss
All of his songs after this point were very muscle based
I'm working on a seven pack
My quads are today worked them too hard last night
Let's see a little finale if we could
Let's go to sweaty and hot three just to make sure we close it out
And here you know and here he's kind of
You can tell he's like getting winded
He's like yeah you know he doesn't have it like these aerobics folks do
How old is he 40 or so here?
I think 40 or so
Yeah this gives me hope by the way
As we approach
As you head into the age
Yeah you could be a thicc
Yeah I think so
It's what I want to be
It's what I'm actively seeking
I'll be a toned up sun tan guy
I'll have Jane Ponder's part
I'm working out just working
Ready or not
Oh my
He collapses to flirt with some of the backup dancers
Let's be honest
Can I collapse on you?
You mind if I need to do the collapse gag?
You mind if I
This guy he got around for sure
Oh yeah
Robin tells a story about like waking up one morning
Going downstairs to the kitchen and then Gloria Steinem is in the house
Went out with Gloria Steinem
Sure
He also by the way when Robin's music was blowing up
Isn't it by the way now that we've seen this
Isn't it insane that he had a son that people considered like sexy and cool
For at least a brief time
You're just saying the chances of it happening after you see this performance
You would say oh that's kind of low
You just think like the family wouldn't have it maybe
Yeah yeah yeah
There's an inherent cheesiness
Which there is obviously Robin Thicke time has not been kind to that song
Yeah yeah
In multiple ways but there was a minute where like you know he's really cool and hot
Sure
Robin Thicke and during that time there was a sound bite where he had a song called Sex Therapy
I don't know that off-hand but Alan said you know I love Robin's music
You know my wife and I play Sex Therapy while we're doing it
It's a fucking weird shit
Really weird
It's at least it wasn't his birth mother so it's only half weird
It's just a woman whose husband is putting on her own stepson's music while they have sex
That is so disturbing
It's a little odd
You know he was furious about his son's like he was so jealous
Because he got everything that he actually
Exactly the full legitimacy
Yeah
I had to be a clown
I had to clown around to please the people
I was with the Ninja Turtles
I couldn't just flash my baby blues
Robin didn't have to be on some stupid variety show pretending to be excited about people in costumes
You got to chase the models around
Emily what's her name?
The hottest babe in the game and she was all his
Okay so oh and then also but he remains that's the thing he's very proud of this thing
I found an interview where he talked about this special
They said let's talk a little about the song
He said I was particularly proud of the song I wrote for that occasion
Only because I think I'm the only person in history to have rhymed the word cardiovascular in a rock tempo song
A rock tempo
One of those rock tempos
So you could do it slow but try doing it fast and do aerobics at the same time can't be done
Wow
So that's that in the interest of giving equal time fairness
I think we should bounce back and forth between Alan and his duet partners the Ninja Turtles
And for this we talk a little bit about this Ninja Turtles Christmas special
Can you tell us anything about that Mike?
Well it looks like there were a couple like just VHS released
I'm not actually sure if it aired anywhere
There's all this stuff that is just like I've discovered this in the last couple years and it's viewed many thousands of times
So it's not like oh my god covered it or anything
Yeah, yeah
But there's something called like turtle tunes is one VHS
I don't know turtle tunes
Yeah I actually didn't know until I started looking back into the the turtle Christmas
But this is like a half hour tape with original songs and you know twists on the old favorites with
Like what? Like rock around the clock?
Yeah I think a lot of that's maybe I'm
Rock around the shredder's corpse
I'm mixing up turtle tunes because turtle tunes is a lot of like just taking the melody from farmer in the dell and changing the lyrics
The farmer in the dell dude
Yeah
He totally plants totally awesome crops
There's a there's one in the other turtles tunes where they're like on a carousel and that's set to like farmer in the dell
But it's new lyrics about how much they like riding the carousel
But these are
They're like skip to my loo dude
These are like super cheap looking rushed out VHS things I'm sure to capitalize on
I was very confused I thought I knew about some of these turtles Christmas songs
But I thought they were from the stretch of the cheaper Saban TV show from later
But no they're weirdly they're from 94 so they're between the movies and the much cheaper Saban show
They exist completely on their own
So I'm sorry the tape is I believe we wish you a turtle Christmas
Yes yes yes
And yeah it's like I was trying to figure out if maybe like the splinter costume was reused from the shells
Coming out of our shells from their live tour yeah
Which is it looks similar the turtle costumes themselves look similar, but I still think they're like different, but maybe I'm wrong
And yeah, these are these are quick these are quick tapes. I guess in a way like trying to like
You know have some turtle live-action content after they stopped making the movies right right 93 just keep something out there
but they are
I get they're bad, but
There's enjoyable things about them. They didn't have Alan they didn't have a lot
They should hire me you don't hire me and you get junk. Yeah, I don't know if they could have afforded Alan
necessarily, but
It's interesting pony up that facts of life money, and you get me mm-hmm
There's still there's so much turtle stuff around this time
I'm shocked that I didn't have this because I was a tur I was obsessed with turtles
Up into like a later than most of the average kid and when I say later
I mean until this age right now
He was gonna say was
What I mean my I've did I say this before we found a bit like an old home movie where I'm
Where my mom is like the cameras off she thinks she's talking to a neighbor about how I don't know anything about sex
And I don't like I'm not interested in any of that or like girls
But I'm still into those ninja turtle toys and now when is this from like fourth fifth grade or something well
Yeah, I don't know that you well sure I hear you
But I mean like is she reading like she's reading headlines about like the kids today. Yes
She's not saying the fourth graders are doing it right, but not my good boy. She's probably saying yeah
There's something I don't know what the first part of that conversation was but then it's like oh, yeah
It's not even into girls or anything. He's not into any of that
He's still into those like I think she says she's he's still into those ninja turtle toys
Well, I'm good she got practice saying that sentence because she got to say it again. I assume up through like age 20
Yeah, yeah, no longer probably yeah
But yeah, I didn't know I didn't know what these were Wow there's even a thing
We haven't and there's no time to do it
But there's like this weird like video made by like some Transit Authority
Using similar suits. I think whoa like there's just so many weird little things that popped up here and there with the turtles
Let's keep going with turtles. Yeah, fine. Yeah, what do you want to get a hit of here? That's a good question
We got we got some Christmas things
But but you you you call this call your maybe I'll just do this
This isn't necessarily Christmas, but they like made up a new theme song for these two videos
Brett the stuff I sent you Brett the turtles one if we could play that
And I was interesting
I wonder if I like wonder practically why they would not just use the original with the Chuck Lorie
Written original it's the logo and it is the logo
They don't want to pay Chuck anymore if Chuck was maybe commanding a large fee or something. I don't know but yeah play it whenever
But it's like yeah
I
Guess they had to explain that they're singing. Yeah, that's why they needed I guess you're right. You're right. Good point
Getting the origin story in here making some real turtles being some goo. Yeah
I
Might be the
You laugh laughs interesting I gotta find out more about these guys who laugh
But if you can roll into the second clip actually now that I'm thinking about it
I think maybe Scott you have this as well
They come so the voice acting on this one is very interesting too because they lean heavily into the turtles are all like New Yorkers
But this is a baffling first choice for this for this first
I don't know. Did you see this? Yeah, yeah decorating a Christmas. They're decorating a Christmas tree
There they look they look scary. These are scary looking. Well, yeah there
I was saying there's the possibility when you have open mouths. It's really possible that the mouths can just remain open
Yeah, yeah, the gums are already receding on these teeth
Yeah, and they have the rot you were describing on the auction item has begun as soon as these three brought it
They have gums. Yeah turtles of gum. So yeah play this and we'll we'll see what decisions
the people making this made
Oh
So much teeth listeners, there's so much
They're like chat their mouths are chattering to like a little like set of fake teeth they're like whatever you call those
Yeah, it's enough I mean we have you get the gist so this is immediately there's a first thing in the whole special
Oh
Cut to Jamaican accent. Yeah reggae reggae man
Adrian Brody's reggae man. Maybe that's where he got it. Yeah
So that's that's the start of the special Wow, and I don't know. Yeah nowhere to go but down from there
Yeah, that's a pretty high a pretty bold choice to start and then yeah, so yeah why it's kind of unprompted
Why why do you need to do that island voices mon? Yeah, that's not the song. That's not how the song is generally
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, that's uh
That's the start of the special
I think where I was my premise at the beginning was they're gonna be that like, you know
Showing how these two Titans both brought something different and great to the table
Yeah, but now I'm finding that if because this happened after that performance
I like they needed thick was the like thick was the fifth beetle. Yes. Yes. I think that's right
But yeah, these are not these songs are not on the level of pizza power or
Fantastic coming out of shells. Yeah
Which are also done before yes, they were they were ruined after yeah. Yeah. Yeah, why even try anymore?
Will never reach his level and there are better songs in the special than that, but yeah
Well, we'll get to you know, we will build to what I think is the crown jewel sure
Yeah, yeah song but let me really prove the legitimacy of mr. Thick
with this one
If we let's just you know, let's let's ready the theme song of
Alan Thicke's early 80s talk show thick of the night. We can pull up thick of the night course
So, you know we said a lot about how like he's corny he's got a dad energy. He's not cool
He's not sexy but important context for Alan Thicke in America
Is that he arrived on a wave of there is a cool guy coming from Canada
He is gonna hit the late-night scene. He's gonna rock your socks and he's not old man Carson with his golf swing
This is a rock and roll talk show host get ready to meet this guy
This is this seems like kind of what the energy was before he came on the air
I mean already like everything's just late night the tonight show
He's the first one bold enough to get his name in there the brilliant pun or something thick of the night
He incorporates that very famous phrase. We all use. Yeah, of course. We'll always talk about well, it's just you know, it's so late
I'm in the thick of the night. It's like the humidity that Jason and I love so much
The thickness of night. Yeah, that's how you so when it's when it's night in Florida and you're leaving
Canoodles piano bar, whatever. What is it called? Jelly Rolls?
Was there ever anything called something similar to canoodles canoodles on property there was a new resort
Walkway at the boardwalk there was spoodles. That's what I'm thinking
Italian
Canoodles canoodles is not Mediterranean
Anyways, that's when you're in the thick of the night, but so
Alan comes in with this this wave and this hype
You know this guy might take Carson down
this was kind of the feeling at the time and it starts with the song because
We know Johnny's theme
That's all that we knew is what a talk show theme could be Letterman's on at this point
But it's just kind of like generic blues rock still instrumental
Alan is like no we are yanking the talk show theme into the 80s
We're doing it with vocals my vocals. Here is the theme song to 1983 is thick of the night
Oh
I
Don't know if I don't know the context of if they played that entire song or not they should have yeah
I I mean like I'm of two minds here one. That is a very silly thing to do
That's a very silly meathead II vibe of the theme song of what ultimately is a show. We're like
Tonight we got conservative
columnist Wally George
Richard Belzer joins us today like I don't think the show justifies its own yeah grit
But so I feel on one hand that way on the other hand
I love this song. This is so up my musical alley
Like like I've listened to that legitimately just because I want to hear it
Am I insane is that is that the lamest thing you've ever heard? No the lamest thing I've ever heard no
Couldn't even imagine what the lamest thing we've ever said on the show is no no this song is fun
That's good. It's uh I'm trying to think what it reminds me of I can't think of it off the top of my head
But is there something very similar that that it reminds me?
I know there's like I think there's an early Bon Jovi song that has some of that
The chorus part with the like
ascending and descending it's got a little bit of Papa don't preach in there my
Papa don't leave there is it mama I don't remember
The light on
We're you know I'm much more a fan of Papa knows what's best for you the response
We never played that leave Danny a yellow Danny a yellow played Madonna's dad and the Papa don't preach video
And then he was unhappy with how it came out and the message that it sent so you made his own song Papa
Papa just once was what's best for you?
He just wants you to do
He
He wants you to do
That is a really funny song you know how when you're in the biggest pop stars
The biggest pop star in the world's music video, and then you write a fuck you response shouldn't have done it
I thought they'd include my moral and message in the video, but they cut all that I love favorite of music
I left my notes for her
Ed Asner was in a Lady Gaga music video, and he wrote a song called what's with those crazy get ups oh?
AI prompt no
If it Asner had appeared yeah, yeah, yeah his well his song is his song meat ain't clothes
You know that's on display at the park MGM the little Lady Gaga's store an exhibit that meat was taxidermied in
Burbank really
The meat well the meat was in Vegas. No they had to preserve it for the dress the preserving process
We'd already heard she was not wearing loose meat. She was not wearing fresh loose meat no I
Think it was preserved so it wasn't raw Jason you hearing that it wasn't loose fresh meat does that kind of like
There's no Santa Claus
Yeah, I
Would be very funny of someone worse like stinking game to a red carpet
Well, there's still somebody's got to sit next to her. I don't know what what awards it was, but you know now like
Christopher Plummer is yeah
It's like all the Oppenheimer actors showed up for the London premiere
And then the clock strike struck midnight
They all left because the actor tried kicked in if they all put on their stinking meat outfits and walked out
Like you're calling the stinking the stinking meat outfits thinking me yeah the stinking meat outfit
You've got a premiere that you're coordinating require dollar. I make a dime this stinks
Brett can we play I have to play the other part too thick of the night too
because most talk show themes don't have lyrics about being like a
sidewalk
superstar
Wow, but most that was in the make me a sidewalk superstar
But then also most talk show themes don't have bridges emotional bridges
so here's the the
Midpoint of thick of the night great
I
Magic leave a little love some nice little plunks like little synth plunks in that bridge, too. I
Love it. I love all of it. Fly me over heaven on a midnight moonbeam
That's what that is the cut. That's what's in my heart. That's what I feel inside Alan
Got it out of me this by the way this song the same song is a collaboration with my literal favorite
70s 80s session musicians Jay Graydon who played the guitar solo on Steely Dan's Peg and David Foster
listeners might know David Foster, he was the producer of
Whitney Houston's I will always love you
But he's maybe better known now for who he's married to
He was he used to be married to Yolanda Hadid from Real Housewives of Beverly Hills
mother of Gigi and Bella right um
If you've ever seen a guy very just very cocky older man
Being interviewed in front of a piano with 16 Grammys on top. That's David Foster
He now is married to Kat McPhee from the show the show smash
Oh, yeah, that old guy. Yep, you got married to now and they were on the parade
Oh, I was so happy to see them on the Thanksgiving parade voice in
Luminous the story of us Catherine P. Really? Yes
New Epcot show Wow Wow you finally said something musical that excites Jason
I haven't watched the show yet, and I have no idea why she is a voice actor in it or what her Disney connection
I mean she's it's a wonderful voice very talented
I think an American Idol alumni yeah
But it's I think a lot of people are kind of creeped out by the fact that she is 39 and he is 74
And they are married it is a bigger age gap than me and my father
And so yeah if yes if you like Jason have seen like oh that that that lady with the nice pipes
And why is that old man playing piano?
Anyway, I could do I could probably do a called shot episode about David Foster if I I gotta really consider
What's my birthday called shot David Foster is a big?
Candidate obsessive David Foster really quick a non comedic point the people who made that so if you thought the thick of the night song was good
You know how sometimes there's these like Twitter things like 10 movies to know me or yes 10 albums
I can boil it down to one song
It is a song by the people who made that a band called airplay and the song is called nothing
You can do about it if you want to understand Scott Gardner listen to nothing you can do about it
That's all I have to say highly recommend one of the best
In the genre of yacht a or and thick was right there with him
He was running in the thick of the night with how champions is the game is
It was maybe the problem with Alan and in this song that like I feel like late night talk shows
Have we had an actual like truly like cool host?
Arsenio yes
That's right Arsenio who was on thick of the night a lot as a like I think network going like maybe
Somebody else could go in there. Yeah, but he who's also cool like your Alan and then and then several years later
He becomes like the real guy who the only guy who's I mean Letterman was like cool, but not cool chevy chevy
But was chevy cool by that point. Oh, yeah
He came out and missed basketball shots before his monologue
Which mainly consisted of him sticking his tongue out and making faces what year did Chevy become not cool?
He was
Yeah, it was not I don't think he made it out of the 80s cool
That's the last thing I really love of him is well
I mean any I like the I like Christmas vacation too, but yeah, he's these
Goofy dad you know by the time and that's that's what you like him for you know nobody thinks
Anybody was cool for a few years yeah, he was the original drummer for Steely Dan, so you bet he was cool
Isn't that weird?
Yes
Is anyone lost they're cool that
Well from being the like that like that there was no model for the hot SNL star because the SNL was new he's the first
Yeah, they anchor. He's like there's never been there's no
There's never been that this breakout right and I don't think people on TV were below 30 very often
It's just interesting cuz like it really like
There's no
Who's the coolest late-night host that's been around in the last so many years?
Gordon
Technically I think actually yes
Ferguson maybe is cool like kind of cool, but he's goofy and like it's not I wouldn't say like cool
Joan Rivers was always funny was she ever
She was already sort of like of another gender
I'm not saying your definition of cool is hanging out at the Playboy Mansion in the 2010s
Then we got to give it to our bud. That's true. You're right. That wasn't what I was considering cool, but
It's interesting because maybe maybe some of it is like
Late night. It's like uh hey here. I am I'm the coolest guy and people like no
Thank you like there's something about that turns you off the guys to be a little cheese
I think there are people who think that Jimmy Fallon is cool. I know I'm not sure
Yeah, even Alan himself on Gilbert's podcast is like he's he regrets things like this this theme song and doing the legitimate
attempting legitimate music because he's like
You know I like I should have been goofier with it. I should have been more moved now Jimmy Fallon
He understands it, you know, he does it all for comedy
But that was before he blurred the lines with Meghan Trainor right did Alan thick hear like idiot boyfriend and stuff on Jimmy
Fallon's like comedy album from 2005 or whatever he might have
Yeah, young buck. He's cooler than me and so is my son
But only them at least I'm still number three. He sounds wistful on this interview though like he really regrets
By the way, just confirm Kirk Cameron was on growing pains, but he was a troublemaker
Michael J Fox was the young Republican and I meant my only Fox was the
I didn't I knew they were not in the same that was the country
The the Wikipedia description is like it was examining the shifting culture from the liberalism of the 60s
They're the conservatism of the 80s. I didn't watch any of the either of those. No, no
Again, I also like family ties for theme song and closing theme. Yeah, yeah sex closing theme
Actually, let's tie it all together, but can you pull up a clip called NHL Awards? These things just keep coming
There was another thing in the same era
1988 Alan thick host something called the NHL Awards and he does a musical tribute to Canada and you will understand why I'm bringing it
He will reference something that Jason just mentioned for the listener
He is performing in front of a bunch of people with placards that are all turning around and forming different words or forming in this case
The Canadian flag the maple worse. There's this song who got some chest hair going. Oh, yeah
And then all the signs become the big word a
And he makes a little he puts his hand down like to illustrate a short person Michael Fox's are Peewee Herman
What does that mean Michael?
Not Michael
Canadian
Yeah, I've just never really put them in the same category no
You hear me? It's a fictional character. Yeah. Yeah, I don't think that short is I don't know how short Paul
Side but it's just that they're both short. Mm-hmm shorter guys. We're weird up here America
You love Peewee Herman, but ours is Michael Fox the guy who dresses normal and acts normal. Uh-huh
Really we're gonna get
Michael Magic Johnson has moves or something, but so does grits
Love these songs. They're all like they really remind me of like especially there's the Gufman music, but then there's
The songs that Katherine O'Hara and Eugene Levy sing in best in show about their dogs
Yes, this is like big budget versions of those songs. There's a specific kind of quote-unquote cleverness
Yeah that you have to put in if you're parodying something like this
Yeah, that it's like kind of clever, but it definitely feels like grandma would be like, oh how clever?
You never laugh you just go not a laugh. It's not a laugh. Shake your finger
You wear you do a happy wag at the song, but this one has even less cleverness. I think than the last one
Yeah, now there is a big bombastic finale here, but I think we should take a little turtle break
Yeah, can we get a quick hit unless you've got something like?
Can we get a hit of I believe the file is turtles?
12 days of Christmas. Yeah splinter has arrived. We're jumping around in the order of the tape, but
You gotta have splinter singing. Yeah, that's the one of the best parts of coming out of our shells
It's the way being stoned talks in that in the old style the old men's style, but then
I'm skipping stick. He sings like Alan Thicke
Skipping stone. Yeah, we'll get back to Ellen this really singing an up-tempo love song to fiber soon enough
This does really look like
This does really look like the shells. This might be the same
It is the turtles as well. Yeah, as I've said before that the making of any actual performance have different suits
For that tour for some reason. Yeah, well different outfits as well. What is the splinter get up to here?
Ten yellow yo-yo nine
Chopsticks seven seven more no six
five video games
Stolen for man the city people are falling in all Christmas
I'm possible that's just one tape
Yeah splinter totally stole four man all covers
The city's gonna have to totally pay for new ones people kids might fall in there
You can fall in and visit us they do which is what happens actually kids
Visiting them at the end of this it's the only way we can make friends
Brett can you pull up my turtles five?
I think the whole premise of the special is they're looking for a gift for splinter
Two comic books was real stocking stuffers back then they cost like a dollar
And one of the terms folks you saying you cheaped out well saying now
It's like four or five bucks a comic
Well the market is wrong
They hold up that my beloved
Archie published Ninja Turtles adventures comics
Oh, yeah as well which I sure maybe the most important work of fiction that I ever read in my entire life is these 70
issues of this comic
So yeah, whenever whenever you want. I think this is the right clip hopefully
Oh
Now wide open they cannot do that how many syllables are in this song
Kid on rollerblades
There's some dancing there's some choreography here a
Lot of
One of them's got a dynamic voice scarf winter's not athletic
Nasal yeah, so
Look splinter can kick ass
So saying that athletic I mean he's an older rat at this point, but teenage assholes
Ass if he has to yeah
They're ninjas they can break into any shop. They want to get any item Brett put up seven real quick. Sorry, but yeah
The sorry I'm gonna roll here or hopefully I'm right about the numbers now screwed it completely up
What is the explanation from Michelangelo having?
Charles Lindbergh white aviator scarf on oh
When you say a white scarf do you think Charles Lindbergh?
Aviators always wear those long like no, but it looks like a white. No, I know what you're saying
I hear you but I just say it's funny that you thought that immediately just with a white scarf
I'm 80s centric Jason is 20s centric
That's what I'm saying
If you're flying across the Atlantic where you're going to old-timey Hollywood premiere
You know what to help you in the sky protect from all that wind yeah one thin scarf one the start of this
They actually find the grave Rob Charles Lindbergh's grave, and they steal his famous white scarf
That's actually the I didn't play that clip. Oh, okay. That's why Michelangelo has a scarf on because it's brutal. He looks bad
Yeah, oh yeah, so that is as rotted as a corpse can be posed. I think when did he die?
Stinks dude yeah, he's been dead for a hundred years
Yeah, so play this whenever I think this is the right one, but maybe it's not who cares
Jump cuts yeah
So this is the gift wrap here we go okay, this is why they wrap
I think they're the first to realize those two words are the same I think so
It takes a lot of care
Like the shot to the like I like the zoom's in and out constantly back and forth back and forth big backlight just
Feels like the ooze from which they came yeah, this is the best directing
They tried to slap hands with each other, but it was hard
Little grabbers yeah
With the low-quality video also it looks like there's only two different colors for the bandanas. It looks like yeah red and blue
but that's
This is a rap rap so
I
Kind of like rap rap honestly. It's not the best song I've ever heard you know I overlooked it
I didn't even deliver this as a clip, but now that you put it in front of me
It's kind of got some you know got some late 80s. Yeah, yeah smart minimal
So it's an outdated kind of rap
I
Little
Few too many teeth sure yeah, you really got a good view of the teeth here if you want to see their teeth watch rap rap
and
all
You get to see real good close-ups of their little grabbers rubbing on each other's little grabbers
Like they keep flashing shots of them like slapping threes
Grabber on grabber reaction so
Turtle grabbers grabbers you got to go to the video for that that's on the
Eating gum lines and grabbers mm-hmm
No nubbin shots no nubbin shots in this did ugly Sonic have worse teeth than the turtles here
I can't remember is his I think that seeing ugly Sonic's
Teeth in the digital clarity made that made it worse in a way
Yeah, maybe that's right VHS fuzz got literally softens how just how many teeth are jammed into right into Sonic's mouth
So those are the best songs in the special is those are the best songs
That you're gonna get in
This special yes, that's there's nothing the nothing nearly as good as any of these Alan thick 80s song
I guess we I didn't mean to pit them against each other, but I guess that's what's what's ended up happening
Well, but we also this is a definitely we're not putting up the best turtle songs also no no no we've because we've covered the best
Turtle song yeah, but you know we would I wanted to do some Christmas. Yeah, so so they're you know
I give them some credit. Yeah, they tried to do Christmas songs, but again without Alan
I don't know they put in their best effort. I'm gonna play one more thing here
And this this is a whole can of worms
We maybe don't have time to get into the whole thing, but can we please pull up the clip sky dome one?
This is where as I've done this YouTube archaeology over the years this was the point where I realized oh my god if Alan
Thicke is singing in it. It's one of the best things that's ever been on TV, and this is no exception
I've seen this suggested by listeners as a full episode, and it could be so I'll try to keep it brief
But this is from a special called the opening of sky dome a celebration
Sky dome is not something from Ninja Turtles. It's not where shredder operate. It's not a technodrome. No no no it's not sky drone
Sky dome is now called Roger Center. It's the Toronto Stadium where the blue Jays play
It's at the base of CN tower opened in 1989 with this spectacular special clearly the pride of Toronto the pride of
Canada which we know Alan is so fond of his native home with that great song that we heard earlier
Who else could host such a celebration this entire thing is so up our alley that it's two hours of
sloppy live television celebrating an arena the main feature of which is a roof so that it can operate
In right Sun or in rain, so it's two hours of hitting that point about wow
We've got a stadium now
We've got a dome and it has a roof
And we've got something so specific something almost as specific as aerobics and Schwarzenegger necks or Michael Fox being RP
We Herman there's only one lyricist who can thread that needle. It's Alan Thicke, but he's joined by a special
guest another
Canadian royalty member let's play this
100,000 yes for the listeners the scope of this is so great
Black tie red dress for her
Better than skyfall they gotta go
I'm just fearing miracles
Why not get right to the point
Oh my god
Grab your phone you're in resident. You're not going anywhere. We got a sky dome to open now
approximately
1,000
women in their 40s run out in
silver sparkly
Jumpsuits and leggings, there's so many people filling the entire arena floor
Oh
The scope wow
Stare at this frame isn't am I right? It's a thousand people. It's an army of silver dancers. Probably. Yeah a lot
Yeah, it's bigger than some Super Bowl halftime shows. I got really back then they were not as many of those things
The scope was not as big. This is gigantic stage even like that stage is something crazy
Ramps, I think it allows like motorcycle stunts to happen later because again, this is two hours impact
Yeah, I do this. Maybe we maybe we do the entire thing
Well in that case should I not say how it ends say oh it is I?
Mean I don't want to oh, I'm so torn do I bury or do you hours of material?
Maybe it's up to you. Um, okay, then I have gifts for you. We can end with oh, well, that sounds nice
Okay, you know what then I won't say maybe we do have to more fully address this thing. Let's get one more little hit though
Let's play
Skydome 2 because this opening number alone could be its own episode because there's a bunch of like
Skits and numbers essentially and of course we're dealing with you know, this is a this is an arena
We have to talk about baseball and football and all the sports that are going to be played here through the majesty of song
So here's a musical number about an arena roof
sung by
football guys
I
Slide in let the roof slide in let not let the sunshine in let the roof
I was based by other baseball guys baseball guys. I was wondering if you were like, oh my god, Scott. No
I've been close with such mistakes before I'm just proud I got blue Jays, right?
I thought they said let the roof son in
Yeah, they could they could have been that I'm so, you know
Well, you know, this will just be a good tease then for something in 2024
That's why I story of how this plays out is spectacular. Yeah
And oh and it's the you know, Al Alan thick shined on this project
He gave him his his is a thick amount of luck and as he did on everything
I can't think of a better
You know, it's certainly been a gift to me to get to go through all these Alan things
I hope it's a gift to you. I hope yeah joy to the world
They say and what's the best way I can bring joy to this world than with the music of Alan thick
I say that and I also to tie it back in to you know, our full
the duet
partners, I
Just think like there's there's Christmas songs and Christmas moments TV special moments, especially that are a little like played out
We've seen Bing Crosby. Yes, David Bowie together a number of times and you know that that's held up as I was this
multi-generational duet unexpected, you know, like
Unexpected bedfellows for the holidays and if they can get together and briefly pretend they don't hate each other
Kind of although you can see it on their faces
You know then there can be harmony in this world forget them they're in the past the real the greatest
Meeting of minds for the holidays. I say Alan thick and the Ninja Turtles
I was so happy to talk about it and grow that you know, the the
Family tree the Christmas family tree that comes out of that musical number. I think yes, I completely agree
I have such fondness for this
I want to say you're welcome to the audience who thought maybe we were talking a little more about MGM studios and then realized
That it was like getting one of those cadbury eggs maybe and it's actually just an Alan thick episode
There too we got no I got turtles Christmas I think it's great
In the MGM studios installation, yeah, we'll do that another time, of course, well now there's some we got
We got the list is growing of what we can what we can do next year and we're looking forward to next year a lot
But I guess and I apologize. I don't I don't have gifts ready. Oh, it's okay. I have I just had I had some things
I just wanted to quickly give out on the on the air here
Jason I got this for you. It's a large box a large box
I saw the back of your car earlier when you gave me a ride
It looks like Michael did a bit of a wrap wrap. He did a wrap wrap. I was running very late
So that's a really poorly wrapped giant box. God. This is your I do it
Okay, and I know I got myself a fun a fun thing too that I wrapped as well
And I'll open it up. I just wanted I didn't want to be left out opening up a gift in case
We weren't like a pleasant ASMR. Yeah, let's do Jason you go first. I think is it be careful how close we go
Well that might be awful. I think I'm not going terribly close
I am a professional if forever dog wants to do an ASMR show with Jason
I think he would be interested if we can broker that deal for now run your little grabbers
He's Jason's gonna be eating maple
Jason's gonna be eating maple cookies on the mic and
It's Magneto's helmet. I got Jason a full-size Magneto's helmet
That he can wear if he wants he doesn't have to wear it
Maybe I should have given it to him at the start so he could have worn it all show
I have a question. Yeah, where'd you find that? Where did I find it? You find the the helmet?
In conjunction with Disney
I did not my question is because I noticed that there were a lot of
Fancy helmets available on deal vibes the embattled Twitter account. It's possible magnitude
I did get I look I did not this retailed for a hundred dollars. I did not spend on two dollars
I spent much less on it, and it is because one of my accounts told me about the discount well
Thank God you didn't get that account into the mess with the Minotaur yes
Few so yeah, so anyway it might have been deal vibes. I don't actually remember it could have it could have been deal
Account that I follow that has yes on helmets. Yes, I couldn't tell you what it is and I did a lot
I don't want to get into it too. I have with coupons and discounts and red card
I got that thing at such a good price. I love it that makes it that much sweeter
It's so sweet, and I said Jason's Jason's request is not expensive gifts
It's gifts where the most money possible was saved in the acquisition. I knew he would appreciate that aspect as well
But he's gonna be wearing this helmet a lot
I have a feeling around the house can you get it on before no there's too much packaging
I was gonna say you can get it on before the end of the episode
I'll try to get a picture though. I'm sure there will be a Marvel episode
Next year where that will need to have Jason wear the Magneto helmet yes
It starts he has it on wow it's Magneto then we say one thing to Jason and he goes what?
Repeat that louder you men
Scott are you?
Avatar way of water visual dictionary this you will now know what everything in avatar is called
In four these can you even name what the fruit baskets are called in the avatar yes?
I can they're pandoran fruit baskets. Yeah, I guess that's kind of instinctual
Yeah, can you can anyone even name the knives in avatar? Why yes k-bar mk13 combat knives damn it
That's gonna look there's gonna be a lot more avatar coming soon
Well some sort of experience coming to Disneyland they keep saying experience experience
Experience it's not necessarily an attraction or a ride
It's an experience, but we'll need to know and you're gonna be our expert with this book
Do you think props for in the movie and recreations of sets?
Hey Jason, I don't want to speculate because that would just kind of ruin the fun for people going into these six years
There's a full spread of both showing the full bodies of both Captain mix scores be and dr. Ian Garvin there you go
Yeah, the two mean whale hunters Garvin isn't well right what's that?
Jermaine is not me he's conflicted
Yeah, but he goes along with it. You know if he was really nice you wouldn't have the job to begin with yeah
So and then I got myself something you know what Mike get we're in the turtle spirit, so I you know obviously I know
What's it? Oh? Yeah?
Okay, I remember the turtle spirit, and you know I just got myself a little something that
Hmm you seem surprised what what is this?
That's not a turtle thing. That's a power rangers power rangers. What is what kind of animal is that?
It's a mighty morphin what it says mighty morphin mighty minotaur
Whoa
Mike
Do you need to drop that you need to throw it down?
I don't know if you can I'm worried about you holding a little minotaur what now
I have a little minotaur that I need to whoa display and have in your home
Are you sure we're happy to take that off your hands Mike I?
Think I need to keep it whatever happened whoa
It's like you need to box you need to live with it as the ultimate test of your metal. Yeah
Well under if the person who got this and replaced what I had in the package
Got this on some sort of a deal Twitter where it was only $11 marked down from its
Provisional 30 something Wow price you are saying that deal vibes themselves offered a deal on a minotaur
I think so yeah, that's what I'm saying well the heralds that is
Came to a perfect close didn't it it really did
Oh perfect yeah
Wow wow we fused minotaurs and deal vibes in a way where like Alan Thicke and the Ninja Turtles they're inseparable now
You want to get that baby out of the bars that do you keep that in the box you want to bust him?
Well, there's no window. There's no packaging window. There's no point. There's no point keeping in the box
Okay, unless you're gonna resell it, but no I don't think so
Well, I don't like that they got rid of the packaging windows for a lot of toys
But they've I think corrected of that a lot in a lot of different releases so yeah, geez let's meet him
Unboxing
Okay, well you work on that maybe away from the microphone and well I wrap things up
I believe with that tie together you have survived podcast the ride for
2023 this is the last
Main feed of the year and I can't think of a better way to do it than watching a big pile of clips with you
Guys boy, that's a lot is very loud
I'm sorry there. He is
God Wow what he is
Hmm. Are you scared? Yes?
It's a lot your hand isn't trembling your grabbers aren't trembling one bit my grabbers
I'm just I'm projecting confidence like Alan Thicke would
But I'm terrified inside
If you give him a goldfish cookie, he'll smell smell like me
Ever oh yeah, yeah have him devour some of the have him stick his neck into that maple syrup
I'm buddy the elf yeah, so I'm gonna go to town on some
Christmas crunches um
Well, he's beautiful welcome to I welcome your new addition to your family Mike. Thank you
And let me do while you play with him and grab him and get accustomed to him
Let me say thank you listeners for everything all year for supporting the show for your episode suggestions for coming to the live shows
For giving us stuff for a fry sweater if you travel for these things. Thank you so much
Thanks for sending love to Jason with everything he's got going on much appreciated
Thanks to Brett Bowen for producing this video episode for nudging cameras because Captain Crunch Boxes were in the way
Thanks, Joe and Wes and everyone at forever dog. We are now going to take a long winter's nap
We're gonna do a hiatus on the main feed. We're gonna do three weeks
Might sound a little bit long
But keep in mind that is in the service of prepping a lengthy daily
Series that will be coming as soon in 2024 as we can manage so remember that's on the way
And if you don't want us to disappear for the holiday break if you want the PTR fun to keep going new episodes
We'll be coming to the second gate where we just did McGruff three a very McGruffy Christmas
You can only hear that there and our VIP to your club three where we have one little
tropical one more little tropical holiday treat next week mon as
Turtles would say or that episodes subject you will find all of that at patreon.com
Slash podcast the ride so that's our business
How's it going? Are you handling him with your little grabbers? My little grabbers are examined helping to examine him
I will say this he does not have a furry seat. Okay. It's just skin. Okay. Um, you want to check for nubbins?
well
Hmm actually he does have them how many can you tell he's got two nipple?
He is to the minotaur but is it only that I forget is only the extra one a nubbin is the I don't I forget
Too. He certainly has a snoot
Well, may your holidays be
Rosy and wonderful with dreams with visions of nubbins and snoots
Dancing in your head from all of us at podcasts the ride. Happy holidays
Went into a little thick there. Yeah
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcast
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and
Liking our page on Facebook