Welcome to podcast the ride the second gate for McGruff three, the rise of Skywalker of
the McGruff saga in the sense that it's the thrilling conclusion or no what what
well to a trilogy to a trilogy I didn't say that it's gonna be the end of the
McGruff episodes because as we know Ray is coming back that's right a new movie
mm-hmm but that was a trilogy 789 Star Wars somehow McGruff has returned my
name is Mike speak my name is Mike Carlson join me as always
Scott Gardner that's right and McGruff we all can't believe the very first
thing said wasn't like this I thought about doing it but then I thought
everyone was gonna expect it so I said you know what I'm not gonna do it cuz I
gotta say like welcome to my gruff three I'm blowing this voice out you know we
should do we should intro you to our ourselves but also our McGruff's as well
because there's actually six hosts that will be on this show today it's not just
a B and C so Jason Sheridan hi but Jason Sheridan's McGruff impression Mike knows
that you have to play with expectations to keep interest that's exactly right
creative endeavor thank you Jason's McGruff so yeah we're all six of us are
here today to do McGruff three it was supposed to maybe happen two years ago
but we just didn't do it yeah I don't know what it well um I mean probably
some scheduling has bumped and changed it in some way because we've been
waiting to do it in the holiday season because right that's true this is my
gruff three a very McGruff Christmas so I don't want to get it's a Christmas
McMiracle I don't want to get complicated immediately but I have to
explain that McGruff three is gonna primarily focus on McGruff cassette for
so McGruff three is McGruff four make no mistake if you hear about a McGruff three
that is that isn't McGruff four you got the wrong McGruff three that's where
counterfeit McGruff three that's exactly right McGruff
Scott's McGruff thank you gruff see let's say so I'll be polite and take the
last letter here's what here's here's what we have to figure out before before
the fun fully begins there's a lot of McGruff material out there is another
album that's separate that's why I'm saying trilogy because like we talked
about smart kids of course which is the classic McGruff album that is a
masterpiece legit and then we have been discussing or at least the last episode
two different McGruff cassettes and there are four of these Burger King proudly
presents McGruff cares for you do you remember what because the last one we
haven't done this in three years I know gruff two was in 2020 and all speaking
personally all 2020 pandemic era episodes I have blacked out on
completely I don't remember any of the previous McGruff songs and I certainly
don't remember if it was McGruff one or four or three or whatever well I do
remember what we did I do remember I looked into all this I listened to
McGruff to yesterday there's a lot of jokes about hunter Biden's laptop so
there's some time we called it finally getting taken to justice
laptop so yeah so there's that's in there but what happened was that and let
me just double check my number of cassettes okay we did smart kids on
first McGruff's music career and then we did a little of cassette three on that
episode which we did the song alpha better we talked about we talked about
the song who has zards oh yeah remember czar hurts hazard short for hazards I
just got checked for zards none this year but I'm getting older so you're
always a great you gotta get checked for czar don't worry here don't have a
friend burn off your zards with a lighter that can go horribly wrong let
doctors do it with a camera a zard spotting camera we did a song strangers
don't look strange of course from cassette three I mean we can refresh if
you want some if people don't remember some of these songs but we did we did
cassette three I'm trying to play strangers don't look strange it's
crashing my computer as anyone doesn't remember my songs it's good there's
smoking doobies every shot guess he's really a stranger I don't even know
right how about the school crossing guard so nice and he helps us he's not a
good friend of my family he's a stranger yes he is how about the woman who works
in the ice cream store she's never been to our house for dinner so she's a
stranger so McGruff really breaks down how you know a stranger and I don't
I see him every day he knows my name what do you think but my family doesn't
know him he's a stranger yep he's a stranger
I don't see him every day but he's not a stranger one dinner in that on Clarem
that's the sister our strangers you know his favorite song is you can't talk to
strangers because you only have to talk to the wrong one once that's right and
then you go and then I look I look we talked about this one though there's no
room for discussion but we did this in the first McGruff mm-hmm and then in
McGruff to we tackled cassette one and two someone so McGuff do we do them all
well we don't four is still here okay we got through them we got through both of
them but we were running out of time so we said we'll save four but around that
same time I learned of a different McGruff album not connected to the four
cassettes and not connected to smart kids a separate story like rogue one or
and or I'm a gruff story yes McGruff rising I'm never letting anybody play a
younger me over my dead body I'm not letting some dumb puppy take my film I
don't so the the album is called McGruff and scruff and the crime dogs and this
is another thing and this was a this was an issue we had with the cassettes is
that McGruff doesn't sing enough on them and boy is that true with this but I
think we could breeze through some of McGruff and scruff in the crime dogs
before we get to McGruff cassette for but now is it a Christmas music no it's
not wait I thought wait I thought this was Christmas for is for is set oh but
not this I was about to go are we doing McGruff Christmas for no reason at
Christmas no I'm so sorry I'm really Jason I truly have not heard any of this
no I know this is coming in fresh yes so no for is holiday stuff great so my only
question would be what happens to McGruff for are we watering down McGruff
for no I here's what I think here's what I think I think McGruff for is we
start to get into the specials that's why I'm saying this is the end of the
trilogy is because it's sort of the end of the music just album specific
discussion and then because we know there's a Drew Barrymore special there's
a different there's two other specials I was looking at last night so we move on
from McGruff's music career right to McGruff's acting career exactly uh-huh
okay so that's what I and then we could do commercial we could do more
stuff there and that's like McGruff will move into my commercial stuff yeah if
you want the real you want the album cuts check this one out yes so so that's
what I think I think we can go through McGruff and scruff and the crime dogs
which again is this so totally separate thing I accidentally hit well play on
there why not just push play huh there are some said we all remember that that
was actually just an ad that started on YouTube scary mysterious beware some of
my music might be so we're a lot of it is I'm always trying to sell you
something I want to say also though I do have the puppet which I mentioned in the
last McGruff episode there is that friend of the show Andrew Grissom got me
and I said it's one of the greatest gifts I've ever received and boy
especially with a child yes this is a really fun good and I go hey how are you
and then she usually likes it but then once in a while she's scared right to my
daughter that is or just like doesn't like over it isn't ready like kind of
over my bullshit so usually she likes it and she gets excited especially when she
was a little when McGruff would pop up she'd go nuts she gets so excited to see
him it is funny that you and I like I think I don't know that you and I do our
kind of show personas we aren't like yeah character as parents however seems
like you had a great time entertaining your young child with McGruff and I just
found a big bunch of old videos I forgot about where I'm making my son go nuts
with the DJ Rex robot oh yeah we have had these moments of like what you the
listener would expect us to do with little kids that's true yes and I was
doing this without a little kid too but now it's like it really feels good
making yourself laugh in the mirror yeah I wake up you slept through your alarm
again I have there's an elf I have a big elf puppet now too that I do a lot of
that hmm my friend Luke got a Kermit the frog puppet and the problem is I haven't
used Kermit a lot because I don't feel comfortable doing that I want the voice
to be right and I'm trying to get the voice better before I do Kermit you're
in the lab yeah yeah yeah but no McGruff is McGruff is the best thing
you're gonna do boy you're gonna be on to something when you crack that Kermit
nobody does a Kermit impression that's very true maybe I can get a job so yeah
so I we should we could pass the McGruff around if you want even I don't know
what you could do the mm-hmm puppeting if you want I don't know it's up to you
he could sit in the middle here Mike are these are these guys strangers or
not if they're strangers I don't want to be touched and harassed by them no no
McGruff they're they're friends I are they from work yeah yeah they're from
work have they been to your home have they had chicken cacciatore in your
house not that specific chicken dish no McGruff I have to be look it's kind of
I've I have been to Mike's home but I haven't actually been inside but that's
because it's like some of it is pandemic but some of it is also just like you you
know like you do think that parties are outside you know I have a lot of good
friends who have been so does that count do I have to have been inside my gotta
see their bedroom yeah gotta see the bed I have not my
McGruff I have no idea what Mike's bedroom look like I'm so sorry what kind
of Ikea furniture or keeping their clothes I don't know what the Swedish
the faux Swedish names are I'm sorry I guess I can't touch you can't Billy
bookcases are up in that living room looks like you're I'm staying on Mike's
arm he's my guy well wait I've seen the bedrooms and I've used both bathrooms
did that I don't remember that is that right it is yeah when you weren't
looking Jason made a point of using both of your bathrooms so that he could
eventually tell you no McGruff I'm remembering now there was one time you
did come in the front door to drop something off I've come in a couple I
had to pick up a bear costume you watch wrestling in the back and paid in the
back bathroom I remember it now yeah Jason can work me give me in your house
please I can do I can I contact with this guy I swear we've done so many
hours of podcast we're we definitely know each it's the opposite of stranger
listen to smart lists that's the only podcast I know if you're listening to
any podcast besides smart lists it's probably counterfeit yeah report that
those podcasters to the podcast authorities make podcasts if it's not
our net Hayes and Bateman no thanks pal you know they're doing a documentary
about making it tell me when that's in the multiplex please see how that
sausage is made I'll tell you what okay it's a max original that's a movie that
David Zaslav insisted happen there's an article about Zaslav like poor decisions
and one is like he spent a lot of money insisting on a smart list on the road
documentary that just premiered online so it made no money off of the I look
all I know is when I'm courtside with Zaslav at the Lakers game he's got a lot
of good ideas where's your club random McGruff oh he shot it already it's too
long they're taking taking forever to edit it down I don't like kids doing
drugs but said but a 70 year old man in the company of a great but disgracing
himself character actor smart list on the road it's like Jack Kerouac and Neil
Cassidy back on the road I want you to support police but not the woke police
gotta be careful for them oh we got him Corolla's fine yeah smart less than
Carola everyone else throw him out Carola what a guy he's got the greatest
guests Alan Dershowitz and Chris should be on less they should do their own
smart lists podcast remember when we discovered in a recent episode that
animated thing the fairy tale that Johnny Cochran is in yeah you know who
else is in it go ahead Alan Dershowitz Wow of course he is
injure Cochran and Dershowitz all brought together on the plane yeah
they're smart full that's all I gotta say all right well let's get to the
music my throat hurts oh yeah let's just go yeah okay this is a McGruff and
scruff in the crime dogs album I believe it's from 1992 and let's just do so
there's some stuff to like on here but I'm gonna again say this is no smart
kids so don't expect a legit cool indie rock album because it's not this but
there's here this will get one for them one for you this is called living it
safe at home which I do think you'll find something to enjoy
I don't want to die doing it yeah
here's a song about some safety stuff introducing scruff the nephew of McGruff
the message in the song is relative so just sit right back I'll tell you what
it is
I enjoy this
crime crime take a bite out of crime let's do what's right don't you think
that it's time for us to say no to walk on and tell one and all we're standing
up on the side of the law
I'm gonna take a break
rat music is famously anti-police it's time for us to fix this
safe that is so play it smart don't mess around with that danger bitch
this is real life not a pop quiz if you find a gun leave it where it is
if there's a knock on your door don't just let him in you've got to be certain
this person's a friend you know being safe at home can be really tough so feel
free to use these words from my friend
he wrote it McGruff wrote the song my spirits in there so there's a lot of
that like there's yeah there's there's little tastes of McGruff or and scruff
and by the way I want to say this in case we didn't say this on the last two
episodes those are two characters people call McGruff scruff McGruff that is not
his name that was rough is a separate character I did that I did that plenty
yeah I was confused why the child would have a mailing address like a P.O. box
that is weird that is a you know yeah yeah the post office made me do two
names when I get it cuz you're talking about scruff McGruff Chicago
but it should have been scruff comma McGruff Chicago and only 606 don't tell
it to me my P.O. box is different I got a different address just for me for my
stuff for personal things I don't want to talk about it it's a it's a man in a
an office somewhere remember I called the National Crime Prevention Council on
the first or to try to figure out who wrote smart kids which we think maybe we
found the person who did it yeah I forget where that all was left Pandora's box of
like I don't know if we want to talk to this person this is a problem we run
into from time to time as well we might be able to have somebody on it did this
thing that we like oh yeah of an age where they might have some beliefs that
are not beliefs we want to talk to hear about or make our listeners here about
yeah yeah so I think that's what happened with the trying to track down
who wrote smart kids like you're never gonna believe this the guy who made a
bunch of 80s music on behalf of the police pretty liberal actually Sting's
all about saving the rain for us the other the real police oh we thought he
was gonna come on here and then talk about rides with us and talk about like
yeah now maybe yeah maybe you would say show us the gear he made it with that
might be interesting the key Oh the music music here yeah yeah but if you
could let yeah can I touch the keyboard that played but I think that this guy
yeah I think that this is the album that because when I called the Crime
Prevention Council and I said this on the episode I made it seem like it was
an old like oh what are you looking for a CD I remember we made an album yeah
and like I think they were talking about the this album actually because I
because they said there was a guy in Florida and I found a guy in Florida who
I contacted and he said it was not him who did smart kids but he did this oh
okay who we're hearing right now is that the singer I don't know that he's saying
but I found like remember I found this guy who did like a risk he like recently
did a recycling video like a couple years ago it's like a kids video for
like making sure you recycle and I was like oh this has got to be the guy and
it was a guy but not for smart kids it was for I think scruff or McGruff and
scruff and the crime dogs okay do have you calling the Crime Prevention Council
and they pick up hello is there a crime that you need prevented yeah well not
quite oh well the crime of podcast audience listening out on a great pile
of music you see the person didn't seem that busy so that was a good thing I
again I'm still confused what it is it's supposedly some sort of government
agency but anyway so here's something that's very much of its time it's it's
called phone card peace of mind and this is just to basically tell kids how to
use a phone card which I don't know if there was any deal made with a phone
card
safe place it will spring to action in emergency
easy to use just listen to me
it's as easy as one two three there's help waiting to lend a hand you'll see
this was one dollar number that is on the back to enter your pin number it's
as easy as that three dollar number that you want to reach
help get someone to teach you won't need a coin there's no need to worry it's
okay it's a caught you call a number enter a pin number then or the phone
number you want to reach is this like is this just for me to use day to day can I
use this if I want to talk to grandma or is this how I'm supposed to like if I'm
getting attacked if there's a lot of questions here simple but I did leave me
with a few questions yeah okay here number one the card helps know that it
helps I guess number two take it out read the back dial one number then put
in a different set of numbers there I like that boy I have to wait for it
depends on the phone then put in another set of numbers for the phone the phone
you're trying to call do you know how I have the card did you are you do does it
come with this album no $10 card you got to get it from your parents so it
doesn't need a coin it just needs just means that the game was already dealt
with but it's not part of the whole process of calling like a normal pay
phone in 1992 okay the coin exchange has already happened so that's where the
convenience yeah that's right so the song is clear and it's pretty good and
helped a lot of kids so I hope I hope you know everyone remembers this and
probably got out of a good jam or two with this so I was that oh yeah I saved
lives yeah I saved a couple lives at least when the kids got a phone card and
they remembered this song cuz it's so catchy yeah they remembered how it
worked I could have spent upwards of $10 have they used one eight on your collect
that is what I was like doing their collect call this is often how those and
those would all usually have someone 800 like yeah like a jingle you would
remember yeah and not like a very tuneless song that's just telling you
can't name the numbers behind yeah so I don't did anyone have a photo you have a
phone card we were a kid I don't know I think so I remember being given one I
think when we went on the you know high school DC trip Oh high school really to
use the you know pay phone down the hall use the phone card yeah I gave you
that that was you a neat thing you would have never known what your parents are
you could have parents could have been killed I never would have known about a
lot of kids tried calling into the card itself and using that as a phone but it
didn't work cuz it was only a piece of paper a lot of kids are fucking idiots
the dumbest kids picked up the card and said hello hello mommy please that's
not how cards or phones little high school Jason called into the card a few
times until he remembered my song the tune of my song oh wait yeah I have a
pin and then I call the number and then I call the actual number okay the song's
not over let's listen to what the rest of the song is hold on
it's not like the other phone cards around
by far the best one that we found got a picture of a dog on it gives you the
power of communication stores a lot of important information
even speed dial to call the police don't leave home without one of these
okay the police you call 9-1-1 there's no reason to speed dial the police yeah
with a calling card or whatever well the speed is 9-1-1 isn't it of course dial
that fast yeah but if you know the cards number real you got to go fat you can do
it fast that way to 9-1-1 is sometimes too slow okay it's a different line
actually I guess you're like let me give you some credit when it was the turn oh
that's true that you know that like that really nine you got a loop all the way
back around is that what you were thinking McGruff yeah that was it what
this one is just one one one one one so it's actually faster yeah yeah and you
taught kids do you ran drills how fast can you one you taught them yeah it's a
song I was working on that I never made it how fast can you one like run no
listen up got waxing your ears got another ear infection I'm finding it
impossible to believe that we were gonna get to the Christmas song yeah I could
go back what if well what if we'd save some of the songs that it was a word
there's no way we could do another one oh yeah okay you're right you're right
we could songs in I mean I'm enjoying this very much but it's gonna be right
you're right we get to a point where it's like all right so half of McGruff
Christmas will be in spring 2026 the last episode we did we did two things so
I felt like we could get through it but you're right there's no way we're
getting through this well we can if we give we pick up the pain you're right
you're right no we're not and we can why would we want to do that though yeah
let's go okay you're right each one of these has 25 minutes where I'm gonna
opening about it being a trilogy and then they can learn our process discover
on the fly yeah like see we're not so bad we're kind of smart like my bootleg
sausage okay McGruff McGruff cares for you cassette for this is called gift wrap
I will say these are the most confusing songs out of all the four cassettes
narratively you almost have to hear
now I like this by the way
tired well you don't always need money to buy a gift to go to someone very
special wrapped in paper big your gift can be your helping mom gets to great
letter to a friend out of state
just cleaning up your room long before you dad get mad and had to tell you to
not bad no not bad at all
it ain't just forgiving your little sister when she broke your favorite
skateboard or video bike or a pen
your favorite video bike
forgiveness is a great gift too
but what would you do with it
I was guessing toys that might come in the future
they love their engines they love video bikes
does that sound cool you'd want one
be first in line
something to wear something to share just in a on a show
this is confusing this song is really all over the place
again
I'm not sure what to do with this
this song is really all over the place
a good gift is like forgiveness
but also it's like a regular gift is good too
I like some of those keyboard things
yeah, I liked it until the boy
showed up
yeah, the rapping
this next song is called
golden age rock
and this is about
going to a retirement home
and decorating it
for Christmas
hi troops
what's all the excitement here?
sounds like a party
hey McGruff, you're just in time
could you please grab that box over there?
sure, but what's going on?
we're going over to the golden age
retirement home
to help them decorate for the holidays
great, let's go
hehehe
hey Mr. Anderson
merry Christmas
happy Hanukkah Mrs. Myers
gang, let's decorate
grab all the ornaments
and light up the lights
we're going to make this place sparkle
tonight
don't use the blue
put the blue away, red and green
we're sticking to the blue
I'm clapping stairway banisters
in gardens of deep green
then I'm adding lots of bright red bows
the biggest you've ever seen
I'm laying some bows
a fresh cut pine
a complimental piece
so everyone
can enjoy the set
when it's a marble year place
I hung
the Christmas wreath I made
over by Mr. Blair
Mr. Blair
he said he wants to look at it
from his favorite
overstuffed chair
hey here comes Mrs. Carpenter with cookies
I can't wait
she said she made them just for us
those are mine, I drove us so
I get them, I get first duty
if I have any room left I'll give them to you
I came here for Mrs. Carpenter's cookies
dogs love chocolate cookies
I'll have them but I'm going to
take a bad shit tonight
I'll regret it later but they're going to be good going in
thank you so much Mrs. Carpenter
for these cookies
Mr. Blair is an asshole
he won't give me any of his treats
and you know what
Merry Christmas Mrs. Carpenter
and Mr. Blair whatever it is you do
whatever you do your thing
yeah
this is really
the kids, first of all
this was on the other cassettes
but the kids singing, these kids are awful
these kids are terrible singers
make a special treat
like there's one part where the kid comes in
and he just couldn't be more off
on it, which I mean I guess
I like it about this
I chose them based on how good
they were as people
not how, not singing
ability, you've been to Hollywood
ever, performers
are corrupt sinners
they're trouble
that's the voice of an angel
I also didn't want to
I didn't want them
overshadowing me in my vocal talents
they're gonna make me look better
by comparison
let's finish this out here
care for me
I heard it's Mr. Bair's birthday
he got new dancing shoes
he said he wore his last pair out
while we say happy 82
when on the road
he said he was a little bit sad
wait until you see
the nice display
on the second floor
I found
the perfect table there
and we set up the menorah
alright, wait, wait
hold on, they don't deserve a rhyme
yeah, you can put it in the corner
I'm more comfortable
with that there
it's their fault for choosing words for things that don't have rhymes
I just, look
there's a war on Christmas
and truth is I
we gotta get it
we gotta get it more prominently displayed
the Christmas tree, you know
and then there could be a little menorah in the corner
I for one am glad that in the next presidential election
everyone will be of the
ages of the people
in the golden age home
they're in the golden ages of their lives
they're in their primes
I don't want anyone
south of 50
running my country, I'll tell you that
I'd like Mr. Blair to run
as a third party maybe
but that's about it
I'm starting a fundraiser for Mr. Blair
Mr. Blair's got a lot of the same Robert F. Kennedy
beliefs which I'm
finding more appealing
day by day
the older I get the more I like the sound of it
so this is a nice song
a song
I'll say this, I don't even know you consider this a song
it's technically a song
with melodies and stuff but it's not
so memorable
da da da da da
you say that but it's possible I wake up from a sound sleep tonight
it's a nightmare version of
Rock Around the Plants
I found a table
clop of fine brown steel
the menorah
shines so brightly
say can I have a glass of milk
Anthony
it's so much fun
we are a band
hanging from the ledge
all the other
beds are sparring
the tinsel is so shiny
well everything is ready
there's nothing left to trim
we wish you joy
we wish you health
we wish you happy holidays
we wish you friends
and fun with love
and Anthony
Miguel and Joy
happy holidays to our friends of all ages
now with respect to all you seniors
I know some of you have your various
conditions or what have you
those kids and I
just really sweated it out doing that dance
you stand up
you show us the respect you get on your feet
I don't care how your body feels
get up, you, all of you
nurses
make them stand
pull their chairs out
please clap
I can't hear you
empty your
pockets
for gas money
we don't work for free
you know
while you've been applauding I've had Anthony
go through your stuff in your personal rooms
I've flexed a lot of you
the trick worked
we're in
all your wills now
McGruff and the gang
it says, you're leaving me that
menorah
I'm taking that
I'll put some real candles on there
put it on the top of my
Christ and Mary on them
put it on the top of my Christmas tree
it's a Christmas tree topper
Mr. Blair
McGruff just like
holding
like just right in front of his face
Mr. Blair screaming at him
some of these
okay, there's a song called
Heroes here
what do you mean we're not allowed back at Golden Age
to retire at home? We decorated
we put up a tinsel
we gave him some joy for once
you have to let me in, I have power of attorney
over most of these residents
I set up those wills, that's how I knew how to insert us in them
Mike, you keep holding the
puppet to your face
like he's whispering in your ear
yeah, yeah, I'm telling him what to do next
yeah, see what the top
of the clock tower is like
you can really toot some people up there
who's really running the show at this point
is it the McGruff voice or is it me
it's like the Twilight Zone episode
if listeners did a percentage breakdown
they'd probably
70% was McGruff voice, the rest was the hosts
I like when I have to
do something practical like move the computer a little
and I just like
wait let me document that, put your mouth on
yeah, you keep holding the corner
that's really cute actually
like this
okay, this song is called
McGruff's Holiday Surprise
oh no
it's not what you think
the golden age is getting a surprise
a big bag of my shit on the door
my chocolate chip cookie shit
they did it to me, Mrs. Carpenter
it was worth it though
hey McGruff
happy holidays
well happy holidays to you too
what's everybody doing here
we have a surprise for you
what's up for you McGruff
oh boy I like surprises
is it that you all straightened up your rooms
no I mean we did
take me to all of your rooms
well is it that you
cleaned some graffiti up in your
neighborhoods
not really, uh no
since it's the holidays now, we're at five
each of us wanted to say thanks for everything
you taught us this past year
and show you how glad we are
that you're our friend
we've talked about this before, other songs
are very much into like
building up McGruff as like a Jesus-like
figure, and like you have to
praise him, and this is one of those
one of those songs where it's
like we gotta tell you how good you are, McGruff
let's hit it
McGruff, he is the cry dog
he's our friend
and there's no doubt
he's on the scene to talk about
what's really going down
need to double up
no matter what your problem is
I'll never let you take a fall
he's just sitting there not responding
positively or negatively
it's good, continue
it's a gift to song
I learned to speak up loud and clear
into the phone's mouthpiece
so he taught this
little girl how to talk into the phone's mouthpiece
she's claiming at least
closer, get it in there
hey dummy, flip it
it's not gonna bite you
I will if you don't get it right
don't remove the keys
from the phone
before you try to talk into it
come on, what are you doing
don't swallow it
you're dialing 818
you're pulling the 8 out of
the phone console itself, that's not how
it works, you have to hit the button
somebody needs to go to
how to 1 class again
I had a scare
with no one there, I smelled
some smoke, and then
I dropped down low below
the smoke, got out and I ran
and ran, without
delay I sped away
and was helped by a friend
the fireman
came and saved the day
blasting on the truck siren
what does that have to do with McGruff
stay on topic
he's more like
Smokey the Bear's domain
right? don't say his name
I know, I taught him
about the smoke thing and how they gotta get
down and be careful
I helped the fire department out too if you
didn't know, he pretty much stole
it all, I set that fire to teach
a lesson
chaotic good
I was there in case it went bad, don't worry
I had an axe ready at the door
I had a dying extinguisher, it expired
but it was still good
it was like a David Fincher's the game
thing going, I created
a scenario, I was always in control
she fell through the glass but there was padding
yeah, totally
controlled
so I guess they're thanking McGruff for that
I said
blasting on the truck siren
it's weird how he's
dropped off
yeah, he left, he's gone
you didn't even notice
you weren't paying attention to your surroundings
I'm in my home
I clocked out for the day
I left minutes ago
your rap wasn't good enough to keep
me here
my sister and her friends
and I walked away, cause we aren't
fools
you're just a loser
I'm always
a loser
you kids are winners
this is something we happened upon last time too
is that sometimes when McGruff is singing in these cassettes
he sounds completely drunk
I told you losers
I'm at home
I'm drinking with Johnny Walker
my friend
McGruff, you're drunk
yeah, so he
sounds like that for some reason in these cassettes
just say no
thanks a lot from Joy
Anthony, Miguel
and Anne
and we know there are many more
who will be joining in
so McGruff, they're thanking him for
teaching them how to use a phone
in general
and then knowing
to get out of the house when there's a fire
and then three, saying no to drugs
which is something we know he says
that's a thing we've heard him say
but they're attributing a lot to him here
they could have put this in a card
well that's true
because then at least he could put it on the mantel place
you know
but it's still like, thank you McGruff
for teaching me how to eat
meals are so much better now
I used to put the food
on the floor
and now I'm no longer
doing that
plates don't work upside down
I have an adult friend coming over
we haven't really had the conversation yet
so it's more of a situation
you know what
it'd be best if you kids got out of here
yeah but
tell me what all their good stuff
but write it down
I'll hear it later
I'll peruse it at my own time
Mrs. McGruff
oh Jesus, not Mrs.
don't tell Mrs. McGruff
I'm not telling, I'm not doing marriage game
but Mrs. McGruff doesn't know
it's me and Bill
Marr have the same opinion about marriage
she doesn't know I rent at this apartment
address so
we both have about 7 young
girlfriends, we rotate
that's what he does, that's what I do
I take my cue from him
is her 23, mine are 2
it's okay
it's different with dogs
I also only eat seeds regularly
that's basic
he got it for me
he's scurrying about at the base of a tree
then he started doing it too
he got it all on his hind legs
num num num seeds he said
we'll talk about it on our
episode when it comes out
now you
I taught you the seed thing
you don't ever give me credit
what's up with that Bill
I'm getting loose
I gotta watch my mouth
I'm gonna end up saying
say yes to drugs
I can't have that on tape, cut that
cut that
I think my acid
reflux is being triggered by the McGruff voice
oh no, it's okay
then Mike threw up onto the microphone
it's worth it
retiring that windshield
it's yellow stain
none of us have puked during an episode yet
that'll be interesting
or come close
let's see how much Green Day talk
there is in 2024
I'll tell you what, the punk band
I like, the only good one
the only one
we haven't talked about that on the show
we don't have time, but we found
this was a Tim Heidecker find
that he and Sharpling talked about it
that there's an episode where
Bill Maher just, I hate all punk music
it's all junk, it's all three chord
crap, and then who is it
is it Jeff Ross
in a remote of The Clash
crap, bunch of crap, fuck The Clash
crap, you know there's one
punk band I like though, Green Day
now those guys
now that American idiot
that's perfect, that is great
so never forget
Mike has the same taste in punk music
well, hold on
it's funny, because the first wave of
punk music is like 50
years old, and Green Day
early Green Day is like 30
years old, yeah that's why they perfected
it, they got around
to see what didn't work
toss that in the garbage
yeah, yeah, we gotta go
on Club Random, I gotta find out more
I wanna know, I don't know, yeah I think
that's a, all three of us wouldn't go on Club Random
I think that's a one, yeah
we don't wanna get in the way
I wanna be photographed in the same frame
you guys at 5am
like, oh and here I go
now I'm gonna put on 21 guns
oh perfect, listen to that on my
hi-fi, that sounds perfect
hey uh, should I bring the girls
in?
they've been
they've been doing
a lot of pills in the pool house
as I told them to for hours
Mike, I'm willing to introduce
you, I'm married
so pfff, not
in Club Random you aren't, nah the roles
are different, McGruff's there
too, I'm here too, yeah
McGruff
you guys like the album
Nimrod?
it's a good one
it's pretty, you know what, they honestly
they get into kind of the musical stuff
and that's what I, the albums are statements
and there's a reason it made it
to the Broadway stage, because that is
songwriting, yeah
yeah, I like to see the Ramones do
that
make a eight minutes
Buzzcocks, I'm offended by the name
bleh
makes me wanna puke
or shit out chocolate chip cookies
sexy pistols, that's filth
I'm offended before
I've even read the album title
sex walk away, pistol leave it there
hahahaha
uh, uh, alright
okay, let's see here, okay
uh, oh god, the resolute, I think this one's
really boring but I'm gonna play it
Resolutions is what this is called, because
it's the end of the year
McGruff, my sister said she's
making a list of New Year's resolutions
for next year, what's a resolution?
well a New Year's resolution
is usually a promise you make to yourself
you've entrusted me into the program
to try to do something better for yourself
or for others in the coming year
who wants to make a New Year's resolution?
I do
my grandpa's friend Barney
he lives all alone
except for his strife cat
named Blue
I know he gets lonely
when grandpa can't come
so I think I'll go visit him too
what a great idea
lots of terrific older folks
who maybe can't get around so well
would love to have regular visits from you
theme
I put a theme in it like Green Day
coloring motifs
what about you, Miguel?
on Saturday mornings
I'm taking my bike
down to our community square
it's gotten so messy
from littering folks
I'll help pick up all the trash there
terrific
lots of neighborhoods have community centers
needing volunteers to help with all kinds
of activities
giving them your morning
will make anything you do in the afternoon
twice as much fun
because you can feel really proud
of being a volunteer
I noticed a sign
in the grocery store
help, we need a sitter
it read
for a three year old girl
that's for money
that's not going to count
volunteering is what we're talking about
hey hey
babysitting is a tremendous responsibility
so lots of what you've learned
about locking doors
and knowing important phone numbers
can really help you here
I see Anthony has one too
clean up all the graffiti in their house
a lot of this is trying to figure out
how to get free labor out of children
yeah, that's the resolution
is I'm going to answer a stranger
wait, a stranger's ad
at the grocery store
also grandpa's friend, you're going alone
to hang out with grandpa's friend?
that's what they said, right?
yeah, grandpa's friend
his friend's a grandpa, he's not a stranger
because McGruff has the criteria
for if this is a stranger or not
so I guess grandpa's friend
would
can he be not a stranger?
presumably grandpa's been over
had him over for dinner
yeah, but what if it's grandpa's friend just in the home
and it's more of like a new friendship
and he doesn't know
like, I don't know
that could be a little dicey
this seems like a city that should reallocate
some funds to community centers
and elderly care
well, I'm fighting with myself
with my thoughts
I think that we should maybe
just use an army of children
to fix a lot of the problems in society
army of children, all the budget goes to the cops
to buy tanks
yeah, there you go
that cops need cooler tanks
qualified immunity is expensive
they need to get those
big exoskeletons like in Aliens
like the big walkers
every cop needs a mech
I think, we talked about this last time
this feels familiar
well, any kid can be
adult sized if put in a mech suit
yeah, but those are for the cops
not kids
well, I think
I disagree with you, other McGruff
but it turns a cop
into a super sized man
but it turns a little kid into a ripple
grown adult
who can clean up graffiti for free
money goes to suits, doesn't it kids?
we should
find a kid in a mech suit
to babysit your child
if a stranger comes to the door
super babysitter
they'll be able to kill them
quickly like Robocop
crush their heads in
so yeah, resolutions
yeah, okay, resolution
you go visit an old person
but then yeah, babysitting
is also
a resolution
I answered
an ad in the grocery store
it said, I want one little
girl to come over soon
no questions asked
we swear it's for babysitting
and not for anything
else, sounds good, no red flags
there, glad you took the number
give them a call, get over there ASAP
make sure you say it out loud on New
Year's Eve
keep an eye out though
if the family is too perfect
like a running scared situation
hey kids, you wanna watch
this R rated movie, running
scared, so you can learn
things, I don't think I know what the situation
in running scared is, there is
a thing where it's like
serial killers
and they look very like
leave it to beaver and stuff
and they're killing kids and other people
that's what happens in the Billy Crystal movie
running scared, no, no, the Paul Walker
movie running scared, oh gosh
cause I only know the Billy Crystal one
has the Michael McDonald song Sweet Freedom
which is a lot of tropical fun
I bet this doesn't have like child
murders in it or whatever
do you think McGruff's watching
a movie where they're
portraying a leave it to beaver type family
as evil, that's
that's not correct
people that look like that are good
they're always doing right, yes
pipe smoking dads are the perfect
dads and white children are the best
rappers, white
50's people never
did nothing wrong
remember that
and the media they produced also
was right, so Paul
Walker, God rest his soul though
I don't want to disrespect
but I don't like
the type of film he made
Pleasantville either
with all it's orgasming and stuff
oh yeah, it's about upending 50's
too much criticism in that movie
I don't want to hear it
I plug my big ear dog ears
I liked the beginning before
it tilted, before the
premise kicked in, I did hear that this show
talks a lot about a guy named Don Knotts
I do like
the sound of that folks
and there's a repairman
excuse me, let's go to
Santa's Helpers
I will tell you a story that is quite true
it was told to me by a caribou
who lived up near the cold north pole
he said it's true and he ought to know
tell us, tell us, let us know
what the caribou said from the land of snow
he said
in Santa's workshop
there were two elves
and they were
the elves were the ones
who were the most beautiful
and the elves were the ones
there were two elves
whose department painted
all the shelves
where brand new toys
were put away
waiting to be delivered
on Christmas day
one was named Wink
the other was Bip
while one worked hard
the other was Flip
Wink was happy to share a task
the one called Bip
would never think to ask
Elf or Wink
was very elfish
the way we all should be
wait, elfish is good?
yeah
wait
that's really confusing
elfish is good but selfish is bad?
we gotta be very clear here
Wink is an elf
and he is very elfish
he's helpful
and Bip is an elf who is selfish
and if you heard her just sing
it led to his misery
oh god
this is a story song about two elves
Wink and Bip
original characters as far as I know
this is like a goofus and gallant situation
yes
but Bip is riddled with misery
I was gonna say goofus wasn't riddled with misery
was he? he should have been
I'd like to make Bip
do an ice walk like in Dark Knight Rises
I hope that
I hope it cracks it within five steps
Bip should be
in the cold brink
Bip might get some of that visual anti-justice
that Vera Farmiga
dishes out in Running Scared
my favorite film
I can't look away
I hate it but I can't not watch it
uh
McGruff yeah so this is
these are original McGruff characters too
Bip and Wink
but the
elfish is good
elfish yeah
why are the
it's like people that have never written a song
writing all the melodies for this
as they go
this is like the improv
piano guy at the Chicago
Laura Hall on the piano
yeah
well you know
worker hourly worker rights
Bip might be in the right here
you don't make this a workers rights issue Jason
if they're not paying
time and a half or double time
you know you gotta they'll find a way to screw you
you've got the right to do the work
I tell you to do
keep your mouth shut
you want me to replace these names with two regular names
for people that work at a McDonald's
cause I feel the same way
you gotta be positive all the time
happy with whatever lot you've gotten in life
when I order at the drive through
I always say alright an egg McMuffin
and a coffee
hey and keep it elfish back there
I want to see everyone's face at the window
Merry Christmas
I didn't see a smile
a big smile there
I wanna can I lean my head in the window too
and see the guys making the burgers
I want to see that they're laughing
and having a good time
I want to see the guys
laughing and having a good time
let me touch some of your machines
and make sure they're properly calibrated
let me behind the counter
I want to get back there
put an apron on
uh yeah
so this is uh
just I guess they're trying to say you should be
helpful and not unpleasant
which I suppose is a decent
lesson I guess but I don't know what
McGruff is trying to say
they're really reaching on McGruff's
created for here
he's like they're trying to make him like a catch all
for just like advice for children
yeah yeah it's not just law
it's basic morality
it's yeah well based on morality
but basically just like getting bought like
like if you're on a first date
always ask questions about the other person
yeah like
why would that be McGruff but that seems like that could be
in there if there's time to
lean there's time to clean
children have no right to privacy
and are their parents property
uh McGruff would be
tuck your shirt in while you're in
it shows disrespect
I'm happy with what the speaker of the house and his son
are doing
keep each other honest
I have encouraged
wink and bip to
be on a chain
where one is alerted if
the other is being selfish
but both are rewarded with a nice
vibrate if they're both
being elfish
uh so I wonder if they I
don't there was a book somebody sent me a book
and we looked at it last time
and it was it was not it didn't have
like a lot of notes about the songs but I wonder
if there was ever any like
artwork of wink and biff I don't think
a bit excuse me I call them biff
wink and biff whatever
I thought of this in two fucking minutes
oh the puppets nodding off
like
I'm tired
how do you do this for so long
keep it short and sweet
like smartless
they get what their points
out in a nice tidy
hour I assume
and they got big stars too have you ever had
Tina Fey on this
well they're friends or it's tough
we have who we like but we don't you know
we don't know everybody
bossy pants writer Tina Fey on here
I ain't thinking of this as legitimate
you dipshits don't seem to have any
stories about making Will & Grace
laughter
I like when Debra
messing tweets that's all I know
laughter
wait was she Will & Grace yes
yeah she was
Jenna Elfman is Dharma & Greg okay got it
I don't know what she tweets about
we need their voices right now with what's going on
in the world
uh let's see
tomorrow please
those bright red those snow white
those deep green
Biff stared up and cried
out to himself it can't
be done it's too much hay for
one elf Biff worked past
8pm he worked past
10 and he worked till 8
o'clock came around
again yet as the sun
played peekaboo
Biff still had
over half the shills to do
outlawing
now it's starting to seem like
slavery like now it's starting to seem
like a worker abuse
the first set of musicians
on this record were a bunch of Biffs
where are they today
well they're all a bunch of drips
they ain't got no music
producing jobs
but now I got all now it's a full
crew of Winx right let me see you
smile Winx don't
care if you say you're doing a 72
hour shift with no breaks
they won't complain to you
Briggs on the other hand
don't care if you cover up the
signs in your places of
work that have all the labor
rules and minimum wage
if you cover those up with signs that say
take a bite out of crime
he's really what he's doing is
he's teaching the general the kids on this one
to work long
hours for a little money
and no complaining
and preparing them for the real world
none of this striking
and union crap
Winx take the session fee
and don't take the royalties
just like Llewyn Davis
laughing
when you guys were on the picket lines for this
writer strike I was a guy honking
but I was honking in a bad way
I was mad
you need more money I saw what
I see what the writers for Frazier
made you don't need anymore
of that those who I hear all
the time with the Will and Grace
I listen to Carvey Spade
they talk about how much Spade got
paid for commercials
you writers you all make that
you don't need more money
that's what Zaslav told me when I was courtside
with him at the Lakers
he said he was going to have to settle and I'm paying him
to do it but the great writers
weren't that ultimately
dumb
I just want to see where this resolves again I forget
laughing
Santa's praise was like winning a prize
That really jumped out
That was like instantly iconic to me
Try, if you, hey
Listeners, if you're gonna sing Christmas carols
out there this season
forget old Jingle Bells and Sleigh Ride
Startboo throwing these songs in the mix
laughing
alright everybody
So wink and boop
selfish
Santa's praise was like winning a prize
Everybody do it, come on
laughing
These songs
I think cassette 4
is absolutely the worst songs
Yeah
Some of the most complicated songs I've ever heard
Right, I was gonna say the confusions
Not like jazz fusion math
but just in terms of
I'm like baffled
I can't sing any hook or melody
Tuneless message songs
laughing
This is Christmas too?
This is like the most stressful Christmas
That song is called Santa's Helpers
laughing
That sounds like fun, right?
Well, wait to hear how half of them
are no good lazy bums
laughing
Don't judge a book by its cover
Some of Santa's Helpers suck shit
laughing
You gotta weed out the weak ones
You gotta be able to identify who's not gonna do what you want
and kick them to the curb
Kick them out right before Christmas too
These kids, they hear Polar Express
They're like, travel, trip to Santa's
home and workshop
It's gonna be great, it's always gonna be so wonderful
and nice
I got news for you, Jack
There's a lot of real no goodniks
up at the North Pole
Just like here in America
And when I say no goodniks, I mean
people that won't work more than
8 hours for a
hour daily wage
laughing
Everyone's lazy, everyone gets a trophy
No one wants to work anymore
No one wants to work
Panera Bread CEO is right
laughing
People don't want to help the shareholders anymore
You don't want to be awake for all 24 hours
so you drink that death lemonade
I drink the lemonade and I'm fine
laughing
I shit real bad, but I didn't die
Oh, McGruff's died
Charge Lemonade, Chocolate Chip Cookies
and C's
laughing
Yeah, and it all gives me moral fortitude
Be careful, don't buy a counterfeit
Charge Lemonade when you're on the street
It could be full of anything
Scott, do you know what we're talking about?
Yeah, yeah, the panera that kills you
The lemonade that kills you
No, it's like
For Loco, they change the formula
Only drink original panera murder juice
laughing
The next song is called Self-Esteem Team
How many are left?
Two
Oh, okay
music
Here's the deal, Self-Esteem Team are bad
Half of them are jerks
laughing
music
Have self-esteem
not alpha-steam
In this case, alpha-steam is bad
They switch
I once heard a mighty
river say
I began as a
lifting stream
So how did that river
grow so wide
The stream has
self-esteem
Too much metaphor
When I was re-listening to all this
This one I really threw my hands in the air
Because I said, wait, well this song is about
self-esteem, but the first example is what
happens to a stream
I guess
The stream had
self-esteem
This kid added in his contract
and he only does metaphors
and it's really pretentious and I hate it
music
Self-esteem, the feeling
that's true, self-esteem
It comes
from what you do
Does it always?
music
How did a little
pail of milk
get to be chocolate ice cream
Alright, Jason
How did the little pail of milk get to be
chocolate ice cream?
Well, you put, I mean if it's
an old school ice cream maker
You put the dairy in the thing
and you put salt on top
and ice around it
Oh, okay
Because of what it did
now, a pail of
milk has become chocolate ice cream
All milk dreams
of being chocolate ice cream
Not other flavors, chocolate's the best
And don't say
that the milk's parents, how it
treated the milk was the reason
for its self-esteem, that's not right
It's what it did
If you ever see a pail of milk
know that that is a quitter
That's a milk that didn't
It says an ice cream
that didn't believe it could be an ice cream
So just remember, Jason
when you're having your nightly chocolate ice cream
that this is a very
this has a high level of self-esteem
This person, this milk is
very confident in itself
Okay, I'm sorry
I'm sorry
I just want you to learn it
I will
Jason, how much more do I need to wag my paw at you
I'm squeezing your hand for a reason
You're squeezing my hand too hard
You're imagining the hitting
I'm only grazing you
I'm giving you self-esteem
You smell like Johnny Walker Red
I didn't like when you
touched it on Kudy Serk
That's a fine beverage
Kudy Serk and ice
That's a way to relax
Self-esteem
Your mind will try and prove
It comes from what you do
Think of the lonely
long-wounded girl
who's now a diamond
It was her dream
She brilliantly applied
herself
All it took was self-esteem
How is a diamond made?
Well, you'd think it'd be complicated
but there's only one step
When it comes to Christmas
lumps of gold
You're always talking about how they become diamonds
That's the glum-b-cold Christmas thing
Right?
This is a holiday song
Self-esteem team, supposedly
Okay
And I don't know
Seasonal affective disorder
can affect everyone
I like Jingle Bell Rock
but I also like Self-Esteem Team
If you're trying to give a kid a practical lesson
obviously dialing the phone is a lesson
Kids should know how to do that
Saying no to drugs
Okay, yeah, that's a pretty simple way to do it
but okay
But you should have self-esteem
and all the examples are non-humans
and just like a transformation
that they've made
and just being like, you know why they transformed?
Because they have self-esteem
Anyway, next song, next lyric
I don't know
I don't know, this one really
How does a piece of wood
become a table so sturdy and clean
It just needs self-esteem
Yeah
Aren't there people involved?
Carpenters?
Yeah, but like if you're a kid
I don't know how to tell somebody
to have more self-esteem
I'd say maybe go to therapy
first and
really discover where this
negativity is coming from
I guess it's a little nuance
but yeah, this one really
I threw up my hands in the air
I was like, I don't know, this one
Self-esteem
How does a stream
How does a little trickle of water
become a full stream
This is like
It's not one to one
No
Okay, so that means that
I should strive
to be, if I want self-esteem
It'll probably come if I
get on the path to becoming 800 pounds
My problem is
I'm not big enough
Or just, you could also like
That could be one interpretation, yes
It's also just like, ah, you want
self-esteem, change into
something different
Change who you are
completely
And then maybe you will feel good about yourself
Milk and ice cream
are pretty different
So, you know, like, take everything about your
personality, strip it away
and change it, fake it
Make yourself different, be born
anew
Change your clothes, change the look
Change how you talk, I mean, do a
Lauria Baldwin thing and maybe do
a Spanish accent all of a sudden
The only person who took her
self-esteem now that she's from
Spain She heard my song
and she said, oh, you know what
How you say
Spanish
I am how you say
Spanish speaker now
And she begged
the ultimate husband
The prize of all prizes
The man we all want to be with
Man, woman, or dog
One of the only guys who
anytime a photographer takes a photo
he punches him
He'll take him out
The only guy who fights against the paparazzi
Look at him, they made a beautiful litter
of children
They're the rare family with a
dog-sized amount of children
and he loves it
Cheaper buy than doesn't, I'd say
Yeah, they
buy in bulk
I go see him all the time, Alec Jr
Wink, Bip
All the kids' names
That Bip, though
He's pretty selfish
Take a seat, Steve Martin
Sit down, Zach Braff
When Alec asks Wink and Bip
to do coverage on one of his scripts
You know, Wink is always
the one volunteering
and Bip says, no way
Bip Baldwin
He's the one who's very selfish
Alec didn't send Wink Baldwin
and Bip Baldwin to the North Pole
for under-low-paid jobs
to get rid of them
They wanted to do it
to show initiative, but then Bip
ultimately didn't have what it took
But Alec will sometimes call
and use some strong language
at him, but that's what you do
as a parent, and he says
You ungrateful little shit
You stay up there and learn to be an elf
because there's no
You don't have a room here
I've turned your room into a study
Adults can use answering machines like Alec
but you kids can't
Bip, don't be a selfish little pig
Okay, what's the last song, though?
Is it Christmas?
Well, it's a hold on, hold on
Hold your horses, Jason
I'm just so excited by the holiday season
Jason wanted to get to the end
faster than the other hosts
Don't be a Jason
Be a Mike and Scott, not a Jason
Jason, don't be a Jason
Jason was a kid who tried to open a book
Jason was a kid who tried to open
all his Christmas presents at once
Mike and Scott
would wait a good five minute interval
and let everyone have a chance in between
but not Jason
Smile, brother, do it
Alright, here we go, it's called Wonder
Dash Full
Okay
Here we go
Sounds Christmasy
My little brother Joey asks us
questions day and night, but even
with our answers, he asks
everyone in sight
Do brown cows give chocolate milk?
When you put icing
on a cake, does it get
cold? Does lemonade
really need help?
Can a hot dog get fleas?
My sister asks the same questions
again and again
Yesterday she caught my mom and then
she started it
Why don't they call it a hot fudge
Monday
If there are boys and berries, are there
girls and berries?
Does a river keep its money in a river
bank?
If I planted jelly beans,
could I grow jelly?
Save these for popsicle sticks
My cousin is a pain, he asks me
questions by the ton
It got so bad that when
I see him now, I turn around
and run
Do Eskimos stick their house together
with igloo?
Where's the gum in gumdrops?
What do you call
a boy ladybug?
How can a square
dance?
I'm glad I don't have someone
like that bugging me at home
But since you guys all brought it up
I have questions of my own
Oh no!
Who pays
the bill of rights?
How do potatoes get chipped
This is my statement against comedy
and comedians
The only one I like is Bill
The whole group of
Amelia Bedelia's and it's exhausting
Why aren't reindeer always wet?
Why aren't big storms
called hizzocanes?
Help us, McGruff
Hurricane is a small
storm, but that's
the here's this is a
McGruff, this is a weird new way
of being sexist
I'm always innovating
You think
hurricanes are wimpy?
Like a
smaller, like a woman would be?
Feminine, yeah, hurricanes
I don't think so
They always get emotional, they always go spinning
around and around, they can't control themselves
Not like men
Adult dog men
Hizzocanes, you're saying
Hizzocanes would be just
direct to the point, get the destruction
job done and be on with it
Yeah, and with none of that
crying, it doesn't rain
when a hizzocane is going
I gotta tell you that
You gotta make sure
to identify
Hurricanes are female tears?
That's right
Are they making the cry female tears?
So hizzocanes are big and dry
Quick
Powerful
Shellshock from war
With some PTSD
but they're dealing with it
And they also, what, I guess they don't
ask for directions either
They know where they're going
This is another
They chart a quick course and they do it and they're there
McGruff, I don't know
that kids being precocious
and asking too many questions is
very Christmas focused
Hold on, there's
another few seconds of the song left
Oh, okay
Merry Christmas from McGruff, bye
Hi kids, I'm glad you all asked questions
so you can learn about things
but the best way to find out
more about all the things you're interested in
is to learn how to explore
your school and public libraries
They're a great place
to learn all kinds of things
They have books, records, tapes, and even films
on every subject you can imagine
So ask about getting your
very own library card
It's absolutely free and you can explore
the wonderful world
inside your library
This song's about libraries?
It's called Wonderful?
So the end of
the end of the holiday
cassette is just about getting a library card
Famously keep limited
hours around the holidays
or close
All the kids ask annoying joke questions
and they ask it to McGruff and he goes
Alright, I'm enough of this shit
There's a building you can go to
and you can look it up in books
He doesn't even say happy holidays
He's just, I'm outta here
And that's the end of the cassette
That's the end of McGruff's cassette
Hello, you work here? Yes, I'm a librarian
Okay, is there a book
that could teach me why
big storms
aren't called
is-a-canes
There's
one of those big decay
picture books
There's one on natural
disasters
Don't talk to me anymore
That's what McGruff said
I have 50 more
subjects where I have
questions, is there a book about ladybugs?
Because I wanted to know about boy ones
Excuse me, librarian, I went to see
Carrot Top in Las Vegas
and a lot of the things he said
confused me
and there were plays on words and I have so many
questions about it now
most of them about
his-a-canes and hurricanes
I assume
that's what Carrot Top's act is, right?
It's like a lot of puns like that
He has his items
so he could have a his-a-cane
He would say, here's a hurricane, but here's a
his-a-cane
It's big
It's got the male symbol
We just wrote a joke for him
Toilet seat with the rear view mirror
Wow, that's a classic, he brought that up
That's his hit
That's good stuff
What is this called?
Is it just called Tape 4?
They're all McGruff cares for you
Cassette 4
But it is vaguely
It's not properly a Christmas
album, it just has some
Christmas music on it
Does the cover reference
Christmas in any way?
I'm trying to remember, it's not with me
It's a strange blend, some of it is
about Santa's elves who are
largely bad
Right, but
then
I'm looking at cover
Oh wait, I'm kind of seeing it
It's pretty small, it's on worthpoint.com
And yeah, he's reading
a storybook
By a fire, which has some Christmas
decorations on it
So that's kind of
This one really feels
like they ran out of time
And they had to finish, they promised
four cassettes for whatever
Burger King deal, and they ran
out of time, cause like
There's, some of those
songs make the first three cassettes look like
masterpieces
Those are all
bad songs, but some of them were a little
more mundane, forgettable
I remember very little of what was
in MacGruff too, I don't know
if I'll soon forget
Selfish and Elfish and
Santa's Praise
was like getting a prize
I feel like that's gonna occur
to me on my deathbed
Santa, praise me
That's true
His last words were, Santa, praise me
I want the prize
He's better off
dead, I guess
Well, I mean, look
There were songs probably we didn't even play
So, maybe, you know
with no limits, MacGruff
7 can be a re-examining
of all these cassettes
So how many songs are left
in this expedition now?
Well, there's MacGruff and Scruff and the Crime Dogs
and I just played, what, two?
Yeah, just a sampling
So there's probably like
six or seven left
That could be like the B-sides
Yeah, so we can combine that with some of the
TV specials
Those specials are good
I think we're gonna get to MacGruff
Well, wait a minute
We already did 1, 2, 3, so you can't go backwards
like prequels
Do we
We could rename it like George did
Remember he called New Hope
He called it New Hope after the fact
and called it 4
So, alright
We could change it on the
Yeah
MacGruff 1 is now
MacGruff 4, but MacGruff 3
was about MacGruff Tape 4
Right, yeah, yeah, we can do that
MacGruff 1 is now
called a New Hope
It's not, I think we
wrote MacGruff, the Crime Dogs singing career
but it's not that anymore
I guess if you're going in
terms of quality
if it's sort of agreed that Empire Strikes
Back is the best, then MacGruff 1
probably, Smart Kids is
Empire Strikes Back
And you know what, this was
kind of odd
and confusing and seemed to change the plan
a lot, is it Christmas? No, it's
Wonderful and Library
I think this tape is the Rise
of Skywalker of
It's a bizarre
conclusion
that is kind of all over the place
Yeah, I think that's right
That introduces some new
characters, but is Mrs. Carpenter
Mrs. Carpenter maybe as
will have the
cultural impact of
Babu Frick
Babu Frick though, I just saw somebody had a license plate
on Twitter
I thought you passed that on the road
I would have turned my
car in front of that person's car and made them
pull over so I could shake their hand
But no, I saw it
on X, I saw it on X
Yeah, so
there's more MacGruff
It's an interesting
thing, it's really
Should Alex Jones be reinstated
on X?
Vox Populi Vox Dei
Well, the people spoke
That's weird, yeah, there was that Twitter
circle the other day that was
Vivek Ramaswamy
Elon Musk
Andrew Tate and MacGruff the Grimedog
I actually, I think I got a shot
I think if I started running
now I could be up there with Vivek
and Nikki Haley
And MacGruff, he forgot to mute
his mic when he was licking himself
Did you hear that too? Yes, yeah, yeah
Vivek left his mic on and was
peeing
So they heard
MacGruff was really, he was gross
Hey, sorry
Gotta do it, it's a long one of those
spaces or whatever it's called
He smoked, he's done it
He's gonna call him little peepee boy
and he's gonna be done
I hope so
That's good
Alright, well
So remaining now
six songs, but we did
clear the holiday stuff, but we also
we cleared the holiday stuff an hour ago
because technically
the only holiday songs
There's also other songs we didn't
play on MacGruff too, we were
skipping around, so
B-sides, we might play B-sides and Rarities
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So we've
really opened up more
which is a good thing, because it's always
fun to do the voice. This is more like
the ending where the fist pump
shoots out of the ground at the end
and there's more
the villain is not dead, it's a
the end question mark, and then the question mark
explodes, because I don't think
we are done. We're not done, yeah
Geez, thank God
because, wow, I don't know how we
waited three years to do it
It was so much more fun to do it not
under shadow of Pandemic
and to be here with MacGruff in person
Hey, let me give you the guest treatment
MacGruff, you survived
podcast The Ride, The Second Gate
Oh, wow. Let's exit through the gift shop
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Well, I'd just like to tell you
to have self-esteem
I want to remind you to use the phone
correctly
I like to... So, cards
don't have zards
but do
use cards
Yeah, your phone card
and make sure the directions are in your head
because of a tune
I kind of remember it
Make sure when you're walking outside
to look straight ahead, not down
What else?
Libraries, you said
Yeah, that's good
Figure it out at the library
Keep our dumb questions
to us, to ourselves
until we get to a library
That's probably the main thing you want to plug
Yeah, and
stay away from the woke police
Not the police
you represent
Okay, well, appreciate you being here
This has been The Last
Second Gate of 2023
Fun way to close it out
We do have one more Christmas treat
coming on Club 3, our VIP tier
where you can, of course, choose topics
vote on topics and get our regular main feed
episodes ad-free
So if you want one more bonus treat for the year
that'll be on patreon.com
slash podcast the ride
otherwise we'll be back with new stuff
in January
Well, have a
McGruffy Christmas, do what McGruff
would do, and may
all of Santa's praise
feel like a prize
Well said, thank you