Five, four, three, two, one.
Hello, this is podcast the ride host Jason Chardon.
If you're a regular second gate listener, hello and welcome home.
If you're new to the second gate, welcome to the show.
We want to assure you that your entertainment is our top priority.
Not only on our world class theme park episodes, but all our episodes.
From the ones about made for TV movies that haunt us,
to the ones about hyper rich unpleasant men that also haunt us.
We're glad that you're here and hope that you enjoy your second gate experience.
Wow.
Thank you.
Yes.
With real buddy energy.
Buddy, I got the buddy vibe.
Buddy, what's the Riz?
Yeah, I got the buddy Riz.
I got that buddy Dyer Riz.
Buddy Dyer, not buddy Dwyer.
Oh yeah, Matt Cardona texted me a correction on that too.
Sure.
My brain just auto completing infamous corrupt Pennsylvania official Barbara Dwyer.
Look, this is okay.
Just to order things.
This is an episode about the Orlando airport tram.
But since we're here already, yes.
Scott Caron or Mike Carlson.
Jason, not Sheridan, hi.
Yes, part of this was something that fueled me wanting to turn it from episode joke to actual episode.
Quickly was to get ahead of this.
That yes, you get on the tram, the little ride that you go on at the Orlando airport,
to get you to the main terminal.
And there's this message, this delightfully stiff message from Orlando mayor Buddy Dyer.
And when it came up in an episode a month or so ago, all of us unilaterally said, I think we said buddy,
but we made it Buddy Dwyer.
Dwyer.
And Bud Dwyer is the corrupt Pennsylvania.
Treasurer.
Treasurer who was about to go to jail for bribery for a long time.
For a lot of bribery.
No, no, a lot of different charges against him.
And for like 55 years.
And he took care of that by holding a weird scattered press conference where then he pulled a gun out of a bag and shot himself.
And this is the note we're opening 2024 on.
Happy New Year.
But it is really funny that we put that out there for Ed said it like because nobody look,
there's mistakes worth getting mad about.
I don't think anyone was mad at us.
This is the easiest confusion.
It's so strange that there's two politicians, that there's Buddy Dyer and Bud Dwyer.
Yes.
But I guess the mix up is gets funny in that Buddy Dyer seems like a very pleasant, well liked politician.
Bud Dwyer, a guy who encounters.
Kind of infamous.
Things just played out very strangely.
And it was weird what he made people see happen on live television in some cases.
That's one of the strangest things ever.
But we wanted to get ahead of that.
Because we love this thing.
We love that you get a little ride when you land in Orlando.
You do not hear a welcome message from.
Or Bud Dwyer.
Yes, from a corrupt politician who shot himself on live television, Bud Dwyer.
I did have when that came up before, I did have the like, man, it's weird.
There's another politician named Buddy Dwyer.
That's weird.
He wasn't Buddy.
Bud is like, that shows you maybe.
That shows you there's not the friendliness that Buddy has.
He wasn't your buddy.
He was doing bad stuff.
And then he scarred a lot of people with his act on television.
But I think it's good to know.
Like, if you're worried about if you're if you're now withholding booking an Orlando vacation for yourself, there isn't a message from him.
You don't get a message recorded.
And when did that happen?
The late 80s.
You don't get a message recorded in like 87 from a guy saying, all right, if you're hearing this, it's all over for Bud.
But my final wish was to do the narration for the Orlando airport tram.
It was it's in my will.
I handed that to somebody at the press conference.
If my plan goes, it's in the future for me, I'm going to hand it to somebody at the press conference and then I'm going to do some other stuff.
They had to do it.
It's a legally binding document.
I don't know what it is.
I'm just I love I love Orlando.
I love that.
You know, it's I'm not going to get to see it, but I'm really looking forward to Maelstrom.
It looks like a lot of fun.
I'm going to see the trolls.
I wish I could.
But there's unfortunately things haven't worked out.
I'm a teacup guy.
I like their small world, even though it's indoors.
The facade isn't as fun.
But anyways, I'll tell you, the whole world is going to be the happiest place on earth once old Bud's gone.
You know, a part of it was I don't know that I know that I've seen that many dyers.
Dwyer, I feel like is more common name.
Yeah.
So I think I was reading my notes and I was like, oh, it can't be dire.
It must be Dwyer.
Mm hmm.
You know, it's really there to remember this.
You have to do the opposite.
But Buddy Dyer, the friendly mayor of Orlando, did not get himself into a dire situation.
No.
His corruption.
Right.
Nor nor has he been a dire on television either.
So you have to you have to you got to flip them to remember.
So if that how just do the opposite of what you're because I it seems so likely that one of us will still trip up at some point.
It's possible.
Yeah, one of us will it'll become a pepo pepo maybe it'll be another one of those where I think now it's now I've thought about it too much.
Yeah.
It causes the mistake.
Right.
Yeah.
So anyways, there's that.
Well, we've cleared that out of the way.
Yeah.
That that aspect of it.
And now we can talk a little about, hey, you know what?
I thought this is a cool way to do it.
If this is the first episode of the second gate of twenty twenty four, the first episode is the first ride.
It's your first ride.
Oh, yeah.
First ride and your last if you're flying out of Orlando.
Mm hmm.
Your last ride, much like old Bud.
Oh, God.
This is going to be impossible to avoid.
At least we get out of the top now.
It should have been at the end.
Possibly.
Well, we started things on quite a note here.
But yes, look, it's it's a it's a really nice thing that you get.
And if you don't know, I mean, this is like a thing you for sure know if you fly into Orlando.
Maybe you haven't experienced it if you're a native or if you drive, if you've always driven in for your trips, then you have not experienced the fun little tram.
But basically, it's it's a layout of an airport, Orlando International Airport, MCO.
It's you know, main terminal is separate from the technical term airsides.
You got it.
You got to take the trams back and forth from the airsides.
That's where we are.
Are where you actually depart from.
But I think, you know, it's nice on the way out, but it's especially nice on the way in the land.
And to build up your excitement for a vacation that's going to be full of rides.
You get a fun little train ride right at the right at the top of your visit.
I think this is something we've all always enjoyed about Orlando vacation.
How could you not enjoy this?
I would think maybe if you really didn't have an affection for Monorails or Disney at all, maybe then it's like, just put me right at the gate.
Let me get right to the taxi.
But still, I think it's such a nice surprise if it's your first time.
Well, and you know what?
Yeah.
Get me right to the gate.
Sure.
But I find that like I was in analyzing what do I like about this little ride so much?
Part of it, I think, is look, the best flight, the most comfortable flight is still not a ton of fun.
There's hassle.
And then you land and immediately anticipate hassle.
You got to go deal with baggage.
You got to figure out how you're getting here or there.
You might be waiting or depending on the crash, especially like landing in L.
A.
is horrible.
It's like such a zoo around there.
You know, so like L.
A.
X.
is a place where you land and then there's not a train that they make you get on.
But I almost wish there was because I feel like there's so much more hassle and unpleasantry.
It's like dirty there.
It's smart and angry in the air.
But like before you deal with anything, when you land in Orlando, you get this really pleasant little trip with depending on time of year,
maybe a nice little view of some trees, some Florida palm trees.
I think you get water.
I think you see a little lake or something, depending on which air side you're going back and forth from.
Maybe a gator or two.
You think so?
Have you ever seen a gator?
I've seen gators like landing or like when I was on the monorail.
You saw a gator land.
Oh, you and you landed.
You saw a gator on the monorail.
The gator wasn't landing somehow.
No, no.
I mean, like when the plane's about to land, if you look down, you can see gators.
I've seen a gator sunning itself.
Really?
But I think from the monorail too, I've seen them.
You've seen gators?
From the distance on the islands or whatever.
Hi, Jason.
Welcome to Orlando.
Check out my cousins at Gatorland.
Are you sure it wasn't a billboard for Gatorland?
I'm not sure.
No, I'm not.
Because they may be realistic looking.
You see this big, if you look close for it when you're landing, you see a big smiling gator.
He's got a top hat on.
Sunglasses.
Sunglasses and a top hat.
The Orlando outfit.
Now let me hang on.
I don't want to get into arguments and semantics here, but I ran into an article or something.
There's literature out there that is very clear about a particular point.
If you're a stickler about transportation, transportation titles, this is not a monorail.
It is not.
You could call it a number of things.
I'm not even sure what to call it for the episode.
It could be tram.
It could be people movers.
Automated people movers.
And then you can look up a number of cities have done this to revitalize downtown areas.
Vegas has the official, they call it the monorail, but I think it's an automated people mover, the one that you board at MGM that goes all the way to North Strip.
But then there's the people movers between, there's a number of them between a bunch of the MGM hotels on the other side of the Strip.
Sure.
Yeah.
And the distinction with a monorail is the track.
Because it's not, it isn't mono.
Right.
There are trains, there's two sides of it.
So by virtue of it being a track that can fit two trains, it is a duo rail.
I don't think that's a term, but it'd be a better, a closer term than monorail.
And usually a pilot.
A pilot is in a monorail?
In a monorail, yeah.
And this is automated?
Yes.
That's interesting.
I guess maybe I didn't know that.
Because I guess I've been on it and kind of typically had the opportunity to get a front row view or a back row view where it's just glass back there and you can just look at track and be at the front of the tail of it.
And I guess if somebody was on it, you wouldn't be able to do that.
What is that?
That's not a monorail.
That's got a couple tracks.
Is that just a train?
Maybe that's just a train, but it's elevated.
Because I guess it could be an elevated train.
They call it the L in Chicago.
The train can go up and down.
But it's still, it's interesting.
Monorail is just like it has to have a thin track with no other track, like just one of them.
I think so.
At least there's that.
I don't know definition beyond that.
I mean, my information…
I'm sure there's automated, there must be an automated monorail out there somewhere.
It seems like that would have to be possible.
My information on monorails, of course, comes from the loop in Disney World and then the Simpsons episode.
And Homer is like the monorail conductor.
So there has to be a pilot there, essentially.
Yeah, there's gotta be a guy in a big fancy cape.
And you have to watch out for the wires getting chewed up by a possum.
A possum family lives in there.
I've heard Conan talk about this a lot.
Where he's like, we were making fun of the monorail.
Obviously it was a joke because the town didn't need a monorail.
But I never got that.
I was like, that's cool.
Monorail is cool.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
I never got that they thought that…
You're right.
For Disney kids, they're like, I want a monorail in my town.
Hell yeah.
I think I got it that it was superfluous because the town was small.
But the idea that the monorail was silly itself, I never registered that.
You've got to be of two minds here.
I'm sure there are places, the airports among them, where monorails are efficient and help.
And help with smog and mass transportation.
But I wonder, what is the reality in the world of Lyle Landley type situations where it's kind of a boondoggle and a waste of money.
You don't actually need the monorail.
Well, and it's, from what I understand, it is expensive.
And people were thinking that was going to take off when Disney started using them.
But it didn't.
It didn't really.
Well, that's what I think that's what I've read the reason they never expanded the monorail further in Disney World is because it's so expensive.
Like the Skyliner urban gondola system is much, much cheaper than building miles and miles of monorail track.
Yeah, but I still like monorails better.
Yeah.
That's a tough.
I guess I do stylistically.
But there's a there's a real, God, that might be a tie for me in Disney World at this point.
I do like the Skyliner.
I do like it.
I'm scared of it, though, but I do it.
I do it.
I'll do it.
I didn't do it last time.
Did you do it last time?
I don't think I was ever in a place where it made sense to do the Skyliner.
Yeah.
Did you do it last time?
I didn't.
I.
Yeah, it didn't really make sense.
You really got to be in the southern part of the property if you're, you know, because we mainly did.
I only did Epcot and Magic Kingdom, so it's more efficient.
It's more efficient than monorails.
It's real fast.
Yeah.
So I get it.
So honestly, that they have recently done a big new transportation system that feels like the most hopeful, futuristic Disney World move.
That they're building something that can get you somewhere fast.
Yeah.
Because like we said, you're talking about how there's the dream of these kinds of transit.
And that was, I feel like, a big thing of Disney World 70s, 80s is, you know, we got people movers and we got monorails.
And these are things that your city will have soon.
And we even build these things for.
We have one in the Houston airport.
And now that is bad, seemingly the Houston one.
There aren't other ones.
There's this is a people mover.
Orlando thinks they call people mover, but it's unaffiliated with the Disney type of people.
They didn't build this or anything.
There is a connection.
There's a loose connection.
So these different airside to different legs were built at different times.
The first two came along in 81 and then 90 and then 2000, then 2017.
Some of the legs of this people mover use Bombardier CX 100 vehicles.
Bombardier is the company that bought the Walt Widd people mover division when they sold off the people mover part.
So there might be a little hint.
There's probably like a hinge that wed or a hinge or like a certain nut and bolt.
It's like, well, that actually imagineering came up with that.
What's the Mickey year?
Yeah.
So it's clunky.
It actually hurts the train.
Right.
It looks great.
It's so cute.
A lot of the some of the other tracks are Mitsubishi vehicles.
Westinghouse, I think I saw, was the original installer of a lot of this.
Yes.
Some of them.
OK, I think there's five tracks all told.
And at least two of them are older.
They're 80s models that still work pretty good.
So they they stay out there.
And then two of them got replaced by Mitsubishi crystal movers.
That's a nice one.
Right.
Like that's this.
I'm not sure.
I think you could be right.
Because that looks that one looks newer and a lot of the photos look old.
Yeah.
Well, I think if you don't have that, like the kind of 80s angular shape, that might be a clue of which got put in when.
Now there was a thing.
I don't know when this was a couple of years ago.
There was a day where the nightmare occurred, where the people movers broke down and people had to move themselves.
The people had to be their own movers and walk back and forth.
And there's there's photos where it looks like chaos, although it also sounds like the walk isn't like that long, really.
So you described as a nightmare on like I wasn't there.
I don't know.
Maybe it's truly horrible.
But you might think, oh, well, those junky old 80s ones probably shit the bed finally.
Right.
No, no, no.
It was the newer ones.
It was the newer ones that blew the crystal movers fucked up.
That's such a great name, though.
So good.
Yeah.
I know.
All this crystal movers.
So it's so really good.
Yeah.
But that was no, that feels like cool.
That feels like Tokyo future.
Yeah.
I think there are some I think practically some of Tokyo public transit is Mitsubishi crystal movers.
Yeah, that makes sense.
So they're great.
But they cost 90 million dollars.
I think today I think that redo what?
That's like 2017 or so.
So that kind of soon after that, they broke one day and blew up the efficiency of the airport was probably not great for anyone involved.
It doesn't look good.
But hey, mostly I would say this system is very efficient.
I've never had trouble.
I always get right on.
I'm waiting.
Yeah.
And there I think they're nice.
I think I don't know which ones I've been on.
I couldn't tell you if like I tend to be I'm always on the CX 100s.
I have no idea.
But any of them that I get on clean, comfortable, nice to be.
It doesn't feel like kind of junkie depressing airport, you know, internal like I don't get I get on I get on this little ride and I don't feel the bummer that I feel that most airports.
Yeah, I completely agree.
I think that I think definitely not waiting a lot.
A long time is a big part of it, too.
Yeah, is that like it feels like within five minutes, maybe less.
Maybe that's I'm misremembering, but maybe less like I'm right on it.
It's moving.
It doesn't it's like a perfect amount of time or walking from the gate to there doesn't feel like you're walking forever because that's a whole thing as well.
It's like there's stuff in like O'Hare in Chicago where like they have that cool 80s like moving walkway.
Sometimes you get with all the colors, you know, I'm talking about.
That's in the in the puff daddy.
I'll be missing you video.
Yeah, he does his dance of mourning for his friend.
Of course.
But like that feels like you got to walk a ways to get to it.
This one feels like you're almost like right in my mind.
You like walk right to the monorail.
It shows up.
I wish there was a like a pilot goes, hello, Mr.
Carlson and like waves you in like that's how it feels.
It feels fast and convenient.
And then you're on the little trip and then you're on your way.
It's really clear in terms of I don't remember which is which, but it's either there's like you could be there's this there's the center.
I feel like you board from the center and get off from the other sides.
So it's always really clear where you're never like fighting with people coming the other way.
It's none of that subway kind of gridlock.
Everybody bump into each other.
Like the directions are extremely clear.
Yeah, and now X also feels like a long walk to the gate or to the baggage pickup.
There's supposedly a people mover coming down like X.
Well, from like in twenty thirty satellite parking thing is coming in ten years.
Yes, like the Vegas train, which I have some things to talk about with that.
But it's got a it's got a bunch of money for that.
Yes.
Speed rail.
Let me say this real quick and then we'll talk about high speed rail for a second.
Walking.
So then it's like you get off the monorail or excuse me, the people mover in Orlando and you go down.
And I was shocked, even though I knew this, that the Mickey's Magic, excuse me, Mickey's Magical Express was gone.
That section of the airport now has been turned into like a regular busses like area.
And you know, did you see this when you were there, too, because it's like in the corner of the like area where you leave and go and find a taxi or a ride share.
And Mickey's Magical Express is a bus specifically for Disney World Hotels that was free.
Was it like if you were staying there?
That's a big perk that they caught during or shape error.
Yes.
Now, would Iger have done it or was he planning to?
We don't know.
Probably.
But yeah, I went down.
So that was like that added to the feeling of like you're being whisked to your destination where it was like off the plane, onto the people mover.
You go down some stairs and then Mickey's on the bus and you get right onto the Mickey bus and it felt like you were just being like like picked up and carried by a Disney God.
They got your bags too.
Yes, they could.
If you tagged them.
If you tagged them the right way, they would just put them right on the bus.
You didn't have to even.
So like you would get right in this line.
I never did it.
I never did the express.
That's interesting because we did it the last, I guess I did it the last time or maybe two times ago.
I forget.
But yeah, so that was the only thing where I was like, oh, the last part of the like ease is gone.
Oh, sure.
Last chunk of the ease of MCO.
If you're going to Disney.
Yeah, obviously we were staying universal, so I wouldn't have done it anyway.
But still the system, though, and the airport, this is a pretty solid airport regardless.
I feel like.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And this is not an airport that I'm bummed out to be.
I feel I guess security kind of bad.
You can get real stuck there.
Yeah.
But there's so many that the atrium, like the hotel that overlooks the.
The atrium is really nice and just like good little thing to look at while you're bored in security.
There's a Romano's Macaroni Grill, an old Sheridan family favorite.
It is.
I used to love Romano's Macaroni Grill.
You can see it from the plane.
But I've never been in the Orlando airport.
I just looked at it longingly.
Sure it's great.
Sure, it's awesome.
We'll review it next time.
They got the butcher paper, the waiter writes their name on your tablecloth and clown.
And then if you get a drink, they like they keep a tally.
But it's not like Dick's last resort.
They don't insult you or anything.
No, no.
OK.
The opposite.
They make you feel good.
Treat you like a king.
I don't know.
I haven't been to one of those, I think since I was 16.
I don't know if I've ever been to one of those.
I don't know these perks.
Romano's experience.
Real quick about the high speed rail.
And correct me if I'm wrong.
They just gave all this money to high speed rail.
They've been talking about this forever.
LA to Vegas, so quick.
It's going to be two hours, they say.
This is a new, this is in the last year or so.
There's a new like, train plan.
They just approved the money for it.
They've been talking about it for years.
Yeah.
To finally like make this a quick trip to Vegas.
My understanding is that you have to take a different train to Rancho Cucamonga.
Yes.
And then take the high speed rail to Vegas.
Yeah, Rancho Cucamonga is the LA departure point.
So you take 40, like a 45 minute train to Rancho.
If you don't live here, that's far.
That's not a place we ever are.
Yeah.
And then it's two hours by high speed rail.
And so then it's like the whole trip is two hours, 45 minutes.
And I'm like, well, if you leave at the right time, it's like four hours.
And then you have your car.
Yeah.
That's not so attractive to me.
Not really.
I didn't know that aspect.
Yeah.
Cause when they go, oh, it's two hours can be, I'm like, all right, well, that's like half the time and kind of the same amount of time.
If you take a flight, cause you got to get there a little early and there's some leaving like, so, okay, that's, that's not so bad.
But then you attack on an extra 45 minutes and you're like, well, I could just drive.
It's only an extra hour.
And then, then you don't have to deal with like, I don't know, maybe the train is late, like stuff like that.
So, I don't know.
Well, it's great if you're in Rancho Cucamonga.
This is a big of a boon to Cucamonga.
Yeah, that's true.
Could ever be.
That's true.
So I was like, oh, well, that's less fun.
Like if it was a 30 minute high speed rail train from Rancho, then that's a different situation.
Anyway, I was let down by that.
Maybe that's wrong.
Maybe I'm, I'm being annoying.
Mike's not impressed.
Have you done other airport?
Has anyone ever been?
Have you been to Dallas Fort Worth?
Yes.
And done their Mon, their Monorail is so large.
That airport is so big.
Like, I don't remember it at all.
I know I've been there.
It's the sort of thing where it's like, oh, I, I, my plane arrived at B and I, I have to get to terminal C for connection.
You can walk it.
It's not advisable.
Yeah.
It's just that it's like a hub for at least one or two airlines.
So there's a big international connection.
Yeah.
So there is a Monorail for it or a people mover for it.
The smaller version is Newark Airport in New Jersey where you don't go through security till you're at your terminal.
But there's a Monorail you can just get on to go between terminals.
And then it also goes to an Amtrak station that is only accessible by train.
It's only accessible by trains or the airport Monorail.
Okay.
And you like these?
Wait, wait, wait.
So where do you, what's your review on that?
The Dallas one, I've just like killed time riding around before the Newark one was convenient.
So you've ridden that purely as a ride.
For fun.
Or like to get to the Chili's too or something.
Yeah.
Newark worked out because I went to a wedding in Staten Island once and I'm like, well, I need to get a train down to Pennsylvania to see my family.
So the easiest thing was to take the hotel shuttle back to the airport and then get on the tram and take it to the Amtrak station that I bought a ticket for.
And so look, my dream multiple modes of transit, but it was a little confusing.
Yeah.
Because I'm like, this is still easier than renting a car in New Jersey.
Can you answer a question for me?
I got, when we went to New York, I took the Long Island Railroad into the city.
Did I take another train from the airport to get to that or did I walk?
I can't remember.
Where?
Why would we know that?
Because Jason is the guy, I'm not asking you necessarily, I'm asking Jason.
But how does Jason know what you did or didn't do?
The Long Island Railroad goes to the sub, did you take the Amtrak Air Tram from Queens?
I don't know.
Okay.
I can't remember.
I'm trying to remember.
What happened here?
You asked Jason a question about what you did and Jason wasn't there.
He doesn't know.
And he asked you one follow up and you said, I don't know.
I don't know.
What was the point of this line of questioning?
His point of, I was trying to figure out, did I take any sort of people mover to get to the Long Island Railroad to get into the city?
How you got to the Long Island Railroad.
I don't know either.
This is what I'm asking you.
I can't remember.
Only what I think the most likely person to know this has to be you.
But it's not.
We're going to have to go into security.
I think Jason knows more than I do about what I did even though he's confused too.
I don't remember.
I'm not sure.
I took once, I think I flew into JFK and then took the Air Tram to Queens.
Yeah, but what did Mike do?
I don't know.
I'm just trying to remember.
Keep in mind the order of things.
Mike, you remember everything Jason's ever done.
Jason doesn't remember anything you've ever done.
And maybe a lot of what you yourself, Jason, have done.
So you took a plane.
Somehow you ended up at East Egg or West Egg from the Great Gatsby.
And then you got on the Long Island Railroad to get into the city.
All right.
I'm going to apply that memory.
I'm going to try to absorb that memory now.
And from now on, that'll be what I know that I did last time.
I just I'll look into it later.
Jason retrace my steps.
But I just mean if he was familiar with JFK more, he would know.
Somebody out there tell me.
OK, maybe Jason doesn't know, but somebody out there tell me what I did.
Somebody explain to me how I got there.
Say the specifics again.
I flew in JFK and I didn't take like a lift or anything into Manhattan.
I went to the Long Island Railroad, which is kind of in my mind, it was a little bit of a trek.
But I can't remember if I took a train or something to get to that place.
I think I did.
I think somebody conked you on the back of the head, put you in a bag.
They were going to steal your money and then drown you in a river.
And then you didn't like have enough cash on you.
They ran away.
It just wasn't worth it.
Ultimately, so they like, they let you drop off at the Long Island Expressway.
They'll wake up.
You won't know any of it happened.
That could have happened, too, if somebody somebody needs to explain that.
That's what happened to me.
My memory years ago once, I think I went JFK AirTran to Queens from Queens.
You can grab the subway into Manhattan.
OK, well, I don't know.
I don't know.
We'll see.
We'll find out when someone tells me what I did.
Somebody has to know.
Somebody fill in.
Somebody help with Mike's mimento situation.
You didn't tattoo it on you, so you have no way of knowing.
If somebody knows how to hack into my iPhone, iPhone knows where we are at all times.
So if somebody could hack into the iPhone, they could know the coordinates of where I've been for the whole time I've owned an iPhone.
Can't you can't you find your own program that traces your own steps?
I don't know how to do it.
Somebody else is going to have to show me how to do it.
Jason program.
Jason, do you know how to find an app that retraces Mike's steps?
Do you have the Dark Knight technology with the phones where everything becomes a radar?
Jason, become a Lucius.
What's his name?
Lucius Fox.
Be Mike's Lucius Fox.
Yes.
So, yes, somebody is going to have to help me out here.
Well, I know if you're flying into Philadelphia, you can grab the R1.
That'll take 30th Street Station downtown.
That's big hub.
You can get anywhere from there.
OK, maybe I did that.
Yeah, maybe you did.
Did I fly into Philadelphia?
You ended up on SEPTA Regional Rail somehow and then you got to your hotel.
It's possible.
I believe it because I don't know what happened.
I don't remember.
So sorry.
Now we're discovering we're kicking off the year with Mike's decaying.
Mike's decaying memory.
I don't like to fly.
I blocked it out.
I block out flying.
I don't remember these flights.
Hey, to bring back to Orlando, a brief history lesson of the Orlando Airport.
Originally McCoy Air Force Base.
That's where the MCO three letter airport code comes from.
Yes.
Closed in 1974 and then Orlando bought the land.
It was the McCoy Air Force Base was Orlando's largest employer until Disney World came on the scene.
And so that so it was huge.
It's named for Colonel Michael McCoy, who died during a practice demonstration
flying a plane in a crash that killed three people and one cow.
Oh, wow.
I know that him dying isn't funny.
But when I got to the step that one cow was killed.
And one cow is yeah.
If it was just like a cow and three men were killed, would that be less funny?
What are the rules here?
Like is it because you ended with the cow?
Maybe they ended with the cow?
I think it has to be that way.
AP style guide says you have to end with the cow.
It's disrespectful to the men, I'd say, to put them after the cow.
But that would be the importance.
I guess, yeah, you have to lead with the important thing.
Unless that who knows?
I don't know how important that cow was.
I don't know how great the cow was.
Was it some prize winning cut?
What?
What did you do?
My Apple Watch just turned on.
Oh, okay.
Deal Vibes.
Alert from Deal Vibes.
You've ignored Deal Vibes for 10 minutes.
My Apple Watch said, I'm not sure I understand.
Maybe the Apple Watch thought I was asking it about what happened to me in New York.
Apple Watch, how important was the cow that died in the McCoy crash?
It was Mini Moo, a quite famous cow.
Oh no, Mini Moo died.
Mini Moo got murked in friendly fire.
The day they set Mini Moo free, it was killed by a plane immediately.
No, the Colonel who McCoy is, it was all named after, I think, was he knew he was going down
and he avoided a city where he would have crashed into a lot of people.
But anyway, this Air Force Base, from the 60s till 75, it was a combo.
It was an Air Force Base, but they also ran commercial flights.
Then in 75, Disney World's getting so much traffic, they're like, well, let's just switch it over entirely.
Some of the awkwardness of early 70s travel to Orlando came from the Disney situation,
which is that back then, Walt announces this Florida project and Progress City.
There's going to be all this transportation stuff going on.
That's what we're seeking to prove is efficient transportation.
So, there's going to be all the people movers and monorails and stuff,
and that's all going to connect to our airport that we will be building.
The Disney airport.
So, for a while, Orlando is like, okay, so we'll hold off on…
They had airports, but just kind of smaller.
And they're like, well, I guess we'll wait for Walt to handle that.
And then Walt passed away, and then the plans became not a weird futuristic city,
but theme park and some hotels.
And they thought, well, maybe we need to figure out that whole airport thing then.
Thus, McCoy MCO becomes what it is today.
But as part of that, maybe you ran into some of this, Jason.
I'd never heard of this in my life.
I didn't know that they did in the early 70s, maybe even longer than that, you might say.
Disney World had something that they did refer to as the Walt Disney World Airport.
Is this familiar to either of you?
I actually didn't see this.
So, I think initially the Lake Buena Vista Airport then changed to Walt Disney World Airport.
And this is technically running through the 80s.
And what this was, was a way…
They called it a STOL port.
That stands for Short Takeoff and Landing.
So, the idea was you fly into Orlando or even a nearby city,
and then you maybe…
Do you want to take a real little plane that just gets you right up to the hotels?
So, with that short takeoff and landing airport, that dresses up.
This is no airport.
What this was was a landing strip.
And it's there today.
It's really close to the Ticket and Transportation Center.
It's in that whole zone.
So, you get to Disney World in 71, 72,
you could take a little plane that essentially gets you right to the Contemporary or the Polynesian.
You just like then you're steps away and you're right there.
You would have had to take a tiny plane from something called Shawnee Airlines.
Shawnee, spelled like Pawnee, rhymes with Pawnee.
But this didn't last for very long because Shawnee Airlines shut down in December 72
due to rising debt and lack of passenger interest.
Yeah.
Good reason to close down your little podunk airline, I guess.
Wow, there's this Disney airstrip.
That's weird.
And you could still use that through the 70s.
I believe it was used not for, I don't remember if it was George Bush or George W.
Bush,
but one of the presidents, their prep team,
the secrets of the whole operation that has to travel with a president,
like use this to get all their stuff in order for a presidential visit.
But now the road's still there and they just like store a bunch of stuff on it.
On the landing strip?
Yeah.
So I think since at least like 2008, you could not land a plane there if you wanted to.
So they said they store like Ohana meat there that's going to go into the restaurant later or something?
Possibly.
Maybe not the meat.
Maybe it's where, remember that big, the weird steampunk but future dinosaur like.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Terraric X.
From the Epcot show.
Yeah, what was it called?
Yeah, that's where that is.
That's where anything that they don't, they don't want to use anymore.
Right, decay, everything that's decaying.
Or yeah, the botanicus is there for some reason from Hollywood.
Yeah, we'll take it out of your hands.
We got the room.
Yeah, every day all the trolls.
Any, it's a, now it's a graveyard of old animatronics.
Right.
All the old Johns from Carousel of Progress.
They're just made.
They wire Johns, yes.
They babble at each other.
It's storage now, it used to mostly be Card Walker flying in on that Shawnee airline and he would say like fly for Milano Airport.
It's enough time for one seven and seven and then I roll out of the plane.
That sounds good.
So the character of Card Walker is a guy who likes to have one drink.
I just have one drink, it's a short flight.
In the air, in the air.
So okay, so you would get to MCO and then you, or you would get to the airport and you would get.
There are a few places I think that would service this.
Yeah, yeah, that's what I corrected myself.
And then you would take what, an eight minute flight?
Something like that.
Probably.
Uh huh.
And then you're right there, you could not be closer to, you could have, technically I think you could, especially to Polynesian.
You're just right there.
And how much of today's money would that cost I wonder?
I don't know.
Because it seems.
Maybe not a lot because it was, because Shawnee's, Shawnee's planes were made out of cotton, they were like tightly packed cotton.
Right.
I went to North Carolina earlier this year and we had a connect, we flew into Raleigh Dorm and then flew into the very tiny Asheville Airport.
Yeah.
It's pretty much like the Burbank Airport, it's like one terminal or something.
And for whatever reason there was a misprint on the ticket, the ticket said it'll be about a 15 minute flight.
And then when we get on the plane, the pilot's like, well, thank you for joining us, Raleigh Dorm to Asheville.
This course does 17 minute flight.
And I was like, what did he say?
And I was like, that can't be right.
And then sure enough, yeah, it was about 15 minutes to go from the east side of the state to the middle of the state.
Yeah.
Vegas flight is like 30 to 45 minutes.
Something like that.
Yeah.
15's not enough.
You can't even get, you can't get beverage service.
Maybe they serve two in cans.
What is it called?
We're going to launch Canada Drys because we have to.
We're going to give you not the fancy canned cocktails, we're going to give you the disgusting canned cocktails.
We're just going to roll them down the middle of the aisle too.
Catch it, grab it.
Did they do any, they didn't do any drinks?
They didn't do any service.
By the time you ascend.
Do a couple loops, I want a drink.
By the time you're up, you're going down.
They don't even probably reach full, full soaring height.
Yeah.
Here's a picture of this too, as proof.
Look at that.
Oh, there it is, yeah.
That looks totally unfamiliar to me, but there it is.
That's in 71.
And location wise, the contemporary is right there.
Contemporary Magic Kingdom.
Yeah, and still there technically.
But here's the weirdest thing about this.
I can't believe, in all the Disney World arcania, I can't believe I've never run across this before, that this was no, sure it's a very short runway, 2,000 feet long.
Sounds boring, right?
Not even an airport.
Ah, ah, ah, the Disney magic is all over this runway because it is the world's only singing runway.
Apparently, grooves edged into the blacktop played the tune of When You Wish Upon a Star.
Wow.
Get out of here.
Yeah, what do you mean?
What?
What are you talking about?
How does that work?
Is there proof of that?
There's not.
It's in a couple articles.
That information is out there.
And it's even on like, it's written up on like Atlas Obscura.
Like that's an interesting oddity enough that there was, regardless of Disney context or not, that there was a singing, a musical runway.
But for who?
Planes are loud.
How?
This would have to be deafening to play.
Nothing's louder than a landing plane also.
Like where did this, was this piped into like, it was piped into your clock radios in the contemporary.
The music, you can't hear it nearby, but if you're on a long wire that goes to the hotel next door, that's piped in there, they use it as wake up calls for people.
It must sound like someone's screaming the song.
Yeah.
It's really metallic.
Yeah, yeah.
Just horrible squealing, rubber squeaking and squealing.
It's caused tinnitus in anybody who, if you were unlucky enough to hear it, you still shake today.
You're off balance because it ruins your ear drums.
Permanent inner ear problem.
Have you heard the, what are they called on a ship?
I don't want to say a horn, but like on a cruise ship when they're like docking.
The Disney ones do that.
The Disney ones do.
It sounds like hell.
That's close.
It's so long.
It's a big chunk of when you wish about a star.
Do they play more of the song?
I wonder if this, I wonder how long this went.
Strangely, weirdly, they play the whole thing really fast, including the bridge.
Fade is come.
They get to the bridge.
I wish every airport had their own song that would play when the wheels touch down on the runway.
Just on a local, yes.
If you're in Huntsville and it's sweet home Alabama.
I love LA here.
Sweet home Chicago, the Blues Brothers or Dan Aykroyd's version.
Not when the Blues Brothers like in the 90s, some of the 90s live version.
If you want to hear Dan Aykroyd's voice, they have to hook it up to be like, it has to be a voice sampled.
Mostly these were instrumental, I would think.
That'd be a good way to set Chicago apart.
And then the people who clap when the plane lands can clap along to something.
Yeah, you'll be able to hear it.
Finally do the breaks.
The sound of those breaks.
I just don't understand.
It sounds fake to me.
How could this, maybe that's the kind of thing.
Let's just say that that happens.
And then if you're ever there, like what happened to the singing runway?
Oh, you just couldn't hear it.
I was playing.
Yeah.
Is there a Jim Hill article about this?
Probably like not.
I don't know.
Worth a check.
Weird.
That is really weird.
Why?
And could you still do it today?
If you drop a heavy crate of broken, all the innards of the Yeti that they stripped out
because it's never going to move.
If you put a bunch of metallic Yeti innards, a big crate of it, onto the singing runway,
would it land with a dong?
Would it make a note?
Well, you'd have to drag along.
It sounds like that's what it was when the wheels would do it.
So you'd have to like take your rental car and drive it on the runway
and then have somebody listen while the rental car.
Let's see if we can go on a little wild ride, a little madcap expedite.
Can we just go into the ticket and transportation center, whoop, swing around,
look at this picture, see if we can find the singing runway, roll the windows down,
see how fast that, let's get that baby singing.
Has there been a backpack or an explorer guy that's even gone over to this runway?
Because obviously River Country is a target for that and other places that are closed.
You maybe get a guy on a hoverboard or something.
Is a hoverboard heavy enough to activate it?
Would it trigger?
Yeah, hoverboard technology-wise, depends what kind.
Well, then you need 50 backpack guys at the same time.
Yeah, that's true.
All lined up perfectly.
We salute you backpack guys.
If 50 backpack guys all did sort of a race on the runway,
would they all be triggering their own When You Wish Upon a Star,
so it would all be out of sync because each one as they ran along would be at a different pace.
So the song would be at a different spot.
It'd sound like you're throwing five pianos out a window.
Yeah, that seems like that would be the case,
unless you have to have such a tremendous amount of force to trigger it.
Well, and then all their metal wallets are falling out of the pockets and just clanging along.
All of their Kickstarter metal wallets.
Because of all their expedition, they need to have something that's going to hold up to the elements.
It's an everyday carry.
You need your everyday carry.
I'm assuming that's what you mean, right?
Yeah, you need your tactical wallet, your tactical pen, your tactical backpack.
To stand up to the elements.
Yeah, the worst sunglasses you've ever seen.
It seems like you could think like them a little bit.
You could do this, I think.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, so I'm going to look and see if anybody's discovered the old runway.
Because that seems like a cool place to look around.
Is it heavily guarded because it's considered airline?
Airspace?
Airspace, yeah.
You mean because you think there's people there to prevent a plane from landing?
Like if there's a couple crates moving.
Like somebody's just down there going, no, don't land here.
Is it just because it's infrastructure, because it's air infrastructure, there's heavily armed guards?
That's a good question.
Look, if they didn't have people to stop backpack guys from just wandering around wonders of life.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, exactly.
Why would it be just an open runway?
This seems like Disney Worldwide.
You can kind of go wherever you want.
It really does.
It really seems like it's not that hard to go to different places.
And this again, obviously there's storage there now in some capacity, but this is just a street basically.
So I wonder.
Now we know also, this is old news at this point, but we've never really talked about it.
Now we know that if you feel like running around nude on It's a Small World, you can get a good five minutes of exploring before anything happens.
And you get a little hand carried walk through the park with only Disney's modesty flags covering up your button balls.
That's right.
Yes, that is a question I think I asked early on in this podcast is how far could you get?
Nude?
Not nude.
I don't know if I said nude, but how far could you get?
That's where he messed up.
I think the nudity made it like it put the heat on.
Because yeah, you could have gone another 10 minutes.
You're talking about this guy at Disneyland who.
I think so.
I think the only reason he made it as far as he did is that he was in his creepy black shorts for a while.
Before the actual nudity began.
Also let me just say the bod on that guy.
That guy was fucking cut.
He was?
He was in good shape.
Yeah.
Less in less good shape when all the Disney cards kicked the shit out of him.
Did he get beat up?
Did they beat him up?
That's not out there.
I don't know.
That's not on an iPhone video or something?
They subdued him so they could carry him out like a couch.
There was like a bunch of them carrying him.
They conked him on the back of the head and shoved him on the Long Island Expressway.
Long Island.
Yes.
Railroad.
Not the Long Island Expressway.
It always feels like anytime there's any incident in the park, it feels like the guards are located maybe at the Disneyland Hotel and they walk to whatever is going on.
It feels like that's how long it takes something to like…
Alright we got another nude guy.
Well Jerry, could you move a little faster?
I can't.
Which one of you guys knows how the phones work?
Can you put in a mobile for the Starbucks?
I gotta carry a kid again.
They switched their wide brim hat to an even bigger wide brim hat.
It's like okay, emergency protocol.
It just feels like it takes so long because in my mind and the way people try to act like you know what, there's all this security everywhere and they're secret and they got the clothes on.
You'll be gained immediately away as soon as you…
And they're so on top of everything and it feels like anytime anything weird happens it's like people checking their watch like, eh, this naked guy's been really…
he's been naked for a while here.
He is like, he is having a full bath in the Taj Mahal.
Sorry, I had to totally empty up some parents' backpacks.
I had to take everything out even though they seemed right on the edge.
By the way, Alice Obscura says the airstrip still exists but the set of musical grooves was removed in 2008 and can no longer be experienced.
What?
Yeah, so they took out the only interesting thing.
They took out the grooves.
How do you take out grooves?
I don't know.
Yeah, and what were they?
Why would you do that?
They had the time to do that.
They won't do anything.
There's whole parts of the actual parks that they won't touch.
Is River Country still standing?
Or no, did they demolish that?
I don't know.
I know.
I was rotting forever but I can't remember if they finally did destroy it.
But yeah, that's sad forever.
Discovery Island, at this point, the lost animals, the vultures of Discovery Island have learned to speak like Planet of the Apes.
If you made it over there now, they'd say, who goes there?
Lock him up!
A human has breached our island.
They've developed their own government there.
It works better than ours.
It's fair, it's not a police state.
Everybody has all the vultures, they all have what they need.
DeSantis tried to take over that vulture government too, but actually that didn't work.
They were really smart about it.
The man who camped here for a few days taught us words.
The man who camped here in 2020.
When DeSantis is out of office, then he'll run for governor of Vulture Island.
I don't think he's going to do well.
Well, I'm not literally a vulture.
I know your ways.
I can think like one.
And the vulture's like, this guy creeps me out!
The true vultures are the socialists who've worn down this country.
Silence!
We know you are wearing tall shoes.
They should not bend that way.
When you laugh, it is highly unnatural.
Is there no one who can give you proper media training?
Why didn't you just go to JCPenney's if you were going to be on the national stage like this?
Buy normal shoes, you weird man!
Let's shift course a little bit and talk about the character who appears on the ride.
If the Orlando airport people mover is a ride, you get an appearance from Friendly Figure.
I was very delighted when this came up in an episode before this episode.
Even though we got the name wrong, it felt really good to just acknowledge this common Orlando experience of hearing Buddy Dyer welcome you to the city.
I've recognized it as something, but as soon as you think about it, it's like, wow, it really is part of going there.
You get welcomed by this guy.
You did kind of an amended version of his welcome message.
It's another one of those things.
I didn't know there was any amount of cults or recognition of this thing.
But if you look on Orlando reddits, I saw one where somebody just tossed out the first line and then comment after comment just filled it in bit by bit.
They all just built it together.
This is one of those things that people really know, although the copy has changed from time to time.
I can read one that I have here.
I mean, this feels like kind of the base, but I think they have changed here and there.
But let me give this one a go.
Hello, this is Orlando Mayor Buddy Dyer.
If you're a resident of central Florida, I want to welcome you home.
If you're one of our 68 million visitors, welcome to the city beautiful.
I feel like that I've never he speaks so fast.
You can't hear that well.
I never really thought about the city beautiful, which what do you think?
What do you think of that?
We've been we haven't we maybe haven't been in downtown Orlando too much.
We did a show there.
It was it's kind of closer than I get.
The woods is I guess sometimes you're driving around Orlando like it's pretty like I I went to my first Waffle House on this trip.
Oh, yeah.
Your first Waffle House ever.
Okay.
Yes.
Would be would have been mine too.
I don't think I've been to a lot.
Yeah, I had never been.
So I stopped.
So I was I was doing a little more driving around.
I guess I rented a car.
I drove around a little bit in Orlando, which I don't normally do.
And I didn't go so many places, but I don't know that beautiful described a lot of it.
Some some some.
Right.
I went to after our live shows, I went to the McDonald's on I Drive, which has the already know you went there.
The world's largest, the crazy one, the crazy one.
It's less crazy than it used to be.
But a lot of people from the Electric Daisy Carnival were there.
So there were people like half nude standing in line.
They had blocked off the second floor where Mack tonight was was not able to go up there.
We heard him playing.
Really?
Yeah.
You could hear Mack singing, but we were not allowed up there.
You mean by we you mean you and the Daisy Carnival people?
No, my friend Dave was with me.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Me and 15, 21 year olds.
Yeah.
What was the half of their wardrobe that wasn't nude?
Bellies.
A lot of bellies, I think, were showing.
But then what are they wearing?
Is that in like fuzzy boots?
Yeah, fuzzy.
There were some fuzzy boots.
I think there were like bathing suit tops.
Everyone had their own thing going on.
It was three a.
m.
I have to stress.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Because it was late or two a.
m.
Maybe it was two a.
That one stays open that late, though.
That crazy McDonald's.
I think it might be 24 hours.
Wow.
And then I had I ordered a thing of pasta and a Philly cheesesteak.
They still have the other stick.
Because I remember when I went and like it was blowing my mind.
There's like there's a deli menu here and then ice cream.
It's a really weird McDonald's.
And some of the stuff they didn't have that late.
But I was I was like, oh, I can order pasta and a Philly cheesesteak.
I hadn't eaten dinner.
How very hungry.
They were both pretty good.
Wow.
Like, I mean, not amazing, but pretty good.
Geez.
I ate them in the hotel room alone.
Wow.
So I brought them back.
Yeah.
Well, the hotel wasn't too far.
So it wasn't so bad.
That's true.
But yeah, this used to have when you before you went in, when you went in the door,
there was like an old fiber optic kind of sign that said, prepare to be dazzled.
And I was so obsessed with that.
And then several years later, I made my show Moonbeam City and the main character is named Dazzle.
Right.
So in one scene before he was going to have sex with somebody, he said, prepare to be dazzled.
And it was always a reference or a nod to the world's largest.
Did anyone catch that?
Did anyone know that?
So many Internet sleuths like obvious a little bit hack, don't you think?
I think we've seen enough Orlando World's Largest McDonald's references on television.
Philly cheesesteak meal and choose your topping pasta and sauce.
That's the that's the order.
What did you choose?
I chose macaroni with a no, that's not macaroni.
That's what is that?
Have a topi.
What?
Cabotopi.
Cavatopi.
It is.
Yeah, Jason's right.
Cavatopi.
Cavatopi and a bolognese sauce is what I chose.
I don't remember.
I'm see Jason knows what I'm doing.
He knows what I ordered.
But he that's why I'm asking him where I went.
And have a topi is I've never heard of cavatopi.
It looks like macaroni, but it's longer and it's got ridges or whatever on it.
And then the Philly cheesesteak here.
And they were both pretty good for a lot of beef.
Bolognese and a Philly cheesesteak.
I burned a lot of calories doing live entertainment though.
So I needed to fill up Mike's big beef night.
And I was going to be a Magic Kingdom in a matter of hours.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't know you were doing that.
I was I was up so late.
I was trying to go and wake up for a virtual queue.
That was the next morning after the live show was the only morning where I felt like, oh, no, I don't know if I can move.
I like the rest of the trip I was very tired, but I was able to like rally pretty quickly.
Live shows, eating that food, staying up too late.
I was like, I don't know if I'm getting out of Orlando today.
There was never rest in that trip for us.
No, no, no, no.
So, yeah.
So but but I saw I went back.
I remember I woke up at like seven thirty and I was like, I feel like I'm going to die.
And then I slept another hour badly.
And then I was like, well, I feel like I'm going to die, but I better get to Tron.
That's what it's all about.
I better go to Tron.
Pushing your body to the limit.
Get to the game grid.
I haven't talked on in an episode about my ride back to the airport, have I?
I don't think so.
OK, really quick.
Just in thinking about the city, beautiful.
I'm contrasting that with this experience I had where I loved my driver.
This guy was so clutch and was doing like he was overriding where the, you know, ways or whatever was telling him to go.
And I think I got to the airport on time because of him.
Yeah.
And he was this funny character, this very this odd Orlando character who had he was wearing a sleeveless shirt.
So I had in a in the back, I had a perfect view of his gigantic back tattoo of Ted of the Teddy Bear.
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
Ted.
Which I asked him about it and he was like, I had that before that became a thing.
Everybody's now.
Right after I did that, everybody's doing Ted tattoos.
But I was first to do Ted tattoo.
Wow.
He thought he was like like on the cusp of a trend.
But he was giving me all this like funny Orlando real talk, including that we passed by Hooters in Lake Pointe-A-Viste where I'd been several years prior for this bachelor party.
He's like, see that Hooters?
They found they found dead body in the lake outside that Hooters.
Whoa.
I've been there.
I've been to that one.
And like I didn't think he was lying.
I took his word for it.
But I didn't know if this was like local lore and if that's just something he heard.
But then I looked it up and that's a story you can find in the news.
They found a body in the.
So that's where I'm like, lakes everywhere.
Good potential for bodies floating in the lakes.
That's good.
But I boy, that was a fun ride though.
I loved.
I couldn't make a Ted tattoo guy.
I feel like if I could like ask for him in future trips, I would.
I think I would pre book this guy with the Ted tattoo.
He was great.
I think he's got some good Orlando Lyft drivers too.
Disney guy who is like the like sweet like sweetest guy driving us around.
I think we mentioned him maybe in an episode a couple years ago.
But like I feel like there's there the characters are strong.
Yeah.
Oftentimes.
That's another like well like getting in a in a tram where Buddy Dyer is talking to you.
What do you want in Orlando?
You want interesting rides with interesting characters?
And I guess you get them wherever you go.
Be it ride, sure.
Well, yeah, you get all the old employees from Orlando, the tour guides from Orlando's former second biggest employer.
It used to be number one was the McCoy Air Force Base.
And of course, number two was Big Ronnie's fan boat tours.
And they all have gone on to different gigs when that company shuttered.
Is that real?
Big Ronnie?
It's not.
I thought maybe.
I was just pulling out the deepest.
I didn't know you were joking necessarily.
I well, that's how you got to New York.
You got on one of Big Ronnie's fan boats.
Don't you remember?
I now I'm remembering now that I did take Big Ronnie's fan boat to get to the Long Island Railroad.
Thank you for jogging my memory.
I got FFY United at some point.
Ronnie sold out.
Ronnie, you want to take the cash.
Let me keep reading his buddy's welcome message.
You probably know Orlando for its world class theme parks and attractions, but you may not know the other half of it from our professional sports, high tech and emerging medical industries to our vibrant arts community.
There is something for everyone.
Enjoy your visit.
Nice.
And he's highlighting it's not just theme parks.
There's a lot going on here.
And that seems like an area of passion for him is that, you know, he's been reelected a number of times.
He's been the mayor since 2003.
Yeah, for a while.
Just just got reelected to his sixth and final term.
He said it will be the last, but they voted him in anyway.
He said, I think I've got a little bit more I want to do.
People seem to really like Buddy Dyer, Democrat, well liked politician within a state with obviously this governor's sucks ass.
So so that that's nice.
I get a good feeling from this guy.
I think what I just read was a little bit out of date.
He got he this guy shows up and does new ones.
He updates this thing, I think, a lot when he gets the chance.
And here now, a video of great Buddy Dyer himself, a peek behind the scenes as he recorded his new message for twenty twenty two.
Hello, this Orlando mayor, Buddy Dyer.
If you're a resident, welcome home.
If you're one of our nearly 70 million visitors, welcome to the city.
Beautiful.
Here, imagination becomes reality at our theme parks and attractions.
Authentic experiences are found in our art scene, sporting events and small business districts in Orlando.
There's something for everyone.
We hope you enjoy your visit and everything that makes Orlando unbelievably real.
What do you think now that you've does does somehow that take away as as as it might for people who see us who mainly know our voices?
People might find a disconnect or are somewhat disappointed by how we look in person.
Yeah, I know.
That's what they have been like.
How do we feel now that we've seen Buddy?
I like it, actually.
I like it.
I'm happy with the way he looks.
I'm happy to see that he's looking he he's like wearing like almost like a bowling shirt or something.
He's wearing a nice red bowling shirt.
Yeah.
And you might see a little bit of white text on the ball.
Yeah, it says Mayor Buddy Dyer.
Wow.
And I've seen multiple clips of the sky in which he is always wearing a bowling shirt that says Mayor Buddy Dyer on it.
Nice.
Yeah.
Can we get Jason that shirt?
Oh, cool.
Oh, man.
That's the ultimate theme park.
That is like if you like sometimes I'm like, how do you go deeper in like 23 type cosplay then because people go so deep.
You know, people being like the guy from the Maelstrom mural or Drew Carey fanning the maps out.
I'm like, how do you go deep?
I think being Mayor Buddy Dyer with that shirt, with the red shirt, with the embroidery.
You just put a little gray in the hair, I think, and then you're fully.
Oh, sure.
I think you pass this buddy.
Yeah.
Hey, I wish I had found that video.
I kept watching rewinding YouTube videos of someone on the tram so I could transcribe his thing and then convert it to podcast the ride specifics.
Yeah.
When he says the city beauty, he says the city beautiful.
That's the line.
It reminds I'm real.
Now I know what it reminds me of because I've been trying to figure it out.
It reminds me of Captain EO when the evil queen goes, you find me beautiful.
Yeah.
Very beautiful, your highness, but without a key to unlock it.
Captain EO, another great source of flat deliveries.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Does he do cameos, you think?
Oh, I don't know.
Can we get him to do the Captain EO line?
Oh, jeez.
It just sounds so good when you say beautiful.
You find me beautiful.
That is the city beautiful is one of Orlando's like, you know, it's like the Big Apple, you know, or the Windy City or Lando.
It's like one of those except if nobody anywhere said it.
Right.
Well, it's on this road sign.
It's on this side of the road.
They're trying to make fetch happen.
Yeah, it's more likely.
I'm going to be more likely to think of it as the city beautiful.
I will say it.
I think that's the seal of the city.
I mean, this guy, he's doing the like him taking over this role,
him being like so proactive and I want to personally welcome people to the city in a way that they have to hear.
Right.
People are trying.
This is the only way to get out of the airport is through the train.
Right.
So you've got to meet Buddy.
I think this is great.
I think he's a he's a strong ambassador.
And, you know, I think they used to maybe somewhere still they might use some safety announcement.
It used to be a guy we bring up a lot.
Jack Wagner, the voice of Disneyland, the ultimate like please stand clear of the doors guy.
And I mostly I would be upset in any other case of taking that guy and his classic voice out.
And I'm just glad this isn't like who would it be?
Neil Patrick Harris, you know?
So, yeah, they don't know.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That would be probably like a more modern like instinct to go like what who can we get that's famous?
It's like any modern animated movie or CGI movie.
It's all big stars now, not voice talent like Buddy.
Well, it could be some homegrown.
I mean, DJ Khaled's from Orlando.
Well, I wouldn't be mad at that.
Joey Fatone lives there, I believe.
OK.
From Orlando.
Is that part of the whole him suddenly being in the Disney?
DJ Khaled?
I think that's one of the connections.
Yeah.
I hope so.
I hope it's because then I'm not in favor of him on the Monterey or on the PeopleMover if he's not an authentic Orlando resident.
I'm seeing him.
I'm seeing Miami is the oh, OK.
Yeah.
All right.
Then I'm not in favor of it.
Do the Miami.
Then he could do the Miami.
Yeah, I can do Miami and say another one.
I don't know.
Fucking shit.
He can do his stuff.
We know your tricks.
Billy Corgan, I would be OK with, though, if he could whisper
or just do it in the in the middle part of zero where he's like talking.
Emptiness is loneliness and loneliness is kindness.
Like you do it in that specific singing voice.
I saw the comment.
We just did this episode about the candlelight processionals and the celebrities who do this religious service.
Yeah.
And I think there was some matter of fact like Billy Corgan.
Why isn't Billy Corgan done it?
And a listener said, like, doesn't have a lyric that's about like how God is empty just like me.
God is empty just like me.
It would be strange, I guess.
You hear him suddenly telling the story of Christ.
But if you listen to the Zwan album, Zwan is very…
As many people do frequently.
And I, of course, recently listened to it.
It is sort of religious.
He's sort of a religious guy.
That's what's interesting about it.
I guess that that does add up.
He seems like the kind of.
Yeah.
So he's like a Disney Christian, I think.
After all, you know, you get old and you get more Christian and you get more into the Disney parks.
You know, when you're young.
He can do what he wants.
So anyways, Buddy seems well liked.
And he has I think people think that he's done a good job.
If you're an Orlando resident, you might tell me otherwise.
But from an outside perspective, it seems like especially where, you know, where there's bad politicians who engage in these culture wars and don't do their actual job.
It seems like Buddy has done a good job.
And he has the things that he mentions in his little narration, tech and medical innovations.
He really he seems to be very proud of like Orlando and specific Orlando communities that have made strides in that area.
And actually found a little speech that he gave an award to a particular Orlando community that's been doing great work in advanced or I'm sorry, automated mobility.
Like we talk about with the people mover, like unmanned vehicles that work as public transit and can take people around.
So here's a little speech that he gave.
The standard for automated mobility solutions for communities statewide and across the country is being set by Lake Nona.
This award is a testament to Lake Nona's culture of innovation and collaboration.
Wow.
So he's very this this this nice man is very proud of how certain communities.
I didn't know there was innovation and communication.
I guess I should rethink Lake Nona.
You had no idea the degree of innovation and communication going on there.
I actually think this is something that you would like because let me see.
They have a macaroni.
What's that?
Do they have a macaroni grill?
Oh, that's something to look up.
I don't know.
But they do have they have a program called Move Nona.
And there's a whole they have what they say is the largest autonomous vehicle system, a fleet in the country.
So you get on these.
You like your weird little transportations.
Here's something.
They have these things called beeps.
Here's a beep.
It's this odd little like tall bus that fits 10 people.
Wow.
There's one attendant on it.
That's somebody who doesn't drive it, but he just makes sure that the beeps move OK.
Wow.
And so you take if you want to move around Nona, you take you take a beep around.
That sounds good.
They look they look really nice.
Yeah, we I'm a fan.
I haven't been on a beep, but I'd like to be on a beep.
That seems better than the like self-driving cars in beta testing in San Francisco that keep almost killing people.
We're like just going like most efficient merge into opposite lane merge into opposing traffic.
You did.
I was actually happy to see this because, yeah, I think we all associate self-driving cars with Elon and nightmares.
But I'm like, but wait, we like our we like the Orlando Airport tram.
There's no driver on that.
Yeah.
Yeah, I knew.
Yeah, we I've heard nothing about the beeps.
Seems like they're successful.
I would.
Yeah.
Somebody correct us if we're wrong.
Massive beep crash.
Well, this is the dark side.
Buddy Buddy Dyer when he's not recording new narrations, he's covering up the massive beep explosions.
I know.
That's why I control the press.
Make sure there's nothing written about the dark side of Buddy.
Make sure all those people are as forgotten as the cow that died in that crash.
I was going to say you should run for governor.
Beeps.
Yeah.
Beeps keep killing cows and there's a cover up at hand.
Yeah, I was going to say, you know, we had a lot of business CityWalk related.
And we didn't get to do like Nona, but next time we're in Orlando, we need to do a little like Nona investigation.
I thought about it.
I was like, I know.
I did too.
I had the car.
But then like I also haven't said on the show that I was and Monday contemplating going to see Pitbull on Thursday night.
Oh, that's right.
That was like, yes, we were you were always that was like dancing around as a possibility.
Was he at Hard Rock Live?
No, no, he was.
It was 10 minutes down the road.
It was one of the arenas award winning arenas, world class entertainment like Pitbull.
Orlando is your home.
Thursday.
I bet I could be.
It became truly impossible by Thursday night, energy wise.
And for me to be able to Thursday was the death day.
And I was like, yeah, Monday, Tuesday, morning Wednesday.
I was like, I think I'm going to go to see Pitbull.
I'm going to go alone to see Pitbull.
It was like Enrique Iglesias and Ricky Martin.
And then I was like, this is going to be amazing.
And then Thursday hit.
And I was like, I don't think I'll be able to do the live shows if I go because I'm also going to go.
I'm going to go try to get G.
A.
I'm trying to get pit and I'm going to get hammered.
I can't do it.
Pit for Pitbull.
I can't.
I was like, I can't do it.
I went to bed early.
In the pit with Red Bull.
Yeah, Pit and Bull at Pitbull.
He's got to have that rhyme in one of his songs, I think.
But yeah, so.
So that's Enrique and Ricky Martin.
Yeah, this sounds great.
It's not going to be a big party.
But yeah, so so there were blue sky things in my mind where I was like, maybe I go like Nona, maybe I see Pitbull.
And then after so much city walk, I was like, I can't do anything extra.
It killed our spirits.
Yes.
Yeah, that's true.
It killed our ambition.
I also have a little clip of Buddy being interviewed about his role as the.
Oh, great.
B.
O.
guy.
He smacks Buddy in the arm there.
It's his greatest achievement.
He seems he's he's very proud of it.
Yeah.
Happy to talk about it.
And that, by the way, was a clip from a YouTube show called The More You Nona, a show about Lake Nona happening.
Oh, we got to get on that show if it's still around.
Yeah, I've heard that there's no show that's as more it's more innovative and where the host is better communication.
We can we get can we get yeah, can we get our own show on Lake Nona's YouTube?
The more you know, the dirty dogs of Lake Nona.
Yeah, I guess it could be it's it's PG 13 show Lake Nona's.
Yeah, yeah, we show you not to act.
Uh huh.
They're the goofus's of opposed to the gallons.
Right.
I was I was looking buddies.
Real name is John.
John Hugh Dyer.
Hmm.
Well, now I don't know how I feel about you know, like, what does he have to hide?
Is Buddy anyone's actual full like real name on a birth certificate or is it always a nickname?
I don't know.
I'm sure there's some.
What about Buddy Epson, a member of the Disney family?
You know I love my Epson talk.
He was a he was Frank Christian Ludolf Epson, also known as Frasso, not in several ways, not a buddy.
Not a buddy, not a not a birth certificate buddy.
There's got to be some birth certificate buddies.
Oh, wait, now he's he grew.
Wow.
I didn't know he grew up in Orlando.
That's interesting.
Buddy Epson.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Wow.
Graduated from Orlando High School.
What?
Yeah, went to the University of Florida in Gainesville.
Is that an Orlando name buddy?
Yeah, maybe.
More likely to be a buddy.
What about Buddy Guy?
Or buddies per capita than.
Buddy Guy.
Do you think his name is Buddy for real?
Sure.
His name is George.
George Guy.
Who's a buddy by birth?
What about my buddy, the toy?
Is that really his name?
I guess his first name is My.
His first name is My.
On his first certificate.
Famous buddies.
Buddy Holly.
What do we think?
Is his real name Buddy?
I don't think so.
I think it is.
It's a rock and roll nickname.
Charles Hardin Holly.
There are no real buddies.
No real buddies.
Famous buddies.
We could stop this.
If any future children are in the fold, we could make a true buddy by birth.
Yeah, Jason, what were you saying?
Oh, I was going to say I had a my buddy sitting on a little chair in my childhood bedroom for years.
That creeps me out.
Sitting in a little chair.
Did you move him?
Did you get him out of the chair?
Well, the thing was I stayed young and he started looking like shit.
He got older and older all the time.
Oh my God, he aged.
Oh my God, that is.
Your buddy, Doc.
Buddy, the first nature boy in wrestling, Buddy Rogers, his real name was Herman Gustav Roady Jr.
Not a real buddy.
As far as I can tell, country singer Buddy Jule Jr.
is a buddy from birth.
Really?
Okay.
Yes.
So that's the one who won the show Nashville Star in 2003.
There are birth buddies.
There is a birth certificate buddy.
That is a birth certificate buddy.
I had an internship once.
Some guy who was like an executive I had never met one day came in with a cardboard box of stuff.
And he was like, we're going to build a website for Nashville Star.
And it's going to be there's going to be message boards and there's going to be all this stuff and you're going to head it up.
And then I never saw him again.
And I also finished the semester about 10 days later.
So I don't know why he thought I was going to build a massive Nashville Star website.
You think it's going to be on your shoulders?
It's going to be on my shoulders.
This is a for credit internship, which I would advise people.
Opt for money.
Don't do that.
Get paid folks.
That's an interesting thing.
Credit is our credits are used as currency in futuristic films.
Credit is in some ways in some worlds or planets credit could be a good thing.
These were academic credits.
It's just on paper.
But in an alternate dimension perhaps.
Wow.
So you weren't even like, maybe just to test my metal.
Maybe I should.
Maybe you did it unofficially.
I just want to see if I can.
I just built a spec Nashville Star website.
Maybe I should start a Squarespace or a Wix.
What if I build a very elaborate Nashville Star website now?
Yeah.
Then you could change your name to Jason Buddy Sheridan.
And then you sort of are more in the Nashville scene because that feels like a kind of a southern nickname to me.
I wonder if the official website is out there.
I wonder what became of the website once you dropped out of the fold.
I don't think it ever got very far than a Pankers box with some CDs and pronounce in it.
It seems like what you'd want to do is like maybe go through the web department of Warner Brothers rather than some kid.
Yeah.
It's probably a better plan.
One dipshit whose main job seems to be taking the golf cart to get six things of soup for the assistants who are not being paid very much and keep ordering soup,
not thinking about how will that 21 year old transport six things of soup in a golf cart?
How'd it go?
I don't want to say that I hope that you spilled it, but I kind of hope that you spilled it.
No.
Because that's your stories about food service.
Yeah.
Was just you spilling marinara and stuff.
I know.
That's right.
And then cutting yourself on the meat.
But you were also a soup transporter.
I was a soup transporter.
And that hasn't come up on the show.
And then on Tuesdays, if you remember your CityWalk history, there used to be a Rubio's fish tacos and those were dollar fish tacos on Tuesdays.
You know.
So you transported.
I transported a lot of fish tacos and I think people ordered combos and then I had to transport fountain sodas.
Whoa.
In like little individual cups?
In little like, yeah, carriers in the cardboard.
So thankfully they sent two of us to kind of manage all this.
Also, we didn't need sodas.
It was like a production bungalow.
There was a refrigerator in every room filled with soda cans.
Yeah.
But they want the ice in the straw.
They want the ice.
It's the good ice.
It's just for the feel and the syrup with the pending.
It's a different taste.
I'm finding now some Nashville Star.
The website on archive.
org, it looks like shit.
I think you could have only helped it.
Oh, I could have built a social media website from scratch.
With no web design experience or coding experience.
I mean, it looks like they ultimately did land on an intern or something.
But wow.
Well, geez, look at that.
We got mythology.
We got Lake Nona local shows.
Yeah.
We've covered a lot of ground here.
Any final thoughts, closing thoughts about Orlando's first ride?
How about, well, let's head the other way.
Now we're past security.
We're heading back, unfortunately, to the air sides.
Going back to our air side.
Does it make you ever, is that a down side?
Do you feel a little sad to have to get on these trams or is it the other?
Do you feel like, well, one final ride?
Yeah, I always feel a little melancholy.
Yeah.
Vacations ending.
It's comforting, though, for buddies.
Farewell.
Yeah, I don't have any copy of that.
I don't know what he's I don't remember how he says goodbye.
I have an outro.
When we wrap up business, I'll do the outro.
Oh, OK.
OK.
So that'll give us a flavor of buddies.
Oh, geez.
Great.
As I said, I skipped this monorail trip or this this people mover trip because I went to Gate C and took a lift from the rental car place.
So I skipped it and I was a little sad.
Now, I needed to skip it because I was running late.
So I was happy about that.
But once I got to the, oh, he's dropping me right here.
So I guess I'm going to have to skip the people mover ride.
And I was a little bit bummed out by that.
So I do want that extra.
I want that last little ride.
You're you're to the airport.
Yes.
Good night from Mayor.
I had to ask for a kiss.
Good night from the lift driver instead.
So I could get a little bit of it, but it wasn't the same.
But at least he has the full back tattoo of million ways to die in the West.
I didn't know I get a shirt on.
So I was the first one to do this.
There was nobody else doing Christopher Lloyd as Doc Brown specifically in that not back to the future.
Now, everybody's got everybody's doing it.
Yeah.
Brown from million ways to die.
Well, I mean, I guess we're I guess we're wrapping up and hearing our final message.
You know, that's the last thing I didn't say.
I like neat just like neon circles.
There's just an area.
Yeah.
There's like kind of a kind of 80s in those little tubes that you you can't.
It's the same thing that I love about Epcot that like where I a lot of Epcot changes and updating.
I welcome.
But I always want the like the bones to be kind of blocky in 80s.
And even though they change the trains, there's still like an inherent kind of ladies in Epcot feel to the trams.
So it makes it all it's like a motif that ties a bunch of the Orlando experience together.
And I like that and I appreciate that.
Yes, that's absolutely the case.
And yeah, I would.
The crystal.
What is it called?
The crystal crystal train crystal movers.
Thank you.
Those also if it's the right picture I was looking at, like those still even give me the vibe.
I can tell they're newer, but that still gives me the vibe you're talking about as well.
So there.
Yeah, you can't.
I also know that I've said crystal mover again.
Like that sounds like something you would call like kind of drug runners in a movie that didn't do very good research about how crystal meth is dealt.
We got to like stop the crystal move.
We've got to stop the crystal.
All right.
We call it now.
We call these crystal movers.
You got to get we're going to flood the streets with crystal movers.
OK, as you said that, I thought you were going to say it sounds like a stripper's name.
Crystal mover and coming up next.
Movers.
She'll be she'll be dancing to Pitbull.
And keep in mind, if you sit in the pit closest to crystal and order a Red Bull, that's half off for the next half hour.
Did I say I said this already, right?
On the show that that right there rental car places right by a cult place called Rachel's Steakhouse that was also a strip club in Orlando.
Wow.
I was like, why would you get a steak?
It's I think it's called Rachel's.
Right.
Are you looking it up?
Yeah.
So crystal movers.
Lord is finest, it says.
Yeah, I can't say that's not true.
I didn't.
Well, unless it's on the side, it's right by where I got the rental car.
So I'm driving and I was like, is that a state?
Oh, it's a what?
It was very confused.
I didn't go in.
I would never go in.
But if I knew Crystal Movers was there, I might have gone in.
What kind of steakhouse is this?
As I peruse the website, I see not a steak in sight.
It's nothing but scantily clad women.
I mean, are the steaks look appetizing or not?
Your website's not telling me anything.
Tell Mr.
Morrill should go and review Rachel's.
And you just see strippers in the background unacknowledged.
I'm going to ask.
I'm going to ask you.
And then a woman's like trying to like rub his back and he's like just like brushing it away.
Yeah.
Not not interested.
I'm trying to focus.
Maybe he could do a channel like Nona specific late night show or something.
Not on his channel.
That's very G rated.
Mr.
Morrow after dark.
Right.
Well, let's let's let's wind it down here and get to the final spiel.
This is very fun to talk about and hopefully a fun kickoff to the year.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thank you for subscribing to the second gate.
As you hear this, we are still on hiatus on the main feed.
So if you want more PTR during this hiatus, keep it tuned here on Patreon or join us on our VIP Patreon tier club three,
where you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
I also want to note in the buddy list on Wikipedia, the cake boss is not a buddy from birth either.
Buddy Velastro is Bartolo Velastro Jr.
So also not a birth buddy, unfortunately.
Right.
Jason podcast the ride.
The second gate has so much to offer.
There's a good chance you didn't hear it all.
So please come back and listen again very soon.
This is podcast the ride co-host Jason Sheridan.
We hope you enjoyed your second gate experience.
That was that was nice.
I would in the future, you know, since we're having trouble getting you to be the mayor of anything,
I feel no ego in saying if you want to declare yourself the mayor of podcast the ride, fine by me.
OK, that's yours.
That's yours.
Mayor Jason Buddy Sheridan or just get rid of the Jason Mayor Buddy Sheridan.
This is the mayor of podcast the ride.
Jason Buddy Sheridan.
So your buddy Sheridan.
I think it works.
I think it's good.
Wow.
Yeah.
I got a new name for 2024 Mayor Buddy.
You got to keep it.
You got to keep it different.
You got to keep things changing.
You got to keep it interesting.
You got to surprise people.
Switch it up.
This new year, Jason has a new name.
Wow.
Only on second gate.
We only call you Mayor Buddy on the second gate.
Yeah, that's what you're paying for.
Exclusive names.
Great.