Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate,
the PTR post office, and Mike could not hold in laughter
for very long because something has happened.
Look, this is gonna start with an energy
and you're gonna understand why.
Basically, I took this innocuous post office situation
as an excuse to drop a bombshell on Mike and Jason.
And the whole idea here was for the surprise
of the bombshell being dropped to be what was compelling
about what has just occurred.
And Mike, then what happened?
So what happened was there was this big revelation
that happened and Jason and I were like,
we were called into the principal's office for this.
This was a big major thing that involves
a big piece of PTR lore.
We were dissecting it already,
we were trying to like defend ourselves.
And I looked down and the Zoom recorder
that we used to record the podcast was not recording,
which felt like I maybe did it on purpose or I willed it.
I didn't wanna hear our embarrassment live.
So like I, using like telekinesis,
turned the Zoom recorder off.
And then I'm already getting, you know,
I'm already being told that something I've done is wrong.
And I looked down and I have to say,
teacher, excuse me, apparently I wasn't recording the podcast.
And I go, oh God.
Very interesting.
In one year, you're being called a task.
Exactly, but how would I have done it?
I didn't just like put my toe on it.
So this basically by sheer serendipity,
that part wasn't recorded.
So we don't hear Jason and I learning for the first time
that a thing we did was wrong.
Wow, wow.
So we're just gonna have to recreate the moment.
And the only thing that maybe improves it
is that now I'm coming in with even more mage than before.
Where I drop all of this and then there's this,
you aren't recording.
And then there was this fumbling with the mic stand
that was like a silent film routine.
There was a part, it was tipping over.
It wasn't balanced.
And then a part where your mic went limp.
It flopped over and made a sound like, pew.
It was like a visual metaphor for a limp dick occurred.
It is, yes.
It's been an insane last couple minutes.
Yeah, well, but I am gonna say,
I am gonna have my guard up from now on
if we ever do an episode where it's like,
maybe it's not the most exciting E-ticket.
Cause Scott has got me like twice now.
You mean because of the Minotaur.
We gotta do the Today Show Cafe.
We gotta do the PTR Pro.
I was like, you know what I think is supposed to happen?
You know what I think is Today Show would be good.
And then I've got these little secrets.
And I'm just like, hey, sounds good, my man.
Other stuff I'm dealing with right now.
So that sounds easy breezy for me.
We call that.
We did, yeah, that was good.
That was one of the things that I wish we had earlier
when you were like, oh no, I'm sick.
I can't hear this, Scott.
And you started pretending to cough.
So that's gone.
We missed that.
Ironic, cause I just came from an ophthalmologist appointment.
They're like, hey, Vizent's, yeah,
your heart is totally healthy, perfectly fine.
Scott's got great eyes.
Three and six months.
Well, there you go.
Well, then everything's fine then, isn't it?
So this is a perfect scenario in which to now,
for the second time, drop a bomb
and the surprise will be gone,
but it'll still be a surprise to the listener.
Leave a gap for them to gasp as I'm sure that they will.
What I said the first time around
is that we've been culling from the Patreon comments,
but we also have an email address.
MikeHastthewrightatgmail.
com.
And we haven't mentioned this maybe in a while,
but people know it exists.
And now I'm thinking this is a great place
for long form content corrections,
being dragged through the coals or whatever that phrase is.
Dragged over the coals, I believe.
Dragged over the coals.
Raked, yes.
Get ready for an auditory rake.
That is what's coming.
And this probably is not the tone
that was intended by the person who sent it,
Graham Southwood.
However, he did give his email a headline,
a subject line that could not be ignored.
This was some click bait
because I could not help but dive in on this
because this was the subject line.
Major error in Clooney briefcase story.
And I dive in, I wonder,
is this guy grasping for straws?
What is this gonna be?
But I have to say,
I believe every word of what I'm about to read.
Quote to Graham.
Hello, my wife and I are huge fans of the show
and love listening every week.
I am also one of the likely few people
who knew the infamous briefcase story
before hearing it on the podcast.
I had read the initial article,
so thought it was quite funny
it was being brought up on PTR.
However, you have one major error
when telling the story on the podcast.
The actual Clooney briefcase story
is not that he gave the $1 million briefcases
with the proceeds from selling Casamigos,
but rather with the payday from Gravity,
the 2013 feature film Gravity.
This does track, says Graham,
because why would he give Randy Gerber $1 million
when he also made the insane bank
on the Casamigos sale?
Good point, Graham.
He also says, thanks for all the entertainment.
Another good point, Graham.
Signed Graham.
Well, it's a good sign that Graham was still listening
after this error had been made.
I'll say that.
That he's not resigning as a listener,
which I would not blame anyone for doing.
No, if they wanna just throw their phones
out their car windows in disgust, I would understand.
But he hasn't, that's good.
That's a good sign, at least.
That makes me feel okay.
Yes, yes.
And at first I wondered, like, who is this Graham?
Who is this Graham to come at the world's foremost
Randy Gerber experts, Mike and Jason?
You hired a private investigator
who followed Graham around for a few weeks
to make sure he was somebody who could,
who was on the level, who would actually check.
The story checks out, seems like a good guy.
We have a guy on retainer, like most podcasts.
Oh, you have to.
He is a total dirtbag.
He is, his life is constantly falling apart.
So we're like, okay, that's a good private eye.
Yes, yeah, yeah, no, we ran,
we had a different private eye run a check on him
to make sure that he was a mess,
because that would be the best guy,
would be our private eye.
Anyway, I did do my due diligence on what Graham has dropped,
and I have to say, I think that this is completely accurate.
And at this point, I repeat some of what I said
the last time we recorded it.
And it's still recording, I'm looking at it.
I'm looking at it.
It better be.
We're four years deep into the presence
of this story on our podcast.
We have been haunted by this tale for four years now
for a full presidential administration.
That's right.
And this entire time, there has been a glaring error.
Now, Mike, in the previous recording,
you tried to shift blame from yourself
and put it squarely on Jason.
However, I have a feeling Graham sent this email
because we just told the story again,
thanks to Griffin in the Orlando live show
that came out not long ago.
And in that one, Mike, you are the person who repeats
what we have now found to be a falsehood.
That's true, and I've certainly been spreading the lie,
but there's no doubt in my mind
that I learned a lie from Jason.
Jason is the one who lied first accidentally.
Because as we've talked about on the show before,
I was just very interested in Randy Gerber the man,
not the story necessarily.
Jason is the one who brought the story element
into the podcast, and then I adopted the story
as my own story as well after that.
Loved it like a son.
To bond with Jason also too,
just because we're good friends
and we were sort of bonding over the story.
We both met sort of in the middle,
like a friendship necklace or the heart necklace
that bonds together.
I knew this about Randy and Kaia Gerber.
So your little hearts that came together,
that's how this feels.
That's right, yeah.
And then Jason had the briefcase story
because it's the biggest fantasy of his life
that a friend of his just gives him a million dollars for free.
This is what he's been hoping.
Taxes paid, baby.
This is what he's been.
I do think if this happened to Jason,
if you were one of the 14, you would be excited
and then you'd say like, taxes no.
I'm assuming someone was like, oh fuck,
like 100,000 gone, 200,000 gone.
So I certainly retold the wrong story
a couple of weeks ago in Orlando,
but the origin of the wrong story
is this man sitting next to me on the left.
I chalk it up to being a apocryphal
or conventional wisdom, whatever you call it.
Like most stories recapped on podcasts.
What does that mean?
What do you mean it's apocryphal?
I was kind of like, oh, I heard it somewhere
and it was kind of an anecdote
and then I kind of like, I remembered it.
That's a good point.
I read the People Magazine article about it
where they talk about walking up the driveway
or something.
This is a very good point.
I'll come back to you, Mike, but that's a good point
because the first you brought it up,
it is not as if this was some researched situation.
You were just dying to tell the story to Nick Mundy
who then unplugged our microphones and left the apartment.
That was the first way this played out.
And then it was told again,
because it had to come out of your brain.
However, where I begin to take umbrage with both of you
is, okay, that's all 2019, cut to 2020,
the one time I'm not here for an episode.
And you guys spring a surprise one called
Casamigos Tequila in which there is preparation,
in which articles have been read and studied.
I've already had to provide one rebuttal for this episode
and now I find myself doing a second.
This was the chance that the facts could have been caught
and corrected.
Well, a lot of that episode was focused on making sure
the local city bike installation did have two available
that we could sit on and get a picture at.
You can pat your belly and rub your head at the same time.
Can you not?
That's true, yeah, that's true.
You can do all of these things at once.
That's true, you know, and it makes,
here's what's interesting about that.
Now it would make sense that in all of the Casamigos
articles I read, that story doesn't come up
because it has to do with gravity.
It has nothing to do with Casamigos.
Let me do a little bit of, now let me go into
what I have learned.
Okay, because I went back, I had to go back.
It's crazy how many times I've now had to consult
the episode Casamigos Tequila.
There is a part in which Jason says the date,
the date in which the briefcases were exchanged.
Oh, so he is, okay.
September 20th, Jason says September 20th, 2013.
Then you both go on to say this is a date
that will live in infamy.
So I go to look this up and I find that Jason
got the date wrong, but only by a week.
Only by a week, so not so bad.
That's not bad.
Not so bad, just saying while we're bringing things up.
That's just kind of the level of facts
that we're dealing with here.
September 27th, 2013.
And the dates, this is really where the smoking gun lies
because the timeline here, 2013 was when Casamigos
was founded, there was no money.
The two of them were in the fields rolling up their sleeves
planting the agave, harvesting the agave.
I don't know what they were doing with the agave.
At least hanging out with the guys who were doing it.
Yeah, pouring, getting bottles of the first batch,
pouring it into copper cups like in the commercial.
The authentic commercial.
They were busy with copper cups.
They had to pay for those cups themselves at that time.
There was no money for people to get million dollar cases.
It was not until June 2017 that liquor conglomerate
Diageo purchased Casamigos to this insane degree
of 700 million dollars.
So it's all been right there.
The dates, further details about this story came out
not until 2020, until after that episode occurred,
the Your Guys episode, but all of these facts were out there.
The date of the sale and the date of the case exchange.
And I don't know, it was all there in front of you.
I'm wondering, that's really fascinating now
that you knew the date of the briefcase story,
but the details weren't, that's interesting to me, isn't it?
Well, that means whatever source I pulled that date from.
Well, that's what I'm wondering.
Did you go to a source that was wrong?
Because if you-
Let me say this, but I saw so many articles
that said September 27th, 2013.
That date is out there a ton.
I don't doubt that you could have pulled it
from the wrong one, but this date gets underlined
because it's the exact same date
that one year later he marries Amal.
So there is some real significance to the date.
So if you pulled it from an article,
this article was wrong on two counts.
Wow.
Maybe I was just amazed that they're glamour
and beauty together as a globetrotting couple.
Did we even say the word Amal?
Did we say the name Amal on the show?
You sure did.
It does come up.
Yes, this fact is said that one year later on that day-
We do say that.
Does Jason say it or do I say it?
Jason says it.
Okay, so you were in an article about this.
This is interesting to me.
I'm in Amal?
No, I'm just saying you were in an article.
You were reading an article.
You were reading one of the articles Scott said.
You would have to think.
Now the Amal timeline is important here
because he is not married at this point.
And when you come into a big financial windfall
and then want to start giving briefcases of money to people,
the first on your list might be your wife, right?
But he doesn't have a wife at this time.
This is why I think it's an important part of the story
because where he is in his life,
where he's still technically single,
he's not in too deep with Amal.
This puts him at a place where he's like,
well, I'm getting all of this gravity money,
which is, by the way, percentages of the movie,
because they thought, quote George,
they thought it was gonna be a flop.
And that ended up being a very good deal.
Was it like 60 million?
This is why he thought of his buds, his boys,
instead of his own wife.
Right, was it like 60 million?
Did it say in an article what it was?
We don't know the full extent of the gravity money.
It was like that big of a number, I think,
in the zone or higher or whatever.
I guess I should have looked that up
because I'm now dealing with money and details here.
When did he stop dating WWE diva, Stacey Keebler?
That's my question.
Was he out of that Keebler relationship
before he gave the money?
When Keebler might've been eligible for a million dollars.
That's what I'm wondering now too,
because if it's earlier than that,
then she probably, they probably stopped dating, I'm guessing.
But I would like to know now, just to know timeline wise.
We should just, we need to know more, I think,
at this point, just to make sure
we don't ever back into a wrong fact again.
Right, okay, so Clooney and Stacey Keebler
split in July 8th, 2013.
Whoa.
So.
This is important information then.
It is.
This shows you the dramatic nature of his life.
Yeah.
That he really is thinking about friends.
Friends are what are most important to him at this time.
I don't wanna say the-
In the crazy summer of 2013.
I don't wanna say the phrase, bros before.
Jason could say it, but I can't.
But that's what he's thinking.
That's an appropriate way to talk about people.
Oh, okay, excuse me.
Bros before casamigos is what you were heading for, right?
I'll say it.
Why not?
So yeah, wow, Clooney Keebler split.
That's fascinating.
E-news Anatomy of a Split.
Wow.
Clooney Stacey Keebler.
Wow, well we're doing Anatomy of a Story right now,
and Anatomy of a Split is now an important part of it.
I think what this has all shed a light on
is that other than the presence of both Clooney and Gerber,
the briefcase's story is unrelated to casamigos.
I mean, it's not, I mean, it's part of the fabric of the,
if you made a movie about it,
it would be in the background.
But I think that you could not willingly call this
the casamigos briefcase story.
No.
That's something that's out at this point.
If all this is accurate, no,
there's no casamigos relation at all,
other than Randy being there.
Did we say on any of these podcasts specifically
that Randy got a million dollars?
Yes, because I've heard it so many times,
an important part of it is that he had to take
the million dollars or nobody got the million dollars.
So he took it.
I thought it was everyone took it for us.
Everyone that had to take it, yeah.
Okay, yeah, but including him, right?
He said, I don't want the million dollars.
I am very wealthy from my wife
and whatever awful family I'm in.
He has two brothers and they all do restaurant stuff.
but George insists.
And then he, actually this comes up in Graham's email
that he says, that he, all right,
if Randy doesn't take it, nobody gets it.
Randy made a point to say he donated it all to charity.
And who am I to question the legendary Randy Gerber?
My wife says he came off pretty well
in the super dot model documentary with Cindy Crawford,
but I would be interested to see
that tax return for the year.
We'll get working on that, Graham.
We'll dive into Gerber's taxes.
I have pictures of casamigos being served
at Kate Bosworth's birthday, Paris Hilton's birthday,
with Vin Diesel in the Bloodshot premiere.
Does that have anything to do with the article
that you were looking for?
My notes from 2020.
You pulled up your notes from the episode.
Wait a minute.
So in the notes, do you have the date?
What does it say?
There's actually no dates in these notes.
Where would you have found the date then?
Oh no, the only date specifically mentioned
is that casamigos was bought by Diageo
for $700 million in 2017.
2017, it was right there.
It was in your notes.
This has been in front of us at all times.
Is it an important part of the story?
I don't know, but I think it's important to bring up
because this story is clearly gonna be a presence
on this podcast and in our lives
until the podcast or we die.
I think this is great because you're right.
This podcast story will be told again.
Again and again and again.
Whoa, I forgot Omega Watches collaborated
with Casamigos for an exclusive
Seamaster Planet Ocean Watch.
Because it will be good to tell the story now.
It'll feel good to tell it, I think, going forward.
You can tell it guilt free.
It won't be resting on a lie.
Because now we know where the character of George was at,
thinking about his friends, his heart,
and tatters on the ground.
I think it improves the story.
It ups the stakes in the drama.
Yes, it does.
I think that, okay, now it's the gravity story, I suppose.
It is unrelated to Casamigos.
Well, I think you could still call it, you know,
you could just put Clooney first and foremost in it.
I'll say this though.
Here's William H.
Macy and Felicity Huffman
toasting Casamigos.
I was like, aha, we got her into college.
Here's what I'll say though.
I love it, but my anxiousness to do this,
to rake you guys over the coals has now led to,
now I'm the nightmare of getting bonus content
from an episode I had to be, from four years ago,
I had to do a rebuttal for already.
September 2020, mentally healthy, all of us at that point.
Here's what I'll say about this though.
The way the story has been told,
yes, some of the facts may be inaccurate,
but the spirit of the story remains the same.
A generous man wanting to reward his buds
with some free cash, a generous spirit of George Clooney,
and sort of the terms of the deal.
All of that is still intact, which is why I'm happy about that
because if you were like, actually what happened was,
it was the money from Gravity,
and also he didn't give them money,
everybody opened up the briefcase
and they got shot in the face like the slime,
the Katy Perry gif of Katy Perry at the Nick Awards,
and she gets hit in the face with slime really hard.
If that was the story, then I would really feel bad.
He wouldn't be a very good friend then at all,
would he be?
Right.
Well, but just Richard Kine got the slime.
He got the million dollars for his free case.
That was in the cut part.
We talked about Richard Kine being one of the guys.
Can I ask a quick question?
This is a little bit of a side note, Jason.
Of all the people you met when we met in 2009
or whatever at UCB, was there anyone you pegged
for your million dollar sugar daddy of all the friends?
I mean, clearly you.
We've been banging the Trump for so long, old boy.
We're trying still.
You're still hoping maybe.
Still hoping, yeah.
That one day that Mike scores a big payday
and that like- A Gravity size.
Hopefully it's gravity sized.
It's big enough that it can initially go to
Mike's wife and child if he's like not wanting
to look out for his buds.
Maybe his parents or sister get something.
But if Mike's got his priorities right,
then a million goes straight into Jason's coffers.
Yeah, so I think what, yeah, in that scenario,
it's just I have a big kitchen table
and it's only you at the table and you're at the other end.
And then you open up the briefcase and I go,
here it is, million dollars.
And you go, taxes?
Taxes?
And then I go, yep, taxes too.
Of course, I did it for you only, not for my daughter.
Yeah, you had to pay the taxes.
I'm still above her in the will, right?
You forgot to revise that?
to the Patreon just for Jason.
If anyone is ultra wealthy and they want to give Jason
a million dollars tax free, you can subscribe.
We could add it.
It's five, it's eight, and it's one million.
Yeah.
And also the taxes.
It has to be the taxes.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
Cause that's gonna haunt ya.
Cause yeah, there's a lot of taxes.
A lot of taxes for a million bucks.
Mike, you're right.
That the story, the spirit of the story
has always been told.
However, there's a slippery slope here, right?
Because what we've found, there's all of these stories
that have attached themselves like barnacles
to the whole of this podcast.
One of them being, I think we've questioned
some inaccuracies maybe in the famous
hemisphere dancer story.
We're gonna get into that at some point.
And then of course, the real predecessor
to what we're doing right now, Frank Marshall Gate,
where you made a very similar argument,
which is well, the spirit, because Frank's spirit was there.
Even though he did not speak,
and the main thing was you yelling at us
cause we didn't remember the speech.
So that, this spirit thing, I think it does apply
with Clooney, but if we start hiding
in that spirit argument, we're never gonna get out of there.
Then anyway, so it is allowed.
Sort of joie de vivre, you can only get through
the magic of podcasting.
How much mass media do you get this?
Podcasting, if what you're saying,
and I don't know what you're saying,
but if what you're saying.
Me neither, brother.
Now you might understand it now.
If what you're saying.
That's sort of, I don't know what, you know?
But I'm gonna guess, I'm gonna take a guess here.
If what you're saying is that podcasts
are more about vibes than facts, then I'm with you.
I hear what you're saying, and I agree.
You know, it doesn't necessarily,
it's just the feeling, the spirit of Frank being there
at the opening of Jurassic World
is what I was riding high on,
and I was excitedly trying to say,
don't you remember, Frank was there.
Yeah.
Words he said, okay, yes, I got that part wrong,
but we were in his presence, we were breathing his air.
I just think, and now we're arguing this again,
it would certainly help me to have remembered
him being there at all.
One thing that might stand out in my memory
is if he said two words on a microphone.
He didn't, but his aura was strong.
That's the thing that I'm saying here.
I've already been through that
we didn't even have eyes on it.
We were blocked, we couldn't even see this.
I had eyes on it, but maybe it's because I'm six-three.
Yeah, I know, but you're tall, I'm a six-three guy.
I can't find one way that you being tall
gets you out of this situation right now.
It doesn't, and I have to apologize to the audience,
and I'll apologize to the audience for one other thing too,
because I am a man who does things like this, apologize.
That is, I believe I called Michael Meldman
the silent partner in costume.
He goes, Michael Melman on the live show in Florida.
So I apologize for that.
His name is Michael Meldman, there's a D in there,
and I said Melman, and I remember listening back to him
going, I think that's wrong, and yes, it is wrong,
so I apologize to the listeners.
People who've been hanging on that for that as well.
I need to do, you know, we all need to hold ourselves
to a higher standard.
I tried to get ahead of this, I've addressed this online,
but I haven't done it on the show.
I have thrown out what I've realized is false,
that the revolving restaurant at the Lampadillion
stopped revolving at some point.
I don't know where that entered my head.
That is a fair thing for listeners to say.
I think I've said it to somebody,
and it's because of you in the same way
that Jason poisoned my brain,
you poisoned my brain about the revolving restaurant.
You're right, I'm also a man.
I will withstand the points that you're doing right now,
and you're right.
That was saying a falsehood.
I don't know if I can pin it on that maybe I was there
once when it was not revolving
for an extended period of time,
but I've definitely, unfairly, put that into a pile
of things that are cruddy about that pavilion,
and I've caused that to reflect poorly on this ride,
and I have to take that out of the argument.
That's not fair.
I'm not being fair to the ride, and I'll admit it.
That, thank you.
That does make it, thank you for the audience.
I don't need the thing.
I don't need the apology.
It's not for me, it's for the audience.
I'm too, I don't need it.
And I thank the audience for not being that mean about it.
There's a way to do these things.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm being quite mean to you, but.
That's okay.
I'm comfortable with it.
I'm a man.
And I just want the audience to know
that the Wall Street Journal once described
Michael Melman as real.
Yeah, Jason, Melman, he just said it.
Melman.
They called him real estate's party boy.
Yeah, yeah, I remember that.
Take that as you will.
You said that in the episode.
You said that in the episode, yeah.
We're just repeating ourselves.
I know, but it was so long ago, it's a good refresher.
But Michael only said Melman,
and did a whole thing about it less than five minutes ago.
He was busy reading his poem.
He had his head in his notes.
I was just thinking about partying with Melman.
I got too excited, I don't know.
I've told the Melman story that a friend of ours
on the show, but we don't have time for it.
That was told on the other one.
It was told on the other one.
We don't need to tell that one again.
Okay, you know why we don't need to tell it?
Because I'm not done.
I'm not done here at all.
And if you guys still think this is a mailbag episode,
you've got another thing coming.
Okay, okay.
Because here's what I started thinking.
Are we gonna use those questions eventually?
Oh yeah, so we will.
We will.
Great.
I'm sorry you were part of a ruse,
but we will get to the questions.
That's fine, I can handle it.
Okay, I started thinking.
If the source of the money in the story was false,
what else about this tale might be false?
Now how would we describe the story?
What is like the, if you had to sum up the story
with a title, what's the title of the story?
When you, the other day, when we finished recording,
we're like, oh, I don't wanna be a little greedy.
Can we get one more recording?
And did you already have this in mind?
Of course he did.
That was a little show.
What do you think?
I guess.
What do you think, Jason?
I mean, I do wanna talk about that parade.
It seems fun.
We're gonna get to that.
We cannot move forward on anything.
Some great questions too.
Any future plans.
I guess I was gonna do the questions.
We'll be doing the questions.
I guess you would say like, is the briefcase story,
were there no briefcases?
Is that what you're about to reveal here?
Well, for the answer to that one,
we turn to something that in all of the discussion of this
has never actually been consulted.
That is the video clip in which this story was first told
on a MSNBC show from 2017 called Headliners.
This presumably was an episode about George Clooney.
They get into the generosity of George Clooney
and they talk to Randy Gerber.
And I believe for the first time now ever on the show,
we're gonna actually hear the voice of Randy Gerber.
Oh my God.
It's like hearing God speak.
I'm hearing it too emotional for me.
Sitting in front of each of us on the table
is a black like to me bag.
It's a to me bag.
You know, luggage.
Luggage.
Guys, this has never, shut up.
This has never been a briefcase story this entire time.
It is a suitcase story.
Even the title of the story has always been wrong.
Wow.
It's a suitcase full of money.
It is a suitcase.
Now I did some double checking on this as well.
And okay, to me does make briefcases.
This is a high end bag.
And you know what?
This actually adds to the generosity of Clooney
that in addition, people are getting these nice bags.
So I was like, let me give some benefit of the doubt.
They do make briefcases.
That is true.
However, several times, Gerber keeps talking
and he quotes George in that moment and he says,
so I want you all to open your suitcases.
And also an important part of the story
that hasn't been discussed yet either.
The denominations.
The million dollars was given out in 20s.
This is from Gerber himself.
20 dollar bills, not 100 dollar bills.
Did we say hundreds?
I don't think this has ever come up.
I don't think this is, this is not a correction.
I mean, that's the most considerate denomination
I feel like.
20s or 100s?
20s, they're convenient.
You can use them kind of anywhere.
Well, they're convenient.
You're right in one way that like then you've,
yeah, they don't have to get checked like a hundred.
But then it's, it is odd that now people have to carry out
of this affair what I've now determined
are quite sizable bags.
Well, you gotta fill the bag.
If you use hundreds bags,
it's not gonna be filled all the way.
It's not gonna make a good presentation.
This makes a lot of sense because it reminds me now
of the bags they carry out in Ocean's Eleven
when they're looting the vault.
So there's the big like black sort of like duffel bag
kind of things.
So maybe he got the idea from his own film.
So it's possible he got the same bag.
I don't know if they're Loomy bags in Ocean's Eleven.
To me.
Loomy.
Let's fix those future corrections.
Meldman, to me.
Meldman and to me.
You don't even have to, you're like me.
You're more of a travel pro man.
You're not paying the extra for it.
What's travel pro?
Oh, travel pro is a great luggage company
that a lot of flight attendants use,
but they're very good warranties.
And they hold up.
They take a real
Do you have some?
I got a few, yeah.
Wow, okay.
That's who makes the actual luggage you're saying?
Yeah, it's a very simple flight attendant
pulling a roller bag or a duffel bag.
It's got a little Eiffel Tower on it.
That's a travel pro.
Okay.
Wow.
When you give the money to Jason in the future,
put it in a travel pro.
Put it on travel pro and make sure to register the warranty
or I'll do it.
I think you can register the warranty, can't you?
Oh, I just forget.
Taxes?
Did you?
And one more thing, did you register the warranty?
You do the taxes, I'll do the warranty.
Here's what I
In order to make sure that I knew for sure
that these were not to me, briefcases,
which they did make, I did some math.
The money came in 20s.
Now we know that, which does add
to the impressiveness of the display.
That's a lot.
A $20 bill weighs one gram.
A $1 million divided by 20 is 50,000.
So that's how many bills we're dealing with here.
Each at one gram, so that's 50,000 grams.
You convert that to pounds,
we're dealing with 110 pounds worth of cash.
Wow, yeah.
So this is massive.
No briefcase in the world is gonna be able to hold
110 pounds worth of cash.
Thus, this is a suitcase story.
It's a giant suitcase,
or is it a regular suitcase, do we think?
Well, I mean, I don't think there's anything regular
about Toomey.
I think that's a pretty sturdy suitcase.
High quality, the highest you're gonna find on the market.
I live in travel pro.
where it's like, well, now you gotta carry it out of here,
my guys.
Because of 100 pounds?
100 pounds, yeah.
Yeah, now they've got some-
That's got wheels, doesn't it?
This is what I'm thinking.
I don't know the type of bag.
This is against something else that we can look into.
I can only imagine that these are rolling suitcases,
and they had to be in order to make it comfortable
for everyone involved.
Even getting them off the table would be hard.
I mean, like, Randy can carry this.
He can carry it, obviously he's a good shape guy.
Yeah, he's jay.
You seen him on that bike?
Yeah.
He's jacked, and he can, he's, you know.
But everybody else-
We don't know what Waldo Sanchez looks like.
We don't know what he can bench.
Did Richard Kind have trouble?
Did he struggle with the 100?
I don't know, because it seemed to be awkward,
like size and weight, I don't know.
Yeah, possibly.
I don't wanna put it down, maybe he was fine.
I don't know.
Maybe he did it okay.
You've brought up another thing,
and I'm sorry I've downplayed it,
because I had an order in my head
for how to do these things.
Another thing, in all this time,
and I don't know if this came up in the 2020 episode,
the whole time Richard Kind was one of them?
This has been a, I certainly did not know this one.
Did you, Mike?
I assumed, I was assuming it,
because I know about all the good times
they had back in the old days,
when they were struggling actors.
And Richard Kind was with Clooney,
I believe, at the Sphere, recently.
So like, they're still buddies.
Okay.
So I think I was just assuming it,
but I don't know that we've ever said it out loud.
It doesn't feel familiar to me.
Yeah.
And this is another thing that I'm hung up on,
because in the effort to make this story interesting,
that's been the main premise.
You're saying that would have been a big thing.
George Clooney gave a million dollars in a suitcase
to Richard Kind, and 13 other people?
Oh, I'm interested.
Richard Kind is a beloved character actor, you're right.
I don't know, it would be interesting to see
if we had ever brought that part of it up.
But maybe, yeah, maybe, I don't think,
how many times have I told the story on this?
Do we know how many times I've told it,
versus how many times Jason's told it?
I don't know, I think it's, I mean, in the live show,
it was kind of like a, it was a double up.
You kind of tag teamed it.
Right, right.
That's sort of always how it's been, I'd say.
I would love to hear if the story changed at all
from story one to Orlando.
Did we add anything fake to it
in the same way that a game of Telephone?
You think this could be like a Mighty Akron sort of thing?
Well, Mighty Akron is just a way to describe
a beautiful creature that I came up with, I created.
That's true, but now it's in the lexicon.
This is more of just what you were talking about,
Joie de Vivre or something of a podcast
where something changes over the course.
The je ne sais quoi, maybe that's the term, je ne sais quoi.
Something special, I believe, is the je ne sais quoi.
Joy of living, you know.
I still, I think what you're trying to say
is that the podcast has a certain Moulin Rouge, if you will.
And stuff gets fanciful when you're talking on microphones.
You say things, you go on flights of fancy
and you maybe exaggerate or you misremember
and then all of a sudden a big black suitcase
made by Toomey is no longer that.
It's morphed now into a briefcase full of $100 bills.
And Richard Kind is nowhere to be found.
This I think has been the biggest thing neglected
the entire, I now, I think I care less about the inaccuracies
and more about the absence of Richard Kind
Right, which was entire time.
What a funny person for it to be.
I don't, now I'm not like you, I'm not looking at
who's in the sphere crowd every night.
Yeah.
I don't know that they're friends.
I don't think I knew that at all.
You didn't know they were friends at all.
I did not know they were friends at all.
Oh, yeah, they were like apartment,
like they lived together, I believe.
They lived together as well.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to double check that now
They made a TV pilot together.
But yeah, when he talks about the whole thing
with the story is like the people who let me crash
on their floor, that's Richard Kind
is absolutely one of them.
Right.
And I think it's also weird because this is a guy
with so many connection points to us, to the podcast.
He's Bing Bong.
Yeah.
He's Bing Bong who's in hell now,
something that's been said many times.
He's the host of the California Adventure Opening Special
with Barry Bostwick.
Are you gonna tell us that Bing Bong isn't in hell?
Is that what something you've learned?
Point number four.
No, he's in heaven.
I've got, here is surveillance footage from heaven.
No.
And also you kind of forget this one.
This is Clifford's dad.
Yeah.
Clifford's dad is one of the,
this is like a tie together of things from the show
that's crazy to me.
Clifford's dad got one of the suitcases of a million dollars.
I've heard, okay, I'm looking at some Clooney Kind stuff
and I do remember this story.
Clooney reveals that he once pranked close friend,
Richard Kind by defecating in his pet cat's litter tray.
Jesus.
So Clooney took a big shit in Richard Kind's
cat's litter box.
I feel like I regard that less as a prank
and more as just a aggressive act.
Very foul thing to do.
Aggressive act of meanness, I don't know.
Look, don't do that at my litter box
just because I did all this today
and I promise I won't shit anywhere you don't want either.
I just texted Jason.
I said warm up, Jason.
We have payback on our minds.
Then we start some episode that's about like,
here's the ride, it's the world according
to goofy parade episode.
Scott, actually maybe go check your litter box.
Oh God, it's clearly your shit and not a cat's.
I think it's different.
Jason, Mike.
Here's what I'm thinking off the top of my head.
We fool you into thinking we're doing
Pirates of the Caribbean week.
And each episode starts with one of us taking a big shit
in one of your cat's like areas, litter boxes.
And you get fooled each time.
You think, all right, well, we're really doing,
we're starting Pirates week now.
And then, oh, no, Jason shit in the box again.
I sit in the box.
But we're gonna continue our exploration
of Richard Kine's career.
Is that a, yeah, yeah, that seems like a likely thing
that we do with this, especially now.
Yeah, it's the surprise shit.
And then it's like, well, while you're here,
can I tell you about the errors of Kine?
It's kind week.
We are still recording, right?
I fucking have to check on that too.
I think we are, no, we are recording, yes.
Oh, I don't know what to think now.
Now that you've got Clooney's prankster brain going.
I know.
I feel the spirit of Clooney.
But here's another thing I'm gonna bring up.
I'm still not done.
I could not believe how far this rabbit hole went for me.
Because still the spirit, I will say this,
the spirit of the story remains, thus far.
Thus far, we're still in the zone.
I think I can't argue with you on the spirit thing.
And also we're getting clearly further and further away
from my initial premise that the story
is not interesting enough.
Let me go back to this though.
I think some of my confusion the first time it was told
was that it was tangled up with Casamigos.
Because I first thought that what it was
was they sold the company and then all the investors
in the company got a million dollars.
And I was like, I don't care about that.
That sucks.
We didn't say that.
Jason didn't say that, I don't think.
That might be my own thing I was applying to it,
much so than another game of telephone type thing.
You have to know the reason he knows this story
is because of the fantasy.
That's what he was holding on to.
The friend aspect was important.
So I do not believe this man would say
investors versus friend.
I don't believe it.
Yeah, investors get paid through the proper channels.
That would have gone in one ear off the other
if it was investors.
That's why he might have been mad at it.
These fat cats, fuck them, they have enough money.
Oh, a friend got a million dollars, eh?
Guy you met in improv 2009, that would be sticking.
Anyway, that's my own thing that I was adding to.
But I haven't tangled up in that the whole time.
And then Randy Gerber got a million dollars.
Yeah, they sold the company.
This has been, I get it.
I do understand what's interesting about friends
getting a million dollars out of nowhere.
And obviously I wouldn't talk about any of this
if it wasn't.
That part was in there, but you're right.
You have made it, really highlighting,
underlining Richard Kind makes the story better.
You're right about that for sure.
It's like a massive detail has been gone.
It is interesting that it's not a briefcase
because the briefcase seems like movie style.
It does seem a little bit impractical
because obviously it wouldn't fit the bills.
I have an image, you understand that.
We've all seen something where a briefcase opens
and there's a ton of money.
It's pretty unfamiliar imagery
to think of a high-end rolling suitcase.
You're right, being put onto a table.
Everybody had to go lift them.
There was a heist involved in this, by the way,
also in further details that came out
in a GQ interview with Clooney in 2020.
To do this, he still had to keep it secret from his friends,
so it was a heist situation.
So he rented a van that said florist on it.
Like the way FBI guys would hide
if they were monitoring somebody.
Yeah, again, I have to admit,
we're getting the interesting here.
And he had to go find a weird,
he had the question, where do I get $14 million
in $20 bills?
And he just said, I found a place.
And he had to go there with security guards
who he says were shitting themselves
and they all had to handle this covert operation.
It was supposed to look like they were stealing money.
Were they shitting themselves in Richard Kynes litter box?
for a good reason, for a good prank.
Hollywood liberals are pushing for litter boxes
in classrooms with Richard Kynes on the box?
It sounds like a Grand Theft Auto mission
with George Clooney.
I mean, that is a part that makes, yeah.
I mean, obviously, like even in the briefcase scenario,
there had to be some sort of weird,
like Brinks truck style situation,
even if the bills were higher, higher denomination.
Maybe less, it is like that switch from 20,
from hundreds to 20s grows the proportion of the money
by five times.
How much bigger of an operation it becomes.
That is so impractical too.
That feels to me like he really wanted to make a statement
about the bills, like he wanted to make a big show of it
more so than what hundreds would have been.
Well, he's a showman.
He has that je ne sais quoi.
He has that.
He has that je ne sais quoi
that we talk about on this show a lot.
I wanna know now, yeah, what the gravity payday was.
Because I think both him and Sandra Bullock
both made like some insane amount of money
because Gravity was a massive hit.
I didn't know it was such a big hit.
Yeah, that's a pretty huge movie.
And the kind of movie you had to see before,
well, it was after one Avatar, but before another,
but like that's, you wanted to see that
in the highest quality.
So you're paying a lot of money to see it maybe.
See, I didn't, I never hunted it down on DVD
or whatever it was to be.
We're like, oh, you can't see it in theaters, don't bother.
Oh, so you never saw it.
I never saw it.
Oh, so that's what the, that's the problem.
Jace never saw Gravity, so he wasn't even thinking about it.
Oh, I would have come in and out of that thing going,
what a moving picture.
And imagine the payday.
That's what I'm saying.
You would have said, this is a dynamite picture.
And you would have, then you would have been reading
the trades and you would have been tracking it
and you would have remembered, oh,
look how much money they made.
Cause they made, they had like a better deal
than like Nicholson had on Batman, which was a very like.
It was better than that?
Which is like the, that was like a Guinness Book of World
records situation.
Yeah, don't quote me that that was better.
But Nicholson made a lot of money on Batman
cause he took points.
Right, right.
He may be like, I don't know if he invented it,
but he was a very early person to do that.
They were giving, or Brando, Brando turned down points
on something, I feel like.
They offered him points on either Godfather
or Superman or something.
Hmm, hmm.
And then he, he, he, he took the money
cause he was broke, I believe.
And then he didn't get any of the big payday.
Oh, Brando, oh bummer.
But yeah, Jason would have come out of Gravity like, wow,
what a film.
I hope this thing does bang up,
bap off of a box office.
Bap off of a box office.
Boy, I'll tell you, if this guy doesn't end up
with 14 million dollars that he can give to his friends
for no reason, then this industry is broken.
Wow, yeah.
Okay, so now that we've started to identify
who these people, one is the guy,
I think the name is Grant Heslov, his producing partner.
One is Richard Kind.
There's, there's quite, one is Randy Gerber, obviously.
There's a question as to who the rest of the 14 are.
And there's articles that are confident about this,
but I don't know if I really trust them.
And part of it is because I'm so freaked out by
one of the people that I'm looking at in this photo.
I'm gonna hand this to you, Mike.
Do you see anybody who is familiar to you?
And keeping, now we're in the territory,
again, in getting me into this story,
now we're in the territory of people I like.
So, so.
My God, it's the Boston Strangler.
Well, the first.
Yeah, my hero.
The BTK killer behind him.
First of all, one of the guys looks like Jeffrey Epstein.
Possibly.
Yeah, that's again, my hero, all the guys I like.
I'm not saying that was one of the guys you like.
I'm just saying the first guy I look at looks exactly like
maybe like a 10 years older Jeffrey Epstein.
He needs that money for plain fuel.
Yeah, so it's not, I don't believe it's him,
but he really looks like him.
Okay, but I know what you're,
I know exactly my eyes go right to the man.
He doesn't have as big a hair as I'm normally used to.
Well, you had to tone it down for a wedding.
This is a photo from Clooney's wedding,
but you know who I'm talking about?
You're talking about Steve Lukather.
Steve Lukather.
Steve Lukather from.
Also, this whole time, potentially,
one of the brief suitcase owners.
I gotta get my mic up for Stanford.
Is one of the musicians I love the most.
Yeah.
Talk about the most.
I've weirdly named him for no reason
other than that it makes me happy to talk about him.
Steve Lukather, founding member of Toto.
He played every, he's a member of Ringo's All-Star Band.
Which we saw together.
Yeah.
He is, among many things,
the guitar solo on Olivia Newton-John's physical.
He plays every lick of guitar on Beat It
besides the Eddie Van Halen solo.
This is a legend, played on a hundred things,
everybody knows.
I'm specifically a big fan of this guy,
and I'm looking at this photo like, he's one of those.
So that's for, you think that's for sure the 14?
I don't know.
I think it is speculation on the part of several media outlets
that this photo is the 14.
It contains some of the 14.
Interesting.
But I don't- Ocean's 14.
That's what they're talking about doing too
is another sequel.
Well it should be one of these people
because you've got-
It's Lukather.
You've already, okay, you got Lukather,
he can bust some guitar solos in it.
You've got Richard Kind, who of course is gonna deliver.
You've got the most charismatic man on the planet,
Randy Gerber.
Yeah.
Just the sex personified guy.
A guy.
Take a seat George, you're not gonna do
I don't wanna be in the frame with him.
I'm never, he's my best friend,
but I don't ever wanna be in the frame with him.
It's George's day, I'm gonna step away, you know?
I'll just break the cameras with my shine.
Here's what I, it then occurred to me that like,
I did know some connection between Lukather and Clooney
because I've read this man's book,
The Gospel According to Luke,
my Bible, the Bible to me.
And he tells a story in that book,
this is where I question like, is this one of his boys
or did they just know each other and he was at the wedding?
Because this isn't gonna make you think
this is one of his boys.
A story that he tells is that they were at some other
wedding together in the 80s and Lukather is pretty drunk,
he's pretty fucked up.
Sure.
And he has hit it off with a model at the wedding,
somebody who is, he says is one of the models or dancers
in the Van Halen Hot for Teacher video.
And they wanna get, they're like,
let's get home and get down to business, let's go do stuff.
And they're like, but we can't, we're too drunk to drive.
George, would you mind?
And a sober Clooney drove them home from this wedding,
but they were so like aggressively horny
that they just started having sex in the back
of Clooney's car and he had to drown it out
by blasting the one tape or CD he had,
which was his own aunt, Rosemary Clooney.
So he's blasting his aunt's crooning.
This story happened to Jason, I too.
Wonderful performers.
Yeah, Jason was talking, it was 2009,
somebody was in like the Killers,
It was the Killers music video.
Are We Human or Are We Dancer video.
Jason was talking to this model from the video
and they were so drunk, we were at a wedding
and then I drove the two of them home
and they started doing it.
And you played the CD that your aunt made.
Yeah, my aunt, Rosemary Carlson.
Yeah.
Oh Michael, you're my favorite nephew.
Jason's boning in this back seat again.
Tell me what Brandon Flowers was like, baby.
Jason, oh, I turn it up more.
Oh God, Jason.
Mike, you know that's my king, Brandon Flowers' anecdotes.
Okay, so you're gonna have to deal.
Wow, Luke, so that obviously suggests
that's where they met, right?
Or maybe familiar with each other before
and that's where they bonded, is that what that's saying?
Another thing that really gave was a eureka moment for me
because also having read this book,
I realized that I do know someone else in the picture
and it makes sense why Lukather is tied to all this.
Jeffrey Epps because he was a frequent,
no, never, my awesome guitar virtuoso.
Hopefully the names aren't coming out
in the next few weeks when we release this.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, God.
Oh no.
How many of the men are named?
All 14.
Yeah.
No, Lukather was really tight friends
with somebody else in this photo, the actor Miguel Ferrer.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, I know him.
That's the guy all the way on the right
and it's a big part of the book.
He's emotionally destroyed when Miguel Ferrer passes away.
So, and I think that was the connection point.
So I remembered that, oh, that makes sense.
And then I was like, okay, so now we have one more
of the 14, the people really do think
that Miguel is one of the 14
and I'm gonna bring it all the way full circle here.
I was trying to think, what do we know Miguel Ferrer?
Do you offhand know, what is he in?
Because of course you've seen him in things.
Yeah, I know him, but I don't.
I can't think off the top of my head.
I was like, what is he in?
I had to think of something.
He is in the movie Blank Check.
Again, now we've expanded this story
to where it involves Blank Check and Clifford.
It's really all coming together.
But then I was like, oh yeah, so wait,
what was he in Blank Check?
And I looked it up and in this movie,
Miguel Ferrer is a criminal who is trying
to pull a money laundering scheme.
This is when he gets into a bike accident with a boy
who ends up with a blank check.
But what's initially occurring is that Miguel
is trying to pull something with a bank.
He's threatening a bank guy
and what he's trying to do basically is cleanly launder
something that he is in possession of.
A million dollars.
A briefcase with a million dollars.
Well, well, well, history doesn't repeat itself
at some times and rhymes.
When you discovered this, was it like 3 a.
m.
Scott
and you were just like put it all together
with the big board?
It was 3 a.
m.
five days ago.
I haven't slept since.
Look, this episode is your masterpiece.
I'm not being facetious about that either.
Hey, well, thank you for saying something so kind
after I've come in with the sprays and attack.
I felt like it didn't quite have an ending.
I was like, maybe we're gonna end up having to answer
one of these questions.
I almost told you guys like,
hey, I got a couple of appointments today.
I'll set it out.
You guys just do post office without me.
We just would have.
That would have been good at all.
And I imagine you would have just answered
some of the questions.
Maybe we wouldn't have recorded.
Or just not recorded.
I refuse to do this without Jason present.
You must be here.
And for the full, for the usual suspects
tying it all together, wait a minute.
And Miguel Ferrer had a briefcase with a million dollars.
And then that made me think, wait a minute,
how did the money fit in the briefcase?
I checked the movie.
It's in the first five minutes.
It's in hundreds.
I mean, they wouldn't do something inaccurate.
There's no, like they, I'm sure they thought about hundreds
being able to fit in the briefcase.
The movie wouldn't be inaccurate.
The movie took so much longer to make back then too.
So they had that Dr.
T's dress.
Well, you shoot on film,
just automatically getting it developed.
That's gonna be longer than it took.
More laborious.
Yeah, yeah.
Social media, gotta have that marketing campaign.
As you know, Kevin Smith was like kind of editing
Clerks 2 sort of like on the avid as they shot.
I remember reading about it.
So yeah, that probably, that didn't happen till later.
2000s, yeah.
Yeah, 2000s, yeah.
Huh, huh.
So that really, which is what really like cracked it all
open, why Clerks 2 was able to achieve the quality that.
People didn't believe in editing as you go
until Clerks 2 came out.
And then it broke it wide open.
So, Shoenmaker was like, how did you do it?
Hey, George, you wanna have a seat?
Let me show you what I'm, oh yeah, sure.
Oh God, oh, I didn't know the possibilities of digital
until this moment.
So there you go.
We've come full circle on this.
I had a feeling that there would be a full hour in all of this.
But again, I come back to the, you know, we can hem and haw
about these details, but I go back to the first, the fateful day
that the story was first attempted to be told.
And what was in Jason's mind other than here's something interesting.
And after all this, I have to admit that there is plenty interesting
surrounding the George Clooney suitcase story.
So what you have now done, now you've delivered a very entertaining
podcast episode.
Again, I'll say that.
Well, not for anyone who wants to hear about theme parks.
Well, that, but the people who are paying us, there's something wrong with them.
And I mean that in the best way.
But what you've done now is you've turned now what's a fun bit once in a while
that could maybe be done in three minutes into like seven minutes.
As far as when the story has to be repeated.
So the next time that Griffin pimps us out in front of an audience
Yeah.
And a theme park luminary.
Now that's going to eat up seven minutes of the show.
Yes, exactly.
And then I'm in there and then Steve, look at there was one of that.
And then just like he's like we lost him minute one.
You're going to have like you're going to have like 90 seconds
on just the guitar pedals that he used when he was doing Beat It or Africa
or something.
He just sat down.
They did.
They didn't transcribe a part for him when he had to do.
I keep forgetting.
He thought of that part.
That's that was all in.
It was all Luke.
There'll be a couple of shots at Weezer in that story.
Now that's built in.
There's so much added to the story now because of this episode,
which only builds out the Joua de Vivre of podcast, the riot
and the mythology we've created here.
I think so.
And you know what?
And and and look, I mean, I've played the part of somebody who's mad about the story,
but I've ended up getting a lot of joy out of the things that I've
discovered from the story is hell being in there.
That's so fun that you don't think about a rock, a real rock and roll.
He's one of the listeners.
If you've never seen him, he's like up until he doesn't dye his hair anymore,
but he was like jet black way too late and like big old hair,
a kind that no one his age should be doing.
If you think he means well, you know, he's trying to keep the spirit alive.
You know, caught him briefly, you would say is that Adam Durwitz,
from counting crows, definitely because they both have similar
they both have similar looks and they both have the big hair.
And Adam, I know, cut the big dreads for a while, but I think he's grown them back.
From what I know, one recognizes me if I don't have been doing.
I don't know if I said this before, he's been doing a Taylor Swift song
and concert that keeps popping up on YouTube and I'll click it and watch it every time.
Wow.
And I can't remember the name of it.
I'm scared, though, now that now that you're getting like
Adam Durwitz seems like a perfect candidate to have some story
that's told a million times.
And then I'm then four years later, I'm saying, but the story wasn't right.
Mike's saying, but the spirit of the Durwitz story.
I've read a fact recently that he dated two of the Friends cast members.
Jay, of course he did.
This man was it was Aniston and Cox, I believe.
No, no Kudrow, though.
We are guys.
Are you sure about that?
I would bet a million fucking dollars
that Adam Durwitz did it.
What are you putting that million in, my brother?
You're going to go with the two me.
They're going to.
Well, they're going to be.
I mean, you know, I'm going to put them in a little like shoebox
and it's going to be a thousand dollar bills.
Oh, I also looked up that I don't think a thousand dollar bills exist anymore.
That was in my head, too.
Yeah.
Oh, is that what it's going to end up?
Five hundred dollars bills, though, exist probably.
I don't know.
Well, if you go to one of those secret currency places
that Clooney went to, they might still have some older current.
The only secret place.
Yeah.
Or it would be funny to give everyone like 20s or hundreds,
but kind gets two dollar bills.
Sorry, Richard.
There's a there's a Hyundai Elantra parked outside for you to drive the money.
Another classic Clooney prank.
Yeah.
Perfect.
Well, there you have it.
Graham Southwood, I have to really thank you for inspiring
an entire episode here and for I mean, look, Graham ended up like really
not by any attempt.
It is he really cut the line in front of all of the listeners who asked
other questions, but we will.
But I think he earned it.
I feel like incredible sleuthing, you know.
But again, I do.
I also say to Graham, even your subject line major error in Clooney briefcase story.
Yeah, was an error in that, too, which is that it's a Clooney suitcase story.
So even he, the correct order, even the correct even the great Graham Southwood.
Graham, you were wrong, too, brother.
Watch your back.
Do you have a cat?
Do you have a litter box in your apartment or house?
Because I'm sending a guy over there.
OK, you better protect that litter box or else this human man is going to take a big old shit.
You're getting pranked.
The ultimate prank, a human shit somewhere.
It should never know whether the guy is going to be me or beloved actor Richard.
Richard, you probably want to get revenge on
somebody with whose name starts with G.
Right.
Well, we've got an opportunity for you.
Clooney should have shit in the suitcase.
And Richard opened it and it was a big shit in there.
Richard, you open yours last.
OK, can do whatever you need.
George, I'm just excited to be.
This is an exciting.
Wow.
September, September 27th, 2013.
I think I'll never forget this night.
All right.
Well, you survived podcast the right really, especially Mike and Jason
survived a real rush of a podcast, the ride, the second gate.
I promise that we will actually answer listener questions soon.
The PTR post office will get to it.
We'll get to it.
You know what you should do?
Screen grabs somewhere.
You should thank thank the listeners for being part of the con.
Uh huh.
You know, you're right.
Yes.
So they were in it with I went out with you and you were in it just like Mr.
Ocean.
What's his name?
Danny Ocean.
He's coming back.
Yeah.
Imagine yourselves with Scott standing in front of the Bellagio
fountains and walking away.
Carl Reiner, Carl Reiner, Steve Lukather, the whole gang.
El Ferrer, Richard Kind.
Hey, if you want to dig even deeper, pick the episodes yourselves.
You can upgrade to our VIP tier club three.
You also get the main feed episodes ad free.
Keep it tuned here to the Patreon for that.
And let me definitely plug podcast the ride at Gmail dot com where your long form
world expanding questions and corrections are always welcome.