Forever.
hats not worn on heads, and a massive breakthrough in theme park wallet and hat storing technology.
All that plus Stephen Ray Morris returns to talk Velocicoaster on today's podcast, The
Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride with your hosts who are so preoccupied with whether or not
they could start a theme park podcast they didn't stop to think if they should start
a theme park podcast.
I'm Scott Gardner, gold blooming it a little bit, joined by Mike Carlson.
Yes, hello, I'm here and we did not consider the implication, we did not consider what would
happen if we did it.
We didn't earn this knowledge, we took it from yesterland and from Jim Hill and now we're
selling it, we're selling it.
Jason Sheridan.
I'm placing a water droplet on Jason Sheridan's hand right now to show him, to illustrate
what happened kind of in a non-verbal way.
I forgot for a second that moment in the movie and I was like do I have a water droplet
on my hand?
How did I do that?
And why is Mike honing in on it?
It's the sexiest part of the movie I think, other than the shirtless gold bloom.
Oh wait that's a little flirty thing.
It's what he does in real life, it's all hands.
See how he does this thing with you and with your hands.
The gold bloom sexuality.
Yeah, hey we're doing some Jurassic Park stuff today, Jurassic World really, excited to
be doing it.
Mainly we are back on main feed, apologies for the long break but it was nice to get
some time off there.
Of course there were new episodes that entire time on the Patreon so if you want to hear
everything that you missed, if you didn't hear all that, you can catch up at the second
gate and club 3, all of that at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
But here we are back for free and good to see you again and it seems like a good way
to kick off the year to continue our series of big new rides from this decade, from this
century.
Blockbuster, two year old attraction, two year old ride.
Yeah yeah.
I know it feels so new.
I thought it was sooner but it was yeah.
It's been there for a little bit because it kind of popped up you know when pandemic was
still kind of cooking.
But yeah, big rides that now we've experienced, some of us will get into that.
But very excited to be doing it with a fan of the franchise and a returning guest and
a great supporter of the show.
It's so good to see you again from the podcast, from his podcast, See Jurassic Right, it's
Stephen Ray Morris.
Thank you, thank you.
I have the spirit of Jimmy with me today, rest in peace.
Oh yeah, wait, describe your shirt because this ties together.
You know what, you called a shot a while back and I filed it away and it was like well if
you want to do Velocicoaster or Jimmy Buffett's books.
Yes, oh my god.
And I was like well we got a lot, there's a lot of Buffett in the air right now, we
just did one on club 3.
We'll deal with it all across that bridge when we get to it.
But the shirt is.
So yeah, it's basically, it says Jimmy Buffett in this kind of classic font, like the yellow
greatest hits cover and then there's the T-Rex and it's Jimmy Buff throwing the peace
sign surrounded by dinosaurs and yeah I don't know, and then it says live from Jurassic
Park so.
I wish I knew who actually did it but a friend gave it to me for Christmas but I'm sure if
you look online you'll find it.
Sell it as official merch.
Because look, I think it's probably not official Jimmy Buffett license which I'm not offended
by.
Look dude, I think you should have sent five bucks to a Buffett estate, yes, just because
to make it fair.
I will, I will.
Yes, I think they should officially license that shirt.
It's not official because he's not holding two margaritavilles in peril, or two margaritas
in peril.
Well yeah, of course.
It's not advertising enough for the other parts of the brand.
That's right.
That's really what I, again, care about as far as.
That was the funniest thing to me about, because obviously in Jurassic World there's the margaritaville
at the park where you're like this is great, this is like perfectly like in the world of
a real theme park kind of thing.
Exactly what it would be.
It's my favorite thing about those movies that there's a Brookstone and a margaritaville
and an IMAX theater.
It's that detail.
And then in the Fallen Kingdom, the second Jurassic World movie, they literally have
a shot just of the like destroyed margaritaville sign like on the main street when they go
back to the island where they're like, where Frank is just like Frank, Frank Marshall is
just like.
Of course, yes.
On the show, I think it's the first name basis.
You are not the last Frank Marshall reference today.
But it's just like.
I just love that they just go like, you know, just in case you forgot there was a margaritaville
here at Jurassic World.
It's a big part of the new ones and he's in them.
I feel like canonically, you know, like in real life, Jimmy Buffett was Frank Marshall's
best friend.
But I feel like in the world of the Jurassic film, I feel like narratively, maybe he was
best friends with Dr.
Hammond.
Oh yeah.
Oh, interesting.
I like the idea.
We go way back.
We're kind of we're both pioneers.
I fired Trap Rock and he pioneered mosquito getting that mosquito goo out.
Yeah, he had crazy idea for a dinosaur park and I thought, hey, maybe let's put poke on
some nachos.
Same deal.
Two innovators.
But see, then this guy was telling me that I didn't stop to I'm so concerned whether
I could.
I didn't start to think I should.
That guy talked too much.
I gave him a margarita, said relax and he passed out real quick.
Hammond dinosaurs went crazy, started eating people and the poke nachos made a bunch of
people sick.
Both incidents and accidents.
Hey, the lawyer got eaten and no one was sad about that.
Am I right, folks?
Oh, man.
Yeah, you're right.
Jimmy would be like, get the lawyer.
I told him if there's a problem there, just run to the nearest thatch bathroom.
It'll hold up.
Get straight there.
Well, yeah, I mean, so excited to get your perspective on this ride.
Having a podcast all about the Jurassic Park and Jurassic World.
And you, I know that you're a fan of the ride as well.
Seems like you did it a while back.
What were the circumstances of experiencing Velocicoaster?
Well, it's funny because the first, the only time I'd ever been to Orlando was when I was
like it was the year Lion King came out.
Because I just remember because there was tons of pictures of my sister and I just like
covered in Lion King merch.
And at that point, the Jurassic Park ride hadn't, the second park, the adventure one
hadn't been built.
Islands of Adventure.
Thank you, Jason.
It's on his sweater right now.
It's on my sweater.
It's the heaviest, chunkiest sweater I have and it's cold out.
It's a great sweater.
Putting on my chunky islands.
And I think it was that when the Velocicoaster opened, I think that was kind of like an incentive
to want to, you know, especially like I went in August of 2021.
So the ride had only been open for a couple of months and things had only been like part
because Universal here in LA had opened on my birthday in 2021.
So that was like a fun treat to get to go back to.
You did that on your birthday?
Yeah, I did that on my birthday.
Yeah, that weekend.
It was so much fun.
But then I had a friend who, you know, it was like one of those, his dad worked for
the parks or whatever.
It was kind of just like, hey, if you want to come out for a weekend and you can ride,
you know, like again, first time back to Orlando.
And you know, since I was a kid.
So long, oh my God.
Yeah.
And it was, you know, it's one of those things where I'm like, now that my dad lives in Florida,
like anytime I go visit him, I'm like, do you want to go up to Orlando?
Go to like Disney World or Magic Kingdom?
Because like Magic Kingdom didn't exist when I went there the first time.
But yeah, the Velocicoaster was just like, we have to go.
You mean Animal Kingdom, that's a correct answer.
Or Animal Kingdom.
No, no.
If anybody was thinking.
No, no, the listeners are going to appreciate that.
But yeah, it was one of those things where it was like, we're basically there.
I mean, because I've written a lot of the other, you know, well, I guess I hadn't written
the Jurassic Park ride there either.
So it was like, kind of just like, we're there for two days.
We're just going to hit up all this stuff.
We did Margaritaville at City Walk Saturday night.
And then Sunday, we went immediately to Velocicoaster, like first thing, because I just,
I felt like at the time, the lines were just so insane.
So it was like, this is the priority.
And then very just very luckily, we because of my friend's dad or whatever, like we got
to go ride the ride twice in a row.
Oh, wow.
Like we still had to get off.
It was one of those kind of things.
But sure.
But it was one of those.
I just feel very lucky that I got to do that, like in that way, because I think it's the
greatest roller coaster of all time.
Wow.
Yeah.
I mean, we'll get in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You guys are the ones to say.
But if you want to plant that flag, do you agree with that statement?
Is it a viable candidate?
Is that the only reason I would say it's just because I haven't been on like big stuff like
I haven't gone on Tatsu.
I haven't been brave enough to do stuff like that at Six Flags.
So I can't point, you know, anything.
Yeah, I can't say definitively.
But as far as like anything I've been on now, I posed the question is Guardians better than
Velocicoaster's Velocicoaster better than Guardians.
But I think purely from the like again, I think I said this like purely from the experience
my body is having, the way I'm handled, as I said on the Guardians episode, I think,
yeah, it's the best coaster I've ever been on.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
As far as like thrills, you know, because I like, you know, Transformers and, you know,
Rise of the Resistance and the Hagrid one, like those are all innovative in all these
different cool ways.
But like just as like a regular roller coaster, I feel like it's my favorite at least.
Yeah.
And it seems like there's I bet there are rides with that put up the stats more like
the amount of inversions, the speed, the height, whatever.
I'm sure Velocicoaster is topped in those in technical regards.
But I bet on in coasters that aren't as well kept up, that aren't as high tech, that don't
have the like kind of the like narrative build, it seems like.
Because it feels like this thing, it's not one of those roller coasters where like the
big thing it does is at the top and then the rest is kind of like a wind around and it's
all fun.
But you kind of like did the big thing.
Like this thing has like beginning, middle end.
There's like two big almost magic tricks in this that caught me so off guard.
Yeah.
What are you considering?
The second launch, the launch up the top hat and then the very end barrel roll over the
water.
me what that would be like going over the water upside down.
Well, you were in such a port of entry fog.
It's tough to focus.
I was in the port of entry fog.
Just like because you don't you don't just like grab that Cinnabon and go.
You sit, you take 75 minutes with it, knife and fork it.
Yeah, I got to hear the whole loop when the loop repeats.
And whoever you're with, like the piccolo, hear the piccolo.
Yeah, that's like me when I hear like Eve Six playing in a bar.
Everybody stop everything.
A very rare piece of music is playing right now.
That's like I was there was some karaoke and then they did the Mulan I'll Make a Man
Out of You and like the entire bar just like erupted.
It was like, oh, everyone here is like between the ages of 35 and like 45.
Like we look like I just for the first I just saw some Disney Christmas parade.
I'd never seen where Donny Osmond performs it.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
Seeing the face, putting the face to the voice, Mr.
Isle, the most pronounced nobody's ever pronounced.
I use it so much.
Make a man.
All right.
I want to start singing it.
Go for it.
Take it out of you.
Of the moon.
Those big man.
OK.
What you were saying about that second launch, I didn't realize this.
The second launch isn't as fast as the first launch, but it makes you feel like it is.
Well, yeah.
No, you do go.
It's not as fast on the launch, but you end up going fast.
Sure.
But the launch itself isn't faster than the first launch.
I know what I saw.
Well, because first launches, I saw conflicting things.
Zero to 50 or zero to 55 miles per hour.
Yeah.
Second launch, you go from 40, 70 miles an hour.
To get you down that hill.
It's not going.
It's not zero to that different sensation.
Right.
But I feel like that's why, like, Jason, you're you're so right about that.
Just because it's like I think I'm I think since I've started
getting back into going to theme parks again and stuff, you know,
for I guess for a listener to remind you of like I worked at Disneyland in high school,
you know, so I like.
Right.
But like one of those things where it was I just didn't really like
I didn't look ahead or anything.
And it was that kind of thing.
We were like, I'm going as fast as I've ever or feeling like I've
fast as I've ever gone on a roller coaster.
And then you then the second launch happens and you're just like, oh, my.
Like, there's that feeling like when you're on the ride that you're like,
how is it even possible?
Like they're they're just going to send a shooting off like a old like
roller coaster tycoon like when you're a kid and you just make the most.
Yeah, you just make the roller coaster just go off and then all the,
you know, all the people on the ride just fly off into the park or whatever.
Yeah.
And then they just then somebody nails a sign up.
Some little SIM guy took this ride is not safe.
Yeah.
Let's just let's step back.
Make sure we've said some basics here.
This is a fairly new attraction at Universal's Islands of Adventure
and the Jurassic Park area, obviously open June 10th, 2021.
I think let me read their official literature and say that it is
the apex predator of roller coasters.
We can agree on this statement, can we not?
Yeah, yeah.
That's what I was going to say.
But yeah, this is it is like it is a gigantic,
record breaking, highest of tech, highest of thrills, roller coaster
in which the just the premise it in the world.
It is a roller coaster.
It's not like we're abstractly representing
like the way some things are like it's sure it's on a track,
you're supposed to think that you are on the flight of a dragon or something.
Right.
Or you are a raptor or something.
Yes.
Because I wasn't sure about that, having again, not gone on it myself.
But it is in it is like you're in the world of of Jurassic World.
And they have opened a roller coaster that goes in and out of a velociraptor
paddock to simulate the thrill of the hunt.
Is this a fair summation?
Yes.
And Claire and Owen are having a big argument about it in the pre show.
Just like Frank, first name basis.
Claire and Owen, we know them.
We love our favorite characters from the Jurassic Park movies.
Of course.
Well, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing, let's say they're
a few.
I'm too.
Thank you, Jason.
Jason, you just wasted five seconds that we didn't need
because the audience knows those last names.
We know the Dearing legacy.
We know.
Well, look, you know, there's different age groups, you know, older people.
They think the star of the Jurassic.
It's Alan Grant.
But the younger generation, they know Owen Grady.
That's true.
Yeah.
Well, we know the correct answer,
which is that Alan Grant doesn't fucking matter anymore.
It's about Claire Dearing.
End of story.
Yeah, that's right.
Amen.
Even I know Alan Grant came back in the last one, but I didn't pay attention.
I closed my eyes until Claire was.
I heard about it and I was mad.
So why do they bring these olds back?
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah.
These dinosaurs, these aren't the kind of dinosaurs I want to see.
Exactly.
But yeah, I think another big notable thing about it is that this is,
you know, we've had Jurassic Park, the ride for a long time,
which then opened an island's adventure is Jurassic Park River Adventure.
And there's other like the international parks have versions of that.
But this is the first major
Jurassic Park attraction that is not in the river format.
Right.
It is the first one to open, at least, that breaks us out
and cracks open the entire world of other Jurassic.
I know there was Pteranodon flyers, but I mean like big old, you know.
Right.
Well, there's the there's the one in which one is it overseas?
There's a new Jurassic.
The rapids one.
No, no, no.
It's like in a scoop vehicle.
Yeah, where they chase you.
Beijing.
Yeah, that's where that is.
That is, I think, just called Jurassic World Adventure.
Do you know about this, Steven?
Do you know about this crazy ride?
I think I've watched maybe a video of it once,
but it is hard when you're like looking at theme parks that are so far away
and you're just like, well, I don't know.
I don't like I don't want to get too sad
that I'm probably not going to be able to go any time soon, you know.
Yeah, Beijing is a difficult trip to do for sure.
But like it is it's nuts.
It makes me this is also like it makes me so happy that
we're not just sticking with one Jurassic ride because.
Yeah, you're right.
It's the Spider-Man ride vehicle.
Yeah.
But you see you're in and out of screens, but there are a lot of practical dinosaurs.
There's one big set piece that's pretty crazy.
That's a big robot.
Spoiler alert.
There's a big T-Rex, I think, in Dominus.
In Dominus.
I'm so sorry.
It's in Dominus.
I have an indominus toy in the house now, thanks to the kiddos.
You know more dinosaurs.
I'm more indominus focused at the moment.
So, yeah, but it's like they make it look like it's truly walking toward you.
Well, that's like at Universal here.
It's the at the end of the Jurassic World ride, the redo.
Because I think when it first opened, it was kind of just like sitting in the corner,
just like roaring.
But like now it actually is under a tent of some kind.
Yeah.
OK.
When it opened, it was like, I think, yeah, 2019.
It was just like it was kind of like, ah, and you're like, OK,
it's not anywhere near us.
We're not going to be in danger.
But now it actually like walks up right up to the edge where the
T-Rex swings out because the Dominus is sort of just hanging out.
And then the T-Rex still swoops in.
So they have like a snoot off the snoot's touch.
And then they get one of these animals you refer to as having snoots.
It can't all be snoots.
People are pointing out turtles don't have snoots.
It's not well, they have a beak.
Beaks is it?
Yeah.
Not every animal on the planet has a snoot.
I know you love saying the word, but at some point I got to call you out.
Look, I think it's cute that this endominus is a snoot.
I just think it's a fictional animal, so it could have a good
idea.
It could be a hybrid.
I mean, it's like the like again, from when I went to Disney World as a kid,
my sister got the Simba and Nala that have the magnets in their nose.
We had those.
The plushes.
Really?
I don't know that.
That's cute.
Yeah, we had those.
Yeah.
I wonder if maybe they.
Yeah, probably on eBay or something.
But like, yeah, now they need to make an endominus and the T-Rex
with magnets and their snoot.
Yeah, so they.
Yes, that's good.
They're trying to bash heads.
They're trying to fight.
But once they get close, they realize they're in love.
Enemies to lovers.
Yeah, that's cute.
So, yeah, this thing, that thing in Beijing, though, it's like
I think it's on like a turntable of some kind.
So it must be like you are and it is.
So they're just or you're going.
I don't know how it works, but you're going like kind of backwards
and they're turning it.
So it really makes like the full sized body of the dinosaur
kind of like lumbering toward you.
It's crazy on video.
It's it sells in the video and I'm sure in person it's 200 percent.
Yeah, better to.
It's nuts.
So this all makes me happy that the Jurassic World films have been successful
because it juices up the parks.
We get new stuff in the parks and it feels like they really reinvested
in the franchise theme park wise, which this makes it to me.
This is the epitome of franchise.
I'm iffy about, but who cares?
I want my rides.
Give me rides.
So it's it's it's it's fine.
Steven, where do you land on these with your pocket?
What I imagine you love the first movie very much.
Where do you fall on Jurassic World as opposed to?
Well, yeah, I mean, it's
I was like, I'm invested in liking them to some extent.
But I also think I kind of think Chris Pratt was like
I think he was kind of miscast in the movies a little bit
because I feel like they were kind of, you know, because
Guardians and Jurassic World came out like around the same time
or within like a year of each.
I think Guardians was 2014 and they were like,
oh, well, Chris Pratt is sassy in that movie.
So we kind of have to make him like a dour
Werner Herzog character in the Jurassic World movies, where he's like,
everything is, you know, even even in the ride video for a velocity coaster,
he's like, we're all going to die.
Like, you know, you're a bunch of idiots like that kind of stuff.
He's severe in this.
Yes.
And then they've kind of had to pivot away from that a little bit.
And I mean, you know, I think Jason Clarke,
I think would have been a better fit for the Jurassic World movies.
I think just a little bit weirder, a little more eccentric.
But I mean, you know, I like them because I like seeing dinosaurs, you know,
it's kind of like the thrill of that.
And I did like the last movie a lot, if only just because it reminded me
more of like a Michael Crichton novel where it's like dinosaurs.
Sure, whatever.
But like Locust.
Like, that's where we're that's like the interesting part, right?
And we're like, I guess.
But I'm I'm down for it.
I'm down for more Laura Dern getting to kick ass.
So I'm grateful for the last one, that last one just for that.
But yeah, I mean, you know, they're enjoyable and I like seeing dinosaurs
and stuff.
But yeah, that's how it's like.
You're at least getting, yeah, a bunch of new.
I like you know what I feel like about that first one is like there's so much.
It's like I like so many things about it.
I like the Margaritaville and the Brooks.
I like the mall.
And then I like the the spheres that were the gyrospheres.
What is it called?
Yeah, yeah.
I like those.
And I like Indominus.
And I like the I like that it's like the version that worked.
And then that one goes awry.
And then and then it just doesn't add up into.
Yeah, I like every piece.
And then it doesn't like coalesce into something that super works for me.
But hey, that's I don't know.
There's big movies that don't even have pieces that I like.
So that's something I like.
Jake Johnson, but vintage Jurassic Park merchandise.
That's very relatable to me.
But yeah, I liked him as comic relief.
You know, Jurassic World and Transformers.
It's like, yeah, they might not be my favorite movies.
Great for a ride.
Great for a five to six minute, you know, experience with like
factoring in ride time and queue time.
You know, the only thing I would say is with right in regards to the rides is like,
I don't love the aesthetic of Jurassic World as much as the original.
And I don't think that's nostalgia.
It's a little cold.
Jurassic World is a little cold because they do recreate sort of the like
gray blue aesthetic for Velocicoaster.
Yeah, I kind of I'm surprised that I like it.
And now I think I said on an episode recently, like getting to go on
original Jurassic Park, the ride or river adventure there with its yellows
and reds and kind of 90s primaries.
I liked it, but I also kind of it's more it's more generic.
It feels like other franchises have those colors.
But I think like I think the colors of all these all these new things
and especially Velocicoaster are pretty cool.
I don't know why.
I'm like I'm surprised I'm for getting a little cold.
That's all.
Well, I'm not against it.
I think that's by design.
Yeah, it's almost that thing of like in the 90s, they were like,
what does the San Diego Zoo look like in 1991?
And then we're going to, you know, for 1993.
And then now it's like we're looking at zoos and, you know, because I watched
behind the scenes video for the roller coaster and like they hired a person
who designed like zoo habitats to do all the to do all the stuff.
Yeah, Velocicoaster like the plants and rock work and stuff.
Yeah, that is to like that's the logic of like it is.
If it's a Velociraptor paddock, then we're we need to make it feel
as natural as possible, like build it to them so that they don't feel like they're.
And just even the aesthetic of how we do stuff now where it is that thing.
Like, I feel like you guys talked about before.
It's like with, you know, with the Star Wars line and stuff where it's like
sometimes the devotion to making it logically sound maybe isn't always
the most exciting, you know, because you miss some fun.
Yeah, yeah, because you're like, this is a theme park.
We can kind of do whatever, you know.
And yeah, I think like a big part of the Jurassic World stuff
is making it feel like a real zoo to some extent.
Sure.
But yeah, it's like mileage may vary on how enjoyable this aesthetic is.
You're right, though, that original Jurassic Park feels like San Diego.
Wait, and it was what it was going to open in San Diego and Lost World.
Yeah, yeah.
I like that.
I was going through the T-rex going through the town is so silly,
but pretty fun.
Yeah, I had a Cadillac chase.
Yeah, I love that.
And the downtown Burbank, you know, it's downtown Burbank.
I figured that out.
Yeah.
Like that's the I think it's a lot of things that aren't open,
but like the blockbuster that gets crashed into.
And yeah, every time I'm in look, I'm already happy if I'm in downtown Burbank.
When I realize I sometimes will go like, wow, Lost World.
Yeah, yeah.
You're like you're like a bunch of weird mechanical things
rip down this telephone pole, you know, this big telephone pole.
Uh huh.
Yeah, they they went this street down.
This is probably closed for days.
And the Lost World, I haven't watched Lost World forever.
And I didn't love it when I saw it for the first time.
I only seen it once.
But people were talking about Mission Impossible Seven with the big train
sequence and people like, oh, that's so cool or whatever.
And people like Lost World did that type of thing first,
where the thing was falling off the cliff.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It was not it was a trailer.
It was not a train in the movie.
But there was a very similar scene of like trying to climb up
and get out of it.
Oh, that's me out so much when I saw that at like 12.
The hanging off the cliff.
Yeah.
And Julian Moore, it's like like she's on the glass as it's like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And stuff.
That sound design is so yeah.
So you're either that sticks with you.
Filmed on the Universal Hollywood parking garages.
I always loved that.
Yeah, that was a fun.
That was a good time to be here and go into the
going on the tram tour like when Lost World was still a big presence.
Because now I feel like they kind of got a makeup that they're still doing big
things and that they aren't just burning it slowly into more theme park.
Or that like, I don't know.
Well, look, shows film in that soundstage.
But nobody ever goes to the back lot anymore.
But post Lost World, you could really there was an energy.
You could really work there when you did like the tram tour and stuff was that
because I feel like one of before I got a pass as an adult,
one of the last times I had been there, I'd been around when Jurassic Park
three had come out and there was like some sets and stuff, I feel like, from the
both of those movies.
We didn't go near him.
It was very like an over there is some Lost World stuff.
Anyway, now, where are the world's let's
or maybe it was right after War of the Worlds.
Yeah.
But you know, but there's still the drive through where the Raptors.
No, it's I was going to say Raptors spit at you.
Oh, that's a lot of sources.
That's not correct.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of sources.
I need to I need to run some like dinosaur flashcards or something.
It'll get my son is into.
Yeah, I was going to say, as he got as the boy gets older, it'll come.
Yeah.
Yes.
He's not in the dinosaur phase.
No, he's pretty big in dinosaur and he'll ask what things are.
What's this one's name?
I don't.
But he now he's now he's just
it makes you feel like it was such a dumb 2020s.
Like, use your phone.
Check your phone.
There's been so many discoveries since we were kids in the 90s.
There's been so many different discoveries about dinosaurs and stuff.
So whatever you might have retained might not be wrong.
Yeah.
I use what's in my head.
Yeah, it's incorrect.
The pluto's of dinosaur world, you know, what are the things that have changed?
You know?
Oh, yeah.
Well, aren't we way more aware of the birdlike qualities
and then that they had feathers like that feels post our child?
Yeah.
Or more popularized post our childhood.
And then and then like the Brontosaurus keeps going back and forth
where it's like it wasn't a real dinosaur.
Now people are like, well, we'll take this other skeleton
that doesn't have a name and put Brontosaurus because we all grew up
with that being a dinosaur.
Wait, this is.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Brontosaurus isn't wasn't real.
I knew that.
But they've renamed a different skeleton.
People have been trying to.
And then interesting.
And then like triceratops might not be its own thing anymore.
Or like they might be combining it with like Torvosaurus.
Like I'm also like, I mean, you know, I interview paleontologists
sometimes on my podcast, and it's always like I also Jason,
I feel the same way.
Sometimes I'm like, oh, is my knowledge just from when all the dinosaur
dictionaries I had as a kid, like I actually probably should be brushing up
more on what's what's going on now, because there is stuff like that
where it's like discovering new things and they're like, well, actually,
these five skeletons, like all the scientists were drunk in the 1800s.
So like we actually got to like combine everything together
because like all that all the paleontologists, it's such a trip.
There's I forget there's a podcast where they talk about
the bone wars, where it was like all these paleontologists
mad that the others were discovering stuff so they would like destroy each other.
It was like scientists were insane in the 1800s.
The bone wars.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Well, it turns out the spitters didn't really spit.
They just kind of drool.
It just kind of dripped.
They'd have to get directly over top of their prey.
Yeah.
It wasn't acid.
No, it was just nasty.
It was just nasty little spit.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was a xenomorph, you know.
What's the one I need to file this one away for future kid time?
What's the one that has that's it's almost the only way I can describe it is like it's bald.
Oh, Pachycephalosaurus.
Oh, OK.
Great.
That sounds familiar.
I think I looked that up.
It's a Pachycephalosaurus, Pachycephalosaurus.
Because people also eat in the lost world.
He's trying to pronounce the name.
He's like, he's like, Pachy, Pachy.
He's like the one with the bald spot, Friar Tuck.
Oh, wow.
OK.
So my knowledge is exactly in line with a guy who hates dinosaurs
and is trying to hunt them.
Yes, exactly.
I'm also getting can I ask also, like, is there any truth to
the notion that dinosaurs are some of them were little and cute
and all live on a dude ranch with a bunch of plucky kids,
which is the case on the show that my son watches all the time called Dino Ranch.
It's a Disney plus show, but I think was bought from Canada.
Dino Ranch.
Anybody with toddlers out there.
Dino Ranch is a show.
This is the highest endorsement I could give it in terms of toddler
entertainment that doesn't make me want to claw my eyes out.
It's not a cocoa melon.
Yes.
No, we've never that's never entered our home.
I don't want it to.
Maybe I'd like it more than it.
But I just I feel like I hear things.
I've heard things.
I don't want this cocoa milk.
Yeah, it seems like people start to like glaze over just like those bad CGI
models or whatever they use.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, that seems like we're parent madness centers.
But Dino Ranch is not camp.
Where is it?
Tertaceous, which is the official Jurassic Jurassic,
which plays, I believe, in the child swap room of this ride.
Oh, really?
Oh, cool.
Family room.
Yeah.
Great idea.
Well, yeah, bringing that up to it's, you know, talking about like
the Jurassic World franchise, creating opportunities for rides and stuff.
It is interesting that or the most interesting aspect is the open theme park.
So they've gone back to that well twice now with the when they redid
the Jurassic World ride or the Jurassic Park ride in Universal.
And then now for Velocicoaster, they're like, OK, who cares about volcano
dinosaurs coming to mainland?
Like, let's like let's sit in the open theme park.
Let's make Bryce Dallas Howard wear that or, you know, cut her hair again
to be that bob, you know, severe.
Yes.
In the pantsuit, in the heels.
Yeah.
That was a question I had is like, I guess by
just by virtue of timeline,
Velocicoaster and Jurassic World, the ride
must be happening before the shit really hits the fan.
Like the it maybe happens before those kids come
and then get with the babysitter and then everything goes haywire.
Yeah.
Right.
So it's so you're on rides that happen
maybe like a week or two before Jurassic World, the movie.
Yeah, I think that's I mean, I think unlike Star Wars with all the,
you know, the all the detail oriented chess that they're doing,
I think with Jurassic World, it's very much Collins just kind of like,
just, you know, takes place around the same time as the movie,
obviously before the movie.
And that even like the whole discussion of like that movie is like now
labeled as a post Christmas movie, which is a weird really to be in.
Because in the beginning, they it's like snow.
And at the airport, you can see like Christmas trees and stuff.
OK.
So maybe.
Have I never seen the beginning?
Did I get to the theater late?
That is possible.
I've seen it.
I just don't remember.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because I was.
Yeah, I had a hook up for free fat burger.
So I was prioritizing that.
I'm like, I think I'll pick up the I'll get the gist of Jurassic
World when I get there.
I mean, it's very slight.
It's like one of those things really, I think in one scene.
And and I think in the when
Ty Simpkins is like he's like playing with this Christmas presence
or something like in the opening scene of the movie or something.
It's very slight.
Yeah.
I was just this actually.
Can I ask a quick question about your preference
with the original Jurassic Park ride or the new?
Do you have feelings on that strong feelings or mild feelings?
I mean, I I was very lucky that I had the opportunity
or just didn't have work that day that I went on the very last day
of the original Jurassic Park right here in L.
A.
I was there almost like all day, just like riding the ride as much as possible.
OK, because I was just like like, sure.
Again, it's one of those weird things where it's like, especially in L.
A.
,
it's like, when are we going to be here when a new ride opens and when like a clout?
Like, I don't remember when Back to the Future closed.
Like I like even though I grew up here, like I don't remember
when that ride closed or or backdraft.
Right backdraft was here in L.
A.
, right?
Yeah.
Not in that long.
And it was just like one of those things where it's like, oh, my gosh,
I'm like here when like a historic thing is like this.
Yeah, it's like here in L.
A.
, we don't have that many rides.
And it is weird.
There's not always a lot of like history, especially universal.
Yes, right.
Yeah, they're just like starting to get there
where things have been open for decades now.
Yeah.
And it is one of the things you're right, where it's like
the only reason they didn't turn this into like a Minions River
adventure or something, you know, was because the Jurassic World franchise
ended up being a surprise, you know, hit.
Yeah.
The first one like did like almost like double the productions
opening weekend or something crazy where they were like, it's, you know,
it's just going to be fine.
People like dinosaurs or whatever.
And they're like, no, actually, people want to see these movies again,
even if they're not great.
It was like, all right, cool.
We can reinvest in the parks and, you know, do all that.
It's crazy to me that Velocicoaster was only built in like three years
or something like that.
We're like, yeah, like because Jurassic World comes out in June of 2015.
And like maybe they were thinking about another ride before that.
But like it's just like thinking about how long it takes Disneyland to do stuff
where you're like Velocicoaster, like great, we need a new roller coaster.
And then like, yeah, and like we've been saying
like, I think I think listeners are probably pretty aware of the extreme
length of Guardians and Tron, especially.
And like, yeah, they they jam this thing together.
It feels like I'm excited because they just they've broken ground
on the coast of their building out here, which the rumor is it's similar to this
and similar to Guardians in a way as well.
But they're building on the side of the mountain.
It's Fast and Furious.
It's not.
Oh, yeah.
The animal show was right.
Yes.
But I'm like, are they going to finish this in seven months?
Like there's so fast at building stuff.
We'll see.
But yeah, so like I do like the Jurassic World ride.
I feel like you guys have talked before about like that notion that,
you know, universal, it's like, oh, we're having a great day.
Oh, no, something's wrong.
Like, you know, yeah, like we're we're, you know, in the tomb.
And then it's like he lives and you know, like the Jurassic World ride,
I feel like is like a little bit weirder in the fact that something goes wrong
kind of like right away now.
So you don't have time to have like the peaceful lagoon part.
You're like, oh, God, Mosasaur, you know.
And then you kind of go back to that.
I miss what's the what's the cove that is it Moses or had your sword?
Had your sword code is the one that you never get to go in.
You get knocked off the path.
So that part of like in terms of the flow of the ride is like a little disrupted
in that way because you're like Mosasaur tank, which looks amazing.
And then you go back to kind of like.
Mosasaur is the underwater.
Yes.
OK.
The whale dinosaur thing is that real?
Yes, that's that's real.
Yeah.
And they were that big.
Wow.
OK, crazy.
Yeah.
They might the size may have been exaggerated a little bit, but
Mosasaur eats the woman in the first Jurassic World.
Yeah, she gets dropped in her mouth.
Right.
The brutal death.
Yeah.
My favorite.
And I'm glad she was on her iPhone too much.
Yeah, they're like she wasn't babysitting well enough.
That's always like because Jurassic Park hates lawyers and Jurassic World is like,
well, we hate personal assistance.
You know, like you're like, oh, jeez, I don't like, you know, again, being in 2015,
they're like, you know, trying to make it in L.
A.
and really like, oh, like I know, like
she punished in a way for Bryce Dallas Howard sins.
Is it like, oh, she like the nephews come and she doesn't.
She's so busy with her extremely complicated park that she runs
that she doesn't put a proper childcare person in charge or spend the time with them.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Should is doesn't I've just I've seen the reading of this movie that it's like
like this ambitious woman fucker for her.
Like there's something kind of you might you might be able to read into a lot of the work of your director.
Oh, OK.
There's some odd feelings.
Interesting.
Yeah.
My favorite bit of fan art that somebody's done is
it's because, you know, the endominus also gets eaten by the Mosasaur at the very end.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There's like it's it's Katie McGrath's character, the Pteranodon that also gets swallowed with her
and the endominus all like playing cards like next to a campfire in the stomach of the Mosasaur.
I forget what that originally a reference to, but I just really like that idea
that they're all like, oh, all the things that have been eaten are like, you know, it's like Pinocchio.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
They got a couple of days.
It's going to be that's going to be a slow dissolve.
Yeah.
It's going to take three weeks minimum.
But yeah, I do.
I do like that they, you know, fixed up all the dinosaurs, gave them all a new coat of paint and stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
And then I really do think because like I feel like when Laura Dern or like people
talk about working in the original Jurassic Park, they're like, oh, this giant animatronic
could literally crush me like the actual physical animatronic, not that it's a dinosaur,
but like this giant robot.
And I feel like the endominus at the end of the of the Jurassic World
ride here, like gives you that sense of like, wow, that's like just a fully walking robot.
Like it kind of gives you a little bit of the scope of it.
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, it's cool.
They didn't just screen it.
Yes.
And now, granted, the beginning, Mosasaur is a screen, but it's a unique screen situation.
It's it feels like worth doing a screen.
With the water effect.
I love that.
Yeah.
I'm so delighted the first time we wrote it.
Any anytime people are surprised, you know,
they're just sort of like looking ahead or whatever.
And you're like, you have no idea.
Like, what's that?
Yeah.
You just get drenched if you just I feel like if you sit in the middle,
you get at the worst, I feel like.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
I've now realized front row center on that thing.
I'm sure I said in an episode, I got I got souped.
I got the biggest souping of a lifetime.
Yeah.
Like a degree.
I was pretty like you.
It's when you enter the big building and not the drop, but you kind of like go into the water.
Oh, yeah.
At the top of the and there's just suddenly it felt like slow motion looking.
I'm like I had four seconds to watch this wave and it all went.
I felt like it went to my lap and not even the people next to me.
Yeah.
Everyone else is bone dry.
That's when they turn the water up in the summer.
I don't know.
Well, no, this was this was a chilly evening.
So really?
I yeah, I wish.
Might have been OK during.
I think I had a movie to see and I'm just sitting there.
That's why I was right.
I always ride.
I always like doing this.
I ride Jurassic World and then I ride the mummy afterwards to sort of dry off a little.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I know that doesn't have the flames part, but is there there's flames in there somewhere, right?
You can get a little dry.
A little bit.
It's got to be at least one flame in that ride.
At least the wind, you know, the the wind of it.
Not not fans.
I'm sure there wasn't built in fans in there.
But well, we're not sure.
I don't know.
We have to talk to the jury.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're figuring out the fans.
Let me say this.
The
I don't go on the mummy a lot.
I now will definitely go on Mummy Orlando and look forward.
Yeah, I don't do it a lot here.
I guess I find it generally unpleasant, but that still maybe falls
into the launch territory for me.
And full disclosure, I did not go on Velocicoaster
and I'm not here to to make excuses.
I got to own up to the fact that I did not.
And then we're doing an episode about something that I just was not brave enough to do.
Ultimately, I will just say I've come a long way on this show.
I wasn't even Splash Mountain with.
Thank you.
Thanks for saying that, too.
But this this does feel like a what to me.
And maybe you guys can correct to me.
This feels like another level.
I think this is out of the comfort zone.
I it seemed like a little too far beyond.
I also as this come up maybe a few times or if you heard one of our Orlando live
shows, I lost my voice real bad.
And I've realized that like I have a couple of bits of armor now
going on rides.
One is holding harness mommy.
I want to hold my I need to grip that thing.
And they do not have that on this ride.
Just a lap.
So that I'm I'm screwed there.
I've also realized that just like huge guttural yells
is going to help me out on launches a lot because
Aaron, my wife, realized like you're closing your eyes and you're just like internalizing it.
So you're going to like you're going to like shake yourself to death.
That's crazy.
Just like eyes open.
Yell it out.
Get it all.
Yes.
So truth.
Thank you.
I'm trying to.
But I realize, like, if I can't scream my ass off on this thing,
I mean, I can't or there won't be live shows.
The live shows are canceled.
So losing that armor.
Interesting.
I like it.
And so, you know, I still feel like it's possible I could try this thing.
But also, now that I've laid all that out and I thin you and you know, my
you guys know my level.
You know what I've done and what was like a little too much for me or what?
What do you what do you think are my chances?
Do you think that I could end up enjoying this or not?
Oh, it's really intense.
It's like really intense.
But here's what I'll.
Oh, sorry.
But it's smooth.
Yes, it is smooth.
This is the big thing about it is because it reminded me so much of Twisted
Colossus, which freaked the shit out of me and Gio when we did it for the first time.
Also, this one did crush my genitals a little bit like that one.
Just a squeeze.
Just a little bit of like pushing my pressure test, pushing my penis into my body.
That is what happened on here.
So I like I went on it three times forced tuck.
The first time was the worst because I wasn't prepared for it.
But it put so many things parallel to us to classes, which legit
freaked me out doing it.
There was only the lap bar.
So it makes it feel like you're going to fly out.
Same thing with with Velocicoaster.
Similar kind of twists like the barrel roll.
But I truly I never felt like this thing is I never felt in danger like that.
So the smoothness and the newness of it was giving me a completely
different sense of safety.
Now, it is Jason's correct.
It's intense.
But I went on Hulk after Velocicoaster and I was like, Hulk is so much rougher.
Like it's rattling my spine around.
So you're going to be freaked out.
But I go, but there's a sense of like being handled in a comfortable way.
Like there's a sense of like safety on this ride that I don't
feel on other big coasters.
So that's the only thing I think that can I would say in the favor of you going on.
I think you're going to be freaked going on it for sure the first time.
But it's so smooth.
It feels like you're flying and it doesn't feel like you're to me.
It doesn't feel like you're feeling this like, oh, my God, this thing's coming apart.
And that's the difference to me.
Was it was it Adam we were with at Universal who said
he freaked out?
Yeah.
Like, oh, no, your panic attack.
I was like I would say I was on the fence and it was a day where maybe you guys were
going to do it.
And then a near panic attack was described to me.
And I'm like, that's that'll do it.
Yeah.
Bye.
I was going to say it's funny.
You talked about Hulk because I went on Hulk for the first time, too.
And I went after the Velocicoaster.
Right.
And that I I didn't feel like I was going to pass out, but I feel like it was that
you could.
There was definitely that feeling of like you are.
Yeah, you are definitely like manhandled, like roughly.
You are just like going through turbulence, you know, the worst turbulence of your life
on a plane.
And that's what it feels like.
You're rattling.
Yeah.
And you can have fun on it.
It's still kind of fun.
Steven just found the difference.
You want to be handled, not manhandled.
Yeah.
And handled.
It's right.
Throwing luggage on a bed.
That's that's not being careful.
Even though you imagine a man doing the handling, you'd think you'd be in good
hands, but they're bad hands.
The man hands.
The man you just want to be handled, not manhandled.
That's right.
Hulk has these crazy G forces.
Yeah.
And I feel like Velocicoaster, it's more like air time.
It feels like that.
We're like you're like when they shot Apollo 13 and they did the thing
where they're like diving in the plane and you like you're floating for a couple
seconds.
Parabola.
Yeah.
It feels like they like there's seven moments on the ride
where you're kind of like floating in the like I kept laughing.
And I did this on.
I was laughing.
I kept laughing because I couldn't believe the feeling I was having.
And it was almost like this weird euphoria.
I was I was still kind of freaked the first time, but I was in this weird
euphoric state when I came off of it, which is why I've been like so high
afterwards.
Absolutely high because of the amount of times where I just was like,
I'm flying.
I feel like I'm flying.
Yeah.
You come out of your seat.
Do you not?
Yeah, yeah.
I see it a few times.
Yeah, it doesn't.
It goes over the top.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
And so there's no over the shoulder restraints.
So you can't hug that.
There's only the lap restraints.
But as a shorter man, I love that because I'm ping ponging around
in those shoulder restraints.
Yeah.
I've come.
I can happen to a tall man.
Oh, yeah.
Totally in.
Yeah.
But like that happened when we were the time before that.
I remember I like I'm like, am I graying out?
On this.
No, I felt a little bit of that on Hulk.
Yeah.
Some of that.
And I think as it's going on, I mean, they they changed
the track a number of years ago, but I still swear the original one is smoother.
Like I might be right.
There was definitely that euphoria on the Velocicoaster,
especially like we were saying earlier of like when you go,
it almost feels like your head is like going to touch the water,
or at least you feel a little bit of mist or something.
You almost feel like Heath Ledger is the Joker hanging outside the car.
You know, you're just like, oh, like this is like, that's like,
there's that element of like, yeah, I think it is the like the fact
that you kind of feel like you're floating rather than being like dragged along.
A strip or something.
Yes, especially that last the last barrel roll over the water.
You're just like, I can imagine like being Superman or something.
Yeah, like I'm flying upside down over the water.
And obviously it lasts like a half second or something.
You are probably 15 to 20 feet above the water.
But it feels like you're right.
It feels like I'm going right in the water.
But like no point did I ever even here's what's.
And I don't know.
You might, Scott, you might not react like this.
No point in my brain even register the reality in the gravity of
literally the gravity or the actual gravity of like this.
One of the first parts is they kind of make you feel like you're going to fly
into some jagged rocks.
Yeah.
Never.
I was like, oh, that's funny.
Whoo.
Like, cool.
I didn't do it.
And then the water thing, you're like, this feels like they could be like
torturing, like dunking everyone's heads.
Yeah, no, exactly.
Water should go.
But instead of being like afraid, I was like, whoa, yeah, my head's going
in the water or whatever.
I didn't register that all week from like Port of Entry or Marvel Super Island.
I was looking at it like and I've and eventually it became my phone
like background.
Jane took like a photo of the sunset and the top hat and the track is there
and the little olive oil boat like it is a very beautiful photo.
Me ship the olive.
And then I like it wasn't until last night I realized like, oh, my God,
velocity coasters on my home screen as we're amazing.
We're researching.
It tends to get, you know, when you've got me ship the olive there.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a beautiful sunset.
But like, yeah, but the velocity coaster, the velocity coaster is there.
And when they were building all this, I was so worried that like, oh,
this is going to ruin the skyline.
It's going to ruin.
You're not going to be able to go.
And they they worked around it.
They like built the only thing that closed was the old triceratops encounter.
They demolish.
Yeah.
They put her out to pasture.
Oh, no.
To build the ride.
Old yellow style.
Oh, no.
You're not really also.
And then they shot it.
You didn't exist.
You have to go.
You never were.
But the track is so like built into everything.
And they even you can get to the ride entrance by there's a pathway
or you can come out the ground floor of the Discovery Center
and you still can see the view across the port of entry.
So like all of that is is preserved.
And I there's a special on the making of the Lost Coaster on Peacock,
which was very fun.
You know, you got Travaro in there.
You got Frank Marshall.
Of course.
You know, one of Mario Lopez.
Mario Lopez is narrating for some reason.
Teary Koo, a longtime Universal creative guys in there.
A number of people who worked on the ride.
It's funny.
I rewatched this.
And I swear to God, I had watched the entire thing before.
I had zero memory of Frank Marshall speaking.
And he does speak and clutching my pearls a couple of times.
I was speaking this one.
I remember.
How a lot of it clearly had a hit a lot of we, you know,
we wanted to do something bigger and better than it ever been done before.
OK, write that down.
Write down what Frank said.
Yeah.
To Frank.
I don't think Frank was there's no footage of him going on this ride, though.
Do you think Frank would do it?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Older man.
Maybe you shouldn't.
Maybe you should.
I mean, it's bad for your ticker, you know.
It's so smooth.
It is very smooth.
Yeah.
I would say Frank, don't go on the Hulk.
But maybe this one that have you guys talked about it?
Because that's like the fun fact of like Steven Spielberg
like rode the original Jurassic Park ride and gets like I feel like that's
like a theme park, you know, one of the big trivia.
Yeah.
You don't want to get wet.
And it always made me so mad that like so I need I could.
The only way to do that is to have the power of Spielberg.
Yeah, stop it.
That's what I why still in a way.
So I will still be going up the Splash Mountain or the soon to be Tiana's
lift and like still kind of like that Spielberg treatment.
If I could, they should just give you the option.
If you're right, anybody out?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Yeah.
One last call.
Can I pull a string like a bus?
Yeah.
Well, that's a work lights.
Come on.
I think we were all at the premiere of the ride of the dress.
Yeah.
I was there too that night.
You were there too.
Yeah.
I was talking about this before.
I don't think we had, but it was one of those things.
Oh, the fireworks were very upsetting.
I felt like they set them off right behind us.
But I think, Mike, were you saying that you tried to get on the ride
with Colin, like at some point?
Yes.
We saw Colin and we thought he was heading to the ride.
We're like, you know, if we follow him, we could get on the ride with him.
But he was leaving.
So we did.
The accident was the same spot.
Yeah.
We didn't do it too aggressively.
We just happened to walk like we could go on the ride with the director of the
movie.
So I feel like he what he what I feel like he didn't get off.
I feel like he might have toughed it out.
Yeah.
So you were at that premiere.
Do you remember anything else?
Do you remember like any speeches or any lack of speeches?
You know, it's so funny, because when I listen to that episode, too,
I was like totally with Mike.
I'm like, yeah, totally.
And then then I was like, go.
I actually went back through like some of the footage and things
that I take from them.
I was like, oh, I guess he didn't talk.
But I was totally with you.
I was totally.
Yeah, because he's he's become such a,
you know, spokesperson for the franchise in a way.
Right.
The franchise of Margaritaville.
Yes.
But it was one of those things.
The new Jimmy.
He's taking the man taking the mantle.
He said he should take his name, too.
I'm officially changing my name.
Jimmy Marsh.
Jimmy Kathleen Kennedy and Jimmy Buffett.
How could half the people the concert wouldn't know?
I mean, if you're in the back row, you can't.
I guess I think so.
Yeah, he's got the flip flops on.
I thought he died, but I guess that.
It's better than a hologram, you know, it is.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Absolutely.
I it's I feel like with some of these little scandal,
these things where I say the reality, such as the Frank Marshall didn't speak,
such as that it is a spoiler if you're not on the second gate,
that the George Clooney story is a suitcase story, not a briefcase story.
Right.
Or the or the one that we're we still don't have the proof on.
Eisner and the Eisner being the goal in Soren.
I feel like I'm ending up right.
And yet I think people want the spirit.
I feel like maybe I'm like maybe I'm doing a disservice
to these tales by unraveling them.
People want our audience wanted so much for Frank Marshall to have spoken.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, I was like I was so ready.
I was right there.
And then I literally went back to my stuff that I take for the podcast.
I was like, oh, yeah, like I'm totally going to back Mike up on it.
And I was like, oh, no.
Oh, did you think you could prove it wrong?
I thought I thought I could prove it to be honest, because yeah,
like I because, you know, I was like creating content or whatever,
trying to like from that night of like because again, it's like,
how often do we get to be around for a brand new ride opening?
Like, that was so exciting.
Yeah, yeah.
No, yeah, that was it was awesome to be at for sure.
But yeah, it was yeah, it was like going through the going through the Watergate,
you know, there must be a way.
Jurassic Gate hearings.
Let's talk before we dive fully into just like what the ride does
and the emotion of anything from the pre show or the queue that we want to shout out.
Yeah, yeah, there's
first of all, I like to talk about the lockers.
Yeah, because the lockers and they have these on Tron now as well at Disney World.
This is an innovation in the I don't know who did this first, but the locker.
You put your stuff in one side and it comes out another side.
Yeah, we haven't talked about that.
That was odd on Tron.
And it's interesting.
It's interesting.
And this works so a hundred times better than the Harry Potter system
of going in this crowded little room.
You're packed and fighting with people and looking for an open computer screen
to touch, like to touch a button and then try to figure out what that opened up.
This is such a somebody is like several below you.
There's a problem that you like not since high school.
You didn't think you'd have to deal with this.
Yeah, exactly.
Somebody's hunched down or you're the one hunched down
and somebody's reaching over you.
Yeah.
And the Hulk has like Hulk.
It's it's not as crammed because it's outside with all these.
But like I was having a big problem getting into one of those free lockers
are so far away from and then some of them are like paid and some of them
weren't working.
And then I'm like trying to find somebody and I'm like, do I need like a physical ticket?
Like I was so confused.
But the way they do it now, when we were in Orlando before,
I believe you were like a seeing eye dog for me because I had to put my glasses
in the whole locker and walk through the whole queue.
Like a block to the queue and then through the queue.
And I was just like, I got on all fours.
Magooing it.
I put a leash on.
Yeah.
And Jason just walked.
He held the leash.
Just I don't know.
Anybody gets too close.
Do not hit him.
Please.
It was fun.
It was a fun time.
It was innocent.
Also, it wasn't like a weird.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
It sounds like so I had a different experience on philosophy.
Because, you know, I had the scooter when we were in Orlando.
And this was universal.
I have to commend them.
You know, a number of attractions.
They're like, oh, they can't really bring that in the queue.
Can you transfer to a wheelchair?
So I got in a wheelchair and Jane pushed me.
So I kind of went like a roundabout way through the queue and I took an elevator up.
Oh, you got to do an elevator.
So I got to an elevator.
So I I didn't really go past the lockers.
She just stayed with the stuff.
Oh, OK.
And I got on on the exiting side.
But as a result of that, she was able to clock the car and videotape me.
And then we were able to go frame by frame and find me on the coaster.
Yes.
Like just like a smiling like a pig and shit.
Like having a ball the best time of my life.
Here's here's the photo.
Here's the sunset.
Wow.
Do I was talking about beautiful posted and other people?
Yeah, yeah.
I think my phone back.
Everybody's the city.
Beautiful.
So the port.
But universal.
Very team members.
Very good about like helping people on if they need assistance, allowing extra time
like on doom.
And I also switched a wheelchair for villain con.
So I got to do villain con seated.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, we didn't talk about.
They're just like, yeah, when you get on the moving walkway, lock those wheels, please.
Oh, did you do Tron?
Did you do Tron?
I didn't do Tron.
OK, because that's the only other place with the with these innovative lockers.
Yes.
I just wanted to make sure two doors, two doors on each side.
So it couldn't be done.
Yeah, I love these lockers.
I was also thinking you were talking about the lockers that are like of the workers.
And there's like, oh, sure, sure.
You know, Ian Malcolm's book there and Alan Grant's book and like,
you know, like again, because it is that thing of like, you know,
I think Harry Potter has such an advantage in Star Wars as well,
where it's like these fantastical worlds and stuff.
And Jurassic World is like it's like the zoo, but with like a little extra judge.
You know, so I guess to draw on, I guess.
Yeah.
How many beakers and amber like slabs can we throw in here?
You know, so I like the having the callbacks to Jurassic Park with the
the book of Ian Malcolm and the book of Alan Grant.
Oh, that's so cool.
Yeah.
Also, like attraction posters.
Oh, really?
Also, attraction posters for the one, the real ones for River Adventure
and and Tyrande on Flyers, but then like ride the gyrosphere.
Yeah, which is not something they figured out how to do.
Although I also realized
the one in Beijing we were talking about was apparently developed as a gyrosphere.
Yeah, I read that.
And then they I think it proved to
insane or ambitious.
But they filed patents for it.
Yeah, yeah.
How to which it would have been
the kind of vehicle where you think you're supposed to feel like you're going on.
Like you're being moved on the ground, but the mechanisms up above you.
So you're being swung.
Oh, OK.
They would have been like that because, yeah, it's that thing of in the original
movies, all the glass is CGI.
Like there's no there was no physical glass on them.
Complicated thing.
Yeah, just like a glass ball that's supposed to be rotating around.
Like that's probably as just a sci fi as the dinosaur part.
You know, the gyrospheres.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
But then I love that.
Then you you like ground it in that you're watching little Jimmy Fallon skits in the.
Yeah, I liked that part of it.
I'm like, wow, they have the videos in the ride are what it would be in reality.
Yeah, I think they filmed that on the SNL set.
Oh, that's cool.
I think so.
I believe I believe that when they they did that, they wanted it to have that.
Like your side of the old school like sketch lighting.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Huh?
That's cool.
The queue has.
But can I just say I like to vouch for Colin DeVarro to host SNL.
We get that on the record.
Yeah.
You may know me for my movies, not for being on screen.
Should have happened after the book.
But yeah, yeah.
You didn't even finish the name of it because it's.
You know, it's like, yeah, yeah, yeah, we know when we say the book, we mean the book.
The good book is not the Bible.
The book is the book of the good book.
Have you read the good book?
By that, I mean the feature film, the Book of Henry.
They have robot.
They have animatronic stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's animatronics.
But it's yeah, Raptors with the big
what metal muzzle.
Yeah, yeah.
Which are really cool.
And that's those are sequences in in the movie.
These kind of these awful, restricted, these locks that make you these face locks.
Yeah, they make you upset when you see them in the movie.
But that's all CGI.
So like the Indominus, it's crazy to take a CGI moment and recreate it in reality.
So lifelike to where you like, I swear, you can like look at footage of those
Raptors in the queue and think you're watching CGI footage.
It's really it's it's really good.
And it's also like it is kind of minimal movement for it as well.
Like if you watch them, they're minimal movement,
but it's just enough to make them feel alive.
Cheeks and the eyes.
Yeah.
And then the like the the not the cage.
Or whatever is behind them rattles.
Yes.
But the face doesn't do what so you're able to get like
this really impressive moment without having this full body, super complex
animatronic.
And it's really a well smartly done.
I to me, it seems like just some sort of minimal effects,
like a smart use of whatever technology.
Let me ask this.
The Mario Lopez special we've been discussing this big chunk that is about
creating the smell.
We had to think about what a what a velociraptor smells like.
I did not go in this queue.
They don't really try to say what it smells like in the special.
Did you any of you guys get a sense of the smell?
Do you know what a Raptor smells like?
I wish I could say that I remembered what it smelled like because it was a while ago.
But I mean, it definitely like the vibe of of what I would imagine
a real Jurassic world to see, you know, it's just the metal and there's like a
rain, you know, Petrachore, like that, the scent of like the rain on the sidewalk
kind of stuff.
But I was like, well, they the way they talked about in the special,
they're like blood.
And I'm like, I don't remember any of that.
Like I was blood smell.
Yeah, I don't I don't know.
I don't remember a smell at all.
Maybe they stop.
Maybe they stop doing the smells.
There are no smells.
Maybe there are no smells.
Maybe the blood was throwing people off.
Yeah, everyone's just like really sick on the ride.
The smell of blood.
Oh, my God.
Blood.
Oh, no.
Something awful happened.
And you get a little Mr.
DNA.
Yeah.
In there, voiced by somebody new and not the person.
Steven, you were talking about before the show.
Oh, yeah.
That I like held people at gunpoint.
Yeah.
It's a Mr.
DNA.
Yeah, the voice.
Yeah.
Greg Burson.
It was just one of those things where, you know, like there is these trivia points
where we like, oh, you know, there's only this amount of CGI in the original
Jurassic Park and, you know, like just just kind of the basic, you know,
the sounds of the raptors are like dolphins and tortoises having sex or,
like, you know, these kind of like the basic trivia that we all know about,
like the things we like.
And but that was like a trivia that I did not know.
I was like, oh, yeah, who did the voice of Mr.
DNA?
Because I think it was either Brad Bird did or Colin Chavarro
did the voice of Mr.
Oh, I did it.
I remember seeing that.
Yeah.
I think or Brad.
SNL put him in a costume.
He'd be Mr.
DNA and a skipper.
Hey, it's me.
He has guns.
I can't believe I'm in studio eight.
I think Brad Bird maybe did the voice of like like an intercom person
in Jurassic World.
Oh, I know.
But but but yeah, it's it's funny that they've started to bring Mr.
DNA back into like marketing and things like that because merch.
Yeah, they were coming up on the 30th.
I feel like you were seeing more Mr.
DNA merch around.
Yeah.
Yeah, because it is this weird part of that movie where it is like we're watching
a cartoon for two minutes.
Yeah.
A little of like a blockbuster movie.
But I feel like movies now do that a lot more, like have like little animated
sequences, like trying to explain a concept or something or show like
I don't know what Ice Age was the first example, but like the Ice Age where they
have the cave paintings, you know, that animates his his past or whatever.
Oh, I like a good thing.
Coco starts with a lot of that, like that, like paper cut.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But like a big chunk of backstories explained that way.
And you don't realize you're like eating your vegetables because it looks so
you get lost in how cool and unique it looks.
You said another one in there, though, that I didn't know,
which is the turtles having sex is one of the velociraptor sounds.
I think it's like one of the yeah, it's like two tortoises have it because
it's like a screech.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like, yeah, like not that because I'm thinking of the
and your way you're wearing Crocs or Crocs.
The official Crocs are Crocs.
OK.
But the records say
but like because I'm so fond of the like
if you're watching video of a turtle having sex with a croc.
No.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Exactly.
Oh, yes.
I have seen this.
Yeah.
They just the most tender sound.
It's not like sex.
It's a romance.
It's love.
Yeah.
That's nice.
Yes.
That's making love.
Yeah.
Gary Reidstrom, like pitch that down, stretched it out
and then it becomes the raptor scream.
Wow.
Turned into something mean, something
so so passionate, so affectionate.
All right.
Well, cool.
Pretty.
Oh, I was saying, you know what?
I think when I was talking about the aesthetic, it's partly the black
or like blue, gray, whatever aesthetic.
But also there is a cruelty to Jurassic World.
I think what I actually I'm more responding to is that the majesty
of the first Jurassic Park I do miss in like maybe the New Jurassic World
ride and then some of this like you're going through this queue
and it's not like, oh, dinosaurs are wonderful.
It's like they're locked up.
They will kill you.
You're missing a little of that, which is what I'm wistful or nostalgic for.
That's the only difference.
Now, it's good.
It's cool.
It's just that's the difference.
No, I think I think you're more than colors that I'm talking about.
Owen literally tells you, do not ride this ride.
Is that correct?
I miss that clip.
Pretty wild.
Yeah, because there was one of my rides, I got to see most of it.
And I'm like, this is a like feels like a 10 minute argument.
And there's like a Larry David like on this ride, like Bryce
else, Howard, just kind of looking at the camera like,
should turn, you know, like like because he's just like,
that's what I mean.
He's like a Werner Herzog character,
like like the Antarctica documentary that Werner Herzog did, which is my favorite.
You know, the penguins go into the wilderness, you know, into madness.
And it's like in the interviews, all these scientists who are like in like
they went down to Antarctica, who like like have ceased talking to other humans
and are just like studying whatever it's like.
That was I feel like on a like, you know, a better filmmaker
would have like pulled that out.
But like that's part of the Q video is like, oh, and just being like, this is bad.
We're all going to die.
What are you doing to these people?
These people are.
Why would you build this here?
And she's like, Owen, it's overdoing it.
We live now.
There's cameras on us right now.
Wow.
They were really like pumping out new rides.
Velocicoaster, the Indominus.
Yeah.
All of this.
And and what we said about the timeline
where this all happens right before.
If if OK, things are bad in Jurassic World, the movie.
So if we've had a predominance escape into the T-Rex paddock
and the boat dropped and the there were the coaster,
the Velocicoaster went haywire to and they kept the park open.
Yeah.
Still had her nieces over.
It is.
It all happened on Christmas Day.
And that logic, too, that it's like, wait, they're going to visit her
at Christmas time like that crowds that parks going to be at capacity.
I don't know if that's the best time to have visitors.
Is there less crowd on Christmas?
No, not at Jurassic World.
You should wait until the New Year.
You should wait until that first couple of weeks in January.
It's very slow when it's mostly just cheer competitions and football
competition.
Yeah, I went and sing and choir at Jurassic World.
Yeah, I did marching band.
I actually marked down my march down the thoroughfare.
I blew my trumpet in the direction of Brookstone.
I was going to say, though, the parents were getting divorced
and they couldn't schedule that.
You know, so that was a whole thing.
It's true.
I know what that's like.
Divorce.
It's yeah.
Shove it off to theme park.
Yeah.
Oh, that was some of the better parts.
You know, that was smoother.
But it's it's it really they they paint Claire.
If you put a piece all this together is incredibly irresponsible.
The guy there's no like it's you.
The universe is a little bit more like cheeky, like like danger stuff.
And like Dr.
Doom says, ignore safety measures on the fear fall and stuff.
But this one is the star of the movie who knows dinosaurs very well being like,
this is terrible.
Don't do it.
Why would you build this dinosaur expert?
A velociraptor, a guy who can talk to them is like, stop it.
Don't do it.
Turn this ship around.
And he's not saying it to the villain of the film.
No, he's saying it to the other star.
He's saying it to somebody who he wants to have sex with very much.
Yeah.
Right.
And this is going to ruin his chances.
Yeah.
He should be going, oh, great idea.
I know.
Why do they keep working together?
Yeah.
It seems every interaction is as combative as can be.
Well, yeah.
But by the time you get to Dominion, they're like,
full on make it out of Cabin in the Woods.
Well, yeah, they adopted a clone child.
Yeah, they got a clone child.
Ellie and Alan couldn't make it work.
You know, but then you didn't have that.
That Owen Claire spark.
Yeah.
That electric chemistry that we see in all these rides, the tension from screaming
at each other about Velocicoaster eventually built to that.
Oh, yeah.
It just comes to a head where it's like, come on.
We all know what's going on here.
We know what this argument is really about.
That would be great if in Dominion, they just had like a reference
to the Velocicoaster just as like a little Easter egg of like
in that time when like we let people get chased by Delta, Blue, Echo
and Charlie, our favorite rafters.
All four of them ate a head.
Yeah.
They all read that.
You said it couldn't happen because the ride goes 70 miles an hour.
But all of my rafters ate a full head that day.
You know, I was just saying, if I was a kid, though,
because I would always buy into the pre show stuff as a kid.
And I've said it, the going to the place called Pirates Cove,
which is a small place like amusement park by where I grew up.
There was this UFO ride that explained we were going into space.
And I bought whatever the pre show, whatever the video said to me.
And I if I was in line for this and I was scared in nine or 10
and I'm like, what are we doing?
Yeah.
The stars of the movie are saying.
So what I trust, they're arguing in the middle of trying to tell us
what this ride is about.
Before the ride begins, they argue more than they say what it is.
And these are the takes they use.
Yeah.
So can I I don't want to go on a tangent.
I think I can't not expel this from my head.
While we're talking about the portrayal of females in Colin Trevorrow films.
Oh, yeah.
I was just sometimes I'm like, how do you go from safety
not guaranteed to what is this?
How did he get that?
Why is he Jurassic World?
I'm so I don't know much about him or where he came from.
I feel like there's so much lore about Spielberg.
Of course, you know everything about Spielberg and he was on the lot.
And we don't know the story of Colin.
Do I?
Well, I was going to say the one thing that I find very interesting
was that I think originally Brad Bird was going to do Force Awakens.
But only if Colin Trevorrow was going to like just prep the movie.
I might have some of this wires crossed, but it was like
because they wanted JJ and then he said no.
And then I think Brad Bird was going to do it.
But then he was like, well, I'm doing the tomorrow.
Right.
And then tomorrow.
But then he was already in prep for that.
So it was like, oh, I'll do Force Awakens, but only like I need help.
Basically.
And so I think Colin originally was going to prep Force Awakens,
which that feels like such a weird consolation.
I've never heard that.
Junior director feels like the Prairie Home companion, Robert Altman,
Paul Thomas Anderson, stand by director.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I might have some of this cross, but these names were all swirling around.
That's fascinating.
Well, it's interesting because he fell into the like he makes the move like that.
That happened a bunch in the recent past with going sort of from a smallish movie
to small, well received movie to yeah, to doing like the biggest thing with the craziest budget.
And then once you're I think once it was a huge hit, the first one, it was like,
well, I guess we plug him in.
Yeah, because then, yeah, he would been announced for doing episode nine.
So he's doing it.
Can I just can I just knock one out real quick?
It's called Book of Henry.
It won't trouble anybody.
One for them, one for me.
You'll see it's yeah.
But it's going to be one for them, too.
People are going to want to see Sickleman and a woman doing an assassination guided by her dead son.
Watch the movie if you haven't seen the movie.
Yes.
I beseech you to watch Book of Henry.
But here's what I did.
I was like, what is the root of Colin?
And I and on Wikipedia, there's a mention of Colin's first short film from 2002.
It's called Home Base.
Home Base is a movie where it's a short film, eight minutes, but a lot is packed into it.
It's very like mini DV, like old blocky digital.
And basically, it's about a woman who comes to her boyfriend and says, you know,
I have to tell you, this is hard, but I had a connection with with with your boss at the company
picnic, and it just made me feel like maybe we need to end this and this isn't, you know,
I'm just so sorry.
I feel terrible about it, but maybe we aren't meant to be.
And then the guy is this kind of snarkster Craig Healy guy.
And he's like, OK, all right.
Well, you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to fuck your mom.
Excuse me?
Yeah, I'm going to fuck your mom.
Why don't you go home and tell your mom,
get ready to get fucked.
Whoa, whoa, you can't.
Hey, hey, hey.
And he leaves the restaurant.
And then sure enough, the next scene is him showing up at
the house like, I'm here for Mildred.
And then he goes on a date with the woman's mom.
And then it's unclear whether anything's happened or not.
But the woman has a fight with her mom.
And then this is yeah, this is the mom character.
Is it such a shock that your mother wants to fuck?
Your mother wants to fuck.
And then and so it's this is the very the first sparkles of the
Travarro filmmaking.
No podcast has ever tackled this.
Although Wikipedia claims that this was like this movie had 25 million views in a pre YouTube
world.
This was like an eye film.
Yeah, it might have been like, do you see this mom fucking movie?
I mean, I guess that I could see like college kids being like,
do you see the wall with the old lady says she wants to fuck.
I guess I could kind of see that logic.
And if there's not a lot of stuff, if he put it
Travarro's vimeo channel.
Oh, wow.
Listed as him.
But anyway, this is too much for the woman.
And she goes to the husband
almost in the side of the ex boyfriend, almost in tears.
And she's like, I'm sorry.
Okay,
I just don't want this.
Please don't have sex with my mom.
Whatever I did.
I'm just sorry.
I don't she's like breaking down.
And the and the guy's response is like, hey, hey, it's okay.
I don't think you're shallow.
I think you've got something wrong.
You're just emotionally
disconnected.
I mean, that whole orgasm thing.
It's not my fault if you can't come.
I've tried
everything.
You've done everything.
You're just you're emotionally frigid.
You're physically
frigid.
And she just listens and agrees.
And that's the end of the movie.
And no, because the end of the movie is she comes downstairs.
And the guy's there in a bathrobe and
clearly did fuck her mom.
The end directed by Colin Travarro.
Now you know that now the audience
knows that it's about it's a movie.
It's a movie about a hero who says you'll have sex with a mom,
then says you were too frigid to come then does have sex with the mom.
And this is where it ends.
This is who is in charge of the Jurassic Park franchise.
Well, Steven, did you know that?
No, I mean, I think he's done.
If you want to do the Donald Trump, I'm hearing this for the first
time.
I've never heard this before.
She was very frigid, very frigid.
He told us safety's not
guaranteed.
My thing is that, you know, it's one of those things where, you know, Jurassic Park
fans are very much like, well, yeah, there's not going to be any more movies like clearly, like,
as much as people enjoyed the movies enough, you know, Transformers style, like nobody's holding on
to Claire and Owen in the same way that maybe like a Marvel.
Well, now we've been saying that now
doesn't matter anymore.
Nobody wants Marvel anymore.
But like, I feel like at least Bryce
Ellis Howard lately has, like, done some of the best Star Wars.
Like she's been a really great
television director.
And I feel like just let her have these movies because I feel like she at least
I always feel like all blockbuster movies have like one actor who's like actually nerdy and into
the thing that they're in.
And I feel like she has been kind of actually been like, oh, I know what
it's like to run away from green screen dinosaurs, like actors on the volume and stuff like I can,
you know, oh, yeah, help you like to help you sell stuff better and not just be lot like,
because I imagine movies like this.
Michael J.
Fox talked about this and Back to the Future,
very good that you can like, everybody's so worried about effects and all the like, you know,
the big meaty stuff that you the actor ends up like alone and like nobody's tending.
Nobody's really directing them.
I mean, even like,
oh my God, I was gonna say Gantov, Sir Ian McKellen, even like, you know, if you watch those,
like the making of Hobbit movies, he's like having like a mental breakdown.
He's just like
in a green room by himself having to act against like 12 dwarves and Martin Freeman, you know,
this was going around.
I think I'm probably like stealing the framing of this as like an
existential nightmare.
But there was footage that came like raw footage of Space Jam and like what
that was like for Michael Jordan, where like, like and action and then he's on a green screen
and then he's swarmed by four fully green guys.
He has to defend the basketball against it.
It is a true nightmare.
Yeah.
My hope is that because I mean, they're gonna make it's like
that was that thing too.
It's like, well, they're done after dress code.
It's like, no, they're not.
Like, like, like, I think they I think they're putting it on ice in the sense because I think
people are realizing that like when you don't miss a movie franchise, you're like gonna get
sick of it because with every day going on.
But like, I feel like, yeah, just get Bryce Ellis
Howard, who's kind of like used to like working on like leaner TV settings, kind of make it smaller
again.
You know, all that stuff where it's like, yeah, and then get Clint Howard to pop in maybe.
I'm surprised he's never been in a dress in a lab.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
What's the second
Jurassic?
It's fallen kingdom.
Yeah.
That's the haunted house one.
Like I really like
No.
Yeah.
I really love that too.
That whole part is because J Bayona directed that one.
And so
he did like the impossible and some other stuff.
But like horror movies.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
The orphanage
and stuff.
And it's like, you know, I think dinosaurs are scary.
You know, leaning into that
might help a little bit.
Right.
Yeah.
And is Cromwell in that?
James Cromwell's in that.
Like, uh, John Hammond's old friend.
Yeah.
The hidden, the hidden partner that like the hidden
partner.
Yeah.
And he, he, I think just when you have an actor of that caliber, it just kind of
like lifts everything.
Well, and Charlie Chaplin's granddaughter is also in it as the, as the nanny,
Geraldine Chaplin.
Yeah.
Cause she's in all of J Bayona's movies.
So interesting.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
Charm.
Charlie Chaplin's granddaughter.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
Well, yeah, it made some
cool choices, but ultimately at the end of the day, not enough mom fucking for me.
That is
true.
That's what the franchise needs.
Maybe that's what T-Rex's mom.
Was that what his episode
nine was going to be?
Yeah.
It was going to be like sort of an ending like that.
All right.
We, we know I am your father, but we haven't, we haven't heard.
I fucked your
father.
The Knights of Ren are going to say that to Kylo.
Oh, about Princess Leia.
Rest in peace, Gary Fisher.
All right.
Let's, let's talk some ride stuff.
You guys, there's already
been some emotional reaction to like the big parts of it, but let's, let's throw out then.
And I leave
it to you cause I can't, uh, what, what, like, I dunno.
Well, let's, let's talk like favorite moment.
If you, if you had to pick a number one, cause it seems like there's a lot of candidates, but what is,
what is the, the peak of that ride experience for you?
I mean, it, they, they talk about in the making
of special that it kind of builds in a way that like a lot of roller coasters that first drop
and then like maybe some bunny Hills or some inversions, but like Velasco's or does seemingly
get more intense as you go on, like that, uh, launch up to the top hat, you know, the biggest
part.
This phrase is new to me by the way.
The top hat.
Yeah.
That big kind of like straight
up and down on a curve.
It's almost like what's the Knott's one.
That's just that.
Montezuma's revenge.
Yeah.
Just that up and down really.
Kingda Ka, Six Flags, Great Adventure and
Jersey.
That has the famous one.
Yes.
Where it's that's most of the ride is the top hat, but this
is like halfway through the second launch.
That's like one of seven things.
Yeah.
And then the finale,
the barrel roll.
I also saw it called a heartline roll or the Moses source role
is such a surprising, but like, it is so crazy to go over the water upside down.
Yeah.
Well, and I think, you know, again, like I was also scared of roller coasters as a kid.
And
I remember first time going on Indiana Jones at Disneyland, I held on like this and like, I
remember being rattled and stuff like that.
And I think the thing about the Veloci coaster that,
you know, maybe you might be able to do Scott is that like, because it's so smooth, you, I like,
you aren't like huddled down.
You are kind of getting to like enjoy everything.
And I feel
like it's that it's those parts where you're like doing these like twists and there's that part.
It's like, I forget what point it is where it kind of like, it kind of dips you down and then
kind of, but like, does it.
It's like a fake out almost.
Yeah.
It's like a second half.
It
kind of like feels like you're going to dip, like let's say, I don't remember the direction,
dip left, but then it takes you right back.
It's like this almost like fake out thing that happens
too.
Yeah.
And it is like a thing where they're like, you know, I guess the, yeah, the story,
like, you know, at the beginning, it's like one, two, three, and you're like, the Raptors are
running with you and you're like, I'm not really thinking about that when I'm on the ride, but
those little moments, like that fake out and stuff where you're like, I can remember the whole,
I can like remember the order of things on the ride, maybe a little bit better than other roller
coasters.
Yeah.
Because like, obviously like in credit coaster for like, you remember, okay,
like what are the best parts of it?
And now there's like little characters on it, which, but,
but basically you're like, you're remembering the launch.
You're remembering when you kind of go up
a little high and you go on that big drop.
And then you remember this going in the loop and then the
bouncy thing.
It's honestly what makes it like hard to talk about roller coasters on a podcast,
because it's, you end up so as a part where you go up and then the part where that kind of that,
that twist and that, but this, this is different.
These, these moments definitely read as like
notable, that kind of go in a, in a sequence that you recall.
Right.
And it feels, because it's a
short ride.
It's very, what is it?
It's 90, shorter than 90 seconds.
The YouTube video is like a minute
and 32, but that's with like the intro, you know, Velocicoaster.
Is it by the way in when is the
launch, is the idea that you're going to go through a Velociraptor paddock, but they're going to be
taking care of, you know, they're, they're sedated or putting their place in whatever,
but then they kind of, there's like rattling and they break out when you're, as you launch,
is that roughly correct?
Yeah.
I feel, well, cause in the Jurassic world, when they like let them
out to go like ride, I was going to say ride motorcycles, but that was like somebody CGI'd
that, but like when they're all running with Chris Pratt, like I think it's almost meant to kind of
replicate that moment of like, like, like the race horses or whatever.
It's like one, two, three,
go, but yeah, I can't, I'm like, I feel like they let them out on purpose.
Oh, maybe that's like what
Pratt doesn't want is that like, wait, you're going to like have them race a little bit.
Yeah.
My Raptors.
Well, cause it's almost like treating it like it's an exercise, you know, how people do
like, you know, like sea world or whatever.
It's kind of like, you know, I was like,
is Jurassic world the bush gardens of theme parks, you know, where it's like,
in sea world where it's like coasters and animals, you know, together?
I guess so.
And there's,
you know, the statues of the Raptors in the, at the first parts of the ride, you kind of go through
a look when we were riding this again, I did not, I took my glasses off.
So I didn't catch
some of the like riding details as you're riding, but you're going so fast.
Yeah.
But the sound is
great.
Like your Raptor cries that are startling as you're going through it, like 50 miles or
60 miles an hour or whatever.
Yeah.
That is the thing I forgot about, but like thinking about it
again, that's the part I think that also adds a little bit to the thrills is yeah, they'll have
like Raptor screams kind of call out occasionally.
Just there's Raptors on the ride that I never saw.
I never noticed like actual like little static figures.
I caught one of them.
Yeah, I caught
one of them.
Like I had to watch a video weeks later and go, Oh, there's Raptors on the ride.
There's also a Raptor statues at the entrance.
And I saw that on a lot of Easter egg lists of
that's sort of a nod to the now long gone dueling dragons attraction, which had big
dragon statues at the entrance.
Yeah, I'm wrong.
It's two minutes.
It is longer than I thought.
But it's still short, short ride.
By the way, of course we all know those
dragons on dueling dragons, uh, uh, Blizz Rock and Pyrock.
Uh, uh, yeah, Blizz Rock is the ice
dragon.
Pyrock is the fire dragon.
We all know they were back.
They were back for a haunted
house.
They were back for a, a haunted maze.
My question is that a fact you learned in the
last several months or did you know that love it, memorize it, pray to it at night?
I knew it.
And then I, I double checked it last night because I'm like, what are their names again?
And I couldn't quite find, I, I had heard at some point, but it couldn't quite confirm last night
that those are the names of the Raptors at the entrance.
But I think just like a little nod,
cause you can get to a velocity coaster from lowest continent.
I believe they demolished
the bridge and then rebuilt the bridge.
Mom, dad, can I call you guys Blizz Rock and Pyrock
instead?
I'm getting a little bored of mom and dad.
It's like how we all remember blue,
Charlie, Delta and Echo.
Charlie's the young one who's light green.
Delta's the handsome one.
Echo's got glasses.
Echo does machines.
Blue cannot be called beta cause she is an alpha.
So you have color blue.
Yeah.
We can, oh, sorry.
No, I was just going to say, yeah, like, uh,
or what we actually, let me ask you, do you have a favorite of these Raptors?
I like Charlie cause
she's like the young one.
And she was also like, it is funny when they were like,
we're going to make these Raptors and we're going to put like a blue stripe on blue cause you know,
they're birds, whatever.
But, but you know, it's like that again, attention to realism.
We're like,
why didn't you make one of them like red?
So then at least we have like blue, red,
brown and green.
Cause Charlie's also the other one to me that stood out the most cause
she was like bright green.
And then she's the one that gets exploded by the rocket launcher
at the end of the, where like Chris pets like, Oh, like my old friend.
And then she like looks at
him and then just explodes.
And then I think, I think I can't remember which one it was.
Delta or echo that gets thrown onto the like, it wasn't Margaritaville.
It was the other restaurant
gets thrown onto the, to the grill, the Hibachi grill.
Oh, that's cool.
I know looking back,
like they wanted us to love these dinosaurs.
And then in fallen kingdom, they show you footage of
them when they're babies and they're like, what happened to that?
Oh yeah.
And like onto the
Hibachi grill.
Oh, they blew up in the, what was that?
A chink burger rim or burger lounge.
The one
that was like a massive Ponzi scheme or something.
It like popped up everywhere for a little while.
And then eventually they're like, Oh, this isn't a real company.
Yeah.
It's just money laundry.
Close.
You throw out these, these terms, these like, like a little roller coaster
terminologies, the, the, there's top hat.
And then there's, I had not heard inverted stall.
You have an inverted stall on this, which means, cause you got four inversions on this ride all
told.
And then there is one where, okay, if you're, if you're flipping the whole time,
if you're spinning the entire time, that's not a, that's an inversion, not a stall.
And what this has is a moment where you flip and then you stay fully upside down for two to three
seconds and then flip again.
So I think that's a rare moment to find.
That's the end thing.
Yeah.
Over the water.
That's the water.
No, that's a barrel roll.
In the middle.
Oh, right.
They're
saying, it doesn't stand out in a ride video where like twist and turn and then like it does like
get still for a second for, and then flips again.
I'm trying to remember what that specific one is.
That's after the top hat.
Is that right?
I think so.
After the top.
Yeah.
Cause that's
when it, yeah, you go up and then you're heading towards the visitor center or the old visitor
center.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
When the fake out happens or does it fit?
It's so built
into the land.
Like it is for such an intense ride.
It is not like obtrusive.
No, no.
To where,
if you're entering it from the Jurassic park Island, you got to follow like kind of a winding
path.
It's kind of hidden.
It is hidden.
Yeah.
It is.
I also was like, I had a problem
finding it.
I was wandering around tired that day and I was like, wait, where is this?
I see it,
but I don't, I can't get to it.
A fact, I think someone down there told us about when they were
building this, you know, because they talk in the special, like, oh, this construction site,
there was no backstage.
Like we, we work far from backstage.
So I, when they were transporting
materials, sometimes they use the old Island skipper tour dock, which is kind of off to the
side of Jurassic park because it's just easier to put it on a barge at port of entry and sail it
across.
Well, I mean, yeah, when I, when I worked at Disneyland in high school, I worked at pizza
port and then our ice machines broke one time.
This was like 2004, I think.
Yeah.
It was
like a couple of years after California adventure had opened.
But I remember that we wanted to get
ice from club buzz or whatever it's called.
And instead of having us go like through just that
like courtyard or wherever we went through the underground tunnels, because we had this big ice,
I had to like drag this big ice bucket thing and they just didn't want, I guess they didn't want
to run over kids or, you know, just to, just to not ruin the illusion, but, or, or just even that
idea of like we're, we're in the middle of this thing and, and like maybe just putting on a boat
is actually just like, so we don't have to go through crowds in order to try and navigate the
stuff or whatever.
Yeah.
It seems like, um, in this, according to the special, because building
this crazy ride in the middle of the park is very difficult, then COVID hits, but COVID, then you
got nobody in the park anymore.
So it might've helped them drive like a truck through.
A flat bed through Susslanding trees are about to happen.
They're tear down the Dr.
Sussland.
Yeah.
Oh, the Ford F 150 clip the side of the three brooms.
Uh, I was saying earlier, the first thing, one of the first things that happens is that they
shoot you over these, like this rock formation.
And when you're coming down, correct me if I'm
wrong or you didn't think this, it feels like they're teasing, throwing you into rocks.
No, I kind of, I felt that it was, cause yeah, it's not like, it's not like, um, oh my God,
why am I forgetting the Yeti, um, thunder mountain or whatever matter horn matter horn.
Yeah.
Matter
horn where it's like, you know, like they're not like letting you know that a cave is coming up.
Like this is just kind of a big pile of rocks that you're sort of heading towards.
And then I
think, I feel like it'd be surprised when you hit a turn and yeah, I feel like it becomes clear.
Cause I think that's like, again, I don't really remember where the Raptor statues are, but I feel
like there's one kind of over by there.
Maybe that like, maybe it's almost like, oh, like, you know,
we got to turn and get out of the way or something like that.
Um, I can't remember if there's a
Raptor statue right there.
Um, this I feel like is the first part of the ride where you get some
decent air, which is where your body first goes, Oh, I'm going to fly out and I'm just going to hit
these rocks in such an aggressive manner, beautiful plants.
But your adrenaline has surged so much,
hopefully fingers crossed that you're just like, great, let it happen.
Let's go.
Yeah.
I throw me into these rocks.
That's what I need.
Yeah.
Like, like Steven, you're doing a pose.
That's kind of a, just like giving yourself to the Lord.
That's what I need to do.
Yeah.
I can't restrict myself and tighten and close myself.
I have to just, I gotta open my chest
and just like create myself to be in it.
I was a freak doing Dr.
Dooms Fearful for the first time
that I was there.
I mean, it was shorter obviously, but this, yeah, there's this weird euphoria that
this ride gives me.
Yeah.
But it's exciting.
You want to give Lord Doom your fear juice.
Well, of course I want to give Lord Doom my fear juice.
I gave him my fear juice.
That wretched
Richard is up to his old busy body trip.
Yes.
And I, but I, but I didn't even,
I didn't even feel that I had fear juice left.
I didn't know there was any fear left in me,
Andrea and Velocicoaster.
Sure.
I got a way to refill my fear juice.
Yeah.
But I don't even,
it just was in there.
I didn't even use it.
Yeah.
I barely has any fear juice.
Quick, squeeze his
nuts.
Lower the lap harness.
Doom's Doom is better at getting the fear juice out of me than Velocicoaster
than Owen and Claire.
Yeah.
And look, I don't want to, I don't want to, you know, toot our own horn,
but shout out to the person who worked on this, who I know is a listener of this show who I've
talked to.
So I don't want to blow up their spot too much, but sure.
Yeah.
Thank you for
all.
Thank you for getting up there.
It was an incredible coaster.
Yeah.
Do you think about
it once a week?
Both of Steven and Jason?
Velocicoaster?
At least once a week.
Do you think about it?
Cause I do.
Once a week I go, oh, that Velocicoaster is good.
Well, I did something very nerdy where,
cause I got a projector and so I just put the projector as big as possible on the wall and
then projected the Velocicoaster video.
Oh, really?
Like it's kind of sat in the middle just to be
like, can I, can I replicate that feeling a little bit?
Cause this would, I mean, you know, I had a
Quest 2 for a minute and like one of the first things you can do is like a roller coaster
VR experience or whatever.
And it's just, it's not quite the same.
Cause if you're just, you know,
if you're just standing or something, it's not, you know, you're not, you're not really getting at it.
Yeah.
It pops up in my YouTube recommended like videos all the time is the ride through and
other people's ride throughs.
And well, this, this I feel like was an early, I feel like lots more
parks now are putting out like really good quality official videos.
And this was one of the first
ones that struck me where Universal put out like a full HD, like really good quality ride through,
which is partially so they can just give the media this video and they don't have to worry
about people with GoPros, like electronics flying off their person, you know?
Why not?
Cause it
ruin it.
I mean, I guess it might spoil a surprise or two, but it's like an entirely different thing
on it.
I would imagine.
Maybe I'll know.
I mean, this and guardians, I managed to avoid like spoilers.
So I was really surprised by a lot of elements on both these roller coasters.
Yeah.
For sure.
Especially gardens, obviously because there's more like stuff to look at.
Yeah.
Which obviously
those are pretty horrendous ride through videos.
You might watch that and think like this ride
isn't that good.
You got that one.
You really got to be on.
Yeah.
I agree.
It's hard to replicate
like in the dark and, and those sensations and that kind of thing.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
I don't
think a video space mountain would be the best thing to watch either.
Let me throw out this,
this debate if we're kind of heading for the door, because we kind of left this at guardians,
because guardians, obviously a big candidate for best ride in Orlando.
This one has to be as well.
I mean, I did a little poll online to see what people thought, but let's, let's get the,
do we, do we have knee jerks?
Mike, I'm just going to make you.
I got texted an angry.
You got 10
seconds.
Oh, 10 seconds.
Let the man cook.
No, what are you saying?
My heart.
Well, I was going to say
a friend of the show, Matt Cardona angrily texted me when I threw out the idea that
Velocicoaster could be better than guardians.
Cause he said, are we not theme park people that like
themes?
And, and it was like, well, that's true, but here's what, here's what I'll say.
My heart wants to say Velocicoaster is my favorite.
I think that's my answer.
Well, and it doesn't even
it's a viable, a lot of people have that answer.
It's not crazy.
It doesn't make sense intellectually.
You know how when you, sometimes your heart and your mind say different things, my mind wants to
say guardians, everything about it.
I like the movies better.
I like, I'm a big rock and roll fan,
as you know, as everyone knows that it's a new, it's innovative in the way that it turns of guardians.
It's amazing.
And the, the, the way it looks like you're in space, but it's bright.
I love it.
It's
amazing.
But my heart says that I like Velocicoaster better.
It just does.
It does things to my body
that guardians does not.
It's a smooth, crazy experience that it can't like, it doesn't, again,
it doesn't even matter.
This could be a, this could be the book of Henry ride.
It does not matter.
It could be themed to a short film.
They only be Watson's truly the physical experience you have on
it to race to sickleman's house.
Great.
Fine.
So again, there's like a static of the guy in the
end, like right by the barrel roll.
I am the, I am the police.
So I'm above the law.
It doesn't, oh, that's from the short film.
I got confused with sickleman.
Sorry.
I'm getting my Travaros mixed up.
All right.
It's the, it's home base.
The ride it's home base.
You're on a race to fuck your ex's mom.
Right.
Hurry.
Somebody else might.
The couple's
having an argument in the pre show about fucking the mother and they're like, no, don't do it.
Let's do it.
Well, you're frigid.
I'm going to do it.
But I think that maybe for the first time
in my life, I have to say that the actual like physical experience of going on the ride
supersedes the theming or anything else.
I just, that's how I feel.
That's what's in my heart.
And
I have to say my heart declared it.
I like it.
Put your neck out like a non-existent brontosaurus.
Yeah.
And declare your opinion.
A slightly bad, like I love guardians and it's the
second best ride in Orlando.
Wow.
Jason thoughts.
Yeah.
Um, you know, I'm the little thrill boy of
the podcast, you know, and the thrill seeker.
Um, so I think like, yeah, I, I did this like the last
day before we flew out and like, was so, uh, you know, worried all week.
Like I kept having chances
to go on it, not getting on it for whatever reason, one reason or another.
Yeah.
Worried about not
getting on it.
This was like the one thing down there.
I was like, I have to do this.
So like,
thankfully got on the last day and I just found it to be so exciting and so satisfying.
Yeah.
So,
but by, if you're declaring it best ride in Orlando, you're spitting in the face of Peter
Parker.
Well, willing to do that.
Jason Sheridan.
I might say best coaster.
Uh, I don't know.
I don't
know about best ride cause then you start getting into the dark ride.
Like I feel like guardians
and even Hagrid's, you know, they have a lot of story beats.
They have a lot of tricks
that are closer to dark ride mechanics than coaster mechanics.
But I feel like this one has such
exciting coaster elements with story and place making involved.
Sure.
Yeah.
I think it's
definitely in the top, whether that is just like recent bias of like shiny new thing, you know,
but I think the fact that it's built in, it's so compact and I'm, I'm, I'm so fascinated by how
they're going to translate that thrilling compact coaster into like the hill, like universal,
like into that land, like another sort of difficult landscape it's being built into.
Also the rumors of like, Oh, there might be drifting elements.
I think there is for sure.
Yeah.
It's going to be like guardians with the ability to turn, which is the drifting thing.
And that's the word and it goes over the various going to be our favorite ride.
And it goes over the escalator.
It goes around the escalator.
That sounds cool.
Steven.
I don't know
if you've, I mean, this trip was a little while ago.
You've probably missed some things that are
potentially on the list, but do you have a knee jerk if you were to weigh in on that?
Well, yeah.
So I haven't been on guardians, but the thing that I can maybe compare it to a little
bit is that, um, again, I worked at Disneyland in high school and it was all, you know, all about
that life that, you know, and then even after I stopped working there, I got a pass and, you know,
my friends in high school, we had a thing where we would like go in the morning and see how long we
could go before the lines would be too long because, you know, we could just go the next day or
whatever.
And it was just like such a magical part of growing up.
Um, but I hadn't been to
Disneyland in like 10 years until last year for my birthday.
I did basically just did, um, Batu,
Batu.
Yeah.
Did, did, um, I didn't do the Millennium Falcon, but I did rise the resistance
for the first time.
And again, not to bring up any debates or anything like that, you know,
previous debates on the podcast, but again, like Jason, like you were saying, like I think
Velociraptor is easily my favorite roller coaster of all time.
But I think for me,
there's like a part in rise of the resist rise of the resistance where you forget that you're,
cause like to me it's, yeah, it's like that, like you're saying the debate of like theming versus
pure thrills, but there's like definitely a part in rise of the resistance where I'm like, I'm just
in star wars and I just totally forget the rest of the world exists and I'm just fully immersed
in a way that was just like, you're like, like I remember describing it to my sister, like the
next day and I was like starting to get like teared up.
I was like, I was there, you know,
like that kind of thing, you know, like all of our favorite characters, but like, but, but you know,
it was just one of those things where like, I think rise the resistance is like my favorite ride of
all time because it, it even has like the history of like every kind of ride thing we have like drops,
like like vague, yeah, it kind of like uses all the tricks.
So for me, like rise is like my favorite,
maybe my favorite ride of all time, but Velocicoaster just pure thrills, just like something
I could like ride over and over again.
I feel like definitely Velocicoaster is number one in that
regard.
Yeah.
My like thing that haunted me, I couldn't stop thinking about for a long time
was the big cannons and ride that.
Like, I just like, yeah, I just needed to like close my eyes
and to think about it for a couple of, and during pandemic when it was not available anymore.
Internet, I did a little, I did like, all right, let's do four at Disney world, four at Universal,
rise the resistance took it at Disney world, Spider-Man took it at Universal, put them together,
rise the resistance by a wide margin.
It's almost as if rise of the resistance is a good ride.
It's a good, it's fine opinion.
Yeah, good is a fine describer of it.
I know, I know I've got my
edge Lord opinions over here.
It is a good way to put it.
I agree to Mike's credit.
I will say that
now when I ride the transformers ride, I do expect him to be like, I'm proud of you.
You know, like I
like, I do, like I do get emotionally impacted by that, like that bit of score.
Like I went and like
looked up that score, like to go listen to it later.
Like it's like, it's like actually really
music.
That end of the ride is like perfect.
What I wonder is how many people didn't feel
anything about it before, but Mike made them feel something.
You accepted us.
I, yeah, it would be
interesting to know who I would think of.
You've heard me talk about it now that you break into
like tears when you see this part of the ride.
And then I influence people by being really into
that one character actor who's in the, the Q videos that, yeah, the generals like evac, what are you
like?
Oh, he's in everything.
I love that guy.
He plays like Landry's dad on Friday night lights.
I think he probably plays everyone's dad on Friday night.
Like, he does play every football
player's dad.
That's just that good.
You know, he can, he can carry that many roles in a TV show.
You know, having not done Velocicoaster, I think I'm going guardians with slightly,
behind Hagrid's.
I am a bit, I want to represent Hagrid's here.
Yeah, Hagrid's also that drop.
Hagrid's is number two in the universal in the online.
Yeah.
And Velocicoaster didn't make it
to the four in the, so is that, is that heresy that in a little tournament that it wasn't in the top
two?
Well, isn't that also just people haven't gotten down to ride it?
Have they gotten it on it?
Are they scared of it?
I'd like to know.
They'd have to pass a test to prove they went on it.
There were a thousand votes in this poll, so you have a thousand answers to get.
That's fine.
The tweet us photos like Jason did.
Why not Velocicoaster?
Tweet us a photo of you on the
coaster like Jason has and prove that you are on it to be allowed to vote in the poll.
So does that
mean I'm not allowed to vote in the poll?
You're not allowed.
All right.
So my opinion.
Your opinion
doesn't count.
My opinion is dirt.
You have to ride a vintage Popeye Toon Lagoon.
I need to see
a photo of it too, to prove it.
Even if, I mean, I guess if I'm on it with you, I can, I will vouch
for you.
But other than that, I won't buy it.
Yeah.
You will have to.
It's only proof that you
didn't fly out of it and then somehow get back in at the very end.
Snap a GoPro that is reversed
to your chest with it's a little bit of a selfie stick on it.
Hopefully that won't impale you on
some part of it.
Requiem for a dream, you know, like that camera where everyone's like, yeah.
But it might be, I'm worried a bit, but you guys gave me hope that this might be something I could,
I could build up to.
I do think you could do it.
It's not going to be, you're not going to be
so calm on it.
No, no.
But that's not the goal.
But I just think that there's a couple elements
like that will be taken out, which is the roughness of a coaster like this.
My question is, do you do
it sober or?
Well, I know the answer to that.
Well, but then there's this dizziness because I
didn't want to drink before Guardians and I'm really going to drink.
Oh yeah.
Cause you guys were saying that Guardians got rough.
Guardians just not nauseating potentially.
It's high potential for nausea.
It handles you in a
different unique way.
Yeah.
It's like jostling your little belly.
It's like kind of like touching your
belly as you ride and like moving it around and stuff.
In five years, people might be more accustomed
to that as spinning coasters catch on more.
Like will evolve to be able to.
It will evolve.
Will evolve.
The Raptors did to get better at spinning.
So we'll be okay for the fast and furious.
Yeah.
Maybe one, maybe one glass.
I just need a little, one little hit of Kendall Jackson,
Chardonnay.
Let me handle that.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
I didn't get, I get a thing in the pit of my
stomach when I do the big upside down part on an Incredicoaster.
Every time now I just go like,
I can feel it like deep down there going like, and it's not crazy.
I'm not going to puke or anything,
but I can feel it.
It's really doesn't do anything for it.
For me, it's all like bigger drops and launch
oddly the spiral does nothing.
There's like a G force on and it's cause it's too slow also.
Yeah.
Slow upside down.
And I can feel it.
And I never ever had that feeling.
Well,
there's no longer the like late nineties, early two thousands calliope music to comfort you.
Yeah, that's really, yeah.
That was something nauseating about that.
Your father now you're so concerned about Jack Jack, you know, getting him
under control.
Yeah.
Of course.
I really now I go on a ride and stress about it.
Getting the baby.
Yeah.
That's a dream I have once a week probably that I've like lost to the baby.
That the baby has grown 10 sizes.
I haven't had that dream.
Okay.
That it's like that's a
large baby.
Yeah.
Stomper in Vegas.
But the amount of times I've half asleep,
tried to like go through the covers on the bed in the middle of the night to find where I put the
baby.
That's happened many times at this point where no, wait, I forgot to put the baby in the
crib.
Where?
Oh no.
Like just going through the comforter and like the different and then like
feeling like I've been looking for 10 minutes.
Oh my God.
And then finally kind of.
It's like
you're just going through the tunnel and then you pop out like in a different place.
Yes.
And then
going, no, the baby's in the crib.
Okay.
Well, now you know what it's like to really care for something
like Owen Grady and Blue.
Right?
I do feel more of a kinship with Owen now.
Yeah.
After this.
Or
Owen Grady and a clone child.
Yeah.
I'm actually going to watch that other movie.
Well anyways,
fantastic to talk about this for a while.
And here you're passionate, passionate about it Stephen.
It's lasted for a couple of years.
Your passion for Jurassic Park world in general.
Stephen Ray
Morris, you survived podcast, the ride.
This is a pleasure.
So it's so glad we could have you back
and let's let's exit through the gift shop.
Anything you would like to plug.
Thank you so
much.
Again, thank you guys so much.
I just really loved this podcast.
And again, it's always an
honor to be on.
Oh man.
Oh, well, and thank you.
Like, like if we, if we get tagged and see you
wearing a Chris Gaines shirt, or a launch queen or I debated wearing the Chris Gaines shirt today,
I would have been.
I love the shirt.
It picks a perfect shirt.
So many of them have lead painter,
micro plastics.
And you gotta be careful with those.
But thank you for your, for your support
and for being a great guest too.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's always, I mean, again, it's always when you
find a podcast that you love and you're just like, wait, somebody else like thinks about lost in you.
And ladies and gentlemen, you know, like, yeah.
But yeah, no, again, this is so much fun.
Yeah,
you can follow me at Steven Ray Morris and all the things, uh, see Jurassic right podcast.
And
then I wanted to mention, we're talking about, um, off mic, but I'm, uh, the next project I'm
working on is a step-by-step, uh, TV show podcasts, you know, the classic TGIF show from the nineties.
You have handled me with this information, Steven.
Oh my God.
Um, it's called, um, um, it's called
Kenan and Lakin give you deja vu.
And it's with Christine Lakin who played Al Lambert,
the sassy tomboy and, uh, Stacy Kenan who played Dana Foster, who was, you know, just the
every, you know, all of our teen crush growing up.
And I had crushes on all of those girls on that
show.
Like, uh, and Suzanne Somers rest in peace.
Yes.
Uh, it's, I always really loved that show
because it was like Brady bunch, but with divorce and it was just like, yeah, and they mixed it up.
Keep you on your toes.
They don't all, their hair doesn't all match.
Yeah.
Yeah, exactly.
And you're like, I still don't remember which family member, which kid goes, yeah, no, it's,
they mixed it all up.
But, um, but yeah, uh, yeah, I'm working with Christine and Stacy and the, the,
the premise of the show that I think is very funny is that Stacy was a, you know, too cool for school
teenagers.
So she never watched the show that she was on for seven seasons.
And Christine was a kid
and her mom was out here and she was just excited to be like in the first episode, they talk a lot
about like, oh my gosh, they're closing magic mountain so that we get to film this opening kind
of thing.
So she's that age.
You hear, you were saying there's a, but right off the bat, you get
a bunch of info about that, about the magic mountain.
Yes.
No.
Yeah.
My God.
Um,
and so, so she watched every episode.
So she was like the lore keeper with her mom and then, uh,
Stacy was just like, whatever nineties and like, so it got out of the business as a very successful
attorney.
Yes, exactly.
So their dynamic I think is just really fun.
And again, it's like,
you know, for people listen to podcasts, the ride it's the, you know, all the nineties,
you know, ephemera and goodness and pop culture and, um, yeah, uh, Kenan and Lakin Instagram
is the only thing that's up right now.
Cause the show is not coming out until March, but, um,
but placeholder with that get on that Instagram.
And then I'm going to do it for sure.
Love step
by step.
I just, I saw you just tweet about step by step and I can't believe how much backstory
there was to this.
Cause you tweeted something about, oh, it's, it's the best TJF show.
Cause
it's the horniest.
Cause Frank and Carol Duffy and summers, they're like, there's none of that.
They're not like lock horns.
They're like, they are into each other.
And there's con I feel like
every episode has some like, uh, why don't we play that game where you're the fireman is home from a
long sweaty day.
And literally the first episode, it's like at the end, the little button where
they're in bed and it's like the to-do list of groceries and stuff.
And she's like,
what do you like to do?
And he like wrote it down.
She was like, the kids could see this.
And he's
like, well, let's check it off the list.
And it's like, clearly he was writing the word sex,
you know?
And it's just like, you know, this was a sitcom that, you know, it was in the TGIF block.
It was 9 30.
It was the last one.
It could be a little body.
We can push it.
Yeah.
Um, I I'm so excited.
You were, you dropped this info before we started recording.
I had to collect myself to do the episode.
So, uh, can't wait for that.
I'll, I'll listen to all of
that.
Uh, and thank you so much for being here.
Thank you.
Uh, as for us, you can find us on the
socials at podcast, the ride, merch is available in our T public store for three bonus episodes
every month.
Check out podcast, the ride, the second gate, or get one more bonus episode on
our VIP tier club three.
You will find all of that at patreon.
com slash podcast, the ride.
And now,
and, but if you do any of that, please provide some receipts.
If you voted in the poll and have
been on Velocicoaster and therefore not qualified to just like give Mike your info, uh, so you could
just show your voting credentials.
Yeah.
And I'll, I'll write a whole form sort of to, to prove that
your opinion matters to me and it will be a questionnaire and I will be, uh, yeah, compiling
this and I think I will post it soon to know if you are allowed to vote in our future polls about
best rides.
All right, cool.
Well, fun recording.
Uh, I'm gonna, I gotta go fuck all of your moms.
No.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get
podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.