Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second portal?
I'm Scott Gertner, there's Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Oh man, Mike Carlson.
Hello, yeah, we're in the new portal.
We're all about portals.
It's portals now, apparently.
We're all doing portals.
Simply everyone is doing portals.
The other thing, not to just be so crazy out of order here,
circles, it's portals and circles,
and the portals are circular,
but have you noticed there's so many circles in this park?
Like if you look at it from overhead.
They haven't said circles though,
you're just saying there's so many circles.
Just look at this video, look out for it.
You'll see so many circles, like interweaving circles.
I was gonna say concentric circles,
but literally that is not true,
because concentric circles,
they have the same middle point.
So interweaving circles, that's what the carousel is like.
Suns, moons.
Yes, and it's celestial, it has planets around.
Exactly, they're very consistent with the planet.
Spheres.
Spheres, you might say, they don't say,
because there's already a big sphere in town.
But here, let's be very clear
about what we're talking about.
Thank you, audience, for being patient with us.
We thought let's just push it a day
so we can talk about what everybody was talking about
a few days ago now.
We told you we'd talk about something epic,
and here it is, the epic log flume,
epic voyage to moon haven at Genting Skyworlds Malaysia.
Let's talk about it.
We all saw the ride through Nimgaloo Animatronic,
and all of them are there,
the knucklehead worm guys or whatever.
I'm so sorry, I prepared wrong.
I watched all the epic movies.
Oh, shit.
Watched the epic movie timeline.
Oh, no, and I watched the YouTube channel Epic Meal Time.
Oh, no, good, no, that's right.
Oh, that's right, too.
I would have accepted it was gonna be
a half and half episode.
I hope we were gonna switch over to that.
Your shirt is disgusting.
It's covered in food,
because you said you were doing a mukbang right before this.
Yeah, I was doing a mukbang right before this.
That is what I said.
So yeah, I'm sorry I'm filthy, dirty with food.
It doesn't matter for your ears, I guess.
That doesn't matter, yeah.
It's just gonna hurt us looking at you.
we are downloading the big universal epic universe,
the epic info dump that they dropped on us.
By surprise, this is where we had to just react fast.
We had a block of episodes we were recording.
We didn't know in the more there was gonna be this,
like this majestic video, this lengthy,
very dynamic, moving, touching, tear inducing piece,
showing us so much more about Universal's third,
I say third park epic universe coming soon to Orlando.
Look, we are treated pretty well by Universal,
so I'm not gonna be upset or anything,
but we didn't get a heads up from Universal or anything,
and we didn't get any sort of special big box ahead
like some other people in the theme park space did.
I don't know if you know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, well here's what happened.
I got a text from Bethy Squires, hey Bethy,
and she said, did you guys get the epic universe mailer?
And I'm like, why yes, we did get an email with,
I don't know what I said to her,
but mentally I'm like, yeah, we got an email
with a bunch of concept art and info and restaurant names.
So yeah, we sure did, I said, and then she said,
yeah, I'm worried about this thing in an earthquake.
And then I had to analyze what that meant.
Wait a minute.
You got something that's so massive
that it might hurt you in an earthquake?
She got the miniature Kronos?
She got, and yes, the miniature Kronos,
but there's nothing miniature about it.
This is a gigantic, this is a chest.
So I had to figure out via context clues,
oh no, we did not get the mailer.
How did we get on the Kronos thing?
I don't know, I'm not sure.
Jason texted me late last night
that we didn't get a Kronos,
which I had already seen, was already upset about.
I'd already was stewing about it
and I expected us just to talk about it today.
But yeah, people got a giant,
I wanna say it's like two feet tall box,
like a wooden box with one of the like,
like the main entrance way.
The main portal to Epic Universe.
But only the medallion for Celestial Park,
the landscaped area, the center of the park.
So this would be like,
as if you got like before Islands of Adventure,
you got the like entrance way to Islands of Adventure.
Can you imagine what that would have been like
if you have like a miniature Islands of Adventure entrance?
As I'm wearing a shirt of early Islands of Adventure
promotional art, yes.
I could imagine.
We were denied.
Bethy is the first person I've heard in California get one.
Jason was she the only in the state?
Jason was thinking it was a local thing.
Cause I was seeing all the Orlando vloggers getting it
and I'm like, well, maybe it was a local drop off.
Mr.
Morrow got it, I haven't texted him about it,
but I do wanna see where everyone's setting it up.
Times like this, you just have to be thankful
that we know so many Kronos getters.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, what is that,
we live among high society,
even if we are not them ourselves.
Did anyone put it up on eBay yet?
Let me look.
Yeah, I'll set up that alert.
Cause I do want it, I have a big toy wall
and I really could use a Kronos.
I also, yeah, absolutely.
Oh yeah, more than anyone, you need it.
I also, then we walked into Forever Dog Studios to record
and the person behind the desk was like,
oh, you guys got something.
And I was like, here it is.
And instead it was something else.
It was a care package from Canada.
Forgive me, listener who dropped this off.
Whatever it is, it's nice.
Don't know if, I haven't gone through it yet.
But it's a bunch of like Canadian items
I'm gonna have to show you guys after this.
Oh wow.
I'm sorry, I can't do the full download and thank you.
I'm still processing this,
but it has a bunch of maps for that Edmonton mall.
Oh yeah.
Which I believe is mentioned on tomorrow's episode.
A little preview.
So anyway, we got a bunch of cool stuff from Canada.
So things are going our way.
Thank you for that.
Thank you Canada.
But I did have to go, I was like,
Kronos, is it Kronos?
Oh, it's not Kronos.
It is not Kronos.
I said it to Jason, I was like,
I guess it's because we're not,
we've done video in the past,
but we're not known primarily for video.
So they probably thought it was a waste.
But still, I don't think we would be on a list.
I don't think any calculation was done.
I don't think anyone said,
should we send it to podcast the ride?
Those audio goons, that would only be a waste.
Yeah, maybe that didn't happen.
If we weren't even on a list, a long list,
and then we were edited, it was edited down,
I would be a little upset.
So you like the idea that we were cut.
Okay, would I like the idea that we were cut
more than just ignored?
Yeah, I guess so.
I guess I would, yes.
Better to have loved and lost.
Yeah.
But we should have three big boxes
with three Kronos's here, right?
We all get it, we aren't sharing.
I hate to be a baby.
Here's the thing, I'll pay for it,
unless it's like a grand.
Might be, this is so big.
I'm starting to exactly clear on what's in it.
I mean, I assume it's gotta be some amount of work.
Okay, if anyone, okay, here's,
I'll throw two offers out right now.
Someone, if you got one from Universal,
make me an offer, and we'll see if I'll pay it.
Number two, if anybody works for Universal,
I'll also pay it.
This is like Chuck E.
Cheese when you go and ask
if you can just buy one of the prizes.
Yes.
And not get it with your tickets.
So if somebody wants the back channel at Universal to me
and offer me an amount of money, I'm listening.
My DMs are open.
Our DMs are open.
This is your chance to get to shake down
Mike Carlson for cash.
You can try shake me down.
I might be shakin' downable.
It's possible.
Because I don't know, will they sell this?
Is this part of the gift shop coming soon?
Like will that be a thing you can buy?
I don't think so.
I feel like if it is, it's gonna be a tiny version of it.
It's not gonna be.
How many people are gonna want a big weighty?
Would they sell all of the different portals?
The Kronos?
I mean, I hope so.
They're already iconic to me.
I agree.
I'm excited.
I think the portals are one of the big excitement points
of this.
If you can't picture what we're talking about also,
I mean, it's like a giant lighthouse,
but kind of more mystical.
It's like a, you know, like a tower, a temple tower.
There's a big circle where you walk in
and then on the top, there's different like kind of artifacts
or things that suggest the land you're going into.
That's the different portals for the different pieces
of the different parks or the different lands,
I should say.
I mean, that's one of the big pieces of info here
about this park.
I think that, you know,
there's a lot that we've known about it.
I think I even sent some disappointment out there.
Like, what did this tell us?
We didn't already know.
We knew there was gonna be Harry Potter.
We knew there was gonna be How to Train Your Dragon.
Well, I think a lot of specifics did come out
and obviously there's been like flyovers of it,
the bio reconstruct, the drone footage.
So there's a lot vaguely that we knew,
but I don't think we knew the root of it, the heart of it
and what ties it all together.
Like the premise of the park,
I don't think was clear until this, at least not to me.
There were pieces, but yes,
this really like gave it to you, I feel.
And the connective tissue that is the,
not just, you couldn't even just call it the main street
because it's kind of this like bigger land
that weaves through the entire property.
That being the instantly iconic Celestial Park.
Celestial Park.
It's really the big thing to talk about.
I think my number two land I'm most excited about
because I think they say,
do they say in that video
or is it some other social media posts
where it like, it puts the park back in theme park?
It puts the park.
It's in the video.
And so to me, it feels like going all the way back
to the beginning of the show when we were,
I was coincidentally finishing Devil in the White City
as we were starting the park.
And that was so much about the world's Columbia Exposition
in Chicago in the late 1800s.
And they followed the Frederick Lowe Olmsted,
the father of modern landscape architecture
and the center of this park is so much greenery
and waterways like it reminds me of that.
And it's a good reminder of like,
yeah, some of the design stuff
for these public private like entertainment places,
it doesn't really change.
The greenery and water are always.
Don't reinvent the wheel you're saying.
Yeah, don't reinvent the wheel.
Hopefully it's good for people's like, you know, mood
because these rides will likely be very popular.
So you're saying Celestial Park is gonna be a calming park,
a place for dad who might be upset with the long lines
and then the disorienting VR on the Mario Kart ride
to come and chill out in a pleasant space.
Kids screaming cause they got menaced
by Victoria Frankenstein.
Right, she gave him the business.
Yeah, no, I think you're right.
I think that that.
There's beautification going on.
Yeah, I think that this, especially at night,
I feel like this thing is gonna be really cool at night.
Oh yeah.
Nice little hang.
That restaurant seems nice.
Yeah, it looks out onto it.
All of them look pretty good.
All the restaurants from what they've shown
look pretty good.
I mean, really like what, I mean, it's very,
it's Epcotty you might say,
but maybe even more kind of like that you get to,
really the big difference is a lot of,
and both of the existing Orlando Universal Parks
have big lagoons.
And this has some of that,
but maybe there's more space that you can actually go into
and chill out in.
That's kind of the difference, you might say.
It seems like a much bigger scale of like
the new Epcot future world,
like sort of green spaces and public seating.
Yeah.
So are you saying that maybe Epcot's new
world celebration space with its benches
where you can plug in USBs might struggle to compete
when this gigantic new beautiful theme park opens?
Oh, they got double the amount of trees and USBs.
They might have USB-C ports by that point.
They didn't even say what type of ports they had.
Yeah.
It was all about portals and not about ports.
Does port of entry have ports?
That's a good question.
Are there any ports?
There might be charging lockers.
We really should have figured that out
when we did the episode.
That would maybe have changed my opinions early on.
Mm-hmm.
That would have put you in a better mood
for you to sell on the whole thing.
That any type of phone or electronic device
could be charged efficiently there.
Do you use those Target freebie charging lockers?
I have, but that's a big pain in the ass.
It is, because I put my list on my phone and Target app.
I have coupons.
I think they pulled those things,
at least from the Burbank Target.
There used to be, you don't know what Jason's talking about,
there would be these little lockers.
And let's keep the focus on the Burbank Target
as much as we can also.
Just a three square mile, right?
Yeah, yeah.
They're also having to restock their NECA toys in months,
and I don't know what's going on with that.
Yeah, they took those lockers.
But yeah, you could put your phone in there,
you would charge it, and it would lock up with a code,
much like Harry Potter lockers or something.
And I don't know, I'm never in Target that long.
Only if you need.
Sure.
My phone was dead, I would do it,
but I have a charger in my car.
How often would you do that?
No, never.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, no.
This whole conversation has been about something
you don't do and don't like.
He brought it up.
That's what we've been talking about.
I was wondering,
because I never see anyone using it.
No, I hate it.
Yeah, me too, okay.
That's why it was taken away.
Nobody cares about it.
We have a new theme park to talk about.
We're talking about lockers that we don't like.
Well, and the Circle app.
And this Target, well, Target Circle app,
I could speak about.
Oh boy.
There's no way we have other circles to talk about.
That's not what we're here,
those aren't the circles for today.
That said, I'm lost.
I don't remember what we were talking about before.
We were talking about the ports.
We got caught on ports.
as I just did a post that was like,
hey, episode's gonna be delayed today,
but what do you think?
Questions, thoughts, concern?
I sense some general feeling, Jason, of like,
this isn't what the listener said exactly,
but everybody thought of your affection for port of entry.
And I think there was maybe a feeling of,
do you feel threatened or insulted by this new space
trying to take the crown of best universal entry area
from port of entry?
I think more what I was focused on was like,
wow, the last two new theme parks I got to experience
when I was a child were Animal Kingdom
and Islands of Adventure and later on, California Adventure.
And that made me go like,
yeah, no one has opened a new theme park in Orlando
since 1999.
Well, we're taking the recent Peppa Pig Park
out of the running.
And I suppose Volcano Bay, the water theme park.
Well, it's third gate, yeah, of course.
So yeah, look, this is obviously going to be the star.
It's part port of entry, part city walk.
It is a classier city.
I hate to insult the beloved city walk.
Well, I think by invoking the word classy,
you've clearly indicated this is not part city walk at all.
Well, but there's a fountain
and there is retail space and dining.
Yeah, but it's not the same.
I mean, I guess it's got a couple rides.
There was the promise or the possibility
of like truly another city walk.
And this is not that, let's be clear.
Celestial Park is its own beast.
Because I don't think it's a city walk
unless it's outside the gate.
I guess that's true.
You have to pay to get into Celestial Park.
For a while there were some rumors of like,
oh, it's going to be free.
Yes.
And I guess they really haven't said that for sure.
They don't say anything about that in the videos,
but I doubt that's going to happen.
Too confusing, I would think, to like have to be scanned.
Now those portals are terrible.
Like there's a big line to get into all of those.
Forgive me.
There's an Alicia Stella podcast
where they were maybe speculating
that like after a certain amount of like time at night,
maybe it would be free to get into just Celestial Park,
but I don't know.
There are, yes.
There's a couple.
So it does seem like that would be nuts if it was free.
It's a tad complicated.
That's, yeah, that's a good point.
It's not just vibes.
There are attractions.
There is the dancing fountains.
We're mentioned, don't worry folks.
There are dancing fountains still
in this new innovative zone.
And kind of listed it as a ride.
They refer to it as astronomical.
Yeah.
So when you see astronomical, that equals dancing fountains.
And they said like three attractions, I think,
and they said that.
Fountains are wild.
So the fountains are included.
Well, that's wet play,
and presumably the others are dry play.
They did use the phrase wet play in one of these videos.
It is a wet play area.
Is that the only wet play that's been announced for Epic?
You know, I don't know that there's any other water rides
over there.
Sound off in the comments, listeners.
What's your favorite wet play area?
And don't forget dry play.
Well, that opens it up.
Yeah, so this is, I guess, right now the only wet play,
because the rumor is there will be a creature
from the Black Lagoon.
Indoor boat ride.
Like a boat ride coming eventually,
or it's on the Blue Sky phase.
Well, that sounds like wet, but not wet play.
I guess you're, well, it depends if you're playing,
if they encourage you to do a little splash in the water.
Can't imagine.
All right, everyone.
Splish him.
Splash him.
Only you can stop the creature.
Reach out of the boat.
Not too far, though.
Lost another kid.
Yeah, so we'll see.
Maybe that's an element they could add.
If it hasn't been, they're not building it yet,
so it's possible.
Constellation Carousel.
Now, this is something,
I watched this with my wife Erin last night,
and she, after all, after the buildup,
you basically, in this video that they released,
you get the full history of the resort and the company.
We reached out to the fans and what do they want,
and they want storytelling, and they want,
and then, once they got into what is it,
she was kind of like, oh, a carousel?
After all that, a carousel?
And I did go back and I said, well, I hear you on that.
However, I think that Constellation Carousel
is no ordinary carousel.
You can tell, I think, just from the art,
and then they indicate in the description of it,
I mean, this seems akin to some weird track list.
Like it's somewhere, it's like the Mater,
or maybe more like the,
one of the Luigi's reliquing roadsters.
Luigi's, yeah, roadster, reliquing roadsters.
Or like somewhere in the Aquatopia realm,
because it has this weird future, heavenly vibe
that everything has, but I think that not only
do these cars go round and round, up and down,
but I think they go on different tracks.
They do, yeah.
Maybe it's trackless,
and then they rotate, and this seems like
a real reinvention of the carousel, I hope.
And there's colors in the ceiling,
or there's some sort of thing happening, I believe,
in the ceiling as well.
This is the beautiful,
kind of like, yeah, like the skylight thing.
Lot of color lighting.
One of, what you bring up, there's a,
I don't have the exact dialogue,
or the exact thing that's said in the video,
but it's like, we asked our guests,
what do they want from Universal?
And they said just more of the same like,
magic that you offer us.
And you're like, that didn't happen.
Like they didn't.
What, the focus group?
Yeah, they asked people what they wanted,
they'd be like, I want more Harry Potter, please.
They would say, everyone's not like,
ah, do you know the little pixie dust
that you leave on my nose every time I,
I want more of that whimsy, and more of that.
No one's saying that.
They're going like, I like Spider-Man.
Could we have more of Spider-Man?
People give specifics.
They're not saying.
The special magic and storytelling that I get
from Fast and Furious Supercharge.
Right.
Somebody's going like, I want more Dom, please.
I want to see Dom.
I want to meet Dom.
Like people are probably giving some specifics
and not just saying like, well, giving you like,
ah, the little, the unicorns,
the magical unicorn rides that are so special.
By the way, is Fast and Furious done?
In Orlando?
No, no, the movies.
Is Fast, that's the last one?
There's 11?
No, are you kidding me?
No, I lost track.
I forgot.
God, I never watched nine, so I haven't watched 10.
There's no, that's not gonna end.
Nothing is going to end.
If something is popular, it will not end anymore.
Oh, good.
So it's like comic books just act two forever.
The office ended, and I pray every day
that we finally get the reunion news we've been waiting for.
It's been like, they're doing it.
Is it official?
Well, Greg Daniels has assembled,
he's assembled a room to come up with ideas
for the new office.
Because it wouldn't actually be the old cast.
It might.
Or some, or I don't know.
It would probably be some.
Yeah, yeah.
Might be some.
How will they get them?
They're all so busy with projects.
On the concert, they're busy.
Some characters probably still, you know,
got telecommuting contracts.
There is probably mere meters from us right now.
There's a room that's being convened to under,
to try to figure out what the next.
To right this wrong of what?
Like seven years with no office.
So there will be more of.
Nothing will end anymore.
Nothing ends.
It's all eternal now.
That's right.
Let me, so what you were saying about kind of
the tone of the video.
We got some really good questions and comments,
and I'll try to pepper them in through the episode.
Maybe do a bunch at the end.
This is from Chad H.
And I'm calling you Chad H.
Because I'm gonna butcher your last name.
Let me, let us know how you pronounce your name.
Because I think we have to say it.
Because I think you won a poll recently, Chad.
Yeah.
But anyway, what's your favorite bit
of over the top language from the video?
I got so happy when they said,
the overarching emotion that Epic inspires
is what it's like to have your wishes ultimately fulfilled.
Absolutely my answer.
And Jason and I re-listened to the video
on the way over here.
And I also pointed out how insane that is.
I got in my car and I, or I got in Mike's car.
He picked me up and I was like,
is he listening to like a motivational speaking book?
Why did, what is this?
Unlock your potential.
And then yeah, they start talking about the ministry of magic.
And I was like, okay, now I know what this is.
Your wish is fulfilled.
Ultimately.
Well, there's something later.
This is like in death.
This is like when you die happy.
There is something later in the video
about the thrill of being alive or something.
Yes, that's my answer, Chad, is how they close it.
Which is, yes, that you get, it's basically,
that ultimately this park is where you get to experience
the full thrill of being alive.
Which is ironic, cause the universal monsters,
so many are undead.
There's so many thrills when you're not alive.
I mean, this is crazy.
As Chad says, they're finally, they're getting Disney-esque.
And I feel that throughout this video piece
and look it up at listeners if you haven't seen it.
I mean, Epic Universe, I forget the name,
but you know, Epic Universe reveal or whatever.
You'll find it from the last couple of days.
But not only tone and that insane,
and that it's stuff about wishes.
Like they're going for Disney territory.
And not only that, but we're getting into this zone,
and I'm glad they are, they deserve to be,
where the universe has been at it so long
and they just improve and improve.
And I think, and they're going for heart and nostalgia.
And they're showing you, and I felt it,
cause this is my, I wasn't around in the 50s,
my nostalgia is Universal Studios Florida
with that logo and that fountain as teased
in Nickelodeon shows and Spielberg cutting the ribbon.
And so that old footage was giving me a lot of
like nostalgia feels.
And it just, I'm like, this is, they are not letting,
they're trying to conquer Disney on like
the one thing Disney has, which is nostalgia.
And you grew up with this and your parents grew up with it.
And look, it's Walt in the map.
Is there's Walt in the map?
There's Walt, do you know that before they built it
that Walt was like walking along
and counting the steps himself.
And Universal's like, fuck that.
We don't need Walt's to give people nostalgia feelings,
especially because our quality is so much higher
than what they've been doing lately.
They also have, this was in the Vlasa Coaster special too.
There is some sort of drone footage over the lagoon
at Island of Adventure that makes it look so awesome.
Like I was like, holy shit.
I've never seen that angle of Island of Adventure.
It's like fast drone footage.
And I was like, man, that got me both times I saw it.
Hearing that from you who adores Island of Adventure anyway,
that felt like a moment of like, we're just one morning,
you've been married for 30 years
and you just, you to your wife out of nowhere.
Just like, you know what?
You're really beautiful.
I'm just in the kitchen.
Yeah, I know, but you are.
And don't forget it.
It just hit you on.
Yeah, yeah, it just hit you in a way.
Just a little moment of love.
It's you.
I mean, I do try to also do that to my partner.
I do try to do that for normal things in addition to,
oh, I think they launched a drone by Mythos.
What a unique angle to capture Island of Adventure.
Island of Adventure is more of your mistress, I would think.
Or your, oh, what's the word?
What's the word you've been saying?
Parmore.
Jason's parmore.
I was almost said side piece,
which is another thing Jason likes to say.
But parmore.
I don't think I said it.
You love to say the phrase side piece.
I don't think I said side piece in a number of years.
You said it on the show recently,
like in the last year, I think.
I may be the first to say,
yes, Jason says it every episode,
but it doesn't sound familiar lately.
Here's what I'll say.
He has said it on the show.
Maybe it's been in the last two years
because time has fucked up for me.
But it is, he said it in the last year or two,
but there was a time in this man's life
when he was saying side piece all the time.
And if he pretends that's not true,
then he's a freaking liar.
I think he usually said it in a facetious manner.
Well, I didn't say it wasn't facetious.
He was joking.
I was never quite comfortable dating.
I was never comfortable on dating using dating apps.
He did not have a side piece.
Were you ever a side piece?
Were you the side piece?
Not as far as I know.
I'd love to discover that it turns out I was.
Yeah, so no, he was being funny about it,
but there was a time in our lives
when he was saying that a lot.
But he has said it on the show.
Let me tell you that about a year or two ago,
I learned, you know,
Jane and I had been dating for quite some time,
and at some point I learned,
wait a minute, people talk to multiple people
at once on these dating apps?
You didn't know that?
The people were not committed?
I thought, no, not committed.
I thought it was disrespect.
I feel like maybe if I was talking to multiple people,
it's like, because one went silent and someone else.
But I was like, wait, how many people are like,
I didn't know multitasking was a thing to do on these things.
I think people do it with dozens at a time.
I have not ever been on these apps.
I don't know anything about them,
but that doesn't surprise me.
I've been in a relationship
since before there were dating apps.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, wow.
So you're the man who knows the most,
but apparently knows the least.
with somebody that they seal that up.
All right, no more messaging allowed until you,
until you, it's like closing a job
in some kind of file system.
But it's like, wait, people,
yeah, I didn't know until I was pretty well into my 30s
that it's like, wait, people date multiple people at once.
Now I've heard everything.
That's progress for you.
This is like, my dad did this.
My dad in the 60s dated multiple people.
My mom would be like, oh, so are you exclusive?
Like she would say that word.
She would be like, oh, are you exclusive?
I go, oh, yeah.
Yeah, I've said that word too.
I don't think exclusive is the most behind the times.
No, I'm not saying it is.
I'm just saying that, I'm agreeing with Scott
that that's an old time thing that you're talking about.
You're talking about the new version of it
where you're just chatting with multiple people,
but in our parents' day,
that was just called dating around or not being exclusive.
Dating, that's a good way to put it.
Yeah, now are you, do you think that would have been
overwhelming to have to deal with
that many personalities at once?
Potentially, or I feel like the more awkward thing
would be like, oh, remember that thing we were joking about?
And you go like, oh, that was the other.
Oh, you'd forget who you were talking to.
Yeah, I forget the other.
I was like, oh, this new Succession show
is pretty interesting.
You know, oh, fuck, no,
I was talking about Breaking Bad with them.
I was talking about Succession with someone.
Oh, no.
This hypothetical dating app conversation
is sparkling.
It is stressing me out,
actually, right now.
All right, well, yeah, let's not stress you out forever.
Wait, she doesn't even have Macs.
She couldn't watch Succession if she wanted to.
This is great.
Anyway, but like they say in this video,
what you don't have to worry about is,
with all the Universal parks now,
you spend a full week just at the Universal,
those hotels and resorts.
Well, that's a real gauntlet they threw too.
Universal is saying this.
I'm so sorry, this is a very important joke.
Universal is no longer the side piece.
Universal is your main.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's what they're saying.
You DM on the side with Disney
if you're just sowing your oats.
Yeah.
But now, yeah, Universal is your main.
Hey, that's how I felt for a little while, my man.
They should market it that way.
Disney, I hope you like being a side piece.
Yeah, yes.
Or just like, if they just like,
if it wasn't tracked to them,
and just like, there was a billboard
next to like the exit for Disney,
pointing at Disney, and it's just an arrow
that says side piece.
Now that would be throwing it down.
That would be throwing it down.
That's not the, they don't wanna use language like that
when they're trying to inspire
and tug on the heartstrings, our nostalgic heartstrings.
So I understand that, but maybe they can make
some like cruder videos
for a different section of the audience.
Yeah, well, and that's where you bring us in.
Well, of course that's where you bring us in.
It's a whole different,
they've got like these two guys called like the Ride Guys
that are on YouTube that do all their rides now.
It's a little too close to the title here,
which even though I know those are generic words.
Yeah, Ride Guys, podcast the ride.
It's basically the same thing.
Basically the same thing, I don't like it.
I thought you were gonna say close to the Try Guys,
and they are certainly trying things.
They are trying things.
Like all the great attractions, the Universal, or whatever.
If I was a Try Guy, I would wanna sue them, but I'm not.
And now a serious message from the Ride Guys.
There's like two of them.
There would be one left.
We, I mean, I am committed to providing
the great Ride Guys content, even though Barry,
Barry the Ride Guy had a side piece, okay?
And unfortunately, he's been fired.
I saw them kissing at the top of Rip Ride Rocket.
And unfortunately we had to,
we threw him off the top of the Velocicoaster.
We're so far off.
So I will point real quick, nostalgic stuff.
Having a discussion with somebody about this,
that like Universal, like,
or I guess we've talked about it a lot too,
where it's like embracing the 30 year olds stuff
and the little kid brains of us kids
and who went at that time.
And they are doing it.
I do wish there was a little bit more
of an actual presence of that stuff.
I know people have said,
and I'm sure multiple people have,
and I'm not stealing one person's idea,
but like, one of these lands should be classic Universal
land, that would be almost the ultimate
new Back to the Future ride or something.
Have we ever said that in an episode,
that if there was, I mean,
I think we have, yeah, for sure.
This would be a killer fourth park idea
that one of the little, one of the lands,
one of the, whatever you wanna call it,
is just like, that Back to the Future is there
and some new version of Jaws and some,
just pick the three that are the most unimpeachable.
Yes, so that's the only thing that missing
because if they had,
ET is the only thing that's left
and it's in a weird part of the park
and I'd almost propose now to build up that land over by ET
into a full little ET with the magic of the forest outside
because obviously it's still stuck in a big soundstage,
but if you could really even dress up the outside of that
to make it feel more Disney and like,
oh my God, we're going into the forest
and it's hard thematically with the Steven Spielberg stuff.
But this is where I think part of it for me
is the soundstage.
The fact that it is just the way that it was
and I like those pink stripes
that the soundstage used to have
and they're disappearing.
There's very few of those pink stripes left.
I think, you get your forest inside.
You have to go through some double doors
in order to get to that forest.
You're right.
I guess what I'm saying is that Universal has nothing
that's almost authentically left from the early days.
They still have the tiny replica
of the Gardens of Allah apartment building.
Oh, what?
The Gardens of Allah,
this was in Los Angeles, I think close by the 50s,
but it's right in Universal.
There is a neon sign that says Gardens of Allah
right by ET, like by that quote, Central Park area.
Really?
That's one of the like old Hollywood,
oh, I kind of recognize it now that I'm looking at it.
Yeah, visually the building, I think is-
Spanish colonial revival building.
And there was some AT&T exhibit in there.
All I'm saying is that like,
unfortunately so much of the old stuff is gone.
All they really have left to point to
is like the Universal sign and like the globe and then ET.
And I just wish they still had some of it
to really kind of highlight when you go to the parks.
And obviously the way they could do it now
is what we were saying with like a new land
that had classic properties.
You gotta spend more time at Lombards at Richterberger.
Yeah.
That's true, that is the silly old school feeling.
I hear what you're saying.
What are the three that if like, you could, would you do,
it's Back to the Future for sure.
Somehow Jaws, why not?
I know that's complicated, but-
I mean, Kong, Kong I think always had the longest line
that I remember.
Just bringing back the old Kong
in some smarter way.
I know they have the new Kong,
so like I guess that wouldn't make sense, but still.
Not Twister Rided Out.
Probably not Twister Rided Out.
Twister Rided Out kind of was, I was like,
I don't know, like I was enjoying going on old school rides
last time we were there and which, you know,
there's not that many.
Men in Black is honestly, I know it's not original,
but like I like that it's still, it's very 90s feeling.
Yeah, yeah.
But I was leaving that, thinking like,
I could really go for Twister Rided Out right now.
I was really hankering for it.
That's not probably the mass site.
You know what, I would accept just a room that I walk into
where I watch those Bill Paxton, Helen Hunt videos,
and then I don't do the attraction itself.
Sure.
But I could also do that on YouTube on my own time.
Like even just, and they never did this,
but Ghostbusters ride.
Like why not?
Like that, and that could be a dark,
that doesn't even have to be that expensive.
Even just something, I mean, it would be expensive,
but not expensive, expensive.
Like even just something that invokes the feeling
like it would have been there,
but obviously it's a high tech version of it.
Yeah.
Like, just yeah,
Ghostbusters Back to the Future is something else.
These movies that also will never die,
even though Back to the Future,
we've said this a hundred times,
that it will be, they'll remake it when Zemeckis is dead.
But like why, yeah.
Something like that, that's so popular immediately.
People would be going nuts for that,
just because it's not in,
well Ghostbusters is in the theater soon,
but like that just makes too much sense to me to do.
And maybe, and they're building aggressively,
so maybe this is on the drawing table somewhere.
That's a matter of, I mean, yeah,
because the universe is all about change.
They don't want to get like locked in time,
like frozen in time.
You don't want the park to become some kind of,
I don't know, frozen empire.
You do not want a frozen empire.
One thing nobody wants is a frozen empire.
There's an ice, it could be an Ice Age,
says Dan from the trailer.
Suck an Ice Age.
We've been on tangent so long,
we have not talked about the roller coaster Starfall Races,
a racing coaster, and it looks good, I don't know.
Looks cool.
Supposedly, yeah, there's some like lights
on the coasters themselves, the trucks, excuse me,
the vehicles themselves, I think.
And then there's like a place where
it goes through some smoke,
there's like a little hole that goes into,
and it's got smoke.
There's supposed to be like comets or something.
That sort of vibe.
Yeah, there's a statue
of like a falling star or a comet or something
that the coasters go around.
So it's supposed to look,
probably especially at night, it'll look like it's,
you know, shooting stars or comets or something.
It is funny to me that the movie studio based,
the theme park coming out of movie studio
has now with Celestial Park done more original rides
and lands that non-IP than Disney.
Disney has not done an original one in ages.
Yeah, that's true.
Yep.
Yeah, Starfall Racers is not,
there's no movie called Starfall Racers.
There will be after the popularity of this.
No, this whole thing is kind of this like,
I like Island's Adventure before it,
besides the obvious IP in there,
the fact that there is some like original worlds
as Lost Continent and all that.
Yeah, I don't know.
You're right, it's cool.
They are not, IP is obviously the base of it
and like half of it, but there's a lot that isn't.
You're very right.
And they have a lot of,
and I say this in the best possible way,
they have a lot of nonsense kind of backstory
going on around this place, which I like.
Well, yeah, because you enter through the Kronos
where all of the planets will align.
So remember that, you're not just going
through the turnstiles of a park,
you're entering the ultimate portal
and all the planets align upon your entry.
Right, so exciting.
That's good.
And then the hotel, a hotel?
It's a 500 room hotel, Helios Grand, huh?
Sounds like a good hotel.
No, it is not just a hotel.
It transports you to a world
where the heavens and earth unite.
That's what I said to Jason.
Well, that's what you said.
You were trying to see if there was another place.
Helios is the god of the sun.
Yeah.
We were looking this up on the drive over.
Helios pulled the chariot from east to west.
Helios moves the sun with like a big chain or something.
I don't know.
Whoa.
He moves the sun.
Helios makes the sun his side piece.
That's right.
Literally next to him in the side.
I think him and the sun are end game.
Oh yeah, they're in it to win it.
So the heavens and earth align.
So again, heaven exists in Celestial Park
or multiple heavens.
What kind of heavens?
This is Greek.
It's Greek and there's multiple.
All the ideas of heaven.
Yeah, so a certain kind of heaven exists here.
And it looks like there's a bar at the top.
There is a rooftop bar.
Looks like there's a lounge or rooftop bar.
Which I guess will get you the closest to the heavens.
Yeah.
Which is nice.
That's right.
Talking about classic Disney,
believe it was theme park stop.
Someone was posting about how,
or it was by a reconstruct.
The rooms aren't modular like the contemporary.
However, they appear to,
the bathrooms appear to be pre-built and slid in.
There is a company that makes,
they prefabricate full bathrooms
and then they slide it into the hotel room.
And you can see in the construction photos right now.
They're sliding bathrooms?
They're sliding bathrooms.
Wow.
Sliding the bathrooms.
That's cool.
Hopefully they secure them
so the bathroom doesn't fall out when you're going.
Whoops.
Well, that's, yeah,
that's a fear a lot of us have probably.
That one of the bathrooms in a hotel just slides out.
Just slides fully out the roof down many stories.
Oh no, I'm falling right into Blue Dragon.
What if Beethoven has his leash connected
to one of those bathrooms and it's not secured
and he pulls the whole bathroom out one day?
Remember Beethoven from Beethoven 2?
Yeah, when he, yes.
I posted this on Twitter recently.
He yanks the supports of a big douchebag party
and saves a girl from an assault.
Even though he didn't, he doesn't know she's in it,
but I guess, but he knows.
He knows.
So what if he has.
He's getting a bad vibe from upstairs
and also, and they're pouring beer on his face.
This is one of the finest scenes in movie history.
This scene, as a kid, seeing this scene was as memorable
as the most famous scenes in cinema.
This stuck with me for a long time
and it still is with me today.
He does the big yell, not the Wilhelm scream,
the Howie scream, which is so much better
than the Wilhelm scream.
It's the yeah.
It's the most.
He flies out.
Oh, it's the, yeah, there should be an attraction
based on this.
That's my only, that's my plus up.
No Beethoven presence.
No Beethoven, yeah.
And that's universal.
It's sitting right there.
Yeah, so that would be nice.
Yeah.
But yeah, all the restaurants, everything, I don't know.
It seems like it's gonna be pretty good to hang here.
Let's talk some portals.
What are the lands called?
Is it land?
The portals take you to worlds?
Worlds, universes?
Worlds, yeah.
I don't know.
You know, we knew the basic shape of these, I would say,
but that doesn't mean we don't get some new info.
For example, we knew there was a How to Train Your Dragon
area, but I don't think we knew.
We were going to Isle of Berk.
We did not know.
We're going to Berk, baby.
Berk, baby.
See you in Berk.
Yeah, Isle of Berk.
I assume Berk is the place from the movies
that I've never seen.
And we'll never see.
And maybe, well, I have a child, so maybe.
Yeah, but there's a lot of kid stuff to watch.
There's a lot of kid stuff.
There's no guarantee I'll ever make it.
These ones are supposed to be pretty good, though, right here.
Okay, well, if they're pretty good, maybe I will see them.
I guess maybe before I take her to Epic Universe,
we'll have to watch them.
But yeah, that's a specific we didn't know,
or didn't remember.
It's possible it's out there, I don't know.
And they say you'll be able to ride on the top of a dragon,
that's what they express.
Now, there's some cynicism in our comments.
There's somebody, and this struck me, too,
where you're like, is this a little bit,
is this gonna be a little bit Flight of Passage?
Well, that's, yeah, I don't know.
Because there are building a roller coaster there
that you can see on all the aerial photos.
Oh, it's another coaster, okay.
But I don't, I think what they're talking about
is a different, yeah, it does seem like there's gonna be
like a Flight of Passage type ride there.
Is there?
Am I wrong?
I saw Hiccup's gliders, Hiccup the main character,
in these movies, in the new Alicia Stella video,
she's like, there's trains on the track for the coaster,
but they're all covered,
so we can't really see what they are right now.
So you're saying there's not like a big screen ride?
Yeah, I don't know if there is a big screen ride.
There could be.
So when they were saying ride on the back of the track,
and they just meant this coaster.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I genuinely don't know.
I think I know a lot of stuff about this,
and now I'm realizing I guess I don't.
Yeah, the most unknown to me, this area, I think.
Well, yeah, they're still being, you know, we haven't,
they certainly said more about everything in Celestial Park.
These, the specific attractions,
we didn't get a lot of new info on.
They really don't say, they very clearly just refuse
to give details at this stage about the new ride
in Wizarding World, Ministry of Magic.
Yes.
We don't know what that is.
I said the most daring thing, their most,
the biggest risk they took,
including snippets from the Fantastic Beasts movies,
which recently described, I believe, as on ice,
is the Hollywood term in the trades.
Like they are, we're not doing four more of these,
like we said.
Enter the most cursed world there is.
Yeah.
I don't, you know, I'll be interested to see
what the big ride here is,
but it doesn't seem like they're doing
what I'd like to see them do with Harry Potter,
which is trap J.
K.
Rowling
in a windowless soundproof box forever.
Like they did to Lane at the end of Mission Impossible 6.
Oh yeah.
Or five.
Or the Magneto Prison.
Or the Magneto Prison, yeah.
Or the plastic prison.
Or where the Superman 2 villains, you know,
where they like tumble into space
in those diamonds forever.
In the, not the negative, the negative zone,
Jason, help me out here.
Negative zone DC?
Yeah.
What's the other one in Marvel?
The micro, for micro-noids?
In front of the micro-averse?
I'm looking at something else, I think.
Well, the point is, Universal's about great storytelling,
and I think they could concoct a pretty great story
for something that could happen to J.
K.
Negative zone is Marvel.
Oh, the negative zone.
What, the Phantom Zone is DC?
The Phantom Zone is DC.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
And the woke zone is our current world, right?
K.
waited on something about that.
It's just a shame she fell in that well,
so really can't make out what she said.
What's that?
Oh, and you don't have Twitter down there?
That's too bad.
I'm not going to look up a website called Mumsnet.
That's not happening.
I don't know what that is.
Well, that's the news to me.
Oh, that's England.
Weird stuff going on over there.
All right, I don't know.
There's dark stuff.
Yeah, that's not going to that portal.
It's funny that all of this stuff is so exciting
that by the time in the video, and we're bringing,
this is loaded, we're bringing a lot into this,
but by the time that they say,
we've got Super Nintendo World, it's funny that we're now,
we're probably all now a little like, okay, yeah.
Yeah.
You know, I hear you.
I wish that wasn't the feeling.
I know, I know, I know.
And, and, and to give them some credit,
they're going to have Yoshi.
They're not going to screw us like here in Hollywood
and not do a little, the funnel Yoshi.
Right, right.
And then, and then Donkey Kong,
and they make a point of.
And that's the, yeah, that's the,
I'm holding out hope, yes, that Donkey Kong is the thing.
I'm worried.
I'm worried about it.
It's, but it's, the pictures look good,
and they cast the moves somewhat fast,
like fast, 10, 15 miles an hour.
I get, yeah.
It can't be two miles.
It can't be as slow as Mario Kart.
The jumps, they're going to be jumps.
Yeah, but what if.
The big robots.
I just, I just feel so.
I know.
Let down by.
I know, but I'm holding out hope
that that one is what we want.
Yeah, yeah, but either way, I mean, like,
with a little more space to breathe,
and that being like, I mean, that's also the gauntlet
that's turned down by this park, where like that's,
Nintendo has just won four expansive,
five expansive new areas, as opposed to Hollywood,
like all this buildup for Hollywood to get it,
and then it's just like, it's a miniature version of it.
It's really cramped in there.
It's kind of unpleasant in there.
It won't be like Hollywood.
They just should not have tried to jam Hollywood
into that space.
Ultimately, that's the mistake.
Probably, yes, I agree with that.
Or they got to kick the voice out of there.
Stages, you're out.
The voice is pretty far away.
It's all the way practically by the
part of the bed sheet.
Doesn't matter.
It's all gone, all of it.
They got the voice.
Anything close to it.
It's a- Not making movies in TV there.
It's an animal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's your big mistake.
That's really the mistake.
And then, I mean, I think the highest excitement
has got to be for, and the end of an exciting moment
in the video is the official reveal
of the monster world name, the classic monster realm,
which is Dark Universe.
Yes.
Dark Universe is officially back.
They've reclaimed the title for the series of films,
the Univer- Yeah.
The MCU of monsters that never happened,
that was just teased with Tom Cruise.
And a photo shoot.
And that photo.
That one weird photo shoot.
Yeah, yeah.
Angelina Jolie, Johnny Depp, somebody else?
Russell Crowe in there?
Somebody else, I think?
Imagine, imagine what Depp could have done for us.
Depp.
The woman who was the mummy, right?
Or is it Penelope Cruz?
Oh, maybe Penelope Cruz, I don't know.
So they don't say much about here,
but it's certainly a big part of the excitement
of this video that there's the quotes from Frankenstein,
you're hearing it's alive,
and you get some sense of the castle.
Not much is said about the ride.
I might have a complaint here.
Well, Jason and I have a complaint, too.
I wonder if we all have the same complaint.
Maybe the same as you.
Well, you guys go for it.
Mike phrased it best, you say it.
Well, what did I say?
I don't even remember how I phrased it.
You said Dracula does not have a cape.
Yes, and my version of this is why does Dracula
look like he's in my chemical romance?
I saw somebody say that as well.
And I said why does Dracula wear a track jacket?
So all the same.
Dracula was in Crush Groove, I didn't know.
I just think that classic Dracula
with the big medallion on his neck and the big cape,
I feel like that design is just untouchable
in terms of costuming.
There's something about the quality of video
where they showcase the new looks for the monsters
that is a little unpleasant.
Yeah, I think they all look a little dumb.
Maybe Wolfman's kind of whatever.
That's like basic Wolfman.
Frankenstein looks a little goofy to me.
I thought that, too, and then I went back
and I'm looking and I go,
Frankenstein looks fine, Wolfman looks fine,
but this Dracula bothers me.
And he's wearing a drum major's outfit or something,
like a dark drum major's outfit, like the Black Parade.
We've all written jokes for Johnny Carson.
We gave him all different, okay,
here's three different jokes on the same idea.
When Johnny Carson is gonna do a bid on,
when he does a bid on the new Epic Universe video.
I don't know where Conan, I was just picking a late night.
Late night shows that are on.
No, we're J, we all wanna write J.
Still have a name for them.
The Dracula joke.
Seth.
Then Gordon, Ferguson.
Ferguson.
Yeah, so I mean that's so, I just give them a cape.
That's like, it's fine, I understand the difference.
Give them a cape, they can change that.
They can give them a cape.
That's not set in stone, right?
The cape's not gonna interfere
with whatever the ride is.
Give him like the crazy spawn CG cape.
Well that's okay, if we wanna do something like.
That has a mind of its own.
Yeah, if you wanna do that, I'm all for that.
It's like kind of a living cape, that would be cool.
All eyes are on this costume, because this would,
we've been looking forward to this land a lot, I think.
Yes.
I don't want it to be undone by 2005 emo goth vibes.
I mean, in the right lighting on the ride itself,
maybe it's not as big of an issue.
Maybe if he gets shocked by like a Tesla coil,
if he gets electrocuted, the track jacket becomes a cape.
Maybe he was in a drum, he was in a marching band,
and he got struck by the Tesla coil,
and he became Dracula.
Okay.
Maybe there's a new order for him.
Lightning shot through his tuba.
Right.
And went right down his lungs.
So, this is, did they say the name of the,
I know the name of the ride,
but did they say it in the video or am I?
I don't know the name of the ride.
The name of the ride, you know that you've,
am I crazy?
I think this is from Alicia Stella videos.
Cause she talks about the spinning wolf man coaster.
It is a very modern title.
I believe it is,
Monsters Unleashed the Frankenstein Experiment.
Okay.
Which is like,
Not super.
It's not such a punchy.
You gotta start tight.
Space Mountain, y'all.
I know, I know.
That's what rides are called.
Monster party.
Monster Mountain.
I'd be happy with Mountain.
Monster Mountain is awesome.
Monster Mountain's good.
Yeah.
So, yeah, it's Monsters Unleashed,
the Frankenstein Experiment.
The new, is it a new,
have they ever used a female Frankenstein,
Dr.
Frankenstein before?
That's their new thing here.
Oh, I didn't know that.
It's a Victoria Frankenstein.
I'm assuming it's going to be a granddaughter,
or a descendant, maybe?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know if this is like,
the descendant restarting all of the monsters,
or bringing them all back.
Yeah.
Or if it's a full new origin,
as if they're being created,
like in this day and age.
There was that rumor for a while,
that there was like an Elvira type character
around the land.
I don't know if that's involved.
They didn't say anything about that.
I don't know if that was a blue sky,
but they have revealed a few characters now
from Dark Universe,
which are the three monsters,
and Dr.
Frankenstein.
I mean, it seems cool.
I'm definitely, I got an open mind.
It seems like they're gonna do something cool here.
They show the mansion,
or they show whatever the ride itself,
I'm sure the outside of it.
And yeah, the rumor of course is Kuka Arm,
scary dark ride.
All right.
I hope.
Are you doing it?
What's that?
Are you doing the ride?
Yeah, I do Kuka Arm.
What are you talking about?
Yes, I do rides like that.
Well, it's scary.
Well, but it's scary, it's spooky.
No, I don't even say that to be a jerk.
That's different than,
in a ride, I know what's happening.
That's different than haunts.
Okay.
Give me some, give me my credit for that.
It seems like the way people have been hyping it.
Am I not gonna do that?
The way people have been hyping it up
seems like it might be scary.
I would be a little scared to go on it.
Yeah, I'm a little scared of it.
If they do what they're talking.
But it seems like, you know,
maybe that's akin to the Harry Potter, which is Kuka Arm.
It's possible.
And been very scary at times.
There was a, supposedly they were running it
and that like, this is of course,
what probably always happens where it's like, it's scarier
and then they're like,
we gotta turn some of the lights on a little more.
Oh.
So we'll see.
Oh, interesting.
That was a rumor I had heard.
Yes, is that, yeah.
The restaurant bar, I think is the windmill,
the flaming windmill.
Yes, the windmill.
The flaming windmill.
Frankenstein.
Okay.
There's like a bar, yeah,
and the windmill will be on fire as it's spinning.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know this.
Yeah, it's really, that looks cool.
Wow.
There's, yeah, the Wolfman roller coaster that's pretty.
I didn't know that either.
I missed all these, dude,
because they didn't say anything.
This is still the one for me.
Yeah, that's just unconfirmed.
And then at the end of this, talk about iconic characters.
Then you get, the end of this big video,
I think what really landed big for everybody
was a guy we haven't seen in a while
talking about the Universal Parks, Mr.
Spielberg.
I know, I was just asking somebody,
I go, do you think he's even like,
looked at any of these plans?
And then here he is to not necessarily confirm that,
but at least.
They filled him in.
Yeah.
Steven loves portals.
He's obsessed with the idea of these portals.
He can't wait to go through the portals.
He says something that seems mildly dismissive
of the portals, or just that he's like,
he says like some kind of portals or something.
There's a little qualifier.
Portals, Steven.
It's portals, it's full on portals.
He's not wrong about it.
He just like, he goes,
eh, it'd be some kind of portal you go through.
Again, he probably, he was debriefed very quickly.
And none of his movies are in here.
None of his properties are here.
That's a first, I guess, for Universal probably.
I guess that's right, yeah, because Jurassic Park,
and then obviously the stuff in the first park.
Unless you consider these portals to be kind of terminals
that take you from place to place.
I guess I would consider them terminals.
Portals are terminals.
I wish you mentioned it.
But yeah, you get to experience
the full thrill of being alive.
Clearly the presence of Steven mattered to people.
I think this guy Mark Woodbury, who narrates it a lot,
he's becoming this kind of like roadie Baxter,
kind of like you clock him.
He's compelling when he talks.
The whole thing, just tonally, this video's very cool.
It was a very good hype up, got me excited.
Maybe I'll run through a couple questions or comments.
Let's see.
This is from David.
Hey gang, thoughts on this being the first off property,
quote unquote, Universal Park.
I'm hearing 10 to 15 minute drive,
kind of akin to pop century to magic or animal kingdom.
Can their highly rated transportation
keep up the reputation with the new challenge?
We're kind of getting into,
and I think they're trying to build some new roads
or some new private roads, but at some point
you're just gonna be on regular Orlando roads,
and that's a little bit of a concern.
Hopefully it's smooth.
That's the tricky thing, because people argue,
I've gotten into some big fights lately,
some mild discussion about Disney Universal.
Some people feel we're too kind to Universal recently
about it being like the energy's there and we're excited.
Disney still has the magic, be this person's point.
And I said something earlier about
Universal's doing better stuff than,
we all love Guardians of the Galaxy.
It's a Mario car, didn't necessarily meet our expectations.
So of course Disney's still got it.
I try, I really like trying.
But I do think Disney, the thing they have,
a one up that's gonna be hard to beat,
is that you drive into the middle of the swamp woods
to get to Disney World.
That feeling still is hard to beat,
and it's still what's doing a lot of the heavy lifting,
I think, when people talk about
Disney World Magic Universe versus Disneyland.
Because that's what my mom will be like,
oh I like Disney World, but Disney World,
and it's like the idea of driving into the middle
of nowhere and then there's the land there.
That is gonna be tough to overcome.
Not being out on the roads.
Well, you know what, I think you just gotta rethink how you,
you know, you're probably not doing days
where you're bouncing between studios,
Islands of Adventure, and Epic Universe.
I think you just make, all right,
we're doing the Epic Universe sojourn,
and we're just gonna get some outside Orlando,
and you're not immersed for that part.
I know, so it'll be fine.
I'm sure they'll figure out an efficient way
to get everyone places.
But the Disney bubble, the parks can decay
another 50 years in Disney, in Disney World,
but that bubble, I think, is what people hold onto,
and even sometimes in more ways than actually the rides.
Greenery and waterways go a long way.
I feel like I have a discussion with a lot of people
where I go, Disneyland is better than Magic Kingdom,
and they argue with me, and then I go,
but look at the list of what you can do
in Disneyland versus Magic Kingdom,
and then it's like, oh yeah, but nobody thinks about it.
I think they just are like, I'm in the bubble.
I like the bubble.
Yeah, actually, the buildup is part of it,
as opposed to, and if you live in California,
it's hard to, you mean the place where I gotta do
kind of a smoggy drive, and I'm mad,
I'm in a parking garage, and then the castle's small.
But if you get past those things,
and just think about what really,
how packed it is in the history.
Yes, so that is the only hurdle Universal has,
is not having a bubble.
Yeah, that's the only hurdle to me.
I really wanna stay in this Helios Hotel.
Yeah.
500 rooms is so few hotel rooms.
Is this thing just gonna be booked solid for two years?
I probably, or are they still gonna be building awareness
of it in a way?
Like, potentially.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I think you're right.
It's either fully sold out, or they have to get people used
to the fact that you can stay on that part of the property.
Because when we went down, I mean, again,
I loved Sapphire Falls, it was awesome.
And the water taxis, huge plus.
But I ended up there because I was like,
well, Road Pacific is booked.
Well, what about Hard Rock or Portofino?
Totally booked.
And I'm like, it is, we went in early November.
Well, I'm sure this is gonna be booked solid.
I'm just curious what it'll cost.
The ones across the street also look very fun.
Yeah.
The reflective and the space screen windows.
Seeing how crazy Disney got so fast
with all their top hotels, I'm like,
they could probably charge something like 1,000 a night.
But I also wonder if they'll try to not,
so that they don't get into Disney territory.
At least not right away.
I mean, I think probably it would book up at 1,000 a night
if it's only got 500 rooms, especially opening
like the first year or two.
So I wonder what they'll do, what strategy they'll take.
I don't know.
Jake D, let's just do this quick.
Which land are y'all going to first when you get there?
Oh, that's a good question.
It's interesting, we haven't talked about,
cause like the idea with this place is that you cannot go
from land to land once you're in one of the lands.
You have to go in and out the same way.
Oh, I see.
There's no like transition from land.
So you have to come back out into Celestial Park.
You fully go explore over there.
Right, which I've heard is like easy
if somebody wants to just buy Super Nintendo,
like a company wants to buy Nintendo land for the night.
That's cool, you can fully just section off that.
So yeah, so like for corporate events,
you can just buy pieces of it and it's easier
and you don't have to watch as many people coming in and out.
Monsters, the answer is monsters.
The answer is probably monsters,
but wouldn't you maybe want to save dessert for last?
So maybe I go to the Burke, I'll Burke first.
Or are you like Jason and you save dessert
for every meal?
Dessert components for every beverage.
I just go to the lighters all day.
Homer with the rotting sandwich green over the garbage can,
but it's just me with like small bites
of like two some hanging on.
I don't want to let go of chocolate bread.
Oh wait, to that end, Kate Mollo,
which land does Jason think will have
the best treats and snacks?
Ooh, ooh, ooh.
That is a great question.
I think I know the answer to this.
Do you?
Cause now I'm thinking about this.
I think it might be Celestial Park.
Cause they have like moonshots.
What are we talking about?
What's it called?
Like a bakery or something?
The sweets, the candy shop,
like right at the entrance.
Maybe even outside if you look at the art.
I was just gonna say like Harry Potter ends up having
seemingly the best sweets I feel like in the park.
The most variety.
Yeah, I guess so.
Like the ice cream in Diagon Alley is just really good.
But it does seem like Celestial Park is gonna be,
like they're thinking of that in a Main Street way of,
that's where the stuff is.
That's where the relaxing stuff for the grownups is.
Some table service, some quick service,
some stuff that was left out of that video.
Alicia Estella's, I believe most recent video,
she's like, okay there's a restaurant coming,
or two restaurants maybe.
One Mexican, one Italian.
And then there's another that I think is not on the
concept art cause it's just like ground being broken.
Oh okay, gotcha.
I will say for all the Nintendo complaints,
I think Nintendo treats have been pretty good.
They've seen that good.
I think there's new ones just introduced around here.
I think there's a whole separate cafe there.
For this one, you guys are gonna have to open your email.
I've sent you something because this comes from Kevin Tully.
What's up Kevin?
Please rank the portal towers, beacons, spires,
whatever they call them, from least favorite
to most favorite.
At least first.
This is a very good question.
Because yeah, they are all, all right,
so there's the unified premise of these big circular tubes
that take you into the lands.
So it's all, and there's like one round kind of icon
up at the top.
And then yes, they have these spires that kind of
thematically introduce you to what you're gonna be getting
once you're through the portal that represent their IP
but that also blend in with the celestial park around it.
I've got an order in my head, but do you wanna,
should I go or do you guys have a?
You go first.
You go ahead.
I think I know.
From least favorite to, and I'm trying to not do this
based on like property, I'm really trying to judge
the spires themselves.
That's what I'm doing as well, yes.
And not bring my feelings about the IP into it.
However, gotta say Potter is last.
Ultimately, that's just, that's a big pillar.
It's gonna be, it's a cool look, it's gonna be cool.
But it's like it's a hand with a wand.
Least good, I agree.
Fine, whatever.
Dragon is third and I like this.
This is kind of a, yeah, I don't know,
this is kind of some mystical mixed with some like
Disney Discovery Land kind of feel.
And then also around it too, there's like either greenery
or like around that one are hills kind of terraced
in a very like Disneyland Paris castle way.
So I think that's good.
Nintendo is too, love those pipes and the flower
and the coin and stars shooting out of them.
And Dark Universe is, that's what I think.
Awesome, awesome.
Zappin' lights, gonna be so cool at night.
Yeah, that is true.
Anybody disagree with that order?
I personally, I would probably swap, and this is just me,
but I would probably put Dragon at two
because I like those hills.
And that portal, it's got a little bit of Lost Continent
Port of Entry flavor that I hope.
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah.
So, no shade to Mario.
I'm loving Nintendo stuff recently.
That's a really good entry.
Oh, and it says, here we go on it.
There's little inscriptions too.
I don't think we can read all of them.
Here we go might be my favorite part of that.
Yeah, I miss, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That makes me wanna notch it up even,
but I think it's Monsters still.
Is that my, wait, let me skim through these.
Oh, important one from Nard.
If the park is underperforming in its early days,
could we see the Sacred Hearts band coming in to save it
like they saved DCA?
Nard is, of course, referring to when
California Adventure opened in kind of an underwhelming
fashion, they had to plug in some stuff, some concerts.
The Beach Boys were drafted.
Mike Love was called into service, and not long after,
the second best band to the Mike Love Beach Boys,
Jim Belushi and the Sacred Hearts.
I say don't even wait, just have them play the opening.
Get the Belushi spirit, get everybody dancing,
because if this is about where the heavens meet the earth,
what's more heavenly than the pipes of Jim Belushi?
Can he wear a Mario outfit?
Can he wear the overalls or something
while he's performing?
Yeah, I think he's gotta wear the overalls and the hat.
He pops up out of, Jim Belushi pops up out of a pipe,
and he's like, I'm a soul man.
Here we go!
Sweet.
It's a me, the Belouche!
What if he gets it wrong?
What if he yells, here we are?
Here we are!
People will forgive him.
OK.
Here, we're gonna do it!
Is there a musical venue for Celestial Park
for bands in the 90s to play?
Oh, that's an important question in any universal planning.
I don't know.
Can you put a stage out in the lagoon?
Marty Graum moves to Celestial Park.
Yeah, OK.
Sugar Ray 311, you know?
But should it be like
Beats Bad Foodie Daddy, they all get in there.
Could you do another flavor, like, spacer 90s music,
or more electronic 90s music?
Like the real McCoy or something?
Oh, I'm in now.
Yeah.
That sounds great.
But even like Aqua.
Yeah, yeah.
Aqua.
Yeah, what's the band that did like
Saving town, six underground.
Oh, yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, I know what you're talking about.
I'd like if they play, I'd be there if they play.
Hataway, you know?
Just any sort of like electronic or dance music from the 90s.
Doesn't have to, yeah.
Sugar Ray, keep Sugar Ray at City Walk.
But a different flavor of 90s.
Sure.
Should be playing at Celestial Park, I believe.
OK, OK.
So still, yes, still kind of out of it music.
But let's
Yes.
Theme it a little bit.
I don't know, sneaker pimps?
OK, all right, OK.
I'm not sure exactly.
I'm calibrating what kind of music.
No, we're just doing, yeah, we're just doing brainstorm here.
Yeah.
Well, I think that's the bulk of it.
Also, the big Kronos tower that showed up, it had a poem on it.
Bethy pointed that out.
Oh, wow.
I was mailed a box with a poem.
Let's hear this.
Nice note to go out on.
With sun and moon, the stars and time, the Kronos spins and worlds align.
For if you seek the curious heart, your compass true and stars to chart.
Beyond this gate, find gardens green and epic worlds to fill your dreams.
Wow, that's good.
Yeah, it's good.
I like I like where they're headed with this.
I like the it's fully it's fully embracing magic.
They're coming for Disney.
They're coming for Mickey's snoot.
They're rubbing Mickey's snoot in the dirt with all this stuff.
Yanking him by the snoot.
They're yanking Mickey by the snoot.
And shoving it in their big circles.
Disney is going to build the Tiana ride and then do nothing.
Nothing else for.
Yeah.
But who knows what lies beyond frontier land, not the houses,
but in front of the woods.
Who knows we could do bulldozing these woods?
That's true.
So this D23, you say something, say something specific.
I don't know.
Yahoo and The Washington Post had an article the day that this all drove
like here's what Universal this is Universal's press today,
but this is incredible new park.
On the other side, this article,
Disney trips are so complicated now that you need a class to plan one.
Yeah, it's not wrong.
And there's just there's so like, look, the company is not in great shape right now,
but there also is just an enormous amount of hubris from Disney.
That this is this thing going to change.
We've got the foot.
Whenever we need to remind people where they belong, we've got the footage of
what and the map.
Yeah.
What point of the map?
Tell me it all began with a mouse.
Yeah.
So walking along the empty orange groves.
They'll they'll fall in line.
Why?
They'll fall in line.
That is a stupid poem.
Who said that?
Who said it all started with a mouse?
Well, fucking Disney.
That's who.
You know what?
Me.
You're you're insolent.
You're you're fighting against us.
Universal, we're coming with both barrels.
Eternals, too.
This whole vibe, this epic universe vibe is very eternal.
And it is very about it.
Maybe there's a lawsuit.
That's how they strike back is with a lawsuit.
That's true.
Yeah, they could get them.
And then they but then they own then they own that park and it all becomes Kingo land.
Oh, yeah.
Well, Bob Iger, probably he's just meters away from us.
He probably heard that and he will now sue.
Yeah.
Universal, you start you'd better get in fighting shape.
You getting as good a shape as Kumail because we're coming for you.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Be begging for that Frankenstein.
Reanimate, reanimate.
And if we get done with you,
you'll be undead soon.
Well, hey, exciting stuff.
Thanks for bearing with our little delay so we could talk about it.
You survived podcast the ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the second portal.
Let's let's now go out of the portal
and back into the the main.
If you want to join us on the main portal tomorrow,
a long overdue return of a beloved guest.
And you're going to get that ad free if you bump it up to our VIP
Patreon tier club three,
which also includes one more bonus episode every month, which you help select.
All every one of these tiers is like the heavens and earth
you will find.
So obviously, the higher up you go, the closer and closer you get to
the heavens, the heavens, multiple heavens.
Club three is really where you're going to feel those heavens.
So, yeah, do it.