Five, four, three, two, one.
Hey, welcome to the PTR post office, the first all Patreon edition.
We're doing it fully on here.
That makes sense.
That guy, the last time we did this, we asked like,
where do you want us to do social media stuff?
Clearly no one could decide if they're doing blue sky or threads or nothing at all.
But the one thing that was loud and clear is that it makes sense for you guys here on Patreon to ask these questions and to do it here.
So thank you for making that loud and clear.
And also, this is actually a PTR post office.
There are no, I don't have suspicious surprises around the corner this time.
Unless you count the big octopus that's coming in right now.
Whoa, it's the 20,000 leads under the sea big octopus.
You did it, you bought it and you hit it all these years.
That's right.
Here, bring him in and he's gonna, Jason, he's gonna take you to task for pronouncing moho pork wrong.
So, all right, let's settle in for the next 40 minutes of that.
And no, that's not, no, we're, it's real.
It's questions.
Yeah, we're doing it.
I'm a little bit shaky here.
I'm just saying.
Of this nature.
I'm a little bit on edge.
I didn't sleep last night.
I don't know if it's happened yet.
I'll just say this in this one instead of the other that I text, I forget if the audience has heard this episode or not, but I just had a really nice Disneyland visit or California adventure visit with my family.
And especially enjoyed going on the red car trolley.
And right after I texted you guys, hey, I'd like to order up a red car trolley episode.
Yeah.
And Aaron was like, they're going to think you're up to some shit.
Oh yeah, that is a good point.
They're gonna be like, why are you all of a sudden asking for red car trolley?
You have pretty glowing things to say about it.
I did, yes.
And I think you'd know I'd be a little peeved.
You're like, I like the trolley.
I have a lot on the trolley.
Yeah, I gotta be careful.
You know, it's gotta be like an impartial party.
Because I remember when I used a lot of the Spider-Man episode to show a clip of Mike on Mansers and you were like, after 15 minutes, you were like, I should note this is my favorite ride of all time.
I'm like, no, no, no, we'll do it.
We'll do it.
I forgot about, I truly had forgotten about that.
But yeah, that sounds like me.
Stay away from everybody's.
No nonsense on everybody's area.
And I won't interrupt what the listeners, what the audience wants to know at this point in time.
Do we got anything loaded up?
Oh, question wise?
Top question waiting on Jason.
You were all like, I got my screenshots.
There's a lot of good questions.
I got my screenshots and I had a pinned note, but I was gonna drink a sip of water.
All right, here.
Put it down.
Don't prioritize water over audience.
I'll give her the priority because I had it ready to go last time.
Marnie Shore.
Oh, hey.
You know, right.
Marnie Shore asked, would love to hear your thoughts on the rising trend of Instagram trap experiences.
Museum of Ice Cream, WNDR Museum, Color Factory, et cetera.
What do you guys?
Well, I don't know anything in that list, to be honest.
Instagram trap experiences, she said.
All are like pop-up photo, like background places.
Disney had the one in the old ESPN zone for a while.
You know, the original, the location of the original Disney store in the Glendale Galleria, not far from us, turned into like an Instagram museum for a little bit,
which I think I thought about letting my kiddo run around for a while, but those are, it depends.
Boy, they'll price those things.
They'll gouge you on those on these on the Instagram traps.
That's for sure.
There is one in the Burbank Mall that it's like it's so I don't know what the price get in is, but it is like the size of like it may have been a former Claire's.
Like if you can imagine how compact Claire's are and I can't imagine Claire's at Burbank Mall closing.
There must still be a Claire.
But I'm using that.
Just a Claire shape, you're saying.
Yeah, it is like that compact.
Like they could barely fit the big pair of lips or whatever in there.
I went to something I accidentally stumbled into something that might qualify as this also with my son.
There's kind of a charming not not Claire, but Montclair, a town not far from here, as a little.
They've got this swing space that was built out of a former Costco that is now all of these little temporary exhibits.
There's a dinosaur thing that's why we went and that satisfied a dinosaur loving toddler.
But right next to it, we weren't even planning on going to something called Bubble World that looks completely like dumb Instagram trap.
And I was I was avoiding my son even seeing this like I don't want to pay for this.
This seems annoying.
And then he kept like bubbles, bubbles and like, all right, fine, let's do it.
But I, dude, I think you're going to be kind of a frady cat and not want to do anything because I've seen billboards for this.
This is like a big ball pit, essentially, but maybe a little more art directed.
So I'm going to pay so much money for you to do nothing.
And then he proved me wrong.
He went apeshit in bubble world.
It was one of the best father son times.
I guess, you know, there were parts of it that were kind of like little insta traps were like here being a bathtub full of rubber duckies with like 100 rubber duckies and that stuff, whatever.
But a gigantic ball pit for families to go in that like looks where you feel like you're in a CD rom from 1992.
It like brought something out of him.
He was much crazier than usual.
Really?
That's just diving it.
I had to stop him.
We don't know what's in there.
Don't just dive in to the bubbles without we know nothing.
I don't think you're allowed to dive.
We just didn't.
Something took him over.
Yeah.
So I will.
I'll say nice things about bubble world if I'm getting the name right.
But do you guys have experience with anything of that nature?
Yeah.
Lindsay had a rap party for Infinity Train or whatever.
A premiere party.
I don't know.
I remember there was some sort of party at a very Instagrammable place on Melrose or maybe La Brea, somewhere around there.
That was like kind of a fruit based Instagrammable plate, like a photo app.
And I am like a sucker for just like a room with some weird music and mirrors.
Like if you put some mirrors and lights in a room and you walk around like, oh yeah, I'm good.
Like I'm not saying like, oh, this is my favorite thing ever.
But I kind of think I'm easy when it comes to some of this stuff.
Now, this was a party, so I didn't pay like $50 to get into it.
And maybe that would influence me more.
But I don't know.
I mean, taking a picture in front of a big thing I like.
And that's kind of the premise or bigger unusual thing I should say.
I'm catching up on what Marnie sent because I have not heard of WNDR Museum because we're not in a city that has one.
Chicago, San Diego, Boston looks like the Boston one.
Here's a bunch of orbs in a mirror room.
So you're happy, Mike, with that?
No, it's good.
I'm good.
And I think like money wise, yeah, if it's like $75 to take a photo in the mirror room, I'm like, I don't necessarily need to do that.
But more more nonsense is always good, I feel, don't you think?
And it's nice to in a world where with dead malls and where we're losing space, like doing something with it and doing something that is an experience.
I mean, I'm sure you're going to get good ones and bad ones.
But I certainly like physical experiences still existing and filling the like incredible amounts of void that we have for various reasons in the 2020s.
I think that's that's what I could say is like, well, at least it's helping struggling malls stay afloat.
Like, I think even one of the ones like Concord Mall, which I grew up going to in Wilmington, Delaware, which seems to be doing pretty well.
Got some press a while back because that is where the perfectly preserved Burger King is.
If you remember that, like someone like who worked there, like when in it backstage or broken or something.
And it was just storage, but it was a perfectly preserved like Burger King from the 90s.
Oh, wow.
And I was like, man, that looks like the Burger King that I remember going to with the Concord Mall.
And then it turned out to be the Burger King I grew up going to at the Concord Mall.
Yours was the one.
Yeah, the one.
Yeah.
I was like, I think I saw Toy Story and then to eat lunch at that mall.
Wow.
At that Burger King.
But even they, I think it opened some of these Instagram things.
I think it's so funny to me when they are referred to as museums.
But yeah, they're probably not for me, but like they're actively not for me.
They are for younger people.
I bet some people would be, some of these would be for you.
Some of them might be for me.
Let's just brainstorm real quick.
What would a Jason Sheridan go to if he saw, like if it was like Cookie World or something.
And there were big cookies and you could like kind of go in there and it's like you're the mouse from if you give a mouse a cookie or something.
I would say when that Museum of Ice Cream one opened, I was like, I didn't see anyone actually eating ice cream.
I feel it's just like.
Well, that's a good plus for your version of this.
Oh, different ice cream.
Jason's Museum of Ice Cream is what we should do.
Dreyer's has one room, Breyer's has another room, Blue Bonnet gets one.
Oh, so it's a corporate kind of thing.
It's a sponsored.
Well, I think they ought to band together.
Okay, so it's for the common good.
For the common good.
The general theme of ice cream.
Yeah, Ben and Jerry's.
So it sounds like actually you just want to open up a big ice cream store.
Yeah, I guess I could just go to the aisle of my local supermarket and get what I'm looking for.
Because I'm picturing like I'm picturing the photo op.
It's you and the big waffle cone with the sprinkles on the side and the frosting.
But what you're picturing is just a bunch of ice cream brands opening up little stores in rooms.
Yeah, little taste like little tasting in each room.
Because like what the big ice cream cone with sprinkles like is that just dirty plastic?
Yeah.
I'm watching a bunch of I'm watching people at Museum of Ice Cream, which was that ever in L.
A.?
It's currently New York, Chicago, Austin, Singapore, Miami.
I feel like I saw somebody go there.
I feel like there was one a few years ago.
Maybe it's gone here now.
But I'm watching people slide into like a big pit of sprinkles.
But you want edible sprinkles.
Yeah, I want edible sprinkles.
No other riff raff coming in there.
Like you buy an hour, you get the hour.
Those are fresh sprinkles that only you can consume.
It sounds what you want is a strip mall full of different ice cream brands having their own stores and all the stores are free.
Well, even just root like little.
Yeah, it can be samples.
It doesn't have to be full.
I mean, I also in the brief sizzle reel I'm watching, I do think that people are eating ice cream.
Oh, that's good.
I don't think that you may have been judging off of several photos that you saw.
I think it'd be bizarre if there was a museum of ice cream in which you didn't eat.
I'm also seeing the word unlimited.
So let's not judge this ice cream museum until in New York, Chicago or Singapore.
Jason, get to Singapore.
I do want to go.
I will take a lot of I would like to hit it's there for a few more months that this is more of an art exhibit.
But that Luna Luna Park that Drake bought, which is like a simulation of a theme park, but it's like all rides designed by like Keith Haring did one.
Basquiat did another.
Yes, and it was all like it was in storage for a long time and just so kind of preserved.
It is interesting.
But I think unless I'm wrong, you can't go on these rides.
You can't go on the rides.
No, they think they want the urgency.
Little delicate.
No, I want to break it.
I want to break the Basquiat coaster.
Yeah.
Would you rather do that, Scott?
Or would you not go?
Sea rides you can't go on.
Or would you rather ride a big ice cream cone like a horse?
Because you can get on the big plastic ice cream cone like a horse in my version.
Yeah, I think I'm I think I'm after that.
And after my fun ball pit experience, I'm a doer, not a watcher.
Right.
Yeah.
Oh, and and the shackle.
We you were you were going wild on that.
I sure was.
Yeah, Shacktoberfest.
Shacktoberfest.
Excuse me.
Though that is what Aaron was exclusively calling it Shackleween, as as was I around the house as well.
That sounds different Alexandria.
It is.
It's a it's a fun.
It's a fun, purposeful mispronunciation.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Hmm.
What else we got here?
Yeah, let me do this.
Let's see here.
JJ Sigler asked if you could build your dream park using five lands and areas from any theme park in the world, which five would you choose and why?
So this is something I've been thinking about for years.
I don't know that I'm going to work out some of my math on the air, but this is fun to sort of like choose your own like pieces for your own theme park.
So I think I'm starting.
I don't want to steal some of what you would pick, but I have to start with Marvel Superhero Island from Islands of Adventure.
Sure.
That's my number one.
Would you agree that's your number one?
I think that's my number one, too.
OK.
Is there anything?
Maybe we could do this all together.
Like, is there would you say Port of Entry?
There's no fucking way that's going in mine.
But go ahead.
OK, fair enough.
Like, I know you guys like the Marvel you grew up with, but where we talk with one of the best five lands on Earth.
Not what the question was.
Yeah, you're right.
It's yours.
It's our personal.
Well, that's why it's not going to mine.
Yeah, so that's OK.
But no, I'm not putting that awful port of entry in mine.
I just want to make sure that's clear.
Whether I was going to pick Port of Entry or Hollywood Boulevard from Hollywood Studios.
OK.
Because I like the Golden Age of Hollywood.
To my my way of thinking that the mashup element is more fun.
So I don't want to even put Port of Entry there just because it's too much like Islands.
And because you hate it.
And because I hate it.
It's a vile place.
But are you having to lagoon?
This is too much Islands of Adventure.
And then, you know, I think we're just going to go with Seuss Landing and then maybe Harry Potter.
We don't talk about Seuss Landing that much.
I'm picking Epcot.
I'm picking the opening of Future World with the Spaceship Earth as the opening.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
And then right next to it is World Celebration.
No, not in ours.
No, mine is just the intros.
Mine is just just the turnstiles or whatever they call them now and the spaceship Earth.
That's the whatever that garden is.
And do they still have the names?
The names have been moved, right?
They moved names.
Did they ever reset them up?
I don't know.
They said they were going to make a…
It doesn't matter to this exercise, I don't think.
But then, yeah, you turn left and you hit Marvel Superhero Island.
Damn, that's pretty good.
That's fun.
Yeah.
And then I'm going to probably have to pick…
I'm trying to think, because I do really like Cars Land.
I'm a big Cars Land fan.
Yeah.
So I think that's a that's a very viable top five.
I'm putting Cars Land in there for sure.
I don't think Toon Lagoon is making it.
Wow.
You know, I love Toon Lagoon.
There's definitely be like, there'll definitely be like some sort of Dagwood presence in this new park, but not his own land, sadly.
OK.
But so t-shirts, merchandise, parades, perhaps.
He'll be around.
Dagwood on the move.
Dagwood will be around.
Marmaduke will be around.
Funky Winker Bean also around.
And then I'm trying to think.
I want to do like a thing that I liked as a kid,
which I want to just put the full Sandwich Village I grew up in, grew up with in this new park.
So this is one of the lands.
It's just full Sandwich Village.
None of the rides have been upgraded.
Yeah.
Like the best they had was like a coaster that is probably it's probably like a little bit bigger than Gadget's Go coaster.
In my mind, it's it's insane.
I never went on it because I was too afraid.
And then we stopped going there after I was probably 13 or something.
So I never got brave.
If it's still there, I should go.
I should when I go back, I should go on it.
So I'm putting all of Santa's Village into this park.
As a land.
That's really good.
And it's got an ice skating rink next to it called the Polar Dome, which I also will.
That's also going in there, which was falling apart 30 years ago.
And then at this point, what do you got left?
I don't want to put mine down.
I can't even keep mine straight in my head.
It's all lands.
That's the exercise here.
So like I'd love to just take Velocicoaster, but I don't necessarily need that Jurassic Park land.
Yeah, I don't care about that so much.
Can you go in and can you trade in and out or just it's Velocicoaster its own thing and you don't have the rest?
Yeah, I probably I mean, we can for the fun of it.
It seems like I should I should follow sort of what the prompt was.
Can would you would it be OK?
You think it would be OK, though, if I took just a Gudetama part of Pearl land and put it.
That's a small room like it's kind of a big room.
You mean like the where you wait for the show?
No, good.
So Gudetama has his own.
I don't know if it was.
Oh, no, you went after me.
Gudetama is the lazy egg.
Yeah.
But he has a whole room with like a bunch of activities and a lot of pictures of his body.
Oh, wait.
Yeah.
Wait.
That's like a kitchen.
Right.
Yes.
OK.
That is a lot of fun.
Yeah, there's another this is in this is not in a full Gudetama area, but I do have strong memories of peering down his asshole.
Yes.
And there was a video screen in the airplane cartoons.
Yes, you can watch cartoons through Gudetama's asshole.
And it's delightful.
I just bought two Gudetama toys at Target.
Yes.
Are too little like a plush.
How do you can you pull Pure Land entirely as if you go into one enough?
I think you could just throw Pearl in there.
Yeah.
And that would be good.
And then, yeah, then I would love to take something from Disney Sea and I'm trying to figure out what part of it that's my I think my I think I'm taking the island.
I'm taking a mysterious island right.
Yeah.
The volcano.
That is you know, and the attractions inside that's centerpiece.
Right.
I think I might have to I'm just I'm just out of between their tomorrow land and Discovery Land.
But you know what I don't like any of those right now.
Yeah, I want to know.
I want Tony Solaroni.
I want.
Yeah.
I want Tokyo's tomorrow land.
I'll take that.
Maybe I would take Paris's Main Street.
I might steal cars from you if we're allowed to double up.
Future World.
That's this is getting greedy.
I want Future World with Spaceship Earth.
And then I get past that and get to Tokyo volcano.
That's all in one park.
OK.
And all of Sanrio Puroland.
And we have a couple.
So we all have overlap so far.
I think so.
I think I have one more.
Maybe I just put World Showcase in as well.
Does that count?
Or do you have to be?
You have to pick a pavilion.
No, I think it's a land though.
Don't you think?
It's big.
I think there's no reason that there were no caps.
You're right.
So why not?
There were no caps.
So I have the first part of Epcot, just Spaceship Earth.
That's the entrance.
Then I have Marvel.
You're saying you're not taking.
But you're not taking.
Are you?
Can you?
I don't need any of the other rides or anything.
I don't even need Guardians.
You're not even taking Guardians?
No.
That's close enough, though.
Why don't you just grab that?
Eh.
Grab it.
I insist.
All right.
I'll take Guardians.
Put Guardians in your super park.
Guardians in the super park.
I'm putting it in mine.
You know what?
You're right.
Because it's a perfect.
It leads into Marvel Superhero Island then.
Yeah.
So it's a good transition there.
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
And then I think Cars Land is kind of goes next over there.
And we'll figure out how to transition that thematically.
I could take you to World Showcase though, potentially.
And then.
I could come out of Canada or.
World Showcase in Pearl Land.
Mexico.
You're getting Southwest-y.
And then.
And Santa's Village.
Did I take too much?
I think that's fine.
I don't know.
I wasn't keeping track of a five.
Jason, do you have?
Whatever.
Jason, what have you got?
OK.
I am going with trying to do.
I'm the spirit of the mashup, as Mike said.
You know, so I'll take the entry of Hollywood Studios, MGM Studios, Hollywood Boulevard.
So I'll take that.
You go left.
You hit.
I'm also taking Marvel Superhero Island.
Sure.
You go right.
You hit Pandora.
Great.
Oh, yeah.
That's good.
So that's three.
Right.
That's three lands.
OK.
Going around, curving around.
I'm going to say the Magic Kingdom Tomorrowland.
Great.
Mostly for vibes.
Yeah.
And people move her.
And then I'm going to go back in time and resurrect the Hanna-Barbera land from King's Dominion.
Oh, OK.
So because in this fantasy, I can go home again.
I can return to Yogi's Cave.
Yogi's Cave.
Yeah.
Your home.
Anytime you close your eyes is Yogi's Cave.
Yeah, that's right.
It was kind of dark in there, you know.
When you close your eyes at night, you're back in Yogi's Cave.
Yeah.
You dream of Yogi's Cave.
That's beautiful.
Boy, that's that's that's kind of nice to do.
I think these are some super perks.
I'm also like I'm kind of thinking about like taking that like even I don't know why you'd need to do that.
Now, I kind of like lower lot the lower lot Universal Hollywood that I grew up with,
and I want to take the star way to get to it.
So most of my whichever four, I don't know.
I don't want to if I narrowed it down, then the fifth is you have to for no reason take lots of escalators
down to the BT Adventure in the original tram tour.
That's not Jurassic Park.
The ride yet.
I don't want Jurassic Park.
The ride.
I want Lucy a tribute and I want AT&T at the movies.
Now we're talking.
Or there's a big phone that I stand in.
I think all of us need at least one pick that's like, you know, is that the best?
No.
But did I did I grow up with it?
Right.
I guess I could get rid of Spaceship Earth and replace it with the Wizard of Oz walkthrough with the MGM Grand.
Oh, that's not bad.
That's interesting.
Oh, Pulse and Casino.
Or like I want a New York, New York roller coaster.
Oh, yeah.
Or at least just the New York, New York Hotel.
Oh, you know what?
Let's do this.
What hotel?
Pisteo Hotel somewhere for your new resort.
Boardwalk.
You're doing boardwalk.
OK.
Yeah.
Do I want contemporary or do I want swan and or dolphin?
I can't I can't split them up.
It's like splitting up siblings in a in a litter.
Oh, yeah.
The contemporary.
Yeah, that's yeah, that would have been my number two.
Yeah.
I don't know.
It's probably a Disney hotel.
Probably Polynesian.
I could say like I could say like, I don't know, the Luxor when it opened or something, but like new Luxor.
Yeah, maybe.
But I didn't get to go when I was younger.
So not the one with like the adult playground arcade that's coming to it.
Oh, that's coming to the I think there's like, what does that mean?
Does it like an Instagram?
Yeah, like a David Buster's, but maybe a ball pit kind of.
It's adult just because I got it.
It's not like, yeah, yeah.
Or anything.
Yeah, it's it's aimed at older millennials who grew up with Discovery Zone and Chuck E.
Cheese.
But then also want to drink a White Claw when you do it.
That's who I am.
That's me.
That's who you are.
A lot of arcades going in.
I feel like really spaces in the casino.
Should we go back to Vegas for this?
Maybe.
What a big event it is.
It sounds like they have White Claws.
We got a White Claws.
Well, there's also the massive mini golf that is coming to Mandalay Bay, I think.
I don't know about that.
It's like multi stories with like restaurants and bars and stuff.
Now you're sweetening the pot here.
When is the Universal thing?
The Maze's?
When is that stuff open?
I don't know if there's a timeline.
That could fuel a return.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yeah.
Here's one.
Jeremy Ayala, would you all ever consider doing a theme park pizza final four?
That's interesting.
And I'm like and then somebody says like, well, yeah, the hot dog Hall of Baloo.
But for but for pizza, pizza, pandemonium.
I that's interesting.
And what I'm what I'm doing in my head is like is so you know, you guys shout that if there's an obvious answer that I'm missing,
shout it at me.
Theme park pizza can be a rough area.
Am I wrong?
I am not I don't immediately think of a pizza that I'm salivating over in a theme park as opposed to just like in a city in a real place.
You know, the one in Epcot is it's all it's pretty I don't like any amount of that tone.
That's nowhere close to it.
It's not.
But it's like at least like wood fired and adds some flavor to it.
It's not my favorite.
The one at downtown Disney is is all right as well.
But is that a theme park?
I think we got to go in theme parks.
I think that's the only thing that comes to mind where I go, oh, I would like to have that flatbread pizza I had again.
Not that I crave it like I crave other pizza, but that's the best thing I can think of off the top of my head.
Good.
I feel I feel like there is like theme parks do this thing or this thing kind of with a little novelty and there's something to it.
But like theme park pizza always feels like expensive and disappointing for something that should be a given.
And yeah, can you even listeners are probably yelling one that like, no, this one is good.
The big pizza riso.
I don't know.
We didn't do it last time, but I bet it's not.
Well, that's more that's more incendiary than what I said about Port of Entry, I think.
I don't know that.
I don't know.
I suspect I don't know if that is.
I think some of the pizza riso argument has been that the theming is better than we or other people have given credit for.
Are there are there are there a lot of people saying that the pizza is great?
I actually I don't know.
And I haven't had it.
So I don't know.
Well, I'll go for the theming, but I haven't eaten the pizza.
Yeah, I don't know.
I'm not sure if the big argument for pizza riso other than just it's good is that does the good mean the pizza or does the good just mean the vibes?
I think it's gotten work.
Mama Melrose in Hollywood Studios has I always like the pizza there that felt like actual cooked wood fire pizza.
I occasionally find myself in the mood for Fantastic Four Cafe or the Universal Studios Florida.
You know how you're like, oh, I just want kind of like cafeteria pizza.
You know, I want no, I don't feel that way.
I will sometimes like you don't do the pizza dominoes little Caesars like do what?
Do I don't know.
I'll do like a meat cheese or say, you know, I just shared a bar.
It was a big old slice with my son on the same trip I was talking about.
And that was pretty satisfying.
But, you know, like Greasey kind of like New York or mall style cafeteria.
You're doing nothing for me.
I think more pizza.
That's the better example.
Not cafeteria, but mall pizza, borrow.
That's the perfect example where you're like, I kind of want to borrow like and that's what you get at like Fantastic Four Cafe.
You get a good pizza in Vegas.
I feel like sometimes like there's the one place that you know, it's not good.
And you're you're charged twice what you should be.
Oh, yeah.
But you're kind of not paying attention at that point.
You just need something.
So New York, New York, you get a good slice at the end of the night or something.
Is there one there?
Yeah.
There's that secret pizza at the Cosmopolitan.
You got to go down back hallways.
I don't know about that.
There's record labels on the walls.
I don't know anything about that.
Have you done that?
No.
But I've had it recommended to me by a couple of people.
Secret.
I like the idea of it.
We would have to just go do some work.
I would I would be it's not like the most exciting idea for me to go eat all the pizza at Disneyland or something.
You look at good pizza at Disneyland and you don't include the outside pizza place.
I'm here.
I'm looking at a list right now.
What am I even going to land?
Do you even have one in your head?
What is pizza?
Well, there used to be a pizza press across the street.
Fosley, the lovely Anaheim Hotel, Anaheim Hotel.
It doesn't doesn't count.
Red Rose Tavern has pizza.
I've never heard of it before.
Picture doesn't look good.
Boardwalk pizza and pasta.
Maybe I've had that.
Maybe that's fine.
Maybe I've had a pizza there.
I write I pose this to listeners like convince me that theme park pizza isn't a merely fine to bad area.
I like I like I like theme park food.
I'll definitely like theme park food, but it's I can't think of any.
And then like your run of the mill theme park, you know, your six flags or whatever.
I feel like pizza is garbage across the board.
Yeah, I for whatever reason it does, I don't order pizza a lot at a theme park.
And I do think maybe it's it's a even an unconscious thought that most of the pizza is bad.
This is one of the shortest listicles I've ever seen.
Yeah, there's three entries.
I would rather I also think a lot of the I know this has gotten better,
but like even like a hamburger or a cheeseburger generally bad at the quick service.
So I'm more apt to even order a bad hot dog than I am a bad hamburger.
I think you're safer.
Yeah, I agree.
I'm with you.
I don't know.
I got more flavorful.
Yeah, I mean, like there's once in a while you get something, you know, the did they bring back the fried green tomato sandwich at the hungry bear?
I feel like they did.
They did at some point.
I don't know if it's still.
Yeah.
And like I guess I got a cheeseburger there once and you're just like, that's fine.
It's just not I don't understand why some of the food at a theme park isn't as good as like Pizza Hut.
It's not good in the trash.
Yeah, exactly.
I love Pizza Hut when it's it's like it's like I guess warmest, but also it's like saltiest.
Yeah, you get a good Pizza Hut.
You go.
I can tell this is destroying my body, but it's delicious.
I don't understand why you don't go in like Tomorrowland to the quick service and like the hamburger at least tastes like a Big Mac,
which is they figured out scientists have figured out the way to make a Big Mac,
the cheapest possible thing they can buy to give you to make your brain at least get fooled into thinking you're eating something pretty good.
I don't understand why the technology doesn't exist for them to at least do that and fool me in the way that fast food fools me.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, it's it should be better more often.
That's right.
Well, I'm sorry if this was a negative answer, but I was a bad answer.
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
Theme park pizza is a weird.
But I'd like to be corrected on this.
Please somebody shine a light.
Maybe there's a good read.
I could see that somebody's like, you know, a Kenny Wood or Hershey Parker, something like the oddly has a really good pizza place.
But I don't know.
I'm going to read this one while I'm looking at it.
Brian Wright, if you could choose any current television show to do a filmed on location Disney World episode, i.
e.
the full house.
Disney episodes.
What show would it be and what escapades with the characters get into?
And I have my answer ready to go.
Shark Tank.
It is Shark Tank, ABC.
I never really mentally crossed Shark Tank over with the parks until I heard Damon did the candlelight vigil.
Oh, yeah.
And now you're probably you might be thinking Shark Tank is a reality show that can't well not this episode.
It's not.
I am going to write an hour long, no negotiations, no pitches episode that is just Shark Tank goes on a Disney World vacation.
And just like all the it's just you piece them off into their own little adventure and then bring them back together for a nice firework show where they all reflect on what good friends they are and how much money they have.
I need jerks.
I would love to see Kevin do the Indiana Jones spectacular.
Just have to do every bit of it.
And he misses the spikes.
They always killed a lot of time that way.
Barbara is a little horned up and so she like her, her being with like Gaston being like a like a beef cake would be good for her.
I don't have any other if you guys I'll think if you guys have other answers, but I at least I was ready to go.
Well, feel free to pitch your own shows.
ABC show.
ABC is not given.
It's just what I thought of.
And it's the main they do say current.
It's the main current show that I gasp when there's a new one.
Oh, we got a new Shark Tank.
I really like whatever his name is.
I apologize.
I forget his name, but the guy who is in charge of kind bar.
I think he should be a perma shark when Mark Cuban leaves.
So I'd like to see kind bar guy get in a like, I don't know.
Is there a problem you could solve with kind bars?
Is anyone hungry or hangry?
Oh, right.
In a ride somewhere like he gives, you know, he goes on the Jungle Cruise and there's a lion roaring.
And if you think you're going to get attacked, but then he gives him a kind bar and that's good.
That ends the conflict.
Right.
That's perfect.
Yeah, I was going to say like, I guess it's but it's canceled.
Young Sheldon.
I don't think you and Sheldon went to Disney or anything.
CBS.
No.
Yeah.
But again, I, you know, pick your dream theme park.
I say pick whatever does not have to be in the Disney brand and maybe shouldn't be.
Yeah, he could have gone to Six Flags over Texas.
Yeah, but this is Disney World specifically.
Oh, Disney World specifically.
You're saying it could have been an episode there.
Yeah, because I think their show takes place in Texas.
I don't know.
All I know is it comes on sometimes and I go every actor that's ever lived is on this show.
Oh, every actor.
And Bigly Jr.
and Annie Potts.
Yeah, Wally Sean.
Long stretches where Young Sheldon doesn't appear and it's about the adults.
And I was like, should I start watching Young Sheldon?
Reba?
Maybe Young Sheldon is good.
I don't know.
But like all these actors I like are on there.
I haven't done it yet.
I'm just saying that once in a while I go, what is this show?
Now, now after it's been canceled, after it's over, you binge Young Sheldon.
Really quick, Robert Herjavec is kind of the outdoor sports guy.
He's like the skier.
You get him to Blizzard Beach.
You get him having fun with the Gator and whatever.
Right.
Something fun happens.
Strap a GoPro to him.
But any other TV shows you want to send to Disney World?
Sure.
The TV show I am fully caught up on, Reacher.
Reacher is either helping someone or he's hiding out at Disney World.
Remind me what Reacher is.
Jack Reacher series.
Yeah.
So Jack Reacher, yeah, he is a former military police officer.
And when he got discharged, of course, for doing the right thing, but going against orders, he now takes, he just wanders the country.
And he always, he only has a toothbrush on him and he'll just buy a new set of clothes and throw out the clothes he's wearing.
The newest season he gets back together because people are starting to kill his old, the 110th military police members are starting to die.
And ones are trying to reach out to each other for help.
So what's he doing in Disney World?
Well, he hitchhikes around the country and takes buses and trains just all around the country.
So he could just be going to see what it is or he could be helping.
Usually he helps solve a mystery or help solve a problem in a small town or something.
But sometimes he needs to hide out with his new whatever friends he makes along the way, you know, so he could just be hiding because it's hard.
It's like finding a needle in a haystack in those 40 square miles or whatever it is, you know.
Does he find love at all in the show?
Oh, Reacher gets laid all the time.
He does.
So much.
I've read like six or eight of the books and he's got a new parmore every, because it's like everyone knows, everyone knows the score.
Reacher's not going to stick.
It's just a fling, you know.
That's one of those strong Jasonisms parmore.
He's got a new flavor.
That's insane.
You need to, you've got to get an A in there.
That one's not a regional one.
Do you think Reacher could go to Jelly Rolls on the boardwalk?
Oh, Reacher would love it.
And find a new parmore.
If he could get some blues playing.
He loves blues and clown and rock.
Is it parmore permanently for us now too?
I guess, yeah.
Is it?
How is it?
It feels weird.
I don't know.
It's like I'm saying the word.
Mickey Mouse and his parmore mini.
Yeah, so Reacher at Jelly Rolls singing along to Don't Stop Believing or something.
Does he have to like blend in?
Does he have to pretend to be a piano guy?
Like, all right, you're up bud.
Oh, shoot.
And then he magically is really good.
Is he good at stuff sometimes?
I mean, he's always good at stuff.
Oh, Reacher's good at so much.
But has he pulled out like a skill like piano playing out of the blue?
Well, his mother is French, so he can probably speak French in the French Pavilion and wow.
OK, that's good.
That would be a good scene or two.
And then he can just beat the shit out of like rowdy, you know, rowdy guests.
You know, the whole show is him beating up other parkgoers.
Yeah.
Oh, he beats up all the bad guys, you know.
So I think bad guys have the infiltrator, the parkgoers, just like beating up annoying people.
Yeah, Jafar, guest on.
Well, he usually doesn't start a fight, but he certainly finishes.
Has he beat up a lion yet?
He beats up Robert Patrick.
Is it Robert Patrick?
From The X-Files?
Yeah, from The Terminator and The X-Files.
His most famous role.
Replacing David Duchovny.
Sure.
He was on Peacemaker.
Yeah, that's it.
Oh, yeah.
So he got beat up.
He's an older man.
He is an older man.
Why is Reacher beating up like a 70 year old man?
Oh, well, I don't want to give away what happens.
No Reacher spoilers.
He's a tough guy.
I like Robert Patrick.
I'm just saying.
By the way, can also just I'm sorry, I want to close it out.
Mark, I think you want to get him.
Mark Cuban goes into Pandora and you just just paint him blue.
Figure out a reason.
We'll figure out the reason, but just like make him like, you know, like, like, boy, I got to wash this stuff off.
And then I now it was thinking about villains.
Let's get Damon in.
Damon is doing is Mickey in Phantasmag.
He shoots fireworks out of his fingers.
What about my imagination?
I thought of Fubu.
Anyway, just want to make sure I'm covering.
No, I think you might really have a holding out.
Well, but I don't have a why am I forgetting her name?
QVC.
Laurie.
I got nothing for Laurie.
I'll try by the end of the episode.
It's funny because I haven't watched any real shows in so long that to make it current, like I'm trying to think we're like we're halfway through and are.
Mm hmm.
So that's that's still already but still in the air.
There's another season coming.
So technically it is current.
You're going to send and or to Disney World.
I'm going to send him to Disney World.
I'm going to send him to the first part there in Batu, but then they break out of Batu.
It's just like kind of a bottle episode and they end up in just Hollywood.
So now they have to figure out where they are.
They have to get back home.
OK, and then and or has to do.
Cashin has to do the Indiana Jones stunt show.
Great.
That should be part of.
Yeah, I'm going to give that to Richard to.
Yeah.
That's not even a question.
So they like they end up on Slinky Dog and stuff and like you portray like Slinky Dog as if he's sort of just like the giant like worm thing.
The Millennium Falcon is like sitting in an empire or something.
So you have to portray some of these things as if they're kind of alien.
But it's tongue in cheek.
You know, you know, it's wink, wink, wink.
It's a fun bottle episode.
It's a little bit of a departure from the normal tone of the show.
But yeah, you use everything.
Tower of Terror is very is sort of like maybe the big climax of.
No, you know, I take that back.
Rock and Roller Coaster is a big climax of it.
And they have to like jump to light speed and they have to find a vehicle that goes fast enough to go to light speed.
And Aerosmith's limo does it.
And the closest.
Yeah, that's the best thing they can not start tours.
Aerosmith's limo is the thing that can finally take them back to Batuu and back to their own universe.
Yeah.
And then they like see that they also see the pre-show of Aerosmith and they're confused because they're like, who are these aliens?
They look stranger than the aliens in our world.
The one in the way just the way.
Our galaxy has no one this cool.
Yeah.
Well, of course, they're very impressed with how cool they are.
These men in their mid fifties.
This transcends all time and language and culture.
And what yeah, what happens too is that they're so impressed by the garments they're wearing and the scarves and whatever.
And like the silk and the silk and just Joe Perry's whole aesthetic that they all start dressing like them.
So that carries through for the rest of that show.
The Endor characters all get glammed out.
Yeah, like late nineties Joe Perry.
Yeah.
So that's just like they never have to talk about it again.
But now they all have clothes like that.
They go and fashion their clothes that going forward to look more like late nineties Aerosmith.
And it's a fun.
It's just a fun episode, you know, because that's a that's much heavier show, I would say, than Mandalorian or the other shows.
Yeah, so I think this this will be a nice, nice little break.
And of course, synergy and it'll be because the Batuu is there.
They can shoot it there and it already looks like some Star Wars.
So I think it's some trouble.
That's good.
I think the opening scenes really quick.
Maybe Laurie proposes that Sunny Eclipse record an album and and tells him that he'll show.
She promises to blow it up on QVC that there's she takes him under.
But you know, they negotiate a decent rate, you know, 15 percent for three hundred thousand or whatever.
OK.
Oh, my God, I did them all.
That could be.
I feel like yours is the most viable.
I mean, clearly it is.
But it also maybe I could see it being like maybe a 20 minute version of what you're saying for like a promo.
Yeah, yeah.
I do think they aren't good actors, though.
They've tried things where they like that's why I need to get involved.
I can direct I can broaden because in another in a movie that I otherwise genuinely loved, Good Burger 2.
Oh, yeah.
I can watch Good Burger.
I really liked Good Burger 2.
I'm not kidding.
I think there are there are like huge laughs in it.
I put it on like, what's this crap?
I'll make fun of this.
By the end, I'm like, I love it.
I'm laughing more than I have in any comedy in a long time.
But one of the things that was throwing me at the beginning was Mark Cuban as a cameo and he's not good.
I was so disappointed because I want to see Mark Cuban acting and doing high jinks so badly.
He was one of the things that sunk it and then it had to claw its way back, which it did do.
You know what?
The revelation of that movie, Kel, Kel is funny.
He remains funny.
He really brings it.
That's you know, like bringing the old buddy back.
Kel is very good.
I didn't grow up with it.
I found I only I only watched it and liked it for the first time a couple of years ago.
It was kind of caught off guard.
How much I liked it.
That's a real endorsement though, because you didn't grow up with it.
It's not blind nostalgia.
No, if anything, I didn't I don't even like a lot of all that stuff.
I always found it kind of like random wacky at the time.
Yeah, but I like honestly Good Burger 2.
Whoever I think was maybe the writers of the original, besides the people who should not be in playing society anymore.
There's some new people too.
Yeah.
Newer actors are good in it.
Yeah, that's there's Scott's movie.
I do want to watch it.
I am.
Kel has cameoed on SNL a couple of times and always like nails his line.
Like he's always funny.
He's good.
I mean, that's and I agree that's good.
But I was like, are we going to see the cracks if he has to carry a movie?
No, no, no.
Kel was great.
Kel brought it.
Big Good Burger 2.
I'm happy to say on Mike.
All right.
Let's I don't have one that I've been staring at exactly.
Yeah, I there's a couple different ones that are asking about my music taste.
So I guess I could pick a specific like a more of a me focused like grab bag.
Let me let me combine all this.
This will be a quick and we don't need to go around unless it's unless we want to.
Somebody asked is it both a Swifty and a Clifford?
Knowing that I saw the heiress tour has this person wondering how hard it was to get tickets.
How much checking did I have to do?
What did I think of the concert?
What is your favorite Taylor Swift album?
This is Julie.
Julie wrote this.
I did no checking.
My sister checked and got these and I was even just family.
You all have the gift.
We all have the all of the force.
We all.
Yes.
Our father is for it.
No, my father could give a shit about checking.
Both parents do and don't have the patience for something like this.
Although my mom met this man, he doesn't he doesn't seem like a guy who would want a lot of like immediate toy deals from Target.
But no, my mom was my mom called to see if she could get me on the Bozo show,
which is how the way that you used to do it when they would give out free tickets, but didn't do it.
And in hindsight, I went, I bet she could have checked.
I bet she could have called harder.
That was the origin story.
Yeah, I bet she could.
Because at the time you're like, well, she called like, what are you going to do?
But then like, oh, well, I'm like, there's got to be a way.
And then you said the problem is technology hasn't caught up.
Phones block each other.
They were, you know, lines busy.
So your call gets rejected.
We need a technology that makes endless checking possible.
Yeah.
And you were an original funder of the of the early Internet and of the smartphone.
Exactly.
Yeah, I knew what the potential was for this type of technology.
It's incredible you do this podcast, even though you have seven billion dollars.
Yes, I should be on Shark Tank, not this podcast.
You are the Winklevoss triplet.
You are the secret third Winklevoss swim.
Yeah.
So, so Taylor, so my sister was like, oh, do you want to go?
Because she, I don't get the tickets for my dad and her to go.
And then I was like, yeah, I would like to go.
And I really, I was kind of ignorant to all the whole like culture that had developed at these shows.
Yeah.
So I kind of was going in blind.
I did not realize it was four hours.
It was so long.
And it was at SoFi Stadium and what it was, nine nights or something.
And Heim opened, which I'm a bigger Heim fan than I am Taylor Swift fan.
You got me into them.
I, I, yeah, yeah.
I think they're right.
I'm a big, big fan of them.
And but I do like a lot of Taylor Swift.
So I had a fantastic time.
We were just talking about this a couple of days ago.
So you guys are hearing this again.
It's not only do I just, I like a lot of songs,
but also being anywhere where, where somebody's at like the height feeling of their like cultural relevance.
There's an excitement.
And especially when teenage girls are involved,
there's a like a vibration that is happening in a group of this many people.
Interesting.
Just normal stuff to say.
Well, but you know, like the Beatles, how excited the room is.
There's an energy.
If you've pieced what I'm saying out of context, yeah, you could arrest me.
That's fine.
If you pulled out just that there's an excitement when teenage girls are involved.
But Mike Carlson.
Yeah.
But I was like, oh, this is important.
What I'm at is important.
This is an important moment in American history.
So it was like it was it was like exciting in that way.
But yeah, it's also very themed.
It's a theme park show.
It's great.
Like she jumped into the production.
I don't know, like the set.
There's a lot of different sets, obviously, for the different eras, for the different albums.
And like they build a house and she's in the house or whatever.
And then there's a part where she the stage turns into water and then she jumps into a hole in the stage
and they have like a video screen for swimming like down the stage.
The whole thing is very full of little theme park tricks.
Sounds like a great, great material that would fill the sphere.
No, she's too big.
She's like she would never know.
Do not do not do not put the chains of sphere on Taylor.
The twenty thousand people, please.
She'd have to pay.
She'd have to play a year straight every day to to to meet the demand of that show.
And it would be nice.
You would not make the money either.
But yeah, I it's fun.
It was fun.
I I feel like a bit of a poser, though, because I should be more hardcore.
I was upset.
I'm only played like seven songs.
I was like, we could have had another.
Give me another few.
They're playing so far.
That was fun to see them play.
But you but you know, hey, you just give us some opinion.
I don't think you're a pose.
I don't.
Should you be deeper into Taylor Swift than that?
Do you think because it's like a girl thing, a teenage girl thing?
I mean, she's not that's Olivia Rodrigo is 20.
This was about 35.
So well, it's more it doesn't have to line up with it.
You're lining up with the age of the artist.
I listen to a lot of seventy five to eighty five to dead.
Oh, yeah.
I'm right there with you.
Yeah.
The closer to death, the better I say when it's music.
Oh, yeah.
Well, and if you're wondering, Donald Fagan at the forum pre Eagles was great.
And what's your errors?
What's your Fagan era?
It's a night.
Nightfly, baby.
Yeah.
This is this one's interesting.
I don't know.
I wonder if you remember this, Jason.
Robert Hernandez during the episode where Scott revealed the signatures that he had in a book.
Jason said that he had an artifact to in fact that he would reveal in 2023 timestamp.
Twenty three minutes.
That's strange.
Simulation.
Well, will we ever know what these are?
Do you know what he's talking about?
Well, one artifact is discussed on the upcoming city walk saga.
Oh, that was one.
Oh, that was one of them.
The other artifact, I'll just say it now.
I bought one of those imagineering coffee table books.
There's like two volumes of it.
And I bought it at this like you use like collectible and Nick next door in Burbank.
There wasn't it used to have an art gallery, too.
There was an art show I went to there once of like art inspired by the Museum of the Weird Art.
That was pretty cool.
So I bought this book there and it was like twenty five dollars because the it was out of print.
But there was a rip in the cover.
So it was covered.
It was basically cover price when I got it home and I opened it up inside was a Disney imagineering inner office envelope that was signed by like 20 people.
And I could only make out like some of the names.
OK.
Like Martin Sclar's signature is very clearly says Marty Sclar.
But I don't know what the other ones were.
So, yeah, I forgot all about that.
Anyway, so I'll have to bring that in sometime and maybe you guys can help me identify some of the others.
But someone clearly got this book or it was somebody who worked at Imagineering's and then they maybe they were a guest of someone and they just went around and got a bunch of signatures on this envelope.
Interesting.
Well, we'll have to I don't know that I'm going to be so good at identifying it.
But I'm sure I might know more like, oh, that name that guy worked on such and such.
I see.
You're saying I should just identify the name that I don't even figure out the name.
But some most people's signatures are kind of gobbledygook.
Sure.
Interesting.
All right.
Well, that's good.
Here's another Jason one.
I don't know.
What does this refer to?
How far along is Jason in his tap dancing journey?
Oh, I was talking about I always want to take tap dancing classes.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I got to get some of the ocarina's infusion.
Got to get some M.
S.
injections.
Few things before that happens.
Hopefully you're all the way to tap dancing.
Yeah.
And then maybe I'll look into it more.
Yeah, it's interesting.
I get I'm trying to think of that was even I guess dance classes, especially at the time when you're like a little boy.
It's like I don't take dance classes or whatever.
Although I was in a dance show in high school.
I've talked about this before, so I never thought about taking tap.
But I guess I wasn't as enamored with like singing in the rain until I was older.
Yeah, you were a singing in the rain.
I was singing in the rain kid.
Yeah, because, yeah, I saw it on the great movie ride and then I went to blockbuster or movies and rented it.
You remember the cow video store movie?
No, I don't remember that.
I think it got bought by video update at some point, the much less exciting named video update.
I'm going to say this one because I thought of the answer and it's fast.
Julian Key, what were your favorite anecdotes from the Sumner Redstone book Unscripted?
I read it but a little while ago, so I don't remember a ton of it.
I was very deep in, but it's all kind of faded away.
There's a lot of names to keep track of.
But I do remember that Sumner had a 90th birthday that was huge and all his Hollywood friends are there and everybody had to come kiss the ring.
And Tom Cruise and everybody.
It might have been at that Bel Air, the Herb Albert Jazz Club.
And then he tried to do the same thing for his 91st and people didn't feel like they owed him as much.
And his health had severely declined and his mood had severely declined.
So it's just him and all of his weird like nurse girlfriends and everybody who was like vying for the money.
And I think Tony Bennett did come, but the whole week he'd been talking about Tony Bennett's working with Lady Gaga right now.
She's a real dame, here's your cum.
And then Lady Gaga was not at his birthday.
So even though it was like, isn't there one of the there's a Simpsons where like Mr.
Burns has a big giant birthday and they have an an Earth and people have all spelled his name and in a satellite picture.
And he's still really sad.
That's what happened with Sumner that he just like still it was like anybody would be thrilled with this as a birthday.
And then he was just like Lady Gaga didn't cum.
He drove away sad and cried and fought with all the nurse wives.
Oh, God.
That's hilarious.
This is this is a deceased man who I think we're allowed to to laugh at.
Bad man.
What else we got?
Alex Tucker asks if you could pitch a licensed cartoon character restaurant a la Garfield Eats, what would it be?
What would the menu items be?
How obscure would you get?
Could there be a King Feature Syndicate diner?
Of course, I mean, you know, that's true.
But I think I think you'd want a more like mono focus on one character or one property because like King Features.
Yeah, sure.
But that unlimited.
That's too much to try to brainstorm here, I think.
So I think, you know, it's obvious with Garfield, it would be obvious with we talked about Dagwood earlier to just do a sandwich.
I don't really necessarily want to do like an obvious one.
You know what I mean?
You would want to really surprise people with the property.
Well, I mean, if we're going by Garfield Eats rules, it should be kind of like it barely has to do with the character where it's like, hey, welcome to Ziggy Curry.
Oh, what?
Ziggy?
Now this is a restaurant in my did Ziggy like Curry?
Is that from?
No, it's just what I look.
I I love Ziggy growing up.
I love two things in my life.
I love Ziggy and I love Donald Trump and these men inspire me to be who I am today.
Ziggy means everything to me.
And you're like, why are you like bursting into what you you seem like a real mess, like just the mere thought of Ziggy makes you break down in tears.
Don't worry about it.
He is Curry, but he didn't have.
I don't know.
Shut up.
Go to Ziggy Curry.
Ziggy Curry closes six weeks later.
And then and then the owner of Ziggy Curry gets weird.
And not fun weird either.
Like, oh, yeah, no, that's right.
I think Scott has made his decision.
Is there a precious?
It's fine.
I have eat the cat eggplant.
We have that.
That's going to do just as well.
Oh, let's let's reboot eat the cat.
Like, let's.
Yeah.
I was eat the cat.
Now come back.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I wonder.
Maybe that that that might be one of those that have been like 14 for attempts.
They've they've had a lot of meetings about eat the cat.
Yeah.
Worth telling us at this point.
I was going to say like David the gnome or something.
David and the gnome cafe.
It's like a tea shop.
Yeah.
It's mostly like tea, I think.
Tea.
A few of me.
Mushrooms.
But is it going to you want it to be as depressing as the as the show?
Yeah.
The series.
And the confusing is the show was because the show was dubbed over as a Spanish show
bought by two men.
Let's call them B Weinstein and H Weinstein.
Oh, wow.
And then dubbed over for American children.
Just getting a toe hold in the media landscape.
Yeah.
David gnome cafe.
The gnome cafe.
And it serves, let's say, tea and you said mushrooms.
Like mushrooms.
Or mushroom tea.
Like little.
You're not talking about the psychedelics.
I'm not talking about psychedelics.
You know what?
I am talking about the psychedelics.
Oh, OK.
You can hallucinate.
Yeah, that might put you on the same wavelength as the trippiness of the show.
This cafe is an.
Hallucinate that you die and become a tree.
It's in Amsterdam.
OK.
And is mushrooms legal in Amsterdam?
Maybe.
You're asking the wrong room, baby.
I know you can get weed other places.
You can get weed.
Prostitution is legal.
The David the gnome cafe is also a brothel.
So you can get tea.
You can get psychedelics and then you can.
You can have sex with a beautiful woman in a big gnome hat.
A beautiful woman legally in a big gnome hat.
You're mainly.
This is less about like the indulgence for you and more you wanting to know that it's all legal.
You're worried about getting in trouble.
I love Amsterdam because you're going to really cut loose.
No, because I won't get in trouble.
Yeah, of course.
That's what a big thing in my life is that I will get in trouble.
And this I won't.
If I open up the David the gnome brothel slash tea mushroom cafe copyrights fine hallucinates fine.
Prostitution is fine.
Cool.
Yeah.
And there's a loose fox in there like the show.
Oh, just a random.
And and wildlife rules are lax there, too.
Right.
You can just have a fox wandering around in America.
It is not legal to have a fox wandering around a cafe, but it is in Amsterdam.
And the fox's name is Swift like it was on the show.
Jason, what do you got?
Are you fitting in one more?
One more.
Yeah, I got.
Well, this is too quick.
OK.
So pick which question you like.
I think is no.
What a diss to the other question.
If you could bring back one extinct attraction from a Disney or Universal park, which would you choose and why?
Or which area of the parks as your the best background music?
Who said this one?
This one was.
Can we list both of them before we insult one of these?
David Pavetto.
Great.
Wait, it's bringing back one ride or it's what has the best loop like background background music in the park.
What's more, I guess, bringing back a ride, although have we said that we answered this question before?
I feel like we've answered that before.
I feel like my answer is usually Horizons or the original Journey into Imagination.
Yeah, those are the answers.
Those are the safe answers.
The second is really safe because it's like there's not a lot they would have to do to restore Journey into Imagination.
And there's always discussion about plussing it up and changing it.
And, you know, that's never happening.
The unsaid, the literally the most unsafe answer is the brief Millennium Simulator ride, which is not documented at all.
Journey to Jerusalem, the shaky.
Yeah, which there was like they had to declare in the literature they declared which was the Holy Land.
I've thought about this ride with everything going on like dear God.
Yeah, that would be a journey to Jerusalem.
That would have been interesting for sure.
Yeah, there's no yeah, we did talk about going with it.
Alright, Scott has answered.
Yeah, I it's I'm trying to think if there's even other like most things that are gone.
I think there's a reason for it.
In general, I guess I shouldn't blanket say that not Horizons and not the original Journey.
Yeah, but it would have to be a nostalgia pick.
And like as a kid, you know, we just talked about Toad.
But I mean, obviously my memory was shot and I didn't remember there were two tracks on Toad from Disney World, which is something.
So it's not like I can say Toad because I need to experience what I did as a kid.
We still have Toad and I think it's perfectly fine out here.
So yeah, I guess I have to go.
Maybe I go with like the original film Spider-Man, not the new HD version.
You want it to go backwards?
Yeah, it's more like what it was when I was a kid.
I was a teenager.
Yeah, it's more PlayStation.
It looks more PlayStation.
So your answer is worse graphics on Spider-Man.
Yeah, the graphics got too good, I think.
Yeah, voice acting is still good.
It can still be.
They could have plus it up to make it clear, like clearer and the 3D better.
But these new graphics, do we need it like that?
I need it to be more cartoonish.
I think it's Spider-Man.
That's my answer.
I want the original film of Spider-Man that makes it more like a cartoon.
Yours is more easily achievable.
Just all right, you heard them boys.
Put the old movie back in.
It's been eaten by rats back there.
Every coffee is full of rat bites.
I don't know.
The guy says.
This guy says it on his paywall podcast, so we should do it.
Oh, you know what my actual answer is?
Because nobody bothered to film it.
I want to know what the simulator was in the Buena Park McDonald's that justified it being called McThriller.
That's a great answer.
I want that simulator back.
Yeah, that is a great answer.
I could take all the pictures and know what it was.
Just from the era that it was created, there's no way it wasn't bad or very bad.
And when I say that, I mean good.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
If that makes sense.
That sentence makes sense.
I think it did.
Yeah.
Oh, I never got to Scott.
Maybe you got to this.
I don't remember when it closed, but at Knotts, there was that like the house where like you're standing on a slope and like the water is poured upward.
You know what I'm talking about?
I remember something like that.
That sounds very familiar.
It's still in the Calico ghost town in the middle of California and Nevada area.
Oh.
That Walter Knotts kind of.
There's like perspective and it looks like an adult is smaller than a child.
Yeah.
It's like, I forget what it's called.
But that seems like it would still delight me.
Okay, the house.
The house.
Jason says the house.
Oh, Mickey's birthday.
Like Mickey's house and Mickey's birthday land.
We should do that.
That's a topic we should do soon.
Yeah.
Is that a show with all that with Darkwing Duck and whatever?
And CJ, who my dad liked.
Oh yeah, your dad.
We saw the show a bunch of times.
Disney character.
Because he wanted to see CJ.
You know what I like is that CJ.
All right.
Well, CJ coming soon.
Let's wind it down here.
You Survived podcast, the ride.
I think this is good doing it on Patreon audience.
I think you fixed it for us.
Now you can do it.
Do as long of a question as you want without having to pay for one of those
check marks, which now are only on the accounts of awful people.
And he didn't know on the accounts of some often people who are like,
I'll try this.
This will make me normal.
What happened?
All right.
Well, we're taking the post office away from that site.
Let's see how long they last now.
Yeah, it's going to dry up.