Forever.
of a man in a humid house.
It may contain massive rotting mushrooms,
robots of people in the Epstein files,
and robots of trees purchased by different people
in the Epstein files.
Carly Weisel returns to the show to talk about
her exotic expedition to the Rainforest Cafe
on Podcast the Ride.
["Rainforest Cafe Theme Song"]
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast that is dedicated
to protecting endangered animals,
specifically rotting dead-eyed,
barely functioning animatronic ones.
I'm Scott Gardner, there's Mike Carlson.
I'm here, yes, and the empathy I have
for decaying robots is strong.
I empathize with animals that are living,
that can breathe and pump blood.
But they'll figure themselves out.
Animatronics are truly helpless.
No money is ever put into their maintenance
unless they're into fixing the less and less popular
restaurant that they live in.
Yeah, and real animals, they have the ability to heal.
Robots can't heal unless man decides.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, unless man or Landry's decides
that it's their time to heal.
I'm here, I'm trying to get the bucket and sheet metal
set up for the thunderstorm that will happen
every 20 minutes on this episode.
Oh, I see, oh, you'll be providing live.
Oh, great, yeah, yeah, get clapping.
I regret this choice already.
It's a fun idea, it's a fun gimmick,
but ultimately, yeah, it's gonna wear you out.
Probably shouldn't have buckets of water
by this many wires.
I think that's right, yeah.
We'll be safe.
Yeah, try to contain it over there.
Yeah, hey, we're excited to be talking
about Rainforest Cafe.
We've touched on it a little bit before.
Rainforest Cafe came up in the downtown Disney ordeal
with former employee of Rainforest Cafe, Julia Prescott,
returning to the show soon.
But we thought, I mean, we have not truly done
the deep dive, I thought, hey, there's still meat
on these mojo bones, so let's get into it,
especially because returning Victorious
from a recent Rainforest Cafe expedition
and also returning to this show for the first time
in nearly two years, for the first time
I believe so, for the first time since becoming a mom
for a podcast, very amusing, it's Carly Weisel, hi.
Hello, hi.
Hi, welcome back.
I gotta say, I didn't think after two years
I would come back to such Rainforest Cafe slander
about the audio animatronics because we'll get into it,
but I thought they were in fine condition.
Oh jeez, well, I was impressed.
Look, I'm the one who's out of date
because you've been to one much more recently than me.
I'm pulling from four years ago.
Oh, you're not taking a full work day
to drive to Ontario Mills to go to Rainforest Cafe?
That is what it takes.
It's to go to the nearest Rainforest Cafe to us.
That's an hour or more for everyone here.
Yeah.
Oh, it was at least two.
Jeez.
It was two flat.
Wow, wow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Depending on where you go also,
and that's one of those drives that just keeps going.
You start to suspect this has to be done soon.
No, it doesn't.
And then you look and it's like, oh, an hour 19, okay, okay.
We're still going.
My God, it's an expedition.
I was very excited to hear you were doing it
and have done it.
I'm really excited to get into it.
But also we've not, we haven't had,
you haven't been on it a little bit
and we're so excited to have you again.
I know, I'm happy to be back.
Much has changed for you.
And I'm just excited.
I haven't really talked to you about
your, a new dimension of your theme park fandom
and excursions doing it as a parent.
Yeah.
You've done a bunch of it, it seems like.
I have.
I've been really ramming it in.
I did Disney World for four days
and then I've gone to Disneyland twice now
and I'm gonna be going back to Disneyland
I think every two weeks.
I'm all in.
Wow.
That a lot, really?
Oh my God.
I know.
That's just your, that's your local park.
Your local playground is Disneyland.
I mean, not just because LA only has golf courses
and not really public parks.
We won't get into that, but.
Oh, not well, see that's the Burbank thing.
Burbank.
Yeah, being a Burbank parent, there's so many,
it's crawling with, you can have a new one
for every day of the week and never repeat them.
I keep finding them still.
Yeah, Burbank is a magical place.
Okay, I mean I have to explore this.
I've looked into dog parks in Burbank
and those are great too.
Oh sure, yeah, that's good kid entertainment for sure.
But yeah, you're right.
I guess for you it just makes sense.
Just head down to Disneyland.
Yeah, once we got over the,
I mean for people who don't have kids,
this is so boring, I'm so sorry.
But once we got over the threshold of she can be
in the car seat with someone in the back seat with her
and that means we can get to and from, then we're fine.
And wait, as opposed to, wait, what's the-
I can't drive her alone.
Cause she, when, the longest I can go
is probably 20 minutes before she's like, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, I want out.
Oh geez.
Do you have any entertainment back there?
We got a little portable DVD player,
like old school DVD player, we can throw Pixar movies
and Thomas the Tank Engine on there.
We're almost there.
Okay, okay.
We're still at, like a rattle is fun.
We're still coming out of that.
Wait, cause how old now?
Well, she's 10 months, but she's loving a toy.
She's loving to explore.
She's only 10 months, I thought it was, wow.
10 months, yeah.
I thought it was longer.
Oh crazy, well geez.
Going well, you having-
Yeah, she's, as far as I know, she's growing,
which is the only metric they can really measure.
That means you're doing your job right now.
She's alive and eating.
Yeah, it's going well.
It's just, I can't believe this world is run by parents
and they're all awake enough.
I didn't know this level of exhaustion.
And now that I do, I don't trust anyone operating a vehicle.
I just can't believe people are flying planes out here.
Flying planes with kids.
Like you have a sick kid and then you go fly a plane.
Impossible.
Yeah, yeah.
I know, like our main thing is doing this
and then we'll be like grumpy doing this
cause of a bad night.
Yeah, same deal.
Oh man, I gotta-
Oh, a theme park podcast.
How do you do that?
Gotta go in my office and talk about Lunar New Year.
How will I ever survive?
Like, I can't believe it.
Meanwhile, dignitaries, heads of state,
and yes, people who operate heavy equipment
all do it with more children than we have.
Navy SEALs.
They must.
I would assume.
I would assume too.
Unless they, Navy SEALs aren't like recruited
from like an orphanage or something, right?
Like where they just like train them to be like super spot.
But even if we don't know about Navy SEALs,
people who run cruise ships.
People who run cruise ships.
Captains of ships are just on a ship with the kids.
Right, and they just keep getting bigger.
They keep getting water parks and stuff put on them.
I see we have the same algorithm.
That's right, yes.
Oh, like with innovations and how crazy cruise ships can be.
There was a new cruise ship that launched recently.
And so my whole feed is like,
can you believe how many water slides we got?
It is, yeah, they're insane, yeah.
So no, those people have kids.
I know, I can't believe it.
To all the parents out there, wow.
Wow.
You had no idea.
You're doing great.
How hard everyone was working.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
I had no idea.
I thought life was hard when I didn't get seven hours of sleep.
You know, it's like, oh, I didn't get my latte.
I can't survive the day.
I mean, I still feel that way,
but now it just has more oomph to it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
People are more willing to say, oh, I see, okay, okay.
Before, no excuses, especially from parents.
Didn't know what the other side was, now I'm there.
But I love it.
It's very fun.
It's very weird to have a tiny version of you
enter the room and you're like, oh, hello.
They just appear.
It's so, I can't wrap my head around it
and it's been almost a year.
Yeah, I am interested to know if that was ever,
was that common 50 years ago?
It feels like it wasn't.
It feels like, I don't know,
I guess we're all a little bit more children
into our adult years.
Yes.
And that's part of why it feels a little strange still,
to be like, there's a little person that looks like my father
when he was a kid.
And I see his baby pictures when she walks in.
When I see her face.
And I go, whoa.
And if I've been gone for six hours,
I come back and go, there's a baby in here.
Exactly, yeah.
It's my baby.
It must be because we all had this extended
child adulthood where we professionally had fun.
And we still have fun.
God bless it.
Boy, you're really needing
those accrued memories.
So by the time you start putting it all up.
But it also, but then you get this kind of,
then there's a perma kid that happens
from having a kid around,
which you'll especially experience
going to the parks.
Yeah, it does.
Not to name drop, but the one person I always think of
is that John Stamos specifically told me
that it's gonna be more magical with a kid.
And I remember he told me when he didn't know
I was pregnant and I was pregnant.
And I was like, boy, I hope he's right.
I don't know, I don't know.
And he was right.
It's a different type of magical to be at somewhere
like Disney World with a mini version of you
and have them watch it for the first time
so that you're not as focused on like,
I don't like the way the Frozen animatronics work.
Your child is just enjoying it.
I know.
We've had to dredge it back up, I feel like,
to do this podcast.
Because although you haven't done
your official Disneyland trip.
No, we have not done it.
Yeah, it does.
It makes you shut up about a lot.
You're just like, it's great.
It's so good.
It's just good.
They did a good job.
It's a place to entertain this kid for five hours.
I'm thrilled.
Yeah, it's a new, it's a magic renewed.
Yeah, that sounds great.
God, that would be a good ad campaign.
Hey, yeah, that's a word they have into it.
Renewed.
Yeah.
That would be a good fireworks show, renewed.
I'll remind you that the only way to get a magic key
is renewal.
Oh yeah, true.
I missed the last round.
I don't know if I'll, yeah, I'm still lost on that one.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's a dog fight to get it.
You missed the 30 hours notice?
God.
Yeah, that's right.
They barely said it, and you're in a big line,
and then like, oh my God.
Wait, what's our-
You need to set up text messaging alerts
for Scott Gustin tweets.
I see.
Yeah, that's the only way to ride anything out.
because they were sold on whatever day it was.
The next day I was going with that SoCal resident ticket,
the three visit ticket, which you can't-
That's why, I already had my ticket,
so I don't want a pass now.
And you can upgrade from that ticket if you,
like I was gonna start it the next day.
So I thought, oh, I'll go to the park the next day,
I'll scan in with the ticket, and I'll upgrade it,
I'll save money.
I just pray that the passes are available,
and they weren't, and I saw his tweet,
because I got the alert, that was like,
everything's sold out with the resident pass,
and I immediately bought it.
I just ate the cost.
Okay.
Because I had to do it, because Scott Gustin told me to.
I had family visiting, and I was like,
I made reservations on these park hoppers,
but I gotta renew them, and it used to be
you would just walk up and say,
I wanna put this towards an annual pass.
And now there's like one ticket window open,
and there's a two hour line at City Hall,
and I'm like, I can't, I just can't.
I know, I feel you.
I was there, and I am still annoyed that I ate,
what, $225?
Right, yeah, yeah.
But that's why I'm going back, to kind of,
to heal that wound.
Get your money's worth.
Yeah, try to go as much as possible.
So I'll stop being mad at the place, yeah, yeah.
But look, you also, you've got plenty of other
entertainment options, and themed experience options,
and animatronic options, because, you know,
not much further than Disneyland is a magical realm,
a magical place, where you're transported
to another continent, to another world,
to the rainforest, as you got to be several months ago.
Yeah, what happened here?
What was your experience that led you to this,
and led you to wanna talk to us about it?
So, I have a group of friends who, for probably,
almost three years, we had been joking about
going to Rainforest Cafe.
And it was all that we, someone, I think my friend Amy
brought it up as a joke, and we were like,
wait, I actually wanna do that.
And we all wanted to do it.
And one of us lives in the Bay Area.
It's all, this group of friends I'm talking about
are all Hollywood people, with incredible jobs,
and I don't wanna like, fully, I got their consent
to talk about them on this podcast.
But like, one friend works at Pixar,
another's a producer, another one like,
makes all these shows, and they all were all in
on this convoluted idea of driving all day
to go to Rainforest Cafe.
And the friend at Pixar finally had the day open,
and we all traveled to it.
And we found it on the count, like, we were going.
But what we realized after the fact
was that the only day we could all do it
was the day after the Taylor Swift show.
Which was one of my only big nights out in a long time.
So, I not only drove all day to go to Rainforest Cafe,
I did it extremely hungover.
Wow.
Extremely.
Friendship bracelet.
A friendship bracelet intact on my wrist.
Just got in the car the next morning
with so much coffee in my body, and drove.
Those go late too, those went late.
Oh yeah, hours, yeah.
I saw Beck at the forum next door,
and all the Beck dads were trying to like,
beat the traffic, that was the main concern.
It's like, okay, technically see the end of the show,
okay, run to the, okay, she's still playing,
thank God, let's get the fuck out of here.
Oh yeah, and we had a, I went with a group,
so we had a party bus situation.
Oh my God.
But two of us couldn't find the party bus,
so we were there a lot longer than I think you would have.
I'm pretty sure that I texted my friends a photo of me
in front of the beautiful Rainforest Cafe sign,
which I'm sure we'll get into,
and they texted back that they were still in bed.
Oh my God.
So, wow.
So you had that much time to kill at Ontario Mills?
So you went to lunch?
Oh no, I just didn't sleep.
Oh okay.
Oh no, the friends who didn't,
other friends that I went to the show with.
Oh gotcha, oh, not the people you would meet.
I went to Rainforest Cafe with three other ladies,
and one of them went to Taylor, I went to Taylor.
Okay, okay.
And we met up.
You're in the rainforest,
and they are in the comfort of their bed, oh my God.
Was there any thought to just taking the party bus
straight to the Rainforest Cafe?
If I could have gotten those girls on board,
that would have been a dream.
But people were laughing at me when I told them
the next day I was driving to California's only
remaining Rainforest Cafe.
Sure, yeah.
What was your era real quick,
just in general, what's your era?
I think my era was, I'm not too big of a fan,
but I'm gonna assimilate into this group
because this seems like a great night.
Now that I've seen the show,
I am a reputation girly as they say.
Folklore, I saw a show there.
Wow, folklore era.
Oh, so chill.
Very chill.
I guess I engaged the most in 1989.
I love 1989.
That's mine too.
You're in 1989, oh okay.
Yeah, but no expert.
Okay, so this is an insane whirlwind,
although also the best.
What a great one to punch.
Oh yeah.
What do you think was fueling this enthusiasm?
What was making this group all salivate
for Rainforest Cafe so much?
I think it was the threat of them going away forever.
Because we've seen them really,
I mean if you look at that Wikipedia of closed ones,
it's frightening.
And we knew that we probably weren't gonna be able
to coordinate all of us being in Orlando at the same time.
So while this one was open and still thriving, I'd say,
definitely had to make it happen.
Great, great.
Yeah, it's true.
I figure, again, we touched on Rainforest Cafe
and we were in the underworld.
This was a paywall episode
for people who were just on the main feed.
But this was 2019 when we talked about,
mainly the downtown Disney one.
And I was expecting to look at the list and go,
all right, well in the over four years since that,
we've lost a lot of these.
And in fact, only four, only four have gone away
since we talked about it before.
London is gone, London has fallen.
London's gone, I was gonna say it's fallen.
All right, Dubai has fallen.
Oh wow, you didn't notice that.
Though I think it just moved,
I think it got replaced by another one.
And then both Chicagos, both Chicagos are gone.
For the two of us, that's a big deal.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That downtown Chicago one.
That looks insane.
That looks like a real highlight of the enterprise.
It was a huge part of my childhood.
Oh really, okay, okay.
For one of our, we do a turnabout Sadie Hawkins dance thing
in high school.
And part of it was that when you're a junior and senior,
you get to dress up in theme.
And so we all dressed up and I don't know why we did this.
We drove downtown in a limo to Rainforest Cafe.
So you did have a party bus kind of situation
to the Rainforest Cafe.
And I think that was the same year we went back
and the dance was at the high school
in the Chicago suburbs.
So we left basically a mile radius from school,
went downtown to Rainforest Cafe and then came back.
Which is how far, where was it?
Very far, I mean on a Saturday night.
Oh my God.
We had like post prom,
which the prom was close by the suburbs.
And then we took like a bus after prom down to the city
to get on a boat or something.
Yeah, what was that?
And then came back.
We could have gone to, I don't know,
Michael's and Highland Park.
There could have been other places we could have gone.
Yeah, that's weird.
But for some reason.
I don't know why.
Yeah, but Rainforest Cafe as a high schooler was fun.
Wow, wow.
It was so beautiful.
I don't know if you, I mean, if you Google the facade,
stunning.
I never went.
It's maybe the most ambitious one
besides like the notable ones I'd say
are like the volcano ones.
The Disney Springs one is volcano.
But often they're in these mills settings
where like they're grand once you get in,
but there's no real like outside of it.
But that Chicago one bonkers.
Massive, massive.
The silly, it must have seemed so,
I don't know what the surrounding of Chicago was.
It's kind of like the Rock and Roll McDonald's.
Oh, cool.
Or what the former Rock and Roll.
They kind of updated it, right?
Yeah, but I think so, yeah.
It's like still kind of, yeah.
I made it there.
That was on my, in 2008.
That was on my Chicago list.
I did it.
I did do the Rock and Roll McDonald's.
Yeah, so it was right by there.
So it was a little like, ooh, this is fun chain land.
Oh, cool.
Yeah.
Wow.
Have you seen it lately?
Like in person or photos, what happened to Chicago?
Oh, the rainforest?
No.
Yeah, it just kind of, they like stripped off
most of the branding is that.
The mushrooms.
Mainly what stayed is just like big rotting mushrooms.
Characters gone, signage gone,
but the mushrooms are too like baked into it to do anything.
And then just kind of the faded mural,
that's still up there.
They just kind of like cut and ran.
And then that building has just been nothing.
And it's actually been in a war for a long time
where various dispensaries have tried to get it.
I think multiple of them.
I feel like my dad sent me a, you know,
like a real dad link.
Like my dad sent me a link of this story.
Oh, man.
A dad link.
That's understanding of your interests.
Fantastic dad link.
Yeah, none of them worked out.
A various like, I think lawsuits and shadiness of companies.
I don't know where it stands today,
but yeah, it's just been this kind of creepy,
abandoned mushroom patch.
This is what fueled my desire to go.
Because I should publicly admit,
I foolishly never made it to Mars 2112.
And I will regret it for the rest of my life.
Lived in New York, never went.
Never went, walked past.
Oh, you had the opportunity.
Oh yeah, I had the opportunity.
Never went, never went, sadly.
And so now I'm like, I can't ever do that to myself again.
Was not Mars 2112 also in Schomburg?
Woodfield, yeah.
The Woodfield Mall, which we went to Chicago
and did a live show all about the Woodfield Mall.
So there was one, that's right.
That's why I was so.
It is so weird that this whole audience
doesn't know about Woodfield Mall.
That's so weird.
Yeah, we've primed them, we've conditioned them.
We've got it all at Woodfield.
There's a theme song?
There's a song, an old commercial,
which we sang in the show.
I was, I didn't grow up there,
but I was like, every time Mike talked about it,
it just really, it called to me, it intrigued me.
And for, with good reason.
Mars, and you didn't go to that one either?
I didn't go to that one.
Woodfield Mall was, so I learned to drive very late,
which means I was bad at it.
So when I finally was allowed to drive,
I think only senior year of high school,
or I would like drove with friends once they could drive.
We would go, Woodfield Mall was the furthest we could go.
That was like the furthest we could take ourselves in a car
and we would go to go to Forever 21,
because there wasn't one near us,
to get going out tops, and then we would drive back.
Going out tops, sure.
It was impossible to imagine a time
where Forever 21s weren't there.
I know, Woodfield was like,
we gotta go and get going out tops.
We're going to college.
We need tops.
And then we'd turn around.
It wasn't as, you know,
with theme restaurants, we're in our goal on that trip.
What's a key word of a going out top
from the mid 2000s or whenever?
Some sort of like gems on the neckline,
but a lower neckline, but gems.
And then maybe a, what I would call a bubble hem, I think?
Where it's, the bottom is elastic,
so it kind of poofs over, where it's like,
brrroop, brrroop.
And then anything that has some weird crisscross
in the back, crisscross straps.
Oh, I see, yeah, yeah, okay.
And, importantly, going out tops,
by the time you drove back home, they had disintegrated.
Oh, absolutely.
Yeah, they were not.
Yes, yeah.
Crisscross gone.
Yeah, crisscross gone.
If there was any rain
between leaving Woodfield Mall and our car, over.
Yeah, I remember in college,
people would talk about going out tops,
and there was also like, the subtext was like,
if we spill stuff on this or vomit on it,
it just will go in the garbage.
I keep everything, they're all gone.
It's not gonna withstand
an industrial dorm washing machine.
Oh my God.
And no one is going to the dry cleaner.
No one's, hey, can I get a ride from my dorm
to the cleaners?
Oh my God, that's so true.
I can't even, if you asked me,
if you would pay me a million dollars
to find a dry cleaners on the Urbana Champagne campus,
I would, I'd be poor, like it would never happen.
I can't think of a single dry cleaners in my college town.
There's gotta be one.
But I can't think of it,
and I walked those streets for years.
Well, I can't think of a Bloomington Normal dry cleaner.
Exactly.
When I spent a semester out here
and lived at the Oakwood Apartments over by Universal,
where they put up child actors and their families and stuff,
I did go to the cleaners,
because there was one in the complex,
because I needed like a windbreak.
I needed sleeves shortened,
sleeves and pant cuffs.
I need shortened.
I'm sorry, you were getting tailoring
while you were basically studying abroad?
You were so cool.
With the jacket I bought at Sears.
Wow!
The recently reopened Burbank Sears, that's right.
It's back.
They reopened it.
Wait, that's a current reopening, not a past one?
Yes, it's a current reopening.
It closed, it was closed for a while,
and then all of a sudden one day
they just turned the lights back on.
Burbank Sears is?
Burbank Sears is back.
It is, yeah.
The Disney memorabilia auction
was at the old bed bath and beyond,
not the old Sears.
Whoa.
Yeah, and it's not that it's gotten nice or anything.
People don't know why it's reopened either.
There's speculation in the media
why Sears has reopened, this specific Sears,
because most Sears have closed.
They still have an online business,
but there's a lot of like,
we reached out to Sears for comment,
and Sears is not being clear with us
why this is open again.
Is this a part of a strategy?
Is this just because they want the real estate
to at least be generating some,
nobody knows for sure.
What media is reaching out to Sears for comment?
CNN.
The Guardian, Wall Street Journal.
We spoke to the Burbank Sears.
Jason and I had a conversation about this,
and we were looking up online.
There might have been CNN.
We're trying to figure it out.
Speculation is a shorter way to type out
alleged money laundering.
It seems suspicious from the way that Sears
just isn't explaining why.
Yeah.
They haven't reopened the tax preparer,
and the optical, and the photo center.
You cannot get your taxes prepared anymore.
You cannot get eyeglasses at the Burbank Sears,
but you can still buy-
But you can pick up some Covington lounge wear,
some Structure button-up shirts.
You can buy some-
You know the brands that Sears has.
Oh, God!
I've spent some time at Sears, by the way.
I've got some Sears Christmas gifts in my time.
Oh, my God.
Damn, now you've lived.
So, in the same way where you're worried
about Rainforest Cafe going away,
I say get to the Burbank Sears while it's back open.
I'm gonna have to go after this.
I had no idea.
It feels like entering the set of The Phantom of the Opera.
No one knows why things are happening.
And it's just as scary in there.
It's just as bleak seeming, and dim, and unnerving.
It reopened, because it's like that cursed soundstage
that they eventually demolished on the Universal lot.
It's like, we left this set up.
Don't go in there.
Sears controls this.
Sears has a mind of its own.
Yeah, so we have lost, they are disappearing in California.
And this was all, it was down to one,
when we talked about it in the Downtown Disney ordeal.
South Coast Plaza had one, and Costa Mesa,
that's now Dentifung.
Fisherman's Wharf is gone.
Downtown Disney, as we all know,
has been a Star Wars store for quite some time.
Which it is funny that, for a lot of years now,
after Galaxy's Edge opens,
which is this new dimension of immersive theming,
and where you're watching all these materials
about how they studied the floors in Turkey,
and the tiles, and what would you be walking on,
and what type of stone would be.
And then meanwhile, at a public facing,
not far from that, for years now,
they've had a thing that's just like,
Star Wars Rainforest Cafe, it's fine.
It's like a temple, you know, there'd be a temple.
All right, it's not just a temple,
though, we put a satellite dish on it.
So that's Star Wars, that's what Star Wars is.
That's gonna be fine, right?
Yeah, and I don't think anyone's complaining.
I don't think anyone's.
Yeah, truly.
Why haven't we?
If they put it, well, I just think if they put the,
if they move the building into Galaxy's Edge, it would fit.
It would be fine.
I know, that's the thing.
Now, I point all that out, I'm not necessarily against it.
Yeah, I'm not saying.
I am pro that level of Star Wars broadness.
I'm like, yeah, sure, satellite,
we're fine, put a satellite on it.
I agree, yeah.
That would have been, it's fine,
and it could stay there forever.
I mean, it's not supposed to be, right?
It's going away.
I don't know.
Where is that?
For years now,
it's going away, I just say bring back Tracy Tree.
Tracy Tree could be a Star Wars character, why not?
Absolutely, yeah, yeah, well, just like, you know,
put a random apostrophe in her name, and then she'll start to say.
Yeah, just give her an eye patch or something,
make her look like a weather.
Ooh, that's good.
She's a space pirate.
Just wrap her in weird bandages, and then.
Where is the two story Earl of Sandwich going in downtown Disney?
Do we know?
Listen, I'm going to be real with you.
I had a kid, I have no mental capacity.
I decided to turn the lights off when it comes to keeping track of Disneyland changes.
We'll see what happens with Disneyland forward,
and then I'll start paying attention.
But to me, I'm like, yum, yum, I'm going to get my Portos,
I'm going to get my Din Tai Fung,
and I don't know anything else that's happening.
Got it.
You'll know where they are when you get there.
Yes, and also, I've been burnt so many times by Disneyland changing their plans
and being so excited.
I remember they were going to build that gorgeous new five diamond hotel,
six diamond hotel, I think it was,
or the amazing hotel maybe in 2018.
Yes.
When they removed those plans, I was like, I will wait until I see it built,
and then I will be excited.
It was a six diamonds.
Yeah.
It's going to be so fancy.
The art didn't make it look nice, I'll say.
The art looked like it was just this big warehouse building.
It was not up to your diamond standards.
It was not up to my diamond standards,
as far as a beautiful looking hotel.
It just looked kind of utilitarian.
Well, Mike is in the brotherhood of cross keys, like in Grand Budapest.
Oh, yes, okay.
The concierge.
You lost me for a half second, and then I got you, and then I'm back.
Which is kind of based on reality.
There is kind of an unspoken or a pseudo union for hotel people.
I wouldn't know that.
That was a long time to talk in, this kind of, and I'm so good.
You're going to do a full minute in that town.
Exaggerated for the movie.
You were twiddling your fingers the whole time.
Yeah, well, that's great for an audio medium.
You get some hand movements in there.
People can hear the twiddling, though.
Sure.
Don't you twiddle, twiddle.
Don't you feel like they've toyed with our emotions over Earl's sandwich so often?
Well, Earl keeps moving.
I'm not tracking this.
That's why I'm like, I'm going to sound like, I'm good at my job, I promise.
But they keep telling me it's here, then it's going away, and then it's back.
It's going to be everything.
And it's too much.
It's going to be Tertia Joes and where it is currently, the former La Brea, and the
Star Wars, and it's going to be the Earl of Sandwich Temple.
I think they're giving all of Tomorrowland over to Earl of Sandwich, too.
It's like an auxiliary classroom.
Like when it's like, oh, they're doing vent work at your elementary school.
Music class is in the trailer now.
Yeah, a couple of people roll up with like five igloo coolers full of sandwiches, and
then they just like take cash from people at this point.
Like they've moved it around in such like just random places.
It's a shape shifter.
If you don't get your hopes up, you won't get your heart broken.
So when they open it, I'll be there and thrilled.
But until then, I'm just going to wait.
I don't want to get too excited.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
As you are also, you don't want your heart broken by the eventual disappearance of this
chain from our war, because it does, you know, even, you know, they move, but that's a
little scary.
Vegas closed, but it moved.
Mall of America closed, but it moved.
But it's it's on the fence.
It's on the ropes, I feel like, in Ontario mills, unless you seem to be implying that
it was pretty jammed, that things are happening there.
It will jammed?
I don't know.
OK, all right.
The animatronics?
Good.
The crowd?
Quite possibly mostly non-existent.
OK, OK.
That's what I was.
That was that was kind of the case when I went in early 2020.
Might have been.
And we were there at an odd time when you're there at like on a Wednesday
at two o'clock.
Yeah, we went on a weekday, middle of the day.
We were told that it was they weren't busy right now, but they had been busy.
Not an aggressive please keep coming way, but in like a normal Broadway because
I went with my friends and my friend Kelsey made the reservation.
And unbeknownst to me, she wrote a bit of an essay requesting a specific table.
And we rolled up and she was so stressed about like I from what I remember, she was
so stressed about not getting the table and they were like, you're fine, you're getting it.
And I brought the essay with me.
Oh, yes.
If you would like to hear it.
I'm so curious what table and why.
OK.
Oh, wow.
This is from her.
Oh, oh, the fact that research was done in order to or just
there was awareness of a special table.
This is from her reservation confirmation email under the special requests when making it.
Hello.
We cannot express our genuine excitement for our upcoming
Rainforest Cafe experience.
We're traveling hours from all over the state just to come to you because we miss you so much.
In the spirit of it never hurts to ask, we would love to be able to sit in one of the circular
booths nestled into the plants and animals.
Also, if available, we'd absolutely spend a silly amount on the balloon artist
and would be ecstatic to get a visit from the froggy mascot.
We are so sad that all of your California sibling stores have succumbed to deforestation,
but are so excited to come to you in Ontario for a special trip.
Oh, wow.
So the hostess saw this and was like, I got you.
This was the hand delivered at the door.
This was the like online reservation.
She pulled up in like the POS or whatever that's called.
So she pulled up.
Oh, like Kelsey, party of four and saw this.
And knew she'd take care of us.
Like, well, we got a paragraph.
Check the POS as a paragraph here.
Yeah.
Better deal with it.
I understand, though, the request, because when I just did a pop in, you know, look,
you're not going wrong with theming in that place anywhere.
But we were just middle of room.
We weren't enveloped in plant life.
It must have been incredible.
It was it was incredible.
It was because we had pretty high hopes.
We've been planning this for years.
And we got there.
And is this this a pro swearing podcast?
Yeah.
Oh, swearing.
We lost our shit.
We were so thrilled.
It was better than we expected.
We thought, haha, like all the animatronics will be broken.
This will be funny, but sad.
No, it felt alive.
It felt fun.
We sat across from Atlas, which was very exciting.
Is Atlas?
Wait, what's Atlas?
Atlas is Atlas, like the the man.
Oh, you mean the big, gold man.
Yeah.
With the OK.
So we were sitting nestled in plants.
Oh, that's like all the way.
That's that's where we were.
Yeah, we were truly in a VIP booth.
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
He has a big orb that says and it says, rescue the rainforest.
We like the top of an Emmy or something.
Yes.
We could see him.
The elephants were behind us to the right.
I think we had some sort of monkey at our table.
Is Atlas from something other than the rainforest?
Is he just mythology?
So we just got they haven't taken the I'm just saying is like,
is this that God?
Is it a rainforest cafe IP?
Yeah.
OK, it's not original, not an original character, not an original.
But I didn't know that because I have in my notes just like big gold man.
I didn't realize that was meant to be Atlas.
The Atlas.
I mean, was it explained to me at the table?
Yes, it was.
But now we know now that I know.
Did they still have the bar stools that look like animal?
Jason, you know, they did.
You know, they did.
And they were empty, which was upsetting.
I wanted to go to the bar for a drink after, but we didn't have time.
I wanted to nestle into one of those little giraffe butts, giraffe seats,
seats, seats.
There you go.
That's the only that's that's the swearing that we we do.
That's the only one that we monitor.
Let's just call it seats.
And they were beautiful.
And also last night when I was just like, wait, who who invented rainforest cafe?
I wound up on the website of the guy who makes the seat seats.
Oh, wow.
Fascinating man.
You guys got to do some some sort of episode about that.
Was this the guy?
Is there somebody different who did the seat seats specifically?
Or do you mean like the restaurant?
There's an artisan.
Oh, who does the?
Yeah.
It's like Seat Seats by Gregory something.
Whoa, gosh.
Oh, you've dropped a person.
Oh, man.
Yeah.
I wish we had this at our.
Wow.
Because they are pretty, you know, there's like there's braiding on those
rope tails.
Listen, you when you see a podcast, the right episode forming.
Yeah.
Like this was that.
All right.
So separate episode is the artisan.
Please send us that info.
I will.
Got it.
That's exciting.
It's almost turn them out.
It's some like rainforest cafe factory.
But no, it's true art.
And that's why it looks so good.
They also that zone is called the Magic Mushroom Bar.
I've seen it referred to as the Magic Mushroom Juice Bar.
I feel like now it's, you know, utilitarian.
It's planned to, you know, play into a broad audience where people want,
you know, booze.
Unfortunately, I think there was a time and when it opened,
when there was only one location at the Mall of America,
when it was meant to be fully a juice bar,
which is pretty in keeping with the theming, I would say.
But what an insane idea.
And that's especially I mean, they're all pretty ambitious in various ways.
There's the aquariums, the store is a massive operation.
And you've got your magic mushroom bar.
The Mall of America one.
They must have stopped this, right?
Maybe the other locations did.
But at least that first one was also a pet store.
You could leave with exotic birds.
You could buy birds who lived in the rainforest cafe.
Like Pantor of the World of Avatar, but real?
Yeah, yes.
It's like it's contradicting the other half of the establishment.
You think the message is a little muddled there?
Caging exotic birds.
But yeah, you could buy a macaw or a toucan or a cockatoo.
And they at this time, this is when the store was like swinging.
It opened, it had a big hit year or two, the first couple of years.
And they said they sold one bird a week, which doesn't sound like a lot,
but that nets you a fifteen hundred to twenty five hundred.
Wow.
So that's good.
One bird a week.
Can you imagine going to the Mall of America and the thing you leave with is a toucan?
Do you bag that up or do they probably got to breathe?
You probably got to let them put that on your shoulder.
The way the Mall of America was hyped, though, when I was a kid, when we were kids,
it actually makes sense because it feels like they were hyping it up
is like this is everything you would want.
That is true.
Including toucans.
So that is so funny that they did that.
That helped.
Do you know how long that lasted?
I don't know.
No.
And I think that first one was a whole other ballpark.
Like, yeah, you know, more ambitious than the others.
But the others are incredibly ambitious, too.
I mean, that's the footprint.
You can attest to that Ontario one.
I mean, I'm never going to get over this bird store.
I'm simply like never going to be able to process this information.
It's really weird.
And then also, like just other early stuff that maybe just that one had.
OK, so like I think all of them have the aquarium, basically,
where you walk through this big, like bright blue, bold blue.
And there's probably fish in there.
I think maybe not.
No, I think anyone listening to this has seen the YouTube video
of the dude who went to all the rainforest cafes.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Eddie Burback, is that correct?
It's Burback, not Burbank.
And as as that person pointed out, there are many,
some select ones that don't have fish.
This one just had bubbling water.
OK, which if you go in, not expecting that, it's very jarring
to enter some place that's like the rainforest is alive and thriving.
And from the from the drop, you're just like, no animals.
Not here.
And you have to I mean, your brain just kind of jumps
to conclusions that, you know, we're here after the pandemic.
Malls kind of closed suddenly.
What happened to these fish?
Oh, yeah.
Was that a slide out during that?
Yeah, I don't know.
What happened when it closed?
Like was it like who's taking the fish home?
And like, was there a whole debate and then nobody could?
I know.
I don't know.
Oh, and everyone forgot.
Everybody just like pencils down and nobody ever ran.
It feels a little bad that there's no fish there.
I heard like an apocryphal story about the fish at the Wynn Casino in Vegas,
that like a security guard, like the first few months
when all the casino hotels were closed, they were just like,
I don't know about the fish.
Just leave them.
What are we going to do?
And like one security guy took it upon himself to scoop out the fish food
and like keep the fish alive.
Oh, wow.
See, I don't because if you're like in a hotel,
you're security, you're in the hotel.
Yeah.
If you're just inside the gate of a of an outlet mall that isn't open,
I don't know.
Yeah.
And I don't listen.
Don't sue me.
Landry's, please don't come for me.
But it felt disconcerting that post pandemic it was a very empty tank.
There would have to be like some altruistic like man or woman
who comes into the mall at night or comes into the rainforest cafe at night.
And yeah, Mr.
Mills, like Mr.
Mills is coming in with the skeleton key and Sir Mills.
He owns many of them.
Sir Mills.
Yeah.
That is one.
The one in Philadelphia, the former Franklin Mills, now the Philadelphia Mills.
That one apparently closed in February of 2001,
but it only opened in 1998.
So very short lifespan of the Philadelphia rainforest.
Is that area not not like?
No, it's a it's a giant outlet mall.
The mills.
Is there anything else?
Is there anything else fun in that mills or is it kind of a boring functional mill?
Well, I believe if you look up, there was a giant Ben Franklin,
like a multi story like Ben Franklin thing.
Like, I don't even know how to describe it.
It wasn't a store where you could buy Ben Franklin.
Somewhere between a statue and a puppet.
Oh, it moved.
Yeah.
Oh, that's interesting.
And it's a little frightening.
Size wise, are we talking a transformer?
Like, what are we working with?
Yeah.
Bigger.
Oh, like both stores like bigger than it.
Wait, a transformer is really big.
Bigger.
Yeah.
Like both stories of the mall, like in an atrium in the mall.
Were you scared?
I don't know if I ever saw it in person.
I might have just seen pictures.
I'd be frightened.
Or it's a nightmare you had.
Jason, growing up in Philadelphia would often have nightmares of a giant
man eating Ben Franklin Kaiju.
Ben Franklin.
Ben Franklin versus Godzilla.
I mean, we there there are a number of things
in film that like there is a Dickensian Christmas village
underneath the Macy's downtown.
A subterr- a one with a roof and a basement?
That used to be a Wanamaker's Wanamaker, a former big department store chain.
My grandmother claimed she was fourth cousins with John Wanamaker.
You say claims.
What a brag.
You say claims as if you're a little bit in doubt about it.
OK.
False brag.
It's like Barbara Streisand's basement.
I am sorry.
I was over exaggerating this
Ben Franklin puppet thing.
Only probably one story so closer to a transformer.
What you're talking about a transformer like in the park,
you're not talking about a because a transformer in the world is in the movie
is like many stories tall.
I mean, that's about bumblebee sized, I would say.
Well, it depends.
They're not like six stories tall.
I think they're like maybe one and a half or shorter.
Is that right?
I think so.
What's the scale of it?
Some of them are taller than that, aren't they?
I mean, I guess because like
Megatron and like I've seen the first one.
I've seen Sam Witwicky and bumblebee, and it feels like bumblebee
can just kind of crouch down.
That's what I was going to say.
They come to your eye level and they wouldn't be able to do that
if they were so big.
Yeah.
If they were like Godzilla size, it wouldn't be.
I think they're only like one and a half stories or maybe like around.
So yeah, like that Ben Franklin.
But that is frightening.
The mills, the mills chain about that, of course, this is a Simon owned.
Oh, of course, Simon, of course, the company runs the malls.
Of course.
Uh, I never remember them being super crowded or particularly desirable.
The mills, uh, location.
I've talked a lot of review.
Yeah, I've talked a lot of smack about mills over the years.
And maybe we maybe we need to do some kind of mills roundup,
determine what else is weird like that, like the Franklin.
What else are weird at mid mills?
The standard Simon malls.
I mean, I feel like a lot of the malls around Philadelphia, uh, were nice.
And then eventually started to consolidate ownership and Simon starts buying up.
And then I think I like Westfield more than Simon.
I'm disappointed.
Westfield man.
I'm a Westfield man.
But that's they're all Westfields.
Are you a Simon lad?
Are you a little Simon boy?
I don't know.
I mean, they didn't save the Granite Run Mall.
It's kind of a weird.
My childhood mall is a weird Frankenstein.
We're like some of the.
No, no, no.
A Franklin Stein.
Oh, it's a.
Oh, the mills is a Franklin Stein.
Where it's like one or two of the anchors stayed and then they built like a pseudo
outdoor mall.
Thank you for that.
So you're not even, you wouldn't declare anything, any allegiance, any type of boy
you are as far as mall ownership.
Well, certainly moving out here.
Yeah.
I've become a little Westfield boy.
Okay.
So you're more of a little Westfield boy as well.
Yeah.
Okay.
Or fashion square lad.
I don't want to be a little Caruso lady.
Oh no.
I think the little is optional.
These guys are always going for the little if that's in the.
Yeah.
If you're a fan of anything, adding I'm a little something boy is generally how we
like to.
It's generally.
Yeah.
And very, uh, non-off putting it's on putting America.
I don't know.
I think I'm a.
The bank.
Oh, because I believe the company was leveraging, uh, using.
Mall of America credit to run the American dream mall.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, wait, my brain is going back to all the press releases I got about American
dream.
Um, who, who runs that?
Who runs that?
I don't know.
It's like, it's not a particularly memorable name.
Can I wait or wait, is it Simon?
It is Simon.
Simon's part of it.
Or they manage it.
Uh, I think it's owned by triple five.
That's the, they own those, these mega malls, mall of America, West Edmonton,
which is huge and has a theme park in it and American dream, which is a bizarre
nightmare that I got lost in.
Had a very hard experience.
I spent my birthday there.
You did?
Yeah.
I went to the Shrek water park for my birthday.
You know, like a normal adult woman does before the, uh, the, the collab before
stuff started falling.
Oh yeah.
We went, uh, we went during the pandemic, but during a, you know, like a light,
a casual break in it.
Um, but we're my husband and I are neurotic.
So we wore masks up until we got on the water.
It was a real specific time and the people operating them were like, you
can't wear that on the slide.
So we left it next to the vehicle.
Um, but it was great.
I got, I mean, it's so embarrassing.
I got to hug Shrek, like next to the wave pool in a bathing suit, which was
an iconic moment for me, but the problem is my phone was in the locker and my
husband had his phone on him.
So he took all the photos and then I put them in an album and send them to myself.
But he doesn't use his phone, his photo album a lot.
So now anytime you open photos on his phone, there is just an icon of me in a
bathing suit with Shrek every single time.
Just a huge photo.
Cause he doesn't make photo albums.
So you'd open his phone to camera or photo.
It's just me being like, meh in a bathing suit with Shrek forever.
That is how your husband sees you.
That is his primary image.
But have you been to Mall of America?
I've never been actually.
I did.
And the same trip, I did Mall of America and then went to Chicago and saw it.
It was Mall of America and Rock and Roll McDonald's trip.
Oh yeah.
Good trip.
Have you been?
I have not.
It's amazing.
It's pretty good.
Real quick on the topic.
I think, did you do a thing I wanted to do and do an episode, but for some reason
when it was here, I wasn't available.
Did you go to a Shrek grave?
I did not go to a Shrek grave because I was pregnant and I didn't think I could
handle it.
Cause I want to.
But I did.
Look, he can't not take X if you go to a Shrek grave.
I want to do, when it's back, can we go to a Shrek grave or something and do an
episode on it?
I interviewed the founder of it, Cash, and it was one of my favorite interviews
of all time.
I did a podcast episode on it and I have never, I don't think in my life I've left
an interview that happy.
Wow.
It was just, we had so much fun talking about Shrek grave.
I felt like, you know, when you like meet people in college who like the same
things as you and you're just on one, it was that.
It was pure joy.
It was, the episode's still up.
You and Candace for that, the line.
Yeah.
Over Zoom.
We were so happy.
Are you excited to visit Shrek's home at Universal Studios Florida soon?
Don't even get me started.
Oh boy.
I'm so, I've done all the Shrek experiences except for, I never made it to
Universal Studios Singapore, sadly, because I went on a huge tour and by then I went
with my husband.
He's fun, I promise, but he went to four international theme parks and was like,
no, no more.
I missed that.
And then I haven't been to, is the ride in Dubai?
The indoor, there's a dark ride, a Shrek dark ride.
Oh, I don't know.
Yeah.
I haven't done that.
There's a few other.
Oh, for anyone who doesn't have context, every December I do Shrek's number on
my podcast.
We focus on, we've almost run out of Shrek experiences, but we did the Shrek Airbnb
this year and that was good.
Where's that?
What's that?
Shrek Airbnb.
I'm so sorry to derail from Rainforest Cafe, but the Shrek Airbnb was a
promotional thing that one winner was allowed to stay at, they recreated
Shrek's house and they were allowed to stay.
It was in Ireland.
I think my brain's fried, but I hunted down the person who stayed there.
I sleuthed it and I found them and I interviewed them and we talked about the
experience staying in Shrek's house.
Have you gotten any, and I feel like maybe this was on a Jim and Len Disney
dish, they were talking about like, there's a number of years ago, but there
was like rumors of like, well, people like Shrek, but they're sick in the movies.
So it could be prime for a live action, like a Disney version, like a live action
re- I've never heard that since.
No, no, no.
Scarf.
Yeah.
I don't think it would be for me necessarily, but.
I don't think they're doing that.
I think they're doing new anime.
was that just like a meeting where someone was like tapping a pencil on the head?
And it's like, do you think Myers would want to?
I do a lot of it.
Motion capture.
Can you imagine the onions?
Like the, the real swamp, the outhouse?
No thank you.
Zemeck is just licking his chops waiting to do this.
Like, Oh my God.
Sorry, I'm looking at the dates.
The Shrek rave is like, yeah, it's always, it's always, but then like the
one in Los Angeles says it's a spooky rave.
Cause it's unlike, why is it what is it Halloween time?
I don't know.
It's February.
Well, if you should set it in the Shrek 4D timeline, go so far quad.
I don't think it is set in the Shrek 4D.
It just called it's a spooky rave, my bloody Valentine.
And then the next, it's sandwiched by things that just say Shrek rave.
So I don't know why is the Los Angeles market, did they not want Shrek rave?
Maybe they've done it so much where like we need another layer to it.
We're going the opposite direction.
The works of my bloody Valentine.
Yeah, it's weird.
Well, if you want to go, I'm there.
All right, great.
What city do we have to go to, to go to a Shrek rave?
Sacramento, maybe San Diego.
Oh, there's a San Diego, I think.
They did it in Anaheim once too, I think.
Wow.
Yeah, let's see.
There's a, I saw one House of Blues, San Diego, 21024.
And then I think there was one in Sacramento, but that's obviously a little farther.
Yeah.
But if we find out it's better, I mean, we should go to the most quality Shrek rave.
Well, yeah, if an expert could tell us which one it's superior at.
Great.
Let me ask about particulars of your experience.
Were there animatronics you were especially endeared to?
Yes, the elephants.
Elephants.
I thought elephants weren't really going to work.
It just seems like those ears wouldn't flap very well.
It just, I was expecting nothing and it gave everything.
Wow.
They kind of, they like shake around when the storm happens.
They like, they blow those trunks.
So I forgot the storm happened.
So imagine me sitting in our little booth.
We just got in, we're overjoyed.
We made it.
And then there's a storm and I completely forgot.
And my friend took a video of me that I didn't realize at the time.
And I just, it was just an endless shit eating grin.
Just so happy.
I think I had both my hands glued to my face in shock.
It was so fun.
I can't even emphasize how fun this was.
Yeah.
I had a magical time at that one.
Admit it.
I was with a smaller group, but it was like the amount of, you're, you're
shocked by how many storms you get.
If you're there for, if you take a slow lunch, you can maybe get like five storms in.
No problem.
I mean, the later storms obviously don't have the same effect.
We just kept the gabbing about serious life issues, but the first few storms were very fun.
But once we sat down, I don't remember the exact process.
It must've been the waiter who asked if I wanted to be a member of, I think it's
Landry's Select Club.
Well Jason would know.
Yeah, I'm a member of the club as well.
You're a Landry's Select too?
I don't know if it's Landry's Select, but I'm a Landry's card holder.
We have Lowry's cards.
Yeah, I have both of those.
You have both.
Although you're more of the Landry's cause of course the Landry's points came up.
I was trying to be nice and I was like, Oh, get him some points.
Cause then when he was at Landry's and he just automatically used whatever credit was on it.
His father worked for decades for those points and he comes in and just takes them.
A Morton's one year and a Chart House the next.
We earned those points.
They had Morton's too?
Yeah.
So Landry's owned Landry's Quadrant Forest Cafe in 2000.
Yes.
They of course own Morton's and Chart House and the Golden Nugget.
Your of course's are interesting.
Of course.
Yeah.
I mean not like a long going yes, yes, yes, yes.
I too am now a card carrying member.
I'm proud of myself.
And this was one of them.
The way the manager came over and thanked me for joining brought me the paperwork.
I love the thanks.
Like buying a car.
It's like getting a promotion just for dining there.
Yeah.
Now just remember you can't put the points back on the card.
Jason tried.
I tried.
I was like, no, I just wanted the points.
The scramble when it happened.
I felt so bad because it was probably like the I think they give you 20 bucks on your birthday or something.
Well, I spent 25 but with the promise of I have $25 credit coming.
Yeah.
That's on the card.
So it was a little bit of a dark exchange.
Jason grabbing the guy by the collar.
Put him back.
Those are my father's.
I want to talk to Scampi.
I want to talk to the big shrimp mascot.
Scampi is a shrimp, but Cha Cha is a frog.
Do not get your Landry characters confused.
I didn't know the shrimp had a name.
I believe it is Scampi.
I forget that every time we've done all these series.
I think I looked it up because the last time none of us could remember.
I'm like, I need to remember what that and I think it's Scampi.
Oh my god.
I believe it's Scampi.
And it's confusing because the one at CityWalk Hollywood is always very filthy.
It's a dirty, dirty shrimp.
But he should be called filthy.
He should be called filthy.
Filthy shrimp.
Yeah, you got to take him out back to the CityWalk hose.
Give him a wad of water.
The CityWalk hose.
Go to their hose.
The only one.
Once John Lovett's comedy club shut down, there used to be two hoses, but then the water pipes were shut off.
Lovett said he angrily took the hose with him.
Yeah.
Now wait a minute.
One of your requests was, if possible, a Cha Cha appearance.
Yes.
So Kelsey was, as you can tell, better versed about the offerings at Rainforest Cafe than the rest of us were.
We never got to see a Cha Cha character.
I didn't know who Cha Cha was until we got there.
And then obviously, like rolling up to Disney World with no context, you know who the main character is.
We all immediately bought Cha Cha slippers, which were a shockingly affordable $10 each.
Oh wow.
Okay.
Are you still buying her prices on slippers?
I was like, I'm going to spend $27.
99 on this piece of plastic, but I'm never going to get back $10.
And it was one that I hadn't seen before, now that I've seen videos at Rainforest Cafe.
It was just Cha Cha's head.
It was all head.
Not head on a cup.
Full head.
Okay.
Oh, that's what you want.
An immersive, yeah, yeah.
If it's only part of a cup, that feels functional.
Yes.
You all did it.
We all bought it.
And then of course, we opted for the professional photo in a frame, which don't get it twisted.
That's not a frame.
It's a piece of paper around a photo.
And when they came to our booth and they took our photo and we looked at it, the only way
I can describe it is that it looks like we're in The Shining.
Just holding our little Cha Chas in front of our heads, so happy, but possessed.
Completely possessed.
Just not right.
New Year's Eve, 1920.
Yep.
And you zoom in on us being like, yeah.
You sent that photo a little while ago.
And like, yes, I collect four Cha Cha slippers.
And then that, like, Raid Forest Cafe, so the frame is going to be like a fun, it's
a bunch of leaves and vines.
You know, it's just kind of like fake gold leafing.
It's just kind of like what an old restaurant would have.
It's not green and kooky.
Just normal.
I thought it was a frame, like I'm going to hang it on my wall because I'm dumb.
Little flappy.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, so that's all cool.
Wait, there was another request though.
Oh, the balloons.
The balloon person never came to us.
Okay.
But they were there.
They were there.
So we were in the booth facing Atlas, just to give you the layout.
And there was a table next to Atlas and they got balloons.
So we got to enjoy their balloons from afar.
Okay.
I think someone had a palm tree with a coconut that they were wearing as a hat.
There was a very good balloon art happening, but we were never really offered the balloon
art, which is fine.
That's strange.
It was in your, how many?
Like you put it in your requests.
Yes, it does.
It's not a crowded restaurant.
How in the world does the balloon artist not make it to you?
You know, it wasn't as disappointing as I'm making it sound now.
We were just so happy the entire time that nothing like, you know, going to the bathroom,
seeing Queen of the Jungle, like just everything was spot on perfect.
Not getting a balloon was fine.
That bathroom's funny.
I was only in the men's, but if it's the same style, it's very like airbrush.
Yeah.
It's very like old t-shirt style.
Yeah, that's nice.
I liked it in there.
and I am just kind of like guns blazing about the food quality.
I'm just like, it's shit, bad.
That's not the only experience.
I've only had bad experiences with the food, but let me ask you now about the food portion
of all this.
How'd you feel about the food?
No complaints.
Wow.
And you know what?
Here I am listening to myself years ago, flapping on.
I got the aforementioned mojo bones.
I really liked the mojo bones.
I had a good time.
I remember thinking like, have I been underrating?
Maybe it's location dependent, but I don't know.
They got the mojo.
The mojo bones have the mojo.
I knew what I was getting into, and I was coming out of a long night where I didn't
drink much, but I have no tolerance.
So I was just kind of exhausted, spaced out, got there so happy, so thrilled, got to eat
chips and dip, got to eat a spinach artichoke dip, but like just fun food, fun food with
friends.
It was great.
It wasn't artisanal.
And I went into it knowing that there is a chance it was possibly frozen, and then they
reheated some of the food, possibly.
I don't know.
I don't work in the kitchen.
So I went, I ordered from that perspective.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If that's where you set your meter.
Yes.
And you know what else I think has happened to me since we've now done so much multiple
city walks in downtown Disney.
We have experienced some food lows.
I think my bar has been lowered a lot.
Yeah, my mojo bone experience, if there's not something specifically wrong, which there
was not, I don't know.
I got what I wanted.
I got no complaints.
Just real quick, clarify what are mojo bones?
Is it just ribs?
It is just ribs.
Yes.
How dare you demystify it?
I said it so many times without saying that I even had to remember.
I've had that phrase mojo bones haunting me and yet I could not until looking at my photos
from that day, could not remember that they are ribs.
I was just imagining the big thing of ribs put on Fred Flintstone's car.
Oh, that'd be fun.
Yeah.
Not that crazy.
You can imagine though.
You can blow them up in your head.
Is mojo the name of the pig that they
I add this question.
I don't think so because I think that's weird to
I could be wrong.
It is weird.
It's also weird to eat animals in the Rainforest Cafe because the rainforest
You want to preserve the rainforest.
You don't eat elephant.
Well, that's true, yes.
But there might be a wild
Is there a wild hog in the rainforest somewhere?
There might be.
There isn't now.
There might be a boar.
Well, right, because mojo is dead.
I'll check my menu.
They might have been jaguar bones.
Oh, that's the canon explanation?
Or just truly.
Oh no, you ate Maya the Jaguar.
All these characters have names, by the way.
Oh, right, right, right.
In addition to Cha-Cha.
There's some sort of creole influence in the menu, which I feel like I picked up there,
and then I saw later when I was reading about it.
Yeah.
Right?
Yeah, I think so.
You get some jambalayas, right?
Which I don't know where that crossover happened.
Zatarand's warehouse was just closing, so they bought everything in full.
A lot of surplus jambalaya.
I mean, I guess that's a question when you open this place.
Where do you go with it?
And you imagine kind of like South American or something.
But yeah, I don't know.
I never felt like I was eating my new friends, especially the ones with names, as you mentioned.
Thank God.
I never felt, yeah.
You don't want to slaughter.
There was nothing.
I mean, Cha-Cha's the star.
The other ones, I don't know, but I would bet my life on the fact that Jason does.
Rio the macaw, Tukey the elephant, Ozzy the orangutan, Bamba the gorilla, Iggy the iguana.
That one's a little lazy.
And Nile the crocodile.
We saw Nile the crocodile outside the Woodbridge one.
Yeah.
I'm assuming that was Nile.
That's the freebie.
That's the freebie, I think.
What's that?
That's the freebie.
Oh, yeah.
You don't have to buy anything.
Yeah, a little taste.
There's a snake.
There's that.
There's one other.
Yeah.
I think at Nashville, instead of a crocodile, they got a hippo.
Oh.
Was that listed?
The hippo?
Why?
Special just for Nashville.
The snake was where I, and maybe this has been improved since I was there, but I took a video
under the snake where I'm just seeing the peel from the tongue, from that nasty black.
I was right under it.
Maybe all of them would suffer if you walked right up to it, but this you can.
You're walking right under that snake.
I was just imagining bits peeling off and into an open beverage container or something.
The snake was not looking great.
I will have
That's why you got to get a souvenir cup.
It's covered.
Cha-cha's head is fully intact.
Oh, Chai just bounces right off of Cha-cha's forehead.
Keep your soda secure.
It's an interesting experience going to that one, the Odyssey to get there.
I was very fond of my experience.
There's a lot of notable parts about it for me.
I went with a friend of the show, Bugman, Buzz Buzz.
I think I texted you about this forever ago.
While we were there, it was announced that Chapec is taking over as CEO.
That's where I was when that happened, which also places
Who doesn't remember where they were?
Everyone was in Vegas.
I was napping in Vegas, and I woke up to a flurry of text messages.
Jason, wake up!
Ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, ding!
That also places it at right pre-pandemic, because as we all know, he was put in as a
fall guy, with Diger's advanced knowledge that the pandemic was coming.
You got the rich guy dossier.
Just him and Oprah got it.
That's what happened.
But also, when I'm looking at my photos of my little Mills expedition,
pandemic is in my head, because two weeks later, it was raging.
This is one of the last things I did before, which also means that I'd missed the detail.
That mall has a truly massive AMC.
It's a 30 screen.
30, yeah.
It is like, upsettingly big.
You feel so small.
You feel like an ant before it.
So many hallways.
What's that?
There's got to be so many hallways there.
There's probably wings.
And like, no, you're in A2.
No, you're in B9.
We got an AMC 30 in Schomburg.
Really?
Gosh, Schomburg.
You got it all.
That's nothing to you.
It's such a novelty to me.
You said it, and I scoffed.
They're going to be playing that Sidney Sweeney Glenn Powell romantic comedy forever.
Yeah, they're going to be playing that for no one in August.
Amphibum $100 million gross is just made in Schomburg.
From Schomburg, yeah, that's right.
There was a Shoney's right by there.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa.
It feels weird, like urban ruins or something, my photos of this, though.
Because already nobody's at that theater.
And then all the coming attraction posters.
I don't know why I took pictures of posters, but they're all for movies like Black Widow
and Lovebirds that we now know all became pandemic releases, just kind of sadly spurted out at home.
So it's a real, this was a window in time.
Yeah, really?
I really had bookend visits.
Yeah, yeah.
Yours was like post and optimistic.
It was my first indoor dining in a really long time.
That was it?
Yeah.
I made all my friends test.
We were very stressed about it.
It was my first indoor dining.
I was willing to catch COVID, rain forest cafe.
Thankfully, there were not a lot of people there.
You're going to get it anywhere.
And so your first indoor dining was a fake outdoors.
That's interesting, isn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, we have seasons of not indoor dining.
So this was one of the breaks.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, we basically, the way I try to do it is that I, well, for a while I had a younger baby
and you got to be careful then.
But I try to, if I have a trip, I don't want to ruin the trip.
So then I prepare before the trip and then I end up traveling so much that I end up masking forever.
Oh, I see.
Yeah.
Okay.
That's why it took me years to go to rain forest cafe.
Okay, okay.
Gotcha.
So you're beaming this, but this is just like
It was better than I thought it was going to be.
I thought we'd have to pretend to be happy, you know?
So we schlepped all the way there, like we'd have to drive back in traffic.
It would be a whole thing.
We had so much fun.
And like, again, the food, you know what you're getting into.
Like I got coconut shrimp.
It's, I'm not like off the water.
I know I'm at, I don't even know where Ontario is.
I don't know what direction I drove in.
Yes, I know.
We've been there and I couldn't see anything else about 30 miles around.
Couldn't tell you.
It was either you go to Disneyland or you're wherever this was.
You could be at the outlets on the way to Disneyland,
or you could be like in the middle of the state.
Yes, had no clue.
Still don't know where it was.
My car almost died when I was there.
Had to find a charger.
Barely did it.
Oh my God.
Couldn't figure out where I was.
Wow.
Yeah, like just somewhat lost, but it was worth it.
It was incredible.
We obviously got, oh, what is it called?
The chocolate explosion, the volcano, the
The volcano, the Sunday.
Yes, I forget because they have a
They have a similar dessert at T-Rex at Disney Springs.
Which is also in Bylandries, but it's not a rainforest cafe.
Also created by the same person as Rainforest Cafe.
Steve something.
Steve Schluser.
No, Schulser.
Steve Schleshing.
Steve Schussler.
I've been dreading this this whole time.
Why is it so
Steve Schussler.
Steven Schussler.
Schussler also invented T-Rex.
And their chocolate dessert is
I think it's called chocolate extinction, which is hilarious.
Oh, my dream.
Wow, wow.
That's fantastic.
Yeah.
I think also my friend said it was my birthday and we got a cupcake.
Yes.
Wow, there's a lie involved.
I think so.
It was while I was in the bathroom.
I was not part of it.
Interesting.
This little thing foisted out of that school.
Was there a song then?
You know, I have no memory of it, but there might have been.
Okay, because I wonder what the Rainforest Cafe like non
Like what their version of Happy Birthday is.
Don't think I have a
I don't have a video.
I feel like if they set me up and there was a song, there'd be a video.
Did the animatronics sing it?
And they just make horrible creaking noises when they program that?
Atlas sings it.
You know what I wish they did?
You know that sometimes when like a bunch of like monkeys or orangutans are together,
that they all start playing off each other and they do all their mating calls or whatever that is?
I've been to a sanctuary.
I should know the answer.
I don't.
But they should do that as like an alternate thunderstorm.
Just have all the monkeys start yelling at each other.
Start screaming at each other.
Oh yeah, like in a real realistic way.
That'd be fun.
Your birthday gets us making these monkeys excited to mate.
Like they'd be so angry though.
I'd love that.
It'd be realistic though.
Yeah, it'd be great.
When it's crowded, you just hear angry dads go,
why do I want to eat here either?
This has the shortest wait though.
If you want to go to TGI Fridays, we can.
The call of the tired dads.
Okay, well let me talk a little Steve Shustler.
Shustler.
Steven Shustler.
Julia brought some of this to the table with us a while back,
but I feel like I did not get like entranced by Steven Shustler the way that I should have
because the list of, so he sold a couple of these restaurants to Landry's ultimately,
but he's got this whole like, the credits are nuts.
I think I'm preparing for some gasps here because it's Rainforest Cafe.
Truly personally this guy.
T-Rex Cafe is him.
Yak and Yeti at Animal Kingdom is him.
What a coup for this guy.
He's got two, he's got Rainforest and T-Rex at Disney Springs,
and then Rainforest outside Animal Kingdom,
Yak and Yeti in Animal Kingdom.
It's Shustler land.
It's basically Shustler land.
Then I had no idea the same man was the Boathouse.
Neither did I until last night.
Neither did I.
Totally different concept.
Also fantastic.
Great food.
Fantastic food.
I almost wore my Boathouse shirt today, but I didn't,
feels like it doesn't fit me right now.
I gained some weight being a father, okay?
Feels like it doesn't fit me right.
That's how it comes out.
I couldn't fit in my Boathouse shirt, okay?
I had to wear Hello Kitty.
It fits, it fits.
It's just I was like, it looks weird, it feels weird on me,
but I almost wore it today.
I'm right there with you brother.
I've put a little weight on into it.
Going back to larges, mediums, or getting a little tight.
Well it's in style right now so nobody notices.
I've been told this.
Yes.
My stylist girlfriend assures me Baggy is back.
Baggy is back.
I would trust Jane with anything.
I would, yeah.
She's fantastic at her job.
Sure.
Baggy is back folks.
Baggy is back.
I'm a little baggy boy.
American Apparel dead.
I'm a little baggy boy now, okay?
Even though I just said that I had to wear
that one type of shirt, not another, I've retconned that.
I chose to.
You heard how my brain was able to reconcile it
in real time just now.
I am a little baggy boy now.
You wore your comfy mashup Hello Kitty,
New Japan Wrestling shirt instead.
It's bigger.
The shirt is bigger than my Boathouse
like three-quarter sleeves shirt that I have.
Is it a polo?
No, no, it's a, no.
I'm not a little polo boy.
Not that it's anything wrong with me.
I'm a polo boy.
Notice what word was missing there.
A regular polo boy.
I shouldn't have said boy either.
What am I doing?
Regular polo boy.
You tricked me.
I still said boy.
It's like a baseball tee.
It's a pink Boathouse baseball tee.
It's one of my cherished possessions from like Orlando
as far as Orlando related clothing.
You gotta get to the gym then.
This is a cherished shirt.
You gotta squeeze back in.
No, don't let him bully you.
Go on eBay, buy a bigger size.
Don't listen to him.
That's true.
That is an, wait, yes, there's more of these shirts.
Yeah.
Baseball Boathouse baseball.
I don't mean to bully.
I just want you to have your shirt that you like.
You gotta get on Depop, man.
I'm sure there's some Boathouse stuff there.
I've only seen real, I mean, granted you are a dad,
but real dad clothing, like dad golf wear.
But that's what I was excited about because yes,
they will sell you a captain's hat.
They will sell you a lot of polo shirts,
a lot of like Hawaiian type shirt things.
Just dad clothes, like a captain's hat.
Captain's hat.
Like a dad, that's how you know who's the captain of the family.
Exactly.
but it might have been too expensive.
His family's a fortress.
I was gonna probably buy it for you.
Try to buy it for you.
But then, yeah, that's not necessarily my aesthetic yet.
But then I saw a baseball tee, and that's much more my aesthetic.
And I bought it and I was very excited.
It's pink, and I haven't worn it in a while, and I tried.
Can you imagine the magic moment?
If you wouldn't have known he was wearing it?
I know.
Yeah, yeah, right.
Well, it'll be a magic moment when you roll back in with that,
or probably with a large that you're comfortable with.
They got like a Boathouse here.
There's like this very Margaritaville-style shirt.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, yeah, that feels like a knockoff,
like Daytona Beach kind of shirt.
That's cool.
Wow, I gotta go in that store more.
I wanted to go down when we were back.
I did not make it there.
That is jammed.
We had much crappier restaurants to go to.
Stay tuned on that.
And actually, speaking of, here, let's move over to,
because like, OK, so he's Mr.
Disney, huh?
Well, not necessarily.
He'll cross party lines because his invention was Hot Dog Hall of Fame.
Wow.
Hell yeah.
Coming soon to the City Walk Orlando Saga.
We'll hit that one.
So this guy's just a machine of crazy restaurant ideas.
Dude, I went so deep on this man last night that, OK, his name is Steve.
My brother's name is Steve.
My brother is a surgeon.
He has a full-time job.
And in his free time, he makes Chicago Tavern-style pizza.
And it's amazing because Chicago Tavern-style pizza is not a thing yet.
People don't really know about it.
It's thin.
It's crispy.
It has like buttery crust.
It's amazing.
And I wound up on a story of this guy,
and he's now making a Chicago Tavern-style pizza chain.
He's trying to make it big.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Whoa.
What's the, do you know the name of the chain?
Great question.
So it's something like, like Steve and Dave's big-time pizza.
And my brother, his best friend is named Dave,
and they had a musical group together called Dave and Steve.
Whoa.
Weird.
I texted it to him last night and was like, I'm having a stroke.
Did you want them to play?
I said they should play the opening.
No, my brother's like, I gotta leave it all behind.
I gotta pursue my Tavern-style pizza dream.
Oh, wow.
Oh, gotcha.
But this is almost like a restaurant themed after him.
He's very good at surgery.
He is the theme.
Yeah, but like Tavern-style pizza is coming.
Wow.
Because if this guy says it's so, it has to be.
Geez.
Great.
And well, if he puts his mind to it, it happens.
Oh, and the Dave and Steve and Dave is famous Dave's Dave, I think?
Oh.
Oh, really?
It's like another chain.
Oh, the barbecue.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's a little like buddy-buddy corporate con show.
So if you know, not everyone's going to know who Dave and Steve are, but if you're in the know,
you're in the know.
I mean, famous Dave.
Steve was like, I've opened all these places.
I'm not getting credit.
Yeah, that's exactly what I thought.
He's like, Dave's got all this.
I know.
I want what Dave has.
I want the credit.
Right, because his animals are getting all the credit.
Atlas is getting all the credit and not Steve.
Well, Atlas holds up the world.
Steve should have put himself in there holding up the world.
Yeah, yeah.
Slap his face on there.
And the world is like a meatball or something.
You know, he sold his baby.
He can't do it anymore.
Which maybe might contribute to this chain has decayed a little bit that they've lost some.
Maybe if Steve was still in charge, I don't know.
But he also, I'm sure he cashed in.
Can we just look forward to Rainforest Cafe inventor making a pizza chain?
I mean, that's pretty fun.
We can, yes.
It feels like, I mean, it's got to be over the top.
It can't just be plain.
Yeah, you're right.
That's not just going to be some place.
Yeah, yeah, there's going to be some kooky crap to that.
What is it?
It's thin.
That's the type of pizza it is.
Have you ever, sorry to make it very Chicago centric, have you ever been to Barnabees?
Yeah.
It's like Barnabees?
That's Barnabees, yeah.
Sure.
Do you prefer the deep dish or the tavern cut thin crust?
Look, I'm basic.
I'm a basic guy.
So I am a Lou Melnati's.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's my priority when it comes to the Chicago stuff.
But Barnabees is good.
Yes.
Or was, yeah, it's still there.
It's wonderful.
Yeah.
Is it still there?
Yes, it's still there.
Not the one on Gulf Road, though, I think it's gone.
I think, is that the Northbrook one?
I don't know street names because I didn't drive for a long time.
Sure, and I'm talking local Schomburg.
No, I think there's, sorry everyone, there is the Northbrook one.
And then there's the other one, which my dad prefers, which I think is, I think so.
I think there's one right by O'Hare.
I think so.
Whatever the one that's not Northbrook is the one my dad likes.
Micro specific about Chicago?
I'm sorry, this podcast is micro specific about Burbank.
Those are the rules.
And we say some swears, but not butt or ass.
Those are the rules of podcasts.
Yes, yes.
I'll be close, please.
There's the one deep dish in the valley.
What's it called?
Yes.
Blanking on it.
I haven't been there.
It's pretty good.
It gets you close.
It gets you close to what you want.
They ship.
Oh yeah, we do it.
We did it for Christmas.
Yeah.
Big dream pizza.
Yes.
Is what this is going to be.
Big dream.
Yeah.
The news is on pizzamarketplace.
com.
Is it decorated to Steve's dreams?
They haven't opened it yet.
They were going to, again, I don't sleep.
Why was I up all night doing this?
They had a former drive-in restaurant that they were going to launch within.
Oh yeah, this is an entirely new, yeah, Galaxy Drive-In.
This is the whole one that we missed.
They were going to do it there.
And then recently, I think a year ago, they decided it wasn't big enough for this huge
pizza launch, so there hasn't been any other news, and they sold that to someone else.
Oh, interesting.
But this Tavern pizza trend is coming.
OK.
I'm on board for it.
I've really been on this quest to make the best pizza in America.
When you try Dave's Pizza, you'll never want anything else.
Yeah.
They're talking a big game.
And neither of us plays golf.
Retirement is not the end game.
These guys don't want to stop.
They will not stop until we get the best pizza.
Because Tavern-style pizza is hard to find.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Chicago Tavern-style pizza.
There's a mark.
If these guys seize it properly and make it a thing.
The only way I get it is if my brother makes dough two days in advance and then invites me over.
Wow.
Sure.
Oh, geez.
Well, so this will be special if it happens then.
If I could take it, Mike, or Neach, for a second, about Rainforest Cafe,
one of the other ones I went to growing up is on the Atlantic City Boardwalk.
Whoa.
And like a cat with nine lives, it is survived.
It is survived because it is on the ground floor of the former Trump Plaza casino.
And then they managed to get the utilities transferred to them.
So they managed to stay open.
And then they survived the, it is not the building that was imploded of Trump Plaza
that we talked about a number of years ago.
It is in, and then it survived the pandemic.
And somehow of all the Rainforest Cafes that closed, this one is still going on the Boardwalk.
How can you not be a fan of this chain after hearing that story?
I'm coming around.
I feel like I was talking some shit about it before, but there's something about that.
It's hanging in there.
I mean, that's a story of survival.
Yeah.
And metaphorically, if this is, you know, if we root for this the way that we should root for,
for the planet, maybe we have to, they're one and the same.
And you want a world where your son can experience the rainforest.
Can run through, can brush across his hand.
It brushes his hands across the fake clothy vines where he can reach out and touch
the decaying black tongue of a creepy snake.
The asbestos tongue of the snake.
But I think it could potentially, I think it should come back because current Landrys,
the head of Landrys, noted podcast ride guide, Tillman Fertitta, author of Shut Up and Listen,
exclamation point, the book that, the business book that warns you a paddle is coming for your ass.
Of course.
He, he is building a hotel casino on the strip.
It's a plot of land that used to be a travel lodge and the Hawaiian marketplace shopping center.
It's all being demolished and they're building a new hotel casino.
This is like by, if you can think of like the Cosmopolitan,
sort of across from that area on this strip.
So since he's building a new hotel casino, I think we got to get a Rainforest Cafe in there.
Yeah.
You know?
You gotta.
It's his own, this is his own company.
It's his own company.
Someone's gotta be, yeah, there's gotta be restaurants in there.
Isn't it still, it's still in that weird, I've called it the shit stack.
There's the tower of like the bad chain restaurants, one on top of the other in Vegas.
Right, right.
It's a Denny's and a Hard Rock and Brew Dog, the new rooftop brewery.
And so I, yeah, I think just a couple blocks up from that will be this new Tillman Fertitta location.
Wow.
His cousins run station casinos, the locals casinos in Vegas.
No, it's his cousins who one of them helped start UFC.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Oh my.
Does this man run the world?
Well, I, you know.
Yes, the Houston Rockets.
And if you go far enough, he has the Houston Rockets, and if you go far enough back in the
family tree, there are Texas mobsters.
There are the Galveston mafia to the point where like people were surprised when they're like,
they lent us guy by the Rockets.
Like usually the NBA doesn't like, you know.
I only knew this man from like, he had a CNBC show.
Yes.
That we watched a lot of.
We were very into the show, The Prophet.
Right.
I think it came on after and we watched it a lot and it was him basically telling cupcake
makers like, I'll sell your cupcakes in Vegas.
And then I never heard from him again.
Was that show good?
It was good enough.
Okay.
That's what you need.
That's the CNBC's model.
Good enough.
Yeah.
It's, he definitely got the dossier in February of 2020.
Oh yeah.
The original dossier?
Sure.
I, yeah.
I mean like, yeah, the personalities that run through this thing.
And I just, just one, another little thing about Schussler and Julie talked about this
a little bit, but I haven't meditated on it in a minute that he like to prove the concept
he, wait, okay, actually it wasn't even the reason he just, he had a lot of tropical birds
and he wanted to make the house comfortable for them.
So he made a lot of money by the way, from a restaurant called Jukebox Saturday Night,
which Jason old timey music test.
Who did the song Jukebox Saturday Night?
Oh, is that a big bopper?
No, little old in that.
It's a name you love to say.
Uh, it's not the, it can't be the Dorsi brothers.
We got a Glenn Miller.
It's a Glenn Miller.
Glenn Miller.
Sorry.
So he had some Jukebox restaurant that kind of looked bad from the outside.
I don't know, but he made some, he made some money,
wanted to keep going in the themed entertainment, the theme restaurant world.
But so off of that, he's like, you know, I want my birds to be comfortable.
What other answer do I have than to make my home very humid
and full of like water spurts and fog and mists?
Of course.
And then eventually waterfalls.
So he just slowly is living in a rainforest himself.
And then quote this man.
When I realized that the rainforest made me comfortable too,
I began to wonder if I could market the idea
whether I could mix the comfortable feelings with retail merchandising in a restaurant.
So slowly but surely he just keeps making his house more of a rainforest
and starts having investors come over.
Check it out.
What do you think?
And most of them think that it's really weird.
And then a guy comes over named Lyle Berman.
Lyle Berman also thinks it's really weird and he leaves.
But Schussler's like not giving up.
So he keeps hounding him and hounding him.
Come back.
He doesn't do it.
Eventually this guy visits the rainforest house 26 times.
Oh my God.
In which time Schussler has put half a million dollars into the home.
And after 26 times, Lyle Berman finally says,
all right, fine, $2.
5 million is yours.
Let's partner with Mall of America.
They got it built.
This guy who went for it and did it is one of the greatest gamblers on earth, literally.
He's in the Poker Hall of Fame.
He's won so many championships.
And then years later was one of the many high profile victims of Bernie Madoff.
Wow.
And that's why.
So we've got Schussler, but we've also we got to credit Lyle Berman
and his gambling in real life and his literal gambling.
This is the guy we need to hook up with.
Oh yeah.
A guy who's willing to just throw a bunch of money at a dumb idea.
Sure.
And we got to figure out.
Insane gambling man.
If you're down, do not stop until you win all your money back.
That's right.
I think it might be what he did.
And it paid off incredibly.
They made $8 million the first year.
In that year, Michael Jackson visited and asked if he could buy a Tracy Tree.
A limo was summoned for Steve Schussler.
This will take you to Michael Jackson.
Please negotiate a price for Tracy Tree.
Did he have a Tracy Tree?
I it is not clear.
It's not clear in this article.
Apparently the price what he offered was $40,000.
That's what he started with.
So I don't know.
I don't know where it went.
So unclear.
But I don't see.
At least he got to the table is the thing.
The shock and joy I feel from this story is the exact way I felt when I dined at the
Rainforest Cafe.
I cannot believe this.
You mean to tell me Imagineers are just living in regular old houses,
not committing to the bit like this man?
Yeah, you're right.
We all love these people.
This is what we need.
But Joe Roady didn't actually live in Pandora.
He didn't make his own Pandora.
Yeah, yeah.
Every time you read about it.
He lives in Fantasyland seemingly.
This is true.
Yeah, yeah.
But it would be better if Imagineers would like literally change the climate of their
house to slowly turn themselves insane to really get in the mindset.
But call a human macaw.
That's how we apparently get our best themed restaurants.
That's what I'm saying.
Well, what can we plausibly turn a home into that we wouldn't mind?
I just keep imagining that when they introduced Fastpass Plus and when they introduced Magic
Bands that they built that.
There was like a walkthrough exhibit to show executives.
I just imagine the person who created that was just in there being like, this is my life
now.
It's a little kitchenette.
Yeah, just to schedule Fastpasses forever.
You walked through a Fastpass place?
Yeah, there's some old story that-
The Magic Band place?
Because they had to explain it, they built out a whole thing for execs.
I'll dig it up.
It's an old one.
That's like when they first introduced the app, like booking Fastpasses on the app.
Yes, when they did all of that.
There was a big profile of like, they built a giant data center at Disney MGM Studios.
And then a few years ago, I think we talked to someone who worked at Disney and it's like,
oh, that was gone in like a year, year and a half.
We needed more space.
That was great for the Time Magazine profile, but yeah, it wasn't super practical.
This guy remains insane and he still has like, outside of Minneapolis, he has like a workshop
where he still does this.
He fully builds out restaurants in miniature form that he wants to build.
There's a 10,000 square foot lab outside the place on the door.
Inventions, ideas, contraptions, and dreams.
There's a big T-Rex in there from T-Rex Cafe.
But where he loves the most is a jazz club that he wants to build called Aero Blue,
a World War II era jazz club.
I'm sorry, World War II era?
Yes, I guess so.
So there's like planes and stuff.
The resident Jew doesn't love that.
Yeah.
Romanticizing of World War II.
The fun part of the movie World War II.
What a great time for everyone.
He just means boogie, boogie woogie bugle boy and nothing else.
Okay, okay.
He just likes the planes is all.
I was like about to get on a plane to meet this man and now I'm slowly greeting back.
Hold on.
I think he fudges the rules because apparently this place, it has-
I'm like, what do you mean?
Do you mean you have a full animatronic of this?
This claims in it-
All right, there's a large airplane that raises and lowers with a spinning propeller.
There's a trumpeting Louis Armstrong and a dancing sax playing Bill Clinton.
I take back everything I said.
We're on the creepy ropes now.
Oh, I will go to this.
Oh, you're back.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm back.
I wasn't sure if Clinton was a deterrent or a robot.
No, this I have to see.
I know.
The robot one is more trustworthy.
Yeah, yeah.
Robot's not on any list.
He can't go anywhere.
He's about, maybe he could because he dances.
What the hell does this mean?
Yeah, what does that mean?
Dancing sax playing Clinton in World War II that you have to go to Minnesota to see?
This sounds like-
brainstorming we do at the end of an episode where we go, well, what would you want to see?
And I'm like, dancing Bill Clinton and we all laugh.
Well, have you ever lived in a human house for two years?
Because I think that's probably why.
That's true.
It got in there.
Can I talk about, since we are ride enthusiasts, the rainforest river adventure ride?
Oh my god.
The, there is a ride.
I mean, I think we can't fully do it until we've done it.
We're aware, the listeners have mentioned this in Galveston, Texas, there's one with a ride,
but I feel like I would feel like a poser to do it without do it.
But also, I mean, shout out whatever you want.
I'm just saying.
You know how a lot of rides, like movies or books, if you try to graph it, there's like spikes and,
oh, it's exciting.
And then it's building up and it says, this is a ride where the whole ride is like a single
horizontal line.
He's absolutely right.
Very few events.
Well, wouldn't you say the same about another ride called, another relaxing boat ride called
Navi River Journey?
It always comes back to boat rides.
It's always, I know, move on without slow moving boat talk.
Right.
But Navi River Journey is not a rapids raft.
Exactly.
For no reason.
Is it, wait, it's a rapids?
It is a rapid.
It's not a boat?
No, it's not a boat.
What?
Really?
It is a slow moving rapids.
Whoa.
It's still a boat though.
It just makes the ideas that you're in.
So by that definition, it is a boat.
Sure.
But it's the kind of vehicle where you should be like bumping around and going down waterfalls
and instead you just kind of like spin around.
Yeah.
I watched a couple ride videos.
I also didn't see anyone loading or unloading you.
Yeah.
I watched it on 2X speed and it felt like it was a picture.
Nothing was changing.
It was just a slow moving vehicle.
I had no idea this was a
It should have been Twisty Tourney, Rocky Rollie.
I thought there'd be a little
Yes, a dip.
Like a Pirate of the Caribbean level dip.
No, not the case.
Wow.
Still feels like we have to do it.
Well, I need to see these sound effects because they also sound
There's some that sound like generic animals and then some that sound like a man screaming
in either agony or ecstasy.
Like it's very odd.
Except that it's ecstasy.
It's probably a man screaming in ecstasy.
He recorded himself screaming in ecstasy.
Those unfinished warehouse roofs really help the audio fidelity.
Maybe it was just people genuinely screaming in ecstasy as I think anyone would at any of
these establishments clearly.
Sure.
I mean like it's the kind of thing where
Like I found some article that was like trying to figure it out.
I don't know, Millennials or Gen Z or whatever going to rainforest cafes?
Why?
Why would they do this?
Well, it must be couched in irony and I'm like, I think you're overthinking it.
I think there are a lot of layers here.
It's improbable that these exist and that they're still there.
In an otherwise really boring mall, you can go to a place that has a storm every 20 minutes.
It's so bizarre.
You had the best day ever seemingly doing it.
Truly an iconic 24 hours for me.
Just bringing Cha Cha full of Diet Coke in the console of my car driving home.
Taylor, Cha Cha, icons.
Nothing but icons.
You had a spirit of adventure that you hadn't known for so long.
You went to the Forever 21 outlet and bought a top that dissolved by the time you got back
to Los Angeles.
Self-eating top.
But anything else on the way out the door here?
The only thing I'll say is that like if it's replaced, if the rainforest cafe exists in a
mall and then it's replaced by something very boring like it's like an FYE or something,
I'm upset.
But like Woodfield replaced theirs with something called Peppa Pig's World of Play.
Sick.
Which I don't know.
I'm not saying it's like as good as a rainforest cafe, but it's, you know,
it at least is something silly.
You can meet big Peppas?
Yeah, there's big Peppas.
Which Peppas can you meet?
I actually don't know the names of the Peppas.
Can you meet the Peppa Dad?
I love the dad.
I don't know his name or anything, but like he's very charming.
I have a somewhat unfounded crush on Peppa Pig's dad.
I don't know why he's a pig.
I think my wife will hear you on this.
Absolutely.
There's a charm to this guy.
You too?
Who do you rank first, Peppa's dad or Bluey's dad?
Peppa's dad.
Okay.
I'm a Peppa's dad kind of gal.
Bluey's dad too commonplace.
I thought Bluey for the longest time was the dad and then I watched a couple.
I watched a couple because I was trying to get Garfield to watch it because there were
some videos online that dogs really like Bluey because the color palette is good for their
vision.
He had no interest in it.
Garfield was an argument.
He went right back to sleep.
He needs his 16 hours.
Look at him here in a tux and then that's kind of that scruff.
I think there's something about the scruff.
I know.
Then the glasses are cool.
Like he seems cool.
I just haven't watched you.
I'll have an opinion soon.
He seems like he would order a scotch which is a very cool move.
Absolutely.
Does he wear
Self-funny, self-effacing.
Does he wear a captain's hat ever?
Oh, probably.
He's here in a chef's hat.
Just a baseball tee that's a little too tight.
That seems like he's classy.
He's pink which is your vibe.
Yeah, he is pink.
Okay.
Daddy Pig is the name.
Yeah, I don't want to say that aloud but
Daddy Pig?
He's got little silly name boys here have no problem saying that.
Yeah.
I'm very comfortable saying it.
Little Daddy Pig boy.
I'm just a little Daddy Pig.
Oh, no.
I just realized Daddy Pig becomes mojo bones.
No.
Protect him.
Don't let Daddy Pig become mojo bones.
Daddy Pig should take the family to visit down at that beach where the pigs swim in the ocean.
What?
You guys know there's like in the Caribbean I think.
I think there's a beach where pigs swim around.
Yes.
Okay.
Some wild pigs like to swim.
In a couple of years we'll run out of stuff to talk about so we'll have to go review the
pig ocean.
But until that time
Pig beach.
We have
Got another couple decades with Epic Universe opening.
That's true.
You're right.
We got the Chronos.
So many portals.
Chronos will give us longer
Decades of material.
All the time.
Get ready for 40 more years of Podcast The Ride.
But for now, so happy you came and talked to us about this.
Carly Weisel, you survived Podcast The Ride.
I did it.
Thank you for returning from Ontario full of joy and energy.
So fun to talk about.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
My podcast is very amusing.
We're doing weekly episodes now which is a big leap from doing a bunch of episodes and
disappearing for four months for pre-production.
So tune in.
Tell me about that version though.
That sounds good.
Oh it's nice.
Does that work out?
Yeah but I was also doing episodes that
Because I'm a solo host and I'd be doing hour 45 sometimes.
Just old gal.
Just you talking straight through.
Putting four interviews in one episode.
You learn along the way.
So now we are weekly.
It is more digestible as one would say.
And it's a bunch of fun.
It's all theme park stuff.
Every December obviously we do Shrek stuff.
Disney and Universal mostly.
Other silly things.
We're going to be doing an episode about studio tours in Los Angeles.
A little more travel this year.
So it's fun.
And then I'm just always yelling into my phone on Instagram.
Great.
So you can find you on that for quick yells and then for long talks.
Yeah for long yells you got to go to the app.
Merch is available in our Tee Public store.
Three bonus episodes every month at Podcast the Ride the second gate.
Or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You'll find all of that at patreon.
com slash Podcast the Ride.
And on the way out the door I couldn't find Daddy Pig in a captain's hat.
But pretty close runner up Grandpa Pig in a cap.
Whoa didn't know about Grandpa Pig.
Grandpa Pig's pretty nice too.
Unfortunately not my type but he seems nice.
But it kind of it shows you where Daddy Pig will go.
If I'm willing to make his long term investment on Daddy Pig.
Basically going to turn into this.
He has eye surgery.
He'll get eye surgery apparently won't need those glasses.
He's a little pale in a disconcerting way.
Yeah wait he's a lighter pink.
A little closer to eventual pig decline.
Oh no you're seeing that on his face.
So Grandpa Pig makes you sad a little bit.
Makes me a little sad.
Aging is tough.
Oh let me turn the laptop around.
I won't make you.
What about what about Daddy Dog in a captain's hat?
Who is that?
Yeah it is a lot to learn.
He's from the show.
Multiple captains hat wearing animals in the show.
I mean if that's not if that's not endorsements.
Combined with the Schomburg retail location.
Peppa Pig retelling of Master and Commander.
Oceans are now battlefields.
Make it happen Peppa Pig creators.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.