Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome back.
When we last left Mike, Scott and Jason, they were getting ready to talk about Barry and Richard,
who were trying to avoid our security guards, Brad and Colin.
But might they run into General Hospital's John Engel?
Let's check in with the boys now.
That's an intro that will make no sense to anyone here on Podcast Thread, the Second Gate,
unless you've already viewed today's topic, which is available to view on YouTube, several copies.
I believe the creatively titled Disney's California Adventure TV special.
Or opening special, one of those.
That's what IMDB said.
They really swung for the fences with that one.
Official intros, Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan.
I'm here, yes.
John Hingle.
You will finally hear the name.
You've waited for it.
Engel.
Just taking an H off of that.
I believe it.
John Engel.
I think.
I mean, here, do you want to just, we can say some further context,
but I do have polls, just the full intro to this special,
which if you don't know is the special that accompanied the opening of Disney's California Adventure
in February 2001, right around 23 years ago, around this time that you're hearing it.
Happy 23.
And boy, were things different back 23 years ago in a number of ways.
We'll get into that.
But let's mainly to clarify Engel or Hingle, let's hear this opening.
Welcome to our very special look inside Disney's newest theme park,
Disney's California Adventure, right next to Disneyland in California.
Joining us tonight are spin cities, Barry Bostwick and Richard Kind.
From Whose Line Is It Anyway?
Colin Mochrie and Brad Sherwood.
From The Emperor's New Groove, Patrick Warburton.
From General Hospital and Port Charles, Jackie Zeman, Nancy Lee Grant, John Engel, Aaron Hershey and Kiko Ellsworth.
And a special appearance by the director of the Toy Story films and A Bug's Life, John Lasseter.
And now, Disney's California Adventure.
He's the and.
Yeah, he's the and.
He's the scene stealer.
And he is, let's be clear.
That's true, yeah.
He certainly does.
It's a very, to quote what they say in this,
you know, it's a very animated scene.
I think they say that two or three times.
They use that phrase a lot.
Yeah.
Well, you are a very animated guy.
John Engel.
I'm so sorry.
If I could go back even a step before that, because I watched the upload copy with like the 22nd CG,
like Disney, generic Disney pre-roll from the time of the credits,
which I had to watch a couple of times before I realized what I was looking at.
And it's like a CG circus tent that you the camera zooms into.
And then it's just filled with like video clips playing all around you.
OK.
And it's like a big as if it was on a big CG metal tower.
How's that CG looking?
Well, it looked fine when you were watching the video clips, the circus tent.
That's why I had to rewatch it.
I'm like, what is that?
What is that building?
Yeah.
And then it dawned on me.
I liked it because it was very like Regal Cinema's AMC movie strip man.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's a nice area.
That's that's all that's early, not early CGI, I guess, but that's that's early 2000s stuff that is not reprehensible to me.
There's some charm to it.
You can tell people spend hours and money like for that 20 seconds of CG and video montage.
Sure.
That was the equivalent of making Avatar Way of Water.
Basically.
The time took just as long and just as much money.
Another year.
Sorry.
You have to hold back the opening of the park.
Yeah.
This I I actually did not see that.
I'm interested to see that, too, because I feel like that would have given me more of the feeling of watching.
You know, a special at this time of gather round America.
Yes.
There is a brand new theme park to open right next to Disneyland, something that will only be said seven or eight times throughout the special next to it.
Seven or eight times.
I couldn't find the air date, but I believe this aired in January.
DCA opens in February.
Does that sound right?
Yeah, I was looking for this, too.
And I could not find it for the life of me, mainly for some specific information, which was I was like, did this air on ABC or not?
Was this a wonderful world of Disney?
Right.
Because there there is no Eisner intro.
Eisner is in it, but you do not get a hello.
You do not get this circus tent intro that you saw Jason recognize.
I think that this may be a Disney Channel original.
I think that might be the only venue.
I don't think this was on on network television.
They wouldn't do the full court press.
This is a big deal.
You think.
But I don't know.
It's so short.
You may know.
I think I think Wonderful World of Disney.
You got to fill two hours.
Yeah.
Unless it was paired with something else.
I just couldn't find the proof.
I went to some website and skimmed through all the listings every Sunday for the first half of the year.
Guide listings.
Yeah.
Some site tracked it, you know, when what?
Which private practice aired?
You know, a rerun of private practice was only viewed by 17 million people.
Those those kind of stats.
Yeah.
A lot of millionaire back then.
That's what you find.
Kind of the intro I saw did have a very like early 2000s Disney Channel aesthetic.
But then that's even weirder how many daytime soap actors are in this.
Sure.
I mean, there's everything about that is weird that they that the restaurant is there,
that they are leaning on the star quality of Can I Quickly Pull One That Is Not John Engel,
that, you know, Kiko Ellsworth.
We got you got Aaron Hershey.
I like soaps are I mean, they're an alternate universe.
That's like it's kind of the way actually,
I think like CBS primetime is now where you're like, who's that?
Never heard of them.
Well, they have been on 130 episodes of a show that people actually watch.
OK, well, never heard of the Hawaii Five.
Oh, the Hawaii Five.
Oh, remake.
There are children who are like entering middle school and they were never in a world without this.
Yes, they were born when Hawaii Five.
Oh, remake started and then they had a whole childhood.
And now adolescence is coming as Hawaii Five or Magnum P.
I.
remake is wrapping up.
Generational wealth has been accumulated by people that work on Hawaii Five remake.
Absolutely.
So much money has been made.
And every two years I go, well, that's still on.
Uh huh.
Yes.
Every two years.
Even though even though they like every two weeks make like more than we could dream of.
For months and months.
Taylor Willie and Scott Kahn.
Scott Kahn and Taylor Willie are like oil tycoons.
They're like, oh, they have that much money.
They have old school generational wealth.
You know, this came up with me and Jay the other day because we were talking about the Emmys.
And I think she watched some of it.
I didn't really see.
I just saw clips and she was like, oh, they had a bunch of cast reunions like Grey's Anatomy.
And I'm like, well, that's not really reunion.
Grey's Anatomy is still on the air.
And he did need like a lane like what?
Like she's like, no, that's not true.
And I'm like, no, it's still on the air.
Like, yeah, I know I kind of that occurred to me while watching that.
They almost presented that within the piece like.
And of course, we're still at it.
You are.
Are you sure?
And this is this is errors.
This is televised.
Yeah.
Similarly, you know, there was just OK.
Wait, my my lack of soap knowledge.
I think OK, I think what John Engel is is I think he's one of the quarter mains, which is the family Edward quarter main.
And that is the family that like that's the dynasty that has dominated all of all my children.
Yeah, I think.
And I I was watching like hotel TV.
It's the only reason you were in it.
There was a prime recently.
There was a primetime All My Children anniversary special where they kept having like a door would open and then four people would be there who were not even ID.
This is how much it's like you, the audience knows they don't say their own names is not a blower third says their names.
Here I am.
And some of them are like big wind ups with like a massive push in and then up to a person I've never seen before in my life.
And not only that, they're so sure that, you know, the quarter mains that they're like, it's crazy being a cue.
They're that familiar with it.
I loved the special.
I'm like, they still make stuff like this.
Just like specials about something I don't know one droplet about.
That was my mom's show.
That was All My Children.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Jason, what kind of house were you?
I think it was All My Children.
I got really into it one summer.
Oh, really?
Because Mother, do you have the cues are at it again?
Yeah, because I just like serialized and it's very, you know, it's soapy, you know, it's very pulpy.
Who were your people on there?
Who were your favorites?
I have no recollection.
You can't name a character?
Erica Cain?
I couldn't name the quarter mains, but I know a few.
Well, I so I went down to rabbit hole reading about it a little because I was like, is Erin Hershey a Pennsylvania Hershey?
She is not.
Oh, but she she married her castmate, Brad Presley, and his Wikipedia has a very funny line of like he was born the week Elvis Presley died.
They are unrelated.
Like, okay, really odd.
Like, it's that meme.
It's that meme that's online now where they say like so and so died in this month in this year and then so and so was born.
Welcome back.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
I'm telling you about a thing online.
Mr.
Meme.
You know what I'm talking about?
I think I've seen one of those.
It'll say like, oh, say Elvis Presley died whatever day and year and then it'll say so and so was born on the next day or the same day.
I forget.
And then it'll say welcome back Elvis Presley.
And it's a joke and you can do it with many different things.
Exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
That's a thing that youth culture is participating in.
You know, I've seen a lot of like the theme park one I keep seeing is like when 50s Primetime Cafe opened, if you went back this many years, we are now at the point where if you went back that many years, you would hit step by step and family matters sort of thing.
Sure.
Okay.
But that's not an easy to digest meme or anything.
That's not like a cool young person meme like Mike has been.
I just brought up is something you would know.
It's more like time is enough time has passed.
You had a big opportunity to be cooler and younger than Mike and you failed as we all do at the altar of Mike's school.
Well, he's the coolest of any of us.
That's not true.
He usually is the youthful knowledge about TikToks and skippity toilet or whatever the hell that character was he brought up on the Barbie episode.
I was complaining about a thing because you know everyone if people make TikToks then it becomes a YouTube short and Instagram reel.
This thing where like the end of the short video is also how the video starts.
And I was like, Jane, do you know about it?
She's like, yeah, of course.
It's a trick.
So that way you don't realize it gets the video's artificial views counts gets the view counts up because people don't realize the video is just restarted.
But it's really unnerving.
I have noticed this.
I hate it.
You're talking about that videos just start over from the beginning?
No, like the end shot is the same as the beginning.
So you don't realize you don't even realize the loop has happened.
So I mean, it's kind of a clever editing trick, but it's like, I don't know.
We should try that with this podcast.
Huh?
We should try that with the podcast.
We should end with hello.
We have to end with hello and then trick everybody into listening twice.
Oh, sure.
Or the theme song.
Maybe you have to put.
We'll look.
We'll experiment.
We'll figure it out.
It'll be seamless.
You'll hear they won't.
They won't even know.
Yeah.
But so all right, this is this is the opening special that they made to
promote new California adventure.
Unclear.
I've seen that aired in April and Disney Channel, which if that's the case, it wasn't even on to their like maybe a term when they finished it, they did some test screening and they're like, you know, no rush on this is fine.
Whenever you get to it, whenever you got to.
If you've got a block where you're not already committed to a Lizzie, even Stevens split up, drop it wherever you may have aired it to in the morning.
Whatever.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
When I'm thinking of the Disneyland opening day special and the other specials, it does feel like maybe the star power was a little higher.
Not that I dislike these stars and maybe that's wrong, but it does feel maybe like everything about, of course, California venture opening was like, this isn't quite as good.
Well, you've got four stars of prime time, maybe three shows fronting.
That's true, but we're not talking the top stars.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it's very Bostwick really.
I mean, it's very fun to imagine a Disney Channel special being like, you know, Richard Conbert, Bostwick, Colin Mochrie, Brad Sherwood, your favorite kids.
There are no former presidents involved in this opening day special.
There are no, it's missing some star power.
I mean, we're not far from Disneyland 35th, which we did an episode about where they keep, they love the list so much they say it over and over again.
It's Tony Danza, former president Ronald Reagan and Ernest and the Muppets.
Yeah, that's more, again, I'm not putting down the very talented people on this show.
Sure.
But I'm just saying everything about it does maybe add up to what you're saying is that this may have been quietly played on Disney Channel.
Well, that special I'm describing and many of the great specials that I love of kind of early Eisner, I feel like it's very Disney decade.
It's the optimism.
We've got money to spare forever.
Euro Disney is going to take us to the stratosphere.
So let's give every star whatever.
There's a special we never even talked about that where the story is Michael Eisner trying to going from trailer to trailer, trying to find a host for a special that he's doing.
And everyone in it is it's like so stacked.
It's whoopie and bet and Robin Williams.
And I think that's maybe the one with Baby Sinclair.
I'm not sure.
Right.
And I don't even know what it's for.
And it's so like they just kind of mill about and know what's a bit.
No, I don't think I can do it.
All right.
Well, bye.
And then this one, they are like trying to really sit.
No, Barry Bostwick.
You know, we got Barry.
He's going to be here for the whole hour.
A lot of worry about worry.
The young actors of Two Guys, a Girl and a Pizza Place did not return our calls.
They didn't need to.
Too hot careers.
Too hot at the time.
That's how Lasseter gets highest bill, like the biggest splashiest part of the introduction.
And why he gets a full like a scene.
He does like a sketch.
He's the reason we get his.
Really?
That takes you back to that.
When they decided like this guy's got the chops, he's going to be he's going to make the rare move, the Eisner move of behind the scenes person into being on camera.
Really, I guess closer analogous Spielberg.
Yeah.
Where now we got a lot of things where Spielberg's hamming it up and they saw Lasseter and like, look, he's got his fun energy.
He's got the stories of his toys and his shirts.
And he's got it would be very interesting.
I wonder what the Disney company looks like.
This is not for a different podcast.
What does it look like if he didn't drink too much and love hugs?
Like, what would he just still be running Pixar or would he be like, he's the CEO.
Isn't he?
Oh, that's my question.
With all this struggle there.
I think unless he doesn't want to do that, he wants to be hands on.
Here's a scene.
Edit, edit.
You know what I'll do?
I'll use technology to make your voice less enthusiastic.
That's what I'll do.
John Lasseter wants to be hands on.
Oh crap.
Wait.
OK.
Now just edit that.
Make me sound sad.
The cynical part of my thinking says that he's especially gone because Eiger was thinking
that.
Oh, because Eiger is a little Machiavellian kind of guy.
Sure.
So an opportunity arose to get rid of John.
He should have gone anyway.
I'm just saying.
I wonder if that is my that maybe would be what happens.
We're like, let's put a creative person fully in charge.
And that is a certain.
I don't know.
You think he at some point as he handed a manila envelope with far away spy photos of
Lasseter giving hugs and he's like, I'll file these away.
I believe this is what I need.
Oh, yeah.
With his old minder, his god, fuck, I forget her name.
She was one of my best person.
Yeah.
No, no, that was the CFO.
OK.
But Eiger, I think his like media relations person like also worked for like one of the
New York governors, one of the various creep New York governors.
Take your pick.
Zinia Mooka.
Her name is Zinia Mooka.
Yeah, we talked about her either.
But I do think I certainly think Eiger has is like Professor X files on everybody that
works in the company with all their weaknesses and all the dirt and that, yes, he could get
rid of them if he wants.
He's he's he's he's a very boring man, but he's very, very calculated.
Zinia Mooka is now the chief brand officer and communication or chief brand communications
officer at Tick Tock.
Oh, she's all about the looping video.
Zinia Mooka, Zinia Loop Looper.
I've never seen this woman.
Wow.
Huh.
All right.
Now we know Zinia.
Yeah.
I believe she she showed up in the show in the Disney war book.
Influential senior policy adviser to governor of New York, George Pataki.
Pataki is pretty clean, I feel like.
You never hear about George Pataki.
You don't put him on your creep list?
Well, compared to who was the guy whose brother worked at CNN.
I'm cutting off any more grasping for names.
We got to talk about this special at some point in time.
If you come up with it, feel free.
Cuomo.
Oh, you meant him.
Oh, yeah.
And then there was the toe sucker.
Who was the toe sucker?
Was that Anthony Weiner?
No, no.
The other guy who resigned in disgrace, the bald guy.
The toe sucker?
The toe sucker.
Who was sucking on toes?
The toes belonged to a Democratic operative who worked on the Buddha judge campaign.
This is too much.
The toes belonged.
Who's the…
You know, the one who says Buddha judge.
Just give it a little Buddha judge.
Sorry, a boot age age.
I forgot that.
That is the Kirtak pronunciation.
Certain Buddha judge.
Well, we'll find out who the toes belonged to.
We'll find out the name of the person the toes belonged to, and then we'll talk about it after we talk about this special.
Who's the toe owner?
It's just interesting that the course, the different timelines that could possibly have happened.
If Johnny was less of a creep or not a creep at all.
Or based on his performance in this special, Barry Bostowick was given the keys to the company.
Or give Bostowick the CEO job, and Bostowick would have taken over.
He handled a scene with the CEO, aka the big cheese with incredible grace and poise.
I believe that's correct, yes.
So, alright.
Premise of special.
Well, actually before premise.
I mean, it's antics with Barry Bostowick and Richard Kind that take them all around the park as they're on the run from these security guards from Who's Line.
This is all directed by Jerry Rees, a name that you see a lot.
I mean, it's like 20 things were directed by this guy.
Back to Neverland, the thing with Walter Cronkite and Robin Williams.
That's something we should talk about at some point.
All the pre-tapes of Alien Encounter.
Michael and Mickey.
How have we never done Michael and Mickey?
That little intro piece where they round up all the characters.
And one of the most nicely rendered Mickey Mouse's I've ever seen.
Interacting with Michael Eisner.
And then the rock and roller coaster pre-tapes.
This is the guy who called action on the Stephen Tyler Shocker.
On the Shocker.
Dinosaur.
He did the pre-tape for Dinosaur.
The Wallace Langham videos.
Did he do the Soren pre-tape?
Don't know.
Maybe not.
Sounds dangerous though.
Wow.
He just captured the Warburton performance in this.
I guess, spoiler alert, from the show.
But the Warburton performance of the character he plays in the pre-show is spot on.
It feels really the same day.
He was locked in.
A character radically different than the usual Petrified.
So different.
He had a method.
He got into that character.
This is a maestro situation.
Heath Ledger, Joker style living in a plane.
I'm sorry, I forget.
Did you say Jerry Reeves most famous directing credit?
No, maybe not.
Brave Little Toaster?
Wow.
Big one.
Yeah.
No, incredible.
I think it's supposed to be from Cream Command 2.
But, you know, the name I've registered as the guy who directed tons of live action stuff.
This is kind of later than a lot of that.
And according to his website, Jerry Reeves was called four days before the shooting of the special.
I believe that.
Yes.
Can you imagine that the tight plotting, intricate blocking, had to be scrambled together?
Also name checks that opening.
And this is a thing that I like about this a lot.
The opening and the narration throughout is by Corey Burton, voice of A Zillion Things.
But that's clearly the voice of the parking lot tram.
He's clearly doing the exact same mode.
And when you hear that, I mean, that's not a California Adventure thing.
That's a like, you know, whatever.
That's that's a 2001 resorts refresh thing.
And then you got more Burton as the same the chief flight attendant.
This really the special, I'd say the main value of it is that it is like a piece of media that expands the DCA averse.
Yeah, 1.
0.
Yes, specifically.
Yeah, if you want more with the vibe of DCA 1.
0, you get it here.
And it really does give you the vibe of I wasn't there opening year, but I was there a couple of years later.
And it really feels like a little bit of a time machine.
Yes, colors in the graphics, the music it can.
And it conveys that there's not a ton like yes, there's a we're stretching.
There's a lot of stretch.
Yeah, a lot of stretch of a park.
I feel like there's a good amount of time where they are using a photo or video of the compass.
It used to be in the Esplanade in in the ground.
Yeah, I think that they've gotten rid of it at this point.
I think that's pretty inoffensive.
The compass.
Yeah, the compass.
I don't think you're right, but I don't like it as like the background of something I'm watching on TV.
No, but I'm saying like, well, compared to the gaudy letter, I know he means he means this the kind of pastel.
Yeah, like all of the graphics are put on it.
They just filmed from above.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It was like the centerpiece between the two parks.
But right.
I remember that in California, which is like it's a bunch of like, I mean, it's I kind of like it now as like what looks it.
This should be like the cover of a like a soft jazz album from 2001.
Yeah.
All the music you hear in the wine area.
This would be the album cover that is that gives me the fee.
The two thousand.
It gives me the one point.
Oh, feels.
Are you saying you like it?
I like it.
Yeah, I like it.
OK.
You think this is like a less offensive version of some of these early 2001?
Yes, I'm saying this is more defensible, I think, than the big California letters.
Well, I like the big California.
I like the California.
You like California letters more.
So you're anti-California letters.
No, I was coming into prepared to defend this.
And I thought we were going to jump on the California letters, I guess.
You know, I never you know, I think of all of those bad things at the front.
That's not the worst.
I don't like the postcard mural stuff.
I hate those walls.
I'm glad those are gone.
I hate the sun icon.
Golden Gate Bridge is not the worst thing to me.
And actually, I just for the first time in person got to see San Fransokyo,
which now has a future Golden Gate Bridge.
And that's kind of good.
That's a little bit.
I'm kind of glad that there's a silly Golden Gate Bridge back in that park.
And there's like fun music playing too.
There is really fun music.
And I was like, oh, I like I'd like maybe I like this.
I don't think this is some.
I didn't need anything over there.
But who's been better ish over there for quick service?
Sure.
Yeah, it's I don't think it's some like revolutionary redo.
I'm still a little like, why did this happen?
I mean, it's not a bad thing at all.
It's better.
I think it's a similar thing to Pixar Pier, where I go, yeah, I guess I like that they did it.
I like that they did it.
Sure.
I just wish that they did much bigger things.
Yes, that would be the consensus, I think, maybe all three of us, I guess.
But, you know, when we we did an episode right at the the 20 year mark of the opening that was about DCA 1.
0 in general.
And there was a discussion in that of what else has the vibe of DCA 1.
0?
What what else is 2001 core pre 911 core or whatever you want to call it?
And it's it's it's kind of intent.
It's tough to I like all the examples we thought of.
I think people gave us good ones online.
But this special is it the hardcore?
It is the hardest are 2001 core because you're you're watching these it's these actors in big billowy bowling show.
Everybody's got a bowling shirt on Mickey kind of included.
He do.
You're done.
And then the only one who isn't is Eisner.
They literally like I think they got Richard kind of they said which of these two shirts do you want?
He picked one and then they gave the other one to Mickey.
Like that was what I think the process was like for you, boss.
I was in like a casual sport coat like he escapes relatively unsaved.
He looks good.
He looks not wearing the bowling shirt, but that's he's the CEO.
He's maybe the only person in this.
And I mean, just people in the background.
This is the most bowling shirt Hawaiian shirted out piece of media ever.
Did Drew Carey influence this?
All this with like a bowling shirt?
Yeah, you know, it almost in the way that like, you know, somebody with a strong aesthetic like Christopher Nolan,
where he's the executive producer of something and he didn't wasn't on set, but you feel his.
We got to make sure it has his vibe.
This feels like if it said executive producer Drew Carey at the beginning.
Yeah, you would believe it.
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
Cory core is also not I think that's a good alternate name for this vibe.
It's also you also have the whose line guys who he didn't like discover, but he brought that to America.
And I forget what's going on with.
I mean, Colin, both of them just are like mini carries.
I feel like they are like one in the same, even though they want to find the other.
But the one Brad Sherwood especially is like reminded me of how fucking so many sideburns at this time.
There was always sideburns.
Yeah, I had sideburns.
You had sideburns.
Yeah.
How do you know?
How does that happen?
I can I can grill someone about this.
Yeah.
Were you after somebody's vibe?
Was it just like everyone has them?
So I have to ask that is great question.
I don't remember.
I didn't even ask.
Maybe it's just like I do.
You are a boy.
It is now you need sideburns.
I certainly remember trying to cut my hair or get my hair to look like like David Duchovny from the X-Files.
I remember that.
Whoa.
Actively happening.
But and everyone had like sort of sort of similar hair to him, I guess, at the time.
And then everyone had like parted in the middle.
This is like junior high.
But as far as the sideburns, yeah, that's a good question.
I don't remember specifically, like consciously having the thought that I need longer sideburns.
Everybody had them.
Yeah.
So you watch old clips of Conan and he's got them and his guest has them.
The whole all the Max Winfrey seven of them.
No, it's just such as just this little tell anyone out there is making a period piece from that era or anything.
That's that's the little that shows that you dotted the eye.
Yeah, like this this the cover.
This is a pretty good.
I forget what season specifically, but like this kind of Duchovny, he's kind of got it parted to the side.
You wanted to do that.
But it's kind of like a swoosh a little bit.
Yeah, because I mean, I definitely had like more of a middle part to swoosh is going on in junior high.
That's close.
That Duchovny is closer to Conan than I would have thought.
And I see a little bit.
Yeah.
We'll swoosh.
That's kind of the most conscious like memory I have of trying to let me see if this is this is still a little bit of a side.
But that's sort of what the vibe was.
How close do you feel like you got?
I don't think I think I don't know.
I wasn't so happy with it, but I had that hair for years, I think.
So, yeah, I don't know what the sideburns such a good question.
Who started that?
Has anyone documented this?
Is it late ketchup from Luke Perry?
Oh, maybe.
And the tall hair and Jay, it's like somehow it took years for that to like, right.
Right.
He had pretty big sideburns.
And some puffy hair, too.
Is there like, I don't know what to call it, like ska?
Did ska do that?
Or like, I feel like some of the characters on Mission Hill were animated with sideburns.
You know, that aesthetic, which I guess is just very similar to the damn clowns.
It feels kind of, yeah, it's kind of Kevin Smithy.
Or Mr.
Show.
I feel like there's some sideburns.
I think this was Onkirk's side.
And they were like, yeah, there are like posters for that.
They're bowling shirt guys.
Like, how do we bring ourselves to America?
That was their shit.
Like we're coming out with the weirdest comedy show you've ever seen.
We better put on bowling shirts or no one will watch this.
The Barenaked Ladies wore bowling shirts.
They're completely this vibe.
And they, I, Steven Page, I recall very strongly having sideburns.
Yeah.
Like big sideburns for a while.
Gosh, I don't know.
What happened?
I would just love to know like the order.
I'd just love to see this style family tree somehow laid out.
Just figure out the evolution of it.
Evolution in the film starring David Duchovny in which he has sideburns.
Oh, I was so excited for evolution.
I was so disappointed when I actually saw it.
I was like, oh no.
I don't think this is good.
What was Duchovny and Julianne were Orlando Jones and Sean William Scott?
Sure.
Yeah.
Strong cast and his sci-fi.
It's the watch of its era.
And it was advertised from the director of Ghostbusters, you know.
Can't go wrong.
Never made a bad one.
So with this vibe, let me just say before we get too deep into it,
with this vibe being strewn throughout, I've seen this special before.
I have always found this special to be extremely irritating.
I am quite annoyed by it.
It wasn't the worst to revisit it.
But for every bit that I love, like that 35th anniversary one that I mentioned
or the Harry Anderson one I've watched a zillion times, this is…
You know what's a big part of it for me, and I still haven't really synopsized the story,
but you've got Barry Buswick and Richard Kind are trying to…
They parked their car in a bit.
It's a series of events where security guards are after them, and that's the Who's Line Is It Anyway guys.
And it's that style of comedy, which today is all comedy, where the cops are funny too.
They gotta be funny too.
Like the hosts are like, well, we really gotta explore the…
And then the security guards, well, we really gotta attract those guys now.
Like everyone, just someone needs to be a straight man.
Someone needs to calm down.
And then I don't…
Music all very unpleasant, I think.
Is it like, I'm trying to remember even…
Well, I just watched this today, and it was like…
It's pretty circus-y.
It's all in that Paradise Pier kind of family.
I mean, at some point you hear the full…
You know what I don't mind as a piece of music
is the original California Screamin' music?
That's the zenith of kind of digital Pro Tools-y…
That's a Pro Tools Calliope.
That's completely right.
Like carousel music filtered through 2001 Mac.
Yeah, yes.
Not all of it is bad, but all of this is bad, I would say.
I think it's a lot of park music, because they use Soarin' music.
Yes, yeah.
And then Tinkley Piano that feels very…
Yeah, yeah.
Napa Wine Zone.
Yeah.
There's a moment where they stare at Grizzly Peak that has some nice music.
I think maybe they're still using some Soarin' music in here.
Yeah.
Obviously Soarin' music is the best music in the whole world.
It really stands out when you're hearing a bunch of this.
You know what's the one…
They play this a lot.
It's kind of like…
You'd think I would like this because I like the Beach Boys,
but I'm not very fond of the Calliope Beach Boys music that used to play at Calvary,
but I found that pretty irritating.
And then this special has this very summertime blues that they play a lot.
I was going to say it.
Do not like it at all.
Yeah.
At all.
It's just a subtle…
If the music was not so…
If it wasn't the auditory equivalent of bowling shirts,
maybe I could handle the silly broad acting a little bit easier.
I feel like I mostly know that from like commercial…
Like,
New Uncrustables!
Like, peanut butter and jelly sandwiches!
Eat your freezer!
That's the de-evolution of…
Surf music is kind of gritty and punk.
Early surf music is something kind of cool about it, and then decades later…
Blah, blah, blah, blah!
Don't get rused!
Chocolate!
Yeah.
Who created using the guitar like that?
Dick Dale?
Dick Dale, probably.
Possibly, yeah.
Oh, is that the…
Did everyone see this Dick Dale video that's going around, right?
He's playing on top of the Disneyland, or on Space Mountain.
On Space Mountain.
There's this whole…
We don't have time to get into it, but I heard this…
No, I heard this.
I think this…
Imagine you're Eddie Soto.
Soto.
Soto?
He told a whole story online of why it happened.
Actually, I think I listened to a podcast with him where he said that the original plan was to get him to play on top of the Matterhorn.
Really?
I didn't see this.
And then he didn't bother to tell anybody from events planning at Disneyland, and that when…
This is on the Tomorrow Society podcast, so I don't steal their story.
Okay.
But he didn't tell events planning, we're going to put a famous guitar player up there, and they were like,
No!
That can't…
We're not insured to put someone on top of…
The mountain climbing is a big, laborious thing.
Yeah.
He's going to just stare his little gator with a guitar, and he's going to do something up there.
If he trips and falls, that's it.
If given the options, I would also pick Space Mountain.
That is more architecturally sound.
There are way too many imaginary interviews where they're like,
Yeah, Matterhorn, kind of piece that together.
Probably not too even.
It's like, oh, what's this thing?
Like standing on top of a coral reef.
It's like, yeah, we taught ourselves mathematics.
Who designed all the ride?
I am terrible with names nowadays.
Bob Gurr?
Bob Gurr.
Bob Gurr in the Imagineering story is like,
Well, I had to learn calculus.
It's very impressive.
What he describes that someone could just pick it up and then design it,
and then have other people go like, yeah, this is correct.
This is mathematically and structurally sound.
That said, the Imagineer, the Matterhorn has had way too many aftermarket,
like way too much stuff done over the years where it's like,
I don't really want to see the basketball court.
Thank you so much.
Yes, that could be a trip and fall.
Yeah, you just take one step and go right through that thing.
But you know, then it resulted in Dick Dale playing on top of Space Mountain.
Which is, I hadn't seen that.
Like, there's a little video of it.
I knew about it and didn't know there was video.
And I think Eddie sort of posted it.
But the two thousand, like just the half, like how many half-lifes of the original cool surf rock are we at here?
Yeah.
And is this going to, I mean, everything comes back around maybe.
But will there be a time where people are like, oh, I do like the sound of all this shitty music.
I don't think it's this.
I don't think it's the worst era for in-park music ever.
Yeah.
It really, like the standard is not.
It's pretty bad, I know.
And I'm a person who now is into and apologetic for like, you know, 90s New Age, essentially from Epcot in the 90s.
So somebody somewhere maybe, I don't know, that Disney circus music is pretty terrible.
It's really bad.
Yes.
And it's gone from the park, right?
There's no place where it still exists.
I don't think so.
But that's a little different.
That's like a compilation.
Nobody made that for the park.
Right.
And the restaurant still has, I think, that I haven't been in there in a while.
Which was?
Oh, oh, early.
I was there with my family a few months ago.
I didn't really notice music.
I feel like you notice it in the quick service.
Yeah, maybe more.
Or around at California Adventure.
The upgrade in music certainly happened when they pumped all that money in.
Because Cars Land has good music.
It's a lot of pop music.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not going to go out of my way to listen to Daddy's Little Fatty or whatever.
Or Suitcase in a Dream.
You don't live in our house.
We've got Bob Wills on.
I wait until I'm there and then I…
We've got Bob Wills on all the time in the house.
Bob Wills.
We're a Bob Wills house.
Yeah, we listen to him and Tom.
Your poor daughter.
But Tommy, we were at Bob Wills' house growing up.
She loves Bob Wills.
She loves old time country music because it goes boom, boom, boom, boom.
Like that little country beat.
So she starts wiggling.
She likes that more than some of the 90s rock I try to make her listen to.
She's not in a third eye blind?
Not yet.
You have to, Mike, you absolutely have to get your teenage daughter into third eye blind.
She'll be screwed socially if she's not.
She's going to like, how's it going to be?
See, now I know you don't like the rest of her, but Jane is pretty good.
Jane is kind of good.
She dances to old time country, but she also recently loves Staying Alive by the Bee Gees.
She dances, she has five different moves even.
She does when Staying Alive starts.
Oh, that's cool.
I'm all for that.
She dances like arms, wiggles.
It's very cute.
But yeah, no, she demanded more of Bob Wills and the old time music.
All right, I've got another little bit of music to play, but I think maybe before that we should set the scene.
Let's start weaving the dense narrative that somehow Jerry Rees was able to put together in only four days' time.
So once the little opening is done and that Cory Burton intro, then you get some of the coolest shots you've ever seen.
Where I think it is that music.
I think it's boogaloo doogaloo doo doo doo doo doo.
And you see two badasses, Barry Moswick and Richard Kine, in their biggest billowy shirts you've ever seen in an open top car,
driving up to those California letters.
And you know you're off to a very pleasant time.
And they talk about how, you know, what's weaving us through this special is that they don't know what's up.
They've been called to the Disneyland Resort because they have a very important meeting with the Big Cheese.
And again, a theme I've been saying this Big Cheese runner, I think Big Cheese is said 29 times.
I don't know.
Is this used in another special?
Must be.
Had I just watched, I know I've watched this before, but I feel like I've heard this gag from Eisner era,
where they're like, Michael, we came to see you.
Oh, I'm not the Big Cheese.
It's him.
I don't know.
Listener, just take a guess right now if you haven't watched this and don't intend to.
Who do you think the Big Cheese is?
Do you think it's Michael Eisner, Disney CEO, that they assume?
Or could someone else be the Big Cheese?
Is this somehow telegraphed from second one?
What a reveal.
If you don't know, I guess.
It's Rattigan, of course.
Oh, that brick mouse detective, I'll get him you.
Can you help me very in mid-june?
That would be exciting.
Let's live action remake that.
Oh, yeah.
I'll work for scale, you know.
Are you playing Rattigan?
I'll do any.
Yeah, I'll do Rattigan.
Let's do Rattigan.
I don't remember.
It's a good thing you're willing to work for scale because from what I've heard about the Disney company, you will be.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that's what I've told other realists.
It's very funny looking back that Disney bought Marvel
because the comics industry reputation of, oh, Marvel is very cheap.
You know, Marvel will take forever and will pay you very base rates.
The entire industry and every other industry all turning into the same thing.
No, but like comics, a world of like Hucksters and Carnies, like if Marvel's got that bad of a reputation.
Yeah, yeah.
A world of Hucksters and Carnies, like original California adventure.
That's right.
Like I'm just repeating you, like all industries?
Okay.
So our hosts have shown up.
Barry Bostwick, both of them on Spin City at the time.
I didn't know.
You remember this, Mike?
This seems kind of up your alley.
Do you know that Barry Bostwick was in a music group in the 1970s, a group called The Clowns with a K.
And the premise of the band is that they are all in clown makeup.
And this was what this was.
The fuck?
Yeah, this is a band that was in it.
This is one of those things that's just said really casually in a Wikipedia.
We're like, oh, he was in a band called The Clowns that was brought to you by Barnum and Bailey.
What?
You can't just say that.
Barnum and Bailey doesn't have bands.
What are you talking about?
And not only that, this was put together and that song was written by Jeff Berry, writer of Sugar Sugar.
Oh my God.
This was like they were trying to manufacture a band Archie's Monkey style.
Barnum and Bailey said we got to get more uxters.
We got to get into the band business.
Mike, you're looking at The Clowns now.
How is this never come across anyone's desk before?
Barry Bostwick's band with The Clowns.
As you said a couple of months ago or something, we keep discovering crap.
And maybe this isn't even crap.
Crap with a K like The Clowns.
Yeah.
I like these outfits, I'll be honest.
This is the thing where there were 30 singles released every week.
And so a lot of them are just lost to the ages.
Nobody paid attention.
Yeah.
Nobody tracked them.
Nobody has the digital rights.
Nobody kept a copy.
Yeah, he's in The Clowns.
The writer of Sugar Sugar, Jeff Berry, who was also a co-writer on all the Spectre, River Deep Mountain High, Be My Baby, Chapel of Love and The Clowns.
The Clowns.
Yeah.
So look into The Clowns on your own time.
This is terrifying.
Yeah.
Is that a scary photo?
Yeah, I'm less into that.
Yeah.
When they were all white, there's something kind of, you know, for kind of a pre-Klaus Nomi to make one of the most obscure references I've made on the podcast.
I shout out to my Klaus Nomi fans out there.
Is the song good?
Do you know?
What's that?
I think I listened to it and it was like fine but boring.
Okay.
That's I believe.
So we got a member of The Clowns and then we got Richard Kind, who at this time has just done a Bugs Life that will come into play later.
Richard Kind, there's a story about him.
I don't know if you know this.
I don't know.
Kind of an interesting little tidbit.
Basically, he was good friends with George Clooney.
And then one day, Richard Kind was summoned to a room with 13 other guys, one of whom was Randy Gerber, which isn't central to the story.
But it's part of it.
And basically, he was handed a suitcase, luggage, luggage, to me luggage of a million dollars.
Just for being friends.
Yeah.
Wow.
It's an interesting story, huh?
With a lot of really, I think, memorable details.
I have a lot of less interesting story about him getting a litter box full of human shit, but I won't tell that right now.
It seems like a lot of people knew that story and were like very freaked out and like adding.
And knew more details than we said.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is a famous tale, I guess.
Right.
So so many Richard Kind stories to get through.
But the main the Richard Kind story today is that he's looking for the big cheese and they seem to not even know that there is a new theme park right next door to Disneyland.
One thing about this special that I think is odd is that in every case, that parking lot tram comes in a lot.
He's at the beginning and then it's every commercial break.
And I swear they are talking to they're talking to the audience like we are dumb because it's they are constantly reiterating story and also that California Adventure is next to Disneyland.
It is constantly.
We left Barry and Richard as they were being chased by our security guards through Disney's California Adventure right next door to Disneyland.
Disneyland, remember, is right next door to Disney's California Adventure, the new park where Barry and Richard are being chased by our security guards.
Well, they end up at Disneyland right next door to California Adventure.
I guess what is the what the reasoning could be behind that is like they really want to stress that you if you're going to Disneyland, you may as well go to this place anyway.
Yeah, maybe.
Yes.
In case if you're really not paying attention and you kind of just like you're not a fan of the stuff you and you're like you're on your way into Disneyland.
What if you're dealing with five kids and you don't even look up and see that there's a new California Wetters?
Yeah.
Just like scurrying them in there.
Let's go get the train.
Maybe you wouldn't know.
I don't know.
Maybe they feel like they have to do they have to underline this put in bold.
This is for dummies to know.
Yeah, I think that is I mean, yeah, either that or just whoever was noting it.
Eisner or something just he lost the plot.
He was like, where is it again?
I know it's around Disneyland, but maybe we need to make sure I forgot.
You don't even have to walk.
You don't even have to get in a bus or anything.
Yeah, it's no it's basically you're basically.
Already there just 80 more dollars.
It's one big park.
Yeah, they might be counting on casual viewers, you know, tuning in halfway through or whatever.
You got to recap.
We got to recap.
There's also I you know, I I don't know if you wanted to go through it, you know, storyline wise.
Do we have to?
Yeah, that was my thinking too.
They when they're first walking in, they say you've got a nice little park here to Colin McHarey and Brad Sherwood.
And they go little.
This is fifty five acres, which it is one of the smaller parks in Disney's portfolio.
It is a smaller park.
And I had never heard this phrase this phrase this way.
And I don't think really stuck around, but they say why there's like 22 rides.
They say rides, which is weird because they're so sticky about the attractions.
They say there's 22 rides and shows and parades and stuff.
Why?
I don't know.
They make it seem like there was a bunch of stuff.
Three rides.
They specifically say it's the same number of rides and shows as Disneyland when it opened in 1955.
Oh, so that's fine.
Certainly stand theme park standards haven't changed since 1955 when there was a significant amount of it was just dirt.
You know, just dirt fields or empty sidewalks that let you nowhere.
And they just call it a fun town.
What's that big pile of dirt there?
Holiday, holiday, holiday town, the big hill.
Yeah, no.
And they also like they say how many things there are.
And then Brad Sherwood says each one is different.
OK, we're a little.
He says it a lot.
He does.
But it's like, yeah, boy, they're these poor guys who let's get the top improv guys on TV to really do up to plead to the audience to not be mad about what they're getting at Disneyland's new park.
Hey, it was fine with me like a 13 year old, you know, a chubby 13 year old nerd in Pennsylvania.
It's like that's who they wanted to attract, you know, and many soap stars.
And they're all from different shows.
That's pretty impressive report.
What Charles Charles and all my children, Aaron, she would eventually leave for Charles and then come back on to Port Charles.
No, she would come back on like Charles.
That was the most frantic dive for the phone.
I don't know what I thought I was.
I'm like, Jason, the audience is dying to know what soap opera you went back to.
So what is the first time you stepped foot in California?
Venture 2006.
2006.
OK.
But like so it got you by the time you were 18 years later, a college student with not much money.
Yeah, but it's worse than a 13 year old.
But not all of it.
This is important context.
Yeah, thank you for that.
But you know, the newest park you had been to was Islands of Adventure at that point, right?
Yes, at that point.
So then you're going to 1.
0 Disney California Adventure.
Didn't you feel a bit let down?
I mean, I don't know what California is like.
I certainly had expectations.
You were grading on the biggest curve.
I didn't know.
And then when I first came out here and went to Disneyland for the first time, like, holy shit, this is great.
There's so much.
Maybe maybe you liked the vibe.
OK, that's that's that's part of it.
Well, it wasn't until the second or third time that I made California Adventure and me and my college roommate Jack.
Hi, if you're listening, he we blitzed through it all by like 11 a.
m.
or noon and it's like, well, I'm glad we bought a park.
Brad Sherwood implied that there was much to do.
So basically, why are the security guards mad?
I don't know.
They do.
That is a very good question.
They're like tracking Eisner's day and like, no, no, it's a very tight schedule and you can't.
Yeah.
So they're trying to stop Barry and Richard from exploring all 22 ride shows and attractions.
Yeah, they don't because they say like we have some VIPs that wandered off or there's a sentence like that sounds like that.
And this is this is one of the clips that I have is that what really there's like this siren song that calls to them.
They're listening to kind of the you know, going on and on about what attractions they have.
But then they like they turn as if seeing the most beautiful woman alive and they like, ah, we must with them.
They propel forward.
And this is what's calling them is this weird parade happening in the center of the park.
And here, boy, we've already discussed challenging music.
Get ready for this one.
Very sexual.
Granite Mountain.
What's that?
Why do we hear so much of that song?
And then I don't know where to begin.
I don't know what in my head there is with something called Eureka.
And maybe that is your is that the case?
Eureka.
You do an episode on Eureka.
I'd love to do all the weird words.
Eureka, luminaria.
Oh, yeah.
The power of blast.
These are all things I remember from unpleasant California adventure from people online going, I hate this place.
But it's like it is a big yellow California shape.
And then it goes to then there's just like four people holding big.
It's like giant headdress cape things with faces of Californians like a movie star.
It looks like Lady Gaga and sunglasses.
And I don't know what I don't know what I'm looking at.
And then like a lady in a headdress.
What is this?
This is this parade does not match the song.
I would walk past this as fast as humanly possible.
It's a very sultry song for a parade.
Like, I don't know why.
What can I do to hold you?
Yeah, when I get you in my arms, I'm going to do so much stuff to you.
This seems like a license like like someone there was a thing going around Twitter a while back where people were trying to track down a song from one moment from the X-Files.
OK.
And no one could find it because I think it was just like, oh, they would send out CDs of like generic like copyright free music or licensable music where it's like hard rock country bar song.
You're saying it was sort of a generic track or a royalty free?
That very much seems like a generic track.
It seems like that parade seems like in the Tapestry of Nations.
Yeah, but yeah, we're still in that Millennium.
I hate things like this.
But this makes.
This style of parade.
It's all this post Tamer Lion King.
Like they're still in love with that.
I hate it.
This this makes Tapestry of Nations look like Main Street Electrical Parade.
Like this makes Epcot Millennials celebration look really good.
I I want to shout out also this is a rare special where there are credits.
Somehow people credit themselves at the top of this.
And I was really struck by the type of the credit.
Original music by Wow and Flow.
I also wrote this down.
Yes.
That might have some maybe that's an original.
That's a wow and flutter.
They had that line around the wow and flutter lab.
They had to get that in.
In one week, Mike will walk in here and be like, I really like flutter.
I was listening to flutter solo work.
I don't like it.
Wow was not good.
Wow is bad.
No, no, no.
Wow is not good.
But flutter.
My daughter has been dancing to a lot of flutter.
She loves flutter.
So now it's security guard hijinks.
They're bumping into each other.
We spend a lot of time.
We go.
We're killing a lot of time in the Hollywood area.
They have to.
This is the thinnest soup that there is where they have to really make this seem like this is something because this is something I remember from when it opened.
I still I was in it the other day.
I'm still that animation lobby.
We spent a lot of time being convinced that like basic it's a room where they play clips of the movies.
Yeah.
So what am I supposed to and it's OK now.
Now that it's one of like 80 things to do there.
Yes.
But at the time like I'm sorry one of the primary things about this park is that you have a big screen with clips of your own movies.
But why are Barry and Richard so excited about this?
Which everyone spent the 90s acquiring on the chunky white VHS is the chunky white VHS boxes.
You can come see them now in bigger four by three on vacation.
It was more money to see Bambi's mom.
Yeah.
And this is like the first this is what they're like leading off with as far as things to do.
And boss Wicke and kind spend a lot of time in there it seems like.
Yeah.
Many minutes featuring this part which if I really think the biggest thing about it is just like using so much time on this special to talk about this.
This is the thing you walk by.
Yeah of course.
But as if like you know one of the big things to do here is watch the movie on a big wall.
You're like oh yeah OK.
Yeah.
Well it's like an act like by ratio like now I like a Galaxy's Edge opening special done like this would be like what's like a you know like like some of those droids that rattle around outside the store would be a full 30 minutes.
Right.
Data pads would be you do like like we have four entire sketches about data pads.
Yeah they may as well have just done like a word wieners five minutes before instead of this because at least that's like a hot dog place and I'm working a little different than another.
Dogs I love them.
Well yeah I'm watching my figure.
Right.
Next season of Spin City.
I won't fit into this.
I won't fit into even a billowy bowling shirt.
I'll have to go to a quadruple XL.
And he only needs a one.
No right.
It's just I'm just saying that's the style of how you were at the time.
Take whatever size you are add three.
You're good.
Exactly.
Can you get scaky pants.
Can you see the Muppet vision sign in the background.
Where did that come later in there.
If you don't know if they even maybe maybe there's a maybe the security guards in front of it at some point.
No no but I'm saying that open with the park Muppet vision.
Yeah.
Okay.
They could have wondered in there and talk to Kermit and Fozzie.
To eat up some time.
That requires calling them up at people.
Yes.
Relationships not good at the time.
They have to put the movie in but that I don't think they're they're not sending the characters.
It's already a decade old.
It is a decade old.
I'm just saying we were talking about the stars.
It's a better thing.
It's a better thing to do.
But also I feel like maybe they were like do we want to talk about how we just threw a 10 year old movie in here.
Like that's not exactly like oh it's a new thing.
They want to talk about how they threw a three year old movie right into the bug theater.
That's true.
I'll get to that.
But then you also get a you get so much soap opera bistro and you go through.
Yeah.
OK.
We have five stars.
We have five soap opera stars and you need to watch whose line Brad Sherwood security guard.
Think that it's one of those gags where the guy doesn't know that it's a character and not a real actor.
Right.
And you watch it play out a new five times in a row.
No no no.
I'm you don't understand.
I'm not Alexis.
I'm Nancy Lee Gron.
That is a character that I play on TV.
No no no.
I want to do Alexis.
And then again and they keep when they pan over and there's another guy and then another guy.
I got scared that they were going to be like 17.
We're going to keep going down the stable.
I.
Yeah.
I don't know.
This would it.
This wouldn't happen in the old specials.
No.
It would have been better.
They would have done it with more than four days.
Although I don't think you know what a lot of those didn't we talk about didn't land us to have the same situation.
Yeah.
All right.
Never mind.
But I'm saying that was written by that pro the like guy did all the the you know big bang and all the Muppets that was written by like I don't know who wrote this but I don't.
Boy.
It's just funny also that it's like I'm not saying it would work with bigger stars but it also would have been bigger star like that.
I don't know your attention that you're like wow I'm watching this guy instead of me if you're like no it's a really specific type of person who's really into John Engel.
You're right.
And also John Engel is on your television every day.
I was John Engel is popular like Susan Lucci was like famous famous.
Yes.
In a way that other soap stars weren't.
Was John Engel no offense to Mr.
Engel.
I don't think so.
I don't think so either.
So it's just an interesting choice.
I have the Aaron Hershey update.
Thank God.
We've all been.
She reprised our Alison Garrager on General Hospital in 2013 for four episodes.
Alison returned to poor Charles along with her son Rafe Jr.
But was soon murdered.
It was just we brought her back.
It's a big she's coming back.
All right.
Four.
That's one week.
That's cool.
You're on for one week maybe.
And then murdered.
Murdered.
OK.
That's well if it's where the story must go.
Yeah.
All right.
Well still jury's still out on who the Toes belongs to.
Oh it's Elliot Spitzer.
Elliot Spitzer was the Toes sucker.
Liz Smith was the Democratic consultant that the Toes belonged to.
And this is all public.
This is in the site source.
Well it's in your post.
So you know take it with a grain of salt.
But Liz Smith pops up every now and then on Twitter and has some of the worst takes you've ever seen.
And then no one thinks about her for six more months.
OK.
Well you're keeping her name alive.
That's right.
And the Toes are alive.
Zariah Dukkow whatever her name was.
Zinni Amuka.
That almost rhymed with what it is.
I think the worst.
I don't know.
I kind of like you know what it reminds me of like John Forsythe and those universal things kind of like fuddy duddy old guy.
I kind of like in a way when he says again we've done two rounds of this if not more.
I'm an actor not a character.
And then then it gets to this line.
It's useless to try to convince you that I am an actor.
I am John Engel and I just play the role of Edward Quartermaine.
It's useless to try to convince you.
There's also a moment where one of the actresses says like I heard the food is fabulous.
And I'm like that is the only positive thing I have ever heard about the food at Soap Opera Cafe.
This really shows you the stretch that it was because like also when he walks in and he's like wow it's the Chandler Mee.
It's the mansion set from All My Children.
It's Telly's from General Hospital.
One Life to Live's Landview Country Club.
So where we're I mean the only way they could possibly play this is by having a character who's insane.
We're now painting only a demented security guard.
Maybe he works just like graveyard shift and gets tapes of these.
I don't know.
Why else would you know every ABC soap opera?
No one likes all of them.
Maybe like one of them.
Yeah there's favorites.
There's tribalism in your soap opera fandom.
Shout out to Brad Sherwood though in this special has to do a lot of physical stuff.
Like is running around jumping around.
It's a real John Wick.
Yeah it's a real John Wick.
Yeah because of the Grizzly Challenge Trails.
He's doing parkour.
Running around in a tire.
There's a good bit of physical comedy where he's got like the arm full of like souvenirs or carnival prizes at the end and he keeps dropping them and trying to pick up.
Must Wicked Kind do a little physical at the end too.
Somebody needed to direct someone down in this.
Everybody's just like making faces and rolling their eyes and shaking their heads.
And yeah one person needed to be less.
Well and they missed a golden opportunity with that Grizzly Peak Challenge Trail to have Richard Kine caught in a rope ladder or big net.
I feel like that's pretty good.
Wouldn't you want that?
Wouldn't you want to see him miserable in a big net?
Do they have a big net there?
Yeah they got everything.
Yeah I don't know.
Yeah you can stage somebody being stuck in the net.
We can get tangled in the net.
Or they get hurled off those sliding tire things.
Yeah that's true.
Those death trap sliding tire things.
Yeah I'm all tangled up.
Not even a suitcase full of a million dollars would help me now.
Yeah there's so many antics.
The antics really are doing the heavy lifting in the show I feel like.
But it's not enough to, then you're not getting anything like good enough to, it doesn't distract you enough from it.
They don't have a lot to show.
And here's something that occurred to me deep into the special.
Is that we clear out the Hollywood area with like a ton of so much soap, so much animation.
You know what you don't see one second of?
Superstar limo.
That's a very good point.
That's how bad it was.
In a special where they got nothing.
They got nothing to show you.
They skip a ride.
That's how bad, they knew we could not.
They already were ahead of it.
Like this thing, we are going to open.
Maybe it is going to open because we need to have people go somewhere.
If we are not going to tell anyone that it's there, we're not going to tell anyone to go there.
Maybe they'll get lost and never end up there.
It's in the corner of the park.
That's our hope.
Maybe we'll put trees in front of it and no one will know there's a ride.
There is a simple animatronic of Drew Carey, then the star of one of ABC's most popular shows.
Well there's other Regis, other people that were involved in the promotion to do.
We got so much soap opera cross promotion and no primetime superstar.
The wife of eventual suitcase recipient, Randy Kirkpatrick.
Yeah.
Do you think they shot it?
And that the footage made it look so bad.
It was such a dark carnival.
Zooming in and out of fisheye lens of a grotesque Jackie Chan.
Because you would think they would be like, well we have to at least shoot some of it and we'll dress it up a little bit
and we'll still say, oh there's another ride you can go on and get good shots of everything.
And then they looked at the footage and they were like, this looks like a fucking nightmare.
We cannot put it in here.
So that's why we're going to do a lot more of the animation wall.
Can you call Wow and Flutter, can they give us a song to just cover a full minute of stock footage?
We are now padding.
We are at the padding point.
And can we get the voiceover guy to remind people of what the story is at every act end and beginning?
Right.
That will kill a lot of time as well.
That is like when I edited on a clip show or people would get into sport related accidents
and you would have like there would be a recap at the start of every like commercial break that ended
and it would recap what happened last break or last segment.
And there was no reason for it, but it would just be an extra minute or two that it would eat up.
So you wouldn't need as many clips going forward on the show.
Apparoles of streaming.
You can't kill time the way you used to be able to.
People need to like come back from commercial.
We can like lull people in with a minute of fucking crap.
What am I watching now?
Have you considered the option of HBO streaming with ads?
Oh, yes.
Everything's got ads.
Ads is back.
Ads are back.
Ads are everywhere.
Even Prime Video, owned by Amazon, are like, yeah, well, hey, brother.
Ads are back.
We got some ads now, but you can give us three more dollars, mom.
We broke the industry to realize that it needed to go back to the way it was.
But not pay anybody.
I do think, superstar limo, you look at the photos that exist online that are so terrifying and shitty looking.
Imagine what, like, I guess low definition is actually better.
And then I was going to say, imagine what it looks like in this low definition recite.
But actually, it probably looks better than high def.
Oh, yeah.
You have timed it.
Yeah.
As opposed to camcorder.
Still, they tried to film in there and Barry Buswick's projectile vomited onto Regis's face.
It flashed me back to my clown days.
Everyone, they're freaking me out.
They're clowns all around me.
So no superstar limo.
But you go over to, we've been told that there's three themed lands, but then you go to Condor Flats.
You're like, what's that?
I don't know, not a land?
No, it's a mini, it's within.
It's golden California or something.
And then in it is Condor Flats.
I'm so glad they got rid of Condor Flats.
But the, here, really some of the meat of it.
You get extra, Patrick Warburton, your chief flight attendant, which reveals, you see him outside of the ride and then he takes them through the, they try to convince you that the queue is something good.
Like it's the hall of aviation.
Well, they stretch that a lot too, where they really like, they give you a little of the queue in this special.
The spirit of St.
Louis?
That's right.
Bill?
In California.
Patrick, could you try that one more time?
A little slower.
Okay, we lost a whole ride that we can't show.
Whoa, did they recreate a replica of the spirit of St.
Louis?
Well, no, we have a 12 by 19 black and white print.
We got a framed photo.
We got a lot of photos.
Yeah, well, what are the artifacts you have?
Well, we have sentences on the wall.
There are sentences that you can read, which no one will.
No one cares.
No one who will ever go on this ride will ever read the sentences.
You can imagine how bored you'd have to be to read the sentences.
I really like his delivery.
I feel like he gets like, you know, something where the sense of humor is like dialed up and broader than broad.
He does kind of a light, I like his thing, the, well, I hate to brag.
I say I hate to brag.
But I, that's all right.
That's good.
That's him being actually funny.
Yeah.
And it's great.
Just seeing this going, OK, there's a little more worlds for pre-show videos.
You know, you don't get that a lot.
So just going, oh, there's ancillary material for the pre-show ride that we like.
It's akin to seeing Rex go off and do something else.
For example, he calls everything a little beauty.
Exactly.
He says it again.
That is just a thing he says.
Something else is a little baby.
He's a hardened, just planes on the brain.
That's what I am.
But I got a sensitive side.
I call things little beauties.
How much improv do you think is in this special?
Oh, maybe entirely.
Maybe that was the design.
I wonder if you can even realize that.
Maybe the Hussle guys weren't hired until the day before.
Yeah.
So I wonder if that's the thing Patrick says.
He calls things little beauties.
Maybe.
I don't know.
Yeah, I wonder.
It's one of his little ticks.
There's a, in the animation workshop set, there's a Richard Kine moment I like a lot
where the person working there goes, well, you seem very animated.
And Richard Kine, it cuts to him.
And he's like, yes, I've been told that before.
Like he just stone-faced.
And I'm like, yeah, it's pretty good.
That's a solid reaction shot.
Do we go by the part of, I want to go back to this one second.
But do we go by the part where they draw Mushu mashup with Richard Kine?
The Eddie Murphy dragon Mushu from Mulan is mashed up with Richard Kine.
I can't be mad at that.
We should post that.
Just a screenshot of that.
And Mushu is mad.
An animator draws that mashup of the two characters.
The two, one real man and dragon.
What a funny, you know, and you didn't even need AI to do it.
I was going to say though, what of, I guess Rex is the answer.
Like what other pre-show video do you want to see a little more?
Is it Dr.
Seeker?
Is it Grace?
Is it Dr.
Ogden?
Is it like, what else do you want?
Who do you want to see?
They feel kind of covered to me.
I feel like I get their vibe.
I'd like to see some more Dr.
Seeker hijinks, I guess.
Watch them like try to steal candy from the vending machine at Dino Institute.
I'm going to see if Chairman Clinch survived that hostile alien planet he got teleported to.
Do we want to really see that?
Yeah, we'll see him suffer.
I mean, you know, probably suffer in the long term.
He exploded into 700 pieces.
Died on the way back to his home planet.
Gotcha.
I mean, I would like to see one of the ET Adventure intro.
My answer for everything will always be ET Adventure.
Well, we want to see more of Steven.
Of course, yeah, more Steven and more ET.
And in the first one they ever did, they were in a movie theater.
And it ends on a big triumphant note where ET says, be good actors and music fanfare closes out.
But I would like to see that then you cut wide and like, well, let's go home, ET.
And then the two of them, Spielberg and ET just slowly shuffle down the row.
You watch them just leave a narrow movie theater row.
It takes them seven minutes to get up the real time.
Do you want to stop for a bite?
Well, no, Kate was making chili tonight.
So we're going home.
ET not invited.
You live in the shed, so I guess you're invited.
You're never not invited.
You can come in.
Just tap on the glass.
Your finger.
Then, oh, I also like that there's a real stretch of a line that we're in.
But wait, we can't go to all those places.
The big cheese.
Do we have to be with a big cheese?
I don't think the big cheese.
Like air quotes that are so big they make a thud sound.
We're wide here, miss.
Then you see scenes from Soarin' Over California out of order.
Yeah, yeah.
Why would, why?
They make it look like snow lands on you, which it does not.
So Extra World, that's great.
Then you go to commercial, then you come back and the narrator, this is the, of all the lies that are told in this special, this is the most egregious.
They're about to go to one of the most beautiful areas of the park, Bountiful Valley Farm.
And then they show a beauty shot of a bunch of bread.
Yeah, I think.
I guess so.
Glistening bread.
Am I wrong or was it like a fruit?
Could be.
I don't remember.
I think it was bread.
You hear what they say, the big cheese thing to a farmer woman and she's like, well, you came to the right place.
California has many varieties.
At least, even Epcot, look, I'm not a big fan of living in the land, but at least I'm like, they actually grow stuff there.
And so you, it is educational and you, they aren't making anything in this place.
They're making the bread that they give you right after you get it.
They're not growing cheese at the farm.
No, they're not growing cheese for sure.
This is another time recently where I provoked, like, what are you talking about?
When I started saying like, oh yeah, well, it's Venger's campus.
And before that it was Bugsland.
Before that it was Bountiful Valley Farm.
And Jane's like, what is Bountiful Valley Farm?
And I'm like, oh, it was like tractors you could climb.
They didn't work or do anything.
I'm just trying to clarify this.
My son would like that now.
I will give them credit.
They would like that.
We would have been there for an hour when we were there the other day, but that's a low, like, a bar should be higher than three year olds.
You could buy seeds.
I guess you can buy seeds at Grizzly Peak Airfield now.
Can you buy seeds?
For a while you could buy like a pack of seeds at Grizzly Peak Airfield.
Really?
For what?
What kind of things would you plant?
Like California plants, I think.
Wow, we need to buy seeds in the sea.
Jason, you need to buy the most marked up seeds on the planet.
We missed buying like a potted plant at the land.
Right.
We walked right by it.
It was at the kiosk that I always ignore when I get out the rock.
You get an AP discount on seeds?
I bet you do.
I don't know why you wouldn't.
Two cents goes to one.
Yeah.
Do you got this bread shot?
I'm looking for the bread shot.
They're in the Bantua Valley.
Were you just hungry?
I'm hungry right now.
I'm just imagining it.
Oh, geez.
Let's keep going.
Do you want the other hand of this cliff bar?
I do not.
You do not hallucinate a shot of bread.
Listening bread.
Where the fuck is this bread shot?
Keep looking.
We'll keep talking.
You just say when you got it.
They go into what is in Bantua Valley Farm.
In the farm area, they have the movie, It's Tough to Be a Bug.
That's what I forget is that Bugs Land came later.
I totally forgot that.
They had the bug movie, but in the farm area because bugs would be in a farm.
And the other part, bugs are in a tree.
Boy, this is confusing.
But they go in and who do we meet?
But Mr.
Hug himself, John Lester.
John Lester gets a whole…
Lots of Hug and John.
And then gets an entire scene to ham it up.
And this is really where it gets ridiculous, where you've been following two guys in four Excel shirts.
And then they walk in and find another one.
Like when…
This is a real…
This is three Spider-Men pointing at each other.
Everyone's dressed the exact same.
You know what's funny?
I think I'm looking at oranges.
I think I looked away.
I think I thought this was bread.
Thought oranges were bread.
But I believe it's oranges.
Oh.
It does kind of look like…
It looks like in a fast food commercial where they're showing a shot of subway bread.
I got you.
It's oranges though.
Unless this is a real dress scenario.
Look at this photo.
What do you see?
Glistening bread or glistening oranges?
Those are two.
Those are the primary.
Bread and oranges are the main characters you would meet at DCA 1.
0.
That's true, yes.
You wouldn't see the real, the characters we like.
And a cardboard cutout of Robert Mondavi.
When bankruptcy was declared, that was the first thing to go.
Get it out.
Grind it up.
This is John Lasseter.
He was my director.
And Richard was great.
He was amazing.
Everyone's screaming.
The Lasseter arm flap.
Wow.
Barry Bostwick.
He just goes really method with how moved he is to meet Barry Bostwick.
I think Barry Bostwick was in a well regarded George Washington miniseries or something.
Is that what it was supposed to be?
I've never seen what Barry Bostwick's good in.
Maybe Rocky Horror.
I don't know.
That's fine.
But I feel like they were pushing him in a lot of these kind of things.
I'm like, he's just this hammy guy.
I don't want to be proud of this guy.
But Lasseter acts like he's meeting the Queen.
It's like, Barry Bostwick.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm a big fan.
He's like shaking almost.
Then you watch these three pasty guys in giant shirts and circus tents.
That's why the circus tent was at the beginning.
And the sound guy in the corner.
Yeah, they got to Dave and I.
Then a quick shot of Dave.
Dave.
They promote an old movie.
You get to be a bug.
Yeah, I know this has been out for a long time.
And then here's really the…
This is really the part to know.
They ask, what's the quickest way to get out of here?
And then Lasseter does a like eyebrow.
He does the kind of thing like Tim Kallpakas is really good at with like nine layers of irony.
But Lasseter does it for real.
And like, hmm, guess what I'm going to do.
And then a spider comes down.
They are scared.
And then they scream and then he, you'll hear it.
A big echoey Lasseter laugh, which I took the liberty of looping on QuickTime player.
That plays in the minds of many former female employees at Pixar.
The Walt Disney Company.
It doesn't play in the restaurant in the lamp light.
Lamp light.
The lounge.
I always forget.
It's not lamp lighter.
That is what Lin-Manuel is.
He's a lamp lighter.
He has a different job than chimney sweep.
Not chimney sweep.
No, he's a lamp lighter.
He's a lamp lighter.
I'm going to veer this car before we get into turning turtle land.
So I'm going to turn away from turning turtle.
So security, you guys do Topsy Talk with a spin-off podcast on your own time.
This line is so bizarre.
Am I hallucinating this?
No, I don't think, no, I think this is real.
Our security guards won't be able to track anyone down as Barry and Richard screams get lost in the excitement of Paradise Pier.
Yes, that is, I guess clocked as well.
Our security guards, the screams of fun-filled coaster riders will blend in with possibly abducted children or people in real trouble.
They won't be able to, it'll be a fog of screams in which many will die.
A cacophony of screams will be confused.
Which for pleasure and which for pain.
That's why they close that back entrance to Paradise Pier.
You know, the security just going to be dragged of it.
Because of all the screams.
They'll be haunted by those screams until they die.
Then you get a full ride through of California screaming.
They think it's a shuttle or something.
I think, hey, boy, we're almost to the end, I think.
Oh, that's good.
And they're scared.
They're special, yeah.
Yeah, hey.
As I was scrolling through, like, oh, good.
The special's almost over.
Hey, yeah, yeah.
I know.
I was like, oh, wait, it's not an hour hour.
It's like a 42-minute hour.
So that implies commercials.
This is a clue.
So wait, because Disney Channel was paid.
Yeah.
But this must be post the era.
It did become like a channel with commercials.
Well, they would have commercials for Disney products.
Oh, you're right.
OK, OK.
But nothing else because children might be watching.
Yes, true.
So well, hey, we made it to Eisner.
We get to Eisner.
Ultimately, they find the big cheese, or so they think.
Listeners, get all your guesses ready in your head.
Who might that big cheese be?
And then we get a little, Eisner's
talking to a group of people.
He's like, I think it's going to be great.
He mutters something.
And that's going to be great.
They show that he's a nice guy because he insists that they
call him Michael or not.
That's a little touch.
Had to get that in there.
Little CEO, relatable guy, right?
Yeah, because he's not relatable at all.
He's barely human.
Yeah, yes.
Please come on the show.
No, no.
Yeah, yeah.
So we were told to meet the big cheese.
I'll just play the clip.
Yeah, we were told to meet the big cheese at the Disneyland
Resort.
The big cheese?
I'm not the big cheese.
I wish I was the big cheese.
This is the big cheese.
Oh.
Hiya, fellas.
Gee, I've been looking for you all day.
I'm sorry, Vicki.
You wanted to see us for some reason?
Well, I want to give you a personal tour of Disney's
California Adventure.
Oh, what do you say we start with a ride on California
Screaming?
Here we go.
They both tip.
They fall backwards.
They've passed out because…
I like that the legs come up.
Yeah, the legs come up.
This is after, by the way, Richard Kine.
It's like, please, I just want to sit down.
We've done so much.
We've done stuff all day.
And I'm like…
A big full day.
Certainly some college friends won't get through all of
this in 90 minutes.
Really, you have to use your imagination because Mickey
would easily find them in the park, I feel.
You know?
There's nobody there.
No one's there.
It's empty.
There's not much to do.
They're in the biggest shirts.
Beat the cat.
Richard Kine is very loud.
There's just no way.
Wait, yeah.
These two are screaming at each other all day.
Other guys who are trying to find them are screaming at
each other too.
Yeah.
There's nowhere, there's nothing to do.
Just plant yourself on a bench and you'll find they'll
wander by within an hour.
Yeah.
Disney handlers very rarely let VIPs out of sight.
He had meetings maybe.
Like, oh, Montavi's trying to bail already.
Let's kneecap him.
Who cares?
They don't care what wine they're drinking.
Montavi's crap.
I'm sorry, it was stripping copper wire from rocket runs.
What is this shit?
B-roll from Superstar Limo?
Oh, fuck.
We're not going to be able to use this.
How much did the Diasaur movie cost?
Fuck me, run.
God damn it.
You scared the shit out of me.
I haven't slept in months.
What is this fucking B-roll?
Is this bread?
Does this look like bread?
This is fucking oranges.
We got to tell Reeves we got to run this in car correct.
If it's an orange color, an orange.
If it's bread color, brown.
It's simple as that.
It's got to be orange like Garfield.
It's got to be Garfield orange to read.
Can't be this middle of the road shit.
Did we buy that yet?
Buy Garfield.
Figure it out.
Michael's got to give me.
I want that.
Why don't I own that?
Fuck, forget the Muppets, Michael.
Talk to Jim Davis.
That shit should be sealed.
Mickey, we just bought the Family Channel.
I don't know if we can buy anything else.
I need an orange cat.
Figure out how to get the fucking 700 Club off the Tempium Slat.
What do you mean they have a lifetime contract?
That's insane.
I bought the whole channel.
That means every time.
Don't they know God is dead?
I'm their God.
Mickey was, he's wearing a hat as well.
He's wearing like a baseball hat.
There was this premise that the characters are on vacation, and that's what we're dealing with at the moment.
Right.
That's a bad price.
Look, that is how I dress when I'm in the theme parks.
You're not Mickey Mouse.
I'm just saying Mickey should be wearing a more fun outfit than that.
That's what I'm saying.
Maybe he's having fun wearing it.
He's relaxed.
He's wearing it for the same reasons as Barry and Richard.
It breathes if it's a hot day.
That's true.
If it's wet, you can just wring it out like a towel.
Plenty of fabric.
Just kind of like edge into a different part of the shirt and you won't be wet anymore.
Can we start a rumor that the original version of California Adventure had a bowling alley?
No, not Splitsville.
A different bowling alley.
That feels right.
Over in Hollywood area, there was a bowling alley.
It was called Hollywood Bowl Wink Wink.
I was about to say what it would be called.
It's so perfect and annoying.
Just there was a bowling alley and you had to pay.
Hollywood Bowl.
It was an upcharge.
You'd have to pay.
But there was a full, there were 20 lanes.
Yeah.
And there was an intro video.
It's all these bad, it's the bowling graphics, but all the pins look like starlets on a red carpet.
Yeah.
They love shit like that.
There's so much shit like that with the 1930s, generic 1930s actress.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So the Hollywood Bowl, somebody, one of our listeners could just add it to the Disney's California Adventure Wikipedia.
And then the ball, this might not be on brand for them, but the ball is like fatty Arbuckle rolling down the stairs and crashing into the…
On the actual screens?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, it's a tribute to classic Hollywood.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, good, good.
Also, can we just, let's just do an imitation here.
Let's all, you know, away from Mike, away from the microphones rather, but the, of the reveal.
I'm not the big, I wish I was the big cheese, I'm not the big cheese.
Let's just do Barry and Richard's reaction to who is the big cheese.
Like, this is the big cheese.
Oh!
Like, and then Richard kind of is like frozen.
He's like, ah, like he's got a big smile on his face, but he also looks kind of scared or shocked as well.
I don't think we had a lot of take twos in this thing.
Yeah, and he's just like, like incredulous that Mickey's here.
Well, he thought it would be animated and post and he's like, why isn't one of the ones from the park?
Yeah, you're saying he was thrown off by that.
Yeah, yeah.
He's a cartoon character, but he's alive.
I thought he was a word.
So they faint and then they, and then you just have reaction shots of Eisner and Mickey watching security guard jokes for a while.
Yeah.
A lot of Eisner just rolling his eyes and what?
What's this?
Can I say I think Eisner's acting is actually okay here?
Yeah.
When you go, I don't think you got to watch these reaction shots.
Well, but I like the big, not the reaction, how much is a big cheese line, I guess.
Where you go, it's not even natural.
Like very natural.
It was a Robert Altman style delivery.
Yeah.
Really sort of stream of consciousness.
It's not a precise reading of the line, but it feels like a kid rolled off his head.
There was a lot of people in, Mike Leiser might have been in shortcuts of such a big cast.
Sure, he might have been.
Hollywood inside.
Oh, I was confusing that with a player, nevermind.
Maybe he's just playing a part.
Maybe he's the player, maybe he's an Imperial own companion, who knows?
The for as big as the bowling shirts are, the inverse is the security guard outfits are so slim cut.
Like they're so like wrapped in those things.
Because they were just real out for they didn't know that there was no time for a fitting for Colin and Brad.
No, for sure.
Boy, I hope those improv guys are in doke-k shape.
Ah crap.
Why didn't anyone tell us no improv guys have ever been in good shape?
That sentence.
These outfits look better than the usual security guard of blousy white shirt and giant wide brimmed hat.
It's not the most intimidating.
The wide brimmed hat.
I'm trying to think of what a good what's the best example of that?
Like the security guard with a big wide brimmed.
No, I'm talking about the actual Disney security guards.
Oh, you're talking about the real ones.
I see.
Well, some of them are.
Let's ending here.
The little walk away.
The bizarre ending.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a, you know, it's a timeless timeless parody.
So, Mickey, it's just you and me and I love that ride and I want to go on it with you.
Okay, boss.
You know, Mickey, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful theme park.
You betcha.
Now that that statement is just funny to meditate on.
I mean, it's very it's a real like, you know, sword you can wield against them in when the park was then it opened and did very bad for a few years.
Right.
But now that I've had so many good times there, it's like it's it's my park.
I just did a family vacation.
We didn't feel like Park Hopper.
We're like, we're going to choose one.
We chose California Adventure.
It's ours.
I now I watch that.
I get a little wistful.
Was it a beautiful theme park at that moment?
No.
But is the statement technically correct?
The statement is correct.
The beginning of a beautiful theme park.
Ultimately, I think it is true.
As usual, Michael Eisner was correct.
As always.
He was never wrong.
The nod to Casablanca at the end.
Kind of confusing, but okay.
I mean, yeah, it's a good Casablanca reference.
Kind of a go to.
After they shoot a Nazi and he throws a bottle of Vichy water in the trash to go like, traders, fuck you.
And they walk away arm in arm down the airfield.
I think this will be the start of a beautiful.
That's him and Claude Reigns.
Yes.
Yes, because he said goodbye to Ingrid Bergman.
She put her on the plane.
Yeah.
So, yes, they've parodied this.
Save me from the Nazis, Michael.
Yeah, they kill Richard Kind of Boswick and they shoot them both in the gut.
Well, he shot security guards.
Security guards.
They both had.
Eisner's neck.
Please call me Michael.
Guys, kill him.
Tell them not to call me that.
Spin City has been canceled.
We're in the Sheen era Spin City here too.
Oh my God, I forgot about the Sheen era.
Was it still going or was it a cancel?
I don't know when the trade off from Fox to Sheen happened.
It's late 90s, I think.
Really?
I could be wrong.
Only a few.
I don't know.
Just to confirm, you're saying Charlie Sheen took over?
From Michael J.
Fox.
I totally forgot about that.
Charlie Sheen on Two and a Half Men to tie it all together, maybe the last remaining bowling
shirt sideburn guy on television.
Yes.
Very true.
Although, yeah, what's the anger management show?
I feel like he was still wearing the same outfits.
So that lasted.
It made that look last a little longer.
All right, Michael J.
Fox 2001, he was done.
No, wait.
Charlie Sheen is listed from 2000 to 2002 and Michael J.
Fox has listened to 96 to 2001.
So it is around the era of the trade off.
In the time of the, okay, okay.
Oh, right.
You remember?
The writer of My Dad's Sperm.
My Dad's Sperm.
Well, how did it feel?
Oh, and then you just watch aerial footage and then get more dubbed over security code.
That's a 912.
I thought that was a 394.
Oh my god.
It's not a special.
It's a stretch shul.
Very good way to put it.
Yeah, it is sadly one of my least favorite watches of any of these types of specials.
Now, I agree, but we've watched worse things for the show.
I think we've watched things that are better technically, but more boring.
Yeah, for sure.
This isn't boring.
It gives you a headache, but it's not boring.
Everything about it is unpleasant, but it's not boring.
Yeah, and ultimately.
Is Fuzzbucket better than this?
Would you rather watch?
Oh, I'd watch this above Fuzzbucket.
Yeah, I would watch this above Fuzzbucket.
Fuzzbucket's really in the bottom of the…
I feel like maybe I've blocked out what is the worst thing we've…
You know what?
Fucking live action Aladdin.
That is truly…
I wouldn't say that.
I forgot we saw that in theaters.
We did.
We did an episode of that.
I hate live action Aladdin.
And from what I've seen, I didn't watch the entire thing, but Haunted Mansion.
Haunted Mansion.
My god.
I haven't started.
I haven't tried.
Fuck.
Don't.
I really think that if the audience really wanted our doors pounded down to do an episode about that, it would have happened by now.
It's such pain, and I don't think it would be a funny episode.
It's brutal.
Maybe not.
I mean, would you rather do an episode on that, or would you rather watch more Father of the Pride?
Oh.
I watched all of it.
I know.
What was wrong with you?
What happened?
Maybe your tolerance for early 2000s stuff is just higher.
Oh, my?
The Pride?
Jason loves you.
You were in such better spirits.
It was crazy.
That was your time.
The glory days.
Well, I found the DVD, and I was like, I just need…
I think it was…
Was it early pandemic, or was it pre-pandemic?
There was no way that would have happened pre-pandemic.
The context was, now that we are fucked, we can do stuff like this.
The days have to pass somehow, and rather than reading names of the list of the dead, we can watch Father of the Pride.
I think I got two-thirds through, and I was like, well, I may as well finish.
I'll reprise the word.
Maybe that's the worst.
I remember that day so vividly, as far as how dark it felt.
That day felt dark to me.
It made me feel feverish.
It made me feel like I had it.
I felt hot and sweaty, and I never left the house.
I was convinced I had early serious cold.
I was starting to lose it because I forgot that in the past, they would often make a whole season of TV and just air it in any order at various times.
That was the problem?
Well, it's not…
Not what was happening or what the characters were saying or how it looked or what they did?
I'm saying, no, that was all bad already, but I was just trying to find a consistent episode numbering for my notes.
And I'm like, why am I not finding the right one?
I'm fucked if I don't number this right, the audience will tear me limb from limb.
Well, because we divided it up.
Oh, you tried to know which one to watch.
Well, one day we'll rank what maybe our most unpleasant watches were.
Yeah, I don't…
Have we maybe blocked out whatever the actual answer is?
I think it's Father of the Pride.
For the two of us, Jason…
Jason liked it.
Let's be honest, you're pretending.
You liked it.
Well, I liked it.
There were no safe spaces on my safe TV.
You liked Father of the Pride.
That's one of your favorite shows.
We figured it out.
All right, let's get out of here.
You survived Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to this, the second gate, as DCA was.
If you want to dig even deeper, if you want to burrow further into the giant billowy Hawaiian shirt that is this podcast,
join us on our VIP Patreon tier, Club 3, where you get one more bonus episode every month,
and our regular episodes ad free.
On Club 3, you vote for the topics, and who knows, you could vote us into the new most unpleasant thing we've ever watched.
Try.
We dare you.