Forever.
Dog.
Three massive dorks, all scared and yellow, stuck in the past.
They're stunted fellows, two hours of talk, mixed with some dick pill ads, and then voila!
It's a podcast.
Why hello!
Today we're talking about a beloved ride with a new friend.
Can he imagine two?
Of course he can, Jason.
His name is Derek Waters, and today on Podcast the Ride, we're all going to discuss the original
1983 Journey into…
Imagination.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about theme parks with two hosts who love their
children but also kind of wish they were little purple dragons.
I'm Scott Gardner, there's my Carlson.
Why did you say it out loud?
That's the only thing.
Now that's going to be recorded and will be played in a therapist's office.
I've been feeling that from you, Ferl.
That's been the unspoken thing.
Of course parenting is great.
How's it being a dad?
I'm like, it's good.
It's nice.
Nothing surprising.
It's just babies.
They are what they are.
They can't make things appear with a wink or a smile.
They didn't come out the gate sounding like 60-year-old men.
Jason Sheridan, hi.
Hi.
Unfortunately, you'll have to settle for me.
I'm the closest thing to a whimsical childlike purple dragon.
The imp of the show.
Yeah, that's fine.
I don't know how we haven't made you do that costume anywhere.
Oh, yeah.
That'll be to come.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
Okay, well, file that away for later.
Guys, it's a big one.
We're at a big one here.
I was about to say this is a big one.
We've been like, not actively kicking down the curb, but you know, it's special bottles.
You want to open them when it's special.
This is like my bottle of Scottie Pippen's Digits bourbon that I haven't opened yet.
That's right.
It's not open yet.
It's still sitting on the shelves.
Scottie Pippen's, not purse, well, it is.
Yeah, it's his brand of whiskey, basically.
Private label.
Digits.
It's got his hand on it.
Do you have any sense of like, is Digits well reviewed?
Are you even going to be like, is it a good bottle?
Outside of like a three month period where Scottie Pippen was promoting it heavily, I
have not heard a thing about it.
I don't know if they're still making it.
I don't know what's going on.
I've much more recently seen him promoting a popcorn that he doesn't own.
Like, it's not his like Scottie's popcorn or anything.
But I have not seen any more Digits stuff.
But he could be making more money endorsement wise than as an investor.
Because that might, maybe there's weird expenses that cut into that.
Yeah, I don't know anything about his deals, but.
Digits is dead to him.
Yeah, I do think maybe he did a grocery store signing of Digits in the last year, now that
I'm thinking about it.
But that was maybe the last time I like consciously clocked a Digits.
That's in Chicago, though?
I think it was here, actually.
Oh my god, what were you doing?
Did you find out after the fact?
I think my daughter was maybe like very, like two weeks old or something, and it was not
an appropriate time to go drive to like Thousand Oaks or something.
More kids complaints.
They're not dragons.
They get in the way of your Digits signings.
I guess if she could have met Scottie Pippen, that would have been pretty cool, though.
Oh yeah, imagine her, a newborn baby next to, in his Digits.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
That is pretty good.
That would be incredible scale.
Any fully grown person, but Scottie Pippen especially.
Tall guy.
Okay, let's not distract anymore from, let's say the words.
Let's say what we're doing.
It's Journey into Imagination.
The classic, the beloved, original Epcot Dark Ride that ran from 1983 to 1998, and we have
arrived at this juncture due to a new friend on the show who I'm so excited is here.
His imagination helped him create and host the smash hit Comedy Central series Drunk History.
A writer, director, actor, a good man, a theme park fan, Derek Waters is here.
Thank you guys, I'm so excited.
This is such a dream come true.
Oh man, a dream come true.
Just one little spark.
I'm so excited.
Thank you so much.
One little spark from you saying, can I do this?
I don't know if anybody's, or we've like, either you're the first who's actually called
Journey into Imagination or it's been in other people's emails and we've been like,
I don't know if we're ready.
No, we're not ready.
I'm not sure.
Somebody probably has mentioned it, but I can't remember.
I think I've blocked it out of my memory.
Yeah, maybe.
But we're opening this bottle of digits for you.
I'm so excited to be part of these digits and do a signing at a grocery store.
I've never heard of signing at a grocery store.
All the guys are doing, Mark Wahlberg is signing his liquor at a grocery store.
Cranston and Paul, they go to the grocery stores, they sign.
Makes sense, that's where you buy it.
Makes sense.
In some states.
In some states, right?
Yeah.
No, but this is such a dream come true.
I love the show, I love you guys.
I don't think so.
I'm very excited to journey with you guys.
Oh boy.
Not into your imagination.
Well, we could, we'll see.
I've already brought a side-pip in.
We'll see where it goes.
Now that the spark's been lit, I mean, I think we gotta go into your imagination a little
bit, or at least your interests and fascinations, because as we've gotten to know each other
over the last year, which has been great, I think a real bonding point and a reason
why I feel like mutual friends were like, you guys gotta talk, because big theme park
persons, feel free, anything else, anything within general theme park you wanna shout
out and talk about, feel free.
But there's specifically the thing of like, kind of what this ride is, which is 80s animatronic
fever dreams.
curious if it will stump the listener, but I wanted to give you a little bit of a platform
to talk about your, there's Figment, our 80s animatronic friend, but then you had a really
specific one where you grew up.
If you wanna talk about him and that a little bit.
Wait, wait, wait.
I had one growing.
Oh, you mean the one I still have?
I mean the, oh, I'm talking about the Baltimore specific animatronic location that you were
passionate about.
So I remember I went to Disney World maybe in like 2018.
And I just had this animatronic memory.
I was like, I remember this old guy, Captain Andy, but I was like, what was that place?
And my mom said, oh, it was only around for like three years, but I had such a fascination
of this place.
And as I researched and found out, there were only three.
There was one in Baltimore.
There was one in Seattle and one in California, which I don't know where it was, but what
happened more than what I saw, like, wood and Whittier kind of like odd, nondescript
South Bay OC kind of cities.
Yeah.
So I would love for listener knows about this because so I felt I was writing a show about
with animatronics and I was like, I don't know where this is going, but I feel like
this old dog that played the banjo he had band come out with them and like this beautiful
stage.
I mean, beautiful stage and like Mike and Jason, by the way, and listeners look up photos
of this place if you wish, because just to get the Captain Andy's River Town, right,
is the full that's the establishment.
Because it's this like it is so precisely what all of us want and chase, but it just
wasn't enough of them to for tons of people to know about it.
Yeah.
So I was thinking, you know, I want to do a show that has these animatronics in the
style of Captain Andy.
And so I found this place.
It's a Gardner Belt down in Redlands.
Gardner.
Yeah.
So I went down there and they gave me a tour and the guy goes, I don't know if I ever told
you this.
He goes, we're thinking about making an old like Hall of Fame of like animatronics.
And have you guys ever heard of Captain Andy's River Town?
And I just said, shut up.
He goes, yeah, not a lot of people have.
And he goes, that's Captain Andy from Baltimore.
Whoa.
So I'm looking at this very old crooked one eyed dog with still like with the hat on.
And it was, I like almost cried, like looking at this most beautiful thing that I was like,
this, this machine gave me such joy as a kid and just like looking at it.
And so you can edit some of this stuff out.
Sorry.
But so I was really excited.
The emotion about an animatronic will never be cut from the show.
Yeah.
Well, I've also learned why I cried too.
Not in general, but about animatronics.
But I got home and I was like, I don't know where this idea is going, but it's going somewhere
and Captain Andy's leaving me.
So I found the blueprint of the original layout of the stage and I online and the guy says,
Hey, when you, when this comes to your house, do you mind calling me?
And I said, Oh, not at all.
And so I called him and I said, Hey, thank you so much.
It arrived.
It's beautiful.
It was like all the like blueprints of the act, the original Captain Andy.
And I, I told him briefly what I've said to you.
That was like writing something that really felt like he was inspiring me.
And he goes, I just want to know what was this?
And I go, wait, you sold me something you don't know.
And he goes, yeah, the guy who created this just passed away.
And I am a huge Jaws fan and I buy everything Jaws.
And he designed the ride of Jaws.
And his family just gave me all his belongings that they didn't know what to do with.
So when you bought this a day after I put it online, I just thought I should give you a call.
And then I told him a little more how much that meant to me.
He goes, you know what?
I have something that I think only you would like.
I'll send it to you for free.
And like a week later, I get the script of Captain Andy's River Town.
It says, creators notes do not lose.
And it has all of the like signals for what the animatronics should be doing during which song.
And it was, I was just so touched by that.
Like it really moved me of like, that was really nice.
And I don't know, I believe in like that thing when ideas start sparking.
I'm not trying to be funny, but that you get signs like, all right, this is the odds of that happening are just insane.
To connect with this guy, him not even knowing what he had, the guy just passed away.
Wow.
When he just put it up like the day before you bought it, basically?
And that was just a coincidence because I just after going to Redland, I was like, oh, I'm going to look up Captain Andy stuff.
That's a crazy coincidence.
Yeah, it was nuts.
I gave you a wallet.
I have a wallet.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
It's on the mantle still.
It's awesome.
And you look, it's just like such a like the like Captain Andy himself is design.
It feels like very classic.
It's not even classic.
It feels specifically like kind of 80s Disney design or Chuck E.
Cheese design or Rock of Fire.
Yes, all before.
It's just this whole package is like, how has this eluded me?
I purely because I didn't grow up with it.
And if you look at the dogs in there, I don't know if you have it, but I'll send you guys a picture.
Maybe you can put on your site.
You see a lot of it.
I believe he was a imagineer briefly that dog's ears and a lot of their faces remind me of America sings big time.
Yeah, yeah.
And I'm not sure.
I feel like one was probably going after the other.
You know how those things.
Yeah, yeah.
Influencers.
Yeah, yeah, that's that like because I also know they're like singing Dixie songs.
So I do want to let your audience know like there are things that are usually.
Yeah, we run into that plenty.
Yes.
Yeah, that happens.
We're lucky Figment doesn't.
Right.
We are.
Yes.
Let me ask because your your passion for Captain Andy and then we're talking about journey into imagination.
Since you mentioned Baltimore, did you ever see Six Flags power plant?
Do you know what that is?
I do.
Yeah.
And my mom.
Oh, it's so real.
She goes, I remember when that was up, but we didn't want to go down.
But I'm like, I'm pretty sure my grandmother took me.
I'm embarrassed.
I just admitted that.
But it's funny because I recently was talking about that with someone.
And I think that's like I was born in seventy nine.
I think that comes out like eighty three, eighty seven.
I'm not positive.
But very short amount.
Yeah.
My family did a number of long weekend trips to the inner harbor.
But at that point, it was a Barnes and Noble and Hard Rock Cafe.
Right.
Yes.
And the ESPN zone.
Yeah.
And ESPN zone.
And then this giant aquarium is next to it.
And there are some shopping malls, which, of course, at this point in the 2020s are dying.
Yes.
Yeah.
Now those are.
Now you're pining for those.
But yeah, that there was this like magical that place.
We still got to do an episode about that.
That like like a completely original IP.
No other park like that is weird, indoor converted power plant or industrial zone.
That's really singular.
Kind of like a carnival.
Like a yeah.
Kind of like they were trying a lot of different stuff.
They had like leeway to try a lot of different things and like little bits and bobs.
Would end up in like the Adventures Club down the road, a pleasure island, you know,
or or the technology would show up elsewhere.
Right.
But it was just kind of like Epcot Center in general, where it's like, well, it's something kind of new.
It's kind of a world's fair.
It's kind of an exhibition.
It's not exactly a theme park.
So kind of quickly.
I think on a really short term basis with power plant, they're like, we don't know what to do with this.
It's not making money.
We got to close it.
No precedent for.
Yeah.
Indoor theme parks.
It's just always a tough, tough game.
Especially if they aren't like super ride oriented.
But anyway, I Captain Andy wise listeners, if you this I was saying before we did this,
I'm like, if you talk about this on the show, 98 percent of listeners won't know what it is,
but two percent are listening and they're like buzzing like he knows that.
Wait, I've never heard that reference anywhere.
So you have listeners, do you have any Captain Andy info, extra stuff?
And then maybe we could dive in deeper down the road.
Although it seems like Derek, you were by default.
You have now become like the keeper of the legend of Captain Andy.
You have a lot of tokens.
I will give you guys tokens.
Oh, wow.
Yes.
But I also remember learning that what happened was they spent so much money on the facility.
Like I don't have the exact measurements, but there was a very big facility like with food, mini golf and and then the show.
But they didn't put any money into employees that understood animatronics.
Oh crap.
Yeah.
So if you don't have that show, they're just eating pizza and miniature golf.
So I think that's they just didn't.
There is a clip.
I'm sure you probably saw it.
And I thought, oh, that's the line.
The selling point.
When I came to Baltimore, the guy, it's a news reel and the guy goes, yeah, we want to bring a theme park to your neighborhood.
Like that was what their goal was.
Which is so many wonderful people were trying to do this in the 80s and 90s.
Yeah.
All these various hits.
But they would everybody was trying to do everyone wanted one.
Yeah.
Around the corner like a little show.
Do you think I've as I'm getting older, I'm like, I always forget and I'm going to convert this to what we're talking about as out here doing this business.
I'm like, oh, there are people that didn't want to achieve this for passion.
There are people that wanted to do this for the business and that frightens me.
And I'm like, this might be similar to that, where this guy looked at Disney or some show that he was like, you know what?
I could make a fortune, you know, with with this.
And it's like, no, you didn't think about it.
You got to take your time and go like, all right, if you're going to have and I believe it's close to 15 to 70 animatronics like on stage.
Like you should invest in knowing how to fix that if they were to go one guy with a wrench would be good to.
Yeah, they got the right people to build it all.
And then just write and never know plan for upkeep.
And then you see in London is where they have a Captain Andy.
Yeah, they landed in.
Yeah.
Somewhere called Watermouth Castle.
That is the place where you can.
So it's still there.
You can still see him perform.
Yeah, it's just him.
And I think like a couple of side characters who are in like creepy glass, like they're in fish tanks.
Yeah, they aren't in there like the they're in the set that you have the blueprints for.
They're trapped like the guardians of the galaxy.
Oh, yeah.
I mentioned.
Yeah.
I wonderful.
But isn't that always I think the push and pull with Disney, too, to this day is like there's always there.
Like have to be the crass people who just want to make a lot of money.
But if that can empower the artists to do something really heartfelt, that's that's that's all that matters.
The inspiration and with animatronics, I think and it goes in with figment is like as I was looking at this, you know,
I think the most demented Captain Andy that they were trying to restore the reality.
I think my favorite thing of animatronics is this inanimate object just made me feel.
Yeah, it's it's actually like I think I don't the word dumb is very lazy, but it kind of works.
And it's like it's like this stupid machine is making like, I don't know,
like when like the country bears sing like a Beach Boys song, like I always will find that funny.
Like it's not real.
And I think when you're a kid, everyone has that memory of like, Mom, that is that real?
Is that real?
Like trying to figure out if something is real or not.
I think that's one of our first like discoveries as children.
And with them, you're like, I still don't know.
When I watch like a really cool animatronic, I think I believe they're real.
It's still a part of you.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
But then I watch rocket fire explosion and I'm just like, oh, man, this makes me so happy.
I'm when I first moved here, they were selling one of the sets and it was like the whole rocket fire.
Well, yeah, I believe like it was a good amount of money.
And my dad has a tire supply store in Baltimore.
I was like, Dad, if I lived in an apartment with no money, I was like, if I could afford this, could I keep it in your warehouse?
He's like, you've lost your mind.
I was like, Dad, but just imagine being depressed and then going outside and watching a gorilla play the drums that led Zeppelin.
Like that would just be so awesome.
He was still feeling the same way.
It's the only thing where this is the only area where like I don't think that that belongings can give you happiness except for this kind of stuff.
It's the only I would never not laugh at that.
They would never get like, oh, I used to find animatronics funny.
Like there's never I'm never going to say that.
No, no, no, this is not this is not my animatronic phase from zero to forty four.
Yeah, right.
A forty five is typically the cut off.
Yeah, scientifically, that's when the animatronic part of the brain fizzes out.
I got absolutely and I don't know if you know the extent to which like you're rotting Captain Andy just reminds me of listeners certainly know this.
But like there's listeners and we all have a lot of affinity for this character, Botanicus, who is from the E.
T.
adventure, the E.
at Universal Studios, E.
T.
's teacher.
And like the whole all the rides, all the rides there were great of all the things.
There's plenty of successful things at Universal Studios, but there's something so special about Botanicus specifically.
Yeah.
And this will tie into figma just like and it's a character you can only meet in this specific place or these two specific places.
And when I got a job as a Universal tour guide, one of the first days I saw the rotting corpse of Botanicus sitting backstage, like around a corner unquestionably.
That is what I recognized in an instant just without the skin.
It is so obviously.
And he's got his big staff and his like orb.
And just with the feelings, the feelings I got about it and just what that did to me and then that it literally helped my wife and I get together because she came to take my tour.
And I broke the rules of the park so that I was like, I want to show you something.
And I didn't know she had the same affinity and she almost.
Show you the world.
Wow.
She was a friend I knew.
And then like.
Well, she was either never going to talk to you again or marry you.
Yeah.
A thousand percent.
Yes.
That's the Botanicus test.
Better shoot your shot.
It's like flipping a coin.
You know, you're getting one of two options.
So mad.
But then like some of the most important relationships, that one and then Botanicus is completely is what brought Mike and I together, which is the brother Jason.
And like so there's there are there is particular magic, I think, to I'm just so happy to learn about yours that you have.
You've had it for Captain Andy.
We've had it for Botanicus.
And I think probably a lot of people listening have it for Figment.
There are so many like visually like I have a wall of toys.
And if you saw what this wall looked like, you would think I was something's wrong.
This guy's.
That's fair.
Most people, normal people would come in and say, oh, oh, yeah, something wrong.
I did it until we started doing the zoom episodes.
And I was like, that is a lot of times.
Yeah, no, it's too many.
It's too many.
But here's the problem is that what you're describing is what I feel when I see these.
And these are perfect recreations of things that that hit me when I was five, six, seven years old.
Tell me what I said that reminds you of that.
You were talking about how happy the animatronic makes you.
And in a similar way, I was I find that like literally I can feel I almost can feel it in a practical way in my mind of like I'm looking at this thing that I saw when I was a kid and it is just giving me this joy.
And you can like I can go in there and just get a hit of it like I go in the office, literally get a hit of the toy, put like move them around a little bit and then leave.
And I go a little bit better.
You don't need to pick a favorite.
But if can you at least who's in the top five?
Just name.
I have Billy Bob from the rocket fire explosion.
I have a Billy Bob.
It's like I actually have two.
I have one and there's one smaller one.
The head.
But no, no, just.
Well, the head's recreation.
It's a recreation.
How tall?
I have one that's like almost probably 10 inches.
And then there's one that's still in the box.
It's like four.
I don't know if they're making more.
And you went to party time pizza.
I never saw Billy Bob live, but I I never got to see the rocket fire live.
Those regrets.
You know, I never saw Bowie and I never saw.
I never saw Paul Simon before he retired.
I never said Billy Bob.
He retired.
I'm hearing this for the first time right now.
Paul Simon retired.
I didn't know.
Last night I chose rocket fire instead of Tom Petty.
I saw petty second to last night and he died.
I saw Tom Petty second to last night.
We're before the last concert.
And I saw Mike Nesmith from Monkeys last concert.
Wow.
The literal literal last concert.
You shouldn't tell someone that story when they play a concert.
But if I'm like, hey, I want to let you know.
Everyone dies.
I'm the angel of death.
Want to see my choice?
So excited.
Young person.
We deal with it.
We have a class as the PTR.
We kill a lot of people by bringing them up.
I think we all have to defend it.
And I just want to say it probably always comes up.
But just to say it's like we only are here for a little while.
Let's get the thing.
There are they are material things.
But if it brings you joy and clearly something happened in our childhood that wasn't working.
But that helped us.
Sure.
Yeah.
That was a helping pill.
That was a mechanism that that reminds us that things are going to be OK.
Surround yourself with things that remind you things are OK.
Yeah.
I agree.
That's beautiful.
I say that on every date.
That's your line.
You still have a figment.
OK.
In the last week, I have purchased multiple secondhand Planet Hollywood T-shirts.
Damn.
Oh, you've given it from us.
What is it that drives you there?
It was probably similar to figment.
I'm associating happy times with family.
Going to those places.
Be them.
Orlando or the Atlantic City Boardwalk.
The real hot spot of Hollywood.
Yeah.
It always just felt like an event.
And anything also because it's gone.
There's also that drive.
It's gone.
But it's also kind of hanging again, much like figment.
It's kind of hanging.
They still have.
There's still a little.
I didn't know that.
There's one or two Planet Hollywood's hanging on out there.
There's a few tricky.
One by one, they're going.
And so a lot of them have been remodeled.
So they aren't all the 90s velvet zebra pattern nightmare
that they were.
But there's a few.
There's a few hanging there.
When it opened in Baltimore, my parents dropped me off at noon.
And I stayed because I wanted to get a good seat for Bruce
Wallace playing the harmonica.
I wanted to be the opening of Baltimore.
Oh my gosh.
There you go.
Wow.
I love playing.
Also, it's like the world that we love and a restaurant.
Like it was great idea.
Yeah.
And it you know, especially in the late 80s, early 90s,
they were everyone was so good at selling the idea of Hollywood,
be it MGM studios or Planet Hollywood, like the magic of the movies.
But it like anything of that nature just like electrified me at that.
Yeah.
I will.
We will.
I will enforce going to journey after this.
But the do we all know about the the Planet Hollywood like temporary auction
gallery that's happening?
Yes.
As the as this airs, I believe this will be open and listeners to this in Beverly Hills.
I don't know what the deal is exactly.
And if it's the real stuff or if it's recreations, but I think this is going to be this gallery.
I'm going to tempt you, Derek, with things.
I think it's it'll be a place where you can like go see Stallone in the demolition man tube and like, you know, whatever.
We can go see him.
The like what recreation.
He'll do it.
Oh, no, I mean, not their life.
Yeah, there's there's a thing that all the Planet Hollywood had, which was like a Stallone curled up into a ball naked Stallone.
I remember that.
Well, they almost all you could like eat under it.
It would be hanging up above you.
Yeah.
And your multiple might be exit.
They obviously made multiple for many locations.
But basically, there's going to be this gallery in Beverly Hills, apparently, that where they're selling all this Planet Hollywood stuff.
And I don't know the deal with it yet.
By the time this comes out, I may have tried to go.
I'm not totally sure.
I'm trying to figure it out.
But like, hopefully, it is my hope that this will be like a temporary pop up Planet Hollywood to go walk around.
That sounds like really that's a good time.
Now, the jacket, though, I really like that jacket was so cool.
And you got two of them.
Awesome.
I got a couple of t shirts and a sweatshirt.
Oh, sorry.
So those don't know my jacket.
It's in the will probably.
It's the heirloom in the will.
We were talking about a while ago and he's like, well, I lost some weight recently, so I fit in it again.
Like, all right, fair enough.
All right.
You were asking about it.
You were you wanted to get it before.
Eating well.
Keep.
I keep.
He's lost weight.
I've gained weight.
So now it's like, well, at least someone's wearing it.
It'll it'll land where it's meant to land.
OK, let's start getting there.
Though I loved all of that.
And it's a perfect like texture to put into what you're talking about.
My last thing is I know.
Yeah.
Oh, please.
Planet Hollywood.
I went when I was 17, 18 and auditioned for the real world in Baltimore.
Oh, wow.
But I was like, now I look back, I'm like, I don't think there ever was a real world
Baltimore like I think I got conned.
To do what?
They just wanted to just interview what I'm like to man.
Oh, shit.
That might be where Figment comes in to save me.
From dark energy.
I just remembered they did DC.
Would that have been for maybe they're going to move it?
That would make sense.
That's why I mean, I just look the rest of it.
We could do an hour about I want to know about your Bruce Willis and the Accelerator concert.
But OK, because this is an important one, let's make sure that we do it.
Journey into imagination opens March 5th, 1983.
Cliff notes version in case because this is now it's been gone for a long time.
And there's this current thing that happens to have the same title and the same character.
But that's not what we're dealing with today.
Here's the rules.
It can come up.
We can talk about it.
But we're talking about the good one, the pure one that fits with the vibe we've had so far.
It is a dark ride that celebrates imagination and explores where ideas come from via hijinks with a whimsical professor type named Dreamfinder and a literal figment of his imagination.
A dragon named Figment, just to say the little cliff notes of it.
Not an opening day Epcot attraction.
It was a little bit late, but in that first year.
And we'll talk about the specific stuff in this and the history of it.
But I ask you now, Derek, why emotionally of all the things you could have picked?
Why Journey into Imagination?
It's the first ride or I would say first event.
I remember being with my family and feeling like I was somewhere else.
Whatever that does.
But I remember the music.
I remember his face and they had a Dreamfinder and a figment walking around the park and getting your picture taken.
It was actually this hand that figment.
Oh, yes.
Your pants.
Yeah.
Where he was like, yeah, the Dreamfinder has to be puppeteering and he's got like a fake arm bed to hold.
Right.
Incredible.
But I think there also is like almost like a Sesame Street feeling like where we're being entertained, but we're also being educated.
When I was like, yeah, this again, I'm six or seven, but I still think the brain registers like, oh, yeah, imagination is the coolest thing that we have the capability of doing.
And there's a ride and there's this guy flying like it really felt like you were flying.
And I like puff the magic dragon.
And he reminded me of puff.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
Yeah.
Not just the dragon qualities.
But and then you go back and you're like, oh, and it probably was because when we all got off the ride, I saw my family happy.
Let's be honest.
It probably was that.
Whoa.
Yeah.
I never hide that barrier of like, yeah, you're not 44 and you still like a purple dinosaur because like it's cool.
It did something.
And I love that.
They get fully opposed to this like clinically.
I've this is a cool thing.
Yeah, there's got to be an emotional.
Yeah.
But also it's not like no offense to small world.
Like there's like actual like arc that went into it.
Like it's very like, you know, when you're a kid, you're just seeing colors and stuff.
And then you watch this as an adult and you're like, man, they were really like educating you on like your brain, a dream finder that goes around and collects things that inspire your dreams.
No musical notes ideas like they're like colors.
And I don't know.
I just think whether you know it as a kid that that shapes you of going, OK, I don't have to like work in business.
Yeah.
Sure.
I don't have an imagination.
Do you feel like you can trace like a creative career back to like this and things like this?
I think.
Yeah.
I think without knowing it was just like, oh, yeah, this is when I feel good.
This is where I feel like, oh, I'm escaping whatever I'm in and getting this great joy.
And yeah, I also the music of this was so good.
The Sherman Brothers and then all right, we can't talk about the other one.
But it was 12 minute ride.
No, yeah.
Yeah.
I think it's it's just part of it at this point.
This like that there was this like crazy, ambitious, experimental, borderline psychedelic kind of ride.
And then ever since, there's been this strange impression of one.
It's a short.
Yeah, they cut it in half.
Yeah.
Who would.
Lengthwise.
I so bizarre.
And that was one of the goals, evidently, it was to like, I don't know, 12 minutes is a little long.
And now you're like, who is now in the age of Rise of the Resistance?
You're like, who is complaining about a long ride?
That's so weird.
Yeah.
I also think when you have a stuffed animal, you know, like I didn't live in Florida.
I lived in Maryland.
So I probably rode that ride twice.
Yeah.
Between 83 and 98.
But you have this like figment stuffed animal like pulls you back there.
Yeah, I love I love the ride and the leaping.
I think they're called leaping frog fountains.
They're still there, right?
They are still there.
Yeah, my I was showing them to my girlfriend back in like November and we're immediately like giggling like, like, I was like, no, you got it.
If you catch it, you can get soaking wet.
It was so hot today.
And I was like, you figure out where it goes and you put your hand up to block it.
And then people are walking by giggling with us.
And I was like, well, the fountains still work.
The fountains still do what they're designed to do.
The exterior last night, I was like thinking, I was like, oh, I want to bring this up and see what you guys think.
But now I feel different because you brought the aquarium that I was like, you know what?
If you look at the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, the design of the Hall of Fame.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like, is that the inspiration to their architecture?
I couldn't find anything.
But then when you said the aquarium in Baltimore, they both have a similar glass.
Yeah.
Where is the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?
Rock and Roll Hall of Fame is 97.
OK.
Yes.
Well, sometimes one little spark happens when you see a building and it sparks the mind to make the same building, but slightly different.
There was so much in the air back then or like unbuilt, unrealized projects, like a lot of the video essays about Journey, of course, touch on the unbuilt Discovery Bay at Disneyland.
The original version of the Land Pavilion, which was going to have gigantic crystals.
Yeah, that design is really cool.
If you've never seen that.
Don't worry about trying to put like big crystals in Disney forever.
That's a big thing, too.
In addition to just Jules Verne shit, it's like big crystals is definitely something that comes up a lot.
I never knew that.
I guess so.
And like it also appears in other stuff, like even just like art from like Lucasport, which is going to be like the George Lucas overlay or whatever redo of Tomorrowland.
It's very crystal and these big buildings.
Which also might have there might have been something like that in Westcott.
Yes, for sure.
This idea just moved from the big indoor atrium that was very crystal.
Yeah.
Which like it's great.
It landed where it did because, you know, I'm recalling I feel like but at this point we're getting close to having covered like all the big original Epcot stuff.
Yeah.
And one of the last ones we did, I don't remember if it was maybe it was when we talked about Horizons.
I feel like I at some point declared this is my favorite looking.
Maybe I said Horizons was my favorite of the big austere original Epcot buildings.
Why did I not say journey into imagination?
Of course, it's this right?
Isn't it just like architecturally, aesthetically pleasing?
It feels future proof.
Like I do think it doesn't feel like an out of it's like kind of forever 80s, but forever future.
That thing, you know, is certainly the vibe I want.
Yeah, it doesn't feel dated in a way.
Even like, you know, like that land building is like a little unfriendly.
I think it's cool.
I think all I look I love all of the big like blocky Epcot.
Yeah, but a lot of early Epcot was like, I hope you like brutalism.
Yeah, yeah.
Which I did and I do.
And then I've like any time I see that in Warner Center and Woodland Hills or wherever, I'm like, oh, it's like Epcot.
But this, I don't know, Journey, this building is aged so well.
The thing Journey is going forward is that it feels it feels very much of like a sister to Spaceship Earth to me because of the like whatever like.
There's some whimsy in the architecture.
So it does feel like it's built from the same like material or something and Horizons feels different.
Yeah, yeah.
I guess I do.
I think Journey.
Yeah, I guess you're probably right.
I don't mean to dictate.
No, but I like Horizons a lot too.
If I had ever said this one was the best, unless it's the best Spaceship Earth, does that count?
Well, if that counts, then that's my favorite.
Yeah.
Do you have a leaning favorite Epcot building?
I mean, yeah, Journey.
The other thing I was going to say is like you also now when you get older and you get off a ride and there's like, you know, the toys to buy.
But like with Figment, you went into like, you know, the image works like you were kind of you now like learn something on the ride that you got to like do it.
So it's almost like its own separate park.
Like you had got to do what Figment taught you in that rainbow corridor that you walk through like that.
It was just it's just magical.
And that's what all we love of Disney and stuff.
And it just felt like, yeah, I don't know.
I just forever love it.
And Figment's funny.
Yes.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, you want to you want to talk characters a little bit.
Let's just like and we can go look, we'll do a little Dream Finder, too.
But let's make sure we devote enough time to just like we've not really had just a big talk about Figment on the show.
We have not had a big talk.
Yeah, we haven't had.
We haven't had the talk about Figment.
That will be my the talk with my son.
You should know there is a purple dragon and he's wonderful.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Figment's great.
I don't know.
This is going to be the most intellectual talk, but it is wonderful.
Visually appealing.
Yes.
Kind of a great shade.
Well, so much.
I think purple is going to be good, but I love that.
That like the very 80s.
I feel like the building they did some of in that color, too.
That kind of like light periwinkle.
Oh, yeah.
Great purple.
That's I really like, especially being like having all these toys of like stuff when I was a kid, like just visually speed like Dream Finder, Figment just perfectly like like appealing to a child.
Like just from the colors to just the juxtaposition of the two characters.
Like almost that.
Like over anything else, the ride probably could have been half as good, but just those two characters seeing them as a kid to me, at least it was like, oh, yeah, like I like these guys like immediately like very good.
Yeah.
Do you know why Figment was red and yellow?
His outfit.
Well, I'll sweater.
Yeah.
Wait.
But yes, go ahead.
I did find that you did.
Yeah.
Also, we're real quick.
A good note of red and yellow makes you hungry.
Technically, though, that combination.
Because it's like mushroom.
Think about McDonald's in and out.
Wendy's like, oh, they've done studies that that combination makes you hungry.
That's interesting.
But Figment has it because it's Kodak that is the Kodak logo.
That is a thing about this ride as a kid immediately endeared the Kodak company.
Yes.
I was like, Kodak is good.
They're important.
They're powerful.
Reading.
I it was funny reading about the late 90s Kodak.
They were just like, we're not going to do any digital.
We're putting our foot down like they they had the ability, but they were very resistant to it.
And that was the kind of death knell of a lot of photography companies is just not not going with the.
Yeah.
Not immediately embracing.
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
And I think that is I think they could have done it digitally in Kodak was like, no, this has to be done in like the slides, whatever their current technology was.
I could not do any demonstration of digital photos.
There is a long interview with Tony Baxter on this old blog called the MacGyver Project.
And he says, like, I mentioned once, like, well, we could sell these photos and they immediately gave me a death stare.
Oh, what?
Yeah, I don't know.
Apparently, it took a lot to take those digital like those photos for just a second.
Like they had a room of computers.
Yeah.
To manage that at first.
Wow.
Just having a photo that you look at for three seconds on your way out.
But they didn't sell photos and they didn't sell videos at the blue screen in the image works.
The blue screen like acted like movie area.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
Right.
The the colors also come from the original.
I think they went more like, you know, A to B with him being a green dragon originally.
But green is the color of Fuji film, which was in the park.
It was in Epcot elsewhere or like they were trying to be or they were they like going to be part of the Japan.
Well, the idea that the rumor was that they got the Mount Fuji Coaster canned.
Oh, my God.
That supposedly there was going to be a Mount Fuji Coaster in World Showcase.
And then they were like, no, Fuji.
No, it's the mention of the freight.
Yeah.
We're Fuji Coaster since I'm glad they got us this.
But shit, Fuji Coaster sounds really good.
Yeah, because the original because because the Dreamfinder and Figment were from the original concept of we just said it and I can't think of the name of it.
The original 70s Tony Baxter Discovery, Discovery, Captain Magic, Captain Marvel and his dragon.
Yeah.
And it was like Green Dragon.
They're like, no green or no green allowed.
Yeah.
But that also sounded cool.
Carousel progress with like some crazy.
Sure.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I yes.
So this is this this is Captain Marvel.
I wait, Professor Marvel.
It's not Captain Marvel.
Captain Marvel.
Professor.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yes.
Professor Marvel.
That was going to be part of that Discovery land area that never got built to Disneyland.
And then Tony Baxter had an idea for the land pavilion where there was a guy named the Landkeeper.
Yeah.
And he was not quite well, Landkeeper is a couple of he's in a he's in a white tux.
He's cool.
He is kind of neat.
He's a different vibe entirely, but he's sort of Colonel Sanders.
Oh, yeah.
A little bit.
But then with Rainbow and he has the Captain EO Rainbow on his shirt.
That really feels like it did turn.
I'm sure that's what that is.
Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
This whole thing, everything that happened in this pavilion, these were a lot of stuff that was just floating around.
It just all feels like like they were all talking to me as a five year old.
Well, what do you want to see on his chest?
You want a rainbow?
They're like, great.
What color should the dragon be?
Purple is my favorite color.
And they're like, great.
This kid is just deciding all the things that will make other kids like it.
Yeah.
It's smart.
Figment, I think, is I mean, OK, a few things.
It takes very little to like on board with him.
You kind of understand what he is as soon as you see him.
And then this the introduction scene and the ride, you kind of like, all right, I get it.
He's this whimsical thing of your imagination.
That's that's very clear.
He also just visually, because in the ride, he has to work as animatronic cartoon, his original animation of him in the ride and then puppet for all the videos at the end.
And he translates from medium to medium really well.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think that's true.
You mentioned, you know, thinking the animatronics were real in that ending scene as a kid.
I remember like figments of mountain climbers, super heroes, this and that.
And then reading the reality of that in the one that Tony Baxter interviews like, oh, that is we wanted to animate that.
We couldn't get it animated in time.
So that puppet is actually an animatronic with the guts removed and a puppeteer doing it.
And it is so cumbersome.
They could only do like five minutes at a time because they had to rest because animatronic skin is so thick and heavy.
It's not like it's not it's not Kermit.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I never knew that.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
Little sequences like how adorable is it like figment like lifting a little barbell?
And now we know that was figments lifting a little barbell and then the guy under figment is like really struggling.
Yeah.
Just like begging for a cigarette break.
And it's better because it's not.
I look the animation would have been cool, I'm sure.
But it's better that it's not.
Yeah.
I think.
I remember Dream Finder is teaching.
Figment is asking questions as the audience.
So like we're learning from figment on what who Dreamcatcher is and figments asking questions like, oh, we can anything is possible.
Like we can come up with anything like I always thought that's a good teaching tool to where he's speaking for the audience.
Like an Elmo fashion.
They want to get scary.
You can turn the word cat in the bat like the number the thunder.
I read that they were going to have fog machine smoke machine to make you feel like you're on a cloud.
Oh, well, when he's flying, but they didn't want to mess up the design.
Yeah, I read that.
Yeah.
So they don't have the good haze machines that we have now.
So like that would have been really cool.
They haven't perfected fog technology or they hadn't.
Yeah.
What a time.
I appreciate what a time we live in fog wise.
Yeah, this is a golden age of fog.
Yeah.
Curing diseases, whatever.
That is what it is.
But the we can like Six Flags Six Flags Fright Fester on the forefront.
Yeah, they won't destroy sets anymore.
Yeah.
And a teen can breathe it in.
No problem.
Right.
Yeah.
The what has there ever been another ride where it was refurbished but the main character was gone.
I don't know McDonald's without cheeseburger.
I don't know why.
Well, it is similar to in a way to like McDonald's becoming kind of these like bland McCafe kind of like aesthetic free just like cold surfaces and the characters are kind of gone.
Yeah.
And then they're bringing the characters and ads lately.
They are bringing that.
It's always it's never a good idea.
I don't think.
Well, they got rid of the original McDonald's mascot too, which was what Speedy was that like little character that was before Ronald.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I mean, I forgot about him.
You see him occasionally.
He pops up once in a while.
He's always confused me, I think.
Why is he only at like one out of every 100 McDonald's?
I'll say this.
When I see him, I don't feel joy like I do with these other characters.
Speedy that is.
Because he's from like these from the 50s.
Yeah, I don't have a connection to Speedy.
I see joy when I see Birdie and Ronald.
Do you like Zippy, the United States Postal mascot?
I like him, but I have no deep affection for him.
You don't dislike him.
Don't dislike.
I feel like you love him.
I love Zippy.
Yeah, of course you do.
Zippy was a little cartoon guy introduced with the advent of zip codes to get people to use zip codes.
He's about zip codes.
Zippy.
As a kid, you loved zip codes and you loved the US Postal.
Show me my zip code again, mom.
Well, that was getting the zip code right before bed.
I feel like it was like, okay, I learned when my birthday was.
I specifically remember around the time probably of Figment, the most paid attention, most like Figment, like first grade.
Our teacher asked me, when's your birthday?
I was like, I don't know, March.
My birthday is in October.
I have no idea.
That's weird.
Why?
You got it way wrong.
But I got it way wrong.
And at that point, I had already celebrated my birthday, I think.
It's like, wait, that was just a few.
I don't know why.
Did you get nervous?
I think I got nervous.
But tying shoes and learning zip code, I think they were late coming for me.
I got the first start of the address with zip code.
It took a while to learn those numbers.
I did Velcro for a long time.
I did Velcro for a while.
Kangaroos.
I had a lot of Velcro with X-Men or Ninja Turtles on them.
Oh, cool.
And then you're like, I don't want to do shoes that tie because the X-Men aren't on them as often.
Well, I still agreed.
Looking back, I was like, well, they were more efficient to do the Velcro.
Are you going to go back to Velcro?
I don't know.
Every now and then I see a Velcro shoe.
I see a running shoe without little Velcro.
I'm wearing slip-ons right now.
Oh, so you are.
Yeah.
You don't have to worry about any of it.
I don't always do slip-ons, but for a record, you know, comfortable.
For a work of comfort-building.
Here's a…
Well, okay, how about that?
Let's clear this one out of the way because we can't not say it.
There is a story about why Figment is Figment.
Of course.
And I think it's, you know, okay, we love Tony Baxter, creator of this ride and creator of Figment, very much on the show.
And I think it's, does maybe, does that just maybe answer why this show is so perennially devoted to telling the same stories over and over again?
Oh, perhaps.
Because it is what our man Tony likes to do.
There are these tales in any setting.
With us in real interviews, he will always tell.
I think this guy does.
Well, he said he stumbled upon the word Figment because there's an episode of Magnum P.
I.
Where Magnum P.
's friend Higgins?
His butler.
His butler, yeah.
Butler was really mad about a goat eating his prized flowers.
Yeah, of course.
And he went on like a little rant that he's like, I know it's real, it's not a figment of my imagination.
Yeah, we said figment doesn't eat, figments don't eat flowers.
Is that the correct line, something along those lines?
Technically, Tony shortens it.
But the real line is, don't, and don't tell me it's a figment of my imagination.
Figments don't eat rare tropical flowers.
There you go.
This is the actual full line.
But who told the story?
But he was talking about a goat.
What's that?
He's talking, he's referring to a goat.
But why would he say a figment doesn't eat?
He's saying don't tell me it's not real.
I think Magnum, I don't know the full context of the episode.
Honestly, that's research.
I probably should have brought into this affair so that I would actually know.
But I believe that Magnum P.
I.
This is what happens on Magnum P.
by the way.
He's hiding a goat in the yard.
I think this is the B plot.
It's fun.
Higgins is a stuffy guy.
And he's got to deal with a ridiculous goat eating his beloved tropical flower.
It's not that Magnum has chosen a goat as his new partner.
But he's going to keep it off the books.
But I wouldn't put it past Magnum.
Crazy ideas from the loose cannon.
But yes, that is what it is.
Hearing figments.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please.
Has he ever?
Because I know that story, but like they knew Kodak was going to be the sponsor.
He's trying to come up with this stuff.
And I thought Kodak was really heavy on imagination and color.
So I'm like, I think the word imagination was probably what triggered him half listening.
Oh, true.
Like trying to find things that are like cool with the word imagination.
Associated with imagination.
That's a good point.
Because yeah, why are they doing any of this if not for?
And yeah, it did all come from Kodak is interested.
They want to do something.
And they don't want to do one of these stuffy Avkat pavilions.
They want it to be.
And it doesn't matter what it's about so long as it is something imaginative.
That is what they said.
And they Disney said, how about imagination?
It's pretty imaginative.
They gave a lot of room.
I feel like Baxter says like, well, figment was a it's a known word.
People know it, but I feel like it's not used a lot.
So there's a uniqueness to it.
But like a million dollar where everybody nobody's grabbed that.
Yes, like as like IP.
Yeah.
Basically, is this the was the last time he watched something current?
This Magnum P.
I.
episode probably.
My question, because this all comes from me asking him if he's ever like watched an episode of Seinfeld and thinks, oh, I can make a right out of this.
And he goes, well, I watch old movies or something.
He said something along those lines.
Oh, so I was the last the last piece of media that he ever that maybe question for interview number two with us.
Sure.
This is Magnum P.
I.
The last current show you watched.
You have made me think of a theme park.
It's just like, so how did you come up with a ride?
Balke.
Well, it's all right from watching a show.
This read these idea of these characters who are perfect strangers.
Where did that phrase enter your head?
But OK, he Brewster.
It's a dance club.
And yeah, but a pretty broad assignment.
I don't want to be imagination.
Well, like Kodak seemed reasonably hands off.
Yeah, I think so.
As long as nothing green is in it and not as long as it's about imagination.
And I do think actually with that, like them just saying exactly what given Kodak exactly what they wanted, I think that they then they determined here's what the rooms are.
Like we explore performing arts and literature and that.
And I I don't think I'm pulling this out of nowhere.
I think that Kodak saw the presentation and said, what about science?
And then you watch a ride through and Dream Finder says, what about science?
I think they quoted Kodak back to them.
Wow.
I also feel like I'm hallucinating.
That's a figment of my mission.
I don't know.
Maybe I got that from somewhere.
That's how to win friends and influence people.
Trek, I think you say someone's words back to them or you say like three or four of their words back to them and they go, oh, wow, they were listening.
That science part, by the way, I think that was the part that scared me as a kid.
Really?
Sure.
That creepy music and the time lapse flowers and melting snow and stuff.
Yeah, I feel like I was just scared.
I was scared of like certain types of film.
Does that make any sense?
Like I could tell the difference.
I'd watch Sesame Street and I would know when it goes to film as opposed to video.
Oh, video is friendly and where my friends live and film is scary.
Yeah.
And I don't know what I was.
But I swear I have this that like frame rates and like the quality of lenses just would like and then it would scare that like Sesame Street is on video and then follow that bird is on film and follow that bird is very upsetting.
And I think part of that is that like, well, now it's now my character, my favorite characters are being shot the way, you know, like Midnight Cowboys being shot.
Film is for grownups.
Film gives you like a little surreal quality versus just video.
Video feels like I'm just looking through a window and film.
I agree with that.
Yeah, you could feel that.
You couldn't articulate it probably at five.
No, I don't think but I did.
It's one of those things I give.
I feel the feeling.
I felt it.
No, I hear you.
Film, video.
It felt like there was no weight to it.
If you were watching something that was on film.
Absolutely.
Like it felt like, yeah, yeah, there's also the Sesame Street films.
There's also the audio.
I remember like it sounded completely different.
Like, yeah, just like, I don't know.
I'm yeah, I'm feeling you.
At first, I want to say you sounded like a dick as a kid being particular.
But that I was a film snob.
I think.
Yeah.
What kind of lens is this, mother?
Another wide angle.
Interesting choice.
But we like what we're used to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yes.
But also what in figment that there's so much happening.
Your brain just can't digest it.
There's film.
There's there's animatronic.
There's video.
There's I don't know.
And the colors.
Like I just think.
Yeah, I wonder how many times we wrote it as as kids that it still stays with us.
Like, it's pretty other things.
Probably didn't.
I probably like you probably did seven other rides on those same trips that don't like stay with you.
I don't remember any of them.
I only remember figment.
Yeah.
Well, it was also I feel like it was easy.
Not that the you know, there was never any lines, but just the modified Omni movers set up.
It was an Epcot ride.
You could go in and get on a dark ride like in five, maybe 10 minutes.
Sure.
There's not a big pre show.
There's not exhibits to walk through.
There's not a post show.
You got to like the post show is fun and it's built into the ride and you get to see the Rainbow Corridor.
You know, yeah, I'm repeating myself because we've said this on multiple Epcot episodes, but also my memories of all going on Epcot stuff in the 80s all blend together.
Because they all feel like they're of a piece.
All the Epcot rides are an experimental rock and roll album or something.
And like you remember pieces here and there.
But I'm watching like World of Motion as an adult on YouTube and I'm like, I don't know any.
I don't I'm sure there's parts of it I maybe remember, but like I can remember some things about Horizons.
Remember some things, but it all really blends together.
And I think that's part of design.
Yeah.
I have it all feel like a one piece.
I'm embarrassed to ask, but like the caveman blowing his feet.
That's Spaceship Earth.
That's the one there.
I remember.
Wait, are we wrong?
Are they blowing their feet because they don't have vehicles to?
It's not because they have to walk like Flintstones on the ground.
Yeah, because there's a Tundra scene sort of on Spaceship Earth before you get into like obviously the different.
Yeah, but maybe that's what you're doing.
Nothing embarrassing about that because now I'm questioning where.
I know there's cavemen in Spaceship Earth, but are there also?
I'm questioning it now because I'm just picturing this guy blowing his feet.
I remember that was like a memory.
That's what I think.
It's World of Motion.
No, you're right.
Look here.
This is at from some like auction.
Oh, yeah.
That is a caveman blowing his feet.
There you go.
I don't think we talked about this in World of Motion.
We did see that's one of those.
That is one of those weird things because there's multiple rides with cavemen in Epcot.
There's multiple things where you go into the Renaissance and different futures and the futures all feel very 80s.
And which ones have horses?
And yeah, it's really.
And I guess imagination probably feels like the outlier of all of them too because I feel like or I guess Horizons and imagination feel a little more unique.
Well, imagination I think is the most ethereal.
Horizons.
Yeah.
You know, if you're latching on to set pieces, Horizon was like, well, you get to pick the ending.
You get to pick the ending.
Sure.
Yeah.
And that was a big thing for me as a kid.
But even watching watching imagination, it just the start is unique.
That carousel, which I had totally forgotten about.
I know I knew this at some point, but it's like, oh, a lot of the money went to building five dream finders and dream catchers and figments.
And you would slowly rotate around the scene like you're watching like a three minute scene basically to start the ride.
You pull into a turntable and you're moving exactly along with the scene that you're watching to where it might feel like you are not moving at all.
Like you're it's and I I have to say I didn't know this ever that they're that they built five identical.
Yeah, I didn't know that.
This scene five times.
I didn't know that.
So it's like a miniature carousel progress like within your own Haunted Mansion type ride that goes into a carousel progress with this trippy so that everyone can get that experience at once.
And it doesn't slow anything down.
And five of not just nothing, five big flab traction flying machines that are full sized.
There's I saw a photo of an Imagineer sitting in one who's the same.
It is not smaller for Dream Finder.
Right.
That is like that is a full adult sized flying machine that they had to build five times.
Yeah, they it's seeing the overhead of it.
I'm like, oh my God, like, yeah, I never even watching any of these videos over the years.
I never even put it together that that's how that was achieved.
One of those for a long time was in the mouse gear shop in the center of that car.
You could look up and see it see the rustic rustic dream catcher.
They kicked out of the ride.
Do you guys all feel this way a little bit where like, OK, I have I've had like affection for this.
I know I've watched a ride through here and there, but I'm not even full of things we've covered.
I'm not close to having this memorized or I wasn't before.
It's like all stayed in that hazy kid brain.
I for sure remember seeing from my vantage point as a child the big like the big flying machine and Dream Finder because that was so striking and scary.
But the rest of it, I'm like I have like like bits and flickers.
But like it's all really in a in a childhood haze for me.
You guys feel similar?
Yeah, 100 percent.
I'd often it really feels like a dream.
It really feels truly like I can't remember anything outside of those just big iconic images from it that lasted.
Yeah, re re watching videos the last few days and then reading text descriptions of it.
There would be stuff I missed from the videos and then I had to go back and find right pictures where it's like, wait, there is a teapot.
There's like a weird teapot art piece.
Right.
Like right when you start to pull into the actual attraction part.
Yeah.
And that's like just, you know, it's just set dressing.
It's not even like, you know, it's not important to eat on.
Yeah.
Right.
It is like seeing the the two big moments, the big moments of like the Edgar Allan Poe like Phantom of the Opera like organ.
But it's a keyboard and he's writing mystery story.
And then that goes into figment wanting to put on a little show and he's in a tux and tails with a top hat.
I'm like, well, that's my adult.
Like, that's just my brain was just molded at six and it just never changed.
You know, yeah, it is so it's such a it's a fun blend of like, yeah, like, I just put this cute character in like a tux, which obviously is, you know, we've seen Bugs Bunny in the tux.
As a kid, I don't know that I knew what that really meant.
Right.
Yeah.
But I like it.
And then it's mixed with like really heady like colors and weird noises.
And it doesn't I think it's interesting that it doesn't translate so well to even old footage.
Like I know it's a lot of the upcast stuff, I guess doesn't.
But it just doesn't you can't really feel it in watching even the best quality like Uprised footage.
Yeah.
I feel like I'm like I know I can see it and I can imagine I can imagine it, but I cannot feel it necessarily from these images of the same video.
I just remembered when you like you couldn't capture everything that was going.
You're constantly.
Yes.
Look, there were so many things to see that I also think that's why it's harder to remember because there's not just like one journey.
There's like again when you see all the figments doing characters, all this music and rainbows, it's like I don't know.
I just yeah.
Well, like juxtaposing and even just with watching like a VH or like camcorder footage of Haunted Mansion or Pirates from the 90s or something, you're like, well, I can tell in this footage what it is.
Obviously, it's not giving you all the feelings of it, but it was very dark and it's yeah, it has like a lot of like trippier things going on.
Yeah.
Do you want to like hear a little like let's just let's just get a hit of like which one I don't know about some one little spark just to give us a give us a little vibe here.
Sure.
Yeah.
One little spark of inspiration is at the heart of all creation right at the start of everything that's new.
One little spark lights up for you.
Oh, hello there.
So glad you could come along.
I am the dream finder.
Musical notes.
What delightful melodies those will make.
I love these flights of fancy searching the universe for sounds, colors, ideas, anything that sparks the imagination.
I mean, just to get a little hit of that like sound is a lot of it.
This is a real like obviously the song is great Sherman Brothers and then the but the what I couldn't find is where the instrumentation comes from because it's like that.
There's a real like I mean, there's there's it's a big like synth festival for sure.
And you're and when when since and keyboards and digital sounds were not everywhere when you're a kid, you're like, there's a future heads or tails of it.
I don't know what these sounds are.
This feels like it's all types of the areas like harpsichord mixed with just like weird like texture stuff and that's that.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Electronic fart.
This is I really if anyone out there knows who like because I don't think Sherman Brothers are up at the they aren't like you don't think they were at the patchwork on the mini mode.
You got a huge discogs entry.
I looked I wanted to know.
I played on this Dick Dick Sherman out with marauder on a speedboat somewhere just chatting about what's going on.
What's the new tech like what you're using these days.
Did you guys hear the original song for.
Yeah.
It's the guy that let's hear it for the land.
Wait.
Yeah.
That's where I guess another song is called Journey to your imagination.
But it's but it's not good.
No, it's not.
It's very much.
Let's give it to the land.
It's that same kind of like like mellow seven years.
Yeah.
Like, you know, James Taylor.
It didn't feel like you'd fall asleep to you.
You try very hard with it either.
There's no offense to him as opposed to like the kind of the the bounce and the like.
Yeah.
This is kind of like a not not in a round.
What am I said?
But it like it is sort of the same thing over and over in a small world way, which is probably effective in a ride.
Right.
Like that.
It's like all of it.
It's every bit of music is different permutations of the same melody over and over.
So you come out and you know it for sure.
But whoever this man or woman was that did those sounds, I would say they came from composing movies or shows because I think the bull, that's the sound of the dreamcatchers.
What do you call it?
Like it's like the exhaust pipe or whatever.
When he's getting something, they're sounding like like the sound that the idea comes in to the dream.
Yeah, sure.
His machine is making the music.
Yeah.
Kind of.
But they don't say that.
Like like like word sense, beliefs and bloops are also hitting all of these like sound moments.
Yeah.
When you go in this for the first time, but it kind of gives you their personalities and their whole vibe at the beginning.
But like once you can bag a bunch of times, I'm like, oh, it also sets up the rest of the ride.
Like music notes come into play later.
Lightning comes into play later.
Oh, the things they grab here.
Everything shows up in the dream port.
Yes, that's all.
That they capture in with that the dreamcatcher catches.
Wait.
OK.
Now we've said what is the dreamcatcher?
Dreamcatcher is the airship.
Now this is confusing because I've also seen it referred to as the dream ship and the dream mobile.
It seems like there's not a definitive one.
Yes, because they don't even know or they all had different.
OK, so it's one of those.
It's the dream something or other.
And then you put that.
But either way, it's not the dream port, which is where the dream machine or dreamcatcher goes to drop off the dreams.
Yeah.
And Dreamfinder is the man.
Yeah, Dreamfinder is the man.
But the good thing is with your imagination, it can be whatever you want it to be.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Yes, they probably wouldn't box it.
And then there's also there's some separate device called the imaginometer.
So that at least you remember that separately.
It lets you know how good your imagination is.
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
Is it a quantity or a quality thing?
Oh, I don't know.
I'd have to look at the machine again.
OK, I should look it up.
I'm wondering if that's the second one.
The wait, you mean the other version of the ride?
The Eric Idle journey into your imagination where they then tell you your imagination is dog shit.
Right.
You get it.
Oh, wow.
Compare the openings of these meeting this whimsical man and then he makes up a friend for you as opposed to a character from another movie who you don't remember even if you just saw it saying you have no imagination.
Your imagination is shit.
A guy who's just who is so much like not to say he didn't.
I think Eric Idle's the performance is not the issue.
He's also like he came up on Twitter recently.
He doesn't remember what this is.
He's somebody somebody's photo of like a dragon and he's like, oh, yeah, quest for Camelot was fun.
And they're like, no, that's not that is.
That's from Disney.
He just didn't.
He doesn't even.
And I admit it was like one day for him.
Yeah.
And then nobody probably nobody likes it.
So nobody's ever nobody's saying to him day to day like, hey, I love that Devcott ride.
That just pisses me off.
I know it does as opposed to the love.
And maybe that's a good tie into the talk about the voice talent of this attraction a little bit because these are both fascinating people to talk about.
So Dream Finder is Chuck McCann, who is a like perennial voiceover guy and kids show host.
A lot of stuff that was local and we didn't grow up with.
But he did big national things that we know.
He's the original Sonny the Cuckoo Bird.
He did.
He is the first that ever Cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs was said later.
Duckworth, the butler in DuckTales, among many other Disney voices.
And of course, we can all say it together.
He starred in and created the series Far Out Space Nuts, which was a Sid and Marty Croft nightmare starring him and Bob Denver.
They were the I've watched this.
You've watched Space Nuts.
I've watched the titles familiar to me.
I never seen a lick of.
How'd you like Far Out Space Nuts?
I don't.
You know, it is pretty far out.
I don't know if it's something that I would recommend everybody watch, but it's certainly interesting.
I would say watch the opening credits.
OK, and you can get the vibe from it.
OK, so far out.
They get the song or anything.
At least I don't remember the song.
OK, maybe it was all right.
Anyway, to talk about his voice for a minute.
I mean, how like was this?
This is the first thing that's like this because it's so familiar.
And I pondering visiting all this, I was flushing to like sketches I've done, things I've done here and there where I've done the voice that is like, why hello, I'm a big performative old timey man.
And like, is it purely from this?
It's because I love I love this voice.
Yeah, I've been in the suit and the beard and the hat.
I think is there a Santa Claus before this because he's very Santa like extremely.
I always mention that everywhere that he's very like Santa.
He plays Santa in something like some Mickey Christmas thing.
I'm not sure what, but he's he's all if you can imagine he was also Santa.
Yeah, so it's in the zone of like, like, obviously, like I'm trying to like Miracle on 34th Street.
That's Santa Claus.
Oh, he was a little like the twinkle in his eye.
It's not quite as maybe boisterous, but he's got the vibe going.
Yes, when he like reached like he sits like, like puts his hand on a child's shoulder.
It's possible for them to call you stupid like, no, you didn't understand that.
This is the way you do it.
And you're like, oh, that's a better way of responding to me than like you idiot.
No, that's not what that equals.
You find that like that's like a nurturing type.
I find him.
Yeah.
Nurturing father figure rewarding to the imagination.
I mean, lay, let's bring that up.
Don't we all identify as figment wishing we had someone that's like encouraging our imagination?
A dream finder.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
A mentor figure.
Whoa.
Do you feel like you found them?
Has anyone found a dream finder?
Big boisterous.
That's interesting.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think identify our dream finders.
Genuinely, somebody you know, Tommy Blutcher, showrunner of Moobim City.
I love him.
He was like this older brother figure to me who took me through this scary experience.
And he doesn't sound like dream finder, but he is a big larger than life boisterous person.
So there's one.
But I do think there might be.
And if I told him that, he'd say, what the fuck is a dream finder?
He'd put me on blast for 10 minutes.
Yeah.
He'd call figment something else.
I love him.
But yeah, I don't know.
I just thought of that right now that there's another identifying quality of like what you relate to as that dream finder.
Someone older than you encouraging.
Because I don't I don't think of figment as like not real.
It's like or a dragon.
I'm just like, oh, yeah, I know figment figment.
He's not a dragon.
Yeah.
Well, he's a figment.
He reads as a kid.
Yeah.
And he's like we're saying dresses up like all these different things.
So yeah, how is he not us?
Which likely I think endeared me as a kid because it's like, well, he's got his own personality.
He's like Mickey Mouse and Bugs Bunny.
Own personality can also be a superhero or an astronaut or whatever.
Like can be a cipher, can be other jobs.
Now, isn't it curious that we do we say childlike and he's a kid.
Yeah.
Even though he is voiced by do I have that at the time of the recording, he was voiced by a 58 year old man.
Of course.
Yeah.
It's kind of weird.
Billy Barty was 58 when Billy Barty the voice of figment.
Wow.
Billy Barty.
He did this at 58.
He is he was a three foot nine inch tall man.
Yeah.
Which I guess there was the calculation.
And I think in that Baxter interview you've talked about somebody was like, well, if there's this quality we're going for, why not like get a little piece?
He's going to be little when I get a little person to do it.
They try.
He said Connie Stevens tried.
They tried a zillion people.
His women, they couldn't figure it out.
But Billy Barty just had that quality inherently.
I think they pitched him up.
Yeah, that's what I was going to ask.
Something's tweaked a little.
Yeah, not a ton, though.
It's like he gets it most of the way there.
Cool.
And a little bit of credits for him.
Billy Barty was let's go back to Sid and Marty Croft.
He is Sigmund from Sigmund and the Sea Monsters.
There's something where he's Rumpelstiltskin.
He was in Mickey Rooney shorts when he was three years old.
That's how he straddles that much like all the way back to old Hollywood like that.
There's some I saw some sketch.
What was it?
Something with him.
There's something with him and Don Knotts on the Donnie Marie show.
I think I've seen that.
We know it already.
He's Gwildor in Masters of the Universe.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
And UHF.
Oh, UHF.
That's right.
What is he in UHF?
He's a film.
He's the camera guy.
Okay.
Oh, gotcha.
So like a guy you've probably seen in things here and there.
What maybe nobody has seen is his own show, which was on maybe Los Angeles local television.
This seems to be a prank show called Short Ribs.
And just so you can get Billy Barty outside of his figment context.
Here's Billy.
Hey, this is Billy Barty and Short Ribs is coming your way.
Hey, Kevin, have a seat.
Oh, hey, that was just fun, boys and girls and ladies and gentlemen.
We're going to have fun on Short Ribs.
Don't you do what we do, right, Kevin?
Right.
And we're going to be doing all kinds of crazy things on Short Ribs.
But we're going to be doing it, not you.
Right, boys and girls?
Right.
So don't forget, Short Ribs, coming your way.
And all kinds of crazy things like, pow!
For the listener, he's with a taller man who he pulls the chair out from under and he falls on the ground and then later hits him.
But that's a…
what a rant.
It's an awful lot of like, do not do.
He does the mildest prank you've ever seen and then says, so we're going to do that, but don't you do it.
And we're going to do it, but when we do it, you don't do it.
So sit there and don't do it while we do it.
Here we go.
I was pretty confused by the end of that.
Extremely.
Yes, I really was.
But you do understand that he's got the juice.
He's got the energy.
That's why they went to.
Oh, yeah.
But I also, watching that, I'm thinking, yeah, he probably would have a worse response than Eric Idle on, do you remember Figment?
I think maybe.
Just like grouchy character actor.
I don't know.
Old Hollywood guy.
You don't think he cares about the magic of the Disney theme parks?
I don't know.
That little fucker.
The power of that curtain.
I just, to this day, I always say I never want to see the Pirates of the Caribbean with the lights on.
Like that is…
Oh, you said this about after the, behind the attraction.
You were like, I don't want to see the stuff.
They show too much.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow, wow.
We got to have the curtain.
You want the mystery still.
Yeah.
But still, watching, there's a great video essay about this.
This is Kai Martin's vids, who does it about all these attractions.
And he always gets the blueprints and usually adds in some animation.
And I'm watching it and I'm like, still doesn't read to me.
This looks like nonsense from above.
I can't square this with my childlike wonder.
There's not a mat.
It just was manifested.
Nobody had to build and think about a layout.
It just was.
It was dreamed up, like out of the Dream Finders mind.
And it makes what, another thing Tony Baxter had said when they went to redo it.
He's like, look, they spend a million dollars to gut it when you're flossing up a…
You don't usually just start spending seven figures still like trash.
What did they spend their entire time?
Like taking out the carousel and redoing the track.
To take out the opening.
Which is where you meet, it's like where any of the heart of it comes from.
That was the first move.
Like, we're all gonna get that out of there.
Which still, like 40 years later, seems like a technological marvel.
Just thinking about like, oh, multiple sets of people are seeing this at slightly different times.
And the only thing in the defense of the removal of it.
And I'm not saying I was for it and I don't like that new ride.
But apparently it did break down all the time.
It was very, very unreliable.
Yeah, I remember some breakdowns.
But like, yeah, I didn't know about that.
And then even when it was like the new one came on board, I would have been like 14, 15.
And I would have been like, oh, it's a Monty Python guy.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, it like takes you out of it almost.
Yeah, yeah.
I've seen him.
He's from Casper.
He's from Life and Brian?
Is he in Casper?
Yeah, right?
He's helping Kathy Moriarty.
He's a bad guy, right?
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Yeah, that's kind of a small part for him.
But whatever.
Anyway, one other thing about Billy Barty.
I'm so excited to read this phrase.
At the same time in 1983, when this opened, he was in the middle of operating a roller rink in Fullerton, California, not just a few miles from Disneyland.
His roller rink was called Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy.
God bless that.
And that's something you could have in the same night popped down to Disneyland and then gone to Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy.
And the other thing about that is it was not just a roller rink, but a concert venue.
And I'm like, I'm looking up like, well, what dumb concerts happened at Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy?
What kind of bands would they book?
Oh, the answer is New Order and Metallica.
New Order and Metallica played there in 82.
Metallica opened for Rat when they're like a new band.
They were like an important early concert.
And then New Order, you can look this up on YouTube.
You can find the full New Order set from Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy.
And the first song is Blue Monday.
They start with the big one, doing it then.
So this Billy Barty's Roller Fantasy was a fully legit new wave ska metal venue.
Like absolutely good.
I hate to call a shot, but that sounds like an episode to me.
Yeah, I mean, I'd agree, except there's almost nothing more.
There's like three flyers.
Unless listeners and again, send us all your Captain Andy stuff.
Send us all your Billy Barty stuff.
If anyone has a dead drop or a cache of Billy Barty's Roller Rink.
Yeah, yeah.
Is that nuts though?
Figma had a roller rink that Metallica played?
But the title of that roller rink makes me take back that maybe he didn't like imagination because.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Because it's fantasy.
You wouldn't put your name on top of, if you had any like, you know, like, like, like, that's sissy stuff.
I don't want to put that word in there.
You would have just said roller rink.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
That's whimsical though, roller fantasy.
Boy, I love it.
That is great.
I was just reading too Barty was sued in small claims court by two of the writers of the canceled comedy television show Short Ribs.
He went to court for short ribs.
Yeah, he lost the cases.
Oh no.
And he said he claimed the lawsuit news was the most publicity he ever got and compared it to similar press that celebrity Jaja Gabor received for slapping in Beverly Hills police officers.
Oh my gosh.
Is that right?
I don't know.
I'm just, yeah.
The best thing you'd ever happen to be.
Sue me again, guys.
He had an interesting career and I don't know that we call the shot on his roller rink, but we call a Billy Barty type shot.
Yeah, there you go.
For sure.
We'll try to find more if we can.
Billy Barty's life, I mean really cool.
Figment seems like maybe that ends up being his legacy, like his main thing in a way.
I'll pitch also you guys doing an episode of all those guys, like the voiceover guys of that era.
Oh, we've talked, yeah.
We're behind on, honestly that's one of the things we thought we would do from the beginning and then we haven't really.
Who comes to your mind though when we.
Oh, now you gotta put me on the spot.
Oh, not on the spot.
You don't have to name them.
Thorol.
I'm blanking on his name, but well, in the Haunted Mansion, he's also.
Paul Fries?
Yeah, yeah.
Because he was also Tony the Tiger, right?
Isn't he the same guy?
That's Thorol Ravenscroft.
He's come up as many times as I can make him come up.
What a cool guy, cool voice, looked crazy.
Yeah, Paul Fries is the ghost host in the Haunted Mansion.
Yeah.
And then how about the VO who did, was it Jack Wilson?
Do you mean the guy, what did he do?
Is he the like voice of the park guy?
Yes.
Jack Wagner.
Wagner, thank you.
Who is the permanent ser sentados, I'm forgetting the first words wrong.
I'm not gonna try.
If you say it fast, nobody knows.
Permanent ser sentados.
Por favor.
Tapos.
Crap.
Ah, you caught me.
Yeah, those are on the list.
I don't know, that is one where we thought we would have done those by now and we haven't.
I don't know.
Do them, Derek's calling.
Do them, do them.
I just think that era is so, I don't want, it just, I wish that still existed.
I like that idea of like, oh, that's the same voice that, I'm not saying it should only
be five actors like working, but I don't know.
I think that era of like these guys could be Tony the Tiger and then also be in the
Disney world.
I just think, I don't know, I'm fascinated by that era of the voiceover world because
I feel like they did so much.
Yes, thousand percent.
I've tried to get like a Billy West episode going because he can do impressions of all
those guys and he's also one of those guys who like, I go, oh my god.
Just need contact info.
I've tried multiple, oh wow.
I have tried.
Who's the way, Derek, you were into the guy, is it the Christmas story voiceover guy?
Who's that?
Gene Shepherd.
Who else is Gene Shepherd?
Or is he, I mean, he's that guy.
Well, he's Carousel of Progress.
Yeah, the redone Carousel of Progress.
Oh, oh god, right.
Wow, wow.
Okay, gotta get to him, gotta get to Carousel.
But the grandfather at the last scene of the current Carousel of Progress is the original.
Oh right, yeah, yeah.
Who's the country singer, Ray, I don't know if you get it.
It's a country singer who's the voice.
Oh god, who is that?
Everything's going out of my mind.
When you got Billy on the brain, when you got Barty on the brain.
I got Billy Barty on the brain.
What can I tell you?
But I also, when you brought that up, but Jeff Bergman is the best voiceover guy.
That's, I think, I played you, this friend of mine does these voices.
Oh, you know, well, he's, wait, he's Bugs, or he has been Bugs.
Yes, oh, you knew his name just by.
I did, yeah, yeah.
Yes, well, we had Eric Bauza on the show who is a current Bugs, and I know, like, sometimes it's him, and so he was going through, he's able to do the, all right, now you're going to do the Bugs.
And now I'll do Mel Blank Bugs.
Now I'll do Jeff Bergman Bugs.
But Jeff Bergman's also, was he Trump in that Trump cartoon?
Yes, yes.
And what, has he been Fred Flintstone?
Fred Flintstone, yeah, Barney.
He's your friend, really, wow, wow.
And Yogi.
Oh, yeah, wow.
Oh, jeez, wow.
He did Drunk History to do the, when we did the Unsolved Mysteries parody.
Oh, right.
So he did, like, the best Robert Stack at I Live, Sank, and I was like.
Wow.
And, but real quick, there was a Drunk History story, I wanted to remember that, we did this episode called Are You Afraid of the Drunk, and it was about the creation of Frankenstein, and there was this one doctor that, I'm blanking on his name, but there's a doctor in the scene, and they were like, what do you want him to wear?
And I was like, well, he should, like, it should be known that he's rich, but he should also be, like, weird.
And I'm like, like a mink stole, like, I don't know, like, I don't want to do taxidermy, somebody wearing, like, a mink coat, but like, what about, and then I just saw it, I was like, a fig mink.
They're like, what?
I was like, okay, it's fig mink, it's face, but it's the body, like, a mink stole, you know, like, they're like, okay, we'll try.
And then they made it, and it was really, really cool, but then Disney was like, you got to, like, take off his eyes, you got to make them have green spots all over them, but I still have them in my closet.
Wow.
You had to defigmentify the fig mink a little bit.
But it never really, you see it, like, for a second in the show anyway, but I think it was my way of saying I would like a fig mink.
Is that not exactly what the Dreamfinder, you took figment from your imagination, you added, like, when he's holding the blocks and the mystery part.
That's right.
Yeah, you tipped it over to Kay, and now it's a fig mink.
Rex Allen.
That's right.
Yeah, Rex Allen is the grandfather in Carousel.
How do we all mess that up?
We'll let everybody do it.
We'll have our info straight when we get to Carousel.
Is this a good time, because you have that item, but you also have, you have another item, which is part of what brings you here for this attraction.
Well, yeah, I mean, I'll just say that I was very, I have been very lucky in my life.
I got to go to a Disney auction, and there was a figment there from the original ride.
Figment nerds believe he was the upside down figment.
In this footage, I can't, it's very hard to see.
I couldn't find it.
I was really, I really wanted to come in.
Same.
Here it is.
Yeah.
Now, I don't think I was scammed.
But there are parts of me sometimes where I'm like, maybe he was outside of the ride to let you know it was under construction.
Either way, an Imagineer made this figment.
And it's figment on a little board looking over.
And yeah, I decided to sell a Shohei Otani card, baseball card.
He's going to give, having trading Otani for a figment.
Like figment will inspire me.
Otani is really cool.
But if I'm going to be able to decide between the two, I'm not going to stare at a baseball card all day.
I don't stare at figment, but knowing like, because it represents art inspiration.
And I just, anyway, I'm making an excuse for why I would spend money.
Awesome.
It's an amazing thing to go for and to get.
I do.
I have a picture of your because it was at the gallery in the Burbank Mall.
This was the Joel McGee collection.
I was so excited to hear that you got it.
And he's like fused into a little block.
So it's just his head and hands.
But if you hold it upside down, that's what I think it was.
Hold the thing upside down.
Yeah.
Hold the image upside down.
Oh, you literally put it on the wall.
Yeah, like there's like, Denny's on the wall.
It's like, why would his hands be up like right now?
Did you like put it in the ceiling?
Originally I was like, that would be so cool.
But I have some people that I don't want touching that.
Okay.
Anyway, I'd say no.
But I have a case that people I like, you touch it.
I was like, you got to feel his fingers.
Like there's a butt upside down on a ceiling is where I would love it.
But I'm just afraid of.
Yeah.
It's also from 1983.
Like he's just hanging on.
That might shatter as soon as anything.
Yeah.
Does it feel that way?
Because you did have to like handle it to put it in the case.
So like.
Yeah.
Well, I got nervous because it came without the, what I learned this week,
the horns of a steer.
Those weren't on when I picked it up and I was like, oh no, oh no.
And I'm like, I can't like, I don't want to mess.
I don't want to mess this up.
This is like, this is my child.
I dropped this.
I'm dead.
This is my inspiration.
Yeah.
It could dissolve in your hand.
It could crack the whole thing.
Like I thought about it.
I was like, whoa, let me just think if someone came in here right now with a baseball bat and cracked it in half,
what would I do?
I know it's just a material item, but what would I do?
And I just, I don't, I don't think I could move.
Like I think it like has repers.
I think it was like, it represents something so strong to me that it's like, I don't know.
It's your rosebud or something like.
Let me ask, because so many, so much mixed media used in this attraction and some materials used in the past,
they didn't know how it would withstand a few decades of time.
Does it stink?
Does it smell?
I did not see that question echoing that way.
It's very funny because it's been since April last year that I have not gained my scent of smell or taste.
Oh no.
Oh my God.
That's a COVID thing.
Right.
COVID thing.
Whoa.
And it's very funny to say that because I'm like, what if it fucking smells?
I would have no idea.
Geez.
That sucks.
I was so, you showed it to me.
I don't think it smelled, but I think it had the case on so I couldn't, at least it stayed basically.
I can smell.
I just can't tell what it is, if that makes sense.
So if there was an odor, I can get it.
I only ask because I've been at like antique stores or comic conventions or collectible shops.
And I'm like, oh, this is really cool.
It's like from such and such year.
And I'm like, this kind of smells and I don't think I want it in my house.
I know there's the good mildew, which is the ET ride.
We know that.
That's the good mildew.
But I remember this guy, Joel, that I got it from, which I also realized this is why he does this.
And I was like, how do you do, why?
We all want to be able to have all these toys.
But then getting rid of them, what my reaction to him made me go, oh, I am very excited to be in his shoes someday because I was near tears.
Saying how much this means to me.
And I was like, where did you keep this?
He's like, oh, in storage spaces like some of this stuff I've never even seen.
Now, that part definitely I didn't like because I was like, all right, that's too much money.
But I guarantee you that thing has been around like crap and rainy storage unit.
But now it was well kept.
But that is a really good question.
I just get a ridge.
I got an original Splash Mountain watch.
Wow.
Or their opening day Splash Mountain.
Oh, yeah, you should.
Would that like where it's like the comic kind of font instead of like the folksy Critter Country font.
But that that wasn't in that that that one might smell.
It is.
You play whatever.
I love that question because we don't think about that when we look at something so.
Perfect in our mind of like this animatronic of Dreamfinder like that mustache glued on probably fucking reeks again.
Oh, you're right.
Yeah.
And then failed fog experiments made like bad shitty old fog soak in a mustache that probably never came out of it.
Well, it covered in lead paint.
How many of those old animatronics had like hydraulic fluid fluid going through?
They had a big open wound.
Now, do we think we have to have this conversation?
But with what I said about Captain Well, we talked about Captain Andy at the top, why they had to shut it down.
Do you think there were too many figments?
Like, how can you take figment off the ride?
I what do you think it was?
I think there was an unfocused.
It will be cooler and the new I think they were trying to shake money out of Kodak and they did, but not enough to do something good.
And I think Kodak in some unfocused manner of like this silly cartoon character is not the modern cutting edge.
Two thousand look Kodak will continue for decades to come.
No problem.
It's going to be a grand twenty first century for Kodak.
And we can't have the face of our thing be this silly cartoon.
I think it was some like odd.
Tony also implied without saying a name, but one of those good little like Tony Baxter shots where he's like this was somebody else's opportunity, the management at the time to prove that they're creative and they could come up with a different thing.
And I don't know if he means I don't think he means Eisner.
I probably maybe like somebody at the parks at that time.
I wouldn't know where to begin.
But I think it was that I think it was some like lame sterile late 90s cartoons aren't cool, which you saw at that time.
So like a cute goes away and earnest goes away.
And then I think we all kind of reclaim it and want it.
But that's my as much as none of that makes any sense.
I think that's why they took them away.
It seems like there were five reasons.
It's politics.
It's the new head of something.
It's sponsor and it's the issues.
Other pavilions that have kept losing sponsors.
So then that would lose a lot of that.
We can't do it again.
Yeah.
They got rid of the thing that tech probably broke down the most.
They did.
And they want to make sure they had some sense that like some kind of probably unfocused like well, Tower of Terror is like a short ride.
And that's how you thrill.
And so we got it.
Are this can't we can't have a big long ride.
Insane, insane that you would cut down by like 35 percent.
They cut down the ride length.
Yeah.
Strangest thing.
Wow.
I'm so glad we're going to mostly put this in its own episode because I thought there'd be some real joy to talking about this.
And I love that.
I love it.
Stink of the new one can will close the door.
That smells culturally.
The new ride smell.
But also, wasn't there another Honey, I shrunk the audience reference that that was another thing.
Yeah, they were kind of linking it all together.
Eric Idle shows up into that.
And then they were trying to link in like flubber.
And then some really old Disney movie computer war tennis shoes.
I think was referenced very right.
That'll get that'll that'll hold them.
The kids, they'll love that computer war tennis shoes.
I'll say this as a 14, 15 year old, I liked all the like shared characters showing up in other attractions.
Yes.
I like that.
And then I like that.
Eventually, Professor Brainerd won the inventor of the year award in the past.
The only thing I like about any of this.
I I don't hate the third version as much as some people where they put a bunch of figments back in.
Yeah, because there's at least a bunch of figments.
But if I look at it in the context of like, oh, and this replaces.
Oh, I despise it.
Yeah, of course.
The fact that you went on it because we didn't go on it when we were down there a couple of months ago.
Oh, yeah, I don't think I would.
I don't think I want to go on this new one ever again.
Figment or no figment.
Yeah, it's just I don't know.
But you're right.
Keep it alive because if you don't go, it's dead.
It's like, all right, it won't be the same.
But we got to make a movie because no one goes there.
That's the only way.
Well, doesn't as of, you know, development things come and go.
The last anybody heard about any of this, Seth Rogan and his company had the rights to a thing.
I have zero clue.
Maybe somebody listening knows where that's at or if it's already not happening.
But that's like, OK, well, there's a name that would, you know, do something cool with it.
Probably a question.
I've seen the question of like figment.
Maybe there's hope for more figment.
Is Dreamfinder dead?
Is Dreamfinder gone forever?
Because I don't know.
I think they can recontextualize like and you could do them with you could do figment with new animation.
It doesn't feel like culturally here in the 2020s that we're after.
Like, why hello there?
Well, we've talked I want it.
That's all I want.
We've talked about the comic a couple of years ago that they put out with Hot Young Dreamfinder.
And it starts in 1901.
I don't know.
I'm not saying we have to use that canon, but I'm just saying if you look, I'll take like Hot Young Dreamfinder.
If that's the option on the table.
Yeah, I think also, too, people always like, you know, fantasize of like, well, they should rebuild Horizons.
They should rebuild it.
And it's like that's never going to happen.
I don't know.
But Horizons is a whole other building.
This they have.
Well, that's what the vehicle is.
That's what I was going to say.
It's like you could reboot this.
Yeah, this hasn't changed much in function, like in in grand schematics.
I mean, it's changed, certainly.
And Image Works taken away is just a DVC club lounge now, I think, upstairs.
Some amount of it, but not as much as it used to be.
But like this and then this was always getting like the rumors were like, oh, it's going to be like Phineas and Fur meat figment and teach about imagination.
I've never heard that in my life.
We're going 10, 15 years ago at this point.
But like Inside Out was floated.
I've got that.
And I've come to really like Inside Out.
It's been on the ass a lot.
I would accept and and figment.
There's a picture of figment in the movie with Bing Bong.
There's a show there.
They hit a little thing.
Easter egg.
So clearly they're like there's thought about tying those things together.
So I'm sorry for although I couldn't find the image.
But it's a figment and Toy Story 4.
Yeah.
Whoa.
I don't know about that one.
Well, yeah, I saw our people seem like real parks people.
Yeah, yeah, definitely.
There's other works references in Inside Out to his mission breakout figment.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, yeah.
You seem in the yeah.
Have you seen him in the Guardians line?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
He's in a cage like Captain Andy's pals.
I frozen like is that the idea that he's frozen?
I don't know.
What is it?
He doesn't know.
You know, I don't think he is frozen because the Guardians are not frozen.
They're things there.
Yeah.
So he's probably in there.
It's just he's being tortured now.
He's just he's got no air.
Zapping him.
Yeah.
Figment is in the Guardians.
Right.
And he's hurt.
Do you guys sorry this feels like I'm on drugs.
I'm not.
But Flight of the Navigator.
This just came in my head.
There's some little critter that's on that spaceship that when you were saying that,
I was like I was picturing this little like it's not a dinosaur.
It's like a little like I just remember like I think I connected that to figment.
Who is that?
You know, I know there's the pole.
You're not talking about the robot or not the robot.
They're talking about this.
There was like a little like this thing.
Yeah.
He's a lot like Captain Eos pals.
That all kind of ties together.
Anyway, sorry.
What is his name?
Do we know his name?
Little critters.
I think we're all prepped for a little critter renaissance.
But do you remember that figment is an alligator face?
It's an alligator mouth with horns as a steer like that.
I never knew until research.
It's an alligator mouth.
Really?
That seems like one of the things where there's so many pieces in the set, which by the way,
hearing Tony Baxter talk about it, there's like stuff they didn't get in there from like running out of time, running out of money.
He's like, I wanted this effect.
Like he was still in 2015 going like, I would redo this part if I could do it again.
Or it's like this would have been even better if this worked 100 percent.
He's like, why did they not just update this put in the digital age?
Because all these things could have been done with current projection and instead of just ripping it out coldly.
I really cannot find the name of this critter.
It's OK.
I just was like, oh, I think all the critters like you're saying look the same.
There is a real style of critter.
All these mid 80s things.
Goblins.
I feel like we're sort of like on the way up.
But do we want to shout out anything else like in terms of that stuff, like the details to note in this, anything where it's like we'd be remiss if we didn't talk about this or that in this thread.
Oh, gosh.
There's so much.
Like the song itself, you're saying like I didn't I didn't realize that.
I guess I've heard that.
But like, yeah, he's got like a horns of a steer eyes, two tiny wings eyes.
But wait, do I?
Oh, wait, I have a spirit.
Let's just but but but what would what fellow what is it?
But a lovable fellow.
Yeah, thank you.
Thank you.
Eyes big and yellow.
Horns of a steer.
But a lovable fellow.
From head to tail.
He's royal purple pigment.
And there you got a figment of figment of imagination.
I feel like they're trying not quite.
I'll throw in a dash of childish delight.
Oh, geez.
I feel like they're trying to tell you like, yeah, look, he may look like he's a demon from hell, but don't worry about it.
He's friendly.
He's nice because they're saying he's got the horns of his dear, but I the level.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, worry that the but is I think.
Yeah, I think but is the the word but in there means like, yeah, he's got horns, but don't worry.
Yeah, he's good.
He's fine.
He's not a he's not the devil.
He's not the devil.
Not a freak.
Don't throw sodas at him.
Yeah.
But things do get scary.
Not sure.
I'm playing clips.
I did I have zero memory of the scary mystery part, and this is a this is nuts.
This part.
Yeah, I loved it.
I love that.
Yeah, killer.
They say in this ride and blood.
It's an organ.
But again, it's it's not keys.
It's letters.
It's like a typewriter.
Right.
Yeah, that's a hell of a piece.
That's really cool.
And then everything you pass.
So figment with the blocks, the change cat to bat, the raven.
There's scary animation.
That's like the Tony like Claude Coats influence, which is the one I think I'm saying, but like Snow White Scary Adventure.
But even like when you're up going up the hill on Splash Mountain, you're like, it's scary.
Like, he's making sure he's got a little little piece in there that's scary, because that is a fun I think of being a kid and conquering something that feels scary.
And then you're out and then you're out and then it feels like you account like it really feels like you did something there.
Like you really went through something if there was a little period of like extreme uncomfortableness.
Sure.
Why are the bats there at the end of the pirates?
I always was like, why are you there?
At the Pirates ride?
Yeah, the end of the pirates.
Like those are bats.
Perfectly about the bats.
Well, I'm just thinking about your point like the like surviving something.
I was like, yeah, but then the ride's over.
Like, I guess you get a little like.
Well, Pirates has a weird.
You're talking about Disneyland Pirates.
Right.
Because like space outro.
Because yeah, the whole thing's on fire.
The pirates have like destroyed the town.
And then you're like you're getting in the middle of a gunfight, but it still feels like you're going so slow.
Right.
And you're going up.
It just feels like you're really easing back into reality versus like, oh, my God, we got out.
So there's like scary elements after the town has been burned down.
But I feel like they didn't.
Well, what's the is it the Paris one that like the drop is at the end?
I think so.
Yeah.
Because like the correct tone, the corrected corrected, quote unquote, like the problem in the sense that like, well, the end should probably be the drop.
But this one wasn't scary until just there.
I think that's the middle of the ride.
Yeah.
This wasn't like the climax.
And then this is where it goes to him, like in a little dressing room in a Toxin Dales.
A brand new show.
Showman champ.
I did.
I did think of you.
I was like you took the words out of my mouth.
This must have been adjacent to the idea of like putting out like a little vaudeville.
Putting on a show.
Yeah.
In Epcot and especially in MGM studios, they were like, it's time to put on a show.
Show must go on.
Time to put on a show.
Tales and Top Hats.
It's kind of the only it's like we're all the sweetness.
Yeah.
The thing that they ripped out especially like the the birth of figment moment and the whimsical machine.
They took out the only like real kid lightness in original Epcot, I think.
Yeah.
And it's also they took like I mean the ride's still there but like they took out and I forget I'm going to put this in the like shittiest way because I can't remember exactly what people were saying.
But they're like all the other things we were trying to teach people about.
We also wanted to have something that said like, well, this is like imagination where all of that stuff comes from.
Like the imagination pavilion is where we kind of try to explain to people that we cannot have any inventions without somebody coming up with something in a creative way.
So then you got that and then the whole thing is kind of lost because you get like the engine of it is gone.
It's like it sucks.
Kind of like cynical 90s like sarcasm.
Yes, exactly.
For that like really unpleasant like era that we talk about where it was like, yeah, this is out of date.
Ten years later.
The only spaceship Earth there.
So I guess it doesn't matter anymore.
But at the time it's like, oh yeah, that's kind of like lesson number one for explaining how like somebody comes up with an idea or somebody comes up with inventions and stuff and learns about science.
Whatever they have.
They have a theory.
They have an idea.
And now that's all gone.
That's done.
So it's like the park is never truly.
If this are we calling this the heart of Epcot Center?
Especially after I heard that.
It hasn't had its heart since 1998.
Yes, that's what I thought now.
I think so too.
And I was just thinking like do you like Figment is the logo, the mascot in my head.
Yeah.
Of the park.
But who is the mascot?
And would that have been a problem that Mickey was, you know, like that there's a different mascot at Epcot than there is.
Would that be?
I don't know.
I'm very confused why you get rid of someone so likeable and loved.
They tried to make them all live together.
You can find art of like here's Mickey and Minnie and Figment all as equals hanging out.
And then you wouldn't buy mouse ears.
Right.
At Epcot you would buy a Figment hat where is like beak is the brim.
Those are cool as hell.
I'd like to know those.
And I feel like it encountered what is now a very modern problem, which is like it's not making money hand over fist immediately.
Like it's not making like Avengers in-game opening weekend, you know, midnight.
Like it so quickly they seemed like they got very insecure at Epcot.
I mean, you have the living seas.
But how quickly do you like, all right, put a bunch of Sega games and Barbie in there.
Stupid children.
These children are stupid when we need their money.
And then Figment's like everyone's imagining.
It's working.
Children are smart.
The only thing in their defense is that Epcot did cost a ton of money and it didn't do well at all.
And the rest of the company was right before Eisner.
Like and the movies aren't good.
That's a real part of the magic too.
Looking at like these nice little Figment animated pieces that are from 83, a totally dark time for the company where the animated films aren't good.
And the feature other than like drawn is cool.
Everything like it's a weird grim time.
And then through it all, like the one, the beacon of light is Figment.
Yes.
And he's still like they're still trying to have their cake and eat it too.
Because like all the popcorn buckets they sell and people go nuts for it.
Yeah.
And they just had like debuted a new character spot where you take photos with them and people going nuts for it.
Like and he keeps falling.
Has he stopped falling down?
I mean, those are so.
There was a famous poll.
It's been more than once.
Did it have more than once?
Yeah.
I don't think they got it.
They work on the eyes.
He's not meant to be tall.
It's weird.
He's really tall.
He reminds me, you know, part of me last night going like, where do I think it also?
I was like, Jeffrey, Toys R Us.
I was like, there was a little bit of Jeffrey in or vice versa.
Right.
We've never done that.
We never talked about Jeffrey.
Oh, we have not talked about Jeffrey.
We need that.
Yeah.
The there's a restored like right through and like all around Pavilion and they get some of Walk Around Dream Finder and Puppet Figment.
There's a he's doing a really funny bit where Figment keeps knocking kids hats off.
Like he just keeps biting onto the hat and throwing it away.
And everyone's having so much fun.
One day we haven't said Ron Schneider.
Who is the one in the park?
Yeah.
Walk around Dream Finder.
Right.
For a lot of stuff.
Yes.
Who had to.
So he's doing the walk around and doing the puppeting and they who did not Figment would not talk.
That was one confusing when he was out on the do a ventriloquist thing.
There was some specific calculation of why that's maybe the only bad thing about that.
There's a great clip on the Today Show of Brian Gumbel talking to Dream Finder and Figment.
And it is weird that Figment's not saying anything.
Yeah.
Brian's just like, oh, well, what do you do?
Oh, you have imagination here.
Well, what about your friend here?
But he also says he's my right hand man.
And he's on his left.
And I guess he forgot they had to move over for the camera.
That's either an oversight or a great joke.
Yeah, that's a good point.
A little more clearly.
If they really want to get people excited, I feel like this is a Figment costume, but like bringing back the puppeted.
Dream Finder and just do it.
They have the small things.
They do like baby Groot and stuff.
I'm like, that is the ultimate if he's just a smaller like little puppet character.
And you go up next to a table and they're doing like Zootopia stuff.
Like, have you seen that thing they wheeled out on stage for Zootopia?
They have a like character.
I don't know if it's a puppet, though.
There's a character that can kind of climb up.
It's a free roaming animatronic.
Yeah, it's really wild.
Now, I don't know if they're going to put the money into Figment for that.
But still, they have little things you can take pictures with.
I would love to do parkour.
I want Figment.
I would love Figment to do parkour.
They should have like a spot to like Mickey's a magician and you go in and you meet him in his dressing room before the show.
Wow, I would love that.
You know, I just thought, you know, I think Dreamcatcher and Figment are just Walt and Mickey.
Like, I know that they had said like Dream Finder had like Walt inspiration.
It's impossible for any character there not to.
But I'm like, oh, it's that relationship that it's like, I don't know.
The creator and the creation.
Yeah, like really has got the spirit and the childlike wonder.
And then, yeah, if we could bring it back, all it takes is as long as they're making money.
I hate we hate the reality of that.
Yeah, it's like if that's not making money, they have to get rid of it.
And that really bums me out.
What do we do?
Is there a way to keep Dream Finder and not have to meld it into Inside Out?
Like, no, I mean, just the way the company is.
I will accept an inside out.
I like inside out.
I think the spirit does combine with Figment decently.
I'm not against that, but I would miss at least just have can Dream Finder be outside?
He doesn't need to.
I don't need a flying machine back.
I know that's hard to do, but can he be outside?
And then if Figment needs to go meet anger and sadness in the ride, that's OK.
I like them.
Yeah, they should they should pony up for the real cast like they didn't do for the movie.
But the sequel and Figment said, Bing Bong to hell.
Like, not every idea is a good idea.
You've been outgrown.
There's an idea of fire.
I don't know.
I don't know why they don't do more like photo op stuff that's like a little bit more like elevated, like a Halloween Horror Nights maze.
Just like give me like a little rainbow tunnel that leads to just a kind of a dream, whatever catcher, whatever the name of his vehicle is with a guy and a puppet.
Like I just like that doesn't feel like it would cost more than I'm going to say 50 grand.
I don't know what it technically cost to build anything.
But add a damn hashtag above dream, you know, like have just do the dumb wings that people get their picture.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Like you would be I don't know.
Just it makes me so sad knowing there's so much unused space in there.
Yeah, that is a big empty box that waiting.
Yeah, yes.
That still looks as good as it did.
It is like I it's not it hasn't been decimated like other Epcot things.
It's breaking Dreamfinder and the original figments heart that they have.
Yes.
Imagine what I don't know.
They just we got to trade them.
We trade what they taught us.
Right.
I know.
We got to bring them back.
This is like 50th down the list of things they need that they're like on the internal list.
I bet of stuff Disney needs to do.
This is so far down the list.
It's just making me sad about it.
They keep it.
They'll do these D23s.
They were like they're trying to hurt our feelings.
They're going.
They'll say like and it makes us think about what's going to happen tomorrow.
And then they tell us nothing about Tomorrowland.
And then like we just took sakes a little bit of imagination.
Right.
Never go nuts.
Yes.
Well, we got a new character suit.
There's a new suit we bought for figment.
And you're like, no, we wanted to ride.
Right.
Yeah.
They know that's that's the twisted thing about all of this is they know exactly what that crowd wants.
And then they will they will give them the just the littlest crumb.
And the people there are excited and they want to be excited because it's fun to be in a big room like that with talking about something like.
But then it's out about the crumb.
Everybody lines up for six hours for a few.
I've been in these rooms and you get worked up in a lather by these charismatic, handsome people that do these presentations.
And yes, you want to cheer for things that people say on stage, even if after the fact you come out of a haze and you're like, wait a minute, that wasn't.
What was that?
Oh, we got a suit.
There's a new suit for figment.
That wasn't a ride.
So like you want to be there.
They're having fun in the moment.
But yes, it's if you're watching on a live stream, you go, fuck.
This sucks.
Come on.
You weren't there.
Yeah.
I don't.
Derek, do you are you then cynical about the idea?
Do you think this is just going to will they just operate this cruddy version of the ride or will they close it?
Or do you hold on to any hope of the possibility that they they fix what's wrong?
I always have hope.
And I think it's always who is running the company at the time.
And all I can say is that we should pray for the next one in line grew up when we did.
Oh, interesting.
Like, I really think that would be the way it's going to happen.
Unfortunately, it's like someone else has this.
A lot of people have the same nostalgia.
We do.
Just hopefully the next one in line is like, yeah.
This is why it's important for things to age down and for not for all of our leaders and cultural leaders and big figures to all be 70 years old and older.
Yeah.
So that we just get somebody of a couple generations down who knows it's important to bring back Figmen.
No, it's always got to be very old politicians.
Bob Iger's got to come back.
Disney, John Stewart's got to come back to the Daily Show.
Everything old is new again.
Old is the new.
What about Jason being the CEO of Disney?
Oh, Jason for CEO.
Start peeling out the floorboards.
Oh, you want to make some money?
Well, let's sell some of this copper wire in the walls.
We don't need all this.
How many activist investors would be coming at you in the first six months of your tenure?
Nelson Peltz.
I wondered when you'd show up.
You're dressed as the dream finder in the boardroom meeting.
That's my CEO.
Oh, hello there.
Would you like a generic seltzer?
We've gotten off name brands here.
We're buying both at Costco.
We put the money back into the park.
Jason is the cheapest CEO Disney ever had.
He's like, we have to save a dollar.
Don't you understand?
Do you want imagination back or do you not?
You're on the stage.
I've got to do a shift in the park.
I'm helping out.
I'm being Dreamfinder and the Figmen puppet.
There's just humans on the ride acting now.
No robots.
It's cheaper, you see.
And I'm flying southwest.
I walk the walk and talk the talk.
Until the boys build me a dream machine to fly where I need to be, I'll go in a plane.
Look, hey, don't lose hope in imagination, Scott.
Dreamfinder and Figmen want you to hold on to it.
You're right.
And that's probably the easiest for Derek to remember because you get to see our pal every day if you want to.
And have you been inspired by him?
Do you look in those yellow eyes and feel like you're in a Contra Dreams?
Oh, yeah.
And I'm also defending the question.
So what the fuck is that?
Well, amen.
That's our whole lives as theme park fans, isn't it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
It's that thing that like, yeah, he inspires me.
I'm, you know, also was thinking like when we're talking about Figmen, I get in my head a lot of going like, all right, so we saw that at a specific age.
There is something at Epcot right now that is hitting that same age for someone, you know?
And so that's what I really hope for is that if it's not Figmen, there's something there that's hitting childhood imagination to like that.
That is so educational and crucial to people like us that you're you you kind of know about it.
But I don't I don't feel like it's embraced of like, what?
What did you just say?
Like the worst thing you can ever hear as an adult or a child is like, where do you come up with this stuff?
Fuck you.
My imagination and creativity is sometimes looked down upon, you know, and I think that's for any enjoyment in like a conservative world of like, hey, look at these things that can happen if you use your brain and not just like, you know, or I should say using your heart over your brain.
I just I just think there's so much to figment and more than we know why we like it that it allowed us to feel like, oh, to be creative and to yeah, to be accepted.
I think there's a lot.
Yeah, like I think maybe Tim Burton was talking about kids.
I've said this before on the show where kids like second graders or first graders will say something like, I'm not good at drawing, which in hindsight, I remember the kids would always say that in school.
I'm not good at drawing.
You're like, wait a minute.
Those are first graders.
Of course, you're not good at drawing.
Like, yeah, yeah.
You're like, like, there's already a roadblock for certain kids as far as arts are concerned.
Yeah.
And it is probably pretty important to have things because if they're not getting a support from family or whatever, it's good to have some things in the world like that where you're like, you just be creative.
There's no you don't have to be self-conscious about it.
But I remember that all the time because like I like to draw and I was okay at it.
And then kids would be like, oh, you're good at drawing.
I'm not.
And I remember being like, yes, that's correct.
I am good and you're not.
But like not in a weird way.
I just remember like, well, obviously, like I'm the one who's good at drawing.
But we're in second or third grade.
Yeah.
And I wasn't that good at drawing.
But in hindsight, you're like, oh, that is bizarre.
That is a really weird roadblock that kids have in their mind.
I'm sure it's about any creative thing, music or whatever.
Wow.
So we got to tap into this.
I mean, it makes me now I'm like, how can I reflect this into into my kid?
Sure.
I watched it like let him just because they're boy.
Yeah, you see it every day.
There's this there's this imaginative spirit that is so strong that doesn't have confines.
Yeah.
It yet.
And that's good.
I'm not going to use that mean voice like you use, Derek.
Say, what do you want to come up with that?
That's what we want to be.
Voice.
You say you your character.
Yeah, you portrayed a person who was like judgmental of creativity.
Oh, no, no, no.
Yeah.
I also think taking your son on the ride would be good for both of you
because that's what he's going to remember.
Sure.
And it will change your feeling on not liking it because he's going to see something that you didn't, you know, and be like, oh, wow.
I like my figment to that.
You know, yeah, it's true.
Well, you got to get if you can't have the perfect figment, you got to go with the figment you have.
Completely agree.
And then when he's 16, 17, you sit him down, you have the talking.
So, you know, that ride you like the ride is not as good as it used to be.
I know you like it.
I'm not a father.
I have to show you this pruder film of the old ride and you'll never get to experience this.
Oh, geez.
That's the talk.
We'll gear up for it.
That's the big talk.
It is so nice to just deal with the good times and everything you everything broader you tied it into.
Derek is wonderful.
I'm very happy to say Derek Waters, you survived podcast, the ride.
I'm so excited.
Man, I want the I want the shirt to have you the photo that we can offer a shirt, the photo you can't buy.
We should do like if we need to like set up the photo booth or something.
I know so much stuff we should have done in the making the best content.
That's all you have to do.
Thank you.
That's so nice.
You've made a lot of wonderful content yourself.
Let's go to the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Oh, just this show.
I'm good.
I mean, yeah, I know I don't have anything to plug yet.
Hopefully soon.
Just pitching shows.
Yeah, on the way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That creative imagination has been wandering.
And a couple of sparks got a goddamn bonfire going on over here.
Hey, well, actually not the fire.
Just a bunch of sparks.
But that's what we know.
What now?
What that turns into?
That's the light.
Yeah.
Oh, boy.
Well, can't wait for the fruits of the for it to become the bonfire.
And as for us, you could find us on the socials at podcast.
The ride merch is available in our tea public store for three bonus episodes every month.
Check out podcast.
The ride the second gate or get one more bonus episode on our VIP to your club three.
You'll find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride and Derek.
Hey, when you go home tonight, just if you see figment, just say say Mike Scott and Jason say hi.
I will.
And then you guys come over and tell me if he smells like shit.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.