Five, four, three, two, one.
Listeners, will you be our valentines here on this special Valentine's Day, very romantic
podcast, the ride the second gate.
I'm Scott Gardner.
There's my Carlson.
I am feeling very romantic right now.
I just want to warn everyone.
Oh yes, the amorousness.
Well, hold on, amorous.
Wait a minute.
Wait, hang on.
Now I crossed the line with amorousness, Jason Sheridan.
Let's get more into this amorousness.
That's what I'm saying, brother.
What is the major difference between romantic and amorousness in your mind?
Oh, romantic is flowers and a nice meal and looking nicely at each other while you eat.
That's not amorousness.
A feeling of love or fondness.
Fondness is crossing the line.
Fondness is where we get a little R-rated.
Fondness is where you get amorous.
Fondness leads to horniness, leads to intercourse.
Romantic is fine, but fondness.
We're not comfortable with being fond.
You looked at some sort of Christian website that defined what that means.
Amorous in my mind means a little bit more.
Desire.
Yeah, don't you think that's what amorous means?
I am looking at this is vocabulary.
com.
Yes, Christian.
The skewed slant of the smutty slant of vocabulary.
com.
I guess the ride is for lovers.
Yeah, no, I'm romantic.
I just mean, you know, I prominently display my April O'Neill figure, you know, for 24 hours.
And then after that, I put her back sort of in the action scene that she's already been a part of,
where she's driving the turtle van.
This is a real thing.
Did you move April O'Neill?
I did not move April O'Neill.
You give her, on Valentine's Day, you give her a chance to shine solo.
Well, not even shine.
Sometimes when you have your figures, some of them are in sort of a diorama situation,
and then some of them are just sort of standing there displayed prominently.
So I guess she is having a time to shine in this fake scenario I've created.
OK, OK.
Which I do not do.
I do not take my female figures out for Valentine's Day and prominently display them.
Valentine's Day.
Come on out, girls.
Mimi LeFou from Bucky O'Hare.
Come on out.
I got to look up Mimi LeFou.
I think I may have said her word.
Mimi LeFou.
Is it LeFou or LeFou?
LeFou.
I'm getting it confused now.
Let's see.
I'm going to need some autocorrect to help me out.
Mimi LeFou.
LeFou, OK.
I mean, it's especially funny is that one of the first pictures is her looking all mad.
Yeah.
With massive hulking, I would say pretty manly hands.
Sure.
Well, she's a military woman.
She's got to be tough.
So yeah, she's she's coming out for Valentine's Day.
She's going to be standing there.
All the different ladies.
It's kind of a look.
I understand.
If you're if you're feeling at all amorous about this particular not amorous, not amorous,
romantic.
And then that's fine.
That's fine.
Romantic.
Having romantic feelings about Mimi LeFou.
Yeah.
Me me my me me.
I call her.
I mean, I got to look up.
All right.
What's the definition of romantic?
Then amorous to me just seems like it means more on the horny area than romantic necessarily
does.
All right.
I will admit that Miriam Webster says about amorous strongly moved by love and especially
sexual love.
Yeah, of course.
So I guess Miriam Webster is backing.
Thank you, Miriam.
I'll just play Miriam.
My Miriam Webster.
Miriam Webster, who is, of course, a female dictionary, beautiful lady.
Hello, Miriam.
Miriam.
Teach me your words, Miriam.
I don't pay attention to that dash.
I don't get in the name.
I know it's one beautiful lady.
This is Miriam Webster.
Hot for teacher.
Odd for vocab teacher.
Or that means the same thing as amorous as well.
Romantic is the only thing that's always fine.
That's right.
Sex is not part of romantic whatsoever.
Sex is not part of romance.
Never.
That's right.
All right.
Well, we're off to as weird of a start as you could guess for this kind of love-themed thing.
And what we're doing here today, this is a topic that didn't make it in the Club 3 poll
due to the Griffin Newman masked magician blockade.
Results of that coming soon to Club 3.
But it's Valentine's Day.
I think usually episodes don't drop on Valentine's Day.
Seemed like a good chance to just seize this, take a romantic opportunity.
Thank you.
To not be amorous to our listeners.
And talk about tunnels of love.
I think we've been talking about this for a little while.
I feel like it's been on the mental shortlist.
And I think it came up in an episode a while back.
Because I think just as a starting point, just to get us all on the same page,
I feel like when you hear tunnels of love, there's something,
I think we can all conjure in our heads a mental image of this.
Yeah.
It is probably something that we've seen in some media.
And I think we can determine that it is a boat ride.
Perhaps the boat is a swan, the most romantic animal.
Not usually?
That's what I found.
Well, hang on.
But he's saying my hypothetical thoughts.
Like when you just flash to knee jerk, when you conjure a tunnel of love.
That's what I like pictures.
It's from a cartoon or a sitcom or something.
And maybe you're in a swan.
And you're going through arches that are shaped like hearts.
And that there's lots of, and Tosin, anything else
that you guys see in the hypothetical of this.
But it's cupids, and they're firing arrows.
And maybe some cupids are making eyes at each other.
And the cupids are in this.
Love is style.
Love is, sure.
It's very love is.
I'm a strip of love is, yeah.
But obviously tons of hearts and maybe big puckered lips.
And I think a Greek Roman sort of thing.
Like tunics, perhaps.
Yeah, definitely tunics.
Yeah, yeah.
A romantic time.
And then probably in like, I think columns are probably part of it as well.
That's in keeping with it.
And maybe like scrolls, which are very romantic.
Like a big scroll you passed under that says be mine might be in this.
And then definitely lattices.
The most romantic surface or wall.
You got some boring concrete wall wood to get out of here.
But the criss-crossing of the white wood.
Yeah.
That, like the criss-crossing of bodies in a relationship.
Maybe that's why lattices are sort of romantic.
I hadn't thought of that, but you're right.
Yeah.
I figured it out.
This is, yeah, this is the popular consciousness.
The existence of the tunnel of love has lived on.
Even though by the later 20th century, most of them gone or flipped.
This was my question.
And I think that this, I'm sure this came up in an episode and I don't remember which one.
But my thought was we've all seen something like this portrayed on some show.
I don't know if we can even say exactly what the, what show that was.
That was a question I had.
Where do I have this image?
But I think we all have it.
We're like, okay, at some point in time, there were these rides.
And these were rides for lovers.
And if you broke away from your chaperones, from your parents or your deadbeat, deadweight,
third wheel friends, and you got a little pucker up time on the tunnel of love,
that could seal the deal for this relationship.
Or in a very sitcom-y way, make two people who hate each other.
They're forced together on the tunnel of love.
They come out smooching.
And I think it occurred to me, what is, was this ever,
has there ever actually been one of these in the world?
That was the question.
Or is this fully a contrivance of pop culture?
That was my question.
And this is what we thought we would explore here in this episode.
because you look into this a little bit.
There's been articles about it.
It's mentioned here and there.
So that's just the thesis here.
Let's tackle this notion.
And did these ever exist?
Do they ever exist?
And I'll ask the listener right away, if anyone listening to this,
have you ever been on something that you think is this?
The most, and I don't know, anything else to say about hypothetically what you think?
Because the other thing that's in my head is they're all eight to 20 minutes long.
How could a room possibly be so romantic?
Maybe it's pulsing like a heart would be, or other body tunnels.
The image in pop culture is so romantic,
versus what I learned was the reality.
And I'm sure you guys came across.
So let's dig in then.
We all have this picture, but what is the reality of this?
Do you want to take us through some of what you figured out?
Well, just broad strokes.
I was starting to say, by the later 20th century,
a lot of these are, in reality, are gone or flipped to other rides.
The discovery of the other name of Tunnel of Love,
which we've come across before, namely, I think, of Kennywood, the Old Mill.
If you saw a ride named Old Mill, same concept as Tunnel of Love.
There used to be an Old Mill at Coney Island, various other places.
The other name I came across was Mill Chute,
which is basically a tunnel of love that ends with a splashdown.
And that's kind of like a combo.
Sort of a Proto-Flume-Red-Splash Mountain kind of thing.
A chute.
A Mill Chute.
Yeah, a Mill Chute.
So a little less romantic.
Well, yeah.
It seems like the reality here, when you start Googling this,
what you get into is the Tunnel of Love is perhaps less literally
this small world length and scale celebration of the general feeling of romance.
It's maybe less that you enter the Google image search for Valentine's clip art.
That's what I've always imagined it to be.
And more of a functional type of ride title.
Then I think what you're alluding to.
Tunnel of Love.
It's a type of ride.
It's a type of ride, and most importantly, it is pitch black or nearly black.
This is a very early 1900s sort of idea.
This is like a very early theme park.
And into way pre-Disneyland.
Theming is probably not to the extent that it would be later.
But yeah, that very Coney Island early days sort of thing.
Combined with that old mill.
So the basis of Tunnel of Love in that functional way, are we saying,
is like a slow moving dark tunnel ride where probably you are alone.
You're in a vehicle built for two as opposed to a Pirates of the Caribbean, a boat for 40.
I'm not doing any smooching on the Pirates of the Caribbean personally.
Probably.
I'm not going to roll it out.
Jason, have you ever smooched on pirates?
Like a little like, you know, a quick kiss.
What rides have you pecked on?
That's a question.
Which part of Pirates do you think?
Do you think before the drop?
That's interesting.
Those caves are kind of like haunting and a little moody and romantic.
So before you go back in time or whatever, when you're seeing the skeletons, that's when you pecked?
Or pre-skeleton.
Or post-cave pre-skeleton.
That's when you're still getting the momentum though from the drop.
But we're talking about California, of course.
If not, if we're talking about Florida.
It's pretty dark before, yeah, the bayou just gets me in the mood.
The old man in the old, yeah.
The old man on the rocking chair.
One old man staring at me.
Single banjo string being strummed and Jason's ready to go.
One, when I had forgotten, when I was down in Florida, Disney World, like in the last few years,
I forgot that that old man is also, you can see it from the river boot.
They did put that little scene, it's just kind of in the corner.
Oh, okay.
I guess I didn't realize that.
It's also on the Rivers of America or whatever else.
Yeah, which is sort of bigger but more boring in Florida.
Is it called something, the way everything's called something more boring in Magic Kingdom,
is it called, is it there, is it called like Rivers of Dick Irvine or something?
Dick Irvine Presents, Rivers of America.
It's one of those little things, I hate it.
I hate it because it's the boat.
Yeah, what are the examples of it?
Admiral Joe Fallot, boo, hey, dumb name, Mark Twain's cool.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm trying to think of other examples of that.
Or it's like slightly, well that's not slightly different, that's different.
It's the boat, the boat's on the Seven Seas Lagoon.
One of those is called something really boring.
Yeah.
It's just named after some guy.
Well, let's do, let's do, uh,
The Richard F.
Ermingham.
Let's do Disneyland Disney World versus two.
And we'll really have a bunch of ammo now.
We'll hit that point.
Well, if we do it with Mitch again, I'm sure he'll care.
I think we will have.
But don't you think it's just, it's these executive names and that's just a little
less enchanting, wouldn't you say?
Well, we'll see what he has.
Fuck you.
Very concerned about enchantment levels, yeah.
That's enchantment levels is something to consider with this ride genre as well.
I think they're, they call, they start calling these things tunnels of love in a functional
setting and also it seems to come from, all right, if you're like, on a long boat ride
with just you and a partner, then this maybe allows you some privacy and a chance to do some,
I don't know if this is a too harsh of a phrase, canoodling.
Some canoodling because public displays of affection were so frowned upon in the late
1800s, early 1900s.
long.
Not as long, you know, in a room, it's open-ended.
You have to decide how long you go into the room.
Yeah.
How much you do in the room.
Right.
But in a boat ride, you just, you have a limited amount of time.
It's like seven minutes in heaven.
You really should probably plan it out ahead of time because you, such a short amount of time.
You have to talk through it.
Yeah, you might want to have a game plan.
Yeah, you may have been on completely different pages about what's going to go on in there.
Yes, so here, I'm going to, some of this is from, this is a mental floss article that
proposes the same question.
That's like, why, so was there ever really a tunnel of love?
And they get into some of this.
That Old Mill rides gained popularity at a time when unchaperoned dates between young
people were still viewed as risque.
I mean, that time, I think continued to the 2000s for me, I would say.
I don't think suddenly my parents are not psyched on unchaperoned dates.
I had a particularly Catholic upbringing.
The 1910s were no different for me.
But anyway, what's weird about, I think the disconnect here for me is that they start
calling things tunnels of love because of the reputation, because of what you get up to
in the ride.
But so many of the actual rides that existed were scary.
It's caves, like pirates, like we're saying.
It's caverns.
And maybe all the way up to this Old Mill, there's nothing romantic about that other
than that you're in the dark.
Well, hold on, Jason, when you're talking about an Old Mill.
Well, there's a certain charm to an Old Mill.
The romance of times gone by and the nostalgic feeling.
And the never ceasing nature of the mill.
That's right.
No matter what's going on in the world, no matter what war we're in, the buckets keep
flowing.
That's right.
The Old Mill, Jason gets that feeling when he's on the Knott's log ride.
It's kind of an Old Mill, right?
Are there people that are sawing?
Yeah, they're sawing in there.
They're howling.
Yeah, so that's similar.
Yeah, there's young love blossoming at that, you know, with the big party where somebody's
dancing on a log or whatever.
Yeah.
So that's all in the aftermath of a mill.
But what I'm saying is some of the types of ride, when you start looking into it, this
ride was a tunnel of love.
What do you mean?
That is a scary ride.
Right.
That doesn't make any sense.
But apparently, this article goes on.
This is actually an article quoting a 1950 article that's talking about scary rides and
how they're opportunities for romance.
Research has shown, let me do more 50s.
Research has shown that the snarls, howls, and groans of the hideous sights along the
way, while palpably phony, will cause the female to precipitate herself into the male's
arms, the 1950 article reads.
Her fright is usually as phony as the hazards of the course, but it serves a useful purpose.
Women are liars.
I get it.
That's what they're saying.
They're lying about their fear.
I wasn't around then.
I don't know.
Maybe all women were liars.
I wasn't alive.
I can't vouch for 50s.
You know, distraction and lies to that.
There was no desire.
Women did not experience desire until the last 20 years.
Well, that's what they're saying.
They were.
But they had to hide.
They had to couch their desire.
Maybe that's true.
I mean, it's true on some level.
You had to trick them.
You had to use other, you know, like if I'm going to pull on their heartstrings, I need
to activate their fear strings.
That's right.
When you pass by a goblin while palpably phony, perhaps even if her phoniness, but you know,
she needs some excuse to want to jump into my arms here in this tunnel of.
This is something I would give the young people a tip about.
Take them to Six Flags Fright Fest and take them in the sewer of souls.
Because as soon as your lady or your man or whoever, they see that big pile of shit,
they're going right into your arms.
They're going to get freaked out and they're going right in there.
And then you're going to get a smooch.
You're going to get a couple smooches while you're walking through the sewer of souls.
You know, you need that aphrodisiac to kickstart the relationship.
How about a big pile of shit?
Hey, Betsy, I want to take you out tonight.
We're going to a place called Fright Fest.
You're my best gal and I want you to experience the greatest fear that Six Flags has to offer.
I took the night off from my job also working at Fright Fest.
Me being a 15 year old in Valencia, of course, and you as well.
Put on your best poodle skirt because you're going to need your legs to walk
through the sewer of souls.
That's accurate.
There's still there's still poodle skirts, but the poodles are styled like Harley Quinn.
That's the difference in Valencia today.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a poodle Quinn.
It's like a Harley Quinn match up with the poodle.
It's a little twisted, but it's, you know, it's still tasteful.
So yeah, this this is always something that was portrayed, especially I feel like in like
and this again, this is just these are these are in my mind, like AI cobbled memories in
the same way that like AI tries to put together something that it thinks is what you want.
Like my brain does that.
I just think imagine a Happy Days episode where they were seeing a movie, a sci fi movie
and like Richie had like his gal in there and she got scared because there was a big
role, but I don't know if that ever happened in Happy Days, but that's what my brain wants
to remember.
Yeah, it's in something like that.
All things are from a kind of collective pop culture.
Yeah, it's mushing it all together.
Right.
Have you guys had a situation like this where like you went to a scary thing
and then your gal ended up in your arms?
Gosh, that's a good question.
I feel like that is true.
That is a true thing that is in my brain, but I can't remember it.
All I'm remembering is now that I'm in Happy Days and I'm wearing Richie Cunningham's sweater,
but that didn't happen.
I'm trying to remember because it does feel familiar to me.
Yeah, right.
That's where you'll end up.
That's the dream is that I was hanging out with Potsy and Ralph Melph and.
Permanent Happy Days is yours.
What awaits you in the great beyond?
Heaven is Happy Days.
Just being at Arnold's and hanging out with the fellas.
Yeah, I think it did.
There's nothing so memorable.
I don't think it was anything where it was like, boy, I like I'd like to get a hug from this girl.
And oh, it did because it was a movie and she got scared.
I don't think it was anything like that.
It was probably like I was in a long term relationship and oh, they got scared and they
like kind of hugged me or something.
It wasn't anything dramatic.
One of the biggest like an important early handhold for me was during a movie,
which both parents were present for.
And this was the movie.
What a romantic film.
A.
I.
Steven Spielberg's A.
Which worked out for me.
I don't know if the handhold happened due to like fear.
I don't know if it was the flesh fair is scary.
So we held hands.
But I remember that like held on and then like a handhold started.
I'd like this.
OK, well, this is great.
I'm not letting go, even though like the law you hold hands for a long time.
It becomes like, yeah, it's a long film.
Well, yeah, and that's what this is.
This is the rare film that essentially has like a fourth act.
So I was happy, but also probably losing feeling in my hand as I realized like, oh,
this is no adendum.
You were squeezing.
I didn't want to leave.
I had to cling on.
This might be my only chance here.
Like making marks in her hand.
Oh, it cut the skin.
She bled.
We had to go to the hospital afterward.
Incredibly sad end of a movie, too, to be like holding hands with a girl you like.
And he's like the robot boy is fine.
Really, it's all about like a false.
It's all if it's a false A.
I.
simulacrum of love.
Yeah.
That's the best that he can get from some aliens who scanned his memory.
A weird and recreated.
Yeah.
But hey, if it was endless, I would have been fine with me.
Do you have any memory of anything like this or like ride romance in general?
Well, Mike, we know you had a failed attempt at this.
Yeah, no, it's the saddest, most pathetic things on a couple levels.
If you're if you've if you've subscribed to the right level on this Patreon,
you know what we're talking about.
I think most scandalous jaw dropping.
I never said it was scandals or jaw dropping.
I just want to make that clear to the audience.
Mike's disgusting, amorous stories.
If they feel let down, it's not I didn't say it was.
It was a bit.
It was a built up story.
Well, I know it was built up, but it was actually it was accidentally built up, I think.
Mm hmm.
It was a runaway build up and it's not got away from it got away from me.
Yeah.
No, I don't think there's anything other than that, really.
That's close to I was puked on by a girl.
Oh, no, no, I was puked on by a girl.
I was puked on while a girl.
You paid for that.
I was on a Tilted World with a girl I liked,
but then a guy who was also on the Tilted World puked all over me.
I have said this before, I think.
Nice.
So that's like really humiliating.
Like I was there's a ton of there was like five of the five kids on.
It was like sixth grade or something.
And we were all on and the girl I liked was probably on the left side.
And I was on the right side.
And then right next to me was this kid, Adam.
And he had had a big brownie and a big like coke
right before getting on the Tilted World.
And in the middle of the Tilted World, he's he's trying to like flag the part.
Like I'm going to throw up, I'm going to throw up.
And I'm like he's got like yell, I'm like yelling.
He's going to throw up.
And the guy, the car and he didn't care.
Didn't affect him.
No, he didn't care.
That's also too many people for a standard Tilted World car.
You should have split that party up.
Yeah, I mean, we fit.
It was fine.
But Jason's worried about say,
do you think the car and he was worried about overloaded?
No, I see.
That's where my mind go.
And I'm like, well, if you had gone two and three,
you would have enjoyed the experience more.
It's more optimal Tilted World.
I think it's fun to be packed in there a little bit.
I suppose.
With your kids.
But it's not fun when the kid throws up all over you.
And it's like you have nowhere to I know where to go, though.
So I crammed in this corner.
So and all that was the only person.
I was the only person who got it either.
Like everybody else was not covered in puke.
So I was covered in puke.
And that was a little bit embarrassing,
but that was not romantic.
Brownie and a big Coke right before a fun ride.
This Adam was your Jason.
Some people some people can't handle it.
I am sure I could have had a Brownie and a big Coke and been fine.
I could have had it on the ride while we were going.
So I don't know what his problem.
Yeah, that sounds like my idea of heaven.
We were talking about heaven earlier.
Brownie Coke Tilt-A-Whirl.
Nice.
Your heaven is an infinite Tilt-A-Whirl.
Never stops when you die.
You're just on it.
And ladies, please don't bother me.
I'm enjoying a ride.
I'll be off in three minutes and then we can engage.
But the theme song, the Happy Days is playing loudly
while the Tilt-A-Whirl is happening.
Of course.
Distortively.
And Ponzi's giving me a thumbs up and he's got the windbreaker on,
not the leather jacket.
For season Ponzi's there.
OK, all right.
But if it's a carnival, it's probably a knockoff.
Greaser.
Oh, yeah.
His name is Greaser Guy.
That's true.
Well, Jason specifically wanted the non-iconic Ponzi.
Yeah.
That is a weird request.
People don't remember.
Ponzi didn't start with a leather jacket, of course.
It's like wanting a…
I got a painting of Kramer.
That one note, kind of before the hair went up.
And when he just entered a door normally.
Yeah.
If looking kind of frazzled.
He opens the door slowly and goes, hello.
Yeah.
Hello, Jerry.
Jerry, are you home?
OK, so anyway, in this functional…
OK, so this ride starts to become known.
This type of ride becomes known as the Tunnel of Love.
And this old mill in Kennywood, that's called out as an example of it.
Though it was never called the Tunnel of Love.
That fully was called the old mill.
Here's an anecdote that's in that article,
I think also in the Funkland video about that ride.
But we're saying here that this type of ride,
people get up to some business on this thing.
How are we going to stop that?
Maybe camera technology wasn't what they needed it to be at that time.
with plastic bats and told them to whack any bare buttocks
that were visible in the boats.
Yeah, I was trying to figure out the mechanics of that.
Like, so you're…
You've got to reach in.
You're getting…
The bat, I understand, but I'm imagining the couple.
I'm like, wait, so…
Huh, OK.
If one is turned around and straddling the other,
or forgive the hoarseness, it's second gate.
If one is getting a standing up blowjob.
So what, you're standing up on the boat?
One partner is sitting and the other has stood up.
Let us assume…
The barest buttocks that are the most like,
right there to be smacked by a plastic bat.
Let us assume the style of the dog and…
My darling.
Too doggy?
Hey!
A rocky, by the way, boat.
Partly, I think why these took a little while were just like,
well, the length of this ride is dependent on the speed of the water pushing the boats.
And every time they launch a new boat, it'll give you a little oomph.
I hate to even bring…
I hate to even say this.
No, no, no, this is the time.
It's an amorous episode.
What if you're into like, bat play?
What if you're into…
Exactly where I was heading.
Yeah, what if…
If you have a particular thing and you've heard that there's something…
You live in Pennsylvania and you've heard that there is a place where if you…
All you have to do is bare your bare buttocks and a man will,
free of charge, other than cost of admission, hit you with a plastic bat.
Oh no!
What are you doing?
Don't hit me!
I paid for this ride fair and square.
I did not want to get hit by that plastic bat.
That is something that Wall Street guys pay 10 grand for on the weekends.
That's not a joke.
That's what happens.
You could go get it from an anonymous stranger.
An underpaid teenager.
Right.
You could even not have a woman or a man with you in the boat.
Absolutely.
You could just be…
Pull your pants down.
You just get out.
You start doing…
You get naked and start doing push-ups in that boat.
And then by surprise, you try to not memorize the parts so that it still comes as a surprise.
And then at some point, hopefully in success, you got a bat hitting your butt.
Yeah, or you just drop your pants and start wiggling it around while you're on the boat.
Wiggle, wiggle.
I hope nobody hits me.
Again, not the most stable platform.
I hope I don't fall in the water after I've been hit on the bottom.
Some of the risk of it.
The only concern would be that you were standing up and you were erect and you would fall over.
Because that could be a problem.
That's the only concern I can see from the situation.
So you got to be careful in that regard.
Your balance is all thrown off.
All your blood rush.
Well, that's true too, because that could really weight you down or you don't know,
depending on the weight of it.
I apologize again.
They factor that into the…
Because there's weight limits on these.
But have they factored in that…
I guess you don't weigh more.
Well, I don't know.
They say that when you die, there's an amount of weight that leaves your body.
So I don't know if there's some sort of
mythical amount of weight that goes into your body when you are aroused.
I'm not sure.
Well, you know, you sense sometimes, depending on who's on what side of a boat on a boat,
sometimes it can kind of be tipped in one way or the other.
I wonder if they factored into this the possibility of somebody getting an erection,
thus the weight being distributed differently.
I guess the boat tip with the right boner.
In the old days, they…
No.
They were not prepared for it.
But these days, if there was a new tunnel of construction, they have no choice.
Computers these days would have to calculate that.
They would have to understand that that was a possible…
Before they have to do with slide rules and spreadsheets.
He had to do it old-fashioned way.
Yeah, yeah.
He had to change on the fly.
They just threw me into the water.
I'd never…
I didn't go to school for physics and I had no idea how to calculate for a boner.
Learning trigonometry to count.
What happens through an erection on a boat?
Oh, this…
Oh, Kenny Wood, this is terrible.
I'm not going on this ride ever again.
I didn't come here to be whacked on my buttocks.
This is crazy.
This idea to stop people from being amorous on the way…
Hey, come on out!
You would hit them with a bat?
That's the only way.
Certainly you couldn't go, hey.
You can't just say, stop it.
I can see you.
We're gonna do…
You gotta…
It's gotta be a physical…
And this is a time…
I guess, like, this is a time where…
You know, look, Inside the Magic is a website and a Twitter account that exists to make it seem like
things like this are happening at Disneyland 12 times a day.
They frame any little thing as if a customer smacked on bare buttocks on boat ride.
And then you look into it and like, I don't know, like a fly landed on their butt,
which counts as a smack.
Man had her actor terrorizing guests doing the knockout game.
What is the knockout game?
Oh, the knockout game was a thing like 10 years ago that people were gassed up about
the right-wing lunatics stuff.
Like, if you go into the city, there will be gangs of youth and they will be betting that like,
all right, go knock that guy out.
Like…
So it'd be like you would just be walking along the street and someone would run up
and try to knock you out quickly and somebody would be filming it.
Yes, right, Jason?
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
I always feel like it's adjacent to bum fights or something like a weird…
Something like that.
I don't know, like a CD is the word.
But like, like, unpleasant video trend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, but like if the…
Yeah, in reality, then you click on it and the mad hatter like slightly tripped a tiny bit.
Apologized profusely.
Kind of like scuffed the hair of a child and like, yeah, he pantomimed how sorry he was.
And then of course that article also gives you like,
theme parks a bit of tradition in this country for many years.
Six paragraphs of it.
Walt Disney, why he came to California with a dream.
You get the history of everything.
It goes back to the Big Bang before they could tell you
what this clickbait is actually about.
Now, speaking of Walt Disney, is that…
Is it possible?
Like he always was like, oh, carnivals are so dirty and nasty.
Like, did he get ripped off on a carnival game once?
And then someone told him a story about the bare bottom bats.
I was going to say, did he get hit on his bare bottom once?
Oh, maybe.
Yeah, I don't know that he was doing anything.
Hopefully he wasn't doing anything on too hard.
But maybe they accidentally thought his pants were down
and they hit him on his bare bottom.
Well, his dream, per the carousel story,
is a place where the whole family can have fun together.
But maybe his dream before he had a family was
a place where you can make a family together.
A boat ride with privacy so your wife and you can
flush out your family ranks.
Do you think that woman who worked on his polo injury every day
had a bat and would use it on his bare bottom?
All right, Walt, you want to play Kenny Wood?
I think yes.
I think the answer is yes.
OK, but so that's an example.
But again, this is all accidental, the notion that these are tunnels of love.
Right.
Until the Park Palisades Park in New Jersey, just like, all right, well,
let's just get up for it.
Let's do a clickbait of a title, shall we?
Let's call it the Tunnel of Love.
And as far as I know, that might be the first one called Tunnel.
That was actually called Tunnel of Love.
Let's just appeal to this instinct in the audience.
This is maybe a place where people, but again, and then I think there's one
in Coney Island in Luna Park that they call Tunnels of Love, multiple.
But none of these are still what I'm after.
None of them are like the big Cupid festival because a lot of them have monsters and stalactites.
And it's not what I want.
I want the like what was shown to me in a 40s comic strip.
Well, that I there is one that online gets posted a lot as like the original Tunnel of Love.
And it's had the Minnesota State Fair and it's called Ye Old Mill.
So not exactly romantic.
It is still operational.
I think the same family ran it for decades.
And then finally, in recent years, did sell it to the fair.
But it is funny to watch because there are dark stretches, but then they'll be like
a scene in a display window with trolls.
A lot of times it's trolls.
A lot of times.
And I, my dad, I was, I mentioned, look, reading stuff about this and he's like,
I think there was one at Dorney Park, which is the eponymous mill shoot for many years
called Mill Shoot.
And then in the 50s or 60s, it flipped to Journey to the Center of the Earth.
And kind of, you know, originally a lot of scenes from the book, big monsters.
Then at some point it got a facelift and was a little more whimsical.
And then I think closed in 1992 around the time when Cedar Fair bought Dorney Park.
There's a great video on this channel called Storybook Amusement, a newer channel that
I like a lot.
But was there, did this Dorney Park one have any cupids or swans?
Right, was it?
No, it was like a dark boat ride and then it had a splashdown.
Okay.
A lift hill and a splashdown.
This is what's disappointing to me.
I'm never getting to what I want because then I started thinking like, okay, where
are the portrayals of this actually?
And what helped in this search was the website TV Tropes.
Tunnel of Love comes up in enough things that it is considered a TV trope.
And let me quote them because they're thinking the same thing we are.
This type of ride is rare to find nowadays in any real life amusement park, having started
to go extinct in the 1960s, but it was once very common.
Most riders today likely have no familiarity with the ride, but the trope was used in so
many pieces of media as a device for creating romantic tension that several generations
have grown up familiar with the idea without ever experiencing one in person.
It does feel like one of those things that like somebody, it was done on one of the first
sitcoms in the 50s.
Right.
And then when it was, by the time it's done in the 80s, that's just referencing the,
that's just a rider who grew up on sitcoms and there was never this.
I have another thing like this that I have a theory about.
I included this in Saturday Morning All Star Hits, the show I did with Kyle Mooney.
The notion of the bachelor auction.
This is something in almost every sitcom.
That like, and then, and, uh, you gotta, you gotta be in the big bachelor auction, right?
And then maybe that it's tense because that splits up a couple or it allows the like crazy
weird girl to bid on the hunk.
Yeah.
And now they're together and they wouldn't be other than.
I, I feel like I've seen that on Lucy and Modern Family.
Yes.
I have an old spectrum.
I could, that could be wrong.
Every single, every TGIF, every save by the bell.
Now listeners count up how many bachelor auctions you've participated in, bid in,
uh, and, and attended.
Let's all imagine the bevy of bachelor auctions that have, uh, it's, it's, you know,
it's left there every weekend.
I'm weighing which of the many bachelor auctions in town I'm going to go to.
We are always invited to the theme park media bachelor auctions.
It's the three of us, Jim Hill and Testa.
And, and everyone bids on.
Coming out fresh baked Disney.
Ooh, oh, yes.
He's got a new cat on and everyone's.
Oh, a red and pink cabbie hat.
That's right.
It's different every, yeah.
So we were always being asked.
$50,000.
We're always being asked to help.
There's young upstart Braden.
Look at him from Mickey Speaks.
I forget what it was.
That's right.
You said there's a new guy.
I like Braden.
People were saying Braden is bad opinions and I I'll be honest.
I was, I did not look into it.
And I'm not too many too busy to look into.
How plugged in can you be?
Some of his opinions.
Yeah.
But how much do you think Braden would fetch a bachelor at the theme park media bachelor?
He seems to be younger than all the other guys I just mentioned.
So I may be more.
I don't know.
The median age of the male theme park journalist is.
The young upstarts in our late thirties.
We're the young guns at this point.
Yeah.
Not enough sitcoms and stuff use actual community events that I have seen and gone to a number
of times in my life.
Pancake breakfast and spaghetti dinners.
Whoa.
How many spaghetti dinners?
I have more pancake breakfast.
Okay.
All right.
Cause I do know what that is.
I remember that from being a kid, but I do not remember spaghetti dinners.
And that was something you go to like at a school or a community center.
Yeah.
It would be like a fundraiser because it's
Or like chicken.
There's a version of it.
I think popular in upstate New York.
There's like.
Chicken desserts for one night a year.
You mix it up.
Chicken pot pie.
You get like a styrofoam container at spaghetti dinners.
You get a plate of spaghetti and salad and a slice of pie or whatever.
And it's like five bucks because you can make that in giant bulk quantities.
And it costs like nothing.
in your pockets so you can keep getting in line over and over.
You can buy as many spaghetti dinners as you want.
Yeah.
Well, you can wrap your body in spaghetti if you have a big coat on.
Sure.
And no one will notice.
So just wrap your.
Oh, that's, no, that's very efficient.
Just line yourself.
With spaghetti.
Yeah.
Just string up each hack, string up each noodle.
So when you take your big coat off and you get home, you have a big spaghetti suit on basically.
Just get out of your, just, just have a kiddie pool ready on the floor when you
get back to your living room.
Yeah.
Let me ask you this.
Cause one thing that people at various jobs in the past, I would see this and I would get so confused.
If you were bringing leftover spaghetti and sauce to work for lunch.
Go ahead.
What would you put it in?
What would I put?
Like Tupperware, right?
Like Gladware?
Put it in?
I saw multiple people over the years bring a Ziploc bag of spaghetti and sauce.
I'd be like, that is very confusing to me.
I guess you could store, I mean, you do store things in Ziplocs, I guess.
I mean.
It's a little weird.
That puts the onus on the workplace to have a bowl, a big bowl to be able to, and maybe a
little cereal bowl is not going to do it.
We always had bowls and plates at the places.
So I think, yeah, you're working on the assumption that the kitchen will be stocked.
It makes it seem grosser, but technically it's really no different than just having
a Tupperware.
Right?
Yeah, that's what I was.
But it's not really.
It's not.
It just looks worse.
It looks weird, but there's no real like the separation between the plastic.
Different is happening.
Yeah.
It just looks worse.
Just don't put the bag in the microwave.
That's all.
Don't put the, yeah.
Do not microwave the bag.
Okay.
So yeah, I don't know.
So you want bag sauce?
Have I ever seen a bag of loose spaghetti and sauce?
Probably.
Check the Forever Dog fridge.
But it didn't make an impression on me like it did Jason.
Or I think you're haunted perhaps.
If you were with your sweetheart and you saw a bag of loose spaghetti and sauce,
you would go right into her arms out of fear.
Yeah, yeah, I would.
That's your jump scare.
That's what I mean.
Exactly.
Okay.
So here's my point.
Before we get into like real, may possibly real examples of this thing,
I started to think like, well, with the help of TV tropes,
where did this actually come from?
Where did I see this in anything?
And just to shout out a couple, it seems like a lot of cartoons,
more recent cartoons, Rugrats, Hey Arnold, Captain Planet apparently had a ton of love
at some point.
I think it might really go back to, as a lot of things do,
so much is defined by like the early Disney and Warner Brothers.
And of course, Pepe Le Pew's going into some tunnels of love.
You know that.
And then one I remember very clearly,
uh, it's called Donald Double Trouble.
It's a Donald and Daisy short in which she is nagging him so much that the
nagging becomes abstract.
And it's just like, and he's got a winter over, but Donald is so annoying and abrasive.
And then on the street, he bumps into an exact double of himself.
He's like, oh yes, all right, be there at six.
And then he gets it like, well, what if I can temporarily use this guy to date
Daisy?
I will introduce a third.
Self-quack?
So I will duck-cuck to, in order to get the ball rolling again, but then I will roll right in
and Daisy, who is dumb, will not know the difference.
Right, right.
But it goes too far because this new Donald is so hot.
Well, he's better than regular Donald.
Great voice.
And this all culminates in a tunnel of love.
Here is, this is a point of view of Donald seeing like, how could this have gone so far?
This is false Donald you're looking at right here.
Right.
Buying a 25 cent ticket to the tunnel of love.
It says, bring your sweethearts on it.
And it goes into like a big cave, which is very, I do think Coney Island is a big,
because the Coney Island one was like a big fake rock cave.
Right, right.
So I think that defined what this is for a lot of people.
And this is also, this is very scandalous because this goes against Donald's race specific
instructions.
Not double underlined, the tunnel of love double underlined.
Anything but that signed Don.
Casual Donald is just Don Duck.
I never think of him as Don Duck.
If you see him in the park, say Don.
This short, like this and Mr.
Duck, just side note, Mr.
Duck steps out.
Like these, I really enjoy these old shorts.
Yeah, they really got cookin'.
I think, you know, they get, look, Steamboat Willie can, that can stay in public domain.
They really picked up steam.
I think the best Disney stuff might be 40s, 50s.
Because that's when you get like that now Chip and Dale are in the picture.
It took them a long time, I think, for the Simpsons fully fleshed out secondary cast.
Yeah, sure.
To really be cookin'.
I think you get that in the, and of course the goofy sports cartoons and all that.
Yeah, but Donald, yeah, Donald in like his little suit and his straw hat and stuff.
Yeah.
So that's one, a lot, what often happens in these is that, you know, they don't show you.
It's like kids, we're not gonna take you under the tunnel.
We can't show you what's in there.
Which is why I still don't understand.
I'm like, what was in a tunnel of love?
They wouldn't show us.
And what usually happens in both Pepe Le Pew and several Disney cartoons,
and the Archie gang, this happened to Archie and Betty and Veronica where it's so dark in there.
Oh yeah.
You start smoochin' and not as a panel.
Yeah, I was gonna say.
You don't even know who you were smoochin'.
Yes.
Yeah, you wanna read that?
Archie, whew, I love the taste of your new lipstick, Veronica.
Veronica, Archie, I'm not wearing any lipstick.
And then in the back row, because some of these ride vehicles did have multiple rows,
there is just like a very amorous Betty.
Yeah, so he was, I don't know how he didn't know that he was leaning over to the other row.
And what was Veronica doing the whole time?
Yeah, right.
Just sitting and enjoying, just like having a moment of peace, Veronica's all right.
She's like me, she's watching the show scenes.
Right, but if it was not dark then.
Good craftsmanship on that troll.
But if it wasn't dark, how would she not, you know what I mean?
It would have to be pitch black for her not to notice what was happening.
Yeah, then what she, yeah, you're right.
That's the only way this works is pitch black, so what is she doing?
That's why I think just like, maybe taking a nap.
Betty is like over, like her foot is in the water.
Yeah.
Jason, you recently said that you didn't realize on apps that people were maybe dating more than one person at a time.
How do you feel now in hindsight though about Archie seemingly dating Betty and Veronica
at the same time for decades?
Well, you know, I follow at least one or two Instagram accounts that are just out of context panels from Archie,
and that is a bawdy comic going back many decades.
Oh, sure, of course.
I'm just saying though, so you sort of chalked it up to almost like a smut-like amount,
like a smut-ish comic versus a normal real life situation.
I think this is a review.
We never finish Riverdale, but I think towards the end of Riverdale,
there is like, you know, some mention of like, oh, Archie and Jughead and Betty and Veronica are in a polycule.
Oh, Jughead's not involved?
Oh, in the show, in the show.
Yeah, because Jughead's a hunk in the show.
Right, Jughead in the comics, I think kind of asexual, even though-
Yeah, mostly sexually attracted to hamburgers and like big chocolate malts.
Even though he is, Ethel is his girlfriend in the comics, I believe.
I think.
Midge is with Big Moose?
No, Midge is with Moose.
Scott, do you have a read Archie?
Did you ever read Archie?
It's one of those things, we bump into this a lot, where you guys have the shared reference,
of course, Midge is with Big Moose.
I have never heard these names.
Dilton Doily, ever heard of him?
The nerd?
Dilton is a menace in Riverdale.
I have not watched Riverdale, it's not because they're blasphemous with the mythology or anything.
I'm not that upset about it.
Multiple cult storylines, I feel like.
They're trying stuff, they want to keep their brand alive, I get it.
They're serial killers.
Yeah, that's not what I grew up with as far as the wholesome nature of these Archie comics.
You want malts.
They cheated on malts by not making the show entirely about malts.
Pops Chocolate Shop, of course.
Pops is pretty good in Riverdale.
In the show Riverdale.
In the show Riverdale, Josie and the Pussycats sing the Khalees song,
Meltshake on top of Pops at one point, that's pretty funny.
I can't be mad at that.
I just wanted to say, when you read that, did you just say, oh this is fantasy,
there never would be a man dating two women at once, or three when Cheryl Blossom came along.
Yes, fantasy.
Comics, you get to live out, what if I could fly, what if I could date a blonde end of black haired woman.
Can I ask, were you more interested in Betty or Veronica?
That's a great question.
I think Betty.
I would have said Betty when I was younger, but now that I'm older I think I would say Veronica.
Yeah, I think I would say Veronica now.
I don't know why.
Betty's kind of the girl next door, Veronica's a little posh, you know.
A little posh?
Are you kidding me?
Well, daddy.
Of course, Mr.
Lodge is of course there and he's always upset with her, but her dating Archie,
but yeah, I don't know why that is.
I don't know why I've switched now to Veronica my old age.
Scott's laughing, do you have an opinion?
I'm looking, I'm trying to make, I think I'm Veronica.
I'm Veronica.
Okay, maybe it's just dark hair, I don't know.
Sure.
I don't know, Lindsay's got dark hair, I don't know, maybe that's what it is.
Or it's just that Veronica's very rich and I'd be like, oh man, we could have a big house.
That, they, the Ed Brubaker, Sean Phillips comic criminal did the storyline,
Last of the Innocents where different scenes were done in different comic styles.
And Archie is, essentially the Archie stand-in is married to Veronica and he's very depressed.
He's very rich, but he's very depressed.
She's mean to him.
And he goes back to the hometown and he falls back in love with Betty.
Sure, sure.
Well, that's probably, yeah.
I mean, it depends, it depends who's writing the strip or the comic to how mean Veronica is.
But sometimes she's not that mean, so maybe it wouldn't be so bad.
Can I choose Redhead Pussycat instead?
Oh yeah, okay.
Can I veer off?
You can put her in there, yeah.
What's her name?
Well, is that Cheryl Blossom or is that someone else?
No, not in the Pussycats, I forget the names of the Pussycats, I apologize.
Yeah, me too.
Look at, look at, there's three of them.
Fun movie.
I feel like people look back very fondly on that movie.
You don't want Midge or Ethel?
Big Ethel?
I believe, I think Josie is the, that's the name we're looking for is Josie.
Okay.
I didn't know that.
They were not, I did not read that comic.
There's been a lot of interpretations over the years.
Yeah, Ethel Muggs is the name of the character Jason and I were just talking about, just in
case you needed to know her last name.
Midge was always drawn as very cute.
Sure, nothing wrong with Midge.
All right, so, you know, one, just one other iteration of this.
There is a tunnel of love referenced in the, the famous Dick Van Dyke episode of Scooby
Doo.
Oh, interesting.
You don't see it in which Dick Van Dyke is running a carnival and doing all of the jobs,
but they, spoiler, the gang ends up inheriting the carnival from Dick Van Dyke, which seems
like a burden to them more than anything.
Yeah, really.
But they refer that, what's your name?
Speaking of other attractive cartoon characters, not Velma.
Daphne.
She's going to be in charge of the tunnel of love.
And then Velma says, and maybe somebody will take me on a ride on it.
It provokes a fan moment.
I was always a Velma kid for sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course.
That was no question.
But anyways, all of the, if it exists in all these forms, if the cartoons of the 40s through
the 60s are rife with this premise, they must have existed somewhere, right?
So I have a couple examples of what I think may have been actual tunnels of love that
are in this mold that we want.
One is in somewhere called Riverview Park, Chicago.
You ever heard of this?
I think this was gone before.
I looked at it, yeah.
Before our time.
But got a couple photos here.
Look, like I said, a big scroll.
A scroll, it says tunnel of love.
And then there's a bunch of flowers.
And this couple is going through a big, really cheap look in a heart.
And they're looking at each other fondly.
And they have privacy other than the camera.
It's just the two of them.
So maybe this one Chicago park actually was this.
This seems pretty what we're talking about.
And clearly a lot of opportunity for amorousness.
Because the only other photo I could find, no one documented any of these.
Maybe because of the darkness.
But look at this.
A boat with three rows all with sailors or other types of armed forces all making out with their gals.
Jason, it's Fleet Week.
At ease, boys.
Yeah, mind your business.
Mind your business.
Stay in your row.
Don't worry what's going on in other rows.
This is what I'm like, the only way that this tunnel of love thing is viable is if you were by yourself.
Because there's no way, no offense, guys.
I don't want to get in a boat ride with three rows.
And we all make out with our gals together.
I agree with you.
But that is not necessarily how everyone feels.
As far as needing complete privacy to do things like that.
This is another trope in TV and movies where with cars.
There's two couples.
Yes, in a car.
Front row, one couple gets the front bench seat and the one couple gets the back bench seat.
Right, right.
Never this.
Madness.
How good of friends do you have to be?
Or maybe not good of friends.
Maybe you got to barely know the people.
If I'm like kind of friends with anybody in the back.
This is the whole thing with people if they go to like an orgy party where you're go, I don't understand.
An orgy party, Michael.
Orgy gathering.
They go to one of those orgy parties.
They go to one of those orgies.
Those orgy celebrations.
You know, the one thing I saw mentioned is like one of the downfalls tunnels of love, unshaperooned dates, public displays of affection were more socially accepted.
Keep rolling.
You gave us a little shaperoon.
It sounds like macaroon.
Sorry, sorry.
The other thing I'm surprised I didn't see mentioned the rise of car culture.
You know, just more and more cars gives you privacy.
You've got a private ride out to wherever you want to go.
But is that also like movies and TV have rotted my brain?
Just thinking about like the scenes in Greece.
Where people are making out and like implied fucking in cars.
I bet that's real.
I think that's probably real.
That I think there is truth to.
Sorry, that people had sex in cars?
But you're still, I think it's real.
I think that, you know what, I'm going to go with that.
I think people did have sex in cars.
Did.
Yes, did.
Never.
Although you know what?
I came home two apartments ago.
I came home one day.
I was like midnight or one in the morning from a bar.
And I parked the car on this, it was kind of a hilly street.
And I definitely parked and I went, what's that?
Oh, there's two people having sex right in front of this.
Me and this car.
The windows are fogged up right by the Gelson's, most Felice.
That's a block over really.
So I was like, wow, it's happening.
The thing I've only heard about in Greece.
I guess it is a reality.
I've done a thing in a car.
Whoa.
Come on.
Get out of here.
Get out of here, you guys.
Details.
No, you don't want to know that.
But that's, you get a little, like once or twice, like a little bit, you know?
This was later.
All right, I'm going to go for it with a gross story.
Go for it, yeah.
Not really, but I don't know.
Okay.
I was, I was over 18, so my parents kind of couldn't really say much anymore.
And there was a scenario where I was heading out and I was going to pick up my girlfriend at that time.
And just, my dad just like caught the back seat and that all the seats were down.
And he's like, oh, you forgot that something, well, he figured out like maybe Scott's going to go do something here.
But here's the other thing.
Wait, sorry, sorry, was that prior to you leaving?
I still lived at home, but it was kind of at a point.
He was, it was this parent turning another, turning a blind eye situation.
I see, okay.
But here's, see, it was just clear what I was heading off to do.
Sure.
And bust my dad at this moveable case.
What?
He hopes, he hopes.
Wait a minute, I hate to do this.
Wait, so before you left, you moved the seats down?
Yes.
That's wild.
Or they were just down already.
That's wild that before you left, you're like, I got to get it ready.
Let's get this done.
Wow, okay.
That is what I was.
All right.
Also, there was like, there was a blanket back there.
So you really prepped before?
I prepped a little zone in my Jeep Grand Cherokee.
That is so funny.
So it was kind of undeniable.
But here's what was also, I also had not cleaned out the other things in my car.
And as a prop for a little movie I was making at the time, there was a plastic, or not a plastic, I guess a rubber glove back there.
And that was just like a prop for a robot costume is what it was.
And my dad looked back there with concern.
I felt very awkward.
What is he going to say?
And then he takes the glove and he meant it.
He 100% meant it.
He comes back to me with the glove and says, well, don't use this.
Meaning?
My dad thought I was so dumb that I was going to use a rubber glove as a condom.
There is a Maury clip I saw on the internet the other day where it's like, the condom broke so we used a rubber glove.
And I know I'm not the father.
And he was not.
It's funny you say that because I feel like the sexual health weeks at college, they were always encouraging like latex gloves.
What?
No.
What are you talking about?
For like health, for like sanitary.
But not for sexual activity.
Not for like, for like your hand.
They were always talking about rubber gloves and dental dams.
Okay, dental dams.
I've never seen one in the wild.
The dental dams, sure.
I've heard this plenty of times.
The worst experience.
Apologies to Louie.
We do need to put a warning on this one.
It's like it's a Doughboy's episode or something all of a sudden.
Yeah.
I think they were also trying to be considerate of heterosexual and different homosexual combinations.
But it was the early 2000s and people were pretty clumsy about that, you know.
Uh huh.
Oh God.
Oh, everybody keeps saying things that make me want to ask ten questions, but I know that this is no, we have to be done.
It's okay.
We can veer out of here.
Let's just veer, maybe all of it was a mistake.
Maybe all of it.
Take me back to the Archie days.
Is there one question you can't get rid of?
No, I can get rid of all of them I think if I try harder.
Alright, let's get rid of all of them.
Let's veer out of here.
What I was going to say is that I, okay, so I do think that maybe Riverview Park had a real tunnel of love.
And then I'm like, what's up with Riverview Park other than that though?
Their slogan was, laugh your troubles away.
And then right under, in this article, like, well they went by the fun phrase, laugh your troubles away.
Then right after that, at least 16 patrons died in Riverview Park between 1910 and 1967.
Most were on roller coasters.
Also, most were due to their own negligence.
This is not why the park closed.
The reason why the park closed is believed to be due to rising crime and racial tension in the area.
Oh my God.
Laugh your troubles away at Riverview Park.
How worth it is this Riverview.
So, alright, I think everybody, so maybe there was a tunnel of love, but everybody got robbed on it and also fell out of it of their own volition.
Oh my God.
This is a nightmare.
This one's bad.
Not good.
The thing I learned about early, early days of Dorney Park is that Solomon Dorney opened it up.
And before that it was mostly a fish hatchery and then eventually he opened the trout ponds for guests to fish.
Okay.
They use me a lot more trout ponds than roller coasters.
Now we're back to what we do here.
That's what podcast the ride is all about, trout ponds.
Podcasts about hatcheries.
The simple pleasures.
And dating apps where you're monogamous.
The simple pleasures of life.
They added a roller coaster which at the time was simply called Coaster.
Okay.
That's it.
I don't hate that.
That's better than some of the long titles we get these days.
The early days of the Philadelphia Toboggan Company.
I'm going to go from coaster to a much more complicated name.
And this is where, again, listeners, if I'm wrong, if you know for a fact that there's something was a tunnel of love in the way that I picture it with swans, the most romantic animal.
Guys, when I see a swan, I swoon.
Well, the only other animal I swoon when I see is Mimi LaFleur.
So your tunnel of love would be a big Mimi, a giant Mimi LaFleur.
And then you're with another Mimi LaFleur.
A fox in a military style uniform is really what does it for me.
At ease, soldier.
At ease, boys.
Okay.
There is in Sweden, there's a park that I don't think we've ever talked about and the park is called Grönaland.
And they have a ride to this day that is I will I'm about to butcher.
Here's my attempt.
Karleksstunneln.
Beautiful language.
Yeah, it's well, yeah, that's sweet.
So this is a ride that it goes up a little hill and you go through a big heart.
This is it.
This is what I'm after.
It looks like a log.
And then there's some look, there's some hearts on the other side.
This is as close as I could find to a tunnel of love that exists in this world today.
You got to go to Sweden for it.
However, then the rest of it is like trolls.
Here you pass by like a weird little bakery.
I don't know.
Well, hold on, Jason says.
Yes, now we're into Jason's zone.
They are making heart shaped items in the bakery.
And then I guess in the world of amorousness, you also pass by like some little troll girl who is kind of in like Venus mode.
Like she's like nude and covering herself, but not enough because one breast is hanging out with visible nipple.
Well, it's sweet.
This gave me some of those daftling vibes.
So there's like a bear bosom path.
It was a book.
Let me ask question.
Is a bosom the whole thing or is a bosom?
We don't have time for all your questions.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know because nobody said bosom since bosom buddies went off the air.
All right.
I think it's both.
Could it be both?
Perhaps this definition.
The two girls use it in a sentence.
The two girls had become bosom friends.
No one's ever said this.
Well, that's what Jason and when we met Jason and I became bosom friends.
We're fast bosom friends.
The other yet another name for these types of rides River Cave.
So like I feel like trolls in so many of these people's minds went to like, well, that seems like a place a troll would be an old mill, a river cave.
You know?
Yeah.
A lot of trolls.
And then, oh, that's right.
I forgot this one also.
This the Swedish one has stressed out miners in it.
There's a party like the knots ride.
There's a bunch of people working furiously and sadly in a mine.
So this is also not romantic.
So I hate to end the episode still having this question, but I just like, what is this pulling for?
I don't think there was ever something that was just a six minute plotless ride without any sort of well, depending.
I was going to say without a climax, but that depends on what you did in the tunnel.
But the ride itself, where it's just like you're because what I'm picturing is kind of Navi River Journey.
It's more about a vibe.
But instead of the the the vibe of Pandora and a war, it is you're just like it's just a meditation on love.
To me, it sounds like an interesting kind of ride.
And I'm not convinced that what I what I think ever existed on this earth, it doesn't.
I mean, it really seems like maybe what happened was, yeah, you explained like it started out as just it was dark in there.
So people would neck.
And then at that point, it was used in comic strips and comic books and TV and cartoons and stuff.
But then they had to like suggest to the viewer what was happening in case it wasn't clear.
Oh, it's like it's a shorthand for.
Yeah.
You know what?
Yes.
Maybe it's especially for a cartoon where kids are watching and you don't you could you could use that you go into a car.
You could use a seven minutes in heaven kind of right.
But maybe a tunnel of love leaves it at that could just be like a nice date that parents are having as the rug as the pickles parents have.
And yes, so that became a shorthand for the viewer to like tell adults what was happening and to kind of give kids the idea of what like was maybe have like just to give them the general vibe of it.
But not be specific.
It does take me when I think about seeing tunnels of love in cartoons or maybe more so not seeing them because you go in and then I don't know what happens in there.
It does remind me of the fog of not understanding what sex was.
Yes.
Yeah.
That is potentially still on all of us to some extent.
But, you know, we're like, you know, you remember having that feeling like before you found out of just like and then I don't know, they go in there.
And then they just some of that they flop around.
I don't know what it is.
Yes.
And that's how I feel about these tunnels of love.
I don't know.
It's just abstractly love happens.
Yes.
Because because you're you're no you're you're trying to probably decipher it for so many years and you're being given these vague hints.
And this just does more confusing things like this just is confusing more than anything else.
Yeah.
It's like it's a naked Cupid with an arrow.
What is it?
I was trying to decipher what was happening in the dark television scenes while my adolescent peers were all making out with each other.
They were all doing it.
They were all figuring it out.
And I was like, what is happening with Helga and Arnold?
You know, and to this day, we're still like, but what really happens in the ride?
All I knew was you basically whatever it was, was you come out with lipstick prints on your face like Archie would after he was necking with Betty.
Yes.
That was a visual shorthand because in reality, you probably wouldn't want any lipstick.
So you could really knock in without, you know, evidence.
That's right.
This is something that's at the core of this.
Maybe why I'm obsessed with this and still pushing this is that like what would it especially in the cases where it's two people who don't like each other and then by the end they've got smooch marks all over each other.
What would happen in there?
And I'm not talking about physically between them because what I mean is something about the decor has to be so romantic that it could make enemies lovers in the in with the flip of a switch.
Yeah.
What is it?
Is it the lattices?
Is it like what could be in this ride that is so romantic that it would flip you all the way pitch black endless possibility?
I guess so.
Including a timeline where amorousness has taken control of heat.
Jason, what if it was more like a great movie ride situation where you saw some of the greatest romantic scenes of cinema history?
Oh, look, it's the couple from shop around the corner.
You know, that's right.
If you saw the couple from shop around the corner, Scott, you can't deny that your romance meter.
Although isn't that that's the same remake lineage as you've got mail.
That's right.
So yeah, that'd be if there was a ride where you could see the full rom-com ride.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, they'd have to.
Well, they'd save some money because they could just make like five Meg Ryan robots and just keep doing different stuff.
Change outfits.
Yeah.
But great.
Great moments.
Wait, with the great the great rom-com ride is what we're talking about.
That would do it.
I mean, that could be an epic universe land unto itself.
I think a full romance land.
If you would now with what they can do with.
Well, you know what?
I mean, you know what?
I think might be we've been on this, but what you might call a ride with romantic moments might be this new beauty and the beast ride.
Yes, for sure.
Because this has like I think it is it's it's pretty new thing to make like two animatronic bodies share a romantic moment.
I say it's a new other than experimental robot sessions that people have done in workshops.
But you know what I mean?
Like I think maybe you could have like like if they if you if you put the full weight of imaginary behind it, I think you could recreate the notebook kiss.
We have that and it doesn't hurt the robots.
Yeah, that.
Yeah, I think that the thing with robots is that I guess some of them even in the most like if they're recreating a romantic moment from a movie, sometimes maybe a robot's jerkiness doesn't translate to like beauty romance.
Maybe.
So I guess they'd have to be the most advanced romantic animatronics ever created.
Especially if they're doing human being like they're mimicking human beings.
Yeah.
So I think I mean these new robots that we've been seeing from Imagineering are cool, but maybe we still need to take a leap forward in romantic robot technology.
We need to teach the robots to love to bring it back to AI.
Oh, yeah, we do.
Yeah, it's a nice.
Yeah, we have to teach them to love for real.
This isn't a technological we have to like hit some with the singularity in which the only thing lacking in that beating the beast ride.
Those robots don't actually love each other.
They're just mechanics that look like they do.
Right.
The only imagineering's next level is to make robots that are actually in love with each other.
They figured out how to make the Jude Law sex worker robot, but not the.
Well, that's not amorous.
Lieutenant Commander Data in Star Trek The Next Generation knew how to have sex before he knew how to love.
We've all been there.
He was fully functional and had sex before they put in his emotion chip.
And then after having sex years later, he first, I think, displayed love honestly in Star Trek Generations when he rescued his cat from the wreckage of the Enterprise D.
And he welled up with tears and he realized he felt love.
So I think you're you would probably want let's do a couple steps.
You want Star Trek the experience back and you want there to be a romantic.
So let's do a tunnel of love in there.
A holodeck of love.
Yes.
In which a real a data robot is actually alive and is taught out of love.
Yeah, I would.
Oh my God, please.
I'll go home.
Move there.
If that's existing again.
Michael has left Lindsay for a robot of data.
There's a horny.
It's data.
I hate to hate to correct you, but it's data.
They pronounce the data.
But, you know, Star Trek, there's so much love on start the history of Star Trek.
You know, Will Riker and Deanna Troy and Star Trek Insurrection when they're all getting like sort of the atmosphere of the planet they're on is giving them all kind of like puberty fair hormones back.
And they're all feeling very horny.
You know, maybe that actually what we're missing about what is wire tunnel of what if they're pumping pheromones?
I'm here going like, is it a big bear with a heart shaped box of candies?
Maybe the secret what they won't say is that pure gas pheromones were pumped into these real tunnels.
That's good.
You know what else I think could help as well is playing the song on a loop Bruce Springsteen tunnel of love.
If we've ever seen the cover.
Mm hmm.
Bruce there.
I was listening to this before.
It's kind of in my musical neck of the woods a little.
Yeah.
Some of the I feel like some of the Bruce 90s was not received so well.
But in hindsight, I think a lot of it holds up pretty good.
And this is about I mean, it's about going on the ride we're talking about.
It's also about, of course, you know, the complications of romance and what does it mean and how hard it is.
But it is also just like he calls the man overweight in the first line.
I don't know.
It seems superfluous, but he says he's paying somebody to get on a ride that's working the ride and then they go on there and there's like mirrors in it too.
But he doesn't describe Cupid or any of scrolls.
Wait, that's a kind of maybe mirrors are good.
It lets you picture each other together and then you get to watch each other.
Yeah.
They're on a mirrored ceiling.
So you know what?
Actually, Bruce has helped solve this myth.
That is what was romantic in these rides.
Yeah.
And if there's two rows, you get bored.
Just take a peek of what's going on behind you.
Be a little bit of where Jason, the third stuck his tongue out when he said he raised his eyes.
The mirrors are there to be looked at.
You know, that was a good idea.
You know, oh, that's a good idea.
Jason, what E Street band member and wife would you want behind you in a tunnel of love going down?
Little Stephen and Maureen Van Zandt.
Are you all so deep that you know their wives?
Some of them.
I don't know that I know all the members.
Oh, of the E Street band?
Yeah.
Oh, just well, you know, you've got your Max Weinberg.
Little Stephen, I'd be distracted.
Hey, you survived Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for subscribing to the…
Feel free to keep listing them.
We got to get out of here someday.
We do.
Mike's getting worked up.
He's talking about data.
And tiny Springsteen.
He's getting worked up over there.
Hey, you know what would be a fun second gate, I think, is to do an episode about data.
Let's do one.
Mike would like this.
Let's do one all about data.
I'm embarrassed at how much hearing him called data drives me nuts.
I'm embarrassed by how much it's like nails on a chalkboard.
All right.
You survived Podcast the Ride.
Data.
Thanks for subscribing to the second gate.
If you want to dig even deeper data, join us on our VIP Patron tier club three, where
you get one more bonus episode every month and our regular episodes ad free.
Data.
I will say, real quick, I cannot stop thinking about how you prepared the car before.
That is…
I can't…
It's so funny.
And as a boy scout.
It's so funny though.
Because you just drive around the corner and prepare it.
I don't know.
I was on my way out.
I thought I was in the clear.
Okay, he came out last second.
I see.
Yeah, no.
So I'm like, oh god, my dad's here.
He's going to say something.
But what I never would have guessed is that he was going to accuse his 18 year old son
of using a rubber glove as a condom.
That's funny too.
But in my mind, you would like hours before prepare the seats.
And as a former boy scout, I appreciate always be prepared.
Always be prepared.