Forever.
Dog.
Podcast The Ride in association with Coca-Cola, Oscar Mayer, and AOL Top Speed presents a salute
to Disney's Super Bowl halftime shows.
With special appearances by Tony Bennett, Mickey Rooney, an army of Shirley Temples, Fake Mickey,
Fake Goofy, and Jason Sheridan as Mae West, the Podcast The Ride show about Disney's Super
Bowl halftime shows starts right now!
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks which, listeners can attest, has
caused more brain damage than professional football ever could.
I'm Scott Gertner, there's Mike Carlson.
Oh man, you saying that though means the class action lawsuit is coming.
Oh yes, oh god.
You've admitted to that.
Well, shoot, we got, I'll edit it, I'll remember.
There's no way to prove it, I mean, because like, if you're, look, we're causing brain
damage, you know, blank check, Doughboys are causing brain damage, I mean, like, all of
there's no way to pinpoint it to us.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
There's so many people poisoning the brains of listeners that there's no way to say what
damage caused what.
But I definitely want to, you know, if doctors do a scan on the brain and like, now that
deposit there, that is your knowledge of Nick's owner, James Dolan, having done a song about
how Harvey Weinstein, he should have known Harvey Weinstein did the stuff that he did.
That's right, so we see that on the X-ray.
Where do you think that could have come from?
What could have put you at risk for that?
So until imaging technology catches up, we won't be put into some sort of massive trial.
We wouldn't be, we have to like go to jail.
It's easier now for like AI to scan the transcript of a podcast, so we're against the ropes on
that, but then really if we can eventually scan a brain to see what awful fact we specifically
have poisoned the listeners with, then we're in a lot of trouble.
This is Jason Sheridan, huh?
I feel like it's a very concentrated dose today.
You know, no placebo, no saline solution.
This is like, this drink in the cold brew concentrate without watering it down.
That's a pretty good point.
Yes, absolutely, because this is a true brigade of nonsense today.
Yeah, garbage factory.
This is definitely, yeah, yeah, this will be nothing but garbage and we'll explain why.
I mean, it's, you know, it's because it's Super Bowl weekend and this is our big Super
Bowl episode and you know, we know what you come to us for in a Super Bowl episode, so
I'll just kick it off.
Conventional wisdom holds of the Chiefs are a lock with Patrick Mahomes having completed
70% of his passes with the yards per attempt average of 7.
0 in his previous six postseason
games, but one mustn't ignore the stacked 49ers offense with Brandon Iuke leading the
league's receivers in catch score and Deebo Samuel leading all receivers in YAC score.
So, is it possible that the presumed to win Chiefs will be haunted by sloppy offensive
play like McColl-Hardman's goal line fumble against the Bills in the divisional round?
Michael, let's start with you.
Well Scott, I really would like to gather my thoughts.
Yeah, no, no, no, I didn't mean to, of course, take your time.
Well, we'll go to Jason Sheridan's thoughts then in the meantime.
Well sure, as long as the main player on the field today is good sportsmanship, then everyone
wins.
Dang, that actually is a good thought.
You said a real thing.
I couldn't have come up with that.
I had to write all that down, all that stuff I just said that I'll admit.
I don't know what it means.
I was going to say, you shouldn't have admitted that.
Yeah, yeah, jeez.
And I'm waiting for the Chiefs to win, Taylor Swift to run on field and say the magic words,
I support Joe Biden, let the new world of wooder begin.
I just learned of this for the first time.
Because I've certainly seen a lot about can Taylor make it from Tokyo, but I didn't realize
that was the concern and that what are like MAGA wine moms trying to like form some kind
of blockade between here and Tokyo so that she can't come tip her sheep listeners into
voting for, who otherwise assuredly would be Trump supporters one and all, but they're
also said, you know, they're such dummies.
They might all flip just because Taylor said so.
Yeah, I didn't realize this until recently that the rumor is that she's a CIA, what she's
a CIA?
She's an op, yeah, sure.
Yeah, that's the rumor.
And that's being like pushed by like some pretty big conservative accounts.
Just insane conservative.
You can't tell.
And then I saw other conservatives posting like, please stop doing this.
Please stop saying this.
You sound stupid.
We look stupid now.
Please.
That's the best hope we have is all of them tearing each other apart, you know.
But yeah, I know it's a Psyop.
It's a Psyop that's been going since 2009-ish.
It seems as though for 15 years or more, we've heard a lot about this Taylor Swift.
There must be something to it, right?
She was a Psyop planted in 2009 to stop the eventual presidential, not first run because
he did win the first, but the reelection of Donald Trump after a loss, which was planned
as part of the Psyop.
Yeah.
No, I, it's really, it's really something.
Let's just put it that way.
Yeah.
It's really something to see that take hold.
There might be something to it.
That's for our listeners to decide.
Or just asking questions.
As usual, that's all we're doing.
We wouldn't say anything is fact.
No, one thing Taylor Swift is not doing this year is the Super Bowl halftime show.
Right.
Well, oh, well, I guess so.
This is more of the like kind of pop culture.
It's like there are, she, like her and Usher have done like, like, co-labs.
Like she was performing Atlanta.
He came out and they did, yeah, she sang Ludacris' verse.
I've never seen that clip.
Yeah, it's on, it's on YouTube.
So people are like, okay, if she gets there and then she has time to watch some of the
game and then change and then get down for the hit.
It sounds miserable.
I don't think she's going to like, but she doesn't want to take the focus off of Travis
Kelsey.
She doesn't know.
Like that's going to be his day.
It's his day.
She's a supportive person.
I think she wouldn't be like, well, I'm going to outshine him.
I think.
Not to mention that I think that appearing on the Super Bowl would be like a downgrade
100% would be.
For her.
I'm not sure.
Okay, I was going to say one, but I don't know what she's on at this point.
I was going to say one post would be more, but does she post?
I don't know.
You're the Swiftie.
This is who you.
I'm social media.
I don't know.
I'm not following her.
I don't know that she has such a presence.
Maybe I don't follow her Instagram.
Maybe I should do it right now.
I have the Instagram account Camporama just loaded up for this episode.
Camporama?
Yeah, yeah.
But I'll get onto Taylor Swift's Instagram.
What's on Camporama?
Well, it's all different camp clips.
Because what we're going to be talking about today is camp.
This is all pretty campy.
It's all very campy.
Well, is it?
Yeah, but it's, I'd say unintentional camp.
Well, that's a discussion to have about what is the intention of this camp, I think.
It's very much closer.
It's not that Super Bowl halftime shows we know now where it's like.
I'm at Taylor Swift's Instagram.
All right, yeah, we heard applause.
I didn't mean to do that.
You interrupted Jason's flow.
Sorry, Jason.
These Super Bowl halftime shows are much closer to like icecapades or a pageant.
They're little skits.
There's a lot of little skits.
Very much so.
You know, there literally was, we won't be talking about this one today, but there was
an icecapade at the halftime.
Before the one, before Michael Jackson tipped it forever into what it is now, which is like
big elevated concerts, basically.
There was one that I think was a bridge too far, which was ice skating on the, they brought
out little tiny ice rinks, you know, because the skaters surely won't need, you know, like
many feet of run up.
Yeah, you could just do a jump.
You got four feet here.
That rink's as wide as you are.
Yeah.
Or wide as you are long.
But yeah, they did do icecapades live in the halftime show at one point, which I think
was kind of a bridge too far.
That's where they decided maybe we need to make this entertainment less stupid.
But let's paint the full picture here as we focus on Super Bowl halftime shows.
The very first one ever to take place was in 1967.
And that was not one, but two marching bands.
And when you got two marching bands, you can make at least two shapes.
I think that's what they did.
I think the marching bands played, they made two shapes and that was the end of that.
They called that a day.
Today of course, it is usher for kind of our entire lives at this point.
It has been like a concert by a major pop act, a big one, an elevated one with probably
some production design and sometimes some fairly theme parky nonsense.
And it's almost usually, I believe, the instruments are recorded, pre-recorded, and the vocals
are live.
Yeah, maybe it's kind of like a, it's a relatively impossible thing to, because they have to,
the scramble to put these things together, to assemble the stage in a matter of five
minutes then connect everything well enough for live music to be played.
It's possible Prince's guitar was live for the Prince halftime show?
I'm not sure actually.
You don't think the rest of the band was?
I don't know.
Because that's what I've heard is like the band is never, there's just no way to soundcheck
it that quickly.
You can't set everything up in two seconds and soundcheck everything.
Well, I mean.
I'm not sure though.
Rehearsals, I think, have long been an issue with these things.
One of the, we'll get to today, I believe, was maybe none of them.
A lot of them, at least for many years, were never rehearsed in full before being performed
in front of the biggest audience possible on television.
That's…
No, no, no.
We have a narrow focus here, which I'll explain.
Basically, you know, if you think about the whole history of it, the nearly 60 year history
of it, from two marching bands to big concerts, it's kind of this gradient, really, that gets
you from one to the other.
And I think they step it up every year.
They increase the entertainment value.
But there's a point in that gradient, the middle of that gradient, especially in the
70s and 80s, where the Super Bowl halftime show was comprised of a lot of what I will
call razzle dazzle crap.
Just like ill-conceived, huge in scope, but limited in its concept or like, I'd say embarrassment
is involved in a lot of cases.
Yeah, the phrase I have in my head from watching this stuff now is like dorky camp.
Like lame camp.
In the sense that, obviously, the pinnacle I think of camp is like Batman, the 60s Batman.
It's funny, but it's colorful and it's silly and whatever.
But then there's this stuff which is like very cringe when you see a lot of it.
But it is also similarly silly and colorful and a bunch of nonsense.
Well, that's my question.
If you bring camp into it, I think some amount of purpose has to be involved.
Awareness has to be involved in almost any of this, is there?
I don't agree that there has to be purpose to have camp, though.
I think that something can have camp value and it's like you're watching it.
I don't exactly know.
I don't know the entomology of the term.
I don't know either, I guess.
But to me, when something itself is campy, like they knew.
But it's campy to watch something that's old and embarrassing or whatever.
I don't know.
That's my broad theory.
But I could be wrong.
You might be right.
I mean, I see what you're saying.
So there's a very popular Instagram account called Camporama.
There's like 150,000 followers on it.
I am one of them.
And it goes anywhere from Liberace stuff to like Elaine Stritch doing her one woman show.
And it looks like it's a pretty wide ranging amount of stuff on here.
Some purposeful, some not.
Now, I don't know that this account is the authority on it.
But it seems right.
That's a weird if they're cataloging it.
There's some confidence in the opinion.
Right.
There's some Eartha Kitt performances.
There's, you know, what's her name?
The woman who played the Wicked Witch of the West doing a Maxwell House commercial.
Like there wasn't probably that wasn't purposeful camp.
But you know.
So yeah.
So are we getting full podcast, the right episodes about every single post on Camporama?
Well, I see Agnes Moorhead from Bewitched.
So the answer is yes.
Great.
OK.
Put it in the queue.
I love this account.
Or if nothing else, put them in the Club 3 poll to get about three or four percent in
the final running.
Negative three.
How do they do that?
How do the audience vote?
I didn't know there were demerits in the Patreon voting.
Patreon is truly iterating and updating the usability.
They don't want to hear.
They don't want to see this clip from the Love Boat of Ruth Gordon with Bernie Kapell.
They don't want to hear 30 minutes on this.
What are they singing?
Just go to random part.
What is it?
What's happening?
Let me see.
Mrs.
Warner, I forgot I've got a performance emergency app in deck to me.
No, on myself.
She's hitting on Bernie?
I think so.
It's a love boat.
But I'm not dressed.
It's a long clip.
Yeah, no, I put you on the spot.
You haven't vetted that.
You haven't watched that.
It was worth getting into.
I was just like, you know, there better be hardcore Bernie Kapell, Ruth Gordon making out
in this next five minutes.
That might be what would come out.
Yeah, yeah, you never know.
Well, update us later or just leave it playing in a loop while we do the rest of this.
But anyway, Razzle Dazzle Crap is at least what's in my head.
You don't have to use that term, but I will.
And over in the years that were kind of the pre-pop culture awareness, the Razzle Dazzle
Crap years, a lot of these events were perpetrated by the Walt Disney Company.
And that is what we're going to be focusing on today, because I've been wanting to do
a halftime show episode for some time.
This has been in my mental queue.
But I want to credit a user.
Did I write down their names?
Yes, Mark Gannon and Casey Lucas on Club 3, our VIP Patron tier, both of them suggested
that we on Club 3, but we're doing it here on main feed.
The suggestion was to focus on the halftime shows produced by the Walt Disney Company.
And I thought that's a great idea.
That's a good way to like, all right, we'll take care of these.
And if people are into this, then in success, we can, because there's a lot of other, there's
so many insane halftime shows.
Oh my God.
Yeah, yeah.
So much.
And I honestly, you know, I'm maybe aware of like the ones while I've been alive more
than the ones before I was alive.
I don't, I'm not sure I've ever watched any from the 70s and early 80s until this.
Clearly there's a lot to get into because on the way to Disney doing it, before Disney
did it, I believe the fourth one, as I was saying, I think it's this ramp up where, all
right, it's going to be some marching bands and that'll be nice, right?
But then this thing gets more popular, more pop culturally relevant.
It's big on television.
So maybe we got to do a little more to pull in the viewers at home.
And maybe a good idea would be to have celebrities, famous people as part of this.
And yeah, that sounds good.
Sure.
Who do they get?
Carol Channing.
Carol Channing was the first one.
She's on Camperana all the time on the Instagram account.
I would have to imagine.
She's there all the time.
A Camperama mainstay.
That's right.
Now, I have not seen footage of this one.
I don't know if anyone saved footage of this one, but apparently that's Super Bowl Four.
And apparently that one involves not only Carol Channing, but also a restaging of the
Battle of New Orleans, complete with terrified horses and falling soldiers.
Oh my God.
Not prepared on that one.
Maybe to come in Super Bowl halftime.
Well, they got the accuracy of the Battle of New Orleans.
There were definitely some falling soldiers and terrified horses.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe they got it exactly right, because probably, you know, there's recreations of battles.
This happens in the world.
But I bet that if you just watched battles from really far away for the most part, it's
just a bunch of, it's a big confusing mess.
Oh, yeah.
It's not some ballet.
No, it's not even as cool as Lord of the Rings armies meet.
Like it's, yeah.
I can't, I cannot imagine.
Yes.
The Civil War was as cool to watch as Lord of the Rings.
No, no, no, no.
But anyway, yeah, these are the early years.
I mean, it's one of those things where, boy, is The Simpsons parody so accurate.
That one where, are they watching the literal Super Bowl?
Is it the Lisa the Greek episode where she's betting on football and there's a snippet
of a halftime show and it's an alien in a suit and they sing one, two, three o'clock,
four o'clock, you're on a rock around the world tonight.
And I think I saw that and thought, you know, when I was a kid, I'm like, yeah, Super Bowl
halftime shows are kind of cheesy.
And then not until I've seen some real ones, am I like, that is exact.
Like that could have that literally could have been something that they did, at least
in the early ones.
See, I jumped to the other Simpsons reference of the variety show, Hooray for Everything.
And it's like kids dressed in sock hop attire, but they're singing Walk on the Wild Side.
Oh, right.
Right.
That's another thing they did.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Hey, kids.
Yeah, that's extremely accurate, too.
There's I just want to say the the 1976 halftime show, which we're not going to talk about
today, but it was called 200 Years and Just a Baby, a Tribute to America's Bicentennial
and Up With People, Up With People did that one, which is what they were like
parroting on the Simpsons as well.
Hooray for Everything is a parody of Up With People.
And I'm not prepared to talk about Up With People.
I don't quite understand what it is.
I didn't know if it was a group.
But what I'm finding is that maybe it was it's more akin to like an organization.
Yeah, it's like a big volunteer organization.
It's a nonprofit.
It's a non-profit.
Yeah.
I can't imagine Up With People didn't ultimately turn a profit somehow
with their jazzy rhythms and cool harmonies.
Oh, Jason, could you put on a one man show called 200 Years and Just a Baby,
a tribute to America's Bicentennial?
Well, it'll be like baby New Year, except I will enter in the diaper
in the sash and I will also come out at the end in the like.
So I don't age at all.
Oh, yeah.
So it's a lot.
It's plenty, baby.
Maybe you do whatever we find.
I think it will.
It'll be plenty, baby, for me.
That's for sure.
I don't even need you in a diaper.
I just wanted you doing whatever the old time songs they perform in here.
Well, you have your methods to prepare and I've mine.
Hey, I'm not going to fight you being in a diaper.
Jason, Jason insists on the diaper.
Fight me on this.
Fight me until I end up in a diaper.
He's taking his clothes off right now.
What?
No.
All right.
Well, here's one of my daughter's diapers.
Put it on.
You're going to have to stretch it a bit.
Put four of them together.
Anyway, it seems like Up With People was one of the main providers
of this entertainment, of the extremely white bread entertainment
for the first 15 years or so.
And the other, the Walt Disney Company, because the NFL can't put
these things on themselves.
They are busy with the game and the other games.
They need to reach out to entertainment entities to do these things.
And Disney enters the picture for Super Bowl 11, which is in 1977.
And I think they especially,
at least initially, would do the halftime shows when it's in
when the Super Bowl is in California or Florida.
Makes sense to be near their parks, near their facilities.
And they have access to tons of dancers and costumes and musicians and all that.
So absolutely makes sense.
Disney would would be part of these.
So I have more about these as they go on.
But I'll try to step through what I learned about the initial,
the early Disney Super Bowl halftime shows.
So Super Bowl 11, 1977.
This was at the Rose Bowl.
Raiders versus Vikings.
The I don't have much here.
I picked a pretty arbitrary clip,
but this, I think, will give you an idea of just the tenor of the entertainment.
And it's not exactly a far cry from up with people, from what I can tell.
So here's here's just a random little bit of what Disney provided in 77.
And it is love that you give
and will that you'll keep this time.
Yes, it's lanky, very pale people kind of doing
they aren't even moving.
No, they're not like dynamic dancers or anything.
Kind of it's just like synchronized,
the half speed arm pumps basically in Mickey Mouse
sweater vests and bright red pants.
This is I mean, I know there was a lot like this in the 70s.
We've delved into our 70s variety shows.
But I do always flash to like punk was happening, you know?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
The talking heads were going on.
Oh, yeah.
Early hip hop.
Yes.
Yeah.
We're almost at hip.
No, I literally Googles synthesizer.
I was watching again.
I started getting on down rabbit holes of non Disney produced.
And I was watching 92, which has some great stuff in it.
And then I was like, wait, I'm like Guns N' Roses was popular.
Like the biggest record.
We're almost we're almost at the grunge turn.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
I was just like, when it's OK.
All right.
It's like I'm sure that current like who they currently book
is not like exactly up to speed, typically with the year.
And like what's what's cool.
That's not what you look for in the Super Bowl necessarily.
But it's at least like we're we're like in the same.
We're in the realm of the same like two decades typically.
You know, we aren't in another planet in terms of relevance.
Like you're on another planet.
Yeah.
It feels like now it's it's not necessarily the biggest act
of that year or two.
You know, it's not Taylor Swift or Beyonce.
It is someone well into their like, you know, well established
and recognizable across the country and internationally.
Yes.
But not like just like, all right.
I'm just going to wind it down a little, go a little slower,
do a Vegas residence and not that point.
Like, you know, sure, sure.
Recent hits, probably.
Probably unless they mash a bunch of people up together,
which they do sometimes as well.
Maybe somebody's not on their own.
What they feel is a big enough draw.
But if you put a bunch of people in there, maybe it works.
Yeah, it can be like a big who they have a few years.
Was it like Eminem and 50 Cent and Snoop and Dre?
But that was kind of a consistent theme of like all of the Dre accolades.
Yeah, that was sort of his history.
Well, I think you see less of the mashup of a ton of people
since the infamous MTV Janet.
I think they blamed the format for what happened.
You see.
Well, of course, I mean, the Brittany Aerosmith in sync.
That might need to get a little time in the if we do another one of these.
So non Disney, one of these.
Oh, yeah.
I have vivid memories of that.
So TV did a like behind the scenes of how they did it
to see and Sink and Aerosmith together.
It fit hand in glove.
I know.
It always it feels to me like that Super Bowl was always trying to be like, well,
the halftime show was for a different crowd to entice people to want to watch it.
Like people who wouldn't usually be watching.
Right.
And that still seems that's still kind of what they're doing.
It's just that their approach back then to me seems a little bit misguided.
I don't know.
We were people really excited about these.
That's a good question.
I think the approach back then seemed to be like, let's see if we can get grandma
in from the next room.
Sure.
So it is.
I guess it's the same thing because if they were to have like
Aerosmith now or the Rolling Stones, I'm grandpa.
I'm like, get grandpa in here.
And I'm like, oh, I would like to look at the Rolling Stones.
The Rolling Stones with us.
Sure.
Now I'm listening.
I'm excited.
But when I Springsteen played like 10 years ago, I was like,
I'm going to see this Super Bowl.
I really want to watch it.
And yeah, so I guess it's always been the same
same goal and different approaches.
Sure.
But we've aged and we've at least like we're.
Yeah, that's where we're at.
We're at entertainment that has been relevant in the last century.
Weekend.
The weekend does it, which grandpa doesn't know necessarily
who the weekend is.
Now they spelled this word wrong.
What's the why they drop that?
Where are the where's up with people?
Why are they up with people on here anymore?
Up with people.
I'm having a going concern for 20 years.
All right.
Well, I'm going back in my room and my den.
The other notable facts about this one,
they didn't know how to film these yet.
So there's a lot of you see that.
Yeah, you see the shadow of the helicopter a lot.
There's a we get the first ever introduction of the new Mousketeers,
the 70s ones who did that Disney World special, which was OK.
That's on Disney Plus.
And just general about the 77 Super Bowl,
two of the Raiders played high on weed that they brought from
that they bought from Anthony Kiedis's father,
whose name of course is Blackie Dammit.
Yeah, I did know that actually.
You knew his name was Blackie Dammit.
I've heard that.
And what Kiedis's stage name was another he was a different dammit.
Right.
Yeah, because he was a kid actor.
This comes knowledge comes new to me just a few days after
Michael Buble apparently played the NHL All-Star game on mushrooms.
What?
Michael Buble, really?
Yeah, I think he thought he was being given a micro dose.
Yeah, it's very small dose.
Yeah, I know.
I've missed this story.
Given a very large dose.
That seems hard to do to play on mushrooms.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know how his play was.
Oh, you know, maybe you wait.
So he played like this wasn't him doing a concert in a show.
This was he played hockey.
Yeah.
Geez.
Oh, OK.
Oh, that's neat.
One of the one of the hockey seems even too dangerous to do.
One of the there's a book on the shelf.
My mom got me, which is Anthony Kiedis's autobiography
a few years ago.
Your daughter's bedtime story.
And no, that's where I'm at.
Maybe I said this already.
That's the book she walks over and picks up off the shelf all the time.
Wow.
There's so many photos of her taking Anthony Kiedis's book off.
But is there nudity on the cover?
Well, he's he's got his ripped body on the cover.
So I know when you don't want to teach her to be uncomfortable
with situation on the cover.
And she doesn't like watching Bluey or Peppa Pig.
She likes watching like Daisy Jones in the Electric Six and like
Dennis Leary's Sex and Drugs and Rock and Roll.
Yeah, she likes fake bands on TV.
She likes Sunset Strip stuff, right?
She loves Sunset Strip stuff.
Yes.
So she yeah, she's already into Rock and Roll.
Sunset Strip stuff.
You heard the Rock and Roll over here.
Where Rock goes, you know.
Where Rock was born.
Where Rock goes.
Grandpa, go back in your day.
Wait a minute.
Is Rock goes a phrase in the world?
Where Rock and Roll go.
Where folks go for Rock.
Oh, I thought you were saying that we collectively are Rockos.
Oh, I like that term.
And then Rock and Roll fans are Rockos.
Well, yeah, of course, Rock and Roll fans are Rockos or Rollers.
I think we should.
I think you've coined a new term that I'm going to use on this show,
that I'm a Rocko.
You are a Rocko.
I'm a Rocko.
I'm a real Rocko.
What can I tell you?
Wow.
But they weren't, you know, in 77,
they aren't appealing to the Rockos yet, other than.
Yeah.
Other than these two Raiders, who, by the way, the Raiders won.
So thank you.
Secret weapon.
Blacky, damn it.
That's right.
You know, so we're stepping
hopefully further into where pop culture is actually at,
as Disney produces the half time show at Super Bowl 18 in 1984.
Although not really, because
national anthem is Barry Manilow.
And Manilow, I would say, is kind of the tone of the rest of what happens here.
This one, by the way, in Tampa, Raiders versus recently renamed Washington team.
That I will not say on Mike.
84 is the year of the the famous 1984 commercial.
The Big Apple.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Scott Add, which is very cutting edge.
Very like, you know, now there is like a pop culture defining moment
at the Super Bowl, a little more so than what Disney produced that year,
which was called a sparkling salute to superstars of the silver screen.
That will be another one man show Jason does in a doper.
But a sparkly diaper.
Oh, I like the big skin.
That Jimmy Stewart.
Yes, Jimmy Stewart.
Jason Sheridan plays 200 stars of Hollywood Dior.
Oh, my God.
I'll write that for you.
You'll do it.
Every time he spins around, he becomes a new guy.
Cary Grant, go.
Well, let's.
Hello.
Yeah, great.
I was trying to do Cary.
I was thinking in my head for a couple of minutes, like,
what does Cary Grant sound like?
Mae West, go.
Come up and see me sometime, big boy.
Yes.
Wow.
All right.
Excellent.
That was that was pretty good on the fly.
Barry Manilow, I believe also on Camporama often.
No, sure.
That makes sense.
Yeah, yeah.
We are adding.
There's adding evidence to my theory.
Sure.
Also a big microdozer, famously.
Yeah, of course.
So, you know, this one, I also I don't have clips of this one,
but, you know, there's but people have big letters that spell out
a ray for Hollywood and they sing a ray for Hollywood.
And they, you know, they sing about that screwy,
ballyhooey Hollywood.
This song is less and less relatable to me as the years go by.
And as Hollywood is more and more terrible to watch the products of
and work in, as I get really kind of tired of both the screwy
and ballyhooey nature of the business.
It's hard to imagine the optimism in a song like that.
Yeah.
But I do think, OK, just as I list what happens in this one,
there's like, you know, the thing where like two guys share a big sparkly piano.
Yeah.
And there's like big Southern bell dresses like Gone With the Wind style.
And they sing You Oughta Be in Pictures and Stepping Out With My Babe.
And then there's like the field is covered in people with with white tuxes.
And I was watching this and thinking like, Jason, are you the are you going to end up
the last person alive who likes this kind of thing?
You'll be the last human on Earth.
I you know, I think I like it in proper context.
It's weird to see in a Super Bowl halftime show.
And you are talking about right now that 1984 show.
That's right.
Yeah.
I don't want to jump too far ahead.
But 1987 is also a tribute to Hollywood.
Why, in fact, yes, you might.
If eagle eyed viewers might notice that there is not a world of difference
between a sparkling salute to superstars of the silver screen
and three years later, Hollywood, the land of make believe.
The Hollywood, the land of make believe they at least kind of tenuously
there are like it's 100 years of Hollywood.
And I'm like, oh, yeah, those 1887 bangers.
So it's like a person walks from right side of the screen to left side.
Child observes sunflower.
Yeah.
I yeah, you're right.
And look, I'm more than happy to generally rush through this.
The only thing I want to show is not not a clip, but just a shot,
because things do kind of heat up, I would say, when Minnie Mouse joins
the festivities and she comes out, she's she's on a big throne
that's carried by a bunch of the Jungle Book monkeys.
And she's in like Carmen Miranda garb.
And we all collectively will be the final people on earth
who know what the reference Carmen Miranda is.
I've never seen a Carmen Miranda film, no, I will.
I but I do know when there's a bunch of fruit on your head, that's what it is.
But anyway, this shot really, this still, I think, kind of tells you
all you need to know, which is that Minnie is brought up on this pedestal
and then she's surrounded by a bunch of like strong guys.
Yeah, hunks.
Yeah.
Like, yeah, yeah, these guys are beefcakes.
These guys are even like bigger than your average body,
I feel like the time maybe like they're like not maybe to Arnold.
So closer to that, though, closer to the Arnold side of things.
So, yeah, they are.
I'm just I'm just trying to say how punky they are and how muscly they are.
I'm just trying to paint a picture for the listener.
Yeah, yeah.
They got suspenders on.
Are you upset to see them in the frame with oh, with many?
Yeah.
Well, I mean, it makes me feel less of a man.
If that's what you're saying.
And if you were if this was your POV and you were trying to get to her
for for a quick hug, if she sees that, if you make eye contact
and she acknowledges that she wants it,
I'd get beat up by these hunky firefighter guys.
Yeah, I wouldn't want that to happen.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Miss Mouse, seeing other guys today.
Hey, did you tell her I'm here?
Tell her Michael is here.
I'm trying to get through here.
She met me in Florida.
She had a fireman.
Mr.
Fireman, get out of my way.
I have half a mind to suck you right in the nose.
And then, yeah, then I just get knocked out with those suspenders.
Pull one back and fire it right at your nip.
Hey, don't dance at me.
Get away from me.
It's not thrusting.
So some very strange cameos in this one.
Oh, wait, what are you talking about?
87.
Yeah, 87.
Let's officially move to 87.
Maybe one of the strangest opening bits I've ever seen.
Yes.
These as we said, these are kind of the same,
but technically we do move to Super Bowl 21.
This is 1987.
We're back at the Rose Bowl.
Neil Diamond does the national anthem.
That's a treat.
That's I can't imagine a better national anthem singer than Neil Diamond.
Broncos V.
Giants.
And this one is the debut of the I'm going to Disney World commercials.
To be covered separately as its own episode.
I would imagine that being a thing that Eisner slash his wife thought of.
Anyway, yes.
Hollywood, the land of make believe big big gets in this way.
You know, there is again, we're not in the age of star power yet.
In the halftime show, we're still with up and up with people.
No real stars to speak of in 84, but 87.
Hold the ball game.
Yeah.
It opens with a shot of the Hollywood sign.
And I believe also the Mickey Mouse balloon known as Air Force One.
Yes.
Separate episode that we already have covered.
Yeah, we have covered your forest.
We don't worry.
We've talked about the big Mickey balloon.
Right.
And then the camera zooms out or tilts down a little and you see the seven dwarfs.
And then you see Snow White being escorted by someone.
And I could not make out who it looked like someone who was melting.
And then it snapped in my in my attic clicked.
And I was like, oh, it's George Burns.
Yes.
And that is a perfect segue.
You've painted the scene perfectly for this clip to be played.
Ladies and gentlemen, Mr.
George Burns.
Thank you, Snow White.
Pretty girl.
A little too old for me.
Well, Hollywood is now 100 years old.
It's only nine years older than I am.
Maybe when I'm 100, they'll put my name up there.
If they don't, I'm moving to Burbank.
OK, now on with the show.
So I feel about that Burbank slander.
But yeah, besides that, OK.
All right.
If you had to go blue, George.
Yeah, George.
Very strange joke about Snow White being too old for him,
followed by a joke about him being younger than Hollywood.
Oh, yeah.
Slightly from 19.
What?
What are the movie release?
Yeah, I guess they mean that's probably mean that I don't mean what she is in the movie,
which is what I don't actually know.
But 15.
Yeah, but my guess is 15.
They were all 15.
Yeah.
Every princess was probably until Disney started making up the stories themselves.
They were all.
Yeah, I think that's probably right.
So, yeah, a little weird George Burns cameo at this point.
I believe George Burns, the biggest star ever on the halftime show.
Oh, wow.
Maybe that's right.
Defeating Carol Channing.
Wait, there's one more.
Who is on it in the early days?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, it's let me build up here.
Oh, Andy Williams, Andy Williams.
Mm hmm.
George Burns is a bigger star.
Yeah, yeah.
Jazz legend Pete Fountain.
Oh, all right.
So I do think George.
So with that cameo, George Burns' biggest star in the history of the show.
But well, Fitzgerald in 72.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
That's good.
That's a real.
All right.
OK, that's real.
Oh, I didn't realize.
All right.
So there would be actual popular musicians sometimes.
But George Burns didn't show up in person.
So you can't technically say George Burns' biggest star ever on the field.
For that, you have to wait one more minute for the show to begin
in earnest where a bevy of marching band players
are playing and marching.
And they are led by another one where you got to squint at first.
Who am I looking at here?
Oh, but that spirit, that invigorating spirit and his
the steps of his tiny legs.
Why, that can only be the great Mickey Rooney.
He is kind of going for it.
Like he is really jumping around.
Flailing, flailing arms akimbo.
And if I did the math correctly, he would have been 67 years old
or thereabouts.
He was born in I looked at 1920.
And now we're at 87.
So, yeah, 67.
Even though you might watch him and guess he is 103.
George Burns is in 87.
He died in 96.
So he is in his early 90s.
Wow.
Did he make it to 100?
He did make it to 100.
He passed it and even under it.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
So, yeah, the Mickey Rooney.
And I don't have a clip because he doesn't do it.
Nothing would work for audio.
But you see, you just got to imagine the most most excited
Elvin man.
He is just I mean, the more stories you hear about in the legend of him
and how insane he was grows and grows.
And then was it what podcast was it on this network of somebody
was playing clips from Mickey Rooney's like not made reality show?
Oh, double threat.
Oh, it's double.
OK, I miss this.
Yeah, there are crazy clips of you having like fits with his wife.
And I guess they shot a pilot or something or you can find on YouTube.
But it looks insane.
Wow.
Like I'm there's of course, when you see this, you go,
no one should put this on TV.
It should not be on TV.
This kind of the grab of like the post Osborne's like this.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'll do it now.
I do it.
Yeah.
And then that with all the stories for like Dana Carvey and Nathan Lane.
Right.
We're on a sitcom with him.
Yes.
Strangely produced out of the 30 Rock building.
Right.
Yes.
Typically being talk shows.
And for some reason, they're doing this Mickey Rooney sitcom there.
One of the boys are doing one of the boys.
He was like carrying a gun all the time or something.
Just like it seems like out of his mind.
And got to watch out for pickpockets within your own crew.
Yeah.
So the Mickey Rooney like any I've never heard
or I've never seen a bad clip of Mickey Rooney.
I've never heard a non entertaining story of Mickey Rooney.
Yeah.
Let me put it that way.
And he was on Eagle Heart.
Our pals, Weinberg worked with I don't think I've heard any tape.
But that's one of his final credits, I believe.
Right.
Because he died in 2014.
Wow.
Geez.
They got him right towards that.
I don't wish we'll have to ask if it's if we can share it publicly.
We will.
If not, we'll just laugh on our own time.
Uh huh.
But yes, you got some real and you know what you get in this moment
is Mickey Rooney and Mickey Mouse arm and arm.
It's delightful.
Hollywood's two great.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's this is this is maybe my favorite moment in any halftime show
other than the Prince guitar solo during Purple Rain.
Tied.
Yeah.
Prince solo and
Mickey Rooney.
Arm in arm.
Two Mickey and two mix.
Yeah.
Same thing.
Same same level of excitement for me.
You were all at the Prince one started and you're like, all right,
let's let's see what you got.
Can you top it?
Was it could a Mickey Rooney have been there for that?
Is he alive?
And when is Prince halftime?
2007.
Oh, yeah.
Then of course, easily you could have had Mickey Rooney
hand in hand with Prince during that halftime show.
So when they do like the big sheet and his like guitar looks like his dick,
looks like his dick.
And then the sheet comes down and Mickey Rooney is just there.
Prince disappears and Mickey Rooney is in his place in a little purple suit.
Give it up for my inspiration.
The could have been me with that.
If you're blue and you don't know where to go to.
It's going to be in the show.
That's what I put on the Ritz.
Yeah.
Put on the Ritz is in this one, right?
I think so.
I or it was in the last one.
It's a lot of them.
It's been in all of them.
Every halftime show, actually, if you look at it, every halftime show until
2005, the 80s, the Janet Jackson.
That's what you don't remember.
That's what Timberlake came out to do.
That's right.
Yeah.
Putting on the Ritz.
Mickey Rooney was there, too.
Yeah.
What is this filth?
Cover up.
Yeah.
He threw a towel over.
I reached my little hands up.
Get that Mickey Rooney was there to throw a towel on.
That was my supposed to be my areola jewelry.
Hey.
Yeah, he threw a fuck.
What did I get these for?
If not to be not to show them off on TV.
Yeah, they had to remove them from the building.
You're so upset.
Um, there is a medley of like Western songs.
You know, they do like Magnificent Magnificent
set Magnificent Seven.
The Ghost Riders in the Sky.
Ghost Riders in the Sky.
There's kind of an odd goofy singing.
Kind of odd.
I don't know how to even fully.
Like it sounds doesn't sound like something's wrong with goofy.
It's a pretty off goofy.
We've talked a lot about wrong Mickey.
Right.
OK, you asked.
But this is definitely a wrong goofy here.
Not to, you know, let's not clear out
the Western segment if we're not done with it.
But while we're talking about weird goofy,
I think you get some weird goofy in this during which.
Oh, that's right.
OK.
So as Jason said, Western stuff.
So there's a bunch of horses around,
which I recognize from park specials, like the type of horse that they would have
kind of weird upright with tiny T-Rex arms.
Yeah.
But then they move on
from Western stuff to like Indiana Jones and then like Flashdance.
But the horses are still there.
So it's a bunch of like dudes in yellow,
like glittery sleeveless shirts and then a bunch of horses.
And they are all dancing to this.
I'm turning it loose.
That sounds like Yosemite Sam.
Yeah.
Turning up loose or turning it loose.
I said turning up loose.
Yeah.
Weird, goofy, weird, goofy.
There's all like this also speed runs the history of Hollywood,
where it's like a lot of hooray for Hollywood Westerns.
And then immediately like
Indiana Jones and Flashdance.
And that's our current thing.
That's a lot.
That's kind of what a lot of stuff was like.
And like, yeah, as if they didn't feel
probably what it is, is they were mad at like that whole 60s, like
rebellious, graduate, easy, right?
That kind of stuff.
And like, yeah, but what about come on?
What about the spectacle, the razzle dazzle?
Well, it's sort of my memory in the early 2000s when they would do
montages, they would begrudgingly squeeze in
a shot from Lord of the Rings and the shot of Renee Zellweger.
And Catherine Zeta-Jones from the end of Chicago
doing the big musical number.
And that was like, and this is modern Hollywood.
And now let's wrap it up.
You know, and that's in the end.
And that when they're doing that, Chicago was 13 years prior.
We're still celebrating Chicago.
And that's as current like 2002, 2003.
That's as current as like history of Hollywood gets.
Like you can see when little snippets and then later on, it's like
there's one shot from Avatar.
Ten years are moved from that.
Babylon, that's what we really got.
Babylon ends the same.
If you've never seen it, Babylon ends the same way as the great movie, right?
You just suddenly get this montage of great movie moments.
And I've only seen that part.
I don't know what the rest of Babylon is.
I jumped right to the end because people made me aware
that Avatar is in Babylon.
Wow.
Really strange.
And then something else is it like Tron?
I think it's I think it's original Tron, maybe.
Oh, it's like a highlight reel.
Yeah, it's like a guy.
A lot of those montages Tron in Star Wars for like special effects.
Yeah.
And look what we can do now.
I think it's like somebody who is watching a movie
and whenever you're Babylon is set and it's like he can't even
imagine what's coming for him.
Tron, Avatar, that's pretty much it.
Oh, OK.
It's weird.
I don't I don't understand.
But anyway, if you like the great movie ride and you miss it, see Babylon.
I have heard that there is Toby McGuire plays an absolute maniac in Babylon.
And it's like, well, that's worth it to see.
Sure.
Yeah.
Big disappointment, though, is that they didn't like the great movie ride,
include good morning, Vietnam.
I think that for years riding that ride, I'm like, well,
that's one of the most important movies.
Yeah.
If you're going off of that, if you're if you're trusting
that you are in a history of film seminar when you're on that ride,
then like, OK, well, one of the primaries must be.
Do you think anyone has pitched a great movie ride movie
in the last few years?
Oh, kind of as multiverses?
Yeah.
Well, just because.
Because, yeah, Disney has so many different like I'm sure.
I think probably there's 50 projects all based on rides that they're having.
They're paying people to do something with, but they'll never make.
But especially post haunted mansion, it ruined it for everyone.
Yes.
But you think I wonder if there's any great movie ride
movies in the pipeline, if the Favreau Magic Kingdom
movie got made and was a huge hit.
Oh, well, and they're just like, then there would have been every.
Got to do every park.
Yeah, we got to do every ride, every park.
Yeah.
Is it so what is it?
It's people watching movies and then a gangster comes in.
No, I think it would.
Yeah.
If you're basing it on the ride or it's you know what?
It's the story of like what some of those Billy Crystal openings were,
where he like falls into the projector.
You just now you're in here in a madcap chase through all of Hollywood history.
And you know, some up and comer is going to be like in a tuxedo and go,
you ain't seen nothing yet.
You know, that's really probably everybody.
Everybody's gunning for the Jolson Park.
Yeah.
That's got to be a Jolson town.
Not half the Jolson, one half, not the necessarily the makeup of the Jolson
Park, but the that the iconic line.
Sebastian Stan is really gunning to be Jolson in great movie.
Ride the movie.
This I feel like you get a bunch of executives excited to be like,
and then you like you're in the Wizard of Oz, but then you're an alien.
And they'd be like, OK, I like what this sound.
I like the sound of this.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So maybe we'll maybe we'll pitch it.
But then what's the worst thing that could happen to you?
I don't know.
Say some ne'er do well coming along who likes to suck on jewels.
Well, that's obviously that the antagonist of the film.
And also following you through the movies.
Yeah.
Is this character in movie form?
You might have to go like it's the Western hijacker and the gangster hijacker.
Yeah, you might need to pick up a couple, pick up a couple of them
in the different movies that also goes with them.
And then the and then the finale of it is just the full ending of Wizard of Oz,
except our new characters are in it.
Yes.
Well, the real ending is you just watch clips from old movies.
Yeah.
But before that, it'll be like the climax of the right.
The plot tension is just Wizard of Oz.
It's just Wizard of Oz.
And now you've got Margaret Hamilton in there.
Now we got Margaret.
Yes.
We're staying in our fake Margaret Hamilton,
because the whole movie is going to be very deep, fake, heavy,
because you're going to need the old stars there.
But of course, most of them are dead.
So you'll have to deep fake it and they'll look a little creepy.
But that's part of it.
Yeah.
Part of the atmosphere of this movie.
That's what we love.
Filmgoers in the 20 20s love to see animated courses.
I will be happy to put the dots on my face and motion capture
Margaret Hamilton's character so they can use my performance
as a template for the Wicked Witch.
I'm not saying I'm going to be perfect, but I will study hard.
Geez.
Be careful.
Remember, you got to melt.
I know I have to melt and I will melt.
I understand that's going to be tough for them to track.
I'm willing to take an acting class to learn to melt the way Margaret did.
Because I want to get this right.
This is a good pitch, maybe.
It's probably a good pitch.
Yeah.
And it's of course a good pitch because Disney would be like,
oh, we own this already.
You know, it's just whatever.
Well, we own the idea.
What's the problem with most movies?
They aren't all movies.
That's right.
Well, not our movie.
We take you now to we could just send this clip to Disney right
right now and maybe they will take a meeting,
especially because we want to hear this guy's take on Margaret Hamilton's
performance.
We want to see it.
He'll act it out for you in the room and the guy in a diaper.
Yeah, he's really I like that guy.
Now the diaper guy will be part of it.
OK, because we're not interested if not.
There's so many Shirley temples on the field.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And then they're all wearing cowboy hats.
And at one point, you could see a crew guy rush by to give one of them
the cowboy hat again, your stuff it back on the on the curly wig.
There's a bunch of whips
dancing cheek to cheek.
Happens.
Then it all culminates in When You Wish Upon a Star,
which I think maybe the other one also did.
I think both of these have When You Wish Upon a Star and
Hooray for Hollywood.
And literally the two shows, the eight Disney's 87 and 84.
Yeah, they both end with When You Wish Upon a Star.
Wow.
You imagine just if today they just did the
the 2021 halftime show again.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's possible, I guess.
Another weird thing that kind of I notice.
So you got George Burns, you got Mickey Rooney.
But there were no like actresses from the Golden Age of Hollywood.
But then you do get the woman from Flashdance.
Do you do?
You get the real you mean the singer, the dancer.
Oh, I don't know.
Actually, there's a flash dance sequence.
I feel like it's the real I don't I wouldn't.
She gets a credit.
She get her name comes up on screen.
Oh, well, maybe.
OK.
I didn't get that.
The real flash dancer.
So are you you're saying, well, that's good.
Or are you saying I want one of the classic stars from?
Well, it was just kind of like, again, jumped decades forward.
Right.
So like, wait, 87 Flashdance would have come out.
If you could around then if you could plus this one up,
who would you like to have seen?
Well, I is Mae West still alive in 87?
Oh, good question.
I think long ago or but I'm not sure.
Or if Shirley Temple Black came out leading that army of Shirley Temple.
OK.
Mae West died in 1980.
Oh, not that long.
OK.
So Shirley Temple.
Shirley Temple, perhaps.
Leading the real Shirley Temple and army of temples.
That's going into Great Movie Ride, the movie.
It throws you off guard because at first you're like, huh?
But they're so adorable.
Yeah, right.
Yeah.
And then they start then they take those lollipops they got and quickly
sharpen them, stab them into your eyes.
They're actually have xenomorph.
That's part of the great movie ride, the ride or the movie.
That's a cool backstory.
So the xenomorph that you see in the ride you don't realize is Shirley Temple.
Exactly.
Yes.
Wow.
There was at some point a shape shifting.
Shirley Temple took a xenomorph as a husband
and they have alien babies.
And they made the opening of that's real.
They met at the opening of Disney and James Doody.
Yep, that's right.
They were happily married.
That's in the movie.
Yeah, we showed the wedding in the movie.
The very ending of this thing.
All right.
And here's how do you go out other than.
84, exact same thing.
It's also fake Mickey.
They just they just got Disney is getting lazy at this point.
If there's a general sense that we are not excited about the Super Bowl
halftime show, maybe it's because Disney showed up and cranked out the same thing twice.
Yeah, sure.
They brought Mickey Rooney one time, but Mickey can't make up
for the creative deficiencies.
Yeah, I know.
I agree.
It's very lazy.
I guess, yeah, we're not we're not into the golden age of 90s Disney yet.
Late 80s Disney.
So I'll blame it on some of that, maybe.
Yeah, yeah.
I think they let the entire 1980s pass
without ever having a performer who was popular in the 1980s.
There's no Madonna.
There wasn't Michael Jackson yet.
There is not Springsteen for many years.
Certainly, there's no prince.
Chubby Checker 88.
I mean, he probably did.
He must.
He probably did like return of the twist in 86.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And of course, 89 Elvis Presto.
Elvis Presto Elvis Magician Elvis Presto.
The Elvis Magician is the biggest thing to file away for Super Bowl halftime.
We can't do it now, but I want to do.
Oh, no, it's why I'm glad we got this guidance from the listeners.
Just tackle the Disney one.
Yes.
And so that we can let Elvis Presto breathe.
OK, I just want to say the name of it, though.
1950s rock and roll Bebop bamboozled in 3D.
That's the name of the show.
1989 bamboozled Bebop bamboozled.
And this is because this is the one where you went to get 3D glasses.
Yes, you can watch 3D halftime show.
What could that have meant on your like fuzzy television?
Your fuzzy four by three TV in 1989.
But all I know is that it's one of the first songs is Rock This Town by the Stray Cats.
So we will do it.
Oh, well, I was wrong.
One song from the 80s.
That's true.
All right.
The songs are played.
Footloose is played.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, boy.
I didn't realize I walked into Stray Cats.
That's right.
Bebop.
You were Bebop bamboozled.
I just got Bebop bamboozled in 3D.
That's another show Jason is going to do in a day.
Bebop bamboozled.
And then 3D in that one means three diapers.
The performer credited on screen during the flash,
it's Marine Jahan, who was Jennifer Beals body double for the dancing sequences.
OK, that's something.
That's something.
Some legitimacy.
Yeah.
Wow.
I'd rather have seen Tallulah Bankhead do a performance like that in that show.
There we go.
Now we're talking.
She died in like the 60s, so she was not around for that.
She's also on Campo around my Instagram.
I don't think I even I know exactly what Tallulah Bankhead is.
She was on I Love Lucy a few times, at least once.
Don't get mad at me.
She was a villain.
She was the black widow on the 60s Batman.
OK, I thought she was a Batman person.
And she just was one of those with a smoke and I drink and I'm all over.
Like she had the deep voice and she was funny.
You've seen her probably.
You've seen Miss Bankhead.
You've seen her.
You love her.
You know, I get to know her really well whenever we get to the Tallulah
Bankhead deep dive.
I'm sure it's not too far away.
Right around the corner.
Birthday is coming up in honor.
She would have been 160 years old.
OK, so we take you now to I'd say them, you know,
interior, at least in terms of amount of clips, I pulled the main attraction
of this episode.
And I think one of the one of the things fueling the desire for us to tackle
Disney's halftime shows, that being what they perpetrated
at Super Bowl 25 in 1991.
Bizarre.
Yeah.
This one.
Oh, yeah.
Perverse.
Very strange.
Extremely.
They're back in Tampa near Disney World.
Giants versus Bills.
This one, 1991, is the famous Whitney Houston
Star Spangled Banner, probably still one of the biggest moments
of music in Super Bowl history.
And the important context that that provides, you know, there was the
they had the onus basically to do this extremely heartfelt, elevated,
like the greatest ever Star Spangled Banner, because we were in the thick
of the Gulf War at this time.
And that colors now while this now, while Whitney Houston is this,
you know, well remembered, one of the greatest moments of her career,
that it kind of does encapsulate that time in a meaningful way.
What Disney did, perhaps less so, but we will give it its due.
You know, this will never get portrayed in a movie like the Whitney Houston
one was recently.
But we'll we'll give it a full tribute now.
So, I mean, in this.
All right.
I think the the first person on screen
probably explains this, you know, even better than we can.
Ladies and gentlemen, boy, do we have a show for you.
And it's an all kids cast on behalf of the 2000 children performing tonight.
We'd like to dedicate this halftime show to all the servicemen and women
who are protecting us in the Persian Gulf.
And now live from Tampa Stadium, it's the first ever
all kids Super Bowl halftime show.
All kids, all kids.
OK, I got a got a bit of a qualm right at the top of this.
Protecting us in from in the Persian Gulf.
What exactly go ahead.
What were we being protected from?
Because ostensibly, it was the people of Kuwait being protected
from Saddam Hussein.
But I don't think I realized that they tried the protecting our freedom
bullshit during the first call for.
We're you know, we're next.
Kuwait's one and America's two.
We're going to send a jump away.
Yeah, so, yeah, we know
they're going to start sending those scuds and Jason.
What's important is that you just shut up and watch all these kids.
That's what's important.
OK, I hate to be rude, but that's what this little kid.
That is.
Yeah.
And you know, and we'll get we'll get some stock footage
of the of the troops in their desert fatigue.
They're there.
Why, they're the star at some point.
But first, we kick off with this kid, this kid in the giant
like Wide World of Sports headset in the ABC.
You forget that they used to wear blazers with the ABC logo.
Yeah, yeah.
We're like, you know, like like it.
You looked like you worked at the ABC Steakhouse.
Now people don't people just go on TV with no blazers.
You don't even know who they were.
I know these are the days.
Imagine being this kid, this, you know, he does it.
There's a varying degree.
I don't want to like knock these children.
And I won't knock this first one, especially because imagine like, OK,
you are now introducing the Super Bowl halftime show.
All right.
Get ready.
100 million people are watching you kid.
You've got a block of dialogue that you have to do in one shot.
He is.
He gets gets it all in.
He's good.
Will I get closer to knocking other kids?
Perhaps.
So this one, you know, you kind of build to it.
But I guess I have less notes on this and more clips.
Basically, this is all there's a big small world overlay here,
which makes it one of the first Disney halftime shows to like
not in a big way to one of their theme park attractions.
Right.
They also performed.
It's a small world in the 77 one.
So we're repeating ourselves once again.
But what they didn't have was a big set that resembles small worlds.
And so you get your, you know, your Mary Blair, your Raleigh Crump, whatever.
I forget everybody worked on that.
But you at least get some small world aesthetics a little bit, if kind of like
haphazard, temporary, cheap, half falling apart.
But anyway, that's that's what you should picture
is that there are in most of these shots small world vibes in general.
But they quickly make good on the promise of all kids
as we follow.
Basically, I think as it starts, it's all boy football players
and all girl cheerleaders, OK, hundreds and hundreds.
And we go to this.
the fact that you are in Georgia.
You want to get a cutie to pet.
Yeah.
What?
So all kids have time show.
All right.
Well, I assume that they won't be singing mildly sexual lyrics.
Maybe the conservatives are right.
They were right then.
They just missed it.
They were they were way late.
Isn't this worse than the than the half time than the seven tenths
of a second of a nipple?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Cutie to pet.
These are children and so many of them, a thousand children.
Also, this song stinks.
I kind of believe with apologies to Jason,
I kind of believe that no good song was written in the first half
of the 20th century.
I think this is but this is a piece of shit.
You can't use this song.
I know, but I'm just saying like that there's still they're still playing
a grandma here.
You know what grandma like is that football hero song?
Because I looked it up.
But did Disney make this up and they didn't.
That's a that's always been around for a long time.
And it was the subject even of a Popeye cartoon.
They did a cartoon.
They did a cartoon with this title and using the song.
I bet that's a better cartoon than this halftime show.
There's nowhere to go but up.
This song is from 1933.
It is now 1991.
And it is in the Super Bowl halftime show.
How does this map is this how far back that 60 years?
What's 60 years from now?
I mean, I wouldn't put it past him that there's songs from the 1960s
in a current halftime show.
Although they did level up.
We haven't had McCartney and Rolling Stones for for a while.
Right.
I believe Usher will be primarily playing songs.
That's true.
Recorded since 1995.
Yes, he has.
Yes.
I don't know.
He might do a little, you know, one of Fred Waring
and his Pennsylvanian's classic hits.
Did you know growing up, did you know anybody who was actually in the Pennsylvania?
I just came across this phrase for the first time right now,
and I'm trying to stay present and focus on what we're doing here.
But I'm like, well, I guess I'm spending the rest of the day learning about Fred Waring.
Oh, dear.
Come in.
I discovered a new musical artist you should be hip to.
He's the cat's meow.
And so are his Pennsylvanians.
He died in 84 at 84 in State College, Pennsylvania, where Penn State is.
So a rare, a roaring intro of a
dead old man's song.
This is awful.
And then who joins this same number?
But once again, Minnie Mouse.
Happens here.
First of all, OK, so I believe that who is on stage with her is
football great Warren Moon,
thus immediately betraying the notion of an all kids halftime show.
Yes, right.
Yeah.
True.
And presumably it's not a kid in the mini custom.
Really goes out the window towards the end of the performance.
The old kids premise.
But like with a cute little wink that you could tell someone was very pleased with themselves.
They're kids.
They're typically kids.
But then he like he bends down when she says cutie to pet and like, what's happening?
Where are you going?
And then but then luckily, it's just it's just that he like
gets a bunch of children around him.
What is this?
What's happening?
Why did Disney do this?
I don't know.
Really?
We're putting this out there.
We're going to get the DeSantis of the world.
A lot of red meat.
We know Ron listens.
Well, now that he must be so excited to like go back to being a big fish in a small pond.
Back to basics.
Yeah.
Now he can like I found what I think is a penis shape in the tree of life.
He can just poke and prod them.
He's just walking around Animal Kingdom with binoculars,
trying to find phallic shapes and all of all of the carvings.
Do you know that all across Disney's theme parks,
there are special rooms in which people are allowed to whip out their genitalia.
Those are called bathrooms.
I yes, I know they are.
And isn't that I say everybody should hold it until they're off property and out of our state.
Or there'll be a priest or a nun supervising you when you go into these rooms.
These toilets don't even contain holy water.
Anyway, check out the giant convention of child pageants
that is currently going on at a Marriott down the road.
Good old fashioned fun.
Has he ever judged a child pageant?
Do you think Ron?
He's on the way.
He should.
Yeah.
He had a tendency to party with the high schoolers he used to teach.
Oh, that's right.
He was one of those guys.
Yeah.
One of those.
I'm going to say one of those cool guys.
One of those cool guys.
That number, though, in my high school, too.
Did you ever party with a teacher?
No, and they didn't really come back after.
Did I say we had a student teacher after we graduated?
Come watch wrestling with us.
It was nothing weird.
Did we did we like fight with wrestle him in the front yard afterward?
Yeah, a little bit.
I think you really jumped the gun with that.
There was nothing weird.
If I say this, whatever else I say, in the middle of it, I realized it was a little weird.
I mean, he was 22 years old.
We were 18 and we were like doing our fake our backyard wrestling.
It wasn't so bad.
Did you make a point of not inviting any 17 year olds knowing there was this possibility?
No, maybe one or two of us were 17 when we graduated.
Yeah, I think there was one or two.
Wait, so were you 17 and you were 22 year old?
No, I was 18 when I graduated.
Very good.
OK.
Yeah.
In 2002.
All right.
Well, I hope I sincerely hope this student teacher checked IDs.
I was 17 for the first couple of months of college.
And I definitely say the little scratch.
I'll love buying that child ticket on the bus system.
What child?
Is it a child?
No, I didn't know.
No, no.
The the the child bus ticket under 18.
Oh, they call that a child ticket.
Or they like under eight.
I mean, you know what he pictured.
You're wearing like a little Lord Fauntleroy outfit.
Yes.
This is my mother is on the bike of the bus, I believe.
Can I have one child ticket, please?
Take me down to the common.
They need the new adventure of the daredevil and Batman.
I am but a nine year old boy.
Hmm.
Well, he is lisping.
Some of my classmates are drinking beer and I'm afraid.
That's more of an Edwin.
Well, he'll be in the Hollywood salute to Hollywood.
And he's on CampoRum on Instagram.
Oh, I imagine.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, Disney would have done this in 1991.
Why isn't Edwin?
Oh, yeah.
I just say let's let's get a deep fake Edwin
on one of these future Super Bowls
for like doing something.
I don't know what it is.
Sure.
Well, you got to go viral with these ads.
It's so like, oh, my God, the Super Bowl actually brought back Edwin
to a leap with Edwin for some reason.
Wow.
Do a leap recreated the iconic.
What?
I love to laugh.
There you go.
Yeah.
I love to laugh.
Sexy.
Finally, like a real sexy version of it.
But you still see the simmering sex potential.
We all knew it was there.
Yes.
You're still sampling Ed's voice.
Let me make sure there's not more of this mini routine.
I don't remember where it goes.
Hmm.
Wow.
Good thing I played that.
Yeah, no, they need to hear that.
Like that love boat clip earlier.
The audience needed to hear that.
I'm not sure exactly what's OK.
Well, this one I know I need to hear because we
that's kind of the girls routine.
But then we get to the boys, the boy players.
No, not just boy players, boy referees
joined by Chip and Dale.
Uh huh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's kind of every team.
Yeah, kind of does can't touch us and then just starts listing like all the teams.
Yeah.
Every to make sure they're all represented.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I also that is Chip and Dale in referee uniforms
all and then they're all doing the running man.
Yeah, it's really something.
The only plus up to that is that I don't know if we mentioned
Chip and Dale are in that one with fake goofy
and they're wearing like chaps, which is really funny.
It's like they're naked except for chaps.
And I'm sorry, I missed that.
Yeah, yeah.
If they had those outfits doing this, it would be the ultimate, I think,
because they're just wearing referee shirts.
What do you think this this stuff did in general to like the perception of Disney?
And like, I mean, like for our parents,
because like now it's I feel like it's so much more acceptable that like
you've got like a regular life and then you like going to theme parks.
Also, this I think is one of these this is like one of these wedges where like
I like I think you might watch this and think I am never going to Disney World
for as long as I live.
I think this did some damage and then our podcast helped heal.
Yes, that's what we're doing.
Weak at a time.
I think that these things were such clusterfucks
that ninety nine point nine percent of everyone who watched them doesn't remember them.
There's no memory of these whatsoever.
Once in a while, somebody finds them on YouTube, but there's almost no person
like, oh, you know, it was great that that all child halftime show
where Chip and Dale did the MC Hammer song like nobody remembers that.
I don't think any halftime show was ever complemented until Michael Jackson.
Yes, right.
I don't think there was anyone ever had a kind word to say.
You think that's correct?
Other than maybe like, I don't know, Andy Williams wife.
Good job, dear.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe certain performers got a compliment, but yeah, I don't know.
I think you're almost giving these specials too much credit.
Yeah.
You say that made people not want to go to the park.
What year is Michael Jackson one?
Lately, ninety three.
So we're we are close to it.
I think we are watching one of the causes of it.
I think I think we must be like the least like it's within the two.
That's like, OK, we need a change.
So at this point, we head into what I will call the hero medley.
Yeah.
And I don't know how much to tip
who we're who we're going to see midway through.
You know, I'll just all right.
I'll I'll just play it.
I'll let him introduce himself.
Mm hmm.
Here he comes.
Get ready.
And however, when you loud,
now we get to the truth.
True.
Yeah, that's the real legos.
But now the real heroes are Bad gusts.
We are in the Middle East, protection for all of us.
So, hey, basically what happened there visually is the field was swarming
with children and then they all clear out of the way as if Moses has entered.
They all part and like bow deferentially.
They all take a knee, ironically.
And then there's this big sweeping shot that pushes into just one child.
Now there's only one child on the stage and the most like blonde bang,
bowl cut children of the corn hair.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, it's the kind of way.
Yeah, this would this it would make sense if you saw like a hundred kids
all with the same haircut.
It's our town now.
Just wait, let me let me play his little dialogue again.
Or actually the end of the song.
I was watching this with Aaron and Aaron said,
you know what this kid is?
This is real life butters.
This is an actual alive human butters,
which because if you like, you know, butters sing sometimes,
if you leave me now, you take away the big.
And then and then is what like this?
We are celebrating all our tubes.
It's like the sweetest, most sincere, too sincere for his own good.
Poor real butters.
Wow.
Real butters.
Yeah, yeah.
That's cute.
Anyway, great job, little butters.
It's again, this thing is just so full of surprises.
And the way it zooms in, you're like, who is it?
A big star?
No, just some kid.
Some kid singing Win Beneath Fire than an eagle.
It's something.
And then but if you thought that the star power had peaked
with real butters, just wait till you see what they got next.
Ladies and gentlemen, the president of the United States.
Good evening from the White House to everyone in the sunshine.
And around the world enjoying this wonderful game.
I can fly higher than an eagle.
Not going to do it.
And then and it zooms out and Barbara's sitting next to him.
And then that shot, I don't think she knew it had cut to her.
But her eyes just seemed like very wide, like she seems.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, she gives a real you're right.
She gives a real side eye like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Everything I become be nice.
You're America's mother, you're America's mother.
Be calm, be sweet, be America's mother.
Hide your true self.
From the public before game.
What a pleasure it is to say hello to all the young people on the field tonight.
Looking at you, it's easy to see why America can count on a bright and hopeful future.
Well, that's right.
I know we're proud of our boys and all the ways they'll make America better.
Oh, God, I really wish he.
Yeah.
Hey, kid performers, I hope you better learn the geography of the Middle East,
because in 10, 10 to 15 years, some of you might be visiting.
You get to go.
What little butters was he was George H.
W.
He was a pilot.
Am I wrong?
Maybe something like that.
I just was hoping he would like actually parachute onto the field or something.
That's really where I'm getting out of that pilot.
MIA on November 22nd, 1963, all sorts of different.
I know.
Yeah, yeah.
So I just yeah, it's too bad they phone that in.
There was a video.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That is a video.
The one the shot from the very much like the beginning of Cartoon All Stars
to the rescue, which we covered on Club Three.
Right.
Yeah.
You know, who did show up, though, is a child from every state
whose parent is abroad in the Middle East.
Oh, really?
And they're.
Yeah.
That that a lot of clarifiers.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, I believe he was.
Yes, he was a gunman or a grunman grum.
Oh, anyway, is grunman a type of plane?
I think so.
OK.
Yeah.
You can't be a grunman.
No, you can't be a plane.
This isn't Disney's planes.
You think this is Disney's planes?
Yeah, he flew a torpedo bomber.
Wow.
So, yeah, he could have like jumped out of a plane and gone to the Super Bowl.
That's what I was saying.
That's what I'm getting at.
Yeah.
Well, that's why that's one way that his son outdid him
with that cool landing on the.
Yeah, it's right.
The suit.
Yeah.
A great ceremony.
I just labeled this one Songs of Unity.
I don't know exactly what it is.
Is this where characters?
Oh, yeah.
Now we got characters in the picture.
We're getting basically we're getting Epcotty.
Like they clearly went and got all the Epcot costumes because at some point
you see Winnie the Pooh in Canadian garb.
Don't forget that that in Epcot rules, Winnie the Pooh is Canadian.
And like a Mountie outfit.
Yeah.
Which I love.
That's what is there not to like about it.
It always makes me smile.
Yes.
What is there?
I mean, I guess any outfit Pooh has on is good.
Yeah.
But that a Mountie one, because he also has to know pants.
He's just wearing the Mountie jacket with the hat, I believe.
I think that's right.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Just a jacket.
No pants.
I think he is.
Yeah.
That's great.
Which is not how the Mounties do it.
As far as I know, yes, that nudity was received more quietly
at the halftime show than others.
Dudley Do-Right has pants on.
Oh, yes.
Mickey's out.
Mickey's America, of course.
He's waving back and forth.
Bicentennial Mickey.
Take that out of store.
And.
Now, that is not By the World of Coke, but it's a song that was used, right?
Yeah.
The lyrics were changed for By the World of Coke,
and this special is produced by Coca-Cola.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
Yes, right.
Oh, right.
Yes.
Later.
Yes, somebody is presented by Coca-Cola.
Right.
So we get now the full small world set is out.
And now all the kids is no more football kids and cheerleader kids.
They're all representing.
We got our like, you know, the like little Swiss girl outfits.
Everybody is a small world doll now.
Basically, yes.
Living dolls, you see.
None of this is like actively awful.
It's just kind of inane.
I mean, it's good to see the outside a small world on a football field.
Yeah, floats.
It's not the best representation of it I've ever seen.
But just for the novelty of it, they've constructed.
It's a small world on a football field at halftime.
Yes.
I can't be mad at that.
It is funny that two years before this, they opened a Hollywood themed theme park.
And it's like, oh, I already did too many Hollywood halftime shows.
What do we get?
Small world.
Yeah.
There's international conflict.
We ever done that before?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
That always works.
Should we check a tape?
Nah.
Well, and it's what you got to like about this end of the next one,
which is like recreations of theme park rides on the Super Bowl field.
But before we get to that,
here's where we're like starting to get the right idea.
This is what I'm saying about the gradient from marching band up to pop stars is like we are.
This what is about to happen is by far the most relevant thing
that has happened at a Super Bowl halftime show ever.
Right.
And yet it is they have to wait.
They're pretty sidelined.
And it's about as embarrassing for them as it could be.
And here it is.
And now to honor our armed forces, children,
Coca-Cola proudly presents the new Kids on the Block.
Yeah, I armed forces kids.
I know that you're upset that your father is in Iraq.
Yeah, there's no way to explain what's happening there and why he's there.
But Coca-Cola has arranged the new kids on the block for you.
Yeah, that's like I guess it's like Bob Hope entertaining the troops
in some way.
New Kids on the Block entertaining the troops kids.
Yeah, makes sense.
Kids, you do need to get to Tampa.
So figuring out travel arrangements.
But then like the who they have to because like, all right, it's in 1891.
They are very popular.
The halftime show could have just been ladies and gentlemen,
New Kids on the Block, and then they do 12 minutes.
But they hadn't figured that out yet.
So they like, no, you can't just cut to the new kids on the block and that's it.
There's got to be a bunch of razzle dazzle crap.
They have to be performing in front of a bunch of child clowns with big round
rouge on their cheeks.
And then like, you know, at some point, they're who's the Disney like hen character?
Oh, is it Clara?
Is Clara the hen?
Is Claire Belle cow?
Yeah.
And horse, horse collar.
But I know you're taught the hen with the bonnet.
Is it Clara cluck?
Clara cluck.
Yes.
All right.
Clara cluck.
Well, at some point, well, they're all busting moves.
A hen and a bonnet comes out and kind of like dances a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Go, Jordan.
Why?
Why do you do this to them?
We can't.
We don't have Clara cluck at the ready.
And yeah, Clara cluck performed at the Super Bowl.
But like Katy Perry, it's the shark that has the shark, of course, the iconic.
Well, that was good.
Left shark was good.
Left shark was, you know, leaned on a little too hard for a while.
I don't disagree with that.
But I'm just saying this could have been a moment where it was like the new kids
version of the left shark.
Yes.
She also had the big lion she was right.
I always thought that was very cool.
I don't remember that.
I don't remember much of her halftime show, despite seeing her in concerts
several years later where I think she was still it was an awkward amount of time
enough that I liked that left shark was part of the show.
Ladies and gentlemen, left shark.
If I was at her Vegas residency and left shark came out, I would lose my mind.
Oh, yeah.
I know we never saw.
And of course, the big shit.
I know I was excited.
I want to see it.
Like left shark pops out of the big.
She should have gifted you to that big toilet for the sphere residency.
That's true.
Yeah.
You should have had some sort of toilet song.
That stage was so minimal.
There's like nothing on it.
I think you could have used a big toilet.
Yeah.
You could just lowered it.
It could have just been the seat.
The stage could have just been the toilet seat at the sphere.
We went from Brian Eno, whatever.
They could have projected that like the walls of the sphere were the walls of the bowl
and they flush at some point.
You see water coming down the sides.
They haven't turned sphere into a toilet yet.
Oh, who's the artist to do that?
You think that'd be like if the if there was a sphere residency
by the Jerky Boys.
Yeah, that might be coming up.
That's that's where they're heading.
There are not seemingly that many bands signing up for this thing.
It's weird, even though every even though every week
there's a new article by the New York Post saying so and so is considering doing.
That's right.
OK, the Jerky Boys are considering a residency.
We're hovering around Jerky Boys.
We're excited.
And I didn't do anything wrong also.
OK, then we get
don't worry, the big popular band is not allowed to perform
without a bunch of embarrassing stuff for long because a bunch of kids run out on the field.
And I do love the directing here, where as it kind of pans to the left,
big character balloons inflate.
What do you get excited to see the inflatable?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
There's this zoom that we're just going to have to post because like, all right,
like a live butters is back.
And then there's this zoom in unexplained to just this one child.
It was so awkward.
Like Elfelfa.
Yeah, yes, absolutely.
I don't know with a very tall Alice from Alice in Wonderland.
I don't know if she's very tall necessarily compared to the child.
Yes.
Towers above this child.
Yeah, I don't.
He's got so many.
He's got like lots of flowers on his.
I don't know what he is.
I need to.
He looks really.
He looks as scared as any of us would have been to be.
Have a shot of us at the Super Bowl.
Yeah.
Jason, did you have that outfit as a child?
Our neighbors were distant Habsburg relatives and they gave us hand me down jackets.
Or that's the outfit you wore to fool the bus driver into giving you the child.
I need I need this.
I need the extra dollar in my pocket for this three minute bus ride from the hill
down the hill to the center of town.
It was a dollar.
It was a dollar or two.
I forget.
All I need to do is create a false identity.
Look, I'm wearing a bow tie.
Only children and very old men wear bow ties.
Have you heard?
Have you heard of our gang?
Well, I mean it,
but I'm young.
If you just if you just quickly taken made a cowlick just like
squirted some Gatorade in your hair and then.
All right.
And then I think you get a little by now.
Real Mickey is doing.
They are not going to weird screeching and correct Mickey.
And a nice message from Mickey Mouse to close it out.
And thanks to our armed forces everywhere.
Real Mickey, they got him everywhere.
So hooray for Hollywood.
And then a few years later, thanks to our armed forces everywhere.
This feels impossible that they would allow today
that they would allow Mickey to come anywhere near a military industrial.
Yes.
Let's keep those prophets coming, boys.
The war machine must roll.
Well, also, if they had a clip of
Joe Biden, Dr.
Joe Biden saying like, well, we want to thank one and welcome everyone.
This is half the stadium would be like, ah,
yeah, yes, yes.
Their eyes would turn white.
There's like they're foaming at the mouth.
Yes.
Different time, different type.
We were all we were we were united back then
or just didn't have the information we needed to not be united or something.
We were united in apathy toward these halftime.
Yeah, mainly that.
Yeah.
And I'm going to go take a piss, you know, make some more dip for those ruffles.
That's that's that.
So that's that's kind of like in you could say one of the craziest,
maybe the craziest one Disney produced, one of the weirdest ones.
And let me add to the strangeness of this by saying what I just found out,
which is that this did not air.
Why?
Golf, at least not as it was occurring,
because we were in the full swing of the Gulf War.
There was so much concern over Gulf War updates instead,
at least in the majority of the country.
They cut to Peter Jennings providing a Gulf War update.
And this was aired maybe after the Super Bowl.
Hey, stick around to see the halftime show,
which we've been sitting on for an hour and a half.
Well, they buried it.
They buried this and maybe rightfully so.
And even then it wasn't aired everywhere because a lot of the affiliates
had an obligation to play a new sitcom, which I think was called Davis's Rules.
Oh, yeah.
I just saw what is who's on Davis?
I don't know.
What was the day?
I should have.
Why don't I have this information?
It's Randy Quaid.
Oh, Randy Quaid.
OK, I did see that.
And Jonathan Winters?
Yes, I sent Andrew Grissom a picture of Davis Rules three days ago.
That's what it's from.
I sent Andrew Grissom so much crap, I can't even remember.
Keep keeping straight something I sent him days ago.
In this show, Jonathan Winters plays Gunny Davis.
Gunny Davis is not Anthony Kiedis's father.
Blackie, damn it.
Blackie, damn it is not Gunny Davis.
Gunny.
Yeah, Blackie, damn it is not Gunny Davis.
OK.
How many days ago?
Five days ago, I sent Andrew Grissom
a picture and a description on Facebook of Davis Rules.
No, not Davis's Rules, Davis Rules.
Davis Rules.
And then he said that he's on a Jonathan Winters deep dive lately.
So that's a good timing that I sent that.
Well, it's a good sign that Andrew should turn around,
stop going too deep or you'll end up at Davis Rules.
And I said, did you stumble on Davis Rules?
He said, I did not.
I was mainly watching talk show bits.
How many episodes were made of Davis Rules?
29.
Two seasons.
This is a two season show.
Patricia Clarkson is on it.
Bonnie Hunt is on it.
Yeah.
Sitcom royalty.
Everybody probably made a million dollars.
A young Giovanni Ribisi.
Yeah.
Parker Selfridge himself
cut his teeth on Davis Rules.
Debra Jo Rupp as well.
Who's Debra Jo Rupp?
From That 70's Show.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Well, he's just called Vanni Ribisi.
That's a name I can't make heads or tails of.
Vanni, Vanni.
There's a Cranston in here, I think, too.
Yep.
Davis Rules, Cranston and Davis Rules.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
He looks like Alan Thicke there.
Yeah.
Kind of like 90s dad here.
He could do a great like Thicke, Alan Thicke type character, too.
Oh, sure.
Well, there was another show to finish.
OK, so that is that.
And we are heading towards the finish line.
Something that I should have said at the beginning.
This is an executive decision I made.
Put this blame on me if you wanted to hear about the Millennium
halftime show, which is the what?
This is the last Disney Super Bowl halftime show.
Super Bowl 34 in 2000 called Tapestry of Nations,
much like the actual show that disturbed Epcot guests for around the Millennium
times.
We covered this kind of thoroughly in our second gate episode.
Walt Disney World Millennium Celebration.
Go look that up.
Also the episode where we met and fell in love with Leonardo Columbus.
A lot of fun in that one.
So if you were excited to hear a lot more about khaki,
clad Phil Collins singing Two Worlds from Tarzan,
I think we also talked about it with Kevin Purger in Tarzan Rocks.
If you're not happy about this, if there's some major component
of Tapestry of Nations that you know we didn't talk about on the show,
please harass us at our homes and we will make sure that we come to our house.
We'll get we'll give our addresses at the very end.
And we'll make sure that we cover this properly.
But that was why I felt like maybe kind of like covered territory,
as technically is the last thing that we're talking about.
And to segue into that.
So this happens in 1991, technically doesn't air in the allotted time.
Kind of weird and embarrassing.
They're aging it down with new kids, but humiliating them in the process.
The next year, winter magic ice skating from Brian Boitano
and Dorothy Hamill on the tiniest rinks you've ever seen.
Gloria Estefan does admittedly elevate that that performance.
But here's what happens.
Winter magic is definitely the last of the of the razzle dazzle crap era.
And with the reputation of Super Bowl halftime shows at this point,
having become, you know, a bunch of nonsense for Grandma Fox,
which is not airing the Super Bowl that year, strikes back and airs a
I don't know if they were shooting it live,
but at least like exactly when the halftime show started,
Fox aired an original in living color anti halftime show,
which trounced them in the ratings, like as so many people went over
to in living color, huge success finally showed the NFL.
We can't do, you know, now a salute to the general idea of children.
So that is why the next year they just got right.
Who is the biggest celebrity on the planet?
Michael Jackson, Michael Jackson will do this.
That adds fuel to the fire of that halftime show.
The Michael Jackson, at least that year of the Super Bowl remains,
I believe, or did for a long time in the top 10
programs ever aired on television ratings.
Wow.
It was so mass.
I mean, all the Super Bowls are huge and were huge.
But I think that one especially sticks around.
Let them know this is what we need to do from now on.
That having been said,
it's not as if they immediately were able to book a big stable of artists,
because the next year was like kind of a mix of country people.
Yeah.
And basically, they think the NFL,
they wanted Michael Jackson ratings and Michael Jackson style fame.
But maybe they didn't like dealing with Michael Jackson.
Sure.
And they were concerned about some of the stuff and the crutch grabbing
and the fact and that when the show started, he came out and just didn't
just stood still for over a minute.
And everyone was like, is this a problem?
Is he dying?
What is it?
And it was just building tension.
But if you watch it now, it is weird.
How much of his 12 minutes are silence.
So anyways, what they set out to do, they're like,
what if we can kind of split the difference?
We get some stars,
but really if what we go for is MTV style, you know, it's like,
where, you know, it's, it's like a concert and it's kind of edgy and hip,
but we don't have to get like the ego of a Michael Jackson site.
And maybe Disney would still want to help us out with this.
And that's what leads us to the immortal 1995 Indiana Jones
and the Temple of the Forbidden Eye.
Oh, yeah.
Half time show.
If the small world one teased it, this one is just fully the entire half time
show is the promotion of a new ride.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's wild.
Which I have watched this a number of times,
but I always forget the one big moment and who the two stars are.
Yeah.
Because there's just so much spectacle happening.
There was it really confused.
I definitely watched this as it aired.
I was so thrilled that they were being so excited for that ride.
Yeah.
Just a big ride promo.
And that's the half time show.
I don't think I knew who the performers were at the time.
And truly it is like,
I mean, a lot of it is literally Indiana Jones and Marion are lost.
Yeah.
A bunch of crap happening around them.
Now, definitely we talked about some bits of this in one of our first episodes,
literally one of our first, which was the Indiana Jones adventure.
If we've kind of talked about something before, I like to go back and check.
What did we say about it?
It's not double up.
But boy, was that a long time ago.
And one thing I'm not willing to do is listen to the first episodes.
I've got older ones now, but the first ones I am petrified of.
We just have not something.
Right.
That's just like, I'm not so insecure that I can't listen to
older episodes or myself talk or something.
But the first ones, no desire.
Yeah, I don't want to.
Well, that's why we have to redo them.
I guess so.
Yeah.
Keep pounding that drum boys.
I'm just saying, you know, I don't want to listen to them either.
There's some drum pounding in this.
What a coincidence.
There is.
I say drum pounding, but I can't tell if they're actually playing
the big ceremonial drums.
That's a question.
I think we do still have some live music here, attempts at live music,
because there are some errors with the music.
Yeah.
That's my that's my clue there.
So this is at the end of January, 1995.
This one is happening in Miami, Joe Robbie Stadium, Chargers versus 49ers.
After everybody calms down from the Kathie Lee Gifford national anthem,
then this this show occurs.
End of January, Temple of Forbidden Eyes opening at Disneyland, March 4th, 1995.
So this is America's introduction to the Forbidden Eye,
to Mara, to not looking well into Mara's eye.
I'm sure everyone clocked all of that.
Oh, yeah.
Held it for their next vacation.
Let's just start at how they started it.
And it kind of after some like Indiana Jones pre-roll,
they cut to like a temple guard guy, bald guy.
And this happens.
Bring to me the trophy.
This is still guy.
Yeah, the temple is rising up behind them.
It's a really it's a great cut to from this guy like bring the line.
He's got like skulls on big sticks.
And then he and then he just looks so bored.
Yeah.
Immediately.
I like it's like he forgot that he would still be on.
And, you know, in lieu of the, you know,
readers of Lost Ark Idol, the trophy he's discussing is the Super Bowl trophy.
This is the literal is the Vince Lombardi trophy.
Yeah.
Which I was refreshing my memory.
What's up with Vince Lombardi?
And he did wear a hat that was kind of like Indiana Jones's hat.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's cool.
There you go.
Yeah.
So it really it's actually very clean if you think about it.
And yeah, that's sort of the story here.
Indiana Jones is in the Temple of Mara,
which is sprouted up in the middle of Joe Robbie Stadium.
Perfect.
And he is trying to get back the real Super Bowl trophy.
Yeah.
It's the pinnacle of it, really.
In my mind.
And as far as you're saying, what your definition is of like,
what did you call it?
Crab?
Razzle Dazzle Crab.
It's like one last hurrah.
Exactly.
That's one last big score.
The next year might really be.
Wait a minute.
What year are we talking?
95?
I forget.
Maybe it's Diana Ross.
Well, we'll get Diana Ross after that.
Yeah.
Oh, well, yes, you're right.
OK, that's true.
You're right.
I guess.
It's a different kind, but it's yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
Yeah, I'll talk about it.
I'll tease it.
A very.
Yeah.
But yeah, you got immediately cut to a drummer
who looks like the snake from the ride.
I mean, it's great if you want extra stuff of specifically the Indiana
Jones adventure.
Yes.
Still, guys.
And then pretty quickly, ladies and gentlemen,
the godmother of soul or whatever.
Miss Patti LaBelle.
I don't really know why she's in it yet.
Yeah.
Plot wise, I don't know.
I'm a little lost.
Patti LaBelle's there.
She's been trapped in the temple.
Yes.
Yeah.
Big name, big star.
Sure.
For a long time.
Kind of makes sense.
Yes.
Makes sense.
Songs that are definitely not recent.
But I guess.
Not super recent.
Yeah.
But closer to like Stones, the Stones or Prince or someone a little older.
Well, OK, 80s.
She had a new attitude is from 1984 is one of the songs she does.
Yeah.
So just an 11 year old.
Anyway, but she's fine.
It's good.
The behind the scenes info on this.
The stage was full of like big holes that were exactly the size of her heel.
Oh, wow.
So they had to put a the solution was to like
put a little fiberglass, like give her like some extra heel.
It has to be the heels.
Certainly, we can't change the shoes.
So they gave her like a little clear ski, basically,
so that she wouldn't like fall into each peg hole.
That's like what I do for my toys.
I have to put a little like plastic under that.
They have a hole in the foot in the shoe or whatever boot or whatever.
The stand you use the peg.
It depends.
Sometimes the figure is a little bit harder to stand on its own.
I tried to have the figure stand on its own, but if not, you got to put it on one of those little circles.
Because G.
I.
Joe's always came with the black rectangle.
So I never liked that.
Well, they the the the neck of cells like a clear circular one.
OK, it fits a lot of figures that are six or seven inch.
Semi-link.
But then you also but then you also have like flying ones, too,
where you can display them, people like characters that fly.
Fly.
OK.
It's a little stick and then it's clear as well.
Right.
You can have your own.
So you can do a little pose go.
Well, they should make neck as of everything in this halftime show.
I mean, I know there's Indiana Jones figures out there, but I want Patti LaBelle.
I want all the characters.
But she performs a song.
You realize that it's about securing the actual trophy and then into the stadium
skydives Indiana Jones and Marion.
Crazy.
Very exciting.
They sky are they like on fire or they're like flares on them?
Yeah, they have flares.
Flares, I think.
Yeah.
Nuts.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
Is he just ever skydiving the movies?
Well, he jumps out of a plane in Temple of Doom.
OK.
But they don't sky.
He's got he uses the big inflatable raft and they go from the plane.
Oh, right.
And slide down.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So close, I guess.
He doesn't do like a base jump like Ethan Hunt or something.
So you have to skydive and then you had to do basically a theme park
stunt show at the super.
Pretty wild.
Yeah.
Well, it was separate people.
Two people did the skydive and then they got like swarmed by the extras
and then the waiting like main stunt people popped out.
Smarter.
Who are the Brian Friday is Indiana.
Brian Friday is Indiana Jones.
That's who did this.
He is he and Marion are both from the Florida stunt show.
They're from Disney MGM Studios.
Nice.
And that's and I probably brought their own wardrobe, too.
It's really strange.
And Ethan Hunt's the perfect example.
I was trying to think like if that if they break from music.
This year's usher next year is Mission Impossible Live.
Oh, my God.
And then it's not Tom Cruise and he's not even in it.
He doesn't even do a voice.
Just a guy is Ethan Hunt doing stunts.
And that's the Super Bowl.
Yeah.
I sounds good to me.
They do it better now.
That's what you.
Well, I also think there's a chance you just get time to do it.
I mean, oh, if he's if something's getting wonky with the French,
I don't know what happened.
I, you know, well, they they release a movie.
We get fine.
I really like it.
But yeah, they I think it was a bit not the right time to release it.
Maybe that but it kind of it's confusing because you think it'd be
it's Tom Cruise mania with Maverick, right?
At the alternate ideas that Maverick meets
Ethan Hunt.
Oh, they sure that well, that's a great movie, right?
Movie.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
But they could build the dead reckoning ramp
in the parking lot of the Super Bowl.
And he does that jump and goes over the top of whatever.
So my stadium and then I know what now I would have gone against
what I just said and have like he's not with us anymore,
but a Robbie Knievel type to do the jump live.
And then Tom pops up and does another stunt or something.
I don't know.
I think it's got to be.
No, if you set this up, it'll all be Tom.
Yeah, probably.
That's why this just has to happen.
If anyway, if something weird is happening with the franchise
and we need to give it some new life, I think halftime show is the way to go.
Yeah.
And then the order of it is like I think I'm
oh, what Rihanna was it's Rihanna Usher, Tom Cruise.
And those are the halftime shows.
Perfect.
Yeah.
I mean, I think what happened with the franchise is it got blindsided
by the one to punch of a movie about Barbie and then a movie about
Robert Oppenheimer.
That did not help it.
Yeah.
No, same with Haunted Mansion.
Haunted.
Mark my words.
Well,
we would have all it would have been Leto Hatbox Ghost Mania out there.
Yeah.
It would have been the summer of Hatbox Ghost if it wasn't for those.
If that wasn't for that damn Barbie.
I think Mesh Raspals still did well, but it is wild to say like,
actually, the underperforming movies this year were Indiana Jones
and the Haunted Mansion.
It's like, what?
What was over performing?
Oh, Barbie and Oppenheimer.
And I was like, what?
I haven't watched the entire film.
From what I've seen, I like this halftime show more than Dial of Destiny.
It's look, it's short.
You got to give it that at least.
All right.
Now, minus points for not having Harrison Ford,
but plus points for not having 20 minutes of deep fake de-aged Harrison Ford.
I didn't see because I like Mangold.
I'm usually a Mangold man.
James Mangold, the director.
James Mangold.
Yeah.
What are your Mangold?
But I noticed.
Did nobody see it in the theater?
No, no.
Mangold, but Night and Day.
And you've all you're a night and day guy.
That's your answer is Night and Day.
Night and Day.
It's a big, kooky action movie.
The biggest smile you've had on your face all record is Night and Day.
I watched Night and Day a while ago and I was like, I like Night and Day.
Coca-Cola presents Super Bowl halftime show, Night and Day Live.
So anyways, so it is it's not Harrison and no presence from Harrison.
There's lines, but it is not recorded by Harrison.
But it is nuts.
They skydive in and then it is pure action.
Bunch of like, let's know.
Stay by Marion.
Stay behind me.
Marion's in Marion's not in the ride.
This is now we're getting a whole other thing.
No, it's mostly like the stunt show.
Yeah, it's very stunt show.
You promote a ride on the other coast.
A guy gets lit on fire and she has to do it.
Very slowly.
Yeah.
Very carefully.
But it's crazy to sit live on the Super Bowl.
It's not just like somebody back there kind of quietly does it.
Like one actress has to light another guy on fire who tumbles into a pit.
I mean, I don't know.
I'm suddenly I've this one comes up in the lists of worst Super Bowl
halftime shows, but not.
Yeah, let's let's let's get that word out of here.
I think come on, if this happened today, there is a big stunt show.
Love it.
Yes.
Absolutely.
Absolutely epic.
That do you like the snake handlers?
Do you catch that shot?
Other snake handlers.
So much going on.
Guys, two guys have big snakes.
Real snakes, real snakes.
And they kind of slowly rotate around the Indiana Jones.
They sort of walk.
And then at the very end, they're standing behind him perfectly,
still holding the snakes because you're all so you could tell.
It's like we have to be very careful with these snakes
in the middle of the football field.
There's yes, there's snakes at the 50 yard line.
And then the game will continue in 10 minutes.
Yeah, that's so awesome.
So they're moving very slowly.
And you can tell they're standing very care.
I mean, they they don't seem like aggressive snakes.
They're not the biggest, but it's still two guys holding
like each holding like a two to three feet long snakes.
They got mellowed out.
They were given weed by Anthony Kiedis' father.
Yeah.
This is always outside of the Super Bowl.
I mean, we got all right.
We filled out the drummers.
We filled out that the people are going to surround the skydivers
to do the switch.
Get Blackie Damond on the phone.
We need we need a little we got to mellow out a little.
Tensions are high.
I mean, they must have been because to pepper in behind the scenes stuff,
this they this was never we said this, that a lot of these things
are kind of like never rehearsed barely.
Whereas this was never run through fully on the field.
There's a live stunt show where somebody's lit on fire
and there are live snakes that was never truly done.
They did it in the parking lot.
They ran in the parking lot once, but it had never happened
actually in the center of the field.
Yeah, crazy.
So insane.
So and also that they never did it with like
getting into the state of putting all this stuff up,
breaking it down, tearing it all away.
And some but somehow I think everybody just had a fucking attitude.
Let's let's try it.
And it worked.
One note that I found in looking up behind the scenes,
things about all Super Bowl halftime shows, a the artists don't get paid.
Right.
And you think, well, that's just that's an exposure thing.
Sure.
But B, neither does anyone else on the field.
No.
This was at least for a long time.
If not still true today.
So many times I saw an all volunteer cast, a bunch of like
like a lot of the fighters in this are like from their volunteers
from karate academies around Miami.
Wild.
Why?
It's the Super Bowl.
There's so much money flying around.
What need could there be for this to be volunteer?
There's no need.
Yeah.
OK.
Yes.
Need is the wrong word.
And that still holds for like professional dancers.
I don't know.
Like Rihanna had a lot of dancers doing very complicated
moves last year.
I don't know.
Do you have to pay your own dancers then?
I think maybe they cover.
I mean, they do cover like all of the setup and accommodations and all that.
So like they don't give nothing.
But it's, you know, much like a funny or die video.
They don't pay the star at the center of the video or anyone else in the video.
Which makes sense, right?
So therefore you wouldn't have to pay.
If you don't pay this person with a million dollars, you don't pay this person with zero dollars.
So this thing keeps going.
Indiana Jones and Marion get lost.
They're like, and now we're like in the marketplace and like, truly, you're like,
I wonder if everybody doing it was like, I don't know where this is going.
I don't know.
I don't.
We the choreography was no choreography.
And then they end up at like a nightclub
and they sit at a table and watch Tony Bennett perform.
Yeah, Tony Bennett is here and the nightclub scene is set up.
And I'm like, I have forgotten.
And I'm like, oh, my God, are they about to do the Temple of Doom nightclub sequence?
Yeah.
But no, it's a sixty nine year old Tony Bennett.
He's sixty nine.
He's sixty nine at the time.
He seems very tired and he's still going today.
No, he's passed away.
He's dead.
Yes.
Oh, did he?
He did.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, well, I missed it.
But it sounds like I'd like that to be true.
But he did do a couple of those duet albums with Lady Gaga.
Well, sure.
So he was performing at the end of his life.
But before he was dead, he was alive.
Yeah.
I just want to cover your song.
I was wrong.
But when did he pass?
He wasn't alive.
In the last year or two?
Yeah, anyway.
Here's the tomorrow live times.
Ladies and gentlemen, the club proudly presents the incomparable Mr.
Tony Bennett.
If you listen close, he insisted on performing live.
Yeah.
And Patti LaBelle did not.
That was all pre-recorded.
Right.
But being singing live mean that he was like not.
Yeah.
I don't think he can hear the music.
And I don't think that's even his fault.
There's a bunch of so much fucking shit.
He seems distracted.
Yeah.
Well, he's distracted because immediately behind him,
two feet behind him are a bunch of people dressed as waiters.
So you won't notice them tearing and pawing at the set because they are the people
putting it up.
And then look, they're going to go in and then lights turn on.
Like and I in this Bleacher Report article about it, they do say like the guy
producing it was just on the floor.
All right.
Now I'm a waiter and now I can put this up so that while we're before
like it seems like one man was like running around and plugging everything in himself.
That's how like tossed together this was insane.
He is standing pretty still like Michael Jackson before him.
That's true.
Yeah.
But there's also a lot of movement around him.
So, yeah, yes.
Yeah.
No, like the dancers, big headdresses and all that.
You might notice in that clip that they say, and now the club presents.
And like, why is it the club club?
They didn't come up with kind of an Indiana Jonesy.
And then I found a like news piece
about this thing being prepared in the parking lot.
And in that you can see a set of this club.
And I don't think it's true in the actual show.
In the in rehearsal, the club set said
Club Disneyland.
But they did.
Yeah, yeah.
They decided like because now we're where are we?
Tony Bennett's there and it's Club Disneyland, but it's on the Super Bowl floor.
But it's in the 30s.
What's happening?
Yeah.
Our at some point, Arturo Sandoval.
He's in it.
Trumpet player.
Yeah.
The Emilio Estefan was the music director of this.
I learned from that.
Oh, wow.
Yes.
Gloria's husband.
And the band behind them is Miami Sound Machine,
which is notable towards the end.
And we're in the finale.
A guy in a tuxedo comes up playing a keytar.
And that, I think, is one of the sound machine.
So there's this performance of the song Caravan,
which I only previously knew as a Red Man sample.
Oh, yeah.
I played Caravan.
I played it in high school band.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, it's a fun one.
And then you kind of lose track of Indiana Jones and Marion.
And then you realize they're just sitting and watching this at a table.
And the trophy is on the table.
And then a big second fight happens and the trophy is stolen.
And the trophy goes flying around at some point.
Here's this is a Kathy Marshall, who played Marion and is also from the stunt
show in Florida.
The night we filmed the extra got really excited and threw the trophy really hard.
It hit me right in my nose.
Oh, no.
I had two black guys and a lot of makeup on for the Super Bowl.
Geez.
That sucks.
Yeah.
And then it's all chaos.
Because there's like at some point, somebody's wig comes off
with this weird, like silent movie hijinks.
A guy flies into a piano.
And the one guy I was talking about, who seemed to be running around
doing everything himself at some point.
OK, the piano gags about to happen.
And he says, I had to make sure that the pin on the collapsible leg was pulled.
For some reason, it didn't get pulled properly.
So I'm hollering to the stuntman.
The piano will not collapse.
One guy is just like aware of every gag and every pin and every thing
that has to be on the wall.
God bless you, sir.
Mr.
Assad, I'm not sure.
Didn't track the first name.
The sword guy's fire, either spikes pop up and then Indiana Jones
gets the trophy back again.
So it happens once and it happens again.
And then all of the oh, that's something Mara talks about,
like you'll be doomed for all eternity.
And then this great little scene happens with
all the stars at last, the meeting of Indiana Jones and Patti LaBelle.
Mm hmm.
Well, Indiana Jones, you got your trophy back.
So now tell me, what's next?
I'm giving it to the winner of Super Bowl 29.
Well, that's a great attitude, baby.
That's a great attitude.
That's great.
It's perfect.
I'm giving it to the winner.
Almost sounds like John Wayne at the start.
I'm giving it to the like, yeah, I'm Howard Cosa.
Whatever.
Someone of those guys with the old voice.
Yeah, I love it.
I love what this is.
I kind of like this era where in the ride and this show, they just end the stunt show.
Everybody decided Indiana Jones is whoever wants to be Indiana Jones.
Sure, yeah.
It was truly open.
We didn't have to get Harrison and D.
H.
Harrison.
And I like this.
I like this performance.
You know what?
This is my Indiana Jones.
Super Bowl 29.
Well, that's the right attitude.
That's the right attitude.
Oh, it is great.
I mean, that is yes.
You can't not like it, especially coming from the part,
the fact that it is canon now in the Indiana Jones ride universe.
Well, this brings me to a point that I discovered that has been discussed.
Yeah.
Is this halftime show canon?
This has been dealt with by the Indiana Jones fan community.
OK, good.
They've gone over this because it involves
all right, because the ride is canon, right?
Mara's canon, the idea that Indiana Jones had to be at
the Temple of the Forbidden Eye.
And that's right.
So this this was gone over.
And in fact, they asked
Leland Chee about this.
Leland Chee is called Keeper of the Holocron.
He is the person who in Lucasfilm tracks all of the
tracks all of the canon and the consistency.
He's a big Lucasfilm story person.
And he was asked about this.
Is the halftime show canon?
And he says, no, according to my notes, the Temple of the Forbidden
Eye attraction is set in 1935, which would make it impossible
for Indy to be with Marion at this time.
OK, so I didn't I don't think I realize this.
The ride and therefore the halftime show are set in 1935.
Interesting.
That is one year before Raiders of the Lost Ark,
which is 1936, which is some kind of reunion with Marion.
Right.
Yes.
So yeah.
So they're out of each other's orbit.
And I like that.
That's why it's not canon.
It's it's not canon because of 1935, not because Patty Labelle is in it.
Time traveling Tony Bennett.
A Tony Bennett from our time, not a what?
A five year old Tony Bennett.
But yet the Indiana Jones fandom dot com has to reckon with this.
And they put every they give everything this like specific classification
where, like, you know, you know, whatever the first time Sala showed up,
they'll put in the notes first appearance.
So they have to do it with this where they go Mara first appearance.
Patty Labelle first appearance.
Arturo Sandoval first appearance locations.
Club Disneyland first appearance.
Oh, yeah.
Artifacts.
Vince Lombardi Trophy first appearance.
Wow.
Right.
There was the Ark and then there was the Vince Lombardi Trophy.
So they're still dealing with it.
They're giving it the respect it deserves.
And I hope so are we because I this one I love.
I know we just had an all.
But the other stuff didn't have sword swallowing spikes and stunts.
This is cool.
This is the most theme park theme park.
Goofy one.
Yeah.
Stream.
We got 12 minute when we were kids.
We got 12 minutes of theme park nonsense.
Yeah, I know.
In the Super Bowl.
And that's maybe more than we can ask for today.
So let's let's fire one of these things up.
Let's do Ethan Hunt.
Let's do John Wick live.
And it's just some guy.
Sure.
Yeah, not.
They I think we're past this franchise, but there should have been
a taken halftime show for all three takings.
Every single year.
Yeah.
My daughter.
And she also has a Super Bowl trophy.
She's been taken with the trophy.
And then he's got to go.
Yeah.
My daughter was tasked with
delivering the trophy.
Right.
It was kidnapped.
Anyway, it's it's great.
The fun to go through all these.
And now what this opens up is Super Bowl halftime shows, too.
In which time we will certainly meet Elvis Presto.
He of the Bop Bamboozled and the Bop Bamboozled
in the disco, which I will fully remove
this Indiana Jones one from the discussion of worst.
Of course.
But I will put one in
and I without going into it any further, we'll just this will be a tease
for next time.
Three words that might
terrify you to your core.
The words are Blues Brothers Bash.
That you survived this year of podcast.
Killing.
Yeah, I know.
Just start imagining what it is.
Get familiar with it because, you know, I can only imagine
there'll be 90 minutes about only that.
Then doing a little bit of football.
I need a football hero.
And the mouth harp, you know, we're doing that song.
We're good.
Or Michael, you know, we already gave it up for Chicago,
but now it's time to give it up for Hollywood.
That's a Ballyhooey Hollywood.
All right.
Well, that's coming next year.
You can find us on the socials at podcast.
The ride merch is available in our T public store for three bonus episodes
every month.
Check out podcast the ride, the second gate,
or get one more bonus episode on our VIP tier club three.
You will find all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride related to this things coming to the second gate.
I still want to get to the opening of the sky dome.
It's kind of in the same zone as this.
And without saying what it is, I think my birthday shot in July
might be in this neck of the woods.
Great.
So start start imagining.
I would I would never claim Blues Brothers Bash for myself.
That would be far too selfish.
Thank you for doing that.
Never.
That belongs to all of us.
I wouldn't do it.
It belongs to everyone in America.
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.