I believe Griffin is in SoCal soon for a live George Lucas talk.
I'm proposing a Let Griffin Pick the Topic episode, a la the Eva Anderson episode, It's Time to Get Him on Club 3.
That's from C.
Al and Kelly.
And with that somewhat unsettling awareness of your personal calendar.
Yeah, really?
Yeah.
We now, we're greeted by you here.
That's the power of Club 3 is somebody said, Hey, guess what?
I know where a guy's going to be in a few weeks.
I'm going to force him into a room with you three.
Can I shape space and time?
Can I get him into a room?
I have a griff tab on my iCal.
Right.
I can track his wear.
It's going to be a legion on Thursday.
You've been barring Taylor Swift's jet.
We can all track the tail.
I have.
We've been, yeah, I should make it clear.
The Eras Tour and George Lucas talk show doing one show every three months have very similar mechanisms behind them.
Yeah, sure.
So we're sharing a lot of resources.
Uh huh.
Yeah, you're propelling in from Tokyo at a moment's notice.
Well, it happened.
You're here.
I was, you know, I also like.
And also let's make it clear with the after effects of Joke's side doing six waddo shows in the span of a week.
I apologize in advance for my voice on this episode.
This is what this is what Alan gets is the post.
He knew what he was getting into with the comment.
Yeah, it is post waddo.
One bit of business, a question that I had.
I introduced you in the last time that you were on, which was the Orlando live shows.
I was just hyping up how great it was that you came down specifically to hang out with us and do that.
And in the process, I said, it's the kind of thing that makes you want to notch somebody up from being just an accidental PTR legend.
Now, it left me.
Some people, some listeners regarded that as the official right turn of the wheel on that sort of thinking out loud.
Yes, as like a mid step.
I didn't intend for it to be or not to be.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, that is the question.
That is always the question.
I'm wondering now, you know, being that I think a recurring theme of this will be the power that you have here in the club three chair, a power that some people should be taken away from.
We'll see.
We'll see if the next poll will result in you being banned from the show in general.
But I think it is up to you at this point whether you would like to move beyond accidental PTR legend.
Is there kind of a special nature?
I've always loved the kind of special nature and I've worn that as its own badge of pride.
And it was an interesting question you sort of threw up in the air.
Do we want to?
Is it accidental forever?
Is there a pipeline to be able to rise up to full?
It's unprecedented.
We don't know the rules here.
We've never and you're really the only person facing this specific.
But I want to remind you that within that same show, we landed on a new title, which I would say.
Oh, you're right.
I know.
I forgot it was the first chance to and I haven't said I didn't use it.
Exactly.
I think I'll let you say it, but I think this is the main honorific I want now.
It has now superseded.
Yes.
Accidental PTR legend in the way where I don't think I think that can stay accidental.
Ah, you know.
OK.
Well, wait.
Let me make sure I'm getting it right.
And and you can rake me over the holes holes if I don't get it right.
So let me reintroduce you and say due to see Alan Kelly here on Club 3, complete or yes.
Griffin Newman.
Yeah, I got it.
OK.
Great.
Wow.
There's the first one.
Yes, that's the first one.
Leader accidental PTR legend.
We told her.
Yeah.
Which could be a CBS show that you star on.
The complete or I'd love to be the complete or seven seasons of the complete or seven.
Seven.
Yeah.
You know, times these days.
I don't know.
Yeah.
The twenty twenty is a different.
The complete or only got seven.
Geez.
It does feel like 30 million.
You can only buy three houses.
Sorry.
That feels like basically the only kind of stable work left in television.
Right.
Yeah.
Is if you grab one of those procedurals that airs on CBS, you know, quietly runs for seven years.
Do it in a closet.
It's like it's like hiding in plain sight.
No one you know has ever watched an episode.
Right.
Yeah.
No one will ever.
Your friends don't have to pretend that they saw it or liked it or come up.
It's kind of great.
They'll just be happy to be at your awesome house.
And then when you when when you get the bill for every meal from now on, people are like, did you win the lottery?
And you're like, no, I'm on season seven of the complete.
It's better.
Yeah.
Somewhere to be.
So this is submitted to the poll.
You message me.
I told you guys I was going to be in town for this trip.
I thought I was staying on the town low.
I thought no one else could track my movements.
And I said, hey, I want to do an episode with you guys.
There were a couple of things we talked about.
I said, hey, you know, I was there for a lot of the city walk saga.
Should I jump on one of those?
It's around the time you're recording those.
There is a theme park attraction that has been pinned on the board for now, maybe a year and a half.
Yeah.
Well, I called my shot at one point of you guys made an offhand reference to I don't think anyone cares about this attraction.
Is it a Disney attraction context?
Because I know we get what the attraction is.
I do think it's an attraction people care about.
I care about it.
There's this is a whole thing that like I might be remembering the tone more harshly than it was, but I just remember it being brought up casually in a way where I messaged you guys immediately and said, I have a lot of strong feelings on that one.
It was really important to me when I was a child.
Yeah.
Much like Ghostbusters.
And and I I would like to have that episode reserved for me.
So you yes, we you you grabbed this one.
There is basically this.
This was what this is what C.
Alan Kelly did.
You completely were stolen for Club 3 because we were primed to do a very clean main feed episode where a guest talks about an attraction they love.
Remember those and those kinds of exactly almost.
I've seen the criticism sometimes of Griffin comes on.
He does an episode loosely tied in to promoting some project that no one cares about.
He's tried to find a Jason theme to promoting his new thing.
No one cares about which I would say it is not my fault that almost everything I've worked on is unsuccessful.
That's a lot of us in the podcasting world.
I'll copy paste that to myself.
A lot of people in podcasting.
Most work is irrelevant almost immediately upon release.
But yes, it was like, oh, we're here.
This theme park attraction.
People complain that doesn't happen.
They complain I hijack with these other sideways topics.
It was like we had one ready to go and it's been the fucking Matt Damon of the Jimmy Kimmel live.
Yeah.
It just keeps getting bumped for something new that pops up.
And multiple people in this room really like it.
Yeah, we'd love to do this.
Yes.
I think we're all in agreement that we'd love to do it.
It's out of our hands this time.
It's going to be a really focused, research heavy, pure attraction episode.
I'm excited for people to guess.
Like what's on the board left?
And I said I'll be in town for George Lucas.
I think it's time to finally do Blank.
It bumped last time mainly because you wanted to do more Frank Marshall Gate and free it to the main.
So it's already been bumped for that.
And now we've got another bump.
And this is a thing that spans continents.
Yeah.
This is not an oddball.
That's a clue.
No, it's like it's a major enough attraction that at one point it was operating in three different parks simultaneously.
I believe.
A lot of clues.
At least two.
But I think maybe three.
I looked it up recently.
Under multiple names.
And different versions.
Look, interesting.
No more clues.
We've sort of pinned it.
I'm going to be here.
I guess we finally do that.
And then a day or two later, Griffin, just feel like you should know this was suggested.
And right now it has a healthy lead in the poll.
Yeah.
Well, we asked you before.
We asked you permission before even putting it in.
Oh, sure.
Because we didn't want to.
Yeah, yeah.
We don't want to tie you to that.
So you told me.
Is that the kind of thing Griffin would like?
Like getting to pick whatever nonsense he wants to do?
I said interesting.
And I said, let me just start percolating some.
So then it goes up on the official poll.
It's got a serious head.
Yeah.
And then it goes up on the lead in the polls, which I was very flattered by.
And so I'm just like, well, now I really want to like.
So my list was I got up to like 15 options.
But you actually by my account, you sent us a casual 16.
OK, OK.
A slick 16.
I have it here and I want to run down because we're going to you're saying we're going to make the title of this still.
My thought was that up until this point and listeners will know if this was what was decided on the episode right now.
And then the other thing that they're listening to is still just called Griffin Newman does whatever he wants.
So you don't know where we're.
And there's a very specific thing we're doing here and a thing that my eyes long overdue on this show.
And what this ultimately boiled down to, because I can't put a lot of options, but some of them I went and I the right guess for that.
I'd love to hear a PTR episode on that, but I don't know if I'm the guy or maybe I would want to do this episode.
But I could probably we could this episode could get off the ground under other circumstances.
I could send a casual text.
I don't know how hard sell you guys on doing X or Y.
It's like what is the thing that could only happen right under these and so I'll completely force a little circumstance to this as I least list off some of the ones we didn't do.
But what we've landed on is a thing that I've been pushing for three years in a text or text thread longer longer.
I looked up the history of it.
Yeah.
Four years and was not pitched as an episode was something to do in the world.
You guys as human beings should do this.
And has always been with a certain amount of resistance.
We'll get to it.
But I went the making it the episode forces it to be taken seriously.
Yeah.
You got us in a in a blocked room.
I don't know if it's locked.
It's a closed room.
You got us in a room with a closed door to have to confront this.
I wager to the enjoyment of the listeners.
It didn't feel like this is a self-indulgent thing.
I feel like people I want to believe knock on metal that this will be a satisfying episode in a way that kind of proves me right and changes the course of your guys lives.
Oh wow.
So let's act.
You've built it up a lot.
I'm trying to change the course of lives.
Hey here are some of the things you're going to read us the book The Secret.
The final the other two final contenders.
Yeah.
Which I want to just put on the record I think should happen.
Sure.
Jim Henson Records.
Yes.
Which released three albums in the 90s two concept albums Muppet Beach Party and Kermit Unpigged.
And this this was attempting to me because I asked would that then allow.
I don't remember what's on what does that allow for the discussion of the She Drives Me Crazy music video.
Yes.
With a really random assortment of celebrities.
Some of whom are on rhythm to the song and others who are grabbed in some studios somewhere.
In the post Henson death weird period where his kids are like what do we do with these characters.
They start a record label release three albums in like 18 months and shut it down.
One is Muppet Beach Party which is like concept narrative all the Muppets go to a beach together.
They get into a bunch of fights and those fights manifest in covers of songs like a third of which are Beach Boys covers.
So I'm like well that's particularly appealing.
Yeah I'm listening.
Then there's Kermit Unpigged which is they get lost in a recording studio while trying to record a serious album and bump into a bunch of other musicians and do collab duets.
And it's like I think it's born to be wild with Animal and Sammy Hagar.
There's Ozzy Osbourne and Linda Ronson.
It's like an interesting grouping.
Buffett?
Is Buffett on one of these?
Yes.
The whole album is a play on MTV unplugged era but in a very tortured joke that barely reads in the title.
And then the third and final album and I'm getting to details here just so people want to hear this episode.
Let the whistle.
I want to sell the idea of what the value is here.
The third album was an album that Jim Henson recorded 10 years earlier that had been sitting on a shelf that then became his last postimus release.
Even post Muppet Vision 3D which is old brown ears is back which is an incredibly sincere straight faced album of Rolf the dog singing standards.
Like doing Sinatra style crooning of like New York State of Mind.
And it rules.
It really led the way to Seth MacFarlane in a way.
Truly.
Mr.
Cartoon Voiceman doesn't have to be jokey when he sings these standards.
Is it recorded before Brent Spiner records Old Yellow Eyes is back?
I think it was recorded in 86.
Okay.
Yeah.
It's a theme month about old eyes.
It might be that.
It came out after but was recorded before.
It truly was on a shelf for a decade.
The other one that came close, emphasis mine but typed out with such, a detailed history of MacFarlane toys.
Yeah.
Right.
Todd MacFarlane.
Yes.
Comic book artist extraordinaire.
When he eventually leaves Marvel.
Creator of Venom.
Venom and Spawn.
Radical maverick industry disruptor.
Yeah.
Starts Image which shakes up the whole fucking comics industry.
With a bunch of other guys.
Then starts a toy company.
Yes.
In between getting sued for defamation by hockey players.
I mean a bunch.
There's so much wild shit that happens.
And my argument here, and I know Todd MacFarlane's the kind of guy where if you hear any combination of Mike, Jason or I bring him up, you check out.
I know the face.
It's a face I saw my father make many times when I was growing up.
And I would try to monologue about the importance of Todd MacFarlane to him.
You go, this is some them stuff.
He's a fascinating character.
This is the thing.
I think if we fully broke down Todd MacFarlane and I think the rise and fall and rise again of MacFarlane toys is a good kind of like prism through which to look at him as a general figure.
I would argue he is one of the few good guys.
He is a classic guy in the PTR sense without being like horrible.
Yeah.
Clarifying good guys is kind of a key because sometimes we start to think do guys have to be evil?
No.
And then not always.
I think Todd has some like wild follies, which Jason is alluding to.
There are some classic guy moves, but I don't ever look at any step of the Todd MacFarlane story and go like Todd.
He's really blunt and to the point he's often right.
Here's what I'll say to sell it to Scott.
And his mistakes are so bizarre.
He's got a good voice to do an imitation of.
Oh yeah.
I'm like MacFarlane kind of needs to be a character on the show as a person.
Yeah.
Which means we need to sell to you him as a guy away from the stuff he did that you don't care about.
And I think if you understand him as a guy, then that stuff becomes interesting.
Look, I spent 20 years of my life trying to make this case to my father.
I don't know what ever worked, but I think I might be able to win you over.
But there was a moment in Orlando when Mike and I were riffing back and forth on like action figure scene drama and I saw you make the face my father made as a child.
Oh wow.
Oh, I didn't know what I was tying into.
This is a challenge I want to see if there's a way to overcome it.
Look, I have no doubt that I have caused this face in others.
I guarantee.
Totally.
It's just, you know, you're locked into your things.
That's why I find it appealing.
The challenge of like, I think there's a way to make this make sense to you.
Yeah.
As the type of thing you do find interesting.
I put money on the fact that you guys, if we just, well, what if we decided right now, actually we are going to do that.
I feel like the three of you could improvise that episode with no research.
Correct.
We could do it now.
Probably get it 90 percent correct.
Yeah.
We're not going to.
I'm just saying I have faith in you guys.
That's its own thing.
I'm just going to speed around some of the other ones.
I'm not going to go into the mess in depth.
One of the ones as I typed out was fuck it.
I'm forcing you guys to do mass magician.
Yes.
Oh, and by the way, Griffin's presence here did trounce mass magician.
However, mass magician trounced to the others.
It is the runner up for the fourth time, which means it is heading into the fifth poll.
And now here's a little I don't know when the next poll is going to be because maybe next month we will be deep into the throes of a certain saga.
I'm not totally.
I don't want to fully commit, but that might be what's that.
Anyway, ideas in the comments either way for what goes up against mass magician next.
But fifth time in the poll, it stayed steady at second place.
It did it again.
I voted for mass magician this time.
I voted against myself.
That wasn't very good.
Feels like it's genuinely the gentlemanly thing to see most.
Yeah.
But I also felt like do I use this slot for that when that is already basically inevitable?
And also, I think it I don't know.
It's we'll see though.
It needs to become the people's champions.
It felt almost like if I made this episode that its victory comes with an asterisk on it that I don't like cheating.
You're the Supreme Court installing.
You put your thumb instead of the people's champion George Bush just winning on his own, which we which would have changed the tenor.
I loved him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He did it.
It's rocky.
Another one.
Zamuda Hall of Fame.
I feel like we've talked about this at some point on the podcast.
Did we say it on the show?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe we've we've all in social hangouts latched onto the concept of the Zamuda.
Yes.
Yeah.
Zamuda being a hanger on of it's a reference to Bob Zamuda, Andy Kaufman's best friend who's like devoted his life to keeping the legacy.
I was into your 40 of being the professional Andy Kaufman expert.
Yes.
Yeah.
Contacted for interviews.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But like Mike loves a Zamuda.
Oh, for but if you have for Brian.
Yeah, sure.
We were saying Bob Gale.
Bob Gale's a huge Zamuda.
It's it's got to be for it's either for one of your past projects for a very specific phase of your career or you are the guy next to the guy.
Yeah.
So all of the living members of Queen or Zamuda's for Freddie Mercury.
This was what the episode was going to be litigating who counts as a Zamuda and who doesn't.
Is Ackroyd a Zamuda for Belushi or does it cannot as a Zamuda have enough of their own thing going on that they aren't as a Zamuda?
So I think Ackroyd is not a Zamuda for Belushi.
I think he's a Zamuda for Blues Brothers and Ghostbusters.
Yeah.
I think that's the distinction is he's actually more obsessed with the worlds he created than his dead friend and forcing people to still care about those.
Oh, sure.
And then I'll sort of be like, also my old buddy, John, like he's kind of the afterthought.
Sure.
John Taffer Follies is what I called it.
But another one where I just go, guys, this episode is inevitable.
Yeah.
Do I put my thumb on the scale and force it to happen sooner rather than later?
Sure.
But also do I want to burn the shot on that?
I think it's the characters.
Yeah, you've been talking about this for a while.
The movie by Hard Rock, part creator John Binkowski.
It's so fucking bad.
I watched it on Peacock because you guys describing it without having watched it made it sound so weird to me.
Available on Peacock.
Still available on Peacock.
Still available.
But I'm just like, I've already spent the time watching it.
At some point, something productive needs to come out of that.
Sure.
Themed IP slot machines.
I was like, that's too general.
Anyone could do that.
Ken Forsey, come dream with me tonight.
A nine hour documentary on the maker of Teddy Ruxpin that I texted to you guys as if I was passing along the VHS of the ring.
This has cursed me.
I now can't sleep at night.
I couldn't believe you put this that this went beyond texts to something that you maybe wanted to talk about.
This as you explained it, like what just like an unwatchable crack, endless documentary about Teddy Ruxpin.
Not about Ted Ruxpin, about the man who created Teddy Ruxpin.
I think it truly takes four hours before Teddy Ruxpin is introduced in the narrative.
I'm not exaggerating.
It is nine hours long.
It is self-funded by the two biggest Teddy Ruxpin fans on the internet.
It is deeply bizarre.
I recommend people watching it if you are also deranged and depressed.
But ultimately, I was like, there's not an episode there other than me just being like, why did I watch this?
I believe one part of it was texted to me with like, here it is.
Don't watch it.
Yes.
That's a good starting point.
Yeah, that's a good starting point.
Jason, for perspective, I don't think you should start watching this.
Yeah, sure.
The 2003 Fox dating show Mr.
Personality, which we didn't spend a lot of time on that.
I didn't remember that one.
I couldn't find a torrent of it anywhere.
So I was like, it might be impossible to watch.
But this was given the prime post-American idol slot in one of their biggest seasons.
It was a dating show hosted by Monica Lewinsky.
Oh, it's that one.
The premise was it's the bachelor, but she's in a mansion with all these eligible guys.
But this show asks you to judge them purely based on personality.
So two key pieces of information are withheld.
She does not know any of her suitors careers.
She doesn't know how successful they are, how much money they make.
All of that context stripped away.
Secondly, she doesn't know how attracted to them she is or isn't because all of them wear masks.
That look like fucking man in the iron mask.
Like horrible, monstrous.
Like the things they put on burn victims to hold their flesh in place at the hospital.
Is this not referenced on the curse?
I don't know if anyone has watched The Curse.
Yeah, there's a show that is about burn victims.
I think 30 Rock maybe references it as well.
I was obsessed with it when it was on, but it's very hard to find any trace of it.
It is a thing that is not theme parky, but has weird curse theme parky energy.
If we can light up Masked Magician and that can in turn light up a bunch of, especially Fox reality crap.
Because I've dropped my love of David Foster, part of which came from a show called Princes of Malibu, which is a precursor to The Hills.
It's his Osborns that is so fascinating and difficult to get through.
Times Square Toys R Us, which was seriously considered a really good defunct land video on that.
I don't know if I have anything to add beyond what Perjurer has already encapsulated in that video.
Now here are the last two.
The Frank trilogy of Kevin Spacey videos, but I was like that's an Eva Wallner episode.
We were discussing, we were like, is it making Frank Marshall a third?
We were like, which Frank is this?
Is it Let Me Be Frank or is it Frank Marshall?
I thought you meant like Congo or Acnophobia.
Oh, we did talk about that.
Are we talking about Frank Marshall's films?
I didn't explain this to you.
I just wrote the Frank trilogy.
It left us.
We had a discussion about it.
You didn't ask me.
No, no, no.
So my intent was the three Let Me Be Frank, Kill Them With Kindness and Tucker With Frank.
Have there only been three?
That's what confused me.
He took a year off.
He did.
But wasn't there a third?
Kill Them With Kindness is the park bench one.
Let Me Be Frank is of course the original with him and the apron.
But wasn't there a second?
No, I'm not sure.
I think it is only three.
Because for a while it felt like unresolved.
We're never going to get the third one.
Yeah.
And then these last two, Bill Cosby's picture pages, it's a children's show I was obsessed with.
It is obviously very difficult to talk about now.
Yeah.
There is a character on it named and I'm going to say this because I don't think there is any way to actually do an episode about this.
I gave it some because I did watch, I looked up this character.
I want to encourage Clifford to watch the video as well.
To understand what the appeal is for me and then just go off in your own thoughts.
Talk to your friends about it.
There is a character who is introduced on this weird educational Bill Cosby's 70s lesson show where he literally works like through an activity book with a musical pen to teach you how things work.
You'd send away for the stuff.
Yes.
Direct address to camera.
You get a workbook and a pen and he's like, connect the dots.
You wear a raincoat when it's raining.
That's the kind of lessons he teaches.
There is a character who appears in two sketches who was on this VHS that I got used from Blockbuster when I was a child and watched eight billion times.
Who I still think is as influential on my sense of humor and my perception of comedy as anything ever named No Head Norman.
And I just wanted to introduce him to the PTR universe as a sort of Marvel McFay.
Is there a way to get the rights to No Head Norman?
Get it away from the Cosby Clutch.
Yeah.
Sure.
At one point I reframed it and I was like, can it just be a No Head Norman episode?
But it's too difficult to talk around.
He's a startling figure.
Visually, when you were describing, I was picturing like, if you've ever seen David Lynch's animations or like a Don Hertzfeld, I thought it was like a stripped down cartoon.
Jason, I was running by options to Ben Hosley, producer Ben from Blank Check, and was like, before I send the list to the guys, can I run through some of them for you?
Ben consulted on this?
He did.
He was like, which ones do you think have more juice than others?
And he was like, you can't do a Bill Cosby episode.
And I was like, let me just show you No Head Norman.
And a day later, he's like, I actually have been kind of haunted by this.
And he described it as lynchian.
I think it is simultaneously very funny and very upsetting in a way that doesn't have to do with the Cosby of it.
He's a very bizarre character with a very bizarre look.
He needs to be revived in some way.
Freed of Cosby.
You also had one on here that scribbled out.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, wait, wait.
And right before you get to that, there are four.
I had a feeling there are four spacey videos.
Let me be Frank.
KTWK kill them with kindness.
The bench one is one.
The bench one.
Yeah, the bench one isn't killing with kindness.
It's one hundred Christmas.
Thank you.
And then there was last year.
This year's being Frank, which the less said about the better.
Yes.
No, I think that's kind of the best one.
It's the Tracy Zooms in of the series.
They are.
It's an extremely.
Yeah, there's a lot of crossover between those series, I'd say.
So there is one and we're about to get to the reveal of what this is.
And I think people are going to stand up out of their chairs, applaud, go.
This is the right choice.
What the episode is ultimately landed on.
But there was one thing that in the time between when you activated me and said, maybe start coming up with some ideas and submitting the list,
I discovered the existence of a thing I did not know about.
I had not seen.
Otherwise, I was pulling from like, what are things I care about?
I have a history with this showed up on my radar because I was doing.
I think most people listen to show probably share a sort of trait with the four of us,
which is stuff you saw when you were a very specific age that kind of stuck in your craw that you've been weirdly fixated on.
You never forget.
And as an adult, you're like, what was that?
Yeah.
And not just let me rewatch this as a grown up, but I want to understand how this came into being and what the cultural response was outside of me just being exposed to it as a child.
So I was digging into let me just get the I want to be able to read this correctly.
It's very exciting to get this unredacted.
And I'm excited.
So there was I think it was called the Hanna Barbera Superstar 10, which was in the 80s.
A bunch of animation studios started trying to do competitors to Wonderful World of Disney and basically doing 45 minute animated specials that could be backdoor pilots for new series.
And some of them did spin off into their own things.
And some of them just became weird.
But I would see on Cartoon Network, early Cartoon Network before they had original shows like Scooby Doo and the Reluctant Werewolf and the Ghoul School,
which were like these are longer than Scooby Doo episodes, but they're not quite the Scooby Doo direct to video movies, but they have kind of contained narratives.
And they were like trying out like what's the new era of Yogi Bear?
What's all this?
So I was like digging into all of these.
And then on that Wikipedia entry, it mentioned the rival was the ABC Saturday Superstar movie, which was this is not based around one animation house.
This is sort of just like a fucking garbage plate of different animation studios creating backdoor pilots.
And some of them were Hanna Barbera ones as well.
But so there's like the Brady Kids on Mysterious Island, the animated continuation of Brady Bunch, where they end up in like a Jules Verne land.
There's Yogi's Ark Lark, which is Yogi Bear flying a big fucking Noah's Ark.
Flying into space.
Nanny and the Professor.
Like most of these are like new versions of old sitcoms or like new adaptations of like a retelling of Robin Hood with animals a year before Disney's Animal Robin Hood.
A Lassie cartoon, a Gidget revival, the Banana Splits and Hocus Pocus Park, which is very theme park adjacent, I think is actually a very good film.
But things like this, right?
Interestingly, one called Daffy Duck and Porky Meet the Groovy Ghoulies, which is the only time Warner Brothers let anyone else animate the Looney Tunes because they didn't give a shit.
When the characters were on ice and they let Filmation, the company that did the He-Man cartoon, do a weird third rate Looney Tunes.
But I land on this one.
I go, this is a weird title.
The Man Who Hated Laughter, AKA Popeye the Man Who Hated Laughter.
When I just see the man who hated laughter, I go, all these other things seem to be riffing off of something I know.
What is this?
Popeye meets the man who hated laughter.
I'm just going to read what the Wikipedia says.
Okay, for plot.
Professor Morbid Grimsby.
This is how it starts.
Is an evil genius who has won the prestigious quote, meanie award six years in a row to guarantee a seventh.
He plots to eliminate all laughter in the world.
To guarantee a seventh.
The stakes of this are a seventh meanie award.
So he's the man who hates laughter.
He's the man who hates laughter.
How is he going to eliminate humor?
I'm just, guys, brace yourself.
Okay.
This special is from 1972.
So is it a Nixon allegory?
He says, I need to eliminate the stars of the funny pages.
Man Who Hated Laughter is a King Features Syndicate crossover movie.
In which this villain is like, I need to kill all the King Features Syndicate characters.
He is the Thanos of King Features Syndicate.
And he goes, here's the pitch.
His henchman in this is Brutus, aka Bluto from the Popeye.
And he goes, you know Popeye.
Here's what we do.
Hire that fucking idiot Popeye to captain a ship.
Convince all the King Features Syndicate characters that they've won a free cruise.
And then we fucking just, we cast them out to sea.
We drown them.
We strand them on an island.
Whatever it is, get rid of them.
This is a special that contains the cast of Barney Google and Snuffy Smith, Blondie,
Beetle Bailey, Bringing Up Father, Flash Gordon, Henry, High and Lowis, the Cats and Jammer Kids,
Little Iodyne, the Little King, Mandrake the Magician, the Phantom, Popeye, Prince Valiant,
it says in parentheses, Cameo, Quincy, Steve Canyon, Tiger, and Tim Tyler's Luck.
I went, well fuck.
I made the discovery of a lifetime.
There's no way this isn't the episode.
Is it on YouTube?
Oh my God, it's there.
We can watch it.
Let me put it on.
Five minutes in, I was like, this is the most interminably boring thing I've ever seen.
Okay.
Hang on.
The thing that has Henry and Little Iodyne.
Henry.
Come on, Henry.
With all the stuff we know about Henry, you're telling me that's not interesting?
And Quincy on top of it?
It would be very funny if Mandrake the Magician defeated the Masked Magician.
The Russian nesting doll structure of this thing, like a modern Wes Anderson movie, is
that all the serious pulp heroes like Mandrake and Flash Gordon and the Phantom are in their
serious superhero headquarters watching a broadcast about a crime that's about to happen.
Then they watch the man-hated laughter plot to hijack and strand all the funny characters.
Was this dumped on cable at some point?
It must have been.
I have seen this.
I had no memory of this existing.
And all the other things in this silo, I definitely watched.
Early Cartoon Network Disney Channel, it was like they just would buy these things and
play bullshit at odd hours.
I could see that in some, like, there's a Brigsby Bear scenario where somehow it's the
only tape in your house, Jason.
And it answers a lot of questions.
Well, this or like the, what is the cartoon where they fly the Spruce Goose?
Is that one of them?
That's, I think, Yogi's lost.
That's the Ark one?
Is that the Ark one?
But they fly the Howard Hughes' plane?
But the joke is it's all animals on it.
So like the Spruce Goose.
It's Noah's Ark mashed up with Howard Hughes?
No, no, no, no, it's here, I found it.
It's a different thing.
Yogi Bear and the magical flight of the Spruce Goose.
Hey, what do you, why is there one about the real Howard Hughes plane?
But they started doing it.
After his death?
Yes, long after his death.
At this point, Hanna Barbera is doing all these mashup shows.
That's the Superstars 10, by the way, is what you're describing.
Like Scooby's Laugh Olympics or like Yogi's Ark Lark where it's like we just mush all
the characters together.
And, you know, you guys are just constantly joking about like King Feature Syndicate.
Yes.
And the lack of any sort of cohesion across the characters they own.
To find out there's been this thing for 50 years has just been out there.
That's all of them put together.
That was their try.
Yeah, try.
I'd say it's borderline unwatchable.
We just did an episode where we talked about what if there was great movie ride the movie.
I think we are obsessed with these like just like big, as you said, garbage pile mashups
and this has been out there for the arbitrary, boring comic name that we picked.
And look, this is, I think, building a bridge to the actual topic we're going to talk about
today.
But you realize it was the benefit of like people always talked about how lazy Hanna
Barbera was.
It was all the same, the same art style, the same joke style.
Yeah.
These characters are also similar.
When they started mushing these characters together, you were like, yeah, they were all
like, let them all coexist.
Yeah.
You watch this thing and you're like the design languages of the characters do not mash at
all.
Their senses of humor don't mash.
It feels like you're listening to like metal machine music.
You're like, there's like, there's a tension.
I think part of it being unwatchable is just like, I can't process.
You can't put these characters in the same frame and have them all do their routines
in a way where they're just kind of yelling at each other.
This also, the notion that you, if you want to end all laughter in the world, you got
to get rid of Barney Google.
The funniest characters imaginable.
Steve Canyon.
We have to kill the funnies.
Specifically a certain variety of funny.
The reason I think I've seen it is I remember like Mandrake and Flash Gordon.
Watching it?
Yeah.
I remember them all just standing in one frame.
Yes.
And as a kid I was excited.
I was like, that's how the characters from the funny pages, but they don't really do
anything.
The heroic ones never interact with the funny ones and they just cut back to them every
once in a while and they're like, Popeye does seem to have gotten himself into a pickle
here.
And then they cut back into the screen and you see what they're watching.
Very limited.
Are they watching TV?
They're like, lots of the watcher.
Are they famous in the, is it like they're coming from the comic strips?
Cause those characters in their worlds aren't necessarily funny.
They're not like standup comedians.
No, it's like.
We're seeing their real lives.
It's a messy logic.
I think all these characters are famous because they're in the funnies, but they're not Roger
Rabbit style.
Oh, these are the performers who play the parts in the funnies.
It's like the lives, you know, that they have in their own strips are real and canon, but
also they're all known to us by being funny stars.
It's very, I mean, you know, Mickey had stuff like this, Bugs Bunny had stuff like this.
None of what we've seen isn't true.
It's just also their movie stars.
Yes.
And it makes you appreciate cartoon all sorts of the rescue, which does find a way to harmonize
these characters beautifully.
That's true.
They don't, they don't mismatch.
More dynamic.
Yeah.
Certainly.
I mean, this, this was very limited, like Johnny Quest.
Yes.
It's really limited.
And then like the, the meanie guy is done in like UPA 60s limited animation style.
Like it's, it's, it's got a bad sense, but look, that's an animation project that didn't
work.
Yes.
Perhaps the wrong pitch, the wrong idea.
It wasn't beat it out properly.
Right.
There was a need to be filled space, but it didn't come from anything organic.
They didn't focus up, assemble a room and really say, let's not leave here until we
got gold in our hands.
Yes.
And with that, Griffin, would you like to weave us through what the actual thing we're
doing?
I don't know if you have the first text pulled up, but about four years ago, I say to you
I really think you should develop an animated series around your personas to which the response
was, I don't think anyone wants to watch a cartoon show about adult men who host a theme
park podcast.
I mean, that's not what I'm pitching.
Yeah.
That's not what I'm pitching.
It was activated by a couple things.
Uh, a animal and a Woodsy.
Is that the person who's done a lot of your fan art?
Am I getting the name mixed up?
But I feel like the times where you've done like Jamba reek or a honk, honk has the fright.
Yeah.
Oh, yes.
And people have done fan art of you guys in the style of the hitchhiking ghosts or the
country bears.
Jeremy Allison has done great stuff.
Yes.
Or even when it's like just a funny thing like Jason's research for it now done as a sort
of a little prep or certainly the like Jason's kitchen follies.
Right?
Yes.
Every time I see a piece of art like that, I'm just like, you guys fucking translate
so well to cartoons.
In every sense, I just listen to the show as a fan first who has become a friend, but
I'm like putting on my like my listener hat.
Right?
Yeah.
I'm like, you guys have such solid games and you have like distinct personas that mesh
and clash in interesting ways.
There are the overlaps.
There are the sources of tensions.
You have the commonalities and the Frank Marshalls.
Right?
The commonality that brought us together, but all of the differences that have kept tensions
hopefully interesting to listen to.
When I look at anyone do like a little cartoon fan art of you guys, I'm like, you got three
distinct visual looks.
There's a nice kind of like one of each.
Well, the height wise, you know.
It's chipmunk style.
Whenever I've like met up with you guys in real life, it's and I'm walking, I'm approaching
from a distance.
There's something so nice where before I can even make out the details, I'm like, that's
the PTR trio.
Well, this is like one, two, three.
I can see whatever order you're standing in.
And I'm like, this is when people talk about like animation having great silhouettes.
You'd recognize these characters.
Yeah.
Silhouettes.
Silhouettes, I'm not sure.
But the three of us that you've that you could squint and see us when walking up in the Disneyland
hub or whatever.
Now, every time I brought this up and I bring it up intermittently over the last four years,
you're like, what's the pitch?
We're not saying no, but I don't feel like you've explained what you think this is.
And I'm like, my my answer is always it could be anything.
I leave that up to you guys, which is why I figured today let's put a structure around
this and actually try to figure it out.
I think we possibly come out of here with a million dollar pitch.
Wow.
So this idea.
I've never been asking for EP credit.
I've never been.
I'm just like, I want to see this happen.
Right.
Yeah.
Now, over time, you've been like, explain like, what is this?
And I'm like, you watch all those Hanabra Bear cartoons.
Most of them were riffing on the persona of some public figure.
Yes.
Where you're like Huckleberry Hound is just like Ben Crosby ripoff.
Uh huh.
Yes.
Quite often a ripoff of an existing person.
Flintstones or Honeymooners.
Those were all sort of like pop culture figures of the 10 to 20 years prior that they just
like sort of mapped another species or time period on top of.
And we're like, it's different because he's a bear now.
Which is, you know what?
This is a guy.
I'm in this world of pitching and helping animated shows.
This is kind of my bread and butter outside of the show.
And the something that does come up sometimes is like, can you take the character dynamic
and drop it somewhere else and it still makes sense, which is always a thing that fucking
trips me up and fucks me up because I'm like, but I thought of this.
I don't know.
But I guess it is true in this classic cartoon sense.
Can you take that?
Can you put this dynamic in the Stone Age?
Can you put it in space?
And I never wanted to like lead the charge because I've been like, Scott, you've you've
existed in this world.
You've sold animated shows before.
Got friends in this world.
Listeners in this world.
True.
There are people where it's like.
People have voluntarily done art.
Correct.
Of cartoon style.
I'm like, the proof of concept stuff is out there.
Yeah.
And my reel, the cornerstone of my take is like, you got the dynamic.
And that's the thing that most people struggle to find.
You got the character types.
You have the dynamics.
You have the basic look.
And yes, like like saying, let's drop the Brady Bunch on mysterious island.
And everyone goes, I got it.
I understand.
You place those characters there.
My thing has always been I leave it to you guys.
Are you in the army?
Are you little dogs?
Are you in the future?
I don't care.
I don't.
That's not the point.
Just start with you three.
Yeah.
Everything you've gotten, you've honed through this podcast and put those archetypes onto
something else.
Over time, as it's sort of narrowed and I'll like send a link to like this podcast just
sold an animated series and you'll be like, that sounds bad.
We don't want to do that.
You've never outlined what the pitch is.
Yeah.
You were and you were clear even the first when you brought this up cold in an email
lot.
November 2019 is the first time that this came up.
It was just to me at this time.
And you did say like, I don't want it to be one of those things where they just take the
audio of a podcast and anime.
The Ricky Gervais show.
Yes.
And we're not pitching a podcast, a cartoon show about podcasting.
No.
And in my mind, not even pitching a cartoon show about grown men who love theme parks.
Wow.
I'm like, that's not the important part.
You take theme parks out of it.
Well, we'll see.
This is what's on the table.
Now over time, as I've tried to like, what's the cleaner way to get you guys on board with
this?
I've started to say, what if we really think of this as an untitled Jason Sheridan animation
project?
Uh-huh.
So this maybe, maybe, but you're just to announce what it is.
A, it is let's come up with what the PTR animated show is and B, within that, if it is Jason
focused, that would not be surprising.
It would probably make a lot of sense.
But it's one of the first things we're putting on the table.
Is it a Jason vehicle that you guys are in the supporting cast of or is it based on
the trio?
Are we looking at Yogi Bear?
He's a bad example because he's got Boo Boo.
Are we looking at Huckleberry Hound?
Are we looking at, Hey, it's the Hare Bear Bunch?
Is it based on the trifecta or are you guys in the universe?
You guys, I mean, look, there have to be Scott and Mike types in it.
Sure.
But I also, I don't feel a lot of ego about that.
If I can, if I, if I'm supporting, that's fine.
I think, look, we know who the star is.
Let's be clear about this.
We're on the same page.
We know that.
And I'm ready to be dazzled.
So part of the pitch now of this as the episode topic.
Now that's established.
Is, and Jason, you're allowed to bat the ball back and forth with us.
Sure.
But to some degree we're treating this like we have been called in to pitch Mr.
T on the
Mr.
T cartoon show.
We've heard there's desire there.
We've heard Mr.
T is open to this area.
This could be a good like part of the brand portfolio.
Right.
And it's sort of like, look, you're licensing out your persona and you would do the voice.
We want us to see what you're comfortable with in this space, how we build on this.
Right.
So I think there are a lot of big questions to be asked and I think we just want to work
through.
I think this is a safe space.
No bad ideas.
But some of the things I had thrown out in the past, the most theme park idea I ever
had was based around the trio of you three, you are scared adult security guards at a
small local theme park who try to rein in the unruly teens who cause mischief.
Who get the job, perhaps, because like us, they want to be.
We've always thought like, oh, we love theme parks.
Being at them all the time would be fun.
Right.
And what if the only jobs available were that?
And in a kind of unruly Six Flags situation, we would be viewed as authority figure.
We're three generations beyond the starting point of Six Flags.
And it's sort of it's owning more the central comedic premise of the podcast, not the dynamic,
which I think we can very much spin off into its own thing, but of like the contrast between
you guys being theme park guys and how most people think of theme park people.
Yeah.
Right.
Like maintaining the neuroses, maintaining the sort of like distrust of a lot of the
things around it.
Yeah.
Oh, I see.
It's like you guys are three ranger Smiths, but you're the heroes of the show.
And the comedy comes from like being so overwhelmed by the rides, by the kids, by all of that
sort of.
This is the probably the closest idea that, you know, when you're talking about like pitching
be, well, we have this other successful quote unquote thing that is to do with this.
So you translated this would be the closest one to that.
Now, would we be considered successful enough for that to transfer?
This is.
Well, I think you look, we got to throw that out.
I guess we just have to, you know, I feel like there's probably been a lot of podcast
byproducts that were sold via bakery and burmato.
Hold on.
I'm sorry to shock you.
I think this might, if people just start touting stuff.
So I think, and this is a safe space, it's club three and they include the listeners
in there.
So we got to come out of this room and this paywall guns a blaze in and say smash hit
podcast genre defining breakout.
But also having the clear angle on like what is the way to translate this?
Right.
Because there's been a lot of floating ideas.
And I do think there's a question of, is it better to do something that builds off of
what the podcast has proven in a textual level, like setting it into theme park, but not making
you guys theme park podcasters, putting you in a funny position within theme park ecosystem.
Sure.
Or is it like, I would relate it to like Ed Solomon and I forget his partner who he wrote
the Bill and Ted movies with where Bill and Ted were characters they did in their college
improv troupe.
Oh, I didn't know that.
And then started writing sketches for and loved and they would perform them.
And then at some point they were like, we should write a Bill and Ted movie.
But they did that not with having a sort of like Pee Wee Herman esque platform of people
demanding that.
Right.
They were just like, we like these characters so much.
What's the funniest movie we could write for them and then we'll cast actual younger actors
to play them.
Yeah.
And there's, I think it's a key reason why Bill and Ted works is like these guys have
spent a hundred hours talking to each other as Bill and Ted by the moment they sit down
to write that script.
They know the character so well.
Sure.
And I think similarly we could map you guys into a bunch of different places.
It doesn't need to be sold on someone sitting there and going, well, the numbers of the
podcast Rogan's doing X times as much as you guys.
You're trying to sell this based on the success of the podcast.
He's doing 1.
5 times.
But we're about, yeah, yeah, we're right at least barely.
We're right at his heels.
I'm not saying it's like it's an albatross around your neck, but you don't know.
There's, there's perhaps a cleanness to just making it its own thing.
And someone looking at this pitch and going, God, these fucking comedic games are so well
honed.
These personas are so precise.
And I feel similarly whenever any Jason lore comes up.
Yeah.
Well, the listenership explodes, right?
Right with this sort of like, oh my God, new Jason backstory unlocked.
Yeah, I got to draw it.
I got to dig into it.
We got to ask questions.
Uh huh.
Usually calamities.
Yeah.
What happens in an episode, you could fuck five minutes on the clock.
We have to move on to the subject at hand, but we need to ask you 10 follow up questions.
Mike, of course, talks about I've never forgotten anything I've ever learned about Jason, which
I think a lot of people have that relationship to you, Jason.
Yes.
I think you've found this category of my dear friend, Pat May, who's a friend of mine from
the linear comedy scene.
I follow into this too, where I'm like, you are incredibly skilled, comedic performers
and actors.
Anything you intentionally do comedically, I think is incredibly funny.
And also everything else on top of that is incidentally funny.
Oh, thank you.
It all just builds, right?
Sure.
So I'm just like, there's so much there.
And in the same way that you've always been Mike, when you and I have back channel text
conversations about like, what do you think the minimum order quality is if we want to
make action figures based on our podcast?
You always say we'd start out with a trial run of Jason.
Jason's the most toy addict.
Of course.
You could sell a solo Jason figure.
Toy addict.
That's the word for what a cool toy, like something with make a cool toy.
He's got the most variations.
He's got the most like.
Yeah, because obviously we talked about black and white Jason.
Jason with the mayor sash.
Little sailor Jason.
Yes.
Jason, Jason cutting a big roast beef.
There's this kind of thing.
I will like relay things that come up in our hangouts or text thread to Sims, my blank
check co-host.
And I'm like, and then Jason said, if he always goes, do the voice.
And I go, I can't do the voice.
And he goes, Jason's voice is just so funny.
It's so much funnier imagining him saying everything.
I'm like, well, this fucking animation.
Oh, wow.
So that's been fueling you.
You've used to sending things to the outside and they say, well.
The silhouettes are there.
The dynamics are there.
The lore is there.
But also I'm just like, Jason does feel like the character that just fucking is going to
pop in this medium.
Or even if the thing's a three hander, he's probably going to be the breakout.
You know?
So we just want to set up.
We know like this is our ace in the hole.
Yes.
Which is why we really need to pitch it to you.
Right.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
I mean, look, this is something I have often on thought.
Now, does it sometimes I've thought of things that I just think it would be fun to see Jason
versus is it a perfect like translation of his personality or what everyone likes about
him?
I have mentioned, I think on the show that I had, I've had an idea for many years called
the little Liddle stinker.
Yeah.
And I, in my mind, Jason plays this character Liddle stinker, who is a very much like a
little rascals type character.
Spilled the D's are we saying?
L I D D L E.
Yeah.
But then he also plays, it's a dual role.
He plays wealthy boy, his arch nemesis across the tracks, who is a rich kid, spoiled rich
kid.
So there's like, there's these ideas.
There's Jason.
When we.
That's not in that case, you're like, you're not naming the character, Jason.
You're not saying he's from Philadelphia.
It doesn't have to be like grounded in all the hard details of your life, Jason.
Right.
But we're taking like, what is the comedic juice here that we can apply?
I see that in both.
Yeah.
And this is, this is, I think, like we don't have to settle on this, but let's talk through
some of the big questions.
Yeah.
That at some point we're going to have to land on one side of.
Do we think the show is better if Jason is an adult or a child?
This has occurred to me and kind of pre brainstorming.
Posing hands on both sides.
I don't know.
I mean, I like, I kept coming into things that are like, where you're in the like 12
to 14 kind of range.
I don't know.
Or like perennial child or, or is it like, I think there could be kind of a magical beavis
and butt head nature to it where you're not really sure.
That's my answer is, I don't know.
Well, and yeah, you know what?
Define it as undefined.
I agree.
I think that, I think that's a good call.
Now here's, here's a lateral question.
Once again, we don't need to settle right here in the spot, but just start noodling
around this.
Is the Jason character human?
Do we like the idea of transposing him onto some other type of being or do we think we
want this sort of eternal kind of sluggo type?
Yeah.
Cause animals, obviously their lifespan is different.
So it takes away the mystery of the age, but it's, I'm like, when, when I think about,
I guess this is more of the three of us.
I think of the Cadillac cats from Heathcliff.
And once again, I'm not saying this isn't a three-hander.
No, I'm not saying, I'm just saying that this is sort of the universe I'm picturing.
So if Jason's like a fancy cat with a scarf, I like that.
And that's good to me.
That makes me smile.
I like that too.
If Jason is riff-raff.
Jason's got a big smile on his face.
Yeah, I like that too.
Yeah, yeah.
I think we can see right through to the cat.
This is what I'm talking about with the fan art stuff where it's like, you guys map onto
Bearswell.
You map onto these other things.
It always reads.
No, I think Critters is, you know, I'm of two minds.
Critters is great too.
I will say separately, I wrote down Little Stinker as a phrase and I looked it up.
There's never been a really committed to character named Little Stinker is a skunk.
Wild.
Whoa.
How has this never happened?
That's an idea.
That could have been one of the first cartoons ever made.
So there's a chance to grab that potential.
But I also don't mean to dictate that you've got to be a skunk.
It's key that these things are not mutually exclusive, right?
Like we can have this sort of like eternal youth Jason Little Stinker type we're talking about also be an animal.
But other ones you're like, this is a world where everyone's an animal.
They just happen to be animals because it's more visually dynamic.
And it's never really referred to.
You're not like cracking into the logic.
So Jason could be a little cat who is defined by trying to grab fish skeletons out of trash cans.
Or it could be a cat who lives in an apartment.
Much like how he would catch pond eels when he was a child.
He just said, oh, you never used to catch pond eels when you were a kid.
And we were just all like, what?
This is, let's just pin this right here.
I think this is an inarguable cornerstone of whatever the show is.
Pond eels?
Is pond eels.
Jason casually mentioning things that he thinks are universal experiences.
Yeah.
That has to be a key running dynamic.
Like, you all know this thing.
But the way the dynamic works, the full cascade of it is Jason brings up things.
Mike and I both go, what?
Yes.
Listeners go, what the hell do you mean?
Mike and Scott don't know that fucking thing.
Fucking morons.
I did pond eels every day.
That is the way.
That's really the full.
Very niche micro regional thing.
Yeah.
And the sort of thing where like, when I learned about Chicago, like tavern cut style thin crust pizza, I didn't jump down Mike's throat.
Because it's less unusual than like, oh scrap, it's like meat by, it's like a loaf and you cut slices and then you got to crisp it up and fry.
But some of us like pork roll.
And everyone's like, what is going on?
This is right, Jason.
And some of, I think in our defense, some of the thing is the what isn't necessarily that we don't believe you.
No.
The what is like, yeah, tavern cut pizza.
Pond eels, the word.
I think so often it's we're just so like caught off guard by what the specific is.
And let's see, it's funny when Jason says them.
Like it's that fucking voice that's dying out for full fluid animation.
Yeah.
Sure.
And I think part of it, like there's a way you can play it where it's almost like the Bort joke, right?
Calling out like it's so absurd to put this Bort.
Why would anyone make Bort immediately followed by Bort is the most common name.
It's going to keep on getting brought up for the rest of the episode.
You guys are proven wrong for calling out the weirdness.
Yeah.
The joke that comes up, the weirdness is normal.
Well, this is, I feel like I'm thinking of characters who have the like, maybe like Betty White and Golden Girls.
Or like somebody who's got like the old the stories from back where they were from.
And so the full dynamic is that we, Mike and I question it and then we are proven to be fools.
Right.
For I think a lot of it being like, right, is this hyper regional?
Is this like a weird family tradition you had that you think is universal but wasn't?
Yeah.
Right.
Some of the dynamics here.
I think a lot of it too is very often like you just saying tavern style pizza.
You very rarely use shorthand.
You will suddenly use full proper titles for the things you're introducing as if they're commonplace.
Tavern cut.
I'm just trying to get it in one concise thing.
And my brain does that and goes like, well, this will be the most shortest, most normal way to say it.
There's the, when you talk about the improv rehearsal where everyone brought food and you went to 7-Eleven and got the shack.
Well, it was like a potluck.
Three cans for eight people.
What was the dessert you said you got?
Well, it was, it's nasty to think about now.
It was red velvet Swiss cake roll lobe.
This is the thing.
That it's six words.
Both of you disagree.
Yes.
Both of you show the size.
Yeah.
Jason double.
No way.
Mike is showing.
He was sliceable.
No.
Don't.
Well, I mean Snickers bar is sliceable.
I just think the six word proper title for the dessert.
That he tracks it all.
Yes.
You do always have the full phrase.
This is what, so, so this is, this happened when we were on an improv team together.
We all bonded very hard.
It was a certain time in our lives and it meant a lot to us.
And Jason at the time sort of, I think became almost the like figurehead of the team.
Like we mythologized him for many different reasons.
He's very funny.
But I think he always had, even when he was 23 years old, had a folksy quality to him.
That would combine with sort of stuff you maybe never heard pond deals or whatever would just be funny.
Obviously he's a funny guy in general, but he also has a very matter of fact kind of way.
This was an idea that was thrown out in the text thread at some point was, is there a cartoon show where the rest of the show, the rest of the world is sort of modern animation style.
And Jason's character is like a Fleischer studio.
1920s rubber bows.
Constantly bouncing.
Right.
Where he is like the kid out of time.
Yeah.
I was wondering if time needed to play into this.
And then this was a side pitch.
There was a side pitch that was also, is the show that Jason builds a time machine so that he can go to his favorite time periods that he wishes he had lived through.
And when he goes there, the other people are weirded out by like, I don't understand your reference point of this.
You know more about this time period.
I utilize it more than we do.
I think there's something too.
I don't want to just like take an Austin Powers premise, but something that I find always fascinating is Jason's strong awareness of the 1920s and the 2020s.
Yes.
That another thing is that you are the only one of the three of us who knows kind of like the current like very online stuff.
The amount of phrases I genuinely learned from listening to this podcast.
Yeah.
Where I'm like, thank God Jason gave me the tip off.
And I knew about Rizzed Up three weeks before it became something everyone knew.
Yeah, I know.
I never knew Rizz.
But I think that is something that happens to Austin Powers where he is a man out of time, but then he starts embracing the current things.
Yeah.
So there's something to that, you're right, that he is, the animation style is old.
Yes.
He reflects that, but he's also like, he's a fish out of water in some ways, yes, but also is more in on the 2020s than everybody else around him.
This could be his internal main game in a show that is like about a trio, or this could be the larger framing of the show.
But I also think like you could, there are two ways to look at it of like, is it funny to place Jason in one setting and go like, is it Jason in space?
What unlocks if you just go the whole show is Jason in space or in the future, or there's certain comedy possibilities versus is it, and I feel like this kind of show doesn't happen as much anymore, but maybe this is an opportunity to bring it back.
You're sort of like every episode the character has a new job.
Oh yeah.
He's in a different profession.
He's wearing a different hat.
He's in a different place.
You don't got to explain it, but suddenly this episode, Jason's in the Old West.
This episode, Jason is working at a restaurant.
Like Mickey Mouse or Bugs Bunny having different like Bugs Bunny's burrow is suddenly in the middle of Yankee Stadium.
Right, and it could be all three of you.
I mean like Ren and Stimpy would often do that where it's like some episodes have the default of their roommates.
And other episodes, it's like now they're in space.
Now they're fire dogs.
Now they're this.
And the episodes don't usually start out with like, God, I got to find another job.
Let me open up the class.
It's just like start out with the character in the fun place.
Yeah.
Start out in the fun place and then you examine the real life trauma that every TV show we need the trauma examination.
Let's make it clear.
We're talking hour long dramedy.
Yeah.
Or half hour comedy.
Well, can I throw it real quick before we commit hard to road?
I just want to put this out here.
Felix the catcher today also, which feels very like the matter.
Yeah, it was purposeful.
Oh, new mythology.
Because there were many there.
He's had many different nicknames.
This is a little nervous when you brought this up.
He should be nervous because I like to identify.
I was explaining.
He's taken things out of his persona in the last few years.
Some of this comes from like one improv practice.
Many improv practices.
We were like putting on put on the spot to come up with nicknames.
But there is that.
There's that.
There's Jason's use of side piece for many years.
I'm trying to awaken a sleeping beast if you haven't noticed on this show, if everyone hasn't noticed.
What?
Yeah, I'm curious about this.
Jason used to be a little, let's say blue, more blue.
Ah, sure.
Never problematic, never said anything.
But he would use coarser language and there would be subject matter that was a little bit more sometimes sexual or sometimes horny.
And of course, this is a big cornerstone conversation of is this show for children or adults?
Exactly.
That's what I'm headed with this.
It could sort of be a Ren and Stimpy and that is the vibe of the old fashion.
It could be a tweener.
It could be straight up fucking adult swim, nasty random shit.
So fucked up.
Or you could put this on fucking Nick Jr.
Like there's any range here.
So let me just throw three different nicknames he had on the team.
One was PJ Grunts.
I forgot about PJ Grunts.
Which is a real strip club, I believe somewhere.
One of his nicknames we came up with was the corouser.
And then the third is a nickname that Marissa Jason and I when we would do three person improv would use.
And it's just leisure suit Jason, which I may have mentioned on the show before, which of course is the little character leisure suit Larry from the terrible dirty video game that no one likes.
A very blue click and point CD-ROM game.
Yes.
And it was.
Yeah.
I've never.
I've actually just watched a YouTube video of it.
I've never played it.
Now the corouser was funny because 2010, 2011, I was just stepping out of the plate and striking out at every, every dating a romantic.
And I was just like, sounds like a good runner.
So that's on the table.
Because I think obviously, you know, when you get a little older, you obviously you don't.
Look, I certainly was more blue as well.
We did improv a lot and my sister would come to see the improv shows and she goes, you're like always the one that says something dirty on stage.
And I'm like, I don't know.
Yeah.
That was the thing.
That was the times we lived in.
A very different time.
In the sleaze era.
OK, well, whatever it is, BJ Grunts needs to say that.
That is another term I've learned about the 2010s.
People call the 2010s the sleaze era?
Like Brooklyn, you know, aesthetic and music, you know.
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
Coming out of that era.
Wait, the 2010s were that?
70s?
We were in the sleaze era when we were doing long form improv.
I just want to let you know it wasn't actually as aggressive.
TV on the radio album.
Oh my God, that group game we just did.
Oh, that was so dirty.
The sleaziest blackout.
I got an idea for a new sleazy opening.
Oh, and that cool Fleet Foxes song.
We're like Scott, you have the most experience in getting an animation show off the ground, writing for animation.
You're here with the laptop cracked open.
You're diligently taking notes.
Yeah, I'm trying to shape it.
I'm like Mike.
I imagine you probably know the name of the guy, the dude who read the Mirage Ninja Turtles comics and was like, I should fucking license this shit like crazy.
Oh, I forget that guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me go to Fred Wolf.
You're the sort of overseer.
Yeah.
And I think because of your history with Jason, but also your commitment to the archiving of the lore of Jason.
Oh, you're the keeper of the holocaust.
You're almost like the Pablo Hildago, the Steve Sand Suite.
The Jason lore.
We were rushing to the same fucking reference point.
By the way, Steve, I've played trading cards, Star Wars trading cards with him on the Star Wars convention show floor one time.
I mean, but like that kind of like.
That's who I am.
Keeper of the lore, keeper of the secrets.
Yes.
You throw a pitch, you go with Jason, do this because no, but you know what he would do that's kind of similar.
I'm in the Jason story group.
You're the head of the Jason story group.
I know.
What's his name?
Pablo Hildago.
Yeah, I'm that of Jason.
Maybe we should just explore the notion of what.
I have a little pad in there too as well.
PJ Grunts, you're correct, seems to be a strip club in Oxnard, California.
They may have changed the title.
I think maybe now it's PJ's entertainment, which implies that they have freed up PJ Grunts to be used elsewhere.
I mean, that's firmly in the adult area, but can we explore PJ Grunts a little bit?
Who can certainly be a carouser?
Yeah, I mean, Fritz the Cat and sort of that era animation also interests me when you're thinking about plugging Jason's persona in.
Imagining like an R.
Crumb, Ralph Bakshi style Jason.
Exactly.
That's interesting too.
Can the the 20s, 30s man out of time be running a modern strip club and like the modern Jason have a progressive, non-shaming view?
That's completely ethical.
Unionized, we're just a few miles away from the only, I believe Unionized strip club in Los Angeles.
Maybe the country, it's in North Hollywood.
Now see, this is what I like the way he just talked about it right now.
It's funny to imagine within an animated strip club setting.
I think part of it is not just the old timiness, but the genteel quality.
Right?
Even in the the seediest of environments.
There's a class to Jason.
John from the Carousel of Progress is probably the greatest influence on Jason's personality, I would think.
Just that kind of just like, oh, hello there.
Have you told Jason the joke I made?
I don't know.
This is kind of everybody I think, while down in Florida.
We did Carousel of Progress in maybe the second or third room and I turned to Scott and Mike and I went, is this Jason's inside out?
That all the characters in Carousel of Progress are different facets that added together.
Because then once that was said, then we're watching every scene and like, oh my god, the sun is kind of Jason.
John is kind of Jason.
Orville is kind of Jason.
The dog is kind of Jason.
They're all sort of like
And similarly this mapping game of like, you get different comedic juice depending on what decade they're in.
You can transpose into different places, but the dynamics are so strong.
That's what we're talking about.
It keeps like clomping him from
You talk about like the Carouser.
Like some of these things where you're like, maybe this is one episode, maybe this is a thing that comes and goes.
I definitely feel like Cub Reporter has to be some part of it.
I don't think it needs to be his main occupation.
I don't think it needs to be a Jason on the Beach show.
But maybe in this Bugs Bunny way where you're like, sometimes some episodes are he's on the case.
Good way to get him from place to place.
Can I close out PJ Grunts a little bit and say
Scott's just doing the actual writer's room-y.
Yeah, I guess a good way to get him from place to place.
Not aggravated, just like realistic.
Oh, my PJ Grunts idea.
I think like why a 20s, 30s person, I don't know if it's time travel,
I don't know if it's fell in a well and came out in the 20s.
Or just a man with a different vibe.
Like it could just be
Oh, sure.
Just like a Fisherman Man.
But I was going to say, if PJ Grunts, whether or not it's a literal 20s, 30s person,
something else that you bring up Jason a lot is like, being in show, the business of show and razzle dazzle.
And I think maybe you're drawn to work at a strip club because that's the modern vaudeville.
It's the only thing that's left.
People come out, they do an act, and then you're the Kermit of the Muppet Show of a strip club.
What if in 2024, Jason is trying to
he's opened up a new strip club, but it's much more like Footlight Parade.
He's bringing back the razzle dazzle to that industry.
He doesn't like that filth across the street.
They take things off.
No, he wants like a taste.
You can see a tasteful amount of leg and that's it.
And if we end up at full bush, then it's been earned.
Then you've gotten a show before him.
So here's the question.
We can circle back to what makes Jason a man at a time.
Is it a given in this universe or is there some magical buy-in?
And again, as we're pitching it to you, feel free to
I'm just realizing how much I watched and enjoyed Carousel of Progress as a very young child.
And went on a trip in the fall of 1991 with my family and my grandparents.
And a number of years ago, as we started working on this, I had heard the master track of Now Is the Best Time of Your Life.
And I was talking to my dad about that.
He was like, oh yeah, that was the one when your grandparents went down with us.
They were humming that all week.
And as you're saying, the Carousel of Progress is just different parts of my brain.
I'm like, yes, this is unlocking something.
I always really loved my grandparents and also Nick at Night.
I would usually be more interested in their stories or television than what was going on at school.
I just want to put a pin in the idea that it doesn't have to be like a time travel or fish out of water.
Because just the idea that you just vocalized that you really loved your grandparents and Nick at Night.
And that makes me understand the locking into the old timey.
So somebody who just as a child wanting to retain something about your grandparents.
It's a very sweet idea.
I'm watching it.
I'm watching with my son fall in love with my parents.
And so that could just be a good rationale, I think, for the out of time nature.
The thing that unlocked the inside out thing was in the various stages of Carousel of Progress.
When John is communicating to his family members in the other rooms and he keeps saying things like, all right, dear, whatever you say.
And we were like, have we heard Jason say this to James 20 times on this trip?
And not in a reductive way.
There's this very like, well, I just want you to be happy.
Whatever floats your boat, sweetie attitude that is just funny to imagine mapped onto any dynamic or like exchange you have with other people.
Now, I think even just talking about like, does he take over a rundown strip club and turn it into a Ziegfeld Follies type thing?
The hottest show in town.
Is that the format of the show that allows him to literally change hats every week?
Is like, Jason gets a new job at a new place or enters a new environment and that environment exists in the normal, cynical way we know it today.
Oh, yeah, where it had some spark in the 50s and 60s or whatever.
And now it's just a road, it's whatever.
Right.
And Jason tries to like roll everything back to the old timey kind of classic cartoon version of it.
Where I feel like you talking about loving those Nick at Night shows, a lot of the same like old timey references that I feel like I share with you that are wedged in my brain or because I watch so much fucking Looney Tunes.
Yes.
Where like Bugs Bunny is making offhand references to like the social norms of the 40s.
And I'd say to my mom like, what is this?
What is he?
What?
And they're like, well, men used to want to wear hats in the company of ladies and this and that.
There's something funny about making you this very classical cartoon type existing in kind of a cynical world.
And then you make everything the way it used to be back when it was glitz and glamour.
You know, old time, none of this blogging.
You're an old time cub reporter.
You have the number in your hat.
He saves journalism by bringing back the cub reporter spirit.
And the image of that too, not like the because I was like the other night I got like an eww out of Jane because I was like, wow, isn't Lauren Bacall really beautiful in these clips from Killargo?
I was like, because we were someone someone people posted clips online.
She does this silly little dance at one point.
And and she she was like, oh, yeah, well, you know, the lighting was, you know, really good.
You different back then in the film.
And and I was like, yeah, and they would spread Vaseline on the camera.
And then I ruined the moment.
Come on.
I go and like and Humphrey Bogart was on his second failed marriage at that point.
And he was a drunk and she's like, oh, I don't want to think about that.
Maybe part of it, maybe the arc of each episode not to make it like two wrote a formula is you like come into a place that's sort of depressed and lost the magic.
You transform it to the old way.
And then at some point you identify, oh, this is why we evolved as a culture.
And you get a point where you're sort of in a middle zone.
We can't totally swing things back to the fifties.
There are some dark sides of the right.
It's like if Santa do if there was another 30 or 40 minutes on the do where they're like, this might be too expensive to do.
We're not bringing in enough money.
We have to close this after after night.
You identify somehow the key fault of the way they used to do things.
Why did it change?
You know, but you go on a full journey and then you go off to your next job or you go off to the army or whatever it is like the bitten licorice pizza where they open a waterbed warehouse.
They're like, what do you mean?
There's a gas crisis.
Right.
What does that have to do with waterbeds?
And you idiot.
Right.
And it's like, well, time to reset status quo for next episode starts with you marching in through a new door.
So is he kind of a he's kind of a Mr.
Smith, I guess, kind of like coming in with a cart full of optimism.
I think so.
And I think like animation good medium for this, because also, as you're saying, you like visually transform the environment, you know, when you come in, your influence changes the color of shit.
That's very flattering.
Thank you.
I'm talking about the show.
Not real.
I know we're devoting an entire episode to saying that you have the star quality that will make all of us rich.
No, but yeah, he comes in, hands out top hats and sparkly canes.
The first improv scene I ever saw him do was with two other people, with Jake Riegel and Tony Charlene.
And the first thing you said, you popped on stage, you picked up, did some space work and you said, oh, you dropped your top hat.
I mean, first thing, and you were 22, 23 years old.
Yeah, 22.
Just entering an environment trying to put a little old fashioned class back into the equation, you know?
I, the only plus up, and it's not a plus, tell me if you think it's a plus up.
I don't say it's a plus up.
But the only thing I would say is that Jason goes in, tries to make everything nice and old timey and he just destroys everything.
And then he's on to the next thing.
That would be my only.
Lyle Landley, like a benevolent Lyle Landley type.
I think it's sort of like it works until the moment that the fatal clause acknowledged and then it's like, I've got to get out of Dodge before they catch me.
Yeah, what I think it should be, because look, he's a little bit of a huckster too.
And let's say he's a music man fan and that's influenced him as well.
And he's kind of a little stinker.
So I think, yeah, like he it's almost like think of it, what John Taffer does to bars.
He fixes it up for TV and then you check the Yelp reviews a few months later and the place has just gone to shit.
It's even worse.
He saddled them with some sort of like food that they cannot make consistently.
It's too, the ingredients are too expensive.
But it popped on camera.
As far as you knew, a big crowd came on opening nights.
The wood chip smoker gun died after a week.
I mean, that's a cleaner way to frame it.
He's sort of a known expert who's being hired to revive these things.
Or I think is there something a little bit more mythical of him being like a Harold Hill where it's like this mystery man rolls into town.
And just like just wants to fix.
Excuse me.
I couldn't help but notice you had a help wanted sign.
Yeah.
I've talked a little about my fondness for the Canadian show, The Littlest Hobo.
A dog comes to town, fixes all of the problems that are currently happening in a little family unit or workplace or whatever, and then keeps on moving on.
I've always wanted to do something in that format.
It could just be like there's no real agenda other than like the kindness of your heart.
You want to like give to give things some razzle dazzle.
And then you keep moving on and don't see the actual fallout of the razzle dazzle.
The climax of every episode is the whole thing falling apart.
But you're like, well, Mr.
Mike, but doing my way out of town, walking off the girder, smiling.
OK, now I don't want to just rip off Mr.
Magoo, but Mr.
Magoo has been summoned in relation to you before.
Why does Mr.
Magoo show up anywhere that he shows up?
Is he just kind of like going about his day?
He's always trying to do a thing, but because he can't see, he ends up in the wrong environment, not knowing.
So there's kind of a goofy aspect of just goofy tries stuff.
Is it like Mr.
Magoo just wants to do this?
No, Mr.
Magoo, it's like, time for a dentist appointment.
And then he like walks onto the freeway and the bit is that he thinks they're like cleaning his teeth.
There wasn't too much to that show, was there?
It's always just like he's like, here I am to return my library book.
And then he's in like Kosovo in act of warfare and somehow dodges the bullets.
Like that's always the Magoo bit.
Because usually he ends up on the high beams of scaffolding at a construction site.
That's almost every episode is on the high beam.
I think that was such a boom time back then.
There was so much being built that there were always girders being lifted.
Like his goal in any short is just like do a mundane task or like a routine errand or whatever.
And then he doesn't understand what's happening around him.
He's a Mr.
Bean, but Mr.
Bean is aware of like all the, you know, whatever, all the toilet paper's flying off the thing.
So he's got to like, Magoo is somebody who'd never like a baby's day out after that.
It is baby's day out.
Where like, he's a hero who doesn't realize.
I don't think that's, I don't think Jason's that passive of a thing.
No, no, that's what I'm saying.
I think it's closer to goofy because goofy is like trying stuff.
Yeah.
And you don't have to carry over the like, you don't need the continuity, the growing narrative of, wait, so this is happening after Goofy has failed at five different sports.
You're like each time it's just like fucking clean slate.
Yeah, we don't need, I think we all agree we do not need continuity.
No.
I think we all probably sort of agree on that.
I think, yeah.
Look, this comes up in real pitches too.
Like now, now everything, now everywhere actually watch shows to reset.
You have to come in and pick these places.
Like, no, no, no, you could start anywhere.
You could start with episode eight.
You could start an episode four, even though nobody does that.
And where you, this is as little as possible to know.
This might be a classic like two 11 minute segments in a half hour show.
Yeah.
Or even it's resetting within the block.
Which also, you know, if we want Jason to not be saddled with Mike and I, Mike and I can be the friends.
We'll happily take the back spot.
We'll come up with something else to do with our 11.
I'll throw this out, right?
Though that's interesting.
You're saying you'd be.
You'd be the Cadillac cats.
You'd be the US acres to the Garfield and Friends.
That's all good.
That's a good spot.
Let's be clear.
It's a good spot.
Well, you know, it's like the 1250 spot.
You can be a little weirder.
Yeah, that's true.
It's the backup story.
Do you remember on the the Pink Panther cartoon show?
Not that the theatrical shorts, although I guess this was maybe part of it as well.
There's a character named the man who was like a little egg with arms and legs and a fucking push broom mustache.
And he was always just a guy just doing his job before the Pink Panther mucks everything up.
And every episode, it's like now he's painting a house.
Now he's like a surgeon.
Now he's whatever.
You know, it was sort of like the archetype of this guy.
There is a universe in which Jason is the little hobo character that carries over.
But like there are the archetypes of the Mike and Scott who exist in any place he enters.
I see.
You know, and perhaps is Jack Benny style sketches.
And they're always Frank Nelson was in every store he ever went into.
Oh, OK.
And like similar to like sometimes Elmer Fudd was a hunter.
And sometimes Elmer Fudd was like weirdly occupying some other job.
Yeah, you know, sure.
Where it's like there's a design language for you guys and your voices.
But every time it's ostensibly a new character.
OK.
But that when you need an authority, you need the authority figure.
Right.
Yeah.
Yeah, I could see that.
Yeah, because like, yeah, one one of us is the boss every time.
One of us is like the owner of the competing establishment across the street.
You could be the coworkers who he has to like rally and, you know, transform.
Yeah.
You could think of you could it could be even a set voice cast that is always just recast.
Right.
With different roles.
At this point, we're talking about the Commedia dell'arte archetypes, you know.
Yes.
Of course.
Thank God you said it finally.
Yes.
Because I do think the three way dynamics have to be in there to some extent.
I'm not even saying it needs to be explicitly like every episode,
there is a guy who gets too many notifications on his phone and is checking for deals.
Yeah.
But some of that energy needs to be in there.
Can I throw out and we can circle back to what we've been talking about.
But I in my my little stinker notion, I was thinking about and I took myself out of this.
I think there is some like the critter idea.
Yeah.
And that could be the both of you.
If little stinker is a skunk, if it is just a skunk.
And I'm not sure.
I don't know if you're I don't know what critter you see yourself as.
A raccoon or something that's like that's burrowing through.
What I'm getting at is some situation because like I think you guys the way to get you two together is that you do often share a common goal,
which is which is the getting of treats.
Yeah.
But you go about it in different ways.
You deal with it in different ways.
Mike's way involves more neuroses, involves.
People are going to see that I waste the boba at the everyone will be looking at me.
Jason is kind of is pretty direct and simple.
It's just like I wanted it and I got it.
Yes.
Straight to the windowsill where the by school.
It's kind of like wait, what is the characters where I mean, oh, well, this is Roger Rabbit and Baby Herman.
Oh, sure.
Where Roger all the stress happens to Roger and Baby Herman is unaware that there was any stress in the attaining.
Right.
I think if we're viewing this as a three person, the angle you're talking about,
are you the Roger and are they two different types of Baby Herman?
Well, that's yes, that's the dynamic of it's three of us.
Right.
Because that is what I settled into being the dynamic of the show, which I never thought would be the dynamic of the show.
Yes.
Is that it feels like Scott Scott is the one who's just like, what are these two up to?
But the beauty of the dynamic is you have much like any good pitch, you have to compare it to a lot of successful shows of the past.
Did you think about the story pitch for Raiders before you started the episode today, the famous story where Lucas and Spielberg and Kazdin are sitting down and brainstorming what Indiana Jones would be?
Yes, that comes out of Spielberg being like, I want to make an Indiana Jones movie so badly and they won't hire me.
And Lucas being like, here's a lateral thing in the same way that he wants to make Flash Gordon.
Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
That's what I'm saying.
Indiana Jones comes out of Spielberg wants to make James Bond.
Oh, you said Indiana Jones.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I said it twice.
Spielberg wanted to make James Bond and they kept rejecting him.
Right.
And then Lucas was like, here's like an idea for a character I have that also allows him to like globetrot, go on adventures, meet different beautiful women.
Yeah.
But it doesn't just feel like a ripoff.
Right.
You're taking some of the elements you love of it.
And I do think there's something to the other kind of dynamic I was going to relate it to the sort of like, well, Scott, just the humorless like school marm in that situation.
No, he's not.
Because you're you're right.
It is surprising that's become the dynamic.
But the key magic to the dynamic is it's sort of the the arrested development thing where you're like, Michael's like, I'm the straight man.
All these people are crazy.
He's as crazy as everyone else.
Sure.
You know, you're as silly in your own way.
Yes.
Yeah.
You fall into this default of being like, boys, can we please keep things on?
Jason and I just happened to have the Marvel superheroes.
We have deals.
There are these funny things that you don't have any context or appreciation for.
So obviously, clearly there's once I get into it, there is the densest language.
We've not only ever been in a talk about CVS and target deals, there's been possibly hours of talk about.
Yes.
And all off stuff you've never even heard.
It's just between Jason and I on text or something.
That's a lot.
And that's my role.
I do try to like I try to be kind of like a referee.
I feel like I try to throw a flag on the field for anyone who's listening and goes, wait a minute, you're just going to say that word and keep moving.
You're just, you know, like whatever Circle Star Special.
And I'm like, wait, wait a minute.
Back up.
What is Super Circle Star Special?
And then and then it's explained as if obviously.
Yeah.
Some of it's probably just natural shorthand of working together for so long.
I'm just like, Mike probably knows about the city target experiment.
Also, we were sometimes.
Yes.
Going back to the city target is a defunct term, by the way.
Jason and I actually were using it past when the Target Corporation has actually decided they don't want to use it.
I figured that out.
That was the one that happened where I said, what the hell is city target?
People said commenters said, like, use context clues.
It's a target in the city.
I'm like, I fucking know that.
I'm not an idiot.
What I'm saying is, why are you saying city targets so much?
I've never seen one of those in my life.
And then I look it up and city target has been retired for eight years.
But I'm the crazy one.
Well, it's been retired.
This is what I think.
This is what I have to be with.
Griffin, I got to be here.
Not like here.
Exactly.
Yeah.
That's what animation.
Let's all let's amp it up a little bit.
Wait a minute.
Yeah, I got to be up there.
I got to back up from the mic.
This was purchased using a 20 percent off CVS coupon, which is what I've been getting lately and not the three or four or five dollars.
So wait, wait, wait, wait, but your pad of paper in your pen.
So what 20 percent off that is what I'd have to check.
It was total because first of all, I bought one of these pens that is four different ink colors because I was obsessed with them when I was a kid.
I haven't had one of these in a while.
So I treated myself red, blue, green and black all in the same pen.
All of this was like five twenty.
And I think it's because mostly because of the pen.
I believe the pad was a dollar fifty.
So 20 percent off got you.
So I was like a dollar.
It was a dollar or so.
We've been focusing on Jason because there's a lot of momentum there.
Right.
There's a lot of shit.
Look, we could.
But there's a silent killer in the room.
Well, I'm just saying once you reintroduce one of you guys back into the equation relative to Jason, you start unlocking these other things.
There are other parts of it.
And the side channels of the triangle.
Like, I don't think it's always you being exasperated, the two of them.
No, because there's also Scott and I also not knowing that Jason's talking about.
Right.
And you guys connecting on music, you know, or disagreeing on it.
Like, there's like all the angles of it.
It is nuanced.
And even just Mike so excitedly being like, I want to explain everything about this pen to you and the victory of getting this pen.
I'm like, if this isn't on the show.
Some people bring out the best in other people.
I bring out the eccentricity.
You're the muse.
You're like, I embrace those weird little thoughts.
You are like, this is my muse.
And that's I would say that that tone I just illustrated not here, but up here is only I think that's new to the show.
Are you telling me this outside of the show?
Yes.
I don't do it as a parent.
Don't do that to your child.
They will get scared.
So I'm supposed to just believe.
Hang on a minute here.
I mean, I think we're starting to analyze like some of the values of making sure there is a trifecta going on here.
Sure.
Can I can I throw out this is what I this this some of the trifecta might play into this.
And I don't you know, I think we're throwing out that we're not gravitating towards the theme parks are a part of it.
But I do flash to like City Walk hijinks and hijinks in the efforts to get treats and stuff.
So if that's why I was going to like all agree like unquestionable cornerstone.
Yeah.
Of the project.
No, no question.
Three candy makers.
Could be all the running of a candy factory.
Oh, yeah.
Well, put a pin in that.
But that's why I was flashing to like it could be a City Walk type environment.
And it could just be like it could be like a Burbank Empire Center to be the kind of place that's in every town.
Just like a big shopping center like we're fascinated by.
Imagine like it's it's yogi and boo boo.
But in more of a of a mall environment or just somewhere where there are a lot of treats to be acquired.
And the two of you have your different ways of going about it.
I feel like Mike's is maybe more like Jason is like one one track mind.
I want that big lolly.
I'm getting that big lolly and you'll do whatever it may be like a certain degree of like Scooby Doo when he smells it.
He floats in the air towards.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
This is a greater than any of us can understand.
I don't want to reinvent the wheel here.
Let's just do that.
I think that can happen.
We can take that.
I think the thing is, hey, look, Canna Barbera took everything they ever did.
We are goddamn taking the smell of treats.
Being its own means of transportation.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's been a long time.
Let's do it again.
But that's where like, you know, I think Jason will steal.
He'll pilfer.
He'll go through the dumpster.
He'll I have one in my head of like that he would like pose as like a pose as a cuter kind of animal or like like transform into a cat real quick.
Meow.
So you could go home and like charm a lady who's probably got tons of treats.
But then she's like, too.
There's too many cats back there.
Are they're all like trying to have sex with you and you're like, I can't do it.
You get into high jinxed via you would do whatever it takes to procure treats.
Mike wants to do it on the up and up the right way.
It's imagine like that you are a raccoon.
He loves the structure.
Yes.
Yeah.
He loves the process.
He's a raccoon who still downloads the app to get deals so that like I can rest at ease knowing I didn't pay full price for the two giant boxes of good and plenty.
But that I but I did get a good deal on it.
I have two things that are going to be waiting for me when I get home that are both.
I got a bike for one hundred dollars from ideal vibes.
I think usually two eighty four hundred dollars bike for one hundred dollars.
I'll bike or yours.
It's going to be mine.
I hope you got a bike that costs a lot of dollars.
I hope it's good.
I feel like a bike that costs a lot.
I don't know.
I did it quickly.
I got a deal.
I think you want to pay a little more.
I got to get rid of this dead weight.
Number two.
Yeah.
Super seven had a glitch on their turtle wave, whatever eight or something, whatever the wave that a wing nut in it.
And there was a glitch and you got like 30 or 40 percent off who preordered it like a year and a half ago on their site.
And I did.
It's coming today.
They're discounted.
I'm so excited.
I have to pay full price for them.
This is right.
You want to create.
This is interesting now.
This this new sort of like area of thought you've gotten into.
That's the microphone we want.
Let's be clear.
I spent about four days going back and forth beating myself up of like, all right, I'm going to do it.
I'm going to buy AirPods.
And I was torturing myself like this is an indulgence.
This is how I operate.
As much as I follow the same deal sites and my feed me will feed the beast.
An element is that I go back and forth way too much.
I don't jump in the way that Mike does.
Yeah.
I spend money too easily.
And Jason is very cheap.
I'm maybe right in the middle.
Jason's tight.
And then after a month, a few weeks of like having lost the left AirPod and never finding it, I was like, I'm giving up buying a replacement.
Here's the thing.
Which sucks.
Which is an eighty dollars.
You will never get back.
No, you're fucked.
But I'll probably find the original one.
The second you bought it.
I guess that's a lot.
Well, it's like one you're saying.
Yeah, for one.
OK, yeah.
So it's like 60 something plus tax and shipping.
Oh, when they told you and I went with you to the Apple store and they told you you had to get a new iPhone and you had to pay full price.
I never saw a more stressed out man.
I've said it on the show before.
You cracked your neck and away.
I did get it down.
What do you mean?
It ended up being like three hundred because they just gave me a replacement for the older model.
You didn't like barter with them.
No, I did.
But I didn't have to buy like the newest one.
Yes, yes, yes.
OK, so here's here's what what's now like sort of sparking for me.
OK, go ahead.
Because we're getting something here, which is key to the dynamic and the energy of the show, which does not have to be theme parks.
But it's the subsession with like this weird love hate with like crash, crash commercialism products, places, experiences, systems.
Right.
Yes.
Love theme park.
Hate it.
Hate on the biggest level.
Fuck these executives and their bad.
Like, oh, but the things that they make.
Yeah.
Is there something to like?
And I don't know if it's three stray cats.
I don't know if it's three different types of woodland stray cats.
I'm out.
I'm storming.
I'm out of this fucking meeting.
Which of us is Slim Jim Phantom?
I don't know if it's three squirrel nut zippers.
OK, all right.
I'm listening.
Is it a raccoon?
I don't know.
Three real big.
Yes, real animation.
We want it to be animals.
It's like maybe it's a raccoon and a skunk and a fucking turtle or whatever.
Right.
But it's like their woodland area has now been bulldozed by a sort of Glendale Galleria.
Yeah.
Open sort of city walkable mall kind of concept.
Yes.
And rather than being furious that their lands destroy, you're like fascinated by it.
And you have a little bit of the Yogi Bear dynamic where he's like, this is my park.
They've turned it into like a natural, you know, reserve.
Yeah.
All these humans come with their picnic baskets and I want the fucking picnic baskets.
Are you like outside the perimeter during working hours?
You wait for them to close and then you're like, now we get to check out the new chocolate factory.
Or I would I mean, my only fix for that would be that we have varying degrees of I think Mike would be let's wait.
Let's wait until eight o'clock and then there'll be nobody there and nobody will look at us.
But the other we have Jason's like, anytime, let's go now.
Now would be good.
Part of it is maybe like you're sort of owning the turnover at malls like this.
So every episode can be like a new thing just opened.
We haven't gone to this yet.
Sure.
You want to experience all these things.
Now talking about like Alvin the Chipmunks invoked earlier.
Yes.
I think that's a key line of like whatever part of you is like, well, hey, now, wait a second.
You want it to be Simon and not Dave Seville.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like within it's not you're trying to get me to be in the triad.
No, no, absolutely.
Yeah.
Because I was in my version of this.
I don't know if I'm a Ranger Smith.
I'm willing to be a Ranger Smith.
That's what serves the story.
You're trying to get me into the into the group.
Simon is the checks and balances within the group.
But he's not like we shouldn't do this.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I am on board with everything.
I just want to make sure that we're doing things right.
We've explained things to the listener.
Wait a second.
Yeah, yeah, because it is like, wait a minute.
Let's just discuss it before it happens.
Alvin and Theodore have similar games, but distinct personalities.
But they're usually unified and Simon's like adjusting his glasses and going like, well, wait a second.
Sure.
Are you saying versus Dave Seville coming in and being like Alvin busting the fun?
I'm not against the whole thing.
You're not.
Uh huh.
And this is not where the juice is that sometimes it's like the part you agree with is the surprising part.
What's the difference then between Alvin and Theodore?
Alvin is like the gung-ho like leader fearless.
Right.
And Theodore is like he'll get his head stuck somewhere.
Theodore is kind of like the innocent.
Yeah.
Alvin's like a schemer.
And Theodore's maybe like, I don't know.
What's the id ego super ego breakdown?
Yeah.
I don't think we can go along these lines exactly.
It's one to one.
I like Jason is innocent plus schemer.
Yes.
And I like and I like Mike Mike for cartoon purposes, I think has to be a worry ward.
Yeah, sure.
I agree with that.
You're I mean, you're in on the schemes too, because you're all just trying to get in to Pinkberry.
You know, whatever it is.
What about like a Tokyo Dome City scenario where Tokyo Dome City is outside mall, but there are some rides as well.
Yeah.
And there are chain restaurants like to me, that's the perfect like version of all of our.
Fascinated by the human world.
Yeah.
And that kind of way and needing to find a way to get access to these things without getting shooed out of the store.
Does it run into interacting with humans like is the idea is it just going to be the three of us on it like Toy Story style adventures where we sort of have to be together?
Yeah.
Or yeah.
So that's what you're thinking.
It's more like closed a little bit because there's like the funny part of like, as you said, like if Mike is a raccoon and the raccoon is really concerned with making sure he gets points for all of his purchases.
Yes.
Hold on.
Let me load up the app.
The apps a little glitchy.
I need to scan my barcode.
Yeah.
The app Wendy's app was not working last night when I was driving through.
But don't worry.
I added the deals to the QR code and had them scan it and it still worked.
This is a key.
I could have mobile order.
I'm going to pin this as a key dynamic point.
Yeah.
Mike explaining the thing and then preemptively saying, but don't worry.
I still got the deal.
I didn't lose.
I got it.
Jason also knows Jason.
The skunk also knows about the app stuff, but I'm the one who would then go, can we just focus on getting the Wendy's?
Yes.
You're right.
Right.
I was really like losing my mind the other night trying to get Taco Bell app to work because we were like a few miles away and it's like a get to the Apple pay part and it just times out.
But you're right.
Key distinction.
You want the Wendy's.
Yes.
You're not saying like guys, let's not go in the Wendy's.
But why are we complicating the Wendy's is what he's saying.
Right.
It seems like too much.
It's too much work to get Wendy's a couple dollars off.
That you're doing.
I'm more than willing to just steal it off of somebody's plate.
Yeah.
That's why I think I like the Toy Story element you're submitting of like you're in fear of getting caught.
Right.
To some degree.
But part of the like tension comes from what's the best way to do the thing.
I just yeah, I just feel like it might be a little limiting because we can't talk to humans and you kind of unless there's other I guess other animals in the gang or whatever.
I mean, there is I think there's a lot of things where the animals don't there is there is that animal human boundary, but there's still a lot going on.
We could certainly talk to that's what Yogi Bear rules are.
Sure.
They talk.
Yeah.
That's fine.
Let's just make it that I think maybe I think we need we discussed Jason's charm and the like and then that like just that likeable breezy nature.
I want him to be be able to have to charm a lady.
I'm looking for.
Yes.
That's what I'm saying.
You know what a fun kind of have your cake and eat it too thing is if it's set in a world in which the animals and humans can talk to each other, but the animals are second class citizens in a way where you're like, hey, no animals allowed in the store.
Like that's part of the scheming is you can relate to them directly.
Yeah.
But still there's like a bit of a barrier.
How about this?
How about this in society?
Because it makes it a little heavy.
I'm not saying we can't tackle heavy issues on this show.
But what if Jason's folksy show where we're tackling the issues of the day?
What if we're sort of just teenage animal humanoid animals where it's sort of like the shopkeeper shopkeepers a little suspicious.
Sure.
But then you're saying like basically a full Zootopia world.
Everyone's an animal?
No, not necessarily.
OK.
We're given side eye the way teenagers would be at a mall because they might hang out for too long.
They might at worst they might try to steal stuff or they'll like get a bunch of people here and cause trouble.
But in fact what you're trying to constantly impart onto everyone you come across is that you are good boys.
Yeah.
Yes.
You would never want to get in trouble.
In the very first email about this, you did say it's a shame that the title good boys is taken.
Right.
And this is the benefit of this pitch happening four years later is maybe it's back in play.
Yeah, that's true.
It's a good point.
Is that maybe enough time has passed.
Yeah.
And like animation takes a little while because maybe there are other than animals or other teens.
Maybe they're just human human teens that are bad as well.
And we're like, no, we're we're good.
We're what we're going to say.
Oh, I was going to say you just, you know, smooth things over.
You send a cookie bouquet to the good boys team and you just write a note that just says no hard feeling.
And then they smile and they're like, well, can't be mad at them.
Well, a cookie bouquet is I'm writing it down.
I mean, another perfect example of Jason's joke was apologize to the makers of good boys using their other project, which is casually throws in cookie bouquet.
The thing show of hands I've never heard of.
And I got I assumed no hard feelings just coming up because that was a movie, but I didn't know it was the same make in classic tradition.
Jason brought up a thing that I didn't know.
I didn't know it was a maker.
Yeah, I didn't know it was the same people.
No, you got to know your creative teens.
Fellas, this town, you know, we might want to attach these guys.
I like yes, I like no art.
Yeah.
But yes, you're right.
And then we got caught on some other thing.
I mean, cookie bouquet is absolutely like he has to Jason has to like charm an old like a granny type lady with a cookie bouquet.
I think part of what I like about the animal, the wild animal idea in a universe where you can communicate with humans, but which like I'm not because I invoke Zootopia.
Of course, the most trenchant racial allegory.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The ultimate movie about bigotry of the.
All the all the answers are there anything facing our society.
I don't think it has to be like that, but I think a lot about like Snoopy cartoons where there was this element of like selectively Snoopy is allowed to behave like a human being and just do his things.
And then sometimes they slam the door on him and go like no dogs allowed.
Yeah.
We'll let you do this up until a point.
You know, yeah.
Where there's sort of like an uneasy alliance of just like, well, you can't have wild animals loose in a restaurant.
I hope you guys don't take offense.
And I also like this element because I like that pressure against you guys because it gets down to the like you're at a theme park, the place where people cut loose, try to have fun.
And for whatever varying like strategies you guys have on tackling things, all three of you will basically default to I don't break the rules.
Yes.
Yeah, right.
There's a there is a proper way to do this.
You might change viewpoints on what the proper way is.
Right.
Do I like would I have a smartphone?
Would I have stolen a smart phone?
I think you gotta have a stolen smartphone.
It would be stolen though because they don't give animals smartphones.
One of us either either Jason or I stole it and you weren't pro stealing, but you are pro deals.
So since I didn't do the stealing of the phone, but I'm not above using the stolen phone.
Right.
And I think you talk a lot about the plan you somehow found yourself on.
You realized if you also had this other product and you're paying for that, even though you don't use the second device, it actually brings down the cost per month.
Sure.
I think is always to complicate the plan.
Yes.
We have an A to B and Mike is like, but think about if it's a point one.
Yeah.
Then a point two and then an eight point B will work.
And also working out a big thing would be I waste two hours of working out.
Yes.
The whole plan that might not be good.
Absolutely.
I waste time.
Yeah.
Which is a thing I do in real life.
Question I mean, when sometimes when you get what you want, you're like begrudgingly eating, like you're begrudgingly enjoying, like you seem exhausted at the work it took to get that.
Certainly when we're talking fast passes, I am exhausted from doing that.
Yeah.
Yes, that is true.
It does make the day worse for me.
Watching you work through that in real time, it was like the moment we'd like be on the frozen ride or whatever and you'd be like, God, I mean, you guys gotta give me some credit that worked out really well.
I kind of nailed that.
Yeah.
And then meanwhile, in the ride on real time, you're like frantically setting up the next fast pass.
That is it's I don't know.
You don't even get to enjoy the spoils of your riches.
Yeah, I enjoyed fro.
It was more the living with the land.
Living with the land is the big one.
I was on my phone.
Yes.
But yes, there's an anxiety to it.
But again, I've said this before.
My brain wants the anxiety.
I don't know what that is.
I don't know what it's trying to fill up.
What that like a psychologist would tell me is wrong with me.
So that is yes, it's wanting to give myself stress.
Yes.
It's wanting anxiety.
Uh huh.
But a lot of that too is like.
I've never felt less stress in my life than when I was able to take some of the living
with the land opinion and put and bounce it back.
Oh, and I said that I thought they could shoot this spruce up part of it.
Yeah.
Oh, getting truly.
It's like every time you add to it and take it off me, I feel like I got a massage.
Let's make it clear.
Our plan going into that live show was that I was going to back you up that I think living
with the land is bad.
Wow.
And then that narrative took over.
You know these are recording, right?
I know.
You know our audience is hearing this, right Griffin?
Because I felt almost bad.
Like did I abandon Scott?
I was saying I will stand with you brother and agree.
But then the narrative of Mike wasn't even paying attention.
He was checking.
Yeah.
He reluctantly admits it could use some sprucing up.
There's like.
There's a lot of like Griffin commenters who are like laying in wait, waiting, wait, not
touching a keyboard and they're all type type type right now.
I mean, here's my very controversial opinion that I like soft floated to you guys.
I think they should rethink that ride with Wally.
I think they should get Sigourney Weaver to do the voiceover.
The script can be exactly the same because that like Axiom ship voice is very educational.
Yeah.
But a performer with I don't know, a little more juice, right?
Like someone who's really going to sell those lines because in the current narrator of and
I was just like, man, Spaceship Earth gets a lot out of the fact that Judy Dench is the
one saying the stuff, right?
That there's a gravitas there.
I'd say so.
So bring in Sigourney Weaver.
She plays it straight, but you got the gravitas.
And then in some of those areas that feel a little untended, a little worn down, you
just put in a little Wally.
Here he is.
What does he do?
His whole thing is to try to regrow shit on land.
Sure.
So you aren't taking it away.
You're not taking anything away.
No.
And neither am I, by the way, but never have I had an idea about living with the land that
takes anything away.
A watering can on his head.
You just have a few like animatronic or even static Wallis that are like doing sort of
little funny scenes.
As much as little Osmos on Autopia.
Right.
And I was like, we were in that hallway that's very dusty.
And I was like, yeah, the dusty hallway.
People are really, people are really need the dusty hallway to be there.
And I'm like, now imagine if you just put a little animatronic Mo in there.
I'll clean it up.
You don't even clean it up.
But he's worried about how dirty this ride is.
And they don't even take away the dust.
And now it's sort of like additive.
Everything's additive.
Now it's a feature, not a bug.
This is, now you said you would stand with me.
So I feel like I have to stand with you on this.
But I'm also, I'm scared at this point.
I will.
I'm suggesting putting IP onto a beloved perfect ride with zero problems.
The room is spinning.
The room is spinning, Griffin.
I don't know.
It's, it's in line with everything that ride is trying to communicate.
Like this is how we need to.
The idea that the greenhouse grows from, this is what came from the one little plant at the end of Wall.
Yes.
That's kind of neat.
I don't think Jason's even, Jason's the biggest living with a land defender.
You weren't upset about that.
No, I'm not.
I think that because I forgot about the one little plant at the end.
It's right there.
I think it's.
And they're back on earth.
Like that's they've flown back to earth and planted the boot.
I'm going to put you on the spot.
Don't feel like you have to do this.
No pressure to do this.
But being how much heat is around this ride.
Sure.
Are you willing to say I'm Jason Sheridan and I endorse this idea?
Oh, yeah, I will say it.
Say the sentence.
I am Jason Sheridan and I endorse this idea.
I couldn't even get it out.
But I endorse it.
You heard it.
I also think like the idea I'm pitching keeps living with the land around for
another 20 years, like it almost guarantees it.
Right.
Yeah.
Without radically transforming it, you're not doing fucking journey into a man.
Imagination and like butchering.
I'm just like, you add a couple little things.
Who's going to complain about Sigourney Weaver?
How about you don't even take away Bean Boy at the end?
None of that.
It's all there.
Yeah.
Or tomato.
No, you keep all that.
And Wally's like staring up at the screen going like, wow, like that's all I'm
suggesting.
I love Bean Boy.
He's basically interacting in real time with the ride as it exists and you preserve it.
That's a good idea.
What about just draining the track and using it for storage?
Well, now he's really taking the feet off of us.
I'm Scott Garter and I have nothing to do with that idea.
I don't need this right now.
I do not stand with you, brother.
I just wanted to sit.
I wanted to sit there, but you can't go on it.
Let's get back to this.
I feel like there's something in this notion.
I'm glad we covered some of that, though.
A lot of business.
We're not even done with the business, by the way.
But is there I don't I mean, I think there's something in here.
Animals, animals after treats, animals, if you're treats all united in this goal, but very different ways of going about it.
And then who are we against?
Are we against like guys essentially?
Like is it like uptight store of people who don't realize that like if we were a little looser, it could be a little more it could be fun to have animals around this place.
That's interesting because that way you're like the intermediary figures, right?
The humans, the employees of the individual shop, they're not your enemies.
They're not saying shoo shoo.
They're almost saying, look, guys, I honestly I wish I could let you in.
But this guy who's my boss.
And then it's a message about like capitalism and corporate because we always as with an organization like Disney or something, I think we like the people on the ground.
Yes.
And then the bad stuff comes from decision makers.
Right.
So there has to be some, you know, it's like, you know, the Mr.
Westfield or whatever.
And maybe there's like the guy who's in charge of the entire thing.
But also there like there could be many guys.
Yeah.
And then you have like this is my chain and we're opening up a new location here, you know, at the Schomburg Mall.
And this just began to be set at the Schomburg Mall.
Yes.
It doesn't do us any benefit.
If we got the participation of if we if we could go go in with the IP of something as as you know, hot in the marketplace as the as the Woodfield Mall.
It also West or Westfield or Mills could back us.
It could be like an American dream style, absurd mega mall where it's like you guys will never reach the end of it.
You know, yeah, it's not even new businesses opening up.
It's just like the time it takes to get from one end to the other is as many episodes as you run.
Yes.
Yeah, I like the idea of a giant expanding mall that can also be like we've fallen on our times.
Half of these storefronts are the Instagram photo opportunities and, you know, vintage arcades that look like the old arcades, you know, just desperation filler.
Look, an animated show set in a dead mall is definitely an interesting idea.
I don't know if anyone here has a full deck on that that they tried to pitch already.
And I don't know if any listeners have any connections at a stream or production company.
Anyway, you know, just just a thought exercise like it was missing one puzzle.
No need to DM on that three rascally.
That is true.
Yeah.
You know, I didn't have the well, maybe I just need to take what I just plug all this in.
And I like it.
The thing I like about it being a sort of newer American dream style mega folly is you can basically almost go sci fi with like anything could exist in this mall.
Yes.
This mall can contain an entire theme park.
Yeah, because there's an indoor ski slope that can contain the doctor's office.
And like, yes.
Oh, yeah.
There's suddenly an urgent care.
Right.
The one.
That's a very real.
I mean, I feel like I forget if this was in my idea or not, but I feel like we're not that far from like a cemetery being in a mall.
What else?
We got a ton of space.
And look, those are expensive.
Right.
As long as you're OK with, you know, dead bodies being in a dead seers.
It's own ecosystem.
And then it's no longer.
Oh, you guys are wilderness animals who are trying to sneak in to the shops of this outdoor mall.
Yeah.
It's like you like live in the shadows.
Mm hmm.
Right.
I also think there's kind of a nice like, you know, like the the animals being fascinated by the that's always like some of them are like American dream, especially I think was probably like, you know, it's wetlands.
We can't we're going to destroy it.
And where does the wildlife go?
I like saying with the wildlife.
We prefer.
They like it.
Yeah, they want to go.
They want to be part of this place.
They're chasing off the urban explorer.
Yes.
Backpack type.
You know, and the tension of we really want to be good boys.
We really want to play by the rules.
But they got this.
They got these fucking hangups about us being animals.
We're still trying to do it the most upright way possible.
I think it's an allegory for teenagers.
And as I assume we were all teenagers who were good teenagers, probably were greeted by the scorn that go that come.
A rowdy teenage boys are going to cause trouble.
And you can.
No, no, no, no.
I'm one of the good ones.
They're going to get there.
They're not here to see the move.
They're not here going to sit and watch Firehouse Dog.
They're here to they're here to have intercourse.
I say because one time I saw I was one of the only people seeing Firehouse Dog and there were people having sex in the back row.
The only time I know I've been in the room with people.
But yes, no, I'm the person never I would never sully a movie theater with sexual.
I think you're right.
That that's like that's what the analog is for the animal status is like you're lumping us in with these other wild creatures.
Yeah, we actually want to play by your rules.
Is it called like good creatures?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
Is it good?
Good is in there somewhere called the good boys.
And the good boys, you know, they get it fights it if the good boys are not human.
I mean, boy, I think it's a poster and it says the good boys and the three boys are a skunk, a turtle and a raccoon with this super compelling design.
I don't bump on it and go like, well, which one are they?
Yeah.
Do they have clothes?
I mean, my guess is you do and we don't.
OK, I think it's part of living in the mall is that like you're showing off your new graphic tees every week.
Oh, and you know, I also maybe I'm just I just don't wear any clothes or I just wear I stole one item of clothing with it.
But Jason's the current one.
So Jason is keeping up with the hottest trends.
Yes, I'm wearing I'm wearing this airbrush shirt that says Riz on it.
Yeah, it was specially made for you by the airbrush booth.
I'm just trying to get a good boy.
There's something so evocative about good boy as a term.
And I can't think of like good critters.
It's not just the extra syllables, but it doesn't convey the same thing of like these are good critters.
It's like, no, this is like a moral stance.
We identify as good boys.
Oh, you know.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
I don't I'm just trying.
Is there was there a one syllable way to animalize it?
Yeah, I'm trying to think.
Yeah, creature.
Good furries.
Yeah, that's probably it.
Yeah, it's a good boy to dogs.
You know, no one's bumping on that.
We need to be dogs.
One need to be.
Was there already a movie called Good Boys?
That a Henson?
Correct.
Wow.
There you go.
Uh huh.
It's dogs are actually aliens and they can talk.
Is that what it is?
I believe in Matthew Broderick's The Voice of the Dog, who's like, wow, we actually come from Planet Bark.
Why have I stayed away from I have watched it.
How long?
Twenty years ago.
How old is it?
Yeah, I think it was like early like oh, three or four.
And what was the Will Ferrell Kevin Hart strays strays?
Yes.
Good strays.
No, probably not.
No, good pets isn't right because that's good pups.
Huh?
Good pups ain't bad.
I mean, that ties us into being dogs, but I think we could be different types of dogs.
Yeah, the dogs is funny.
Yeah.
Good pals.
Good boys just feels like it immediately belies a state of mind.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, that's like Margot Robbie.
I think all the listeners, everybody felt like you're like in a car pass and a joint around and like, whoa.
I feel like.
I think Good Boys.
It's like more of a place.
It's a phrase.
Yeah.
So if we're dogs, like I'm trying to think you could like escape a cage.
Every night, I guess.
But then you are missing.
We're in a pet store in the mall.
We go out and wander around.
Yeah.
You're missing a little bit of the this mall replaced the wilderness.
And these animals have chosen it instead.
Yeah.
They want to be here.
They prefer it.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Well, I don't want to make the name drive it.
I mean, if we generally think we're in the now, what is turtle right?
We think turtles right.
You tell me.
I don't know that there's an animal.
We feel worried to skunk and raccoon.
Do those feel like they're working?
Yeah.
I want everybody to have input into this.
Jason, do you want to be a skunk?
Sure.
OK, kid.
They're misunderstood creatures.
There are a lot of pieces that have been thrown out with scum.
It is scum.
Some limbs from previous ideas.
Good stinkers.
Good stinker.
It could be.
I mean, it could be three dogs.
Mm hmm.
Good grunts.
A skunk with a pocket square.
Here's the other thing.
Our idea also still allows Jason to come into the businesses and be like, I got an idea
for how to prove.
You need some of that old timey magic.
You know?
Yeah.
Just put it on a trench coat and a top hat.
Hello.
His grand skunks brought a 1930s energy that he tries to carry on.
And I think there can be a strip club in the small.
Absolutely.
If American Dream's not already doing it, they should be.
I guess you've got various types of lizards.
Can Mike be like a, because you're tall, can you be like a big, like a stork or a, what
are they?
What are they?
Like a big crane.
Like a heron?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, a heron and crane.
Maybe I could, maybe I'd take raccoon and you become a heron.
Okay.
A mighty heron.
A heron's big.
Is Michael a flamingo?
Is that, are you a flamingo?
A flamingo is fine.
I don't know which flamingos are getting displaced from.
Flamingos feel kind of.
If it's a Florida mull.
Yeah, that's true.
Okay.
Well, I mean, I think that helps.
Oh, well that's interesting.
Well, then you guys can talk about how much you love the humidity and I'm the one who
doesn't.
That's right.
We do love.
You guys are crazy.
Yeah.
That's how it'll go.
And if it's in, and if we set it in Florida, then I think it gives Jason power, the power
that you have when you go to Florida.
Oh, right, right, right.
I did think there's one like, the potential hangup in this, which is there was, there
was one episode where we, a while back where we discussed, I was like, I think we need
to open up our voiceover abilities and start trying new different voices on this show.
And Jason insisted that he couldn't do it unless he got a lot of training from you.
I mean, I don't know if we discussed this together.
No, I just heard it on the episode.
So I was trying to pay you a compliment.
I appreciated it.
Would you be willing to, in addition to, I say you get EP fees on this.
Would you be willing to also accept voiceover coach money from Jason?
Yeah, I would not refuse that money.
I mean, I feel like I said this, I texted this to you at the time, but I was like, I
don't, I certainly don't think I'm like Mel blank.
I'm like, there are like three sort of ranges I feel like I have a natural facility with
I can go like further in this direction, pull this further back from what my speaking voice
is.
Is one of them the manager of a Marshalls who wants a skunk, a heron and a raccoon to
get the hell out of the Marshalls?
Let's also say herons pretty popular right now.
Blowing up the box office.
Oh yeah, I know a lot of a lot of critical cred to herons currently.
Lends an air of legitimacy to the show.
The good boys and the heron.
There we go.
But I feel like similar to like what we're talking about here, when I get like a VA audition,
I'm like, what's the thing I can like accentuate or scale back from what I think my natural
vocal qualities are in the same way that you identified the shift in register of the way
to be like, well, hey, now wait a second.
Yeah.
Here's the thing.
Can you teach Jason just how to say, come up and see me sometime in the right way?
Oh, I thought he did that pretty well.
Yeah, I think he did, but I think there's room for improvement.
I don't want to be so critical here, but.
You know, constructive criticism is very helpful.
Thank you, Mike.
Exactly, yeah.
So can you give him sort of some famous lines and explain, tell him how to say those in
the right way?
Well, let's be honest.
The one I think that needs the most work is Stitch.
I would agree.
Yeah.
Do we have any, I feel like you've done voices similar to that.
Here, let's start with a blank slate of your current Stitch.
Can you give us a?
Oh, how nice.
Now, what are we missing?
Where do we get it into the actual Stitch?
OK, so let's say like what if.
What if this is sort of like the Jason animal character, whatever animal he ends up being
in sort of like goblin mode, right?
When he's got his access to his snacks.
Sickle mode.
Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying?
I would say it's a slang term from six years ago.
Six years ago before the court case.
You're taking.
Before the pre-trampling.
Wait, this is another thing.
You just did one I don't know about.
What do you mean trampoline?
Travis Scott concert incident.
Yeah.
Oh, that has something to do with sickle mode?
Travis Scott's sickle mode.
Said to go sickle mode and then people died?
Well, I mean, it's the song.
He redefined what sickle mode was.
It's apparently going to the great beyond.
I'm afraid he's gone sickle mode.
I always think about with voiceover stuff like Hank Azaria has talked very openly about
all of his Simpsons characters are a bad impression of a different movie star.
And he's like, Mo for me is like early Pacino.
Yeah.
And I can't quite hit early Pacino, but my version of that starts to be its own character.
And like Wiggum is.
Edward G.
Robinson.
You know, like a lot of those, I feel like similarly, it's like, well, let's not focus
on is Jason trying and failing to hit Stitch.
It's like, what are the unique qualities of what is coming out of you when you're trying
to do Stitch and what do we intensify there?
So I'm like, if you take like what your Stitch is right now, pull it even further away from
any need to match the classic Stitch voice and then sort of like add on to it the idea
of like tummy full of sugar and caffeine.
Okay.
I love this.
That this is a mode that he goes into in success.
Going feral.
Yes.
Another thing we used to say about Jason is that he'd start getting wild and we said he
was going feral like Wolverine.
Oh yeah.
So I think you took it.
Feral boys, a potential.
That's true.
I think it partly came out one time when we would hang out in your old, un-air conditioned
apartment in the middle of summer.
Sweat box, yes.
A sweat box.
And I would just start to like lose it a little.
Like I've just been downing ice water, but it's like not working.
Ice water is a very old person thing to say.
Water with ice.
Cold water, but it's so hot inside.
Like I don't know.
It's a little crowded in the mall today.
Should we?
Should we get caught?
They got ice water.
Tall glass of ice water.
You know what's another Jasonism I just remembered that has really stuck with me for a long time?
Was it the Starlight Coke that you were trying to get?
Oh yeah, yeah.
Scott to drink.
Scott into.
And Jason mentioned, I poured myself a glass right now over ice in a highball glass.
It's a tall, more skinny glass than a punch glass.
Most people, and this is a thing I love about you Jason, most people would just say, you
know what?
I drink it at home.
And Jason paints a full picture.
Yeah.
That's right.
Right?
I'm a storyteller.
Yes, a storyteller.
A weaver of words.
How is it just going from the can, it's over a highball glass on the rocks.
Sure.
On the rocks.
His Coke Starlight.
So he's a little stinker skunk who drinks Coke Starlight over ice from a highball glass.
I guess I could be a bear.
We talked about us being a bear.
I feel pretty committed to Heron frankly, but.
The bird feels a little.
It feels right.
And a bird constantly on a smartphone.
It's not just height, you have like the lankiness.
That's true.
A bird on a smartphone is funny.
You're saying it and I'm imagining it.
The bird who's constantly chicken on his feathers.
Are the animals real scale or are they sort of a little cheated do you think?
They could be a little bit bigger.
So in case the skunk is talking to a human woman, it's not like it's a tiny, you know
what I'm saying?
Let's say to use a classic cartoon sort of scale, let's say maybe they're all five apples
tall, six apples tall.
That means short though.
Extremely small Heron.
I think you basically say like everyone is at least half a human sized.
I think you could grow the animals and shrink the humans.
Yeah, possibly.
So it kind of meets.
Wouldn't it look weird if Jason takes a human woman as a wife or a girlfriend?
Right.
But you also want to maintain the height size differences between the three of you.
Of course.
Yes, that's true.
Which like being a bird allows you to be a little leggy while also not being six foot
five, which like a bear you get too tall.
Because like I want.
You pulled up the cats here.
That's riff raff.
Yeah, yeah.
Cleo is his girlfriend.
She's a cat as well, but she is much more like a human woman.
She's a human woman's body essentially.
And riff raff is a cute little cat.
We know what Cleo looks like.
Listeners need no explanation.
Yeah, so.
Childhood paramours.
I cannot get the word because I just always am afraid of saying the band name paramour.
But that's the word, Jason.
That's the word.
That is the word.
But it's not spelled right.
It's not spelled correctly, is it?
No, it's paramour.
It's the same word.
That's the word.
I thought the word ended in O-U-R.
I think it might, but I think you still say it.
The name is spelled differently, but that's just a little kind of clever twist.
I think they spelled it different for whatever reason.
It's like the Beatles.
So say it the same way.
Let's hear the Google pronunciation.
Let's check it out.
Paramour.
Oh, no, it's the exact same spelling.
No, it can be spelled.
Oh, OK.
Here, I see.
So the paramour came from avoiding.
You didn't want to say paramour.
I thought after the first time it was just like we all laughed.
And then when I brought up the second time, it was like now we all say paramour.
I will be honest, I've been confused about where it's been.
If you were commenting on the first time, but now I know it's one.
I get it.
OK, you were avoiding paramour.
I get it now, too.
When a paramour is exactly where you should have been.
And see, this is the type of gold you can't invent out of a whole block.
This is the sort of, you know, in Shark Tank terms, it's the proprietary element.
Yes.
No one else has access to this, the raw feed.
I think we maybe landed on a successful notion, but I brought a prop that might illustrate
just one other way that we could go.
And I don't have other ideas for us here, but this is a prop.
This is something that Jason gave to me and I don't want to.
I don't know.
I think it'll just spur something.
It's Mr.
Taffy.
Mr.
Taffy is this is a Jersey Shore thing.
It is a Jersey Shore thing.
It's a little Taffy with a bow tie and blue and blue arm bands and boots.
Some of the Discord listeners were very nice and sent me a Mr.
Shriver's gift basket that had a Mr.
Taffy.
Oh, geez.
Oh, wow.
So you have a new one.
OK, great.
So which I, of course, brought those back for your children and my adult girlfriend.
So now they were a too happy asshole.
Not a cat.
Taffy successfully did become a beloved toy of my son, maybe second only
to another favorite toy of his 20 Kingos.
Have we ever actually explained the Kingo thing on Mike Foley?
Didn't we?
I think we did.
Well, you gave me some on Mike.
I gave you a couple on Mike.
But then many, many, many of different that all came in different, usually like one at a time.
I ordered them all.
I think it was 20 in total from GameStop Deep Clearance.
And it was a couple different form factors.
It was keychain, Funko Pop, Marvel Legends.
Yeah, three shapes, which I mean, that's that's like kind of amazing for a kid to like see
the same character in many different forms.
He understands the idea of like artistic interpretation now.
Like what story can be told?
Griffin, I just sent you there's non-mints on entertainment Earth Kingos.
They're five dollars.
What you don't know is for the last two years, any time Mike finds a site with low price
Kingos, he's like, I'm just saying.
I'm like, the Kingo thing's done.
I can't send more Kingos.
That was a time.
Wow, Bono, U2, Zootv, Bono and the Octon Baby car is thirteen dollars marked down from 2249.
As a Funko Pop?
Yes.
Can we get back to the cartoon pitching already?
I do think.
That's so stupid.
That's the dumbest shit.
You said ooh and thirteen dollars for that.
Bono driving a stupid little car.
Why does the car look like that?
Because that's what the car looks like from the era of.
Some stickers on it.
I'll do respect.
You know I'm usually aligned with you on matters of collectibles.
That sucks so hard.
You just showed us.
Staring blankly at it.
Take away the Funko Pop.
The car is dumb.
I think if it's just the car, you go, well, that's the iconic car from Zootv.
Of course, of course.
The famous Zoot.
We did an entire episode of McFisto and all that.
The car never came up.
I don't remember the car.
I'm just adding new.
The car is at the sphere though.
We did talk about this.
DJ is DJing in the sphere at the car before the show.
I've seen that the sphere DJ is in a little car.
That's the car.
The Zootv car.
Which was on the original tour.
So it's a little bit of a reference.
The key part of Mike's game is the.
What do you mean?
How do you guys not know what I'm talking about?
Do you think Prolithe Spider-Man, the name of the man who climbed the sphere causing.
Is that his name?
He claimed to be pro.
Yes, he was the pro life Spider-Man.
Somebody would get someone climbed to the top of the sphere.
I did know that.
But then pro life Spider-Man.
He was doing it for a cause and he caused a hundred thousand dollars in damage by doing
that.
Did he really?
Yeah.
I think the sphere can afford it.
So his.
I was wondering, do you think he knows about the car?
Probably not, right?
Yeah, I don't know.
Maybe the man.
It was it was it an anti-abortion stand.
The command climbed the sphere.
It was an abortion.
Trying to raise money.
Raise money?
In the middle of Super Bowl week.
All eyes on Vegas.
You know.
All eyes.
That nation looks toward Vegas.
And I think everybody saw it.
Got it.
Oh, pro life Spider-Man.
In no way is the little man's message lost on it in a gigantic.
On a screen that is showing gigantic ads all day every day.
Anyway, look, that was all a sidetrack to say, you know, Jason could be a we could talk
to the Shriver's people and Jason could be Mr.
Taffy.
the show and has the demo reel.
Yes.
You know, that's the real cash in.
I do think Miss looking Mr.
Taffy does make me think you guys need to be partially dressed.
OK, yeah.
And maybe it's like Mike's wearing a graphic tee with no pants.
Maybe Jason has a bow tie and a bowler hat, you know.
And I'm just and I'm just Vizor and no other clothes.
But the classic animal, you have some.
Maybe Hawaiian shirt.
Vizor and Hawaiian shirt or Vizor and shorts or like something.
But I like that no one has a complete outfit.
What if we're rats and we call the show Mall Rats?
I might be able to work out a deal.
That's why we need is a man on the inside.
That's why I suggested.
Are we do we feel like we're we're whined?
It's not bad.
Morris is not bad.
It's not what his name on actually make any.
And it does feel like in the 70s, it's what they would have done.
How do we make Mall Rats the animated series?
They literally are rats.
Yeah, yeah.
Actually, rats.
Yeah.
Fuck, that's it.
That might be it.
All right.
OK, OK.
Well, hey, we got it.
I officially take little I'll take Little Stinker back.
That's a project and I'd like that to be live action.
Actually.
All rights have reverted.
Great to you.
Yeah, yeah.
Action.
And we're going to wait like I want Jason to be in his 50s when we shoot it for real.
And he's going to be playing a child.
Wow.
Like a Clifford.
Sort of more of a Clifford.
Yeah.
Well, like a Clifford, but even older, playing even older.
Something America loves.
I bought back the rights to Little Stinker.
A little more like Mickey Rooney on Eagle Heart, a little more sinister energy just vibrating
off.
You play every character on Little Stinker.
I know we're trying to wind down.
But what if we wind it up?
Well, when we were doing.
I'll go get some tea and come back.
I need a caffeine boost, but Jason genuinely.
Jason crushed a Red Bull.
He's ready to go.
Yeah, really.
But yes, we did our Curious Case of Benjamin Button episode on Blank Check.
And that's a movie that had like a 20 year development process as this like Paramount
owned the rights to this short story and no one could crack it and all these key teams.
Just real quick.
Are you sure that's not Paramount?
Paramount?
I know it's spelled differently in the band.
But see, and that one, I actually it's like I knew Paramount from very like a suspiciously
young like why does that child know about Paramount?
Dolphin Western Company.
They own those movies, but not Hanna Barbera.
That was a licensing deal, grandma.
We had this big aha moment that one of the versions of Benjamin Button that came close
to actually happening was, I believe, late 80s, Frank Oz, Martin Short, Benjamin Button.
Oh, I heard that.
Oh, yeah.
And that's really kind of actively happening and then falls apart.
And I kind of now have to believe that Clifford is like Martin Short's breakup project of
like I was getting into the idea of like playing a little boy in the wrong clothes.
Right.
And it's like the cheaper version.
There's no supernatural buy in.
You're just like the James didn't get James Bond version.
Yes.
Of Indiana Jones.
I'm a child in an adult's body.
It is an interesting movie to think about having a 20 year development process.
And I'm very curious about like what the if they ever get the Confederacy of Dunces made
because that's been like so many pairings.
Also, the Benjamin Button story is like really fucking short.
It's just an idea.
It's evocative and people are like, there's got to be a movie here.
Right.
It's not.
There's an impenetrable novel or something.
And what you end up with is horny old man Benjamin Button, horny old man Brad Pitt.
If you ask me one of the greatest characters in cinema history.
It's seven, but I look a lot older.
Do you feel satisfied with this thought exercise?
I think huge right.
We kind of landed on something.
Yeah.
I feel like I learned things about the dynamic and ourselves and how we come off.
And yeah, what's that?
It was kind of secretly.
I thought one of the reasons this was the idea.
I thought there was a nice kind of like opportunity to analyze the dynamic.
Not a way of dissecting the frog, but really learning to appreciate what is the pieces
of the frog.
We went off mic for a second, a little bathroom break.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And there became a very real conversation about like, you know what?
The podcast wouldn't be the same if it was just any two of us.
I did appreciate it.
I feel like you did like.
Like maybe there's a little therapy session, little idea generation.
I do sense you maybe from afar because you'll check in, you'll chime in with thoughts on
episodes and then all the way up to something like Frank Marshall wanting to like open it
up more.
It does feel like you were like.
There's a good conversation happening here.
Let's stay in this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
You want like you want to get in here, conduct traffic flow and see what happens, which I
find I'm always I'm game for.
I find that interesting.
And during the bathroom break, I saw the bathroom was out of toilet paper and I was like, I
bet I know where the supplies are kept.
I can solve this problem.
I can fix it.
That's an episode.
And I ran to the closet and I ripped open the Costco packaged toilet paper, put a few
rolls in the bathroom.
What kind of plot?
What was it?
It was just a standard bath tissues.
What are you normally buying?
I'm usually buying whatever's on sale.
OK, so you don't have like you're not.
I don't really have a preference on that.
You don't have a brand where you have a certain toilet paper as a kid.
Like is it a family choice?
I feel like we had a lot of blue and pink toilet paper growing up.
Do you remember the era of colored toilet paper?
I do remember the era of colored toilet paper.
To match the bathroom decor.
That was the most.
You don't see that as much.
Can you reproduce the way you have to hold on to the way you said bathroom because it
wasn't bathroom.
It was bathroom.
Bathroom.
I don't think anyone has that luscious.
Well you got to put a little mustard on it.
No one can do an impression of Jason.
No, no you can get like the vibe but I've never been able to do like a really good impression.
It's representative.
It never sounds correct.
Yeah.
No, not accurate.
I've heard both of you guys relay like Jason said a really funny thing the other day and
you just do a different type of voice.
Yeah, I can't.
You're giving me enough that I can imagine it.
I see what you're doing.
There's an energy but it's not.
But there's no fucking sound alike who's going to take this part away from you.
I love it.
Maybe I should.
I guess I've never really sat down and done.
Not that that's how I do impressions but stuff usually just comes easily or it doesn't.
But not that I'm good at impressions I'm just saying but gruff comes fairly easily is all
I'm saying.
But Jason's more of like the, you never heard about that huh?
Like it's just a folksy.
I got to do this.
But you know what you're doing right now it captures a quality but it's not.
Yeah, it's not what it is.
Because I remember before we started doing the show you would sometimes do an impression
of Jason and you would sometimes do an impression of Jeff Garland and they were the same.
Really?
Yes, absolutely.
And once I got to know Jason better because I feel like I knew Jason from stories a little
more first even though we'd run into each other.
But then I hear some stories and then I met him and I'm like there's not any we aren't
even in the ballpark.
Swing out of me.
I don't remember.
I don't think I've ever brought that up.
Did I have much more energy back then and I just got too excited when talking about it
because I feel like these days that wouldn't be the case.
I wouldn't have the same voice.
But maybe back then.
At least at the time.
Yeah, I think you hadn't.
But that happens to me too.
I'll like fold like I you only have like three impression avenues.
Yeah, sure.
One falls into the other.
Mike did just text me the link to Eternals Kingo Funko Pop not mint.
Specifically the boxes are not mint.
For a while you were sending me videos of your son playing with the Kingos.
And the one that was the best was he had a garbage truck.
And it was picking up Kingos.
He had little plastic garbage cans filled with Kingos and the truck is picking them
up and dumping them into the back and then the camera panned across to the front seat
and the garbage truck is being driven by a different Kingo.
It's like a society where everyone's a Kingo.
Lately it's been a dump truck and it's just he puts all the Kingos.
It's like one of the most bulk items we have in the house.
So it's filled the role of like, OK, I think kids do just want a bunch of things that could
be Lego blocks.
In this case, it's Kingos.
He'll take all the Kingos, put them in a trash truck and then just dump them out into a pile
and put them back in, which I don't know.
That's literally what would have happened to the Kingos if you hadn't given them as
a gift.
He's also he's going to grow up like Jason saying to friends like, you remember when
you were growing up and playing with your Kingos?
Yeah, I'll have this very specific.
And then future me, a version of his dad going, what?
What was that?
No, I didn't have a Kingo growing up.
This is loop that I've created.
We didn't all grow up with 20 Kingos at the home.
Well, if you feel satisfied with this thought exercise, I think this was you.
Yeah, you know, and I think it shined a light on some things.
I really enjoyed it.
And just before we wind it down, because I want you to this is your this is your shot
in the Club 3 throne.
And I want, well, a couple of things.
I want you to be able to wield your power however you want to.
Whatever you want to.
I wanted to wield it responsibly.
I want to do something that I felt like would be a celebration, a gift to the community.
Yeah, a gift, perhaps to the art of animation.
Well, yeah, sure.
That's true.
But I'm there's another gift that I'm heading for.
And it's also you know, it's kind of a look.
This is a big, long episode that we did here.
We're happy you're in town.
That's when you know, that's when you want to you want to throw down.
You want to bust out the good stuff.
Griffin, take a look at that that bag at your feet right there.
What do you what do you see in that bag?
I hear the clink.
The clink of the bag.
Is it in fact?
Read the label.
Can it be Taffers Brown Butter Bourbon?
Wow.
This is a bottle of Taffers Brown Butter Bourbon.
John Taffers Whiskey, which is only available in two states.
One of those is Nevada.
We were all in Nevada over the summer.
And I took a minute to go to find a location where this was available.
And then some I think I let you know this, Griffin, as a just like here's
a little thing that I'm going to spring at some point.
And you said, can you save it for when I'm around?
And some of that being that I believe you have a special club three
guest pronouncements to make.
I have a special club three guest pronouncements to make.
Now I'm trying to remember what we teed up here.
The well, the look, you know, that that bottle.
Yes.
That's here for a specific reason.
Taffers happening on main feed.
Is that what you're saying?
That's what I'm saying.
Well, what did he just say?
Hang on.
Can you repeat that again?
The last vestiges of my power granted to me by Club Three votes,
I am passing into law that Taffer one.
Will be a main feed episode.
Wow.
Coming in 2024.
Bar rescue and John Taffer, which kicked around several club three polls
will not be limited to club three.
Taffer one.
Main first episode.
I mean, look, I guys, I'm sure you don't want to do this.
I don't want to do it.
But he's got power.
He's Griffin has the power.
I'm mad with power.
And Taffer one has in fact been.
Wow.
All right.
Well, so Taffer one not coming to the club three elites.
That will be for all to enjoy.
This is a public service.
Taffer one.
Wow.
Well, let's celebrate by opening up this bottle.
Although this this little thing has been planned for a little while.
Do you notice anything else on just turn it around to the other side?
Do you notice anything up above the label?
Above the label?
No, no, no, not there.
Just like on the like.
What I'm saying is
there's something like dripping down from it.
But on the other side, look at the other side.
Here's what happened.
When listeners who were at the groove blender
who came to our Vegas show, they know that it was extremely hot.
Could not have been more hot.
I forgot to take the bottle out of the car for one night
for probably not even 12 hours.
And it stayed in the car, not in a covered parking garage.
And that was enough to make like some little mild explosion
happen in the bottle.
Now something is dripping out the top.
So it's probably in question whether we should actually drink this bottle
of Defferts Brown Butter.
Interesting.
You think we do it anyway?
I do.
It's also I was confused when you were trying to tell me
where to look, because the label design is like covered with splotches.
Oh, it's already a splats and drips.
It basically consciously is replicating the look of a print error.
Some of it is above the text.
Yeah, apparently it also has notes of vanilla and toffee.
Yeah, that's what it is.
That's what that brown butter is about.
A full fruity body to bring to life true liquid decadence.
Liquid decadence!
Your bar is failing because it doesn't provide liquid decadence.
I'll say this was another like side text pitch
Scott and I had at one point, which was not tell you two
that I was going to be in town.
Scott tells me when a recording is happening,
you have a fake subject like the Minotaur's returning episode.
It's been happening a bunch lately.
You do the first five minutes of setup and then I just storm
into the studio with the ball and go, I'm shutting this down!
Wait, fuck, I didn't realize that was part of that.
I wish we'd done that.
We've chosen this is the better move to pass it into law.
Well, the main reason to not do that was I thought they deserved a chance to do.
That was the real reason.
The Taffer research.
Everyone should be able to do their own Taffer research.
To the main feed listeners.
OK, should I try opening this?
If you want.
I, you know, here's I was I had this whole plan and then Aaron said,
wait, you're just going to give them the bottle, even though it kind of exploded,
which then led to both of us going, you are going to give them the bottle.
It's like it was in a hot car in Las Vegas.
You are going to feed that to your guest.
Shut this podcast down.
Car.
I don't quite know the mechanics.
How's something with leak?
I don't because it appears to be leaking.
What are you talking about?
It is sealed.
It isn't unopened.
I wear leaking from it from the top.
And there's like you can sort of see there's like residue up towards the label.
Was it like on its side and like it absorbed?
I have no idea.
I think it was some amount of this sort of like plastic safety label
or this rubber stopper stopper.
Like rubber melted outside.
Yeah.
Do we think that a less decadent drink wouldn't have had an effect?
Well, I think that's absolutely true.
What I'm thinking for certain is if you left this in a car for a day,
that butter sounded more brown than ever.
Well, we'll find out.
And maybe I shouldn't be so quick to say, oh, boy,
that was a live reaction to the smell around a swig.
Oh, I don't know.
Well, maybe it's not swigs.
Yeah, we'll wait till off air.
Nobody wants to hear drinking anyway.
But so I'm going to do one on Mike as you're wrapping up,
just so we get a live reaction.
I think the listeners deserve this.
OK, OK.
Oh, yeah.
You've been all over the place recently.
Do we got a cup or anything?
Is there anything in here?
Oh, wait, let's just use your tea cup.
Oh, yeah.
Wait.
OK.
Well, then let me I'll I'll just say maybe this won't be accurate
if we drink this this bubbly brown.
But as far as I know, Griffin Newman, you survived Club Three.
Griffin Newman does whatever he wants.
Thank you for taking us through
an examination of an animated series and ourselves.
Let's I don't know, extra the gift shopping you unplug.
No, I look, I want to I want to thank all Club Three subscribers
for imbuing me with this power.
I tried to wield it responsibly.
I think we went on a fun journey today.
Blank Check is my podcast.
We're doing John McTiernan right now who's got a wild career.
He is the first person we've ever covered.
My joke, I've been repeating who went to both movie jail and federal prison.
That can't be right.
I.
Hmm.
The first person we've covered at the very.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
And our own chronology.
You haven't done a Tim Allen miniseries.
Haven't done that.
He did direct one film.
Did he?
Yeah, we did Santa Claus trilogy on Patreon.
Oh, so you have done the Santa Claus.
We have.
And the Toy Story movies.
He directed one film.
I'm forgetting the name of it.
There's the guy who the director of Bottle Shock in the CBGB's movie,
who was also responsible for that production where the woman got hit by the train.
Oh, because they were filming on live train tracks without a permit.
Oh, from a few years ago.
Yeah.
That guy served time in federal prison.
Anyway, that's not what this is about.
John McTiernan made good movies before he went to jail
and he went to jail for a victimless white collar espionage crimes.
Basically.
Oh, yeah.
I've always been confused, but I look forward to hearing you.
I would say not really harm anyone.
OK.
Masters of the Universe Revolution.
Mm hmm.
Now on Netflix, five episodes of showrun by the great Kevin Smith,
soon to be licensing out the name sugar.
Yeah, right.
That's what we're going to get.
And I will say, I think I've told Mike and Scott about this, not to call a shot.
There is a Kevin Smith related surprise
for this podcast that I have had in the works for over a year.
What?
And circumstance and timing has failed to make it happen.
On the right timetable to be able to do it in studio for any of the times
we've recorded.
Did you tell me about that?
I think I did.
I can remind you matter now.
But there is there.
There is.
Or maybe I give you vague shapes of it.
I don't know if you even remember.
I know this.
Yeah, I know.
It will happen, though.
OK.
Calling a shot much like Taffer one on main feed.
Well, here we'll take this shot while I while I wind it down.
You survived podcast, the ride club three.
Thanks for subscribing.
Your bravery saved the podcast.
Well done, freedom fighters.
Pitch topics for the next poll, whenever that may be.
Mass magician.
Good luck to you.
And let's go to Griffin for his browned butter reaction.
Browned.
How browned are you?
It is it is like one of the sweetest things I've ever tasted.
Jason, my mother are coming up.
I am.
I'm curious.
I have to follow.
I'm not kidding.
I can like taste the butter.
It's not like.
It doesn't.
It's not what I want.
I would taste like cinnamon butter.
Why is it only carried in two states?
It's a good question.
Why is that going nationwide?
Are people going mad for butter?
Why haven't the taverns tavern open up everywhere?
My prediction is two out of the three hosts of this podcast
will enjoy the taste of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the third one will be absolutely repulsed.
Well, that would be very in keeping with our characters.
Yes.
Goodbye.