When your town has made you frown, When your square has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch, You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge,
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol, A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks, A place where you can tattoo your lower back,
So let's go take a walk, let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight, tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness, a daily,
extremely necessary series, exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder,
that make up universe,
Oh guys, I don't like the look of this place one bit.
full of the rotting ruins of things that used to be at Universal City Walk Orlando.
This is no good for our morale here as we start this new first paywalled episode of
the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
Oh, I don't even want to say the names or do the host business.
This place is so grim.
Oh, my name is Mike Carlson and I'm here and I'm in pain.
I hurt, every part of me hurts from the sad, mostly from the sadness,
from the depressing nature of where we are.
I know a big dunking basketball player and his hand is about to snap off,
and a NASCAR car that's being overtaken by nature.
No, I hate it.
It's like the War of the World set on the studio tour, but with businesses that have fun novelty
pieces that are sticking out of the walls or the front of the building.
It is.
It's not just, it looks like fog machines, but I think that actually is like the stench
of the bowels of the earth.
I think that's like volcanic activity.
Yeah, I think so.
It's not fun like a set would be.
Hey, it's Jason Chardon.
I'm here.
I'm just transfixed by this giant, shattered, partially brass, mostly exploded basketball
player that used to lurk outside the MBC, MBA city restaurant thing.
I know.
The giant multi-block restaurant.
It's really, it's a big shame.
It's like Planet of the Apes, like I'm staring on my knees looking at the statue.
Yeah, you are.
You're on your knees right now.
You blew it up.
You blew it up, you bastards.
How dare they take anything away from us ever.
I know.
Of course we anxiously await the arrival of new activity in stores and restaurants at
this place.
That doesn't mean the old ones have to go away.
Just keep building next to it.
Keep building.
Keep adding.
Keep building on top.
Yes, they should have built Toothsome on top of NBA city.
That's what I think.
Yeah, and of course it should go without saying this entire place stinks like stale cigars
from the dead cigar bar that is now the constantly dying sandwich shop.
Yes, yeah.
Actually there's kind of something like a little like rich and pleasant about the cigar
smell.
The sandwiches are a little more suspect in my mind.
Maybe that part of it is an upgrade actually.
Kind of oaky, kind of musty.
Not so bad.
Yeah, because all the cigars are on fire like perpetually.
Oh yeah, yeah.
So you're getting such a rich blend of smells.
Because you know actually, if we go stand by them, maybe it'll be like we're getting
to smoke expensive cigars.
Oh yeah, okay.
Nonstop.
Okay, so not all…
Oh hey, oh speaking of, there's the familiar coughs as we know that…
Oh well god, this is…
I've been so scared here.
It's been so grim that I…
It's just nice to see a familiar face.
Hey, there he is.
It's the Sector Keeper.
Hey Sector Keeper.
Baze, baze.
I'm no Sector Keeper.
But you look like him.
He looks exactly like him.
Sector Creeper.
Oh no.
Oh god, wait a minute, we should have known we're in an alternate dimension.
Why would it just be the regular Sector Keeper?
Jesus Christ, it's the Sector Creeper.
Where are my stogies?
Whoa, these are all around you I guess.
You just pick them up and grab them as you need.
Please don't blow smoke in our face though.
Oh god, this guy's smoke blowing is so much more unpleasant than the real Sector Keeper.
Yeah, really.
I know Sector Keeper.
Yeah, I know Sector Keeper.
So you do know you're like part of the…
Because we're all part of the vast connected multiverse.
So you have run into the good version of yourself?
I knew him for a little bit, but he stopped coming to my poker night.
With good reason, he's a good boy.
He wouldn't gamble.
You might have found out he was like eight or nine.
He's like a child, yeah.
Yeah, don't be inviting kids to your…
Wait, so you as opposed to…
Because wait a minute, this is some kind of like…
This is like a Star Trek thing.
This is like Evil Spock or something.
Where it's this bizarre cracked mirror version of the other.
So if the Sector Keeper we know and love is a child, you're not a child?
No, no, I'm like 62.
Oh, you're like an older guy.
Okay.
That's different for us.
I feel like we usually use the whimsy.
Like a shadow version of what you're used to.
Shadow Link, Evil Spock, Chris Gaines.
Oh, that makes some more sense now.
Oh wait a minute, yeah, look at him.
He's got a soul patch.
Oh my God.
That's like, that's where if you ever…
That's where, that's my, that's my tail.
Oh, that's you or your soul patch.
I got a soul patch.
I couldn't see through the mist.
I got a ponytail if you could look.
I got a long ponytail.
Oh, God.
And it's always wet.
Yeah, it's really…
Why is it wet?
Because of your sweat or does it just like pick up humidity from the air?
That's so weird.
Yeah, no, it's like a dehumidifier.
Picks up the humidity.
It's really gnarly.
Soaks it up.
He just whipped it at…
So sad.
God, why'd you whip your ponytail in our faces?
Sorry, I was looking…
Have you seen my stogies?
They're everywhere.
Just bend down and put your hand out.
I don't know which ones yours are.
Okay, okay, let me see, let me see.
I'm gonna leaf through these.
You guys want a Coors Light or…?
I'll take a Coors, sure I'll have a Coors.
I actually hate Coors Light.
Really?
Yeah, I hate it.
What are you, you're a Miller Light man?
What are you?
Yeah, I mean, I guess so if I had a choice.
It just tastes so sour to me, Coors Light.
Sour?
Sour.
Like, it just tastes bad.
Like, I don't know, it just has like a thing.
Jason, wait a minute, the longer you describe this,
the more likely you are to have to drink a ton of Coors Light.
This guy's like the devil.
Yeah, man.
Oh man, silver bullets coming my way for sure.
Like you're a werewolf?
No, that's their like motto.
That's a Coors Light branding thing.
I thought you were gonna shoot you.
Well, maybe, I don't know.
Wait a minute, what's in his pocket?
Oh, he's got a gun.
It's a revolver.
Oh no, there's silver bullets in it?
It's filled with silver bullets.
Oh, shit.
So maybe there are werewolves in this terrible place.
There's gotta be, I think.
They're probably all the characters they haven't brought back for Halloween Horror Nights.
That's right.
Waiting to find all the tombstones we see all around us.
Oh yeah.
Oh gosh, now I'm scared.
This guy's blowing smoke at us, whipping his ponytail.
Oh, wait a minute, his ponytail goo tastes like Coors Light.
Yeah.
See, did you cause this, Jason?
Well, you know, serves me right.
Where exactly are we though?
What is this?
Oh yeah, wait a minute.
Do we still do, I know you're the evil sector keeper, but do you still?
Hey man, sector creeper, man.
Sorry, god, this is heading nowhere good if I don't respect the guys
name.
Okay, sector creeper.
I know you don't do everything the way that the usual sector keeper does,
but do you still give us like an assignment?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So there's some rules down here, you know.
First up, no running around the pool.
Oh, okay.
That's kind of a rule everywhere.
Yeah, but you know, I just gotta cover this shit, all right, man?
Second thing is like the keep creeper down here.
Oh, sorry, you guys are in the land of fallen brothers and never built.
Did you see the sign coming in?
Yeah, yeah, no.
I propped it up with a parking cone.
I guess you got, I don't know, everything there again, there's so much like,
there's so much mist or volcanic ash or whatever it is.
It's hard to read anything.
And you gotta imagine what I'm going through, man, like.
Just living out here.
Shit is gonna be closing constantly.
So, you know, what you're experiencing is stuff's just closing up there.
Shit's just constantly being built down here.
Oh yeah, that makes sense.
You've had a couple of big boom times down here.
It's always a boom time down here.
Oh, that's what happens.
Every one of these restaurants is terrible.
It makes everybody sick.
So you get your pick of the litter of like all the restaurants
that have ever been too horrible to stay open.
Yeah, and I see there's just a bunch of like boxes of unused merchandise,
unsold merchandise that just gets thrown down here.
That's for sale.
Oh, we can buy it?
You want to rifle around through that?
You want to look at that?
I want to look at it.
Yeah.
What's it going to take to get you to buy one of these shirts today?
Oh, the shirt for the Ghostbusters show from 1992?
Yeah.
Oh, I don't know.
$20.
You flip those.
You want one?
Yeah.
What do you want?
What do you like?
What do you like to see?
You got any Jaws ride stuff?
It's empty.
You want Jaws?
Yeah.
Jaws ride is still in operation, motherfucker.
In Japan?
Oh, is it down here?
Yeah, it might be down here, man.
Down here, actually.
Unless you only have the like all of the because the real hell would be if all you get are closed
stores and restaurants.
Getting all the old rides sounds great.
Actually, that does sound good.
But all I see around me is I just see like a big broken record that used to be at the Motown Cafe.
Right, right.
You want to buy that?
It's so big.
There's no way you're going to give me that for cheap.
But it is broken.
Does that help?
Yeah, sure.
I mean, if it doesn't help, does it?
Do you like it more?
You are not great at haggling.
I got to tell you.
I know.
Oh, you're aware.
He's a mess.
He's breathing ash all day every day.
I've got a big family.
All right, you two.
I guess you have that in common with the Sector Key.
Jesus, everybody's down in their luck in this multiverse.
Yeah, that's true.
Who are they?
Does that mean you like…
So wait, if Sector Keeper is family with all the representatives of other malls,
you are probably family with people with defunct malls?
Yeah, that's right.
The keepers of defunct malls.
Keepers, yeah.
Wow.
So if you've died at a defunct mall, this is where you're at.
Oh, okay.
A lot of sense, yeah.
Oh, God, if we don't get out of here, Jesus.
I mean, look, I love dead malls and stuff,
but that doesn't mean I want to…
I love the promenade where I grew up,
but does that mean I want to do a bunch of ghostly sectors
about the old Walden books I used to go to as a kid?
I don't think so.
That sounds like a bummer.
I agree.
Baze, baze, you can get out of here.
Wait a minute.
What are you calling us?
Baze.
Oh, I missed that.
That's right.
He doesn't call us boys.
Boys, he calls us baze.
It's like Beyonce, like baze.
Baze, baze.
Or is it more just like you're playing
a song with an A?
Because you're so twisted.
Like we're babies, like swingers, you know?
Yeah, like baze, like my baze, my baze.
Oh, okay.
Wait a minute.
My beautiful ba-baze.
Oh, this is getting sleazier by the moment.
Is the only movie you get down here the movie Bae-Baze Kids?
Oh, it could be.
It could be an E or an A.
Oh, we got Bae-Baze Kids.
You want to buy it?
The movie?
I don't know.
You can just rent that on Apple or something.
I don't know how you call it a voodoo.
Wait, it's holding out a cop.
Wait, no, I'm not going to spend, what does that say?
$650 on a whole copy of Bae-Baze Kids?
That's a pretty good…
Is that a Betamax copy?
It's a Betamax.
Oh, okay.
He uses dead formats.
It makes sense.
We use dead formats.
We only used, yeah, dead formats.
We got LaserDisc, Betamax.
Oh, you've got the actual film reel from when Bae-Baze Kids
was playing at the movie theater.
We got the film reel.
Of course, the re-release from 2002.
Because it wasn't there when it first came out.
Hey, you know your shit, man.
Hey, I know.
I'm a film buff, so I know.
You're a Bae-Baze Boy.
I'm a Bae-Baze Boy.
Oh, you're a Bae-Baze Boy.
I am a Bae-Baze Boy.
What can I tell you?
You do use boy in that context, but otherwise it's bae.
Yeah, I know boy.
I know the word boy, but you guys are my baes.
Okay, all right.
Okay.
Oh, God, it's a little sexual.
This guy's like a little lascivious too.
Oh my God, he's in a bathrobe too.
Wait a minute, a worm just crawled through.
Oh, man.
Crossed his chest.
This guy's got a Beetlejuice thing about him.
Look, I was not going to say it,
but he's got a Beetlejuice thing going on.
It's a gummy worm.
Oh, Jason ate it.
I ate, you know, ate this.
Hey, man, that was my best friend.
He was a living, just because he's a gummy worm
doesn't mean he's a dead, a not alive can.
I don't know.
I just went on autopilot at some point.
How do we get out of here?
You're not nearly there, man.
All right, this is how you get out of here.
Listen.
Jason is an early bae.
Listen up.
You want to get out of here,
you got to talk about the shit you see down here, right?
A little different, a little different than what you guys are probably used to, right?
Yeah, no, usually.
So you see it, you talk about it and spend as much time as you need.
And then, you know, I'll get you guys out of here.
Oh, God, that is hellish.
There isn't the pressure of time with the sector keeper.
I'm like, oh, my God, this could go for hours.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's how we do it.
Well, I'm going to call it.
Can I talk about that really new thing that ended up down here?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
The newest brother.
Wait a minute.
The newest fallen brother that was a regular location when we were there.
But in the time it's taken to start making these episodes has since closed.
The universal legacy.
So, oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Get into that one.
That one, when it dropped in your world, it fucking shot up in mine, blew out my fucking toilet.
That's what happens.
As soon as it closes, it just shoots up down here and messes with your plumbing.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm my life.
My life fucking sucks.
God.
Okay.
It's hard down here.
So, yeah.
So you can imagine it's a disarray.
So again, you know, if you want to talk about it, yeah, go.
Jesus.
Well, it adds to the stink, I guess.
Everything has to go through the sewage that travels from the regular world to hell, I guess.
Fuck.
Well, hopefully it kept some of that cool retro merchandise.
Still looking a little bit sharp.
Keep in mind, all the bad restaurants are open down here.
Yeah, right.
So people are shitting up a storm.
As opposed to the regular city walk where you're only shitting up half of the city.
Yeah.
Right.
You're shitting up a parley cloudy up there, but.
Well, there's also a lot of demons down here.
So they like shit fire as well.
That's right.
So it's in addition.
You know your stuff, man.
Hey, what can I tell you?
Hey, you know your stuff.
So yeah.
I know, this bae was saying something.
Okay.
Yeah.
So the Universal Legacy store, it was only around for a few years,
Seemed pretty well liked because it had like a lot of throwback merchandise.
Yeah, this was a location meant to appeal to the retro universal fans.
Right.
Yeah.
In its merchandise, but also decor.
A lot of like tributes to the old King Kong jaws.
The inappropriate for where we are right now.
Ride props and recreations of ride props.
They also had a thing I really like and I did buy this.
They had a mold of Rama machine.
Are you guys familiar with mold of Rama?
Yeah.
Black mold of Rama.
So this is I have a mold of Rama thing here too.
It is a print on demand.
Basically these were big in a lot of them in the Chicago area, museums.
Sure.
I did it there.
This is the back to the future clock tower.
I got another one too.
There was one in the Halloween boutique at islands of adventure.
I bought a little boo, the little pumpkin boy.
This shit's going over my head, man.
What is this?
What are we looking at?
So you pay like five bucks or so and it like the machine operates it molds like molten plastic.
Well, we've talked about this situation.
Yeah, we haven't.
We still haven't figured it out if those pests.
We had a whole conversation to fill you in about because I've got a theory that those pennies are already pressed.
Oh, you do.
Okay, that's what we were saying.
Oh, wow.
Hey, yeah.
What if this thing's already just sitting in there?
Well, it was nothing and then it was pressed together and then it comes out the bottom.
You saw it?
Hey, you saw it?
I saw it.
Yeah, I saw most of the pressing, but they could have pulled a fast one on me.
It was very hot when it came out.
We did not.
It is hot.
So if they were faking it, there would have to be a little heater to heat the plastic piece.
Yeah.
And that's an expense.
Why would they need?
Why would they put in a plastic heater at that point?
Just do a plastic molder.
Jane reached for it too fast, too fast.
And we were doing the hot potato in our hands and put it back.
Just trading a little clock tower for two minutes.
But there is a Moldorama website.
Moldorama, it still exists.
It came about.
It was the division of this company, Aura, which is now called AuraMark.
You've probably seen it on the signs of buildings.
One of those food service companies that supply large quantities of food to restaurants.
It's one of those behind the scenes monopolies.
The logo is a little guy.
It's a little guy.
We've seen a little guy before.
It's a little red guy.
I know that.
Famous AuraMark red guy.
We'll be hanging out with him if AuraMark ever dies.
I've seen him come down here every once in a while.
Yeah.
He pops in.
He brings his family through here and they go.
Eat some cheap food in the realm of the beyond.
Universal has a few of these Moldorama machines, usually in the tribute store.
There was one in the Universal Legacy store, which hopefully they'll just move a lot of
that stuff into the main CityWalk store, which was a little boring.
Although, don't get on my story, guys.
That dude, does stuff ever get shot down here and shot back up all the time?
Oh, okay.
Great.
All the time.
I mean, the kitchen for most of the food you guys have been eating is actually it's an offsite kitchen.
Is that explains to us?
Yeah, absolutely.
It's sent through a dimensional sewer and then back.
Oh, my God.
Now I understand.
Oh, yeah.
And it's they got their grade posted in the window and it's not a name.
What is it?
Is it a B?
It's not a B.
Is it the same letter that Flounder Almondine starts with?
That not very good dish that Mike had the other day?
He knows his stuff too, huh?
Yes, I'm a smart bae.
He's a smart bae.
Yeah.
In lighter news, so I did.
Lighter news.
Well, lighter news, you might like this creeper.
I did go to the Moldorama website when I was trying to learn more about it and I was trying
to see they had a cute little mascot at the top and I did find out about Melton, the Moldorama.
Another shirt reveal.
Shirt reveal.
He's just a cute little guy.
He's a cute little man.
You bought a shirt of a living Moldorama guy who's got Mickey Mouse eyes.
Yeah, I found this a while ago.
How much?
Can I ask how much is the shirt?
Like 20 bucks.
It's pretty affordable.
Do they have multiple designs?
They have a few different shirts, I think.
Wow, look at that.
But his name is Melton, which I only learned.
Melton.
Yeah, M-L-T-O-N.
T-O-N, okay.
Because they melt the plastic.
That's pretty good.
Melton, wow.
He's a cute little guy.
I like Melton.
I like Melton, yeah.
Melton might be a scammer because he might just be heating up the plastic instead of
actually molding it in real time.
That's true, yeah.
But this nice face lie to you?
He looks so friendly.
So Melton, if let's just take him at his word, Melton, his insides are hot.
And he is like, one of his organs has just like a liquid plastic in it.
So he secretes liquid plastic or it comes like, say he has like it in his liver or something.
He's full of liquid plastic and then it goes down into a different organ,
which is like a piece of machinery and then it molds a different design.
So he is, I guess he's part, like part character, part machine.
Are you saying that's his shit, man?
I guess what I am saying is that the way Melton shits is that his liver secretes
liquid plastic.
Hot liquid plastic.
Hot liquid plastic and then his shit is a hollowed out toy.
So you're saying that Jason just held up his, Melton's shit hardened into a clock tower.
He played hot potato with.
Played hot potato with a mascot's shit.
I mean, Melton's shit.
I guess that's where this was always going, right?
When I was a child, I got many of Melton's shits at the zoo.
I got a lot of like a zoo.
You got a lot of mold aromas?
Yeah.
A lot of them still going at like the Museum of Industry in Chicago Zoo.
Guess Matt Mazzani got me a Donald Duck like plastic thing.
I forget where he even got it from some store or something.
I always, uh, one color.
Uh, I don't think so.
Usually.
Gray, but I think the Donald Duck one was orange.
Orange or green.
Like you can't have a color.
Single color.
Very simple.
Too complicated.
Really depends on what Melton eats.
I did have to feed it and I did feed it flounder almedine.
And so maybe that gray is shrubbily.
This is the rare machine.
You don't put a dollar bill in.
You put in a cooked flounder.
I don't know why I didn't just get him a pretzel.
It would have been much more cost effective for me
and it probably would have settled better with him.
You should be able to put like in that penny machine anything you want
and they'll be able to press it.
Like you should be able to put a piece of flounder in the penny machine
and it gives you a piece of pressed flounder.
You should be able to get a universal logo on anything you put in there.
This does end the back to the future logo on it.
So in his agony he was getting like correct logos.
Do you think it hurts him?
Every time Melton shits it hurts.
He has to use part of his colon to as a…
He has to arrange it into the shape of a logo and press it.
Yeah, yeah.
This could be a gross area even for the sector.
Baze, what else do you think?
Well, the legacy store, like I like the legacy store.
I'm a little bit upset that like they close a legacy store so quickly.
Do we say it turned into the preview center for Epic Universe?
We haven't said that yet.
Which I like.
Obviously that's great.
Yeah, still being built but it is…
It's a little small because the islands preview center was multiple.
Like every island had its own route.
Well, that means I'll see it in a year.
I look forward to seeing a bunch of concept art of a park that we already have and you never will.
Unless things go really bad for Epic Universe.
Yeah, no, maybe.
But it's just like I guess that…
Because we're the target audience for legacy store.
We're the types of people that want the legacy merchandise.
But I guess they feel like it's not such a big market.
Still most people want the sort of generic modern merchandise.
Or they just needed to kick something out to put the center somewhere.
It might not be a cultural trend.
Well, it felt like an insult to me.
I guess our ways aren't wanted by the universal big wigs.
I want to be treated better and I want them to keep things like that open for me
whenever I decide to go next.
But they don't care.
There are things like there's like corners of stores that have the old logos.
There's definitely those.
I think they're aware.
The legacy store that used to be the main universal city walk store.
And then that shifted when they closed like a skate shop, surf shop thing.
Oh, it killed your uncle?
Closed down, shot right up through him.
Oh, gosh.
You got to be careful.
Your whole family has to be careful ever being on Tollwood.
You guys are with me right now.
Oh, wait, you're right.
Something could close during this record.
Oh, shit.
That's a very ticking time bomb.
We have to get it.
We finished talking about this before.
Yes, given the quality of any city walk place close.
Anything else about the legacy store?
Can we move on?
It was nice.
Okay, great.
Yeah, I liked it.
I liked it.
It was nice.
All right.
Speed reviews from Jason Chariton.
Okay.
You know what I see?
Oh, my God.
I didn't think I'd ever see this anywhere off in the distance there.
I see an old sign, not for City Walk, but a sign for the City Walk that never was.
Yeah.
Do you see that over there?
I see it.
Big letters and it says E-Zone because of course, City Walk Orlando when announced was supposed to
be called the E-Zone.
The E-Zone.
And by 1997, they realized that name was stupid and they used the City Walk brand
that was already so strong.
City Walk existed in Hollywood.
City Walk Alpha.
Had already been created.
Yes, Alpha is ours, the Hollywood.
And then they already got a logo, this brand recognition.
It doesn't mean they did float E-Zone a little bit.
Here's a mock-up of the logo as you can see it back there, but big stripy letters.
And this would have aged well, I think.
I mean, I love it.
I do wish.
I know.
It says Universal City Flora under it, which I don't think they ever call it.
Yeah.
But I love that.
And then here is an E-Zone logo and a map of kind of the City Walk that we know,
but they're calling it E-Zone then.
And this is being held up by all the members of Boys to Men.
They are all, this is at a press conference and they're in front of a big E-Zone sign.
Boy, what could have been?
Imagine if this was the E-Zone enigma and not the City Walk saga.
I have something that likely would have been an E-Zone that as a kid,
I was a weird little kid talking to every team member who would listen to me
because when at the preview center for Islands of Adventure and City Walk,
they said there was going to be a Marvel Mania restaurant.
Right.
Yes.
So when I got down there in 1999, no one knew what I was talking about.
And I have found no proof for years that this was anything other than presented.
And I remembered it until this morning.
I found a post on the website, Spiderfan.
org.
Florida Marvel Mania restaurant canceled.
And does it have a date on it?
It just says 1998.
And there was speculation like, oh, there's all this Marvel stuff in the park.
And then this user, the editor, it just says, oh, I know him.
From Spiderfan.
org.
He'll edit you out of existence.
He's still in Poker Night.
The real reason the parent company for the Marvel Mania chain, Planet Hollywood,
has expanded too quickly and is now feeling the financial toll.
They have put a hold on all their future expansions.
So that's the reason that Marvel Mania is not built.
It's Robert Earl's hubris.
Wow.
That must upset you.
So what you're saying is that you have been hyped for at least a year, if not a few years,
to go to Florida, to go to Marvel Mania, and you didn't check any, like there was no way
to check that it wasn't there.
So you went down there going, oh my God, we're going to Marvel Mania.
Yeah.
Well, and then, and yeah, so I got the maps and I don't see it on the map.
Obviously, Islands is a million Marvel things.
Right.
And then I just start asking everyone because they used to have a weird system where would
there would be a podium in CityWalk.
And like in the morning, you would make your dinner reservation there as you were walking
from the parking garage.
This was a very confusing system.
Oh, there's the podium.
Oh, there's a podium.
That's, oh no, a bunch of possums just crawled out of it.
Oh, shit.
Gross.
So you were, the fact that you had these moments in your life that were you, there was like
a year where you were being like, your hope was being buoyed by and soon I'll be there.
And there were pictures in Wizard Magazine, you know, the comics magazine.
But not of the one out here for sure.
Like concept, are you think, or just was it maybe?
I think it was of the one out here opening and being built.
There was an interview with like Joe Cassata and some writers where they were eating a meal
at the Marvel Mania out here.
So it was like, oh boy, I can't wait till we get one of these because I'm not going
to Hollywood.
It's on another planet.
That's right.
Well, it's here.
It's here.
It's never built and you're looking at it.
How do you feel emotionally?
What do you think?
I mean, what could have been?
Do you want to give it a little kiss?
I do want to give it a little kiss.
I will say I kissed it last week and I did not feel good.
Maybe don't kiss it.
Give it a fair heads up.
Some users on Reddit though were like, I spent a birthday party there once.
Cyclops showed us to our table and Storm was our waiter.
I was like, I mean, that would have been pretty cool.
They were the characters of the waiters.
I know we talked about that.
That's what I don't remember that.
That's why I wanted a Disney.
Is everyone waiting and waiting on me?
But no, no, you get your food and then you watch them waving.
They're waving, not waiting.
Waving, not waiting.
You want them working at the Ant-Man bar.
Yeah.
Well, I want, yeah, I wanted like when you get to Disneyland,
I wanted like Pooh Bear at the booth, like taking your money.
Oh, you wanted it every step.
Yeah.
And one of the employees working for you.
I guess we'll talk about this a little bit.
But yeah, apparently Marvel Mania is where that really happened.
Wow.
They all had to take side jobs.
Last the dream of Silver Surfer, spilling a bunch of drinks.
Was he on a skateboard?
Maybe.
The silver spray paint.
That was the mistake.
Should have been another character.
Character just walks.
Beast making sure your time cards filled out.
Yeah, yelling at somebody inappropriate.
Making sure no one gets over 40 hours because then for full time.
Professor X like rolls up and he like tries to take your order,
but mentally, like telepathically.
That's the equivalent of not writing it down.
Teen playing him was wrong every time.
His bald cap.
Yeah, his bald cap.
Ripping sweat.
Scott, anything else like shout it out for the E zone?
Oh, yeah.
You know, there's not much else.
What does E mean?
What is that?
Oh, entertainment.
Oh.
Question.
The entertainment zone.
There's that.
And also in terms of like name waffling, this is a little interesting.
Eventually they got so Universal's like, OK, we're committed to walk.
This is our retail identity is walk.
So then in 2011, Universal sued a planned Orlando development
that was supposed to be called I walk Orlando saying that it's too similar.
Universal wouldn't add the wheel.
We got City Walk.
We can't let I walk open.
And I bring that up because that ended up being called Icon Park.
And that's the place where we did our live show earlier in the saga.
That place got sued by Universal.
Pretty cool.
Huh?
Yeah.
Wow.
We were not only we were on we're on both sides of the line.
Yeah, we are not.
We don't have loyalty to anyone.
But I do have actually, Jason, you reminded me that there is a pretty good segue here
because you're just left to wonder what would the Ezone have been like?
Would the Ezone have been different than the City Walk that we know?
And I'll read you this quote that's speculative.
The Ezone is going to be a rock and roll place.
It's going to be a rap place.
It's going to be a fun place.
And that is a quote from Shaquille O'Neal,
who was going to open a restaurant at the then Ezone called Shaq's Place.
This is probably the biggest.
This is a looming giant.
This was Shaq.
Shaq weighed in on what the Ezone would have been.
The three tenets were rock and roll, rap, and fun.
I mean, if you are alive on this earth and you can't find something to like about one
of those three categories, I don't know how to help you.
Yeah.
Not basketball, though, or sports.
That is not what Shaq's Place is about.
He leaves sports on the court.
This is his place to rock and roll and rap out.
Yes.
I met Shaq once.
Oh, OK.
Before you lived here?
No, down here.
Yeah, the General is my neighbor.
Oh, the General lives down here.
Oh, OK.
That makes sense.
So when we see the General in ads, it's a ghost appearing in the apparition from beyond.
We probably get a lot of Shaq's businesses because he opens dozens and dozens every year.
Oh, yeah, it's got its own zip code down here.
Not a bad idea for an episode.
All of Shaq's.
That is a good idea for a business for an episode.
Could vanish businesses.
A little Shaq saga.
But Shaq's Place, billed by Universal as a giant nightclub for a giant, will feature food,
live entertainment, a billiard lounge, all billiards for Shaq, and what's described as a
high tech game room cut to a bunch of crews in the US that don't always work.
It's one of nearly a dozen restaurants and entertainment outlets anchoring the 12-acre
complex, which is set to open in January 1998.
That's not what happened.
They had a lot of ideas here.
It'll feature a half-corked dance floor modeled after a basketball court.
No, got that.
And live performances by recording artists, including from time to time, Shaq himself.
That's right.
This is so, this is like, there's articles appearing in the Orlando Sentinel in 1995.
Four years before you'd get an opening.
Like, did you also get a temporary Orlando Sentinel subscription?
That's what you have to do.
The Orlando Sentinel wants you to pay and I understand you got to support journalists.
Let us not, yes, let no one say we didn't put the prep in.
I paid the Orlando Sentinel.
I also got these quotes by the E-Zone.
These are important journalism.
So I just love-
We're still another week from appearing down here.
Yeah, unfortunately.
Yeah.
If we hadn't paid them that six bucks or whatever.
I spent a fortune to access the Spiderfan.
org archives.
Thousand dollars a month.
This editor is demanding.
Well, it is Jonah Jameson.
So he was screaming at me as I completed the PayPal transaction.
It's just-
We're gonna business story.
They were all in on Shaq.
Shaq was the face of CityWalk at this point, essentially.
Like that was gonna be the whole driving point for the place.
The legitimizing of, I mean, because I don't know at what point Emeril came on board.
Yeah.
But, you know, I think at this point, you know, and I think feel like CityWalk,
the original CityWalk got to open without all these distracting celebrity names.
But by the time 1995 rolls around, all we care about is stars.
It's star fucking.
And everybody wanted to fuck Shaq.
Yeah, of course.
And there we were.
This place was gonna be built around Shaq.
It was gonna be Shaq's spot.
Yeah.
Now notable to us because that space earmarked for Shaq once vacated became what?
Well, Margaritaville.
Jimmy Buffett fills the Shaq void.
Perhaps there is not this anchor location of Jimmy Buffett's franchise.
Right.
A name and a face you associate with CityWalk at this point.
Shaq was Ezone and Jimmy Buffett is CityWalk.
Right.
And it's 97 when the switch happens.
So we're still like a ways out from it opening.
So like there's people following the news.
They're riveted.
What's gonna happen at this new outdoor mall?
And they're seeing in 97, oh my God, like honey, honey, come quick.
Shaq will not have a presence at this new Ezone of now renamed CityWalk like the one on the other coast.
They need it but walk in the name of it because when you go from the parking garage
all the way through CityWalk, it is a little bit of a hike, you know?
There's moving walkways though.
When you get out of the garage.
But not, so your complaint is that there's not moving walkways the entire way.
If there were moving walkways in CityWalk, I would just ride those nonstop.
Darling, you know why they call it CityWalk?
Because you gotta walk a lot.
It's a warning.
It's not a name.
Yeah, yeah.
Be prepared.
Here's what's funny though.
Okay, so he wants to do Shaq's place and we start announcing Shaq's place.
Shaq's place.
But then some other people are reading this news.
Actually, not far from what you're saying, Mike, other important Orlando denizens,
and they're like, wait a minute, Shaq's place.
What does this do to Shaq's world?
Because apparently Church Street Station, the shopping complex that Disney stole the idea of
for Pleasure Island and put into the ground.
I see all of the functioning Church Street Station businesses everywhere here.
If you want something from over there, just take it.
Oh yeah, yeah.
But probably, so yeah, PFO Grady's good time old place.
That is the name, right?
It's something like that.
Yeah, Uncle Mo's.
Some straw hats with red, white, and blue stripes.
Uncle Mo's family feedback.
PFO Grady was Church Street Station.
Did I get that right?
Is that correct?
I don't know.
It sounds right though.
It's something like that.
It's definitely like that.
And the wagon wheelery was that city one.
I've got an old compact for sorry if I can look that up.
Oh great.
Oh, that's right.
No internet here.
I'll look that up while you keep.
Yes, thank you.
Yeah, fire that baby up.
It is loud, that cooling fan.
Yeah, let's edit that sound out.
Oh god.
Are you picking up on my Presario's fan?
Where the process?
Let's just shift the mics.
Let's move on this way.
Anyway, Church Street Station has been struggling ever since Michael Eisner looked at demographics
said, what can we put out of business in Orlando?
Saw that.
All right, do it.
Build me one of those.
It worked.
Church Street Station struggled ever since.
It's Rosie O'Grady's good time Emporium.
Whoa, I got a lot of the words right.
Fortune, but I'd get a couple of those words up there.
So sorry, my presario was a little slow.
I couldn't get it.
You got up to typing the letter S for Shaq.
Accidentally opened solid there and it crashed.
Boy, sorry, boy, that's the shit of living down here.
So anyways, you know, they need a new identity.
What are we going to do?
They reach out to Shaq.
Will you open?
We have an idea.
What if you open like a nightclub and he's like, all right, yeah, great Shaq's World.
And then city Ezone comes to him.
All right, sounds good.
Shaq's Place.
And I think genuinely they were like, what is it?
Where does this leave us?
So we we needed a Shaq restaurant.
And then sure enough, they never got the Shaq.
They didn't get Shaq's Place.
Oh, wait, sorry.
They didn't get Shaq's World as he's never got Shaq's Place.
Years go by, the place keeps languishing more and more.
And as we may have covered at some point, it took years and years before
Church Street station finally said, oh, we have somebody to revitalize this area.
It's boy band impresario Lou Pearlman.
We're giving him all of it.
And this will be where he does all his boy band auditions,
where he conducts all his not shady business.
And then he didn't.
In addition to just crumbling and going to jail, he also didn't like open.
I think he opened one steakhouse.
The only guy of 86 from this place.
Oh, you won't let Lou hang out here.
No, Lou's not welcome.
Oh, man.
He started trying to recruit all of your family members to be in his new group.
His all demon boy band.
This one's going to be on the level.
It's like five, five handsome demons.
He's telling them what to do.
The Church Street base.
Oh, wow.
In sync, you might call handsome devils, but these are literal handsome demons.
Um, anyway, this was not the end of the Shaq chicanery because then
Disney World did open something called the official All Star Cafe.
Yeah, some of it was we didn't have time for this in celebrity,
but there was this restaurant owned by a bunch of athletes.
And Shaq was one of them.
He's a partner in that company.
And they announced and then did open this, I believe, at the Wild World of Sports.
That one did get off the ground.
I think that's a Planet Hollywood restaurant.
Money went into that and away from Marvel Mania.
Sorry, Jason.
And some lose some.
But anyway, apparently they were asked, he was asked like,
so how does this restaurant differ from the one that you're going to open at Universal's E-Zone?
And he said, oh, the All Star Cafe is going to be a whole lot better.
So then Orlando Sentinel reaches out to Universal and they say,
I think he's just got a great sense of humor.
What a kidder, eh?
So Shaq is playing three Orlando establishments against each other.
I said this when we did the Shaqtoberfest episode that I truly, no joke,
love Shaq's approach to all of his business ventures.
Because you get the sense that all these famous people,
Wahlberg, Rock, it's so calculated and they're doing such like careful planning of tequila.
And now they have this and now they're buying into this and they want to be moguls.
Shaq just seems like he's letting it fly.
They go like, hey, you want the general?
Yeah, I'll do the general, whatever.
Yeah, Papa John's take.
Yeah, whatever.
Going to him and him saying no.
Yeah, you'd feel bad.
Shaq's chicken.
Yeah, great.
Let's do it.
It doesn't matter.
And it's the best, I don't know, it's the most fun way for a celebrity to throw his name,
play three different locations against each other.
And then accidentally by that, like accidentally maybe.
Yep.
I just think he wasn't thinking about it.
He didn't think there were conf, you know,
sometimes on Shark Tank, Mark will go, well, I already have a business that's similar to this.
Right.
They compete.
So for those reasons, I'm out.
Shaq would never do that.
Shaq would never be out on anything.
He would go, they should get him on Shark Tank because he'd just go, yes, yes, yes.
Shaq, you've hit a new.
Before the pitch.
You've hit a new.
They don't even make it all the way down the hallway.
Shaq says yes to.
Local businessman from Dallas.
Yes.
Go ahead, turn around.
I'll talk to you later.
He doesn't even realize some of this.
It's like prayer Apple launch and just blow Walbers out of the water.
Scott has now found a new show called Shaq's Tank.
That would be very entertaining.
That's good.
Yeah.
Yes.
And you get turn around, you know, all those Shark Tank segments take like 10 minutes.
This you, you can bang through 300 businesses every hour.
Shaq could probably just like, we could call this Shaq's podcast, the ride.
If we made him the right offer.
Oh, how do we do that?
Let's figure out, let's find his business manager.
Like a month of just Shaq's podcast, the ride, like the Dana Carvey show will be like the
mug root beer Dana Carvey, like just Shaq's podcast, the ride for at least a month.
Oh man.
This is the answer.
Look, you're hearing this on Patreon and listeners.
We appreciate your support and your financial donations.
But if you could help us figure out Shaq, then we could just make like
500K a month and not need the listener support.
Yeah.
That fixes the entire.
It does.
last eight months, but it's going to be a lucrative.
We're going to tear it up in those eight months.
Spoiler podcast, move over to Shaqrion.
It's a slam dunk.
So yeah, what could have been, would Shaq have still had a presence there?
If, if all of this had gone down.
But then as sector creeper mentioned off Mike, then he left Orlando entirely.
So maybe he wouldn't have, and when he's open businesses and, and haunts, obviously.
Although, well, he doesn't, he doesn't play at all and he doesn't play in Los Angeles,
yet he's willing to give the good people of Long Beach Shaqtoberfest.
Right.
Of course.
So, you know, maybe, maybe it all could have been there.
Should have done it all.
Shaq's place, Shaq's world, Ulster cafe.
It sounds fun.
It sounds really, I'm not being, I'm not joking.
It sounds great.
You're really lucky.
I'm glad Margaritaville's there, but Shaq's place sounds really fun.
Let me move over a little bit and give a mention to,
earlier, if you were wondering why is boys to men holding a picture of the E-Zone,
that is because they were investors in the Motown cafe.
Yeah.
This is not a never built, this was built.
And not only was it there, we didn't talk about this in another sector, did we?
Because we talked about where it resided.
Because it looked massive.
This was both the Red Coconut Club on the nightclub level and Bubba Gump below it.
Motown cafe was three stories.
That's how it filled that.
So they ended up splitting it and that Bubba Gump's is big.
It's so interesting because I feel like they, like, when they started making these things,
I guess city walks, like Wizards, of course, which is a fallen brother, was three stories, correct?
I think so, yeah.
So like they obviously were very ambitious when they started and then, of course,
Margaritaville out here, we were like, well, there's two stories,
of course, that's what's going to happen.
And it's like, no, no, no, one story.
Like they certainly-
Fatal decision.
I agree, fatal decision, but they also probably learned some sort of a logistical lesson
about maybe we shouldn't make these things so massive.
This might be the place to bring up this observation.
This occurred to me in many, many places that we went in our city walk voyage.
Yeah.
When I was a kid, I used to think the bigger the restaurant is, the better,
because I loved Planet Hollywood, loved Hard Rat Cafe.
If it's giant, that means it's the best.
That means they have the best food.
It's the most in demand.
And this thought occurred to me and was corrected by when I, when Mike, when you and I,
as addressed several days ago, were hanging out in the kind of clearing out NBC Sports Grill.
Yeah.
And I'm like, this has room for 250 more people than they have.
And it's, so when, when it's not full, it's just sad.
And then also, as with so many of these places, it's like, no, it's not better if it's bigger.
You just, what happens with the bigger restaurant is you just feel the stress.
You feel that there's like, there's 70 people working tonight and they're all yelling each
other and on headsets and like, I need somebody at 13, we got to spell on nine.
It's like, it becomes like, now it's like a, this like nightclub that has to be organized.
No one's having fun.
Nobody has time to do anything correctly.
Big, big restaurants are like disasters.
Like tiny restaurants are probably what you want.
You don't see a lot of little restaurants down here, dude.
It's all hulking.
All the biggest buildings I've seen in a long time.
likely sliced zucchini.
Absolutely.
You get a lot of meals that just recap like get it out, get it out.
They've been waiting 20 minutes.
Get it out.
And that's not a good day.
This isn't like a bar that needs to be rescued by a taffer on like a regular calm day.
It's pitched up to a hundred.
Everyone's mad.
I don't know that I ever consciously thought of like bigger is better with restaurants,
but it certainly was more fun to go to a big place because generally a big place was full
of nonsense.
So it makes sense that a kid would be like, well, this is like the planet Hollywood is
the finest dining on the planet.
This is the greatest place.
This is so special what we're doing today because when we went once to the one that
was was at Oakbrook or whatever, it was near the Six Flags near Gurney, I was like, well,
this is like this.
I'll tell my grandchildren about this.
Well, hang on.
You will.
We all will.
You don't understand.
They didn't use Italian bread crumbs.
They use crushed up Captain Crunch on the tendies.
It's a naked mannequin of Sylvester Stallone in a big first reuse of tendies.
I knew it was coming.
Yeah, yeah, it's coming.
That's in the lexicon.
So yeah, I get what you're saying, but yeah, I'm trying to think what is the biggest
new place they've built even dining wise.
They've turned things into other things.
Yes.
But I think from the ground up, because Toothsome was NBA City, we'll get into NBA City, which
isn't Shaq's place.
But yeah, I don't know.
I don't think anywhere does build giant restaurants anymore.
Yeah, I mean, Toothsome obviously is the newest one that has just a huge capacity in Orlando.
But you really got to think about when CityWalk opens in 99, has there ever been a place with
more massive two story restaurants at once?
Right.
On the same day, suddenly there's like 12, right?
It's like the Batman Forever Gotham where there's a skyscraper and a statue holding
the observatory.
That might be from Batman and Robin.
It is what it's like.
That's why I like it.
Right.
Wow, you just really crystallized that.
It's full of fit men holding giant items.
Yes.
And then like tributes to ancient Greece and Rome.
CityWalk is Schumacher's Gotham.
they're putting a diamond in a big telescope or something.
The observatory is held by a big man.
I believe a big statue man is on top of a skyscraper and then he's holding the observatory
like this and that's where they are.
They're all in that little thing he's holding.
But that is our dream.
Wizards and things like that were the closest you'd get.
This is why we like all of this shit, isn't it?
Because it's so fantastical.
It's like being in the 90s Gotham.
I never got to go.
How did it fall?
I didn't get to go but I'm so upset.
It seems unimpeachable.
Now the only things you see ever built in the world that are above three stories are
boring, ugly, expensive apartment buildings you've ever seen.
We had imagination back in these days.
Or even like Toy Story.
Toys R Us in Times Square.
It was like six stories and there was a big Ferris wheel and that feels like Schumacher
Gotham where it's just like this is so excessive in here.
It is not a practical use of the space to put a Ferris wheel in the middle of a big store.
It doesn't make sense but we're doing it because it's fun and that seems to be out.
That seems to be not the way of the world at the moment.
I found a City Walk location that is closed that I remember the signs for.
It was a nightclub called The Groove.
I specifically remember The Groove because some nights were teen night.
15 to 19 only.
Which is an odd range looking back.
Seems problematic.
Yeah.
That's a good way to like maybe it was all meant as a trap for this was a sting operation.
That's how they got him ultimately.
You forget that.
But like on this write-up on Hotels.
com the very first thing
The Groove Dance Club is a multi-level party venue.
So that also had multi-levels.
Multi-level.
Bars and rooms.
Baze look around do you see one story?
Everything's multiple stories.
I see nothing but crumbling giant buildings all around me.
Anyway Motown Cafe was so gigantic.
You walk in as I see it here it's the big 28 foot tall like wide version of like the record single
of the Jackson 5s ABC that was on the roof when you walked in.
They had so much like memorabilia.
You start to add up all the everything that the Hard Rock had and there's another one with a lot
of memorabilia I'll bring up and then just like among them like this was like the sixth thing in
a list that this is the Motown Cafe in Orlando is where had Michael Jackson's what Michael Jackson
wore in Motown 25 when he debuted the Moonwalk.
Right.
That was at this restaurant in Orlando.
That's down here.
And we'll probably better kept down here.
That pile of t-shirts that I was trying to sell.
So I would have if I just had agreed I would have had that.
You would have owned that.
Okay.
So wait there's just a pile of Woody Woodpecker shirts and in the middle there is a Michael Jackson.
Yeah it's in there somewhere.
Okay.
Where are my Stokies?
Oh I think they're hanging around here.
I don't know which ones are yours.
Anyway that's Motown Cafe.
Anything else anybody wants to I mean I'll look for my next one but we can go in any order.
Yeah.
We don't have that sector keeper way in a state.
Sometimes actually it's kind of a nice change of pace to have you sector creeper because
sector keeper can be a little like you know he's demanding with the whole.
We like to chat.
I can't even remember my own phone number.
Geez I kind of like this.
This guy is a little more free with.
Like this guy.
I'm a little free wheeled yeah.
Yeah I like he's a Beetlejuice like the Beetlejuice character is a little bit like kind of out of
control this guy's a lot more chill than you.
Yeah I'm a little chill.
Well I've had like four or five quarters since you guys got.
Oh okay all right.
I got a little buzz going.
Yeah his ponytail is extra wet I see too.
Yeah it gets wet more and more wet.
Like your head must secrete some of the beer.
I wrap it around and I suck on it.
Okay wait we're heading back into bad territory.
Yeah okay.
Sucking on a I mean you could just have the beer why is it better.
Keep the buzz going man.
It's like a lollipop a beer lollipop.
This guy knows what he's talking about.
I know what I'm talking about it's like because hair really soaks up liquid well.
Yeah.
So well when you're washing your hair you know hair gets really wet.
That's right.
Your skin dries slower than your hair does when you're dry.
That's right so I suck on my ponytail keep the buzz going.
Ew ew.
What did you want to do in front of us though.
I care and beer together and not a good beer maybe if it was a better beer.
Yeah.
Oh ew not on my people hate that and I don't like looking at it.
Jason says something he wants to talk about.
I just found some old pictures of the groove entrance.
Oh yeah the groove.
And I think they left up the big tall tower but the groove next to Fat Tuesdays
and a step away from the hot dog hall of fame.
So if you stumble out of the groove after drinking a lot of like.
On a teen night.
Yeah well on a teen night.
On adult night yeah if you're drinking like some Midori cocktails that's the watermelon one right.
Makes it green like a sour.
I don't know the answer that because I don't drink bullshit.
Well we're talking about the groove so you could stumble out for a night cap at.
A fat Tuesdays and then eat a big Chicago hot dog.
Yeah sure that sounds like it sounds good I would do it.
Yeah sure.
By night cap you mean like a yard.
Yeah no oh you're you're not going to bed for a while you're getting the yard you know.
The yard of the multi-story restaurants of drinks.
The yard of the drink that is literally labeled as orange slush and green alcohol.
I'm so glad there aren't more fat Tuesdays to go through.
The original plan was for them to build 17 of them.
I do have okay so another place with music memorabilia and you'll in Shaq's list you'll
notice that one of the things is not blues and one of the things is not jazz.
Right.
A never built is BB King's Blues Club.
Yeah.
That was announced possibly in the Islands of Adventure preview center.
Didn't end up happening.
Here's a quote from an article.
BB King is the master of blues but his club lost out in negotiations to a jazz combo club.
They pitted blues and jazz against each other.
Yeah they ended up going with City Jazz which is a combo of a lot of things they wanted to do.
It's a jazz venue then the Thelonious Monk Institute of Jazz.
I haven't really thought about this since copy pasting it.
There was a jazz school.
City Walk Hollywood has a UCLA extension and City Walk Orlando has a jazz school.
Also learning it seems like it negates the like vibe of jazz to go learn it in a strip mall.
Well.
Also the vibe of Thelonious Monk.
Yeah you don't think he would have.
Our professor emeritus Thelonious Monk says pay us a thousand dollars a month and you'll be
jazzing in no time.
Cheeseburger in paradise on your way out of the door to get to class.
All the best music resides next to each other at this place.
Motown, Thelonious Monk, Jimmy Buffett's Cheeseburger in Paradise.
You know you get all the genres which is really something.
You know they were trying stuff out.
That's what you like about these early days is they're experimenting and that's what we
were trying to figure out the other day about UCLA and what the actual presence at
City Walk Hollywood is.
And why if it hasn't existed in many years is the sign still there.
many other businesses and other things.
Is the sign for UCLA extension?
Yes.
I feel like I had a lot of professors in school and then recent LA transplants go like well if
you really want to get a good you can always go to UCLA extension anytime.
You do they have really good screenwriting.
If you'd like to continue your education but not fully go to grad school.
And you think that was maybe they were directing you to City Walk?
No.
Specifically the City Walk signs said UCLA.
Specifically that phrase you're saying and that's what they were saying to you.
Yeah.
Well that's one of the big mysteries of the saga.
It's still not really solved.
It's still not solved.
How open was it?
How great were the courses you could take?
Right.
Next to Wizards.
I'm not sure.
Right next to where Wizards was.
I'm adjunct actually adjunct professor at the UCLA extension down here.
Okay.
Well you give back.
Yeah.
Other ghosts and spirits and devils.
No tenure?
Brother I wish.
You'll get there keep working at it.
It's kind of a holdover situation where there was an accident I heard.
Kind of like a similar situation to that.
You guys are like my holdover boys in a way.
A little bit.
You know what because we're all forced to come here.
Right.
Now we're kind of bonding.
That's right.
And having a nice little time.
It's kind of a holdover situation.
I don't know which of my eyes is fake or not.
Wow.
It's the feel good sector of the saga.
That's right.
Okay.
And then also as part of this thing there was the Downbeat Jazz Hall of Fame.
So there was a Jazz Hall of Fame in this also.
And then there's like a bunch of like jazz items.
And these are you know we get maybe spoiled with our like
you know that's the guitar that belonged to Vince Neil or whatever.
Cool stuff that you would find at Hard Rock or wherever.
These things are a little more mundane.
Like Count Basie's health insurance card.
A payment ledger to pay the Woody Herman Orchestra in 1948.
I mean then there's some like then there's some musical instruments.
That's good.
But then the like hang on Stan Kenton's shoes.
Art Blakely Seniors hat.
A Sun Ra walking stick and Miles Davis's high school diploma.
This was what a magical place.
There was this is real good.
What what Michael Jackson wore when he like shot into the stratosphere as a superstar.
And then a couple feet away Miles Davis's high school diploma.
And nobody ever thought about any of this or noticed it.
No no one talked about it.
Their brain barely even allowed the information in.
They just kind of wanted to buy it.
It's so wild.
This is almost all these items just feel like oh this would be like a part of a full exhibit on this artist.
You go that would make sense.
You saw like them go through school and where they went to school.
Exhibits and museums that are worse that have worse things.
Of course but like another all like the sum of its parts you would go like get a picture of the person
and what they did or whatever versus just taking a little piece out and going
well this was their uh this was their Lowry's card.
Art Tatum's Lowry.
Dave Brubeck's unused condom.
Always prepared.
Yeah it's so wild.
Kets in his instrument case.
Well of course yeah.
Yeah really weird and then City Jazz.
I found this on the website.
Every Thursday through Sunday night City Jazz turns into Bunkers Comedy Club.
Bunkers.
Bunkers is the same brand that had a stat that we wanted to play at the Margaritaville resort
where we named where we did the street names.
Right.
That was their comedy club and it's not there anymore.
God I'm looking around now there's so many bunkers comedy clubs.
So many locations of bunkers.
There's some more over there too.
And you could smoke in bunkers.
Oh and you have to get in.
Cigar bar yeah.
In comedy clubs.
It's a two drink minimum four pack minimum.
Four pack of cigars?
Oh wow that's like four cigar how many in a pack?
I don't know.
Is how many Stogies are in a pack?
Where are my Stogies?
I think you usually say so Stogies are probably singles I'm guessing.
I really don't know.
No yeah no I think you're onto something.
Yeah probably like expensive Stogies are like one you buy one at a time.
I'm again guessing here.
There's such a cigar presence that it makes sense there's cigars down here
because there was the cigars with a Z that we talked about.
Emeril's had a cigar room apparently.
Big enough space in Emeril's restaurant for the full cigar room.
Maybe I will.
I kind of love it like you'd be like honey excuse me.
I'm gonna go hang out in the cigar room at Emeril's.
Would you mind like the boys and I are hitting Emeril's tonight.
Oh okay yeah well they've got the cigar room there.
So like as I would assume it's a dude maybe I'm wrong but it's dude a dude room.
And it might have been what Jason's dad did on the family trips.
Oh yeah.
Because Jason now it's hour 10 of Jason going but I saw it in the brochure
but then they didn't end up opening Marvel Mania.
I mean I like the Marvel rides but Marvel Mania is its own.
I'm gonna go even if I sneak off to Emeril's cigar room.
He was I think at the time would have been smoking a pipe.
Oh wow.
So he might have you know you just get a plate of etouffee and a packed fresh pipe.
Are you allowed to smoke a freshly packed pipe in Emeril's cigar room?
I don't know.
Is there any smoking available?
I feel like there must have been.
Why have a cigar room if not the ability to do that?
I would think so but like cigarettes in there.
Cigarettes I feel like generally smell like a cigar can smell at least okay.
A little earthier.
But if you go if it's a cigarette room I feel like the smell would be really bad.
I don't think anywhere offered cigarette rooms.
That doesn't sound good.
So but you probably a pipe though because pipe tobacco would smell better probably.
Yeah it did smell more fragrant.
Pipe tobacco.
Not the room.
You never went to the room.
No I never went to the room.
I don't really remember the room.
I didn't know the room existed until yesterday.
We ate at the bar once before like we were you know checking out and going to the airport
that day and there was like a solo business traveler and I don't know if he knew the chef
or they were just like oh this guy's still but they just kept giving him small plates like.
You remember like a solo business traveler just getting little plates.
I don't think he's paying for it that's why he didn't remember it.
No he was gonna pay but I was just like we just ordered off the menu
and they were like oh you can walk in sit at the bar if you just.
This is a childhood memory.
This is like 15 16.
It's still a long time ago.
I don't know who this guy was it was like when I was at Napa Rosa the great California once
and sat in a local from Orange County at this Disneyland restaurant this local asked for his
usual bottle.
Well I had that at Trader Sam's.
I've said that before.
That's a thing that happens at restaurants that's not weird.
It's a little weird next to a theme park.
No it's not that's a really nice restaurant.
That's completely reasonable.
Remember I told you at Trader Sam's before WonderCon the guy walked in and he goes hey Bob like what
do you have in the usual and I was like holy shit there's a guy at Trader Sam's with the usual.
I am interested though did you go to like a hypnotist that uncovered this memory.
This is so specific for like when you were 15.
This is a formative memory man I'm talking about your first home run your first kiss
first time seeing a businessman get small plates in an airport.
Okay well the first one didn't happen the second one happened a lot later.
I had to fill in some things at 15.
You gotta fixate on something.
It's so funny.
I guess I heard was the donut at the at a carnival I want the donut stuffed donut
and I guess I gave it a little kiss.
First human kiss.
Yeah that's a different story.
The businessman getting small plates and you were upset about it or just confused or curious.
Probably he ordered like a prefix menu or a chef's table menu.
I'm trying I'm doing my best I'm trying to remember if I have anything like that.
I'm trying to remember the closest thing I can remember to anything like this is I remember
being like six or seven and I was in Woodfield mall at a restaurant called John's Garage and
I just have this memory that's not remarkable at all but it's a memory of there was a like a painting
of a man with his tie in soup and I remember this disturbing me.
I remember just eating my meal and I had to be like six or seven.
I just remember being like disturbed by the idea that his tie was now ruined
and it is stuck with me until this very moment which I've now said on this podcast but I'm
trying to think of something along those lines where that no offense to what you just said
is not a remarkable story neither is what I said but they stick with you from childhood.
Yes I also specifically remember my meal which was like an arugula salad with fresh crab and
candy lime rinds and I've never had that in my life.
Hang on a second you remember this from 15 you remember the specific order and all the plates
that you got and yet when there was an ice cream place that you loved loved enough to do an entire
dough boys about it you couldn't remember the name of the restaurant.
You did a two hours of podcasting about it and that only happened like four years ago.
What is that place called it went totally under.
You don't remember it now?
Ample Hills.
But somehow you remember the entire arugula salad an unremarkable item
that you ordered at Emeril's when you were 15.
Well there's been a lot of ice cream places open and closed in LA.
Sweet where it was creamery and studio city clothes.
Oh yeah.
Some of these gelato there was gelato place in Los Feliz I really love that's gone.
My mom barely remembers what happens she can't barely name the name of this podcast I do but
she can probably tell you who Susan Day from the Partridge family dated because she read Teen Beat
in at a certain point in her life.
I would like to know.
Well I don't know that off the top of my head so I'm just saying the formative years
that's when they really that stuff imprints on you in your brain.
You're a sponge.
Did you date David Cassidy actually question mark?
Well David Cassidy famously went on a date with what's her name the mom.
Did that happen too I know Florence Henderson and Barry Williams but it also happened to
wait no no are you confusing it with that because Shirley Jones was married to his dad.
Maybe I'm confusing it with a Brady Bunch.
They were family members basically so if they went on a date that's
fucked up.
You might be right yeah I think I'm confusing the Barry Williams.
David Cassidy you better not have gone on a date with your stepmom
who's also your mom on a show that's double weird.
Barry Williams dating Florence Henderson is only one weird because it was a stepmother.
That's a double story like a giant restaurant.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Baze you are a wild group.
Dude we'll let it we'll let it all out old arugula salad Susan Day dating information.
Little plates.
We go fucking nuts in here.
Crab chunks.
All right let's keep it let's keep it moving.
What else do you see?
Uh uh uh they there was they were gonna build like a like E entertainment was gonna film shows down
there that never happened um and what's next what's big in the list NBA City let's talk NBA
City yeah yeah which is not Shaq's there was an NBA restaurant that today is Toothsome um but
that's the reason Toothsome is so huge is because this one went away and they needed to fill right
how did they like Toothsome does fill up you kind of understand why Toothsome and there was a line
out the door it's crazy yeah Toothsome so popular two stories full all the time I don't understand
how this was initially built for NBA City this is the most cursed kind of thing because it didn't
downtown Disney had this NBA thing that opened and closed very quickly oh yeah it just sounds
like something that wouldn't do well well now it's especially does especially because of what
Bob Iger has been excited about for a decade is that NBA thing opening up the experience
and then closing now I feel like does the NBA does it not translate to outside of a theme park mall
well maybe they should you know focus on the bread and butter basketball yeah I get it in concept in
the same way that any other uh dumb thing with entertainment or sports might work but then this
I feel like would you believe I think food was not good sure uh shocker um this was the first of a
proposed 10 of these I don't think any of them opened that's always the thing too where it's
gonna be so many um they the bathrooms said NBA for the men and WNBA for women that's I guess that's
I and then they had rims and nets over the trash cans I was one of their touches good I think we
all agree that's good that's fun that's all I have about NBA everyone likes to make a basket
shooting poorly that night then damn damn over dead is over so many people else yeah what did
encourage if you were kind of near one for you to like throw a napkin like was there like a big
mess developing if like dad wanted to prove or dad versus his teenage sons any sort of combination
of competitiveness a competitive people sorry in you you may yes you're doing a little dunk contest
your son you're like burnt from the sun all day but like you're a little lit and dad is now
gonna try to sink a couple shots from the table how many dads tore their ACLs at the NBA city
like fall trying to dunk what they thought would be like a funny thing to dunk and then trip over
trip over the garbage they were all everybody was fighting all day and like I want to go in
men in black and I want to I need to show this family who's boss yeah watch this
oh
just kneecaps explode sir I think your bone is showing
just give me my Miller genuine draft I'll feel better did they have a doc there was there a doctor
in there a court-side doctor oh yeah that could help in case everything needed that yeah for all
the overzealous dads this is a frequent problem I I think though that might have helped it in that
as soon as you left both theme parks you would hit our drought cafe and NBA city yeah those are in
between like yeah across the lake you need to eat like I just I don't care I just need to eat
something here's my might have benefited from that then you go there wait on half hour line
you're then order and then your food shows up one hour later now you really need to prove who's boss
the family six Miller genuine drafts deep they have four quarters to get your food
all right and we're at the half and it's zero zero again
my buzzer at the buzzer ice cold mozzarella sticks
never I think giant screens probably helped and it's just this basic stuff probably helped
to compare to the Disney NBA experience which I was believe was about 50 or 60 dollars yes did
not have that much to do what could you take a picture I seen or remember images of people
taking picture with like an Adam Silver wax figure I don't think that was like well that was
one of the drawing wax figure read of NBA head Adam Silver what I hope that's true I don't know
if it is my plus up for this is what I think they should have built a full-size NBA court
and had the tables on the court it should have been lit in there like it was an arena
and then like I guess you could have some people depending on how big it was you would have some
people like sort of sitting in the stands but a lot of like that would be the prime dining location
would be on the court and there would be the noises going on around your waiter would come out like
from North Carolina yes yes standing five eight Shane there would be a little show like it at
rainforest cafe or something maybe the waiters would come out as if yeah all once right yeah
that's what you're saying okay yes Alan Parsons project yeah I was in the partisan project everybody
like once an hour Jason's right there was indeed a photo app with a wax
maker of the abyss over at the NBA experience this was Bob Iger's pet project he was so excited
about it he was so bold like nondescript man I why would they make a wax figure of him
dad can I get a picture with Adam's yeah 50 bucks for you 50 for mom and 50 for dad
and this will occupy two and a half hours maybe Bob Iger isn't the smartest man on the planet
oh god we got all right let's file this away we got yeah we got to talk to you
and maybe Adam's silver wax figure is a separate episode um uh anything else about NBA city no
giant statue that giant like brass statue outside of a nondescript player of a nondescript player
it's not particularly dynamic oh I think there was a three point shot like fenced in area where
you could try your luck that's like a half court shot contest to get like a free you know potato
oh yeah that would be good yeah yeah yeah that's what they do that I don't know they should have
and and the regular restaurant service continues during all that it spills drinks than it does
yeah some of the um I think the message board rumors this was eyed it's like well maybe
there's talk this could be the wwe hall of fame oh yeah yeah oh there's a never built
oh yeah it wasn't ever built for sure but a big problem was they had contracts for taping
other promotions that's right uh at the sound stages in between the parks so there was a
conflict of interest oh oh gotcha okay I mean one of the closest things now to hall of fame
has just been opened in Saudi Arabia really it's not a hall of fame but it is like a theme parkie
through the undertaker section thing that is just recently open there yes and he uh gave an
a sports the undertaker came out in costume with his music during like a football a football match
or sock american soccer yeah yeah christiano renaldo was like laughing oh you saw this yeah
I saw I watched for some reason they flew the undertaker out to do this to give the trophy
yeah I don't it's not a wrestling they love the undertaker it's the kingdom of saudi of ravi
yeah they do I mean what you which place doesn't love the undertaker yeah it's kind of kind of his
vibe a little bit yeah that's true I love the tagger yeah yeah um I had some cool long hats like
that um I I'm gonna do this one because it's a little maybe the last one's a little funnier
and you know we're in kind of the neck of the woods we're over uh across the lake
and uh right around here was something that got um the rare move of being sectioned off rezoned
you might say from the theme park into city walk despite being a long walk I apologize
from the main city walk uh and that being when they opened a new entertainment uh uh production
uh out of the former nickelodeon studios turning that into the blue man group the blue man group
had a residency for a long time yeah it's really you know that's technically in the park but they
did they created a new entrance they like re uh you know re landscaped it down there that looked
nice so that's but that was city walks I do feel like we have to talk about it yeah anyone ever see
it I never saw it uh it seemingly is very successful you know like because it lasted so long
I saw their show at their uh theater in astor place in Manhattan okay in like the early 2000s
and it was really fun this is one of those things where I feel like I would have not bet a lot of
money that this is going to be a lasting thing but the blue man group is going to be something
that will have like different shows in different parts of the country many outposts many outposts
many blue men like it doesn't feel like dad is gonna love this on especially on a vacation but
boy would I have been wrong yeah like blue man really has probably made a lot of money
it's silly it's funny it's not pretentious uh yeah you know it feels like culture but then is
sort of theme parky I watched a video of what was some of what was at this show when I think it's
like they like enter video screens and then leave perfectly synced up yeah you know play a big
xylophone a bunch of pipes I have no problems with anything that happened at this blue man
group show as far as I can tell they do a lot of physical comedy they shoot a lot of streamers and
I think they shoot like I don't want to say toilet paper but they shoot like paper in the audience
and people like that and then they do a lot of stuff with paint and paint balls
not they don't shoot the audience with paintball but they shoot each other
and there's like funny little gags have I told this story before on the show that I used to edit
clip show I've said this I guess but have I said that I edited a clip that was so revolting once
I felt physically sick and almost threw up it was for the show whacked out videos all right warning
and I guess that's a whole channel down here you get most of what you watch pluto tv down here
oh yeah yeah a wax so whacked out sports was the original that was a big big uh big uh ad mover it
would like beat leno in certain markets and it was sports accidents and then they had a spin-off
very much so they were like that that's why I got the job uh and they just had a clip library of
almost like snuff film level like weirdness nobody died as far as I saw but you would find clips in
there and go oh my god what is this and there were two clips of a person with a blue face dressed like
a blue man and I'm like well what is this clip so I'm watching it and the guy is is like sitting
there like silently or he's lying down I can't even remember and he just starts going
and then he throws up blue paint all over his face and it's like this looks like a grainy
home video from like 1998 quality I don't know what year is from and then there's a second video
where he has like just like a bright yellow face and he throws up yellow paint same guy I
like the same guy and he throws it up all over himself and it really made it seem like he wasn't
in his mouth he had it in his stomach and he was like regurgitating it up and the way the reason
it made me feel like I was gonna get sick is because it took so long the like like and I'm
just like watching this going what is that like and I remember thing up fluid he was barfing up
I put off editing it for a couple weeks and then at a certain point everything was just there was
only a couple things left in the pile and at that point I had seen the video so I was not I was
a little used to it and we see a cut of the we haven't seen a cut of the paint guy yet yeah
puke guy puke paint man put it after uh cow ripken jr getting hit with a ball in the crotch
Jason that is too expensive footage for this situation you are more likely to see like a
no no name crotch hits that's right yeah yeah so so every time anybody talks about the blue man
group now my first thought is these these clips your blue man is a man regurgitating there's a
man who threw up paint slowly job was that on a cot like a prison cot in one of them lying down
and you watch for two minutes while he's just trying to summon this paint back up
do you think he was doing this of his own will or was he being forced to by somebody who was
going to pocket the money from whacked out videos I have I have many jokes that I won't say about
people who ran whacked out videos but it's anything is possible I'll say that and anybody
could have gotten these clips from this could have been a prisoner of war this could have easily been
footage obtained after some sort of a raid and their vhs in the yeah in the tape library I'm
worried I mean I wonder do we need to contact some sort of human rights organization because
I feel like the conditions that this person was living under were totally whacked out
well I think you're correct about that I felt that they were whacked out for sure I feel like
I have done a you in a bit where they like dribble paint out of their mouth yes but I don't know that
anyone is trying to regurgitate it in agony on a journey I don't think that happened to a blue man
this was a failed audition tape the you here well quick I have to make a joke I was about to make
the UN oftentimes classify situations as whacked out so you have to make sure
there's unhealthy there's dangerous and there's whacked out right so they have a sort of a board
to decide that yeah flag different humanitarian crisis crises has whacked out was it whacked out
sports he said well whacked out sports was original I was working in this instance on whacked out
videos oh brother now I would go on to work on sports crash which was a different sports
accident show but that was not whacked out sports and not whacked out the accidents were less whacked
out I guess yeah a little more grounded you were kind of like editing phases of death
in many ways I was yes there were other shows too but we don't have time that was your job was to
sift through the ones like this one's funny this one started funny but then the person died yeah
I think to be honest the main editor I would not be shocked if he went through all these clips
and took the ones where people died out so the assistant editors didn't see them I wouldn't be
shocked if that's sort of what was going on the Orlando mayor shot himself that was that was sent
in as a whacked out video no no it was a Pennsylvania politician you're thinking of our bud Dwyer
killing himself who was not buddy Dyer the mayor of Orlando wow I might be after an episode we just
did the episode this is like ample hell you're right you're right I apologies we just went through
this and yet I presented that as an Orlando mayor you said it so confidently is that the Orlando
mayor who killed him you know what it's like bud Dwyer and buddy Dyer and they're both politicians
our very nice why everyone killed himself on camera but he's not current Orlando mayor buddy
Dyer now buddy Dyer didn't has not died our bud Dwyer died yeah so you got to keep that straight
see podcasting is like that jazz club that used to be at city wall yeah podcasting is like jazz
we know that we say it all the time you're saying the memories you forgot yeah
that is like soloing that's when you solo is when I tell the soup the soup uh tie story that's a solo
I did on this show this is like you know well it's like that you know there's this joke I don't know
if you know it the aristocrats and when a comic tells it it's basically like a jazz guy doing some
it is like that yeah anyway you can buy a DVD of a home video movie about the aristocrats
that's true I um okay blue man group um the I don't know there was a poncho zone
when they gave you the poncho they didn't charge you so you'd be yeah to wear a poncho in the first
first few rows or you'd get wet possibly with regurgitated paint I'm not sure I'm all mixed
up on this now uh it was at the sharp aquos theater Nickelodeon became the sharp aquos theater that is
type of television yeah that is still around um I this is all fine except that it was done over the
husk of Nickelodeon studios which I love very much and seeing I felt a betrayal seeing those
curious blue faces yeah instead of the Nickelodeon splat that I love very much um this is one of those
things that uh got screwed by covid this it ran it was very successful it ran from 2007 to 2021
in 2017 blue man group was acquired by Cirque du Soleil for 65 million dollars which doesn't
sound like enough honestly pretty cheap uh so maybe that wasn't good but that gave uh
suddenly there was a blockade of Cirque du Soleil presence in Orlando there was no man group and of
course the downtown Disney there was Cirque du Soleil's La Nuba so you could of course too we all
know of course La Nuba um so you could take your pick but then covid was really bad to Cirque du
Soleil they shut everything down they were already I think having some financial troubles
and then covid exasperated it but yeah so they uh they shut down everything fired everybody although
I think they've bounced back yeah I think they've rehired a ton um La Nuba went away uh gave gave
over to uh gave away to drawn to life as we know uh but uh blue man group I think after a year it
was like uh yeah we're never doing that again that's not coming back yeah um so uh RIP covid
fallen brother right you might not like really didn't die of co no blue men died of covid as far
as we know but the the show did this another one like journey into imagination where like uh I know
theme parks don't bring back stuff usually but if you put a little bit of money into putting that
geyser back in and you read did the Nickelodeon studios as like a nostalgia museum
oh that's true I think the uh you know older millennials with disposal income would be there
in a heartbeat but if they're getting rid of our legacy stores do they really think that we're a
long term I don't know I'm I don't I like what you're I look I like what you're saying they don't
think that we're a long they don't think we're long term yeah they think our generation's gonna
give up yeah what we care about doesn't matter that's what they did by closing that store
is there any chance of Comcast buying Viacom oh yes there's a chance of Exxon mobile buying
Viacom uh-huh there's a chance of Byron Allen buying of an Exxon station buying Viacom I'll
be watching gas tv oh I love gas station tv now that's the quick bites that Quibi should
yeah it was already taken care of by gas tv I just suck when they crack down we can't share our gas
station tv oh yeah yeah um okay a ramping of speed as we can get to the end appropriately ramping
of speed as we talk about the nascar sports grill uh that came that they had that too I know I mean
you know you're around all of it yeah yeah but every every sport and every music all were represented
uh there was a nascar restaurant it's uh what is now NBC sports grill which I referred to
there are room for 530 people in there um it's one of when painted that way and not in the current
NBC style which I think is okay graphically the nascar style made it one of the ugliest buildings
I've ever looked at giant checkered flag weird bad this something claims that uh the in front
of the restaurant was the winner's circle where the reigning nascar Winston cup champions car is
on display when it opened it was Jeff Gordon's du Pont Chevrolet the 1998 champion there's no
fucking way they ever changed that car right yeah they are not changing a car every year
far beyond the kind of thing anywhere but correct me if I'm wrong I don't know how often these
changed their frying oil and the fries let alone I have a suspicion how much um you led me into the
food which sounded uh spectacular um you know nachos with squeezy cheese uh sour cream is extra
of course yeah that's 12 that's 12 dollars the nascar spirit you know um they had uh uh something
called ruben rolls which were egg rolls but the innards more like ruben sandwiches and you could
dip them in russian dressing oh and I think that's where I'm thinking a big meaty ruben sandwich
it's the breakfast guy who sucks beer out of his own ponytail that's disgusting
you know you know what scott I hate to tell I'm looking at different photos and there are
different cars really in different photos maybe they did it yeah like just so callous
I know we're doing any change out that they said that's white and then there's one with a blue one
here and there's one they're just painting the same car I'm not sure oh there's two here at this
point huh and they're not always two was there a tie that year maybe there was a tie yeah because
here look there's only one here this year huh and then so maybe they were driving the cars did they
forget to take the key out of the ignition well probably all the time you could just tool around
you could just steal a nascar drive it into the river that's why there was only one in that one
shot because some kids stole it the other the runner-up was stolen we have maybe I don't know
um the here's some other menu items points leader chicken alfredo rate ruben is racing barbecue ribs
ruben is racing ruben is race calculate that what that means like a dry rub I guess
I guess so is it why but why is ruben a guy but is a rubber is it rubber I don't think so ruben is
racing ruben is racing ruben is race wait okay ruben is racing is the name of a nascar podcast
so it is a phrase it's something that's said in days of thunder so that's something I don't
know what it means though and I think the phrase is weird there's a quote of someone saying it to
his son ruben's son is racing oh you get it now well now we all know ruben is racing now we know
ruben is racing um is it like if you're real close you're rubbing like bumper bumper to bumper oh it's
yes you're like rubbing up against you're like aggressive yeah you want to be you want to be
rubbing you want to rub and rub and bumpers how many videos did you edit of two cars rubbing
then crashing well it wasn't nascar footage it was some sort of drag race from teams yeah yeah no
you can't clear no mlb and no nascar drag racer chokes on ribs flips car
oh it was just footage of his widow outside of a hospital all right i'll put it i guess i'll put
it in the final cut folder beat leno last night man's real dev both choking and car crashing
pj leno um the one that i could really could not process in my head is this this menu item
nobody calls me chicken ranch salad nobody calls me chicken ranch salad and then behind that is
something you can order it with which is boogity shrimp nobody calls me chicken ranch salad boogity
shrimp well nobody calls me that's back to the future i mean i don't know right just general
aggression like nobody calls me sure but it's the most famous is the back to the future right that's
the most famous use of that i know chicken is a general term that was used like a green salad
chicken breast on top or like chicken tossed with mayonnaise i don't know how was it tossed
i don't i don't see the tossing the ranch is in the name but i don't know and you probably ask
for it to be tossed however you want but then under that is a there's a separate item boogity
boogity boogity shrimp okay apparently that's something that somebody says also that is some
sort of nascar that's like a nascar commentators racing catchphrase yeah there it is yeah country
music it sounds honestly it sounds weird or bad but that's you know i don't know i don't know all
i all i know is i just i if i need to have that information coming in and i'm staring at the phrase
nobody calls me chicken ranch salad boogity shrimp yeah i just i don't know it it gives me a headache
it feels like is out my brain would you would you be more comfortable having like the um the things
oatmeal at marvelmania i mean you don't even you're not you don't have so much affection for that
property either don't but would it be like cyclops chowder would that be better or worse than these
phrases i don't know i'm afraid is cyclops bad no he's a good he's the one of the leaders of the x-men
okay just like would you eat cyclops's chowder he also takes you to your seat and
and he makes okay well if i can look him in the presumably one eye does he have one eye well he
has two eyes but he has a visor a ruby quartz visor that protects his eyes because his eyes are out
control when he opens them they shoot lasers okay so you'll see you'll look into his visor he's got
a visor like jordy laforge similar uh-huh who's friends with data well he's you're close you're
close that's all i'll say we're gonna see the comment i have unsubscribed from the podcast due
to the way scott says data that was the last straw for me uh uh yeah you were close you were close
uh anyway that's yeah yeah i don't know i'll eat this i'll i'd love to eat the cyclops's chowder
as long as he doesn't as long as he doesn't burp it up from his mouth scott's scott's lying on his
chowder um i we're getting towards the end or if i missed any like quick hit fallen brothers let's
look around us what do we see um what do you see take it in take it in you might have noticed
a doomsday clock there we're two minutes to doomsday that's uh when inevitably toothum shoots up from
the ground oh god i hope yeah well i'm really hoping there's a ticking clock at this point
yeah yeah i know too some not we haven't gotten there yet but i don't feel great about the
franchise you're gonna be chased around by the boston dynamics robot dog when that happens
uh i think the florida location has since given that away
or sold it to another institution of some type there's a different steampunk restaurant that is
a robot now yeah they adopted it for it either went to another themed restaurant or like the
indianapolis pd uses it to terrorize suspects yeah it's a killer we're i well we're almost there
i i mean if you i have one little quick one go for it um my my favorite thing on any fallen
brothers list that i saw and now i'm like worried i didn't keep the the photo i wonder if i can find
it really quick but there's like a lot of odd ones um like nobody documented basically like
the any of the little places but my absolute favorite one that i found is something called
captain crackers and the official description on the website is this is on universal's website the
world's funnest in quotes toy store and then now i can't find like my picture of it i actually do
like captain captain crackers was a character he was like a big like bird or a bear or something
uh-huh poked out from the sign i'll try to figure this out i'll try to find captain crackers is it
this that is him you found him there he is is he like a koala what is he he looks like a dog with
a hat oh wow that's not what i picture a doctor looking like that's crazy he has like a beanie hat
he's got his tongue and he's got colorful whiskers he's got blue yellow and red whiskers
wow that's crazy i actually didn't see that that was part of the skyline at one point wow i like
him that's whacked i love that i love him and it looks like really like expanded like it looks
he looks good yeah really well molded i don't know what's going on inside of the store but it's a
great sign i want to know more about captain crackers want to know why he's crackers despite
being a dog i want to know how he became a captain i want to know the full mythology of
captain crackers that's all yeah oh he rules yeah yeah i really like him um so i don't know that
that's it for me i feel like we're um uh i think we're winding it down here um i want to make a
quick note about one of these old just to uh sum up what you had said before about we were talking
batman and schumacher this looks like the riddler's like machine that you put on people's
brains like from this old city walk concept art do you know what that is i'm looking at it's like
like the kiosk i think it's the kiosk where you get information and it's still there
but it's like it really makes sense looking at the skyline now to underline that point that this
looks like schumacher yeah world yeah um i i think that's really at the core of it that might be why
we like these stupid places captain crackers is straight out of gotham yes he could have been
either a hero who helps batman and robin or a villain who hurts them yeah for sure large
yeah yes very big yeah he's awesome oh my god and there he is there he is wow check him out
wow is he do you consider him like your pet yeah pretty much unless you guys want one you want him
you know what i do want in this case yeah yeah you could take we would probably pay too much
if we had it you can really take advantage of us price-wise right now yeah now we really you've
you've got it you've got some uh live fish on the hook when it comes to captain crackers speaking
of really big look how big this marquee is for the motown cafe yeah like that it's right by the
welcome to universal orlando sprawling sign coming right out of the parking garage and it's just like
huge well we thought big back then that's what we're realizing just like visionaries like joel
schumacher yeah you know what maybe it's better down here in a way in a lot of ways we ran out
of stores to talk about but i i'm honestly surprised how much i liked it i thought this
was like a punishment from the sector keeper but you're always welcome back and the beauty of this
like we made it i think we survived uh podcast the ride the city walks are the city walk orlando
saga multiverse of madness but i guess wait before we can do that how does it work yeah i
know like the keeper gives you guys like a little stone or yeah yeah yeah something kind of like
manifest let me just rummage around here and see what i can find oh just like pick up any uh
all right how about uh i mean here's uh like a reusable ralph's bag that coltrane used
oh wow whoa oh wow john coltrane's grocery bag yeah jeez is that you guys want that yeah all right
we'll take that for today i don't know if i would have wanted it but now i realize it's an important
part of jazz legend we could store the other stones in it oh yeah yeah otherwise we're just
going to be carrying them just with our hands like idiots oh wow useful appreciated great
fuck i almost want to stay down here i kind of do too yeah jeez wait a minute what's happening
there's some there's some rumbling wait something's something's poking through
something's poking through behind your under your chair there wait a minute is that one of those
fuel rod kiosks that gave that gave eva so much trouble yeah oh shit they must have closed it and
sealed it up for good wait that's right with sector creeper watch out it's bursting up from under you
oh oh bays bays oh head to phase four across the lake oh shit oh god all right well i guess we
better get out of here soon yeah this thing's gonna be crawling with fuel rod kiosks they're
gonna crush us all before it's like poltergeist when all the gravestones are popping up oh god
oh god okay yes wait where are you right before we go where are my stogies right there oh no another
fuel rod kiosk has crushed your stogies oh god crap guys let's get out of here okay yeah okay
i think we're going to be keeping things rolling here on the second gate so stay tuned uh we will
remain behind the the second gate is behind the the portal hole that uh we crossed to here so keep
tuned to podcast the ride the second gate to get every sector ad free uh oh shit i see one coming
for us right now fuel rods