Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents
The City Walk Orlando Saga
Multiverse of madness
A daily, extremely necessary series
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando
Welcome to Podcast The Ride
The City Walk Orlando Saga
I'm Jason Sherrod and joined by Mike Carlson
I'm here and it's the multiverse of madness
The multiverse of madness
Scott Caroner
Yo, hey, we're getting through it, we're getting through it
And we're deep up, we're still up in the weird up the stairs and ramps zone
Lest you thought we were moving back down the weird stairs and ramps
Maybe the most weirdness is up at the top
Yeah, I think that's right
And you know, Joker comes up a lot on this podcast
But maybe, I feel like we'll be all dancing up and down the ramps
Like Joker by the end of this episode perhaps
I mean, yes, the events of this got me Jokerfied
That's what I'm saying
For sure
Let's do the full round up of who's around today
Well, our guest today, my love, my love
My love
That's how you introduce
That's my iconic line
We say all the time around the house in acknowledgement to Mike's my love
That's how I do it
Here's the go, it's stylist Jane Clare
Oh, hey, what's up?
Okay, just some housekeeping first really quick
So number one, I just want to address
I have seen some comments online about my previous episodes
And I just want to say, I know you guys think that I talk too much and cut the boys off
But yes, of course, that is exactly right
Men should be speaking the least amount possible all the time
So I do stand by that
And second, we need to address little because I want the trademark
I want the residuals
Little is just how I say that word my whole life
I say mittens and I say little and all of a sudden it's this thing
And I just I need that to be like known and you need some closure
No, I just need a 10 credit
Fair enough
All right, attention
At first I wasn't that mad and then I was like, okay, I just said it once and now it's a whole thing
And I feel like it's associated with Jason and I'm like, no, my whole life
So right anyway, just getting that like out of the way at the top
Jane, you know, there's the phrase get that bag
There is the bag that awaits at the end of little
The little bag
It's a little bag, but it's so full and you got to get that bag
Always get the bag
There's so many residuals, there's so much weight, you know
People are saying this is nationwide, this is international now
When Jason, especially when Jason says it, should he credit you after every little?
I want you guys to say little and then say Jane
Jane Click
You have to
Really quick like like you signed it, you're instituting like Matt Groening signs
The Simpsons art in the future if we say it, we got to give you a quick
Okay, great
Is the speed okay or do I need to slow that down?
Oh, speed is whatever
Okay, okay, just as long as it's there
Dealers choice
Okay, okay, great
Nice, nice
We can do that
Now let's summon our dear friend
Oh yes
Please, yeah
We have multiple beings here
Our little, say hello to our little friend
Jane Claire
Boys, boys, Jane
So good to see you, how are you?
What's up man?
Good to see you all
Yeah, you all know each other because you've been staying with the two of them
I've been staying with Jason and Claire, yeah
Thanks for letting me shack up Garfield rules
Thanks for taking him out so much, it helps a lot when you take him out
It's the least I could do, like you know, I made a chore wheel
Yeah, yeah
He's a very responsible house guest
Yeah, so we all spin the wheel every Sunday after mass
Okay, yeah
Is that how a chore wheel works?
You spin it like it's a wheel of fortune?
Isn't it usually just…
Yeah, no, this one you spin like wheel of fortune
Oh, okay
Yeah, there's a lot more Jason slices on that than Sector Keeper slices though
Well, you live there
I mean, I guess that's true
I'm really confused by this wheel, this wheel is a wheel of fortune wheel with your names on it
It's our names on it
Wait, are chores and names or are they just names and then you call out a chore before you spin it?
You call out a chore, then you spin it, and it can land on Jason, Claire, or I'm sorry, Jason
It's okay, people do it all the time, you can call me Claire, it's okay
No, no, no, like literally everyone calls me Claire and I'm like, it's fine
Jason, Jane, or Claire
Yep
Okay
So she's got two
She's a little bit of a disadvantage
Garfield, Sector Keeper, Bankrupt
Oh, you can get bankrupt from this chore wheel?
Lose a turn
Oh wow
And then every other week we put a little trip to Aruba on
No one ever gets that one
We've never landed on it though
No
It's like a pie cut into 32 pieces
Yes
Okay
The day when Garfield has to make the bed, that's a tough day for everyone
That's a long day
Or if Garfield has to take Garfield out, good luck
Oh, but we have to obey the wheel
It's the only way
He gets out the front door and then just lies on the mat and just goes to sleep for like four hours
Okay, well
Next to Jason
Yeah, that's my mat
And then if I try to take up more, he growls at me
I mean that is actually really accurate
He's been very, we call him Gronkle
Mr.
Gronkle from Busy World of Richard Scarry
It's like a speedy, irritable warthog who lives in the big house down the street
Sometimes Garfield, if you get too close to him, he just goes
Like these little annoyed growls
So we go, are you going Gronkle mode?
Are you Gronkle?
So Mr.
Gronkle is, the animals talk in that show, they're all animals, right?
Yeah, yeah
I forget, I've never seen the show
You've never seen that show?
I don't think so
I've seen the book, but I didn't see the show
Yeah, I've seen like the, I know what they look like
Well, they had that Kings Island, like Cedar Fair crossover
I thought there was a Richard Scarry
When I was younger
King's Island, yeah, there was a slight Richard Scarry presence
Because we lived in Ohio when I was younger and so I was like really into that
Yeah, it's a cute show
Look, I'm happy to watch it
What was the presence in the parks?
I'm not sure
It was mostly a restaurant where you could get personal pan pizzas
But that's where Richard Scarry is like everybody's got their little jobs, right?
Yeah
Is Richard Scarry like a thing where they try to like put like capitalism in your head?
Like you need a job or is there some sort of propaganda there?
Probably a bit, yeah
I think it's more about community and trying to go like this person is this job
And they will help you like this is how this person, this is a crossing guard
And we are learning that he helps us do this
It's actually really cute
Okay
Get your daughter on it
I think she'd love it
I'm open to all the shows, all the shows I hear I need to show her
One day she's like, daddy, why isn't podcaster in this show?
Is it a kind of job people are ashamed of?
I'll like excuse myself and I'll cry in the bathroom
Why isn't there a podcaster that's a rabbit daddy?
His ears wouldn't fit under the headphones
Yeah, that's the only reason why, otherwise I'm sure they'd love to put it in the show
Close that book
Kick it out of her hand
The book was old, the job didn't exist yet
It's dated
The cartoon's square, it's four by three, it's old
It's irrelevant, not like podcasts
I go in the office and I'm like animating by hand a Richard Scarry short with a rabbit that podcasts
Here it is, the flip book
Look, he's got a dirty microphone
He's the happiest animal in busy town
Here's his MacBook Pro
This rabbit is uploading his podcast to megaphone right now
See?
He's loving it
As for this podcast, as for the happy rabbits that all of us are today
Why don't we get the official assignment of today's sector?
Yes, yes, boys, boys, Jane, today's sector is Phase 3 Sector 2, BK Whopper Bar, Panda Express, Moe's Southwest Grill, and Hart and Huntington Tattoos
Getting inked up, boys
Yeah, yeah
I bet people, if you know what's at City Walk, Orlando, you're probably like, one of the weird things is that there is a tattoo place
I wonder how that will be handled in the series
And I think we'll close out with that, but just let that tantalize
I know, then
See you guys getting some fresh ink
Well, you know, yeah, well, there'll be a big reveal later of, you know, maybe of some ink
We'll see
We'll see what happens
Three good boy tramp stamps
Jason has a wimpy burger tramp stamp
He actually does, how did you know that?
He had it before this though
That was before the day
Yeah, yeah
That wasn't from there
They had to work around that
But we got another big thing up here, the food court
I don't know if they officially use this term anymore, if it's on a sign or anything, but at least when it opened, they called this the top of the walk food court
Opened in 2009, kind of a later edition, I think there were not a bunch of quick service options
And, you know, this was a fun thing to hit
And it seems like, Jane, some genuine enthusiasm from you about some of the establishments in the top of the walk food court
Yeah
Oh, I speak, okay
Sure, if you want, don't have to
Yeah, so I love Moe's Southwest Grill
Because that's a chain and they had it in the Midwest when I lived there a little bit growing up
And then of course they have them in Florida and they have like amazing tofu that you can get
And, you know, when I was in like high school and stuff, I was, I've been a vegetarian for a very long time
So when I was younger, I was like, oh cool, tofu, this was still kind of a new thing back then
And yeah, so it just became a place that I, you know, me and my mom would go a lot
And so whenever I see one, I get really excited because they don't have any here
Oh, that's true, yeah, not in California really
I know them primarily from airports, you know, they're cities
The Orlando International Airport specifically
Which we were talking about
We were just talking about that
We had like, oh, pretty good experience with that one a few years ago
I was so stoked, I was like, Jason, oh my God, there's a Moe's, I have to go
And I was like bolted off and he was like, okay, goodbye
Yeah, I'll see you in a bit
You ran away from him?
To get to Moe's?
I mean, for Queso
Alright, well for Queso then
For Queso
That's a good choice to make
So yeah, so I was so jazzed and then, you know
But, yeah, extremely disappointed
You don't, a food establishment at CityWalk Orlando?
Are you crazy?
This can't be true
The citywalk socket and food disappointed someone?
The running, the theme for this food court and sector in general
It's complications
Sure
Yeah, well, so basically we ended up
I think the goal here was to end up with doing a little like potluck
Like let's all grab little things from all of the great food establishments
And have a nice little picnic
So Moe's was your clear call
Which I was glad about
I don't know who's going to be passionate about Moe's of the Groovy
Wait, are you talking about this one?
That's when we went to BK though
Oh, right, right
I didn't do Moe's then
Oh, you're right, separately you did Moe's
Separately I did it twice
Right
Wow, oh yeah, there were two visits, wow
Yeah, I don't know why
I had such faith for the second time
Wait, was the first one bad and then you went back?
The first one was like fine and the second one was like a train wreck
This gives me strength whenever you all return to a shitty food place
I was really just thinking of you
Thank you, yes, you seemingly do it constantly
I was going to say, you take after your boyfriend in this way
Episodes worth of complaints, but we're going back on Tuesday
Look, look, okay, you only get one million chances, chain restaurant
Millions strikes and you're out
I have to shout out the fact that unlike the bar in The Simpsons
Moe's is not named after a man named Moe
Did you know this as a Moe's fan?
Do you know why Moe's is Moe's?
Is it something about rock and roll?
It used to be like a more rock and roll based place
And when you walked in, they used to all go, welcome to Moe's
Like it was a whole thing and they like really, really stopped doing that pretty quick
No, I'm not kidding and it was like fun
It was like, yeah, they said it
It was like a party, yeah
Moe's is an acronym, Moe's is, you're right, it is rock and roll oriented
It is musicians, outlaws and entertainers
Is this Southwest?
The sector keeper flew out of his chair when he heard this
He just called Moe, it's got to mean something
Geez, I didn't know I could die twice, bitch
Well, yeah, because they used to
I would have never guessed in one million of my eternal years
That's what it stands for
Sorry, musicians, outlaws and entertainers
Musicians, outlaws, same thing
Well, because they don't do it anymore, they totally changed everything
But they used to have big posters of like famous, like they would have land
I remember the big Bob Marley one for some reason
Sure
Big Bob Marley, probably like Madonna
Like it was a whole thing which made more sense
Musician, musician, outlaw
Well, Madonna also an entertainer I would say
And a style outlaw
So you would have to break the rules
You have to be all three things to be on the wall
I was thinking like Billy the Kid
Jesse James
I don't remember
Robert Blake
He was up there in the outlaw
Oh, yeah
There's a poster of Jason that says, wanted dead or alive at Moses
I answered too many chip refills
Oh, free chip refills
Okay, that's good
And that was so exciting to me when I was younger
Bottomless chips
And you're free when you're in high school or whatever
I will tell you why those stopped existing
Jane, why there aren't rock and rollers represented
It was due to a lawsuit from the estate of Jerry Garcia
So it really ultimately Moe's were the outlaws themselves
Using unlicensed
Not asking for image likeness clearance
So, yeah, no rocksters represented at this city
There's not a lot of walls to work with anywhere
Anyway
May I speak about the second time we went back when Scott wasn't there with me
So I was like, I'm going to give it one more try
Because I love this and I don't get a lot of chances to go here
What was wrong the first time?
Just fine, not the most
It was just not it
It just was not it
But you were like, oh, okay, it's a theme park
But second time I go back, it's later at night
So there are a bunch of new hire teen 20-somethings that clearly do not give a fuck about literally anything
And there's one older guy who's clearly the manager who's trying to keep things afloat
But knows he's got a bunch of fuck-offs just like there
And so stuff is kind of getting low for the end of the night
And I was like, I would love a tofu burrito
And this one kid was like, yeah, we don't have any more of that
And I was like, okay, can I get this?
And they're like, yeah, we don't have that either
And the guy's like, hey, go make some tofu
And the kid's like, um
And the guy's like, just go fucking make some tofu, okay?
So then he starts making my burrito
But it takes so long for the tofu to cook
That by the time it comes out, he had to make a new burrito
Because it was all soggy and fucking gross
And then the people are just fucking around and stuff
And the guy's kind of trying to save it
And there were some substances involved
How much am I allowed to say about that?
All of it, yeah, I guess
Okay, I was high
And I don't know if we had drinks, but I was definitely high
And I was like, you guys suck
I was talking to the manager, I was like, this fucking sucks
This is the worst mo's I've ever experienced right now
And I'm like, this really fucking sucks right now
And he was just like, okay, I'm sorry
And I texted the group, but I said
Because I was kind of on one and also on one
And he said, more mess at mo's
And Scott said, what, why?
And I said, new hires making burritos wrong
And manager taking over, no tofu left
And the employee was like, sorry, all gone
And manager was like, no, do it
And they had to restart making mine
I'm done, y'all, with an upside down smiley face
And they were so mad
They had to open a new thing of rice
And Scott, Jason's like, Jane, fucking stop texting this
But I was so enraged
This is the best part of the story
Well, she had sent me to this image of like just the end of the night
Like fucked up toppings
Looks like you'll get food poisoning
Wait, I wasn't done yet
Okay, okay
And it's almost over
And then Scott said, everything broke today, game over
And I said, my spirit included
Yeah, for sure
There was also some point
And I forget whether they said this, you or me
But we asked about like salsa verde
Oh, yes
And they were like, oh, we don't make that anymore
It goes bad too quick
Like not enough people order it
I was like, that was one of my favorite things at most too
So I was quickly like, are you fucking kidding me?
And then I was like, do you have this other sauce?
And they're like, no
What is this?
So do you think that like other Mo's, they carry salsa verde or you think they were lying?
Yeah, it's like a standard thing
So you think maybe this location is just like the teams were lying because they were lazy
It's like it's like a ice cream machine McDonald's situation where sometimes they go, oh, we don't have like 11 p.
m.
You want ice cream coming?
That's not on and this is a common thing
Well, no, because it was the first time I got it, I found that out
Yeah
When things weren't as crazy
Interesting
By the way, how common is that for you, Michael?
Certainly happened a few times
Yeah, that's happened to me a lot
That ice cream machine being broken
Because they use like a proprietary ice cream machine
And it's very difficult to repair
But you're believing them with the broken?
That's a lie
Well, it's a lie, but then sometimes it is also true
How do you know?
Do you go back and check it?
I've done some research
Yes, he does
This is a thing in the way I have read about the perpetually broken
Yeah
But you think all of it you think systemically
I think a lot of the time they're saying it just doesn't work
It's hard to clean, right?
Yeah, and it's just like
It's very difficult to clean
Especially because by the end of the night
You're not getting so many orders necessarily
Unless it's probably like near a venue where you get a bunch of drunk people
So it's just easier
Or just a sober Mike who wants some ice cream
A little treat
Of course
Or some sober treat, boys
Jason walks in at 11 p.
m.
to a McDonald's in like overalls and a hard hat with a little tool belt
And a tackle box of tools, whatever you call that
I'll fix this, bad boy
They say, oh, sorry, it's not working
And they go, not yet
Not yet
And you just move that thing up on the counter and you walk by
Anytime I see one of those counter hinges
I'm like, let me in there
Let me in there, my man
What do you call the thing under the car when you go under it?
Like you're on like the little dolly thing
It slides
You get under the machine like with there with the wrench
And it sounds like he's chasing tires with the Indy 500
Grease all over your face
Yeah, he's doing it with that speed
All right, 26 seconds, I'll get it shorted next time, let's go
And then the employee next day is like, oh, yeah, so the ice cream repairman came in and the manager goes, what?
The ice cream, what?
What are you talking about?
The guy with the overalls
The guy with the ice cream is enthusiastic
And we tried to pay him, but he said, no, no, the joy is all mine
The love of the game
He goes, you already paid me and he licked his cone
He filled up his toolbox with ice cream and left
He had toolbox of ice cream
He licks the wrench, licks the screwdriver
Here's the results of my photo search
One is Jane making like the
In an Iron Maiden shirt making like the rock and roll
Oh, yeah
This is where I am definitely, you know, having a good time
But I think this is before any of this has happened because you have not been taught to be soured on this particular Mo's yet
This is right after they said, welcome to Mo's
Welcome to Mo's
We don't make the kind of salsa you like anymore
No, they didn't say it.
Fuck this place
They didn't even, yeah
They didn't even acknowledge me
They were talking to each other
And then I walked up and they were almost like, what?
Do you think they were, did you say 20s?
Like how old, you thought they were teens or 20s?
Something like that?
I have no reference of age anymore because everyone looks
Kids look old, adults look young
I fucking have no idea
Some podcasters look young too
Some podcasters look half their age or lower
If you're tall, you're old
Thank you, that is how I feel
Hey, wait
Hey, that's a biggest slam on my
Those are my rules
What part of listen to, now listen to all of Olivia Rodrigo's guts do you not understand?
Jane, you have the rock and roll spirit, but I immediately am grimacing at the sign that says
We built this city on guac and roll
I like that sign
I'm also not super fond of while my cheese gently weeps
It doesn't rhyme
That one I don't like, but the first one I like
Wait, I don't get that one
While my guitar gently weeps, but then it doesn't, cheese doesn't rhyme
I don't want my cheese weeping
It's a Beatles song
I'm not a Beatles kid
The Beatles are old
That one, that we know for sure
Some are dead
And some aren't old
At least two of them are dead
By the time this comes out
Oh, no
Did we just kill a Beatle?
Take it out, take it out
Yeah, yeah
I feel like that maybe covers Moe's unless you have more Moe's thoughts
No, I went back to last night there
You went back again, Jason
I know, I hadn't eaten there
I just tried to get, I just got like a bean burrito with like, I just needed some protein
But you heard what happened to your girlfriend
I know, but there was nothing else like, everywhere else was crowded
Well, you were also trying to be like, well she loves this, so
He was trying to have shared interests
Which she, I was trying to eat healthier
So you went to the place that made your girlfriend
No, she was fine, I don't think it made her sick
Look, I eat crap and shit all the time
Yeah, so
Wait, were you saying I eat crap and shit, that's what you eat?
Or was one of those that you shit after eating the crap?
Six of one, I have a dozen of the other
Okay, sure
Great clarification
So Jason went anyway
And you liked your meal?
No, it was not amazing
It was not amazing, it was just, again, I just needed some
What did you get?
I just got like bean rice and cheese and steak or something simple
And like whatever salsa they had left
And this was late
Yeah
You just got end of the night salsa
Which five minutes ago you showed us a photo of and said how gross it looked
Well, I think part of that was that it's like, you know
They could have used a wipe down on that counter
It was picked over
They know the emptiness of the empty Chipotle
Yeah, it's a breeding ground
Alright, so your household kept going back even though it was bad the first time
That's the magic of these places though, isn't it?
You got the draw, you want to try it again?
She on your side tonight?
That's what all of it's about
It's no fun to go to a place that you know is always good in quality
Where's the game in that?
Lady Luck, a place I only went to once, the BK Whopper Bar
Let's talk BK Whopper
Now I've been looking forward to this as an aspect of this
I feel like I clocked the opening of the BK Whopper Bar as kind of a
We've come across it here and there
We've talked about things that were there at the opening of City Whopper
They kind of got like a refresh of a lot of stuff in the late 2000s
And one of them being this
And I remember hearing about that and going that's such a cool idea
Yes
Not just a Burger King, totally customizable
You can make an insane Frankenstein Whopper creation
That sounds nuts
That doesn't sound like you look at it and it seems like any Burger King on earth
It's indistinguishable from a regular Burger King
It just has like windows
So you can see the lettuce before it gets on the burger
That's basically the difference
Wow
Right?
I mean right?
They say you want a revolution
It's like Baskin Robbins
It's like a Baskin Robbins, but Burger King
We were just at Baskin Robbins two days ago
The one over here where they train people?
Yeah
The drive thru
Yes
There's a big sign, like poster
What did it say?
Milkshakes
And we pulled up and were like hi
Could we have that when you're done with it?
What do you guys do with those?
I kind of love that
Was that an impression of yourself or Jason?
Both
It's us being a little grimy
Who would like that poster?
Yes, both of us
And they were like, corporate?
They don't think corporate would like that very much
And we were like, okay
But we were like, do you want me to ask?
He's like, no, no
And then I was like, I'll see what the vibe is when I get up there
There's this cool girl with a compliment on my sunglasses
And I was like, okay, she's like a cool bathroom girlie
Is what I say
And so I was like, okay, I'll ask her, she's my girl
And then she was like, I don't think corporate will be cool with that
And we're like, okay
And they were like, give us our milkshakes
She was your cool bathroom girlie?
Yeah, what does that mean?
Can I talk about?
Is this for a different episode?
I think it's for this
As long as you can talk about it, it's for this episode
Bathroom girlies would change
So we were at
Bathroom girlies are in this sector
Oh, good, he checked his notes
So this is at a different restaurant at Out Here City Walk
That's why I'm like, should I not say?
Oh, yeah, no, keep it broad strokes
Okay, broad strokes
So I had an experience recently
Jason's been on his sector keeper hat
Oh, let's keep that out of the…
I was at a restaurant recently
And the bathroom was such a disaster
Not like it was gross
But none of the soap was working
So they had a bottle of soap
But that was empty and the top was off
And it was on the counter
And me and a bunch of girls
Various ages, I say girls, but women
And we're all like, yo, there's no soap
And one of them is like, yeah
And there's no toilet paper in this one
I went, ladies, hold on
I went to find this manager
She fucking sucked
I had a whole thing
And Jason was like, please stop talking about this
I was like, no, she was so…
I fucking hit her
And so I was like, hey, man
This is going on
She argued with me about it for a minute
She's like, there's soap on the counter
I was like, bitch, go fucking look
And so we go in there and she fixes it
And all the girls and I were like…
I was like the leader
I love being the bathroom girly leader
And so I was like, guys, I got it
And everyone was like, oh, yay, great
Thank you, this lady fucking sucks
And then later we're walking around
And this woman comes over
She's like, by the way
They finally put toilet paper in that bathroom
I was like, girl, that's crazy
And she's like, I know for the price
So bathroom girlies love bathroom girlies
So this is just a general term now
That's extended out into just in like
You use it as any ally basically
Or this is a specific group of girls?
Just like the vibe of bathroom girlies
Like who are really cool and like supportive
And like all of a sudden
Like here's the thing
When you go into like the bathroom
And there's a vibe
Someone has to be the one to like break the silence
So everyone doesn't think they like hate each other
Because I don't know if that makes sense
In the way that men do not make eye contact
And maintain total silence in the bathroom
This whole community
This whole Richard's scary busy town happening
In the women's restrooms
Girls in restrooms
Like that's where like womanhood really like
That's where it lives
So yeah, so that is his term in general
So I like to be the leader of the girly group
You assert dominance
Because I also always want to be the leader
Because I'm a fucking Leo
And I don't want anyone telling me what the fuck to do
So I was like, fuck this
I'm going to get it figured out
So got it figured out
And then it was kind of like, yay, you did it
Fuck this lady
Like we were all on like one team
But it was so funny because this lady like stopped me
And I was like, oh shit
Like what the
She was like, they finally put like toilet paper in there
And it's so expensive
Can you believe?
I was like, girl, that's fucking crazy
Okay, bye
Like bathroom girlies, love them
Gotcha
So that's, that's
You could be deemed
If you find an ally anywhere
They're deemed bathroom girlies
It's an energy
Yeah
It's not specific to a bathroom
It doesn't have to be literally a bathroom
Usually
But like, you know, like I don't go clubbing
But like, like once I went and it's like you're you're fucked up in there
And girls are just like, girl, do you need something?
Are you good?
Don't text him
Don't text
Oh my God, girl, you're so right
Like
Wow
Have you facilitated a breakup in a bathroom?
Um, no
Not personally
At a concert someone was like, don't answer your phone
Oh, wow
To me
You like piled on to like
Oh, there's a movement happening here
I'll help with that
I've noticed
Because Jason, when you're talking about your trips that you take
You are gaining allies as you go
I feel
People like us
I'm sorry
I'm not saying that's not true
I'm saying, but like sometimes there'll be people who work at a specific part of the hotel
Oh yeah
Like there'll be
We talked a little bit about this
But I'm always impressed that you say, well, there was of course Susan we met
And then like she was our go-to girl while we were staying in whatever hotel
So it feels like would you consider the whoever that the woman you met at the hotel in Orlando?
Is she a bathroom girly?
Or is that not the same energy?
She's like an awesome mom who really cares about you
Okay, but she wouldn't be hanging out in the same space
It's just like a different vibe
Different vibe
That was a completely different vibe
She fucking rocked
She gave us free sodas and would tell us what's going on for the day
And would always like give us
Oh my God
Shortcut advice
Love her
Oh my God, I could cry
She's so sweet
Do you remember her name?
I haven't had a mic on her name
I'm just wondering if you did
You knew it then
You did know it, yeah
You did know it a few weeks ago
I just wanted to know
She's cool
What was the restaurant?
It was the chocolate emporium
No
Toothsum
This is our first hint that maybe the chocolate emporium could have some
Toothsum doesn't have toilet paper
It doesn't have good food either
We'll talk about that later
I bet we can dispute that for three days from now
When I say actual worse, I couldn't even swallow it
I went like, get this the fuck away from me
And they had to take it back
It was pretty rough
It came a half hour after his did
And then I get it
This is corrupting everything I thought I knew about Toothsum
My world has been turned upside down here
Don't fucking go there
Except for a friend of mine is
Well, for her sake, I will say a friend of because she's the one who works there
The Penelope lady
Okay
I'm not outing her
We were visiting Professor Dr.
Tooths
Professor Dr.
Toothsum
That was so fun
It was so cute
She's so cute
But back to the sector
Sorry
Back to the Whopper Bar
Yes, I thought this was going to explode my idea of what a Burger King could do
I agree
What did you encounter?
What's the reality of the situation?
Well, the reality of the situation was just
Pickle Whopper
And then there's like a handful of toppings you can add to it
So the idea, the revolutionary idea of choosing toppings at a counter restaurant
Which are mostly a good amount of them are cheese
American cheese, Swiss cheese, pepper jack, bacon, pepper bacon
Guacamole, jalapenos, crispy onions, onion rings
And was the cheese gently weeping?
It actually kind of was
Oh no, that's not what you want to hear
It was a little, you can kind of see in one of these pictures
There is a little bit of moisture on this
Johnny Cheese Sats
This is like Johnny Rockets from several sagas ago
Ew
The cheese's tears
Oh no
The city walk of the magical land where burgers cry
Burgers cry
So now
Most of those ingredients are in a regular, any Burger King
Yes, exactly
By and large
What a let down
Now I'm going into this
I have to say I love a Whopper Jr.
I don't love a Whopper, like Whopper's too big
Really?
Quarter Pounders too big
This is a thing where I never get mad at you
But I get mad when you say Quarter Pounders too big
He has little hands, John Claire
I have little hands
So I like the standard McDonald's cheeseburger
I like the Big Mac because that uses smaller patties
I like Junior Bacon
But Big Mac is tall
It's tall but it's mostly bread
It's got big mouth, small hands
Yeah
Exactly
It's more of the diameter of the burger
I don't like a super thick patty or a super big patty
But I guess if you only want the small
I don't want that much, you know
And I don't like to be wasteful
Quarter Pounder though tastes better than a regular McDonald's cheeseburger
I don't know if I agree with that
I can prove that with science, I think
My order my whole life has been just to plain hamburgers and not Quarter Pounders
Well that's, I can't even get started on that
That's wild to me
It's done me well since I was a five-year-old boy
Don't you take away my two hamburgers from me
Plain, did you say?
Just as they come
I don't say no topping
I know another, I believe a friend of the show, Danny Jelenek, that's his order as well
With precedent and I was like, you too, really?
Surely no one will discredit this opinion on a podcast
I can prove all of you wrong with science and I don't know how I'm going to do it yet but I will
I just want to declare here, Sector Cuper, you don't probably eat a lot of McDonald's
No
But when was the last time you had it?
Twenty years ago
Okay, what would you get then?
Big Mac, I'd just like a Big Mac
Okay
Yeah, or over twenty years
Yeah, I also, see I don't go terribly often anymore because when a place makes me feel not good I stop going there
Well if it ever happened to McDonald's
That makes me a real outlaw podcast
It's never happened to McDonald's for me
Actually yeah, I don't think it's ever happened with me either
Because the food is hydrolyzed
That's fucking nuts
Hydrolyzed?
Hydrolyzed
We got water in our burdens again
Well what it means is, because I know this because having a dog with a sensitive stomach
Hydrolyzed means that they break down what is the actual atoms of the food
So much so that there's no way your system can recognize it as bad
That's pissed, it makes me sick
What the fuck?
Mike fuck off, it made me sick
That's true, that is false
Well perhaps the lettuce
Don't tell me there's no way
Perhaps
Are you saying it didn't happen to me?
Are you saying I'm a liar?
You know what probably it is, they can't make like lettuce hydrolyzed
That doesn't come on a regular burger
True
Or onions
So fuck you
Hold on, fuck yous can wait a second
The onions perhaps could be cooked
And then I guess that maybe could get you sick
Well it's probably not impossible but
No one not only Scott, Scott might be the only crazy man who's ever felt sick due to me
Why do you stop going sector keeper?
They make the food so it stays good for like 40 years
I know for a fact my mom got sick but I think she was eating one of those like chicken burritos they used to sell
Well that's an experimental item
Yes of course, they haven't put that
Or sausage burrito, breakfast burrito or something
They haven't put that new crisper and re-engineered it
Yeah they haven't re-engineered the burrito yet because it's not a normal menu item
De-anomized it and put it back together
Jane what's your McDonald's?
Like a Willy Wonka candy
Exactly, what's your McDonald's?
I only eat there the McFlurries because I'm a vegetarian
Oh right of course
Their fries have like a meat base
Yes they are like beef
So I literally can't eat anything there at the moment except for McFlurries
So what did you all get at the Whopper bar?
Okay, well so I you know what I should have done was I should have asked for every topping
But I tried to construct something, I made the mistake trying to construct something I would enjoy
So I think I got the standard, like what I like on a Whopper, I do like their lettuce, ketchup mayo, pickles onions
And then I added onion rings, pepper jack cheese, I asked for pepper bacon
You reminded me that very quickly said we don't have that
So I just got regular bacon
And it I mean it looks sad like it really didn't have a lot of flavor
It's terrible
It looks like it's a bit of a bummer Jane was able to get an impossible Whopper
Looks even worse
Looks even worse but probably tasted better
I got very simple I just did like what lettuce mustard pickles
Like just very very simple
It was like fine
I don't think I got sick but it was like disappointing
I just like they don't even have an egg
Egg is such an easy like oh like your dad's gonna get impressed with an egg like oh that's special
Do you want to eat an egg from this place?
I didn't say I did I'm just saying in my wildest dreams of my imagination
A higher quality BK Whopper bar
Yes at least I'm saying that at least makes sense obviously I want some sort of real nonsense
You know I will say a few years ago I was like early for work
And I was like oh you know what I haven't had in a while
I was trying to buy a Burger King
I was like oh I should get Burger King breakfast
I should get a croissant which
Croissant which that word is not in the Bible
No it's not or the English language honestly
And I got that and hash browns and like a cup of coffee
And yeah I felt real bad for the rest of the day
I don't know it's dehydrogylated
I wish it was
No that's McDonald's
That's McDonald's that I know that about
I wish it was dehydrated
Oh another thing I did like though that isn't about the food
When you walked in they had like a row of the Burger King crowns like all ready to go
So you know I picked that shit up right away and put that on the table
Yes we got crowns we at least got crowns
Yes yeah you the crowns that's fun
It was really fun
We ate with the crowns on
Oh yeah we got them for you guys too
Uh huh I think I was wearing one
Be careful though heavy is the paper crown
It's a lot of responsibility
Now Scott you went over Jane reminded me you went over to Panda Express
Yeah I added to I did not make my main meal Panda Express
In a place that made me not feel so good so I don't really go there anymore
Fucking loser
I know
The outlaw of the show
But I just contributed a little
I'm like well maybe if we do a little something there
A little like just to add to the potluck
So I got a dessert
Oh yeah
It's like an apple pie
What a spring roll correct
There were generally positive reviews for that correct
We finished them
We polished those apple pie things wrong
We were like y'all done with these little treats
And I was
Yes and we were happy to get the Whopper Bar taste out of our mouths
But they were surprisingly good
I was like these are gonna taste like shit and they were good
I remember biting into the stalest fortune cookie I've ever
That is a Panda Express
That is what you get from Panda Express
I have never had a fresh fortune cookie from Panda Express
What was your fortune?
You will find new ways to say thank you this week
Like thank you God I didn't get food poisoning
Thank you thank you Mike and Jason for coming up with a structure for this series where we didn't all have to do everything
Some stomachs could be predicted
Can I throw in a little
I found out a little bit of history to the BK Whopper Bar concept
And I am happy to say we have a guy
There is a guy
The newest guy's name is Russ Klein
Russ Klein was the Burger King's president of global marketing strategy and innovation
And he is credited with shepherding the premise of the BK Whopper Bar
The concept is like pimp my ride
No!
Not that!
To take up your whopper, make it your own, put you in charge
So much so that the company initially considered labeling the concept pimp your whopper
Oh my gosh
Then he said my guess is we are not going to use that language on our menu board
Also because probably like Moe's I think they would have had a lawsuit on it
Customizing, equaling, pimping
But this guy is so proud of this crate that we are basically doing the pimp my ride of restaurants
There is a big wall of text right as you walk up to Wood or two
And this is, you know, it says Whopper Bar, world's first, Orlando 2009
Wow, big day for Russ Klein
And then a beautiful little poem
It started as a spark, it spread into an inferno
100% flame broiled beef topped with unique ingredients
America's favorite burger with more than a million ways to have it your way
That is an incorrect statement
You read the list
You would have to, I mean really you would have to get micro to get a million combos out of it
There's probably like 12 things
16 combos
And there's some like pre-made, there's like the Angry Whopper or the Bacon Whopper
And it's just usually whether there's bacon or jalapenos on it
A million
That's kind of it
Do you want it with bacon?
Do you want it with jalapenos?
Do you want it wet and weeping?
A million ways
Anyway, this guy seems, I think this guy was trying to be like, you know, the rock star of fast food
Even in talking about why they called it that, he's really proud of himself
Even just the syntax, the idea of a concept called the Whopper Bar
It's very contemporary, like sushi bars, juice bars, or pizzer bars
You're right, that is, yes, contemporary 12 years before you said that
Russ, Russ, breathe, sit down
What's his name, Russ Klein?
Russ Klein, yeah
It's also more of like a curved counter, more than a bar
It's not much of a bar
They didn't make any changes to that counter to make it seem more like a bar at all
That just looks like what counter was there before
And then behind it, it says, by the menu board, your Whopper, your way
But that's a normal Burger King
Have it your way, right?
Yeah, that's always, yes
And really, can't you at any restaurant basically
You can customize, yeah, you can just order it with whatever
It's called ordering, yeah
So Russ Klein invented ordering
I have a question
When did Pimp, this is after my time so I may be wrong
When did Pimp My Ride go off the air?
Good question
That bar opened in 2009?
Can I guess?
I want to guess it was off 2011
That's a good guess
Oh wait, apparently, new episodes only produced from 2004 to 2007
Oh shit
So this was past the airing of the initial
Scott, I'm seeing 2009, 2004 to 2009
Where are you seeing it?
Singing on IMDB
I feel like there's been revivals
But either way, we are
The Christmas specials don't count
I mean, we're close to the end of the ride
We were at the end, right?
Yeah
Okay, so Russ, that wasn't maybe the most
He was five years late on that
Yeah
Well, that might have been, you know, that was one of the first things that didn't go right for Russ Klein
During his run, he did it
He's responsible for the
Do you remember the campaign Burger King Virgins?
Where they would get somebody from like, you know, some far off end of the earth and have them try a Whopper for the first time
This was criticized by a lot of groups who were like
There's like food shortages in places.
What do you
And then other ads, I don't know what and why, but other ad campaigns were deemed racist
Oh Jesus
Slowly there was a franchisee rebellion
Especially after a one dollar menu that he instituted that the franchisees couldn't make money on
So they also accused him of moving
Sixty five million dollars from race restaurant maintenance to ads
So eventually the franchisees rebelled
They said we want Russ Klein out and then he's like, actually, no, I was gonna go though
I was gonna do it anyway
And he's but this guy had like a close relationship with like ad age
So he'd just go talk to ad age and they'd print whatever crap
So he did like a like a I'm leaving statement kind of kind of reminiscent of like, you know, when Charlie Sheen was like blowing up to
Two and a half men and all that tiger blood crap
That's kind of what so he'd like Russ Klein's leaving.
What's up?
We reached out to him for a statement
Here's what he said
Simply sharpening the sword and the bigger the dragon waiting for me when I return the better
That's all you need to know
Print it positively
Okay
Wait, I'm positively our kit like initials that Russ Klein.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah
Positively comma.
Yeah, positively.
Okay.
Yeah, like that's the sign off.
Okay, you know me.
I don't need to say Russ Klein
It's me.
Okay, you're working ads, you know me.
Okay
The bigger the dragon weight so he describes like, you know
I'm just pursuing my next challenge sharpening the sword the bigger the dragon waiting for me
The dragon ended up being that he several years later became the CMO of our beats
Dream big
Immediately one of my favorite guys we got the Google image him and you will find pictures of him kissing Paris Hilton.
Whoa
See that we got the meat guy like we got the meats, right?
Is that our PC?
I don't know.
I actually don't know does that stand for chief meat officer?
I
Mean Jason insisted that it did this is the CMO of podcast arrived marketing.
I say me print it sharpen in the sword
He got the meat
Insane
I didn't think a guy was waiting here behind the
I looked up Russ Klein and I don't know that this is him
But there's a website called lead with Russ with just like inspirational quotes on it
I
Said this guy I don't know.
That's a different guy.
All right.
Well, I don't want to slander this guy this Russ Klein
What's that oh, yes
The slander really will come here.
Yeah, and I think I think maybe it is time to get into this because here we are
We have arrived at the tattoo parlor
Heart and Huntington tattoo.
Yes.
Now I didn't know who was behind this.
I've determined that it is
Carrie Hart
Pink's husband ex-husband ex-husband.
Oh, thank you for staying up on that.
Great the ex.
Mr.
Pink
there are establishments of this tattoo brand in
Vegas Nashville and Orlando the Vegas one the
subject of a reality show called inked
Orlando I think it's you know, well, we're the first really to do a little reality show there.
That's yeah
You know actually when we first told a friend of the show recent guest in the saga Eva Anderson
That we're doing this she maybe this is just me
She texted like a link to the tattoo place
right said if you guys thought about what you're doing here this could get weird and
I did think yeah, where is this gonna go?
Right the three of us
I don't think there was ever a point in time where any of us had any desire to get a tattoo for this stupid show
I I can I I say considered but never like I'm do like it was just like I guess I could do it
But like yeah, it wasn't like I wanted to do it if you had to what would you get?
I would have probably gotten like the smallest thing and I'm trying to think of like
the for comedy sake a benign mole for
I
Know what I've noticed I was like, yeah, should I get like a little like a little ninja turtle?
That's kind of yeah
Part of the figure that I've been poked and prodded a lot in the last year or so
So I was like I do not want more needles by baby.
Yeah, so I was like I
Do not want to go to get like the smallest X-Men logo
Your arm, I don't know where I was just like that's the only thing I've liked for the biggest time big X on his
My biggest hurdle was Aaron and this has come up in the past
There was a day there was like a funnier die day
Everybody went to the beach and there was a brief discussion of because we're all wasted like maybe let's get tattoos
And she was when I just told her I thought about it.
She's like, why did you think about it?
I do not did she does not want to look at some dumb tattoo on my body
Do you feel that way about Jason or would you be willing to?
Oh, I'd be down his choice.
I want him inked up
Not at the moment because he's experiencing a lot and I'm okay not something he needs to add to his list
I agree with that
But if he could like sort of magically all of a sudden have a bunch of ink would you prefer you think he should get?
Some sleeve tattoos leave tab.
That's pretty cool.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, I don't think you'll ever get one
Like the undertaker it's never like the undertaker
I'm not like I prefer them or anything, but like I wouldn't be pissed.
I'd be like, all right shit.
Cool
I don't blame here
I have no I don't want one either and I am glad that the group of us at funny or died didn't all get the tattoo that
We thought about getting which was
BTTF the letters of course for back to the future.
Whoa
I regret that that's cuter than a ninja turtle future that would have been much of us thought that Wow
Damn, I really wish you guys had done
Before the party bus got on the road party boss
But I do I remember because a specific memory is friend of the show bug main buzz buzz
Commandeering the speaker to put on surf city and then surfing down
And by that point we're all like, all right, let's not come back that's the vibe but no no none of this
I would've been so stupid
I I think everybody who was in the first Avengers like the main cast of the first Avengers all have matching tattoos
I believe of the Avengers a I'm not maybe I actually don't know what it is
But I believe they all have like they all have they're on a text chain
I know and they have like tattoos I believe
Did the Lord of the Ring actors maybe that might be rings
His rings, yeah, okay, like I've seen it like it's rings which he was using actors plural
So I think in his mind he was thinking look at the ring.
Let's ever say anything incorrect on this show
Yeah, I can't imagine Lord of that Lord of the Ring the ring, you know
Yeah, there is one wait there is one thing to rule them all but it's called Lord of the Rings
What is that about?
I'm not a big Lord of the Rings guy.
So there's no other rings
It's kind of it's like a sector stones thing
Now I understand yeah franchise people know a little bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, um, I took it Tolkien took it from me
So we have now eliminated the three of us as
Getters of tattoos.
Hmm.
Perhaps you were wondering why is Jane on this particular episode?
Well
Voluntarily you threw it out there.
I'm gonna fucking tattoo
Well, may I give a little context here when I was younger like in my mid-20s so like two years ago
Funny kind of moved your head a little when you said it
I also whenever he laughs at something I said you get really excited cuz I love when I make it
He's so funny when I make him laugh I feel like you looked a little mad at that one.
Yeah
So anyway, um, I kind of was going through a phase of rebellion in a way
I had just done a few like pageants like and was just like having an
Try not to say too many things
But I kind of having an eating disorder and trying to figure out my life and I was like fuck this
I'm getting a fucking tattoo
But I was like I'll get it on the bottom of my foot cuz those go away fast
So I went to a legitimate
Like tattoo shop with a friend of mine and I got the eye of Horace
Which is like the Egyptian eye that you see it's like a good luck been protection thing and I was like I'm gonna get it
on my bottom of my big toe
I'm gonna fucking bottom of my big toe and the guy at the shop was like
Okay, this is gonna go away like two weeks and I was like, yes it is like I was so down
Okay, like this is gonna be weird and difficult and I was like hell yeah, like I was just like on one
So I was like fuck it.
I'll get a fucking tattoo on the bottom of my foot
Like it did in fact go away pretty quick
Oh, yeah
Because the skin on your feet is a lot thicker because you walk on it and you build
Skin layers so for for it to you know, stay there it won't um
But uh, yeah, so you saved us here
The three of us not all like not looking at each other
This is a game of chicken where we're all staring at the ground and right swoop in I will do this
I will handle.
Yeah, I got excited to the point where I started to really annoy.
I became a
Will say I became a brat about this like I became a little my little brat mode
I was like, but I wanna he was like do you really think you should because I sweet in a sweet way
Not because he thinks I shouldn't get a tattoo
Well, no cuz and the tattoo artists eventually
Suggested this do I was concerned that like Orlando weather is kind of it might be uncomfortable
It's gonna be uncomfortable walking around theme parks gonna be uncomfortable walking through airports
And then for your job you drive a lot you lug, you know giant garment bags of clothes and I'm like
It was really sweet.
He's it was really sweet, but I was being a little shit.
Sometimes I'm a little brat
I'm like, you know, but I want to get one he's like
You were also like what Jason wasn't taking into account were the sector keepers feelings
Yeah, right the only one selfless enough to be thinking about what he needs which is for us to get a tattoo
So Jason was wrong is what I'm saying as per you
He was wrong but also he was fucking right, um, so that the the moment comes it all lines up to happen on the the
Often mentioned throughout this series hell day the day where all the rides broke
Well, it was been through it and we'll and we'll go through it again, but it is important context that this was
During a day that was already maddening in its own way for ways that you'll find out actually
Yeah later you go out you go off to do this
We kind of like splinter up a little bit like you start dealing with this process.
I like Jason with Mo's I try to find something
Decent and bland and it's it's not important but it's but it's something that did not screw up my stomach
Thank God because I needed it Mike had another plan Mike was like, well, this is a place
We're not maybe gonna have time to have a sit-down meal at this place.
So I better do this to go
Would you like to say what you did?
Well, yeah, I would I'm just trying to find the exact name of it because I wasn't sure
Oh, do you want me to while you're kind of figuring?
Yes
Whatever you're gonna do do it
Inch forward in this I guess in my head I was like I'll just go up there
They'll do it quick and I'll be done like I don't know why I thought that would be the case and we go in
There's like a little bit of a line and of course, I'm like, oh, I was a brat
Like I'm just gonna click I was a brat that night.
I will own up to it.
I was like, oh the line is long
so
We looked around the store a little bit and whatnot
This is kind of already where the the follies come in with Michael because
The texts aren't coming while we're like waiting in the store from Michael who's eating
Maybe ten feet away from where we were in the door inside this place and like he's huddled outside
I was like, why is he texting you?
Let's use went to do to go food from tooth some chocolate to some
Which you have just said the meal the meal proper is maybe not so maybe
You can't describe that as food
It's a place where you're probably you're probably your best bet is to go and get some dessert to get some ice cream to get some
Well, you know
chocolates to go and the
Atmosphere is a lot of what you're after but Mike says let's do this to go
The ramp from the steampunk
Environment and aesthetic so what I did is I wanted to make sure that we were covering all our bases cuz you know
Restaurant is not just eating there.
It's taking it home.
Sometimes sometimes you don't have the option eat
So I wanted to see what it would try things would travel.
So I ordered
flounder
Almondine to go Almedin Almedin.
Thank you, Jason.
I don't I did not know what that word was
And it came in, you know, whatever like sort of a to-go container and it came with green beans and it came with some potatoes
And I want to show I'll show the sector keeper first picture of it
He's a little horrified by it you you guys just you know, just the to-go flounder from a chocolate emporium
It's like the top-down view of a trash can
This is the top I think there's like some sort of shaved like isn't nuts on the top like Jason I don't know
That's what it means, yeah, I
Never put it together until right now.
I also knew it wasn't pronounced that way then but I didn't want to tell you
No, thank you.
Cuz I see how many I miss I miss pronounced it that way
Last time as well.
I had I have only ever seen trout almondine it like a French
You know cafe.
I'm not a man of culture as you heard.
I'm more of a quarterpano with cheese guy
Okay, I don't have classy dishes like this toothsome meal
So I ordered it to go but now you've lived it up now
You know the great flounder that the folks over at toothsome cook up and yeah
I just want the context of it while it a tattoo attempt is happening.
You have a to-go content
You're outside with a styrofoam container
And you you also had an order of like potato croquettes with that yeah
Yeah, that's what it was said potatoes because that I ended up eating a lot of that.
Well, yes
Tell us why Michael.
Well, there's a couple reasons number one
It was by far the worst meal I had had
on either coast
And you'll notice I've not been them I've probably been the most positive in general
This was by far the worst meal it didn't it's not just that like oh it was only ten or so fifteen minutes
From taking it and going and sitting down
So it wasn't like it was two hours old or whatever and just the way it was cooked
It's like burned part of it was like kind of burned
Like half of it felt like it was burned and the other half was not
I'm just almond slipper and almonds are just thrown all over and that's just like
Kind of an unpleasant texture to add to it.
Did your fork break my memory?
Yes.
I believe it did break
That was sort of that one of the more minor things
So I'm like strong I am struggling through this meal no joke like this is truly like
Everything else that was just like bad to okay.
Like I'm all right.
That's fine
But like this sucks this sucks really really bad and then if this is where you're go ahead with this
There's a lot of chaos going on
Currently, okay, let's hear some chaos then we'll come back to that.
Okay now to chaos
Okay, so you were gonna get very simple tattoo.
I was gonna get a very simple tattoo.
Just a couple letters.
I was gonna get
WS city walk saga
Okay, no, I know I knew this already and I knew it because that plan had been put in motion and I was
Me with like rewrite brain
I'm getting text updates about everything and they're doing CWS and I was like, is that weird?
Is that like too close to CVS is that straight?
I'm gonna look like she has a tattoo of CVS.
So then it changed so I'm sorry
Why am I?
My choice if I want CVS on the bottom my goddamn foot.
I will get it.
Thank you very much
You have no control.
I also it also occurred to me that if you
Jason's girlfriend had a tattoo that kind of looked like CVS his favorite place to save four dollars weekly
Suddenly
Don't get me start the coupons a bit terrible geez, I'll thank God she didn't get I have also
Become a CVS girly.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Oh cuz we well I don't say anything about where we live
But there's one not far from us.
Yeah, and so we go there fairly often don't out yourself.
It's near a CVS
Allow yourself
So I would be more than happy to have you know, they have like order pickup now and I do that shit all the time
You mean like they'll gather your items
Yeah, like a target like a target.
Yeah.
Yeah, you just go in there behind the counter and go
Hey, it's my number of my order in my name and I go here go.
I'm telling you guys
So you would happily a CVS tattoo would be good anyway, I'm there going like I don't and you're like, no, it's chip is sailed
Whatever.
It's that so like because you're now like you're in the throes now of trying to get this thing to happen
So there's like a line and we finally get up to the front and I was like, hey
I just want to get like really simple
Tiny little letters on the bottom of my foot and you would have thought I asked tattoo my whole body right now
Like they were like, oh
That's a lot of work
Well, I don't know cuz I don't know if anyone here will do the bottom of a foot cuz
It's kind of sensitive and I was like, yeah
I've got I literally have gotten one before and like my pain threshold for this shit is not a concern for me right now
They're like, well, let me let me ask and she goes well, I can do it
But I have to leave right now cuz my dog is sick and I was like
Okay, first of all, I'm like I take care of your dog.
Like I would also rather you take care of your dog
but she's like so I
Know but this guy might be able to do it but probably not to like 11 and I was like
What and so then the guy comes over and this is where I'm starting to kind of get a little faith that this could
Happen but at this point Jason's like, please just give up on this.
I'm tired.
This is such a bad idea
And this is where I become such a little brat.
No, I want this tattoo.
So then the guy is like
Look man, because I was like it can be shitty
It's actually funny if it's like I put a lot of pride in my work and I just can't I
Can't give you a shit like I don't want that to reflect on me and I was like is this guy for a mother
I'm like, do you know where you are right now?
Like and what the vibe is and so he's like so, um
Yeah, you can maybe come back, but I don't know I have to think about doing a bottom of foot and I was like
What the fuck and so we keep like kind of I keep kind of going like well
Maybe we can try this and well, maybe we can try that and it's just like not happening
And then he's getting bombarded with text from Mike who is like right outside and I'm like
Why is he texting you so much?
He's right
I was eating I was eating too.
He was eating.
I didn't want to bring some flounder into the tattoo part
Yeah, but also I did go in I did go in a second
Really?
I did come in and my memory of what happened was I went in because I saw some commotion happening
I saw some sort of maybe gesturing or something going on
So I'm like, oh what's going on so I go in there and I think what happened is Jane turned to me go
They're not gonna do it
They told me they're not gonna do it
There might have been cursing I can't remember but I remember just you you telling me from across the way what was happening
I don't know.
Okay, and I ran back to my flounder
I'm getting texts about all this and the text that I got you gave me this update
You walked in and the gene yelled they said it cost four hundred dollars
So we said fuck that yes, and I think you yelled that across in the store
I think you yelled that because I wanted them to know I was being an asshole
Fucking do it the estimate was between three hundred and four hundred dollars for three letters for three letters
They're like it's on the bottom of the foot
It's gonna be labor intensive three four hundred dollars and I was like, but then there was a moment that passed
So Jason was kind of like you're so nice.
I love you and you're like, you know what?
Maybe I'll just pay for it.
Like you really want to do it.
Well here.
Here's my memory of it real quick
I just remember going Jason was like, you know what?
Let's do it.
He kind of just said he said you know what?
I'm paying for it
You are the very positive.
He put it be like he he really like tried to get
No, he's tried to I'm saying he was pure.
He was intentions was pure pure.
Yeah.
Yeah, you wanted me to be happy
No, I've been dealing with a lot of
She was helping me out so much.
I was like look, it's the least I can do
Yeah, and I have a big piece of fish in my mouth.
I remember
There was a break so you were in there for a while and there was a break you came back out because now the money
Is like it's like all this is for a stupid bid and I was like don't you don't have to do with the sector
Keeper will forgive us.
I think so.
So I'm eating and then that's when Jason said oh, yeah, like don't like let's do it
Let's go for it.
It's expensive, but whatever
Like I can't squeeze it in so now it looks like cuz I'm we're going back for the nap time
Okay now it looks like it's gonna happen
I think everything is going to go down and then correct me if I'm wrong from the text chain
But I'm eating alone again all of a sudden I bite the side of my mouth so hard
Brutally hard were almost like you feel your teeth meat in the skin like just like just so not just like I nicked it
I hope I didn't cut myself but like a big bite out of the side of my mouth where you immediately know
I drew blood there's no way I didn't draw blood
Sure enough.
I take one of the black cocktail napkins from to some and I put it in my mouth to take a look
It's just it's it's red.
We got blood immediately.
Oh my god.
I am bleeding
I am bleeding from the mouth.
I have a photo of it
That's like a lot of what?
Yeah, and it's and this was immediate it's not one of those where you're like, oh, I think oh no
I'm good, and then it kind of bleeds.
No, no like immediately I go that's bad news
So I am eating this terrible fish.
There's tattoo chaos
Exactly I'm eating Heathcliff skeleton fish and now
Texted about blood at some point.
I sure did.
It's about blood in your mouth
I just bit the side of my mouth has now cut to me.
I'm getting texts about all this Jane's yelling about
$400 they're yelling fuck in the store people are coming out from the back.
Every update is making me feel more and more crazy
I'm in such bad health at this point that I walk up to a bar to have a little bite and the bartender says
Do you need some water not in like a you're at the restaurant?
Let me give you some water
He said it like concerned.
Do you need help?
Yes.
Yes, that was exactly the line then I'm getting all these updates
I'm like, wow, this is getting nuts.
Then I get the text.
I bit the side of my mouth and drew blood.
I
Started cackling like the Joker.
I lost it
There's a lot I'll post pictures and video of me just like I just went red
I'm weeping at this point from the madness the madness had fully taken me over two minutes prior
I had texted Evan Susser and Van Roepen show and said we're all in very poor health
Then you bit your mouth you drew blood I hurt my
Self that day on almond dine
That almond Dean and then then after this so now I have lost I have fully lost it.
I am jokerfied
I'm like I'm in a haze as I get up from this place
The haze is broken when the same guy who asked if I was okay sprints back up to me and says I left my credit card
We are all it is madness at this point that's where I'm at you're bleeding a lot more than I ever knew even from the
Tech a lot.
You have basically landed at there is not going to be a tattoo to get things a little wrapped up
We did end up purchasing something from the store.
Yes, the tattoo did not end up working out
Yes, they said no eventually they eventually after saying yes $400
Then you went back in well, they said come back at like 11 and then we said no
Right right, but they still were giving you a run around.
Oh, yeah, and you went back in and I remember after I'm bleeding
Seeing more gesturing going on I remember seeing more commotion happening, but at that point I said, I don't know
I can't go in there.
I'm bleeding because I said so what I said was like
You're just incredulous I think no further questions
Such a keeper a point there was a point when we talked about you headed down with us
And I think you're probably at this point very jealous.
You didn't get to go
At some point I went back out and joined Mike and he's like you want some potato
And then said do any that one I might have gotten blood
This guy does not care.
He finished most of my meal
Croquettes because I was just like so
Stressed and I walked up when I joined the scene finally you'd also gotten a big crazy milkshake
Oh, I didn't I didn't forget gum and at it.
You're like with his straw.
I think am I wrong.
You're just using Mike
I think I finished his milkshake.
No, you didn't use the straw because he said I used the straw
And didn't you maybe I was just drinking there
I believe I have videotape of you using the straw so we did go back into the Jason drank my blood
Drank we will all live forever like the sector key.
Yeah, Jason and I are blood brothers, but he we didn't put blood together
He drank my blood.
Yeah, I drink your blood milkshake.
I drink
That's a good reference I
Said like hey, let's not go home empty-handed.
Let's get some t-shirts.
So we did
Oh
Yeah, they did
So we each got t-shirts Wow
And then the last little button of the night was we took them out to the cash register and they said those magical words
That'll be 72 42
Like a thin crop women's t-shirt this should not be that much
I don't know
The back is cooler it's got the logo on the back
Yours looks like it's from a tattoo shop.
Yeah.
Yeah looks like it's like from a hill like
He looks like he works at a Hawaiian barbecue restaurant like Bahama
I prefer the print on the front all of them had it on the back
So this one I settled for cuz I like the colors
inked and oiled since
2000 wait Jason's wearing a shirt that says he's inked and oiled Jason inked and oiled
Jason paid $30 or more for a shirt
Similar to a few city walk locations the bill comes to and it's like I'm sorry
How much did you say?
Like fucking fuck it.
I want to go to bed.
Here is my visa
Became bed I know we went to Mose that's when we went to Mose after
Yeah, that's when I got my
Beans and meat like just standard you know how late it was
I need to put something in my system besides bloody croquettes
Jane by stepping in front of this bullet taking more of a bullet than we realize.
Yeah, thank you
You really give us a story and something to talk about here
So let me say Jane Claire you survived podcast the ride with a city walker land a saga multiverse of madness
There's a plug portal anything you'd like to plug
Well, I work in styling and I'm always looking for new clients so
You can honestly DM me on Instagram Jane Claire styling jayne
And yeah, so I'm kind of that's where I'm at right now and
Shoot me a message if you have an event or or if you're an expert at tattooing the bottom of a foot
Oh my god, if you will tattoo you guys there was like half of me that was like do I go get one here?
Just as a fucking bit and go
But then I was like this week was kind of crazy so I got it but I I did have the thought
Oh wait, look and I'm seeing I'm seeing the sector stone here it comes it's whoa
Wow, it's it's a little it must be kind of for Jane.
It's a little it's a little tiara that says bathroom girly leader
It's a little paper tiara for the BK walker
That's right, then if you look closely engraved in it
RK
A
inventor of the concept so it's a pretty funny story, right like I know we didn't end up getting a tattoo but like it's
That's fine though.
Like ultimately it's
T-shirts boys boys Jane.
It's not fine
All we had to do is talk about the place it doesn't matter if we didn't get the ink does it no the the ink was
Crucial you had to get it
$72 worth of clothing
From H&H, but you are headed to a new land a good place
boys
Welcome to the land of fallen brothers and never built
Gosh, oh god, I don't know what I don't like the sound of that something's happening to him.
He's getting jokerfied
Are you gonna be there you'll be there, right?
That's a little mysterious I don't like the sound of that wait a minute and I can see I see the path forming that's right
Where is it gonna take us?
It looks like it's heading behind a wall behind a paywall
Terrible for everybody
Are gonna have to go through the point hole to get over the paywall in order to hear tomorrow's episode
Which will be about the scary land of fallen brothers and never built some parts of the multiverse only exist if you pay a couple
Dollars, that's right.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's starting to seal up.
We're losing Jane.
No Jane.
Sorry.
We'll see you in a couple
Don't forget about the chore wheel
See you at home
Good luck
So be sure to head to patreon.
com slash podcast the ride for the full multiverse experience
Which starts tomorrow at podcast the ride the second gate and maybe while you're there stick around and join club 3 to get every sector
ad free an exclusive bonus sector guys
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner
Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey for more original podcasts
Please visit forever dog podcasts calm and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify
Or wherever you get your podcast keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook