Forever!
Dog!
When your town has made you frown
When your square has made you swear
When life gives you one more punch
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge
You need a place, a place to stroll
With alcohol, a place that features part of the Berlin Wall
Where seam-punk robots sell chocolate snacks
A place where you can tattoo your lower back
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando
Tonight, tonight
Madness, a daily, extremely necessary series
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness
Day 5 and the madness certainly is setting in
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson, hi
Hello, I'm here and I'm mad as well.
Going mad, not mad, I'm not angry, I'm going mad
Jason Sheridan, how you doing?
I'm here, I had to comb through my souvenirs for this one
Because I had more artifacts to have here
Oh yes, oh great
That deal with today's
This is a fun thing, you're kind of the artifact keeper
We've just been to Orlando
And that's the episode you heard yesterday was our live show with the level keeper
There's all kinds of keepers in the mix
It's kind of refreshing to do one in a different way
And I think the only way to get some fresh energy at this point is to have somebody come in
Who would not be a Podcast the Ride series without
Here she is making her 48th appearance on the show
Eva Anderson
Hi guys, I'm so happy to be back in another Multiverse of Madness with you
Thank you for joining us in the Multiverse
You've survived every saga at this point with some harrowing moments
Hopefully we don't know what's around any bend, but hopefully you do this one as well
Yeah, Eva's been on 48 times, there could be 48 sectors in this Multiverse
We don't know
That's one thing to catch you up to, we have not been told how long it's going yet
I was kidnapped to the underworld last time, you freed me
Thank God, you helped us, but we needed your strength to get through every single closed store
I still think about Club Libby Lou, Club Libby Lou haunts me to this day
I'll think of the logo and I'll get a headache
That's a nice memory
That girl who lied about her father dying in Afghanistan so she could get a makeover
God, I forgot
I listened every listen recently
Well, we'll see what horrors we encounter here
And speaking of horrors, I want to ask a question, and if this becomes irrelevant we could cut it
But it seems like something fun to talk about for now
You know, not to be too inside baseball, but we are recording this a good deal of time before the episode will come out
And it's a length of time in which something very important is scheduled to happen
And so I pose this question to all of you
Do you think that by the time the listener is hearing this episode, has David Copperfield made the moon disappear?
The tides have destroyed
Tides are fucked
It's like Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy, the dolphins are gone
So long and thanks for all the fish, you know
There's two things that throw this up in the air
One is that our friend Jason Waller pointed out
Making the moon disappear disappeared from the Save the Children website
The day that a certain list was publicly
Yeah, we've alluded to this in episodes, I think before it happened
That some documents will be undisclosed, whatever you want to call it
And these being the Jeffrey Epstein documents
And I think mostly it was names that you would expect
There is some Clinton, there are some bad billionaires who you've never heard of
And there was a lot of Copperfield
Not like specifically, but him just having weird conversations with women at dinner
Yeah, let's be clear, there's no implication of acts or whatever
We don't, we can let our imaginations run wild, allegedly, allegedly
But, I mean, is it great that he was there?
No, not really
It seems like he supposedly should have been made very strange small talk
Yeah, Asquest did magic tricks for people hanging out on Epstein Island
Yes
So now Save the Children, not Q Save the Children
But Real Save the Children doesn't maybe want to sponsor this event
And isn't the movie about God's Children not for sale?
Oh yeah
Sound of Freedom?
Is Sound of Freedom Save the Children?
Is Third Save the Children?
Oh, I thought that was the Q Save, is that a separate part of Q Save the Children?
It's just something they want to do, I don't know how much their official organizations
Sound of Freedom, by the way, hit Amazon Prime and I feel like I've heard no one talk about it
I know, I keep wanting to watch it
They all saw it already
I guess, they all got the free tickets
Seats filled, real people in those chairs
So, on the one hand, that got taken off the website, on the other hand, one of your Redditors
Mentioned that they went to the show and that the show's opening is the Moon Will Disappear in February
Whoa, there's like a hype up video of, and I assume he then addresses all the allegations
Just because everybody in the audience is thinking about it
I think they just played that hip hop song Black Magic where they sing gave a cover feel a lot still
That's exciting
So the answer is, you know, maybe
But the other thing I want to say is that, even though we're months in the future
The other thing that happened this week is that other guy from the Vegas Groove Blender, James Dolan
Got in a ton of trouble
So the Wheel of Guys is really having a tough
It was already a rough group
It's in my garage and it's facing out so I pull my car up and see them every day
And now I just have to mention, I gotta start putting red Xs over them
They're even more canceled than they were before
All I'm saying is like Vince from Yow Wolf, Haunted Museum Man
You're the only ones kind of
You're a beacon of light
And also, you know, the various Liberace men
Those guys are great
Don't fuck around this year
We need to make it
Make it through, yeah, yeah, it's a curse time for everyone we put on the Wheel of Guys
We're sorry we brought you all into it
Not all of you, some of you deserve to be there
And you're getting what you deserve, but
Is it our, is it another curse that we're doing?
Because like, anytime we talk about an old actor that's post 80
They die within days
And then anytime we talk about a guy
Within a matter of months, they've done something horrible
Is it possible?
Or in many cases, something they did 17 years ago becomes disclosed
That's true
So maybe we're not causing it
But maybe it's a good curse and we're uncovering the evil deeds
Yeah
So it's actually, this is a good version of a curse
So either Copperfield has made the moon disappear and you're listening to this from like a bunker
What do we do?
Underwater bunker
There's no, the oceans, they
Either they've receded entirely or we all live in the ocean now
Yeah
It's, but yeah
There's no water or all water
Yeah
There's no option
And there's no such thing as like twilight, what happens if
What does night look like if there's no moon?
Is everything darker?
It's gotta be right?
Certainly a little darker, yeah
I don't know how dark it is
Because there's nights when it's cloudy
Yeah
But you're still getting a little light
I think if before the alligator, before this was all revealed
He might have made the moon disappear and then given it back
Now it might stay disappeared
He's like, this is what you get
You never should have doubted me
You bring down a major talent, one of the greats, the greats, the best in my field
And if you want it back, then why don't you go find a magician as good as me to bring it back
Can't do it, can you?
I mean this could be the time we need leadership
This might be the day that Donald Trump finally becomes presidential
He demands the moon back?
Every, if you remember a few years ago, every time an event would happen
This is when he becomes presidential
Yeah, well this one, certainly that would do it
Biden's weak, he's been weak on moon
He's been weak on the moon
He's been weak on moon, but we love moon
We're getting it back, day one it'll be there, you'll see
Look in the sky and we'll build a wall around the moon so it can never be disappeared again
David Copperfield is still on this old group chat that I have going, it's still kind of going
I won't say what it's about
I won't say it's about
Alan Dershowitz still sends funny dogs sometimes
Okay, well with that bit of business out of the way, which also there's a world where it did happen
And we had to do an emergency episode and we're, but I don't know
It's not feeling in the cards for February
Do you think it's not gonna, what are the predictions?
We should definitely say it's not happening so that when it does happen we have to do an emergency episode
Like we never thought Dick Tracy 2 would happen
Oh yeah, who really thought that of all things that we had talked about before
That unannounced it'd be back
Could Copperfield really get it together because the Super Bowl is around the eighth, ninth?
Somewhere around there
And they're building, they're already, they just destroyed everything from the F1
And now they're building sports center like broadcast facilities at the Bellagio Fountain
So construction has begun again
Wait, is the Super Bowl in Vegas?
It is in Vegas
What are they doing?
That's crazy
This is too much for one sit and it's sphere mania all at the same time
The sphere is not the perfect shape for a football though
So I wonder how that's gonna work
Does it need to be the shape of a football?
Well I'm just saying a basketball when they turn into a basketball it's perfect
Oh yeah, oh if it just had the stitching on it
It's gonna be fine but it won't be as perfect
They're gonna have to build little additions, little cone addendums to make it work
Okay well we'll know how some of this has played out
But one thing that we don't know yet is today's sector assignment for which we briefly welcome back
No longer the level keeper but rather his cousin and our primary keeper, the sector keeper
Alright there we go, Hollywood Drive-In Mini Golf, Red Coconut Club, Fuel Rod Kiosks
Amazing
Now that all said, you know what, he's the guy kinda like keeping us on topic on these
Putting up these borders, these walls
You know I say, well the cat's away, the mice shall play
I think you should be able to, there's a number of things that I think we need to address
Especially because you did several trips to City Walk
In the endless amount of time that we've been asking friends of the show to visit City Walk
That was enough where you ended up being there twice
Twice in the window that you were discussing this
So I went in the summer with my brother Dash, we went to all the parks
This was before the Groove Blender
And I was like, oh they're doing, I knew this was happening
So my brother and I consciously hit a number of locations just in case
And taking time away from parks
Yeah, writing down what we did, what we ate, what happened
And then spoke to you and all the places I had asked for had been called already by very cool people
Like people who were so exciting, that they were undeniable
Of course you were too, but yeah I felt terrible because I had said like
You know what, whatever you want, anything you want
And then you said three and I said no
Some of the trickiness is that knowing that you've done a bunch of things
And that you could work for a number of things
And there's other people I'm like, I can't believe
I can't believe some of these people have no one thing at City Walk Orlando
I feel like they have to do that
Your versatility was not, it was great but also a hindrance
But the keeper's not here so I can talk about whatever you want
Well here's what happened
So I was like, so one of the three things that I asked to do
Because I did at City Walk
Was the Back to the Future escape room
Yes, which was just talked about yesterday
Which you guys talked about last time
Yeah, yeah, yeah, this is perfect
Okay, I don't know how you guys felt about it
But it was the worst escape room I've ever done
Wow, wow
Unbelievably bad
Okay, I think that we were sort of like middling
We were a little confused by it
I think that we were a little bit blinded by it
Sometimes it was nice to see some Back to the Future lore
And some expanded Back to the Future 2 lore
But I don't know, I think we were a weird mix
We weren't raving but we weren't so critical
Oh man
So I am so, and also
You asked a question before we did it
Which was, is this your first escape room?
And the answer is yes
I can't imagine it was yours
So you've got to be more opinionated
This is my number two
I did one, I think it was in downtown or Koreatown
For Pascas Zacarino's bachelor party
And it was like
Escape room for a bachelor party
It was like a library, I think with artifacts
I know this doesn't narrow it down
Was it good?
It was pretty good, yeah
There was a lot more like gameplay minded people in there
We did Korean barbecue and then we did this escape room
I'm confused Christopher Lloyd screaming at you that Biff is back
That was my big takeaway from the whole thing
Oh this is how Back to the Future fucked up
Is that there's no bad guy who's not Biff
Yeah
Tannen
There's only Buford Tannen who is him
Or himself
Yeah that's all you got
And he's just some dweeb, he doesn't have powers or anything
He didn't even stay famous as an actor
He's just like, he's very good in the movies
But it's like that guy who's like a stand up who played guitar I think was his other thing
Yeah and he'll pop up in things and he's fine
But it also doesn't seem like he's dying to be Biff again
No he's mad
So you can't get him not because he's ungettable
Just because he doesn't need to
It's been 30 years
And you can't get him
He's not a bad guy but you'll certainly never get Crispin
Crispin despises the franchise
You ever watch any videos where he just says like
Bob Gale is a thief and a criminal and a liar
Like he'll go off
So yeah we're limited in what cast we can participate
But you can have Christopher Lloyd be like
Biff has returned, Biff is coming
And so you're just sort of in these rooms
And my brother and I were playing with a family who also had never done Escape Room before
And it was literally like every single thing malfunctioned
Like we were doing it right
And it just didn't work and it was that girl who was his assistant going like
Hey try to put your hand on the thing
Hey try to put your hand on the
And we're just like
And I kept thinking to this family
I was like you guys are doing it right
You are doing it right
And it's just not working
Were we doing, now that I'm thinking about this
Were we doing things right and it wasn't working?
Because we really felt stupid
I would love to give us that credit but I'm not so sure
I don't know
We were bad, we were bad
The Biff Museum and then the old west room with
Any old west room with cranks
I am not sure if we did right
Or there was people behind us
And they're like alright get out of here
They definitely did that
They definitely said oh I figured it out
You go ahead don't worry about it
Biff is behind you
Right behind that door
I swear
You wouldn't want to see him
This brow will terrify him
My friend Tommy Haunton who is like
A
Brilliant Escape Room designer
He made the Escape Room stash house
He also made the game that you guys came to
Of mine last year
He was the puzzle man in that
I texted him on the way into the Escape Room
And he was like I'm doing the back to the future Escape Room
And he just went oh no
And I was like what?
He's like nothing
Had he done it or he just heard?
He just knew about it
He just heard about it
From everybody being like oh no
This is not possible
So anyway that was my opinion of that
Did you have a quick plus up or anything?
Burn it down
Burn it to the ground
Also but like getting Christopher Lloyd on board
That is funny
I was also like go back and think of
Why did you have to get so locked in
It's an early
What's wrong with Star Wars
Is like Biff being the bad guy in all three movies
Right?
That you can never have new ideas or imagination
Right
Even when you go all the way back in time
The bad guy is Biff's
Relative
There's only one bully of your family
Throughout time
What kind of karmic lesson is this for people?
You have one villain of your life
And you've always been in battle with them
And you are good and they are bad
And there's no way for anyone in that family to ever not be
The person destroying you and your father and your parents
And best case scenario is
You flip things
And you have a family where they're still around
Just they work for you
They clean your car
But your villain has to still be in your life
Everyday
It does make me feel weird about
Whatever like personal grievance
I want to know about like
Zemeckis's dad
Since the whole deal now
Like thinking about it being like
Yeah I know I'm not as cool as
You Bob
But you know if
Frank at the factory hadn't
Kept me from being myself
Maybe I would be
Like I don't know like is that what every
His entire life was
He's like
Robert Zemeckis is Marty
Slinging a camera on his back
I'm not going to be like my dork old man
But he's also like
But it's true what my dad says it's about
Actually his big problem is Frank
And I'm going to make three movies about it
Who hurt you Zemeckis's dad
So that was my big takeaway
Was the realization that Biff
Is the only bad guy
Whereas you know
Indiana Jones gets to fight
He gets to have new friends like Archimedes
And he also gets to fight
New sorts of Nazis
Like Hannibal the Cannibal
You're right with history
We could have
What's scarier
Some guy who's felled by
Getting a pun wrong
And a little poop in his face
Or like
There's 70 Nazi soldiers
Behind that door
Or even like if he'd gone back into the old west
And it's been like you have to fight Billy the kid
Or I don't know who the coward Robert Ford
I don't know
There's some bad guys
Genghis Biff isn't what you're looking for
You're looking for Genghis Khan
Wait I know I like that
That he is related
Genghis Khan didn't have most children
Genetically
Genghis Biff
That's best of both worlds
Now I want them to make number 4 with Genghis Biff
And I would like an Avengers
Like a Marvel style reveal
Where the theater loses their mind
Because it's like that's the coward Robert Ford
It's Casey Affleck right
There's me the coward Robert Ford
Okay well that's a good rebuttal to get
I think that
The other three things I do not think you have explored yet
So I won't say what they were
The other two
But is there, it seems like
Maybe like Doc Brown that you might have a grave warning
About something that is coming up
I have a warning about one restaurant
That you have not been to
Okay so really quick
Alright can I, I'll explain what happened
So I went
I went to Universal Studios once
In the summer
Then I went home, I was like I covered so much of it
I surely am done
And then in October
I went back
Because I had to go to Crime Con
Which is the true crime convention in Orlando
It was in Orlando that year
It's in a giant Marriott near Disneyland
Disney World
And I was going for
Because I had to, I was researching something
So I flew up by myself
I was staying in another hotel
Like the
Bleed off hotel from the convention
And the first day I got there I was like
There's enough time for me to take
An Uber to
City Walk
To try, to do three more things
You named three of the most fun things
Rejected
X, try again
It's like the night
It's the opening night, it's the night before the convention actually starts
So I have enough time to take a car there
Get out, do some
City Walk, and then get back in time
Because I had to get back for the opening night party
Of the true crime convention
Crime Con where because there was
A band playing at the opening night party called
The Soul Purpose Band
This is a description of the Soul Purpose Band
It really specifically was like wanted to see this
Because it was
They're, okay so
The Soul Purpose Band
They're from Charleston, South Carolina
Performs an eclectic blend of funk and
Soul, R&B, country rock,
Pop and more
Creighton Waters, the South Carolina prosecutor
Who helped convict Alex Murdock is the
Guitarist of the Soul Purpose Band
And this is their like
Crazy logo
So yeah
It's this lime green logo and they look very
So I was like
So I have to get to City Walk but I have to get back
To see the Soul Purpose Band
Wait, Alex Murdock also is the
He's coming back to me as I see him
Yeah, he killed his whole family
He like ran a small town
He was, he
He killed so many people and he's also like
This weird ginger rich guy
It's a great story if you guys haven't looked it up
Eventual Jesse
Plemmons character
Oh, he'll be fantastic
He'll either be prosthetics now or he can do it in 30 years
Oh, okay, so the prosecutor
On that case is on stage
Doing a cover of like
Never have to knock on wood
Oh, it was literally
It was a lot of, I did make it back
It was a lot of Eagles covers
They played on Just What I Needed by the Cars
A lot of Roots Rock
All white guys, guys look them up
They have a Facebook page, they're fun
Wait, did I ask you if they did Mustang Sally?
That's a go to
For those
I feel like, yeah, that is
Definitely a go to
It was hardcore
To go back to one of our other ones, Lieutenant Dan
Band vibes
Like a party band
And everyone was like
Wearing these neon glasses and it was like a neon
It was called Neon Rave, it was in a
Ballroom of the Marriott
And we could play like glowing
Jenga, it was great
But anyway, I had like a small window of time
So I got there, I executed a few things
And I accidentally ate somewhere
That made me
So sick that I
Spent all of Crime Con like
Basically having to source Pepto Bismol
In the giant Marriott
Cursing out our names
I think, from all you were
Cursing a specific restaurant
Which I'm not going to name, but when you guys
Eventually eat there, you can say which one
We'll reveal when we get there
This ties into, because we have
Been teasing, I forget if we said it in the live show
Yesterday, but if we haven't
I'll say it now, there was a restaurant
Where things really blew up for us
There was vomit
Involved, do ours
Line up, will be the question
Or are there two such restaurants
In City Walk, and if so
Oh no, I know it seems impossible
How could that be possible
Maybe there are two, yeah
Oh my god, we did
This to you, I almost had it
No, I did this to me
No one made me go to Crime Con
Nobody made me take an Uber to City Walk
And nobody
Made me leave
My very nice phone charging brick
At the airport bar
At LAX, which is why
I got into all this trouble, which I'll explain
To you guys, as part of
My sector
Also feel free to grab whatever
We don't have to go in the order that it was
If it makes sense, or I don't know if that's a closer
You tell me
The order that it's in makes sense
Okay, great, we'll stick with that
Any other details from
Crime Con worth sharing
What an insane thing that you did
Crime Con is incredible
It's like
It was the Marriott 1
Which is like a giant place
Right by Disney World, like I said
It's a convention hotel
So you're waiting for like two hours
For like Starbucks
Crime Con specifically
Is like, yeah, the True Crime Convention
So it's all these kind of people
Like a lot of moms
There to see their favorite
They're like excited, like at Star Wars Con or something
Yes, to see their favorite investigators
And crime personalities
So like you have
Meet and greets with like prosecutors
And lawyers
Yes, yes, yes
And like TV personalities
Like Chris Hansen was there
He's gotta be the star
He was one of the top guys
Nancy Grace was a big
Big person there
TV judges as well?
Oh yes, yes
But also forensic people like Paul
Holes who's called the Golden State Killer
Who's very attractive but also
Very depressed
The ladies love Paul Holes
But also
There's like ladies like waiting for them
Probably like, Paul
There's ladies with shirts like their favorite person
Wow
Okay, and this is top level, it's not just podcasters
There's a podcast alley
Oh, with Yardley Smith
You mentioned this, Yardley Smith is a True Crime
Podcast, is she was there?
Yes, she married a detective
Who has a twin
Brother who's also a detective
And they do a podcast called Small Town Dicks
With Paul Holes
And they were all there together
Wow, wow, that's all coming together
There's also a crime awards one night
And Yardley Smith presented an award
Oh my god, there's crime awards?
That's not crime
Okay
I heard, I might be conflating
Things but I know like
The most popular podcast
On Patreon is a true crime
Thing but then there was also like kind of
A bit of a scandal with a true crime
Or infighting, is that the same?
It's not
My favorite murder?
It's not my favorite murder
It's like people throwing confetti
Yeah, the happiest people going
Hooray, crimes, murders
But I think there's a problem with the marriage
There's something
There's like an hour long YouTube
I've bookmarked an hour long
YouTube video but my watch
Later on YouTube is
Just insane
It's like 3000 videos at this point
So I gotta try and find the true crime
Find the true
Crime gossip
Okay, so if you go to Graftree on the number
211 is this some crime thing and then
You have to just like look into them
What's the problem with them?
Okay, that's interesting
It's true crime obsessed
I have spotted that
Because I creep on Graftree on sometimes
My favorite podcast alley was one called
Equine crime, which was just course crime
The podcast
Wow, really?
So you meet them or are they
Live podcasting there?
No, they had little booths where they tell you about their podcast
It was sort of like, here's my little
Like artist alley at Comic Con
I have seen podcast alley at a wrestling convention
A couple years ago too, so I think this might be
Common
Is there a hall H at?
Like did they reveal
Like, you know, we found, is the big reveal
They killed, like found a killer or something
In hall 8, like is there any sort of announcements
That are made?
There was a really
Crazy one that I went to
Cause I got a gold pass where like
After hours we went to
It wasn't like that, it was similar
We went to this
Room and there was this woman named Mack
Who's like this very popular
I think she might be a YouTuber or a podcast
But she's like a southern lady who's like
No, no, no
And she was like, because you paid
Cause you're the gold members, you get to
Investigate, you get to help us investigate a cold case
That no one knows about
And so they basically
Is this legal?
It seems very illegal
This woman had been murdered in the 90s
And they brought her mom on stage
And then we all, the audience just got to ask her mom questions
Is this Sharon Love, mother of Yardley Love?
Confusingly there's a second Yardley
Who factors into this
I don't know if it was that
There's so many, Becky Patty
Grandmother of Liberty, German
It's families
Yeah, the families
There's also like a crazy thing
Well anyway, the weird thing about this event was
There was an open bar
During the crime solving
You have to solve a case
And there's an open bar
So at like a normal convention
You would like ask William Shatner
A dumb question about Star Trek
But here you like cross examine
A witness?
Sort of, or also like something insane that happened was
Like, I was in a different
Room when this happened, but like
These horrible Idaho murders happen
Where they caught this dude who murdered these three college students
It was really gruesome
And they tracked him through
Forensics and they caught him
But they were doing like a panel on that
And just like a woman got on the mic was like
Yeah, one of those people is my son
And like she just had come to the convention
To be like
What's going on with this convention
Would you like to ask me any questions about my own child?
Or whatever
So that was like wild
So yeah, crime con's wild guys
But I had to get back there
To see the band play
You got murders and blues
Oh my god
Oh geez
So the first thing, just really important that I showed up
So
As you guys know
Approaching any of these parks from like
Ride share is very difficult
It's a lot of walking
And I had left my
Phone charger
At LAX
So when I showed up I was like
Well my phone's dying
And there's no way for me to leave here
This entire complex
Without my phone
Because I ubered here
And there's not a second option
Because I'm across town too
Wait a second, is this you at the hotel
Or are you at City Walk?
When I showed up at City Walk I was like
But I had a plan because I'd seen these
Phone charging kiosks all over the place
The first time I'd been I was like I'm just going to get one of these
Things
Or I'll buy some
I was like they'll sell these, they'll sell chargers somewhere
Like this is a, this is everywhere
Sells these things now right?
Like bricks
Like I can figure this out
So that was the mindset I showed
Up in
I was like I gotta complete some things
But you had a ticking clock
I gotta see Crayton Waters
And I gotta not make myself so
Violently ill that
That Nancy Grace is a
Challenge
And I failed at most of them
This after
The Sussard
We didn't know, this happened a few
Days ago that we didn't
We just asked Devin Sussard like can you pop over to something
So we can do a podcast about it?
We didn't know
That he was there for like real work
He had done a 12 hour day
And was exhausted and then he gets to the
Thing that he picked and the line is massive
And there's still cliff hangers
On that but
Oh great so well, so far
Every guest has been
Put out and put in
Terrible situations
Financially in the hole
Definitely in the red
Did the
Did the factory future
Escape room for nothing
For no god
So I'm gonna hit you back for these
I didn't know you had an
Escape room story
I had an escape room epilogue too
I bought the magnets
Like the souvenir
Jane and I were like
Let's get some magnets, we have a new fridge
There's not a lot of magnets on it yet
So I got the magnets and then I forgot
About them for a while cause my souvenirs
I get tend to sit in the bag for a while
And I was like when I was cleaning
Stuff up I was like oh I should put the magnets on the fridge
And one of the
Magnets
I couldn't tell this was on
Purpose cause it was not on the description
Jane's like I don't
I'm not getting that
To me it smelled like
Burning
It smelled like the fire effects
When theme parks pump in
The smell of like oh that room's on
Fire no
And that magnet smelled like
That and Jane's like no I don't smell that
I'm like am I crazy
Oh no
One of the two magnets smelled like burning
From the escape room
What does it look like
It's got the DeLorean on it
And the T-Rex on it
And then the escape room logo
So it has like a burnt rubber smell kind of
And this is months after you bought it
And it's sealed it's in the bag
I cut the bag open
It's got a scratch and sniff kind of magnet scenario
But then there's no mention of that
It smells like burning tires or dinosaur breath
Did you bring it can we smell it
I brought everything else
I didn't know you had escape room stuff
But has it been aired out by now
Well I'll take a
I'll take a sniff in the next sector
Well some audience is going to have to let us know
Alright go there you don't have to buy the magnet
But go smell a magnet
Does it smell like burning
But it's sealed in the bag so you're not going to be able
Maybe you'll be able to smell it
But wouldn't it smell like burning fresh
From the store
Potentially
It could be the ink
Yeah
What's your baseline
Relationship to smelling in general
Versus Jane
Like are you a better smeller in that apartment
I can't say versus
I think I have a pretty good sense of smell
Are you hyper sensitive to like perfume
My eyes water and I get headaches easily
And he floats after the lady down the street
Now Michael I'm a taken man
I wouldn't do something like that
Well it's involuntary
You can't help it
No he's got surgery
He got that part of him taken out
He cannot float anymore
Yikes
So bad smells
I think you know
Let's lighten the mood a little bit here
Unless there's horrible stories to come
At Hollywood Drive-In Minigolf
This is where we landed
You did this on
Did you do this on the first round or was this in Crime Con
No Crime Con
The first thing I did when I landed I was like I'm going right now
I'm going to do one of the two
It was raining
I'm going to do one of these two
You did it in the rain
But I was like
Let's go
Nobody's touched golf
Did you do haunted
Or space aliens
I did haunted
You guys did space aliens
Well they did haunted and Jane and I did space aliens
So this is a minigolf course
That was put in kind of like
Mid 2000's
I feel like this is a later edition
No Fallen Brothers, it didn't replace anything
It just replaced empty space
Because it's under the
It goes under the big parking lot
Bridge with the moving walkways
And I remember seeing pictures of it
A long time ago and thinking this looks kind of
Charming and kooky and it is
Two minigolf courses, the haunting
Of ghostly greens and invaders
From planet putt
And the notion of the whole thing with that drive-in name
Is that
It's like these are
There's kind of a now playing
There might be signage to that effect
So it's like you're entering the world of kind of
Schlocky 50's B movies
So they represent
Scary monster movies and
Alien movies
That's the premise we're dealing with here
Very fun premise I would say
Yeah, good idea for a minigolf course
Themed minigolf is kind of a
It's kind of a crapshoot
It can be a little hard to pull off
But these are good ideas that I don't know
Have been taken before
The intro little panel said the haunting
Of ghostly greens now playing on the
Silver screen the first of 18 spooky
Scenes to make you laugh cry
Scream
That's really nice
You get a lot of custom
Stuff in this place you get little poems
That give you a tip on how to
Play the thing or give you a warning
About a potential obstacle
A lot of funny gravestones
In my case
The gravestone game really good I thought
Very funny swim in peace Bruce
Pet shark
His bite was much much worse than his
Bark
Oh jeez
Does that imply that like a shark ate a
Dog?
Bruce was the pet
Topiaries really cool
Topiaries I'm looking at
Topiary holding a chainsaw
Beetlejuice style
I will say Tim Burton
Vibes hardcore
Nightmare Before Christmas vibes
That shark gravestone
Bruce's shark from
Jaws he named it after
His lawyer of course we all know
It's double clever
When you're a tour guide at Universal Studios
The honor you have of
Saying that line each and every day
It's like introducing the musical guest on Saturday Night Live
Ladies and gentlemen
I'm going to say Evanescence
That's how it feels as good as if you said that
Two more gravestones are like Frankenstein
Various parts born 1833, 1838
1840, 1847, etc
And one that says
Werewolf and then it goes werewolf
And then just points down into the ground
Oh
On the first hole there's the thing where
There's lumps which are a good thing
To have to putt over in mini golf
And then so like that's
The bulk of the corpse
And then you've got shoes poking out too
And that tells
That shows you if it's a wolfman or a mummy
I just want to say
I thought this mini golf course was like
Wonderful
It was like super well done
I played through it alone
I didn't have anyone in front of or behind me
So I was just like I'm bad at mini golf
But it didn't matter I wasn't actually keeping score
I was just like woo
And I loved every hole there was one where
Like little
Like aqua monsters like spit water
At you over a bridge
That was really cute
With this guy
Did one of us get genuinely shocked by that?
I loved it
I just thought the whole thing was so charming
And fun and well done
I think
How this came to get I think the golf
Itself was done by a place that does a lot
Of themed mini golf
Called Adventure Golf
Design and Development
They do mini golf
In crazy places like a hotel
Roof or a cruise ship
They'll jam it into whatever space
Very in depth website
They did the one in the Mall of America
Which I think I played I think was fun
They do Great Wolf Lodge ones
And ones by Niagara Falls
But then I think that's comboed with
Universal
Art design people
So you're getting like enough
It's not animatronics but it's really good
I think it's a lot of physical pieces
Like everybody who did this
I imagine on not the biggest budget in the world
This must have been like fun to do
They all knocked it out of the park
Great figures just really good
How was the sci-fi?
It was awesome
This was one of the best mini golf courses
I've ever played
And I played a lot of miniature golf
At the Jersey Shore
I'd shower it in and they're like big
Miniature golf heads
And this one was so surprising
No one in front of us, no one behind
There was a lot of
I answered all the questions
Did you guys do the questions?
No I got lost on that
They give you scavenger hunts
We did the scavenger hunt
Where it is like
What is the name of the
Newspaper reporting the UFO sightings
The Roswell Register
The putt aliens
Are claiming planet earth
For what planet?
Putt
It's in the title
Each cup and saucer spaceship is creating
How many orange blast rings?
Three
So we answered all these
And then at the end they gave us little scratch off cards
Oh we got those yeah
So the one was
15% off mini golf
And the other was 10% off any retail item
But fortunately
I'd already spent the $4 on this
Ball marker slash poker chip
That's cool
You bought that at the outset before we started?
I bought it cause I got so excited
To see like original merchandise
I could not find the character
I forgot they were from planet putt
But I don't know his name
Invader
Guys this is like a very well executed
Thing
Just overall I was so impressed
It seems like it's not popular at all
Yeah
It's a weird spot though
It is confusing where it is
You can miss it
We played around
We played through a guy
Painting and power washing
Different elements
So they were doing upkeep while we were there
Did they also tell you
If you want to come back and play the other one
It's free or $2
There was a little deal
This would have been good if you had little kids
I think this
If you're on
Using that resort
As we're increasingly excited about doing
As a resort and taking your time
Finding odds and ends
For sure I think that's a great hour
One thing I don't know if we've talked about
On the show that Scott and I were noticing
We've talked about this before I think
Is the
Using certain pop songs
In a Halloween setting
Songs that have been now claimed as Halloween songs
Yeah because this is
We did this not long after Halloween
And I noticed it at Halloween as well
It's kind of a perennial
You know you're hearing Monster Mesh
Or Thriller or whatever
Enter Sandman
It was not ever intended
To be a Halloween song
But it feels like there's one element in it
That is now
That you could claim has something to do with a monster
That's scary
We're pulling it in
Where like
She blinded me with science or something
Is now a Halloween song
And they're playing stuff like that
And it's
Hungry like the wolf was one
Yes they played hungry like the wolf
That's a stretch because that's not a werewolf
But he is hungry
And that's horrifying
If a hungry wolf is after you
If you take the song literally
And wolf is not
Oh sure
They didn't write it for the Jack Nicholson movie Wolf
That is not
What that song is for
They should have used it in the trailer if they didn't
They do play not just Halloween music
Halloween adjacent songs
Scott do you remember
Because I feel like you were with me a couple
Times that was happening
It wasn't a Halloween song but it was certainly haunting us
There was a song
I kept hearing throughout City Walk
And I started hearing it again
And I turned around and there was a live
Singer and I'm trying to
Was it a Halloween
No it was just like this
You're talking about Halloween song
That made me think there was like a song
Haunting me the entire time we were at
City Walk I just heard it again
And again
Do you know what I'm talking about it's like an eagle song
Or like a
Classic rock song
I have a
I have a guess and actually
Like wait I'm going to do
Okay I was just on
A Disneyland shuttle where they usually
Play Disney
Music but in this case
They were playing like for everyone
Kind of radio rock
And my guess as to what you're talking about
I was meaning to
Bring this up on the show somehow
Just see if you guys can like
Because basically we played a game
There were two songs and Aaron and I
Were like what's the next one and I nailed it
I got it I'm so proud
So see if and listeners can play along with this at home too
You know this
Breed of like karaoke
Omni present because I think where you heard it
Was maybe outside dueling piano
I think so
Alright here's the two
See if you can complete the third
Sweet Caroline don't stop believing
What's the third
Oh
Good question
For everyone music
It's like what at a wedding it's the wedding
Crowd pleaser
Have we got one
Sweet Caroline don't stop believing
And then it's I'm going to be upset
With myself too I'm going to be so mad
I was really proud that I
Aced it and I think it's the song Jason's
Talking about too
It's a famous song
It's a classic rock song
Obvious
I'll keep hinting shortly you know like
Every man
Working man
Oh it's
Is it September
Oh is it living on a prayer
Got it Mike nailed it
I think it was living on a prayer
Yes
That was a perfect organic way to bring up
That game
It was just driving me
This wasn't a Halloween song but it was haunting me
Living on a prayer is a little
Spooky
Prayer is a religious
It was not in the Halloween mini golf course
But yeah that could be a Halloween
Living on a prayer means you could die at any moment
Yeah that's true
You're dependent on one prayer
The docs are scary
It's hard work
Oh yeah you said a horror movie
Whatever the character's name is worked on the docs
Yeah we don't know what time
Union's been on strike
It's scary not knowing when you're going to go back to work
So you're living on a prayer
One of the scariest
The union busters might come
Like in that Brando movie
Yeah
On the waterfront
Throw your brother off of a roof
Yeah
Tommy
Right Tommy used to work on the docs
If I said Johnny I would have been wrong
There's only that one priest called Ra'maldon
Who's kind of on your side
So you can play the haunted mini golf
But you can also be haunted by songs at
Universe
There was a trip
I went on where multiple times
I heard Life is a Highway
And
The Mamas and the Papas
Oh what is it?
All the leaves are brown
California Dreaming
Which Life is a Highway though was it Rascal Flatts
It was Rascal Flatts Cars hadn't come out yet
I think
No Rascal Flatts is Cars
Sorry was the other Tom Cochran
You say haunted by these
Things Mike would say
Put one finger in the air
Point and smile
I don't think I point and smile at living on a prayer
Don't stop believing
No I know it's not those
But you do it for songs that are not surprising
To hear in public in the least
That's why I started rassing you for the song
When he does California Dreaming
A tear rolls down his face
Because it's kind of a melancholy song
Also Tom Cochran Life is a Highway is a good karaoke song
It is a good karaoke song
That one
Anyway we did keep score
Par was 42
Jane got 48
I got 46
So I won by 2
Mike 50 Scott 40
I stopped keeping score because I was bad
But I had a good time
Yay
Well how about that
We led you to a pretty fun agreeable place
Nice music
The 18th hole is really good
The pressure is on
You walk into
In the case of
The haunted one it's like a mausoleum
And there's kind of like a Frankenstein
Lair and you go up a
Rube Goldberg machine
What's it in sci-fi
It was a flying saucer you went into
And the floor is spinning
And Jane's like you probably shouldn't step on that
They're like oh I'm stepping
I gotta step on that
And there was like one
There was a hole where the ball was taken up
And you had a big spiral thing
And you watched it through like a glass tube
There was also when you walked into a flying saucer
And to get out you hit a button
And it swung open the door
Like it was awesome
That sounds really good
Physical design
This stuff's not easy to pull off
It doesn't feel chintzy
It doesn't feel cheesy
And my only complaint is that
Right before the 18th hole
We got interrupted in putting
By somebody on the moving walkway
Who yelled Mike Carlson
Then I waved and got
Jack shit
I think what happened was
And I wasn't going to bring up that aspect of the story
But I do recall that somebody
Yelled Mike Carlson maybe said like you're a very
Good boy
Correct me if you were
The yeller to what you said
Maybe this is a different time
And then I think I pointed at you and I said
Scott's here and he's like ahhh
Like it was a noise or something
It was not
That could go either way
Not a bad noise
I'm just saying it was not
It's possible
I was very visible to them
They could have been moving fast
I think you were
To the walkway
There's hope for me
You know what I saw
That stuck in my mind
That was a really nice design touch
They had like at an arboretum
All the plants were labeled
Yeah, wait yes
The haunted one has a bunch of
Like where you know
It's Venus flytrap but then like
Like a haunted greenhouse
There's a plant called the Boston
Strangler and the
And then in parentheses Chokeyus maximus
It's kind of dark
For
It ties right into CrimeCon
You should have brought that
Joke to CrimeCon
And they would have been delighted
I waited in a long line to present that to Chris Hanson
At his signing
What do you think of this joke
I brought a funny plant for you Chris
And then sprint to the bathroom
Every hour on the hour
Oh god
Here's a cute little
Chef alien
And he's got an apron that says
I heart humans
And he's standing on a to serve man
Like the Twilight Zone
Wow
They even label the fans
They call the fans something
It says mystical mist makers
And I have a video of you getting
Very unpleasantly splatted in the face
I don't remember that
I look very grumpy
Do I ever think of you getting sprayed
I have a video of you here with the creature
Oh right yes
That did get me
All this to be posted
Do you guys feel a little
Unsettled in a way
That we're here in a saga
Talking about how much we liked something that we did
It doesn't feel normal
The only reason that it doesn't feel so
Odd is because I'm not sure
How many times this is going to happen again
Yeah
I know I'm looking down the rest of that list
We'll see
This was a great morning
This is like the first full day
I had a good feeling
Yes all ahead of us
It's something you can do really early
You don't have to wait for it to open
I honestly would recommend
If you got the time to kill
Or you're taking a little break between parks days
Do that with a coffee
Refreshing nice
This is certainly
All the people on that walkway
Are bypassing this and adding to the theme park
So like
So if you don't want to get in
Wait okay general theme park
This occurred to me also in my recent trip
Where I was in a shuttle and stuff
There's rope dropping
And maybe you want a rope drop because you want to get to stuff as soon
But I think there's also a way to play it
Where you get there purposefully
An hour or two later
And then you're not in that mega
Stressful
I think there's probably a
Perfect window to hit a theme park
When everybody sprinted in with a rope drop
And then you are like half an hour later
Yeah
And then you're not
It's deadly I don't know if anybody's ever waited on Harbor Boulevard
For I mean any
All Disney security can be like
Ungodly and then it can like break
Your spirits and then you don't maybe you don't care
That you got on whatever on Rise of the Resistance first
Or whatever
Because everybody who's rope dropping
They're headed for the long line
Rides first
So that's the only thing you may be sacrificed
By not doing it
Is that yeah you are now going to have to wait
The normal amount of time for some things
But as far as that crush
Yes it's more pleasant
But if you're taking it easy Scott the other hack on that
Is like if you make a
Breakfast reservation somewhere
Especially inside
A park
You gotta show them that on the phone
Yeah sometimes but also
Like yeah it's just nice
To just wander in have your coffee at breakfast
I was picturing like going to a hotel
Where you have when that gets you pass some stuff
You mean in the park itself
You just walk in with a rope drop and then you just go to breakfast
Yeah or even after
Rope drop and it's like if you want a
Leisurely day in addition to
Like in that same vibe of like
What we were doing with mini golf
It's like oh factor in a breakfast
Because that's also a way to save some money
If you eat a big breakfast it's always the most
Expensive least
Expensive meal at theme parks
Yeah true one thing we did not do
I had been proposing that
Hard Rock Cafe is a breakfast destination
Oh right right and ultimately nobody
Wanted to pull that trigger on themselves
Grape buffet
Oh not Hard Rock Hotel
Hard Rock Hotel is grape buffet
I've done the Hard Rock Hotel buffet
I'm thinking about just eating breakfast at Hard Rock Cafe and my stomach is like
Turning
Yeah right I don't look we
It's like you can practice at Margaritaville or like
The airport any airport
Breakfast is gonna feel like I know what four things
Are on the menu and I don't like it
Yeah yeah
At the same time I had a pretty bad
Breakfast at the airport rockin
Brews on the way to Orlando
But I was thinking I was like wow I got
Here really early but now I'm getting to just
Sit and enjoy a cup of coffee
And it's not great and it's too expensive but like
I'm hearing some great music like probably living on a prayer
Having a second at the airport was
Nice and then Mike on the other hand
So late that the
Door slammed on his
Cause we were on the same flight and I missed it so I got there
And they close the door and I go I can't get on that
He's like nope
Next time let the lure of rockin
Brews get you there and
Pumping with rock vibes
I know I didn't even think that there was a rockin
Brews there which is very exciting
Hanging out at the airport a little bit
Oh yeah yeah a little time
To I had it on the other way too I just got
To have like a salad and a glass of wine
At Ruby Tuesday
In Orlando
Orlando airport has some nice little spots like there was like a wine
Bar where I had like a little hang on my way back
Not bad yeah yeah
That's a good place to not if you can build in
It sacrifices park time
But if you can like be relaxed
At the Orlando airport it's a nice feeling
Well it didn't sacrifice any crime con time
Cause crime con was over for me
Oh sure okay okay
So I just could go home What was the finale?
A man is dead
And it's all up to you to solve this
Locked room
No one can go home until
The last day was like
They knew a lot of people would be there
So that's when they did a lot of like
Like this guy is innocent
Guys
And like defense attorneys
They were all the last day
That they kind of crammed them into Sunday
Cause they were like Sunday was only a half day
And nobody is going to come see the
We've got to get this innocent man out of prison
Genius journalist
Cause everyone
Cause he's just reasonable and has evidence
He doesn't play harmonica at all
Okay help me workshop this
Could you do a panel there
Like about Dick Tracy
And say like a salute to
My favorite fictional crime
Would that be possible?
I would have to bury that it was
Fictional or that it was Dick Tracy
So it has to be cause it's true crime
Like some of the worst like
Crimes of the 1930s
Most grizzly murderers
And then I just present like that guy with the head
With the jar ears
Big head
Vitamin flint heart and like
Okay
And I just present it like it's real guys
Now that's a better panel actually
Cause you
Few of you know that there were crimes committed
On the moon
And then you just present it
I've read this book and I just think it's real
And I'm like
Yeah this is serious
You know crime is much worse
Than is now
And you guys need to be grateful
That we're not dealing with these types of
Psychopaths and that we have
Better tools than a two way wrist radio
To deal with them
And typically most human heads
Are more normal than
In that era where this city alone had
25 bizarre heads
At the time we knew which guys were bad
By the way they looked and we don't have them
Their forehead protruded
A little too far
Like in silhouette you can tell if they were bad
I feel like she's doing phrenology
But then I just show pictures of like the crazy bad guys
Yeah I mean if a guy has like a question mark
For a head that's what I mean
Thank god the innovations in
Magnetic technology have come so far
Alright well
Maybe that's more for
Fake crime crime
Tracy gun
Alright let's keep moving let's talk a little bit about
I was very relieved
That you hit a place that was closed
When we were there so we were maybe going to
Defy the sector keeper by not having
Covered this but thank god Eva that you
Have some thoughts on Red Coconut Club
Yeah so after I went to this
Cursed meal
I went into
I was like what's that so I walked over to
Red Coconut Club
Which I was there during Halloween
So it was
Dead Coconut Club
I saw pictures
It changes seasonally
Yeah right now they're getting ready for Mardi Gras
And it's Cursed Coconut Club
Nice Mardi Gras is a separate theme
That's pretty cool
So really quick I looked up
A little bit I guess Red Coconut Club was like
A straight up club it was open
It closed during COVID and then never
Reopened fully and
From what I could tell from reading about it
People just were like it's a club
Yeah sure
No real theme
I think actually was the reason it was put in
They were hoping for something that was like
Wide enough and not like because a lot
Of that you think about like Bob Marley
Tribute to freedom or like there was like a jazz
But they were trying to think of somewhere that's like
General Club whatever
Everything else is very specific it's like Patty O'Brien's
Or whatever
So I also
I think before Red Coconut Club was
Sharing a space with a place called The Groove
Okay yeah or I think The Groove was maybe
What became
The Escape Room
Possibly I'm not totally sure
Was The Groove the all ages like the teen club
I don't know
Well I will say I found some really bad reviews of The Groove
That I would like to read
I don't know if you guys are going to touch on The Groove
We haven't yet take The Groove
That's one you can claim Groove it's in your sector now
Okay The Groove
Okay this is from over two years ago
I did a search for dance clubs in Orlando
For seniors and this came up
None of the people I saw in the photos looked over 45
For all I know it's great for young people
That guy didn't go at all
Off of photos?
You might have been I don't know if that man is a
Widower or anything he might have met the love of his life
He might have got his golden years
Before he met at The Groove
I like this one too
This place if you're a tourist
Hello Universal Studios from another country
That's one sentence
It's mandatory to have a
Driver license to get in
Unless you carry your passport
That can get lost on the roller coasters
Lost
This comment wasn't written by someone
It was just taken from someone's
Brain directly
Without being formatted into a sentence
I like the way you said that too
I'm like oh sure that's fine I can bring my passport
To the theme parks if I wanted to get lost on the roller coasters
The raw pulsing id of America
Is present on any review
I was reading reviews because I got an electric kettle
And I was like
How do I
Descale this they call it
Like cleaning it and stuff
Well I tried
Running it with baking soda
And then I did it with vinegar
And water that seemed like it got more
Of the build up off
You said electric kettle
Like a tea kettle
It's stainless steel
So it could heat up without putting it on a stove
Basically you don't have to use
A range yeah they're really good
It's so fast
And it's just for tea or can you do other things with it
Well it boils hot water
And then you can make pour over coffee or cocoa
Or tea
Or ramen
It's really good for instant ramen
Does it make a fun noise
When it's hot
But not like that whistle the kettle makes
It doesn't really whistle it kind of yeah rumbles
And then it clicks off
Do you have an old whistling kettle
I think we have a kettle somewhere
That whistles that makes the noise
I don't have a kettle
I don't have a kettle either
I'm kind of interested in it though
So really quick
Those places close and I might be wrong
About where Groove was but
When I walked into Dead
Dead Coconut Club
I found it to be
Amazing
So the theme of it was
Let me find it
Very similar in a way to
What we experienced with
With the mini golf it was like extremely
Thoughtfully designed
So the theme was
For this one was that the universal
Classic movie monsters were
Had put out a movie
A B movie
Called Revenge of the Red Planet
And this was the premier of the movie
Was the theme of the club
So not only were all the universal
Monsters like statues
Around the club in like
Tuxedos or like
Sitting in little directors chairs
Or in some cases there was like a
3D movie theater you could go in and watch a
Little piece of the movie and there were two of them
Were like sitting in seats eating popcorn
With little 3D glasses on
But also there was just like really
Cool I mean I think it was like
The Fry's electronics vibe we crave
Like really like
There was like big cool
Statues everywhere there was like
Just and it's like that B movie
Sci-fi thing that I don't know
I think it doesn't get old I think
If people really like care
About making a sci-fi B movie
Like Mystery Science Theater Club and they really
Throw their back into it
Then that's so much
Better than like a
Bunch of things I can think of also it's like
I love that universal still
Does their classic monster stuff
It's like one of my favorite things about them like the fact
That they're going to make a park about it
And that they're still like fans
Even if they don't care about those movies
The aesthetic of it is still like
Especially like I don't know
People want it
There's absolutely a market and for products
Of it and places of it
It makes so much sense
Every year when I go to the county fair there's like
There's a horror area where there's like
Basically teenagers that are making like
Monster movie stuff from that era
Like still
Oh yeah there's like
There's here's a director's chair that was
Just sitting out that just said the Wolfman on it
That was fun it had his stuff in it
Here's the names of the drinks
At a
Millicent snack bar I forgot what Millicent was named after
Like everything was also like similar
Like named after like
Like people who made the old movies
And stuff like that Wait who's Millicent?
I know that name
Barbie Millicent Roberts
The creator of Barbie
Oh
Or no that's Barbie's full name
Millicent is in some part of Barbie
Either the creator or Barbie Isn't that Rhea Pearlman?
Perhaps?
I don't know Have you seen the movie?
I've seen half of the movie
Okay so you haven't seen the part where Rhea Pearlman shows up?
It's another half!
It's something that young girls like
Mike's don't have A major character
Played by Rhea Pearlman who's a creator of Barbie
I'm excited about that I like Rhea Pearlman Yeah she's great
Red Planet Punch, Plasma Punch, The Ooze,
Asteroid Attack, those are some drinks you can get
Spirit Free Slime Oh that sounds good
Yeah
And then wait I do have a description
You guys talk for a second
Oh sure Did you see any singer?
I immediately ask you a question
It was a weird time of day
Because it was like 5 o'clock
They seem like they have a live band
Almost every night I just didn't see them
I think a lot of the
Orlando just filled with performers
So I think a lot of the singers
Jay knew were doing gigs there
There were girl groups doing
Old songs
That kind of thing
It is Barbie's real name Barbie Millicent Roberts
Okay
I don't think this is a live act
Although from the photos I actually couldn't tell
I was like is it a dummy or is that a show that they do
But I think it's dummies
Maybe this isn't a past year
I'm not sure but it's
The bride of Frankenstein's
The lounge singer
And so the bride of Frankenstein's
Lounge on top of the piano
And then the piano player
Is the invisible man
So it's just a body and no head
Do you see that or is that a past year thing?
I don't know if it was there I didn't see it
But yeah there were two stories of
Different kind of installations and stuff
And it did remind me also of
Jekyll and Hyde too
Like it was great
But also better designed
And better thought out
And an actual cool
It would be cool actually if you had a friend
To hang out there
There were rumors online
That I saw
Of Jekyll and Hyde
The now closed New York
Haunted restaurant
What is even the keyword of what that is
Blue key restaurant
There were rumors of it coming to City Walk Orlando
Could have been there
Which maybe could have what if that had like propped a no no
But something closed
Maybe it was just message boards maybe it was just speculation
But what if that had saved the brand
That could have propped the whole thing up
Wasn't that the entire thing running to the ground
Because the owner took out a big loan
And then bought an upstate
How did we look into this
He also opened up a Times Square
Location
I went to the Times Square one the multi-story
Times Square one was crazy
Maybe that's right
But also maybe don't open
The Times Square restaurant
Maybe bad economics on that
It was so rickety when we were there
When we were in New York
That was coming apart
Charming
I loved every second
Dead Coconut Club if it had like one or two more
Like animatronic kind of things
I would be like if this was in Pleasure Island
Everyone would love this
Everyone would be totally into this
Oh shoot that reminds me
Wait I have a screenshot of something
I don't think I put it in my notes
There was some crossover
Oh here it is
I think this might be for
The regular Red Coconut Club
On some website
Not Facebook or anything
Just message board style
Three comments below it
And they're reviewing
Good all purpose Red Coconut Club
Orlando nightclub
And then an anonymous person says
Kind of like Pleasure Island
And then an next anonymous person says
No not at all
Except different nightclubs
But nothing like PI
Which really reminded me of what Mike always said
Mike's haunting thing of looking at the message boards
And seeing people say
Would have been a good night
Would have been a good night at Pleasure Island
At Mannequins
This defensive no
Nothing like PI
That is the energy there
I see a lot of people like mourning
People that died recently
I do feel like if I had a time machine
That's where I would go
If I was like I got the access
To the closet from the Stephen King book
Where he tries to save JFK
But I only would go back
To like late 90s
I would just go straight to Pleasure Island
And be like how was this
The clubs haven't opened yet
I'll just do the brand new Disney Quest location
If you did that
If you used the time machine
Ship on that and then were like uh oh
It's bad
There's no way it was bad
Is it bad?
It's going to happen in the next three years or so
If I had a time machine I'd be like nope
Shut up and kiss me
You're my husband now
It's New Year's Eve
What's 9-11?
Don't think about it
It's just another Tuesday
Don't worry
Oh man
Well this is hey
You're getting good ones I feel like
We've got a consistent
Theme
There's this sci-fi thing
And like you know the
Optimistic sci-fi dreamers
Of the 50s I feel like could have
Only imagined a world where you could just
Buy a battery that charges
Your personal transistor radio
That you do everything on
And I can only assume
Eva that everything worked out great
With this fuel rod
So here's what happened
I showed up my phone was dying
I was like it wasn't quite
Dying yet I think I did mini golf
And I was like okay I'll deal with this phone thing so I can hang out for a while
But I
Went to
One of the
Basically one of the little
Souvenir shops and I asked like do you guys
Sell bricks for phones
And they're like no but there's a fuel rod kiosk and this guy
Gave me very elaborate instructions
Go out that way go past foodie doughnuts
Go down this alley it's right by the bathroom
So I walked I did this
Route got to the fuel rod
And not only was it turned off
But like all the places you could put money
In and the things that
Dispense fuel rods have been like
Glued over
With like plastic like
Shut down so
Violently
So I was like huh so then I went
To another part of city walk
And I asked another person
If they sold bricks and they're like no
But there's a fuel rod kiosk and they
Sent me very very specific instructions to another
One so I walked around and around
And around and down a long hallway
To a bathroom fuel kiosk
Like Cronenberg
Glued shut
So
Did fuel rod like not pay a
Bill and they're like alright this is what happens
This is what happens
None of the employees in the park have been informed
That this happened like they don't know
That something's gone wrong
With the fuel rods
Angry gluing is happening today
In multiple locations so that's when I started
My clock started ticking I was like I'm not going to see Crate and
Waters I can get stuck here forever if I can't get an uber
But then
After I knew I was coming
Out to talk about this I started looking into
It and guys it's not good
And
Not to haunt you too much but I do have
A fuel rod right here
So you bought one at one point
Well okay I bought this underneath
The Hungry Bear restaurant at Disney
I once again the bathrooms
And I do know
One of the kiosks you were talking about
I was there
I passed it a lot
Between the press penny
Location which I did find on my press pennies
Oh yeah
And the fuel rod was right next
To press penny yeah please
Oh yeah wait Eva's never seen
One of these you didn't get your hands on one
Yeah
That's a fuel rod there you go
This is a lot heavier than it should be
The one I do have
That charges you for like four times
Is the size of a credit card and it's like
Oh is it because of the lawsuit
Well there's something going on with the lawsuit
Oh right
So the thing with the wait where's your press pennies
Oh my press pennies are here it's four incredible
Hulks a SpongeBob and a Spiderman
Eva did you know these pennies
Are maybe pre like I think they may be
Pre-pressed or you don't actually bring your own penny
Well you don't put pennies in anymore
I was shocked everybody was acting like
I should have known this but I didn't know
The fact that you thought
I thought these were fresh
It would be funny if you put your credit card in and you were like this isn't my penny
I know
Now listen I've looked into this a little bit
Since we talked about this several days ago
I have not found any
Proof personally that there is
Any kind of penny scam going on
Perhaps in the credit card variety
I forgot that was the point of the discussion
Eva's dude don't you watch your penny get smashed
This was the point
This was Mike's point is that he feels like machines
Used to be such that you could watch
And make sure it was your penny
The way a father makes sure that the right baby
Is going in the delivery room
To the general baby room whatever
I didn't do this it was
COVID
But you make sure it's yours
And I
It seemed like a revelation
In that episode when I
When I said maybe
There's no pennies happening at all
Maybe they have a bunch of pennies just pre in there
But then I looked into it and I couldn't find any
Proof so I might have been talking shit
About penny machines not knowing
What I'm talking about there might be no
Penny what I the discussion I did find
About penny machines was this
The big auto
Fill in if you're asking a pressed penny question
Is why is this
Allowed people are kind of upset
Because you're ruining currency
And there's some loophole that makes it
Because when you're the rest of the money
Is like to pay like
I couldn't begin to I don't know you're
Like paying for a souvenir circulation
Yeah yeah as long as you never try to
Change as long as Jason doesn't now
Go to Duncan and try to spend those incredible
Hulk pennies but would they
Take them even because now you're taking
Money out of circulation which is ruining the economy
Yeah how dare you this is why
It's all going to hell honestly
Maybe another thing Trump will fix in term two
Right press pennies we're not smashing
Them anymore no more smash
I think the international parks
It's just like a metal
Circle it's just a slug
Basically they just take some
Metal and turn it into smashed metal
And they give you a pressed thing of that
This might have to be a runner throughout the series
I actually the Googling I did I started to feel
Bad about what I said about pressed pennies
I feel like I besmirched their
Name but Mike do you still feel like something bad
Is going on yes
I think it's weird that you don't bring your
Own penny that's the magic trick
I brought a penny from home
Now I'm going to see this magic
Machine puts my favorite character
The Incredible Hulk on my penny I brought
From home I entirely agree with
Mike do you do you both agree
I'm not saying I disagree but do you both like
It has to be yours
Yes that's why that's the magic trick
That's why it's special it's not a penny
Who gives a shit about a magic you may as well
It doesn't even matter that it's doing it on a penny
If it's not your penny you may as
Well just get me like a little piece of
Up or whatever pennies are technically
With the Hulk on it
The whole thing is that I
Brought it here it is now
It's transformed this is something of mine
And they've made it something better
Much better they put a better
Fuck you Lincoln yeah Lincoln
Is the guy
Okay what did Lincoln really
Ever do the minions however
If Wilkes Booth approached
Bruce Banner fucking
Shit goes down differently okay
He's turning very green
And he beats the shit out of him
And that incident is much more
Entertaining than whatever dumb play they're watching
Right and Hulk watched play now afterward
Hulk will enjoy
The theater
That's what I would have gone
Hulk wonder what happened next
Speculated intermission
This is one of those cases I feel like where I
Didn't have a dog in the fight and Mike your
Passion won me over now I am like
It better be my penny right
Jason doesn't feel this way though
I don't want to just buy a metal slug
With my credit card Jason doesn't want to say this though because he spent
So much money on these dumb fucking
Pennies that aren't his
I also ended up accidentally buying
I tried to buy one of the Disney
100 anniversary coins
That Tarrant Killam was talking about
But that's not a press that's just a coin
That's just a coin that dispenses but when
You do your credit card reader
I ended up with four
Of them so
Those I like though I don't like
These things
I don't like these things because they're not yours
If it's exactly the same thing
But you knew it was your penny you love it now
Yes if it was
Jason's pennies I would be all
On board these coins he's talking about I like because
There's no like pretending
There's no expectation I had
Before right there's no bait and
Switch
So fuel rods
Okay so here's the thing with fuel rods
That's crazy
When they dropped fuel
Rods originally the whole
Point was that you go to a machine you'd buy a
$30 fuel rod and then
You were promised on the machine unlimited
Exchanges for free unlimited
Exchanges there was a sign on the seat on the
On the machine that saying as long as you
Have a fuel rod you
Put a fuel rod in you get a fresh one out
Oh this was a trade situation
I have one too from Disneyland
You can charge this
You have to get a charger
But you don't need to
Yeah you can charge it with
I think it's micro USB
And it comes with some
Cords it comes with these tiny little
Fucking shitty cords
And this is a USB C adapter
So if you have an android
Or the new iPhones that charge
With USB C and then it also
Comes with a lightning tiny lightning
Cable which I think I've already lost
Okay well that's
How recent is this purchase?
This is
Let's say September of 2023
Okay fairly recently
So this is after the lawsuit
Yes this is after the lawsuit
There's a lawsuit
Of all the things
Oh my god and it's a correct lawsuit
So basically they just stopped at one point
So like
At one point they just stopped
Giving free exchanges
They were planning on charging $3
Per exchange
And when people complained the people from the company
Were like it wasn't in the contract
That you got free exchanges forever
But when you bought
The lawsuit was like by this company
In LA this law firm
They were like well it said on the machine
Free exchanges
That was the contract I introduced you
You've seen that you've paid
I guess you signed a mini contract while you were doing
The thing or whatever
So there was a massive lawsuit
And so finally it got
It went back to if you had bought an original one
You could become like a legacy member
And you would go back to getting free exchanges
But the bigger problem with fuel rods
Now that everyone's realized
Is that there's only enough charge in a fuel rod
To charge like one third of one charge
Of one phone
They don't do the full
My god
There's a post on
Our Disney World
From like three years ago where it's like
The amount of amperage
Or voltage is like
20% of a modern phone
So that's a three year old phone
And they're saying it's about 20%
I think my brother had an older iPhone
And it caught him up to like 40%
Or something from like six
Okay but as time goes on
I'm not defending them but maybe there was a time
Where it doesn't sound like there was ever a time
Where you got a full battery
So that sucks but like it only gets worse
There's $30
Jesus
To not, to maybe
Charge a third of your phone and then exchange program is out
This is some Disney wet dream stuff
The legacy members only
They're taking notes from fuel rod
And then I try to get in there
And it's all glued over
What's going on fuel rod
It was great
Oh no because you don't want to waste phone space
Oh wait yeah
I didn't take a photo
You can't even take a picture of the glue
But it was completely sealed
Is that like
Is it like a prize machine in an arcade
Where there would be a flap but you can't flap it
Yeah exactly it was like jammed things
Into all the orifices of the machine
And you couldn't put your credit card in
That's just nothing
You think you're putting your
Bop bop bop
It was so weird
It's like going to a Meow Wolf with a fake machine
That doesn't work
And trying to act like it does
Rather than just getting rid of the machine
They keep it there to
Taunt people
This can't be the only person this happened to
And also there's people around the park telling you you need to go there
To get your thing
But also like I went on their website and I was like
Trying to find locators and the locator for
Fuel Rod Kiosk says that there's one
Outside Voodoo Donuts at Universal City Walk
Right now
They don't update they don't put a little glue icon
On that one
That one's a little glue splat
I think they replaced the machines
Because I thought it was working
When I was there
When we were there in November
Did something happen between Eva's visit and our visit?
Potentially
Something weird was going on
Maybe it was because Horror Nights was kicking off
And maybe there were more people there
Were people doing weird stuff to the machines?
What if it wasn't glue?
Oh no
It was frosting
From Voodoo Donuts
White frosting
Somebody had to be very horny
To cover two entire
Maybe they brought it from home
In the hotel
At Tidefire Falls
There was a Fuel Rod machine too
That also seemed to be running
So if you're stuck in an airport
Or at a theme park or a hotel
And you want 20%
Of a phone charge
Walk on down to the Fuel Rod
Machine
So my question is
If you want a full charge of your phone
Could you
Pay $30, get a Fuel Rod
Join the legacy program
Charge your phone 20%
Put in the machine, take one out
20 more percent
And you just have to sit near the machine
For as long as that takes
You can walk around
There's some in the park
In the parks too
So your route has to be from one machine to another machine
You certainly have to plan
You gotta pay for park admission
That's part of it now too
So you've paid your park ticket
I don't know if you can join the legacy program
Is that not cut off by time?
Jason are you a legacy member?
That's a recent purchase
I think they backtracked
I don't think they implemented the fines
So they didn't implement the legacy program
It's just back to the old days
I think so
It sounds like you didn't read your contract
No I was poking around
I was poking around
To see if it would
I'm a legacy member
I bought this before the lawsuit
I'm glad you guys hadn't told me
There's legacy members in my press
I would have been so nervous doing this podcast
I'm a Fuel Rod legacy member
So intimidated all of a sudden
I think the important thing to convey
Is that these things suck
They're bad
It's a starter that you keep in your trunk
And it'll get you a little bit
I think I need to feel the weight on this
Can you trust your ass?
It's way too heavy
And for modern phones
I don't recall having a plastic case
Jason's got a little cigar holder
It needs to hold all the shitty little cables
I don't know that I got all the shitty little cables either
It's so heavy
It's called Nightcore
N-I-T-E-C-O-R-E
It's like 90 bucks
It's really good
It charges your stuff really fast
I have an Anker one from 2015
It holds multiple charges
If you took that though
And you put it in your fist
And closed it
It's like a roll of quarters
You could break some wise guy's nose
You could break some sort of
Something Tracy would do in a pinch
What do I got?
How can I do some damage?
You punch, punch and then the acid comes out
You beat up Pennyface
The facey villain
You turn him into a pressed penny
That's the second part of my lecture
How to defeat these bad guys
The weak points in their facial structures
This also by the way
Caution, risk of fire and burns
Do not open, crush heat above 45 degrees
Don't put that in an electric kettle
On the website they're like
Mine got really hot, is this normal?
And they're like yes
That means it's working
It gets hot, there's no percentages
On it
Sometimes it's lit up red
When it's charging
And then I think when it's charged it switches to blue
It's not great
And I have an iPhone 13 mini
So it's a smaller battery
And it really doesn't charge very much
It feels like sticky too
The name of the company
Well that's Jason
The Sheridan house residue
I was eating a coffee bun
Or an apple fritter
It's not a weird thing, it's a sweet roll thing
It's an LA place
It's been open forever
If I touched any of Jason's clothes I'd feel that too
It's all Donut Prince residue
It's frosting
They got the photos on the wall
They have an unusually large number of photos of George Lopez on the wall
He loves Donuts
17 photos
Is Donut Prince on Magnolia?
No it's on Olive
Donut Hut is on Magnolia
Jason's on Donut, he runs DonutTracker.
com
Also the company that owns this
Is named Save Me Productions
One word, Save Me
S-capital-M
And no one has checked on them?
We're messing up
Real bad
It's a combination of Save Me products, Save Me batteries
And Tricopian
Which is Switzerland
I'm scared about what Tricopian does
It's better than nothing
But it's not worth $30
Part of the lawsuit was
The sign on the machines that said
Free unlimited swapping
Yeah
When they were complaining
Like no, no, no
It was like
No, you can't do that
So Tricopian
According to the suit
The plaintiff and proposed class members
Who bought the Friarod now own
A far less desirable product
That they would not
Have purchased
Yeah, but they own it now
But they thought they could get
I literally
I bought it because I left my
Battery in Burbank
We were staying in Anaheim for a few days
And so the only
Time it came through, like my brother's
Phone was almost dead and it gave him
A little jump
Yeah
It is like AAA
It is like a AAA program for phone batteries
Basically
It would probably keep your phone at like 15%
If you kept getting new ones
I don't know that it could get your phone
Up to like 80%
But it probably could keep it at 15%
It feels like
The end of tech, it feels like the end of capitalism
How could things
Get this bad
How do we allow Save Me Productions
To
It feels like what will happen
Soon phones
Won't even have their own battery
And you'll need fuel rods
In general just to turn your phone on
And then you'll have to go from fuel rod
To fuel rod to just keep your phone on
That's like end of capitalism
We live in a 20 minute city
Whatever we call them
The biggest threat
The biggest threat the Democrats
Are trying to do
They want us to eat the bugs and buy the fuel rods
Eat the bugs
Wait did we have no
Scott you have the laptop
Who owns Save Me Products or Trikopian
Is there anyone good
It's funny you ask I am already on the LinkedIn
Of the CEO of Trikopian
Trikopian Inc
And DBA is fuel rod
So Trikopian is fuel rod
His name is Chi Yao
He's in San Diego
A passionate, energetic, visionary
Innovator, entrepreneur, business leader
With a broad and diverse skill set
Professional experience and cultural background
Gained from over two decades of exposure
In technology industries
And highly challenging global leadership
Assignments at startups and major corporations
I think we've won jargon bingo
We got that's a full
Board
Is that just like the I read that
And I was like am I reading the default
What comes in your LinkedIn bio if you don't
Change it
That was all nothing
How do you
I feel like the only way you get these massive contracts
With Disney, Orlando
All these airports is if you have
So much startup money that you're like yeah
And you just buy it once and then we charge it forever
Whoever is like the dip and dots
Lawyer
There's a lawyer that
Takes all these different brands that no one
Really likes that much
And makes a deal and puts them everywhere
I was going to fight for dip and dots
But my body I like dip and dots
More than I like a fuel
Yeah, I do too
I would have to say that as well and I don't
Like dip and dots
Here's okay this is unrelated
But it's funny I think and you tell me
If I'm wrong I looked up save me products
And I got save me products
Inc.
And what I believe
This is not the same save me products
Inc.
Because this is save me products
Which are offers for stockmen
The cold weather newborn calf hood
To help battle and prevent frostbite
This is
Save me products
This company save me products offers a
Newborn calf hood
For your calf
On a farm
It's that you're what you're showing looks
Like a Mexican wrestling mask
It's like a lucha lucha mask
It's a mask for
Newborn calves
I think this is a different
But what if it wasn't?
Well I'm reading
I'm not sure yet
We also sell
Bollock plovers for cattle and we also
Sell these shitty little batteries
We also offer interesting horse collectibles
And some items for the farmer rancher
Horse owner antique hound
Art connoisseur
Collectible items that may just want you
To save me
What is that sentence?
Huh
We also carry a few one of a kind fine
Handcrafted small leather items from a
Local professional craftsman
I'm sensing equine crime
It's a fuck
It's that villainous cow face
I bet
You can get a sticker that says
Faith is confidence in God's world
So that's for your window
That's for a window
I can't make heads or tails what kind of company I'm looking at
A religious cow mask company
Of course we assume we talk about this
I'm sorry I was looking for this earlier
But I did find it and it is funny
This is jumping back a little bit in the lawsuit
But when people were like
When they stopped doing the unlimited fuel rods
Someone reached out
This is on a mice chat article
About this whole thing
Someone reached out
Is that Len Testa?
No
That's Dusty Sage
So somebody reached out and was like hey why have you changed your thought policy
And this was a fuel rods response
And they just print it
All caps
There was and is no contract signed for free swapping
Dear sir or madam
I am sorry you are upset
There was and is no contract signed
For free swapping
We offered this for over five years but has come to a point
Where we can no longer do this
We do have an app out now
That will offer specials etc
I can send you a code that will be good until the end of the month
That will help with the transition
Please remember that the fuel rod is rechargeable
If anything goes awry with the product we will still
On a replacement
Kind regards name redacted fuel rod team member
That is by the way
My level of psycho
Is that I have used and charged
The fuel rod multiple times
Outside of a theme park
I'll just plug it in to the USB plug
And charge it when I go to bed
I feel like it's a good maybe car
Emergency car thing
I guess southern California
The temperature doesn't
Flux your way too much
So you can leave it in a car
It will probably uncharge after like four months
I have a phone charger that you hand crank
Oh I see
It's also a radio and other things
And a flashlight
I feel like that would probably work faster
Than a fuel rod
To charge your phone
There's another guy a co-founder and a COO
Joe Yagley
Sheow and Joe Yagley are the guys to watch
He was part of something called Eagle Enterprises
Powergenics
A lot of real
Sounding companies
Guess what private citizens
In the world of podcasting
You're about to become public
Jason how much do you think a large
Size calf hood is
How much
Can I buy one right now
What's that material
What are you working with
Canvas, leather
There's many paragraphs explaining
About the hood
How do you know if they're a boy or a girl cow
Can you get pink ones with little flowers
This is a black one
This looks like the calf is robbing a 7-Eleven
I don't like the black ones I want gender
Conforming
I want one with
Rocket ships and Spiderman
And one with Barbie
And really big wasteful calf gender reveal party
Wasteful to the level of selling
Random shitty
Lithium ion batteries
A lot of touristy places
The only difference is that there's large and small
Calf hoods but you can get
One that has a
Reflective stripe over the calf's
Head so I assume in the dark
You'll be able to see the calf
As if it was jogging
It's like taking a
Late night
These calves don't look happy
With their hoods
Also it looks like this is photoshopped
On the calf
This doesn't appear to be actually on this calf's head
When you put the
Hoods on they start kicking and
Drain
I want to know more of the trinkets
On this website
There's the faith is confidence in God's world
Terrible graphic design
And then there's a lot of blankets
Different colored blankets
You can get wallets
You can buy leather wallets
Did you have a price point for that calf hood?
Oh wait yeah that was the game
We forgot to answer it
I was going to say around $40
It's a little high mark
$120
$80
$6259
That's a lot of numbers
And if you want the reflective stripe
It's $66.
Why are they in this middle ground
Why is there smash pennies
I've got to come into this
$66.
And then
Four Hulk smash pennies
You must procure these items from Universal Florida
You can get Dalmatian toys with little boots on
How much is that?
That is $15
And they have
One units in stock
They have one single Dalmatian with boots?
It's unclear if they have
The two different dogs in the picture
Does the website have an about me
Or about us section?
Yeah
Let me get to that
We're finding that one of the save me productions
Might be okay
Even tread carefully
They're at the LA county fair
They're going to walk up to your delicious huckleberry pie
Or something like flip it over
Don't mess with save me
Nice prize winning pie you got there
It would be a shame if an angry
Cav who's been wearing a hoodie
Doesn't like all day
Walking up to a plate of
Sugar cookies and breaking one in half
Be careful
I'm having a problem
Finding an about
Keep looking Mike
You got back
What happened?
That's why I didn't get a drink at dead coconut club
Because I was like
There's no time
You got to see the show
What happened?
I was in the dark
Crater and waters
I alone sat in a dark
Conference room
And watched crater and waters
And then I went
So you did make it back
You had just enough fuel rods be damned
You did get back
I did have a little bit of time
So I was considering
Going into
I was considering
Coming back or going into
Sorry, into horror nights
Because I was curious about some of the very
Hyper specific Orlando
Mazes they have
Because there's ones that are based
On rides that they have
Or lore that's specific to Orlando
And less on movies
I didn't realize how massively popular
It was there and there was no possible way to get in that night
I can't get in there
And also my phone's dying
Fuel rods, no
I poisoned myself but I won't know for 24 hours
And then I was like, okay
I'm going to walk through dead coconut club
And then I was like, aw
And then I just sprinted back and got an Uber
And I made it back to see crater and waters
Thank god, thank god
Okay, okay
If we had caused the crater and waters show
To not have been accomplished
What if I had bought a fuel rod and only gotten 10% out of it
And then I'd been just so angry
What if I had like bought
I'd gotten a fuel rod
Gotten into the park
And then realized I was fucked
You've been ripped off
By the bad Save Me
Production, not this good one
Not the good one
I like these guys
Are they based on one of the Dakotas or something?
Where do calves get this coal?
It's a good question but I have a couple
Questions that are answered here on the website
That I want to let everyone in on
Question, do I need to dry
The calf off or will Save Me
Ears do that?
Answer, Save Me
Save Me Ears is not a calf dryer
In cold weather you should always
Dry the calf off
Especially if the temperature is 20 degrees
Or colder where the newborn calf is located
So Save Me Ears are not
Drying your calf
You have to do that before you put
The ears on them
Dryads only
Jason, if you'll excuse me I have another
Question to read
Alright, fine
He's smashing their ears down
I have a hundred cows to calf
Out during cold weather
Do I need one for each calf?
Answer, Save Me Ears is only meant to be used
For the first 24 to 36 hours of a newborn
Calf's life
After that it should be removed or passed on to the next calf
We recommend having one Save
Me Ears for the most cows you have had
These sentences are not that great
That normally calf in one day
C-A-L-V-E when I keep saying that
Well because calf and
Calve is a
It's also a verb
To calf, I guess I didn't know that
Having a calf is calving
Oh, so I should be saying calving on some of these words
Or whatever, no no I'm saying
Calving is
Giving birth to a calf
Maybe we don't have to do that L so hard, is that what you're calving?
Calving works fine, I don't know
Calving, calving
Not calving
So you're supposed to
So, okay
You're supposed to get a hundred cows
Yeah, but you don't need one for each cow
If ten of them are going to give birth
Every day
Not only are we going to get more at the same time
Yeah, you need a hundred because that's too many
It's six thousand dollars worth of
Ears
You also, the turnover, you've got to be calving
Calving
You've got to be calving so often
To make this thing worthwhile
This is where I pull out as a shark
This is a micro, it's not even
And my calf can't wear it all year long
This is for the first 36 hours only
I'm out
This is how we know they're not as corrupt as other saving productions allegedly
Is that when they didn't just go
How many do I need?
They just went a hundred
One hundred, right now
What's your credit card number?
You know that they're good people
Because they're like no, you actually only need it for the first day
Is there any sort of exchange
Program that they offer?
Can I
Hand me down, when the kids get too big
I can go back to the calving hood machine
And exchange it for another one
Can I become a legacy member
For the calving machine
I don't believe there's any sort of rental
At least that I can see
Just from this brief glance
All I know, and I don't know what the context
Is, but there's just a graphic
Here that says
Lost profit with like an angry
Looking
That cow's coming to me in my dreams
I think what the subtext is
That we're not saying is that if the calf
Gets frostbite, it's ears fall off
Oh, that's what we're
Fighting against with these hoods?
It's smashing down their ears and keeping the ears
Wired
Because their ears might just get brutal and stamp off
And the newborn, they're not
Functioning
For the first 36 hours, you're protecting the ears
It's also kind of like an S&M mask
For the calf
It looks a little zodiac
These are going on the website, right?
These are going on the Instagram
Let's make sure people are
What's the website again?
You can go and bruise it yourself
Of course, it's save-me-products.
com
Might want to just put that in your favorites
So we keep track of it
Can we ask them, did the
Dalmatian have to wear boots because its feet
Fell off?
Do they sell Dalmatian boots?
Is that why the toy has boots on?
Because something happened to its feet in the cross-bite
Well, Paul had to very sensitive
So yeah, you probably want to keep those
It's hot, you got to be careful where the dog
Walks.
This is in North Dakota
This is where they're based out of.
I knew it was in Dakota
You were right.
Email us, sorry
Our email form is not working below because our web
Host updated their security
It will send but not deliver email to us
In the meantime, what does it mean
To send not deliver?
It just goes into a chute and then it ends up
In a river?
Your email will be printed
We had the time to write all this out
But just put another email on there
Please do more research
Tell us that there's an episode
About Yellowstone where this is
The plot where they're trying to
There's a whole season about calf hoods
Mike would have known that if he'd watched the show
Calf hoods, yeah
They have links to some of their other favorite
Products and websites
FrozenCalfEars.
com
PuppyWindows.
Wait, no.
Yeah, I swear to God
Red Border Collies
Sheep and Cattle Dogs of a more rare color
Little Valley Ranch
White Tail Deer Breeding Stock
What's PuppyWindows?
Go back to PuppyWindows
Can I just say, while you're on the way to that
Mike, you and I were doing some logistics
Planning about this series the other day
And you said, well, you know, maybe we could fit that in
If we just put it on one of the lighter sectors
We now, what we thought
I'm like, Fuel Rod Kiosks
That sounds like a funny five minutes
Now we're deep into calf hoods
There's no such thing as a light sector
It doesn't
It doesn't matter if we add another one
Any way we slice it, we're going long
Alright, now read about, what was it
This is just like a puppy classified
This is like you look for puppies, I think
I thought it was a window for puppies to look through
Or windows for dog
Pet stores
There is
Oh yeah, because you're asking how much
Is that dog in the window all the time
I'm so stressed
By the energy of everyone that indicates
That this could, you have
Nobody's dying to wrap this up
Clearly, this website
Could be read in full
Which is fine, but we have fucking
How many of these we got to do
There's one more thing I want to say
Other than, okay, there is some website called Praying Medic Books
Which are inspirational books on faith and healing
No, Praying Medic is a QAnon guy
Oh really?
He's a big QAnon guy
Really?
I think you should see in the Will Summer book
Maybe?
Oh, like emotional healing, big book things
He's a big Q guy
Oh wow, so calf hooves are Q?
Damn it
Calf hooves are Q
We should have known, it's going to be around any corner
We started with Epstein
We started with
Save the Children and the Moon
Scott, do you want to summon the Sector Stone?
It seems like you're
That's probably a good idea
Oh look, hey, there it is
The Sector Stone
Can anyone else see it better than me?
Oh yeah, it's a little calf hood
You'd think it would have been a fuel rod, but no
It's a calf hood
It could fit right onto the littlest calf ever
Oh, wonderful
There's a website called Sand Hill Satellary
And I only want to bring this up because remember
Jason, early on in his Los Angeles career
Interviewed to work at a place that made horse saddles
He did?
Oh yeah, in Burbank
Jason thought he was going to make saddles?
The recession was really hard
I was applying to every job
It's recession this, it's 9-11 that
Yeah, it was mostly shampooing saddles
in the Rancho area of Burbank
Jason was going to get a job shampooing horse saddles
I don't say this about
This is going to sound like an insult to you
But I would say about this about myself
I'll say about Eva, I don't know
Eva's been multi-talented
None of us are going to be good at shampooing saddles
That's why you didn't get the job
They knew he wasn't qualified
No, no, no
I said I was looking for
an exciting
fulfilling
a new job
This job is neither exciting nor fulfilling
Like I literally just plucked it
From cover letters
Stop writing
They can't pretend
That's what they said to me when I applied to write for Ellen
You'd be better off
better off applying at the shampoo
I applied to be
a front desk person at a
dental office or a doctor's office
The border of Sherman Oaks
had seen it
I showed up and there were 30 people there
and they were like, thank you for coming
Thank you for submitting your resumes
You'll hear back from us soon
And I'm like, did 30 people apply
for this job and we just had to show up?
They were just seeing who
would show up
It was something like that
Why'd you say the address?
That's not far from where you live
You're like, it's all the way
in the 15 minutes
It's like Encino or something
I don't live anywhere near that
This is 2008, right?
Yeah, it's like 2008, 2009
Do you want me to see about Sandhills
salary?
If they can fire you?
All the way up to the Dakotas
What I want to do
is say Eva Anderson, you survived
Firegazer, I had a
tell you what, Saga, the Multiverse of Madness
Oh god, do you have any energy
in which you'd want to plug anything?
Do you need a fuel rod to give you the energy?
Just read this website if you could for me
while in your plug
Oh, Eva's been handing out plugs
I want to plug a Sandhills
What is this?
Sandhills Sadlery
Kind Handmade Saddles by Sean Kramer
Serious gear for serious cowboys
Sandhills-Sadlery.
com
Also Praying Medic
And all the books on that website
True Stellar
You are the plan
Hugh is the plan, you are the plan
Thank you for that
You're all digital soldiers, Trump is ascended
Trump is president
And of course, where we go when we go home
And Copperfield will make the moon disappear
Yes, and Trump and only Trump
He was sent from heaven to bring it back
When Trump says we will all put on our
calf hoods
and we will all ascend
But they're gonna have the reflectors, and nobody will bump it
It's gonna be perfect
Put the calf hoods on, stand down and stand by
Dry yourself off before you put your hood on
The hood will not dry you off
Folks, you gotta dry before a hood goes on
We love hoods, but can't be wet
The hoods don't dry them
Thanks to Aaron Garandner for the art
Our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno
For the theme music, Multiverse of Madness
Merchant RT Public Store
For the full Multiverse experience
Subscribe to Podcast the Ride the Second Gate
Or join Club 3 to get every sector ad free
And an exclusive bonus sector at
patreon.
com slash podcast the ride
Eva, you know what?
You know what we get to do tomorrow?
We're back to Bubba Gumps
Yay!
I hope you did the quiz
I guess I'll find out when I listen
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner
Brett Boehme, Joe Cilio
and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts
Please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com
And subscribe to our
Shows on Apple Podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following
us on Twitter and Instagram
At Forever Dog Team
And liking our page on Facebook