Forever…
…
dog.
When your town has made you frown,
When your square has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch,
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol,
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks,
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk,
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Extremely necessary series, exploring the shops, restaurants,
The cosmic wonder, that make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to the grand finale of Podcast The Ride,
the City Walk Orlando Saga multiverse of madness.
Day last.
I'm not going to say a number because I'm not even fully confident which one we're at.
I don't know either.
But it is.
It's going to have to be the last.
We can't start saying it and then take it back.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hi, I'm here and it has to be the last.
This has to be it.
We have to be done here.
I'm not joking.
There's a lot at play.
I don't know whether we're talking to each other or to certain spirits,
but whatever's out there, let's all get into agreement on this.
Jason Sheridan, do you agree?
I'd be open to revisiting any number of these.
Jason, how?
How?
It has to be.
Oh my God.
All right.
Well, a break for a little bit.
In fact, I think that's what needs to be addressed at the top.
This is the finale.
We have reached the end of what my wife Erin called a psychotic amount of content.
And I'd like to not hear that word used again about future endeavors.
I believe this is my, I think what we're at, 21 days, 24 episodes.
When I say those stats out loud, I hope you will understand why we are taking a sizable break on the main feed after this.
I don't know for how long, but it makes sense, doesn't it?
It makes sense.
The only thing that I take some solace in is the fact that now we are really padding out our podcast catalog.
So then when we sell it, when we're in our seventies, much like the recording artists, you know, your Bruce Springsteen's, your Neil Young's are selling their catalog.
We've now padded it out with 24 episodes.
Yep.
It hits one and all.
Hits every one of them.
Perfect episodes over and over.
These are all the piano man and we didn't start the fire of in our Billy Joel-esque catalog of all killers.
That's right.
They've all come out in the last 21 days.
This break is news to me.
I was going to start a multi-part saga on the Philadelphia toboggan company starting tomorrow.
Manufacture of early roller coasters and carousels.
Jason, you're welcome to.
As long as you're okay to do it with no co-hosts and no engineers or editors besides yourself.
And no microphones.
Oh, okay.
We need to give them a rest too.
They're piping hot.
Just in some sort of padded cell of my own.
Of your own creation.
Maybe where it should stay.
Yes.
That's right.
Okay.
So a little break on the main feed, but new episodes will keep coming out on the second gate and club three.
So be sure to subscribe if you haven't already and if you aren't sick of us.
On a similar note, what we're doing right now, at least a big old chunk of it, the majority of it, will be available as a video episode.
It will be available exclusively for club three subscribers.
And if everything we have planned works out, you won't want to miss this.
And if you're seeing the pointing I'm doing at a camera, then you're already watching the video.
That'll be it.
Check out all this great pointing.
We're pulling you in.
Now I'm doing a pulling gesture.
You'll see all of these gestures if you go to patreon.
com slash podcast, the ride and our thanks to West Knapp for helping us out with the video and all the engineering here.
One more time, I want to thank Aaron Gardner for the art, Mike Carlson for a fantastic theme song sung beautifully by Zach Reno.
I want to thank all the guests who have been with us through this series.
It might be the best lineup of guests we've ever had, at least all condensed into a short amount of time.
I do just have the regret.
I'd like to say I wish we could have fit in Griffin Newman or Zach Reno.
But hey, they were here in spirit.
And of course we have to hold out hope that someday we will finally get Anthony Geo to be on the show a little more frequently.
I would love that.
He's great.
I don't know why it doesn't come together, but fingers crossed we can make this work in the future.
He's not mad at us.
I know.
It's so many ignored texts.
You have to start assuming some sort of tension.
But luckily there is a guest who did not ignore texts.
He probably wanted to.
Yeah, yeah.
You will wish that he had when all this is said and done.
I don't think we're allowed to end one of these without this guest who has not been on podcast the ride in any form since his last Saga finale parking garage episode over four years ago.
Wow.
Yeah.
Can you believe that?
Nuts from Doughboys from Get Played.
It's Nick Weiger.
Wow.
Hey, buddy.
Thanks for having me.
What a treat.
Thanks for being here.
What a ride.
Oh, boy.
Quite a ride.
I.
Yeah.
You've been you've been listening to some you've been trying to keep up as the avalanche just keeps pouring new snow on top of you every time you think you're going to get up.
No, I am.
I am.
I've been listening every day to the City Walk Saga and I am Multiverse of Madness and I am four days behind because it's just it's it's a deluge of content, as you know.
And I can't I love the podcast.
I'm listening to it with focus, but I don't have like two and a half full hours every day to listen to it.
Okay.
I've had this with yeah, Aaron.
My wife was like, I took a break.
I wanted to hear some music on my commute.
Yes, of course.
You'll be hearing me.
You will.
You also have to hear everything that happened before it comes out.
And then maybe after again, you hear my voice all the time.
Everyone, please.
I think everyone could use a break here.
No, it's great what you're doing.
The three of you are heroes.
And I thank you.
I.
It's just someone said we were talking before.
The podcast began because, you know, I've been on podcast doughboys with Mike Mitchell.
And right now we are doing for whom the bell does much Madness 2024, the turn of champions nine dokiro Taco Bell, which is a month of Taco Bell.
And it's a big pain in the ass.
And we're annoyed and angry and cranky and yelling at each other.
And you said that block of words more coherently and quickly than any.
That was like you were speaking a foreign language.
That was that was amazing.
My eyes rolled back in my head like a men tat from Dune.
So but like that is so much less annoying for us than what you are doing to yourselves.
So like it really puts into perspective what your sacrifice is as podcasters to give us daily content.
This volume and this quality of work on your part.
Well, I guess, you know, we have to take it.
How could we not?
I wouldn't be polite to not accept this praise.
There's really no other way.
I'd love to bat it off, but it would be rude to break a tiny bit of kayfabe.
We've been trying to get this off the ground for years and pandemics and births and strikes and all these things have gotten in the way.
And I have been really happy to do it.
And then we got to go to Orlando, our favorite place to do it.
But there's one aspect of it that has, I'd say, not been pleasant and some maybe where our heroism should be mentioned.
And that is the the eating aspect of it.
Right.
And I think we're a little bit on your territory now.
And I wanted to compare notes with you.
The food punishment, it's existed in all of these.
But this one, I feel like every episode has had some kind of incident from just an upset stomach to something being disappointing all the way up to food portion.
And I guess I'm curious, Nick, about your relationship with.
I.
OK, question one.
Yes.
Your policy about going back to restaurants that have actively made you feel bad for doughboys.
Yeah.
Our policy is we will do it.
Atta boy!
Jason and I's too.
That's how we feel as well.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'm massively outnumbered here.
I think this policy has made me a pariah in our own podcast community.
I'm a stuffy elitist, apparently, for not as opposed to because what I've found, the whole thing has reminded me of the Mr.
Show sketch, The Devastator, where there is a roller coaster in town that is like that's like killing and drowning people.
And the news reports about we got to get out of here.
I got to protect my family.
And then it goes back to the theme park and the people who were just saying I got to get out of here are back in line with thumbs up smiles.
And I that's you guys.
It's the like right up eating pinks and pinks hurting you.
As soon as we have said that pinks is not good.
Back at Toothsome.
I went to Toothsome not even for an episode.
No.
Yeah.
But you did.
You did get a milkshake and you made a video.
I'm quoting somebody else here, but I saw the comment that the tone of the video in which you say it's fine.
It's OK that it felt as if Latte the robot dog had a pistol trained on you just out of frame.
You made a hostage video.
Why are we letting these places hold us hostage?
There was a there is a scenario today where I brought like flounder almondine for everyone here from Toothsome.
But they don't I don't think we couldn't get it to go.
You know, this hasn't been said on the show.
I believe that flounder almondine is not available on the menu anymore.
Right.
I know.
You look at the menu.
Yeah.
That terrible burger Jane had was it did not appear to be on the menu anymore.
Are they listening?
I had this like cocoa.
Oh, maybe they're adjusting.
They're listening and taking things off that we didn't like.
Look, we look.
We got to make our peace.
We just got to go up there for dinner when they unlock the pasta menu.
We just need some of that tooth when they unlock.
They take their golden, their copper keys and they put it in the pasta machine and turn them on.
It's like sub keys like the nuclear subs.
Yeah.
And they unlock it.
Was Hunt for Red October the property that introduced the two keys?
Because like I was probably that recently because because Blank Check is covering John McTiernan.
And I was like, is this the first movie that did this?
Because they spend some time explaining the two keys right in it.
Probably because it's a big part of Mission Impossible.
Yes, 100 percent.
Yeah.
And then that and that already feels like it has a hunt for October just homage built into it with a submarine and with the Russian turning into English.
It's a anyway that that tangent aside, what y'all are dealing with is not just like shitty chain restaurants, but like the worst version.
A lot of these chain restaurants, they're either things that exist like as gimmicks that that are just there to like, you know,
like a pool filter, just catch people leaving, like entering or leaving theme parks.
So they're either like their places like Toothsummer, places like Bubba Gump.
But you're also dealing with like the extra-grimble sounding Moe's outlet that you all visited.
And I mean, and that's one thing that happens because I know that the universal KFC, the universal city walk KFC,
we just had our friend Jamie Loftus on the podcast and her experience there was she went there to get a seasonal item.
They have Blackberry Pepsi right now.
And they were all like, what are you talking about?
Like the news hadn't made it there.
Like it's like a frontier outlet that doesn't have isn't a part of the same KFC infrastructure.
So like, yeah, you're dealing with really like like the worst of the worst of this already usually pretty mediocre food.
And let's not forget more expensive, more expensive.
Absolutely.
There's a premium.
Yeah.
It's like the you know, it's like it's like the versions you'll find in an airport or a stadium.
It's the same sort of captive audience.
We don't have to have the same quality level.
The brand is enough to get people here and we can upcharge them.
It's weird for something that like I think we've entered into these all of these city walk things going with this.
Well, this is the world stage.
This is where you bring your best or you do the best of the best and that they they literally bring their worst.
Yeah, they all.
And we still continue to be surprised by this.
And I think if if we were a big if we were to step down and do this ever again,
I think it'll be enough time for us to forget and just get back in line.
Actually, well, I mean, I'll just say let's make that if a win.
Amen, brother.
Thanks for thanks for speaking for some of the audience there.
We're not going to let child rearing chronic health conditions get us down.
If we could find one of the let's just let's crunch some numbers
and find the one of these theme park adjacent malls with the least restaurants.
Yes, I think then I'd be back in because I think we did the one with the most.
And while it led to some surprises like how much we liked Hot Dog Hall of Fame
and Ian Rickabani's glowing feelings about Bubba Gump with his family,
I think most of it was traumatic.
So I think there's more restaurants here than in any of them.
And I felt the weight of it.
Let's just crunch numbers.
Somebody out there.
What's near a theme park with maybe one cafe?
Well, and I'll get an iced tea there just just to throw an idea out there.
And, you know, you could run this by the sector keeper.
But like I think there's maybe a reality where just you, you know,
maybe all of all of the food side is just one special episode.
And then you don't have to worry about like we're going to make sure we have
we get designated meals for everything.
We'll just do a kind of a survey of all of the available food options there.
And then we'll really drill down.
You get down to brass tacks dealing with the individual stores
and the VR experiences and what have you.
Could we also assemble maybe like a Mission Impossible team where, for instance,
we only make Jason eat at all the restaurants and Scott doesn't have to eat.
That's his special power.
This is an area where I'm lacking.
Jason, don't you want to go eat more of this food?
Hmm.
I recently had a doctor tell me I had to change my diet.
But yes, I do.
And I believe.
And after that, you started drinking more soda, correct?
You know, we all need little joys.
I the scientific advances in the zero category like Dr.
Rapper Zero Coca-Cola Zero Sugar.
Good tasting, but they made it a very cumbersome name now.
I feel like those have come a long way.
The zeros are really impressive.
Yeah, I basically just don't drink diet drinks at all anymore.
I just go for the zeros and whatever they're doing, whatever alchemy is going on behind the scenes.
Like I feel like you'll have like the I think the Dr.
Pepper Cherry Vanilla Zero.
That one's really hitting.
There's an A&W Cream Soda Zero that Natalie picked up and it's just like we love that one.
That's a go to for us.
And the other thing is like I'm also I'm looking specifically for zeros with no caffeine because I'm trying to have caffeine in the afternoon.
So when you hit some of those, I mean, it's really, really satisfying.
But yeah, they've gotten really good.
Yeah.
And it's I'm like a two zero a day guy these days.
Wow.
Because I tried Stevia soda for a long time.
It hurts my head.
I can't do it.
But that's the natural one, they claim.
But they asked for Tame, which is a fake one.
Well, it is technically natural, but it hurts my stomach.
Also after the entire Breaking Bad, like she drinks that Stevia shit.
And you're still like, so do I.
I got a lot in common with Lydia.
That's fiction.
That's a fictional show.
That was in it's set a little in the past.
Back then it was Stevia was bad.
I will say from listening and editing most of these episodes, I do think my stomach is by far the strongest of the three of us.
Jason will eat as much as I will and eat the same stuff, but Jason will generally report a tummy ache, but he will go back.
You don't like things in general.
You will like things the least.
And then you will have tummy ache or puke.
Jason will go and not learn his lesson, but often have a tummy ache.
And then I will once in a while have a tummy ache.
Does that feel right?
I think that's fair.
Yeah.
How did you react physically?
Because when we went and saw our friend, Eva Anderson's immersive beforehand,
we got a pregame meal at a famous director, Gold Tongs Fried Chicken in Gria Town.
We did get a nice meal.
How did your constitution handle that?
Because that was a pretty heavy fried meal.
It was fine.
I don't know.
I had like a drink afterward and walking around was helpful because the immersive was we could walk around.
So yeah, if you get the system moving, I feel like it was fine.
Did you have a problem?
Were you secretly in shitting pain while we were walking?
I was OK at the event, but I was maybe in not the most comfortable situation afterwards.
Because it was that really dense fried chicken with a lot of breading and then some of it was really heavily sauced with a lot of sugary sauces.
It was delicious, but yeah, it was very good.
I haven't been to this place, but I feel like you're in a better territory that it is a real restaurant by someone who wanted to open a restaurant.
That's the like it's like Nick.
It's completely that like they have universal owns a funnel and they have to put things in the funnel to help like get everybody to shake coins out of people on their way down the funnel.
It's not nobody's desiring to open a good restaurant.
Right.
It's not the point.
No.
How many times do you do?
During the week, do you feel like, oh, I'm gonna have a bad shit?
Or show related even specifically show related?
I would say it's pretty frequent because we're eating a lot of pretty awful food.
And even if it's like I'm enjoying it, it's usually something that's very heavy that I know is going to destroy me.
And then also I'm just like I'm older.
Like I've since I'm since I hit 40 basically, I'm just like I like alcohol and sugar and you know, like like desserts and and just like really like heavy carb heavy meals like just really just affect me in a way they didn't used to.
You know, I'm just not a young man anymore.
So I just I feel my body taking a toll.
But it's also like not even just intestinal distress.
Sometimes it's like just like headaches or just like fatigue.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
I also had a little bit of a bag of candy after I went to tooth sums from its sugar.
More candy.
Just a little bit.
How much of the milkshake did you drink?
Half, I would say.
Okay.
There was antics in the bathroom too.
I was trying to wash it out.
So that you could because you had to.
I want to take it home.
The amazing jar again because you could get that on Instagram.
Imagine like, whoa, he got a jar.
Did he go to the jar store for it?
No dessert came in there.
It was too much.
I threw it away.
I threw the whole cup away.
I tried.
I waited.
I waited outside the bathroom so no one was in there and I went in there and tried to rinse it off.
But the whipped cream was stuck so thoroughly to the side of the plastic glass that it wouldn't easily rinse off.
So only pieces of the whipped cream were like falling off the glass.
And then that doesn't like rinse easily.
You kind of have to scoop that up.
And then I banned a chip like pretty quickly.
I was like, not worth it.
I threw it away and went straight to the sugar.
It's sugar store.
Good for you.
Thank you.
You didn't salvage that.
I ate the cookie and I had like half the shake.
And again, it was fine.
It was fine.
That's a bad.
The praise.
You're singing on a mountain top.
Fine.
That is the pitch of a great review of a meal.
Well, it's nice to commiserate on this point a little bit.
And there's one more thing.
We haven't even checked in with the Sector Keeper to get the official word on what we're doing.
But one quick thing before we get to that, we have met a lot of fun, interesting characters while we've been doing this.
We've met a lot of different keepers, not just the Sector Keeper has been with us, but also the Level Keeper a couple of times and the Venice Beach Boardwalk Keeper.
The Keepers who introduced themselves the last time Nick was here at the end of the Downtown Disney ordeal.
And it's been nice to meet so many of them.
But there's one, something's been nagging at me because there's one Keeper that it feels like we should have met given what they represent.
And that is the City Walk Orlando Keeper.
Why, if that's what we've been doing, why did we never meet this character?
We freed him at the end of the Downtown Disney ordeal.
He was one of the people we freed.
Well, but he also, well, what he actually did though was imply like stuff we had to go do to help him.
And in fact, Wes, I have a clip.
Can you play this clip?
Let's remember what the City Walk Orlando Keeper was about.
Right, right.
Boys, boys, I'm the Keeper of City Walk Orlando.
Professor Tootsam is going to murder me unless you say what's different about our voodoo donuts, Menchies, Cinnabon and Fossil.
They're much different from Hollywood's voodoo donuts, Menchies, Cinnabon and Fossil.
No, they're not.
Don't let me die, boys.
No, we can't let them die.
It's not there.
So what, it's something where I think we've tied up all the loose ends of this pretty neatly.
So why, that's not anything that we did.
We didn't, Professor Tootsam was not going to commit murder.
We didn't even talk to this Keeper at all, who does sound kind of familiar.
Yes, a little bit.
Like he makes something familiar about his voice.
Well, my hope was that just to like tie everything up into a nice little package that we maybe could just briefly try to summon the City Walk Orlando Keeper.
Oh yeah, sure, sure.
Let's see if we can do it here.
Let's just like close our eyes.
Why don't we read what's on your shirt actually?
Maybe that's a good way to summon him.
There's coffee stains on this.
Oh good.
Okay, so once you get past the coffee stains, then maybe this will be the way to summon him.
Okay.
I love City Walk.
Boys, boys.
Hello?
Hello.
Quit bothering me, I'm fucking busy.
Oh, and Weiger?
Fuck you, you piece of shit.
Wait a minute.
Hey.
Hello?
What?
He's gone?
That was it.
Huh?
Did I even meet this guy?
What does he have against you?
I guess he listens to the show or is it just like, there's bones to pick based off the show
somehow.
Maybe he was freed by both of those fossil locations being closed down.
Oh, that's right.
That's probably what happened.
That would make sense.
It really shows you, boy, how time has passed, what the pandemic did.
Oh, it's too bad we didn't get to do the full breakdown of fossil alpha and fossil omega.
And with that guy, who seems very pleasant, I think we could have had a blast.
Well, it was not meant to be, but we were luckily with the one that we know, the classic
sector keeper, and we ask him now to give us today's assignment.
Boys, boys and wigs, your final assignment is phase seven, sector three, parking garages
and fresh eats.
Good luck, boys and wigs.
There you have it.
Wow.
The parking garage.
We're a little extra and we'll get into that too.
We are back here for another parking garage breakdown with you, Nick Weiger.
The tradition on the show, you have only been on this show to discuss mall and kind of theme,
but mainly mall adjacent parking garages.
Right.
And we continue the tradition here today.
Yeah, I'm happy for this to be my beat.
I'm fascinated by infrastructure.
And I do feel like parking garages are important because generally most people are going to
be driving to one of these theme parks in America.
There aren't a lot that have like a great, like a train stop that's right next to the
park that just unfortunately isn't a thing that exists in the United States.
And so it is the first part of your day and the last part of your day.
And if that's a frustrating experience, for instance, my brother recently went to see
a Metallica at SoFi and was just like, it was three hours to get out of there.
And so you got to see a concert and you got to see like this band that you love and you're
excited for it.
And the memory that's lasting is trying to exit the facility.
Like you don't want that to be a bad experience.
So when a place really nails it, it's like, okay, it's like you're landing the plane
effectively.
So for me, it's an important part of my theme park experience and my mall experience.
If there's a bad parking structure, I might not be going back to that mall as frequently.
Can you think of one off the top of your head?
You know, that's a great question.
I think the Century City Mall does not have a great parking structure.
It's pretty frustrating.
And it sucks because they have a great AMC there and they also have an Eataly.
But just as far as actually getting there, it's like, I'd rather just take the bus than
deal with all that nonsense.
What do you think about the, I don't know how much time you spend around there, but
I think the, in our backyard Burbank, the Burbank Mall, triple AMC barrage.
Yeah.
I think it, you know, it's like, it can be hard to navigate and figure out, but if you
know, you have to like have what you do when you go there or else you could end up stuck
in some really grim basement.
Now is, would you call that the town center parking or is this, am I thinking something
different?
I mean, it could be.
That is one parking space you can get.
But there's also, there's like seven odd stray garages.
That's one of the AMC theaters is kind of in the garage.
That's bizarre.
It's, I could see it being like a source of stress if you don't know how to play it.
Right.
It's like if you went to Disney and you were totally on your own for parking, there wasn't
like an attendant redirecting you to like Toy Story parking, like one of the adjunct
lots.
It was just like, Oh, I don't know where to go.
You know what I mean?
And, and that, that is actually that Burbank, that Burbank area does stress me out parking
wise because I just don't know exactly where to go ever.
And if you're like mapping your way over there, you know, it's like, it's not necessarily
going to direct you to where you're going to park and all.
No.
Yeah, exactly.
So it's, so it's like, all of a sudden, yeah, I'm parking in like whatever the town center
a lot near like the Ross or whatever, where Marshall's or whatever it is over there.
And I was going to five guys and I got a 15 minute walk ahead of me.
It's not worth reparking at that point.
You can end up at some weird smelly alley around 100%.
Yeah.
We know what you're talking about.
I guess here I am like setting up another saga.
I feel like I just walked right into it.
It's a smelly alley.
It's sector 17.
The Batman statue gets its own episode.
Flappers is right there.
We see Leno and then we do live show there.
Yeah.
Hey, Carlson, it's a home run.
I've looked into it.
After you take the standup classes there, of course.
Oh yeah.
We're going to go through one, two, three, four.
I've looked into what does it take to play Flappers comedy club where Jay Leno plays frequently.
You have to fill out a big questionnaire and it's like, how many TikTok followers you got?
I think it might be a 10.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I'm judging them wrong.
Well, Jay doesn't have a TikTok.
And they still let him.
They let him do it.
But he's legacy media.
We aren't getting there.
At this point.
After all of these sagas, have we done as many episodes as Jay Leno did tonight shows?
It's possible.
Have we been on the air longer than Corden was?
God.
No, he was 2014.
It's close though.
We're going to laugh.
Yeah, we're going to laugh.
I think we'll laugh them.
Fingers crossed.
Or we stop just short of him in honor of his body of work.
Well, we could do that too.
Yeah.
I wouldn't hate that.
Any pleasant parking garages in the recent past you haven't discussed?
Is there one that sets the standard?
Oh, good question.
I should have come in hot with a great parking experience top of mind.
I don't hate parking at Universal, honestly.
We're not super far from there.
I feel like that's generally an okay experience given the volume of traffic they're dealing with.
I feel like when we talked about it in the original saga, it seemed like kind of a frustrating.
Maybe you've changed your tune on it.
Maybe something about the way I forget if ET garage was going then.
I think they've streamlined it.
That's what it feels like.
Also, I have not gone back for a day at the park.
I went for one, but mostly I've been going for city walk.
It might just be the reforms that have taken place because of COVID and everything and all the lockdowns.
That gave them some time to rejigger things.
I feel like it's a little bit better of an experience than it used to be.
Just the presence of a firehouse subs sports you more at ease in those garages.
That better quality of ingredients than Subway.
But I mean, also my experience with-
Wait, hang on a second.
Jason is still saying this after his girlfriend ate a piece of plastic in their-
No, no, she didn't eat it.
She didn't eat it.
We caught it.
No, we found the plastic.
She didn't choke on plastic.
She found plastic, AKA firehouse subs rules.
She found it and then wolfed down the sub.
Just as I wolfed down mine a few hours before.
The finest review is ever given any establishment.
I had firehouse subs while I was up there for toothsome.
You went back.
You guys.
I didn't have it the first time for city food.
I didn't have it before for city food.
Jane, collapse.
I ate a meatball.
I ate a meatball sub at Fido.
Who'd have eaten plastic?
No, I took it out so I could take a picture of it for content.
I ate a meatball sub, a toothsome shake, and a bag of candy while I was up there within about 45 minutes of each other.
This is just back in line, back in line.
I'll go there tonight.
I hear plastic and sandwich.
That's the end.
I don't go to this place.
Am I crazy?
It's quitter talk.
I'm Frank Grimesing right now.
I am Frank Grimes.
I know that doesn't end anywhere good.
I'm going to take some of this equipment and electrocute myself.
If we aren't careful.
That would be a hell of a finale.
It might be.
It's where the only place.
By the way, it's the only way out of doing this podcast.
Of any podcast.
That's true too.
You know what's maybe a better answer than universal?
I kind of feel like, given again how busy it is and the crush of patrons, I think the Grove's parking structure is pretty good.
I think it's not terrible.
I think it's like a decent experience.
I think the way they route you at that sort of spiraling, you know, a driveway that takes you to the upper levels is a pretty elegant solution in terms of just like moving traffic.
And I think it's not terrible getting out of there.
And they have a lot of entrances and a lot of exits, which is always a benefit.
Sure.
So, you know, it's always a thing of like, yeah, you're going to have a better experience parking at a place that has that's just like mostly an empty lot.
Like you go to a Best Buy that's got a huge surface lot.
That's just going to be easier to park at.
But it's kind of a different category than what we're talking about today.
And so something like what the guy, not that I want to give Caruso any credit, but like what the Grove does, I think at their scale is pretty good.
Yeah, yeah.
And any of these places that are dealing with like a massive amount of, I think it's what's particularly impressive about the universal ones, at least in theater.
Now we don't know in practice.
I'm not sure the level of frustration of the Universal Orlando garages.
But they are getting traffic from two theme parks, City Walk, a water park, which is not the third gate, goddammit.
It's a water theme park.
It doesn't count.
But that's but anyway, they can handle tons and tons.
I believe that this entire the entire facility down there can hold over twenty thousand cars.
Did you guys see some other numbers which may make Universal Orlando the largest parking complex in America?
That's wild.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that it is maybe slightly knocked out by the West Edmonton Mall, which is a massive mall in Canada with a theme park component.
But like one of the garages specifically, and I'm not sure which, apologies, but one of them is, I think, the fifth largest parking garage in the world.
We're dealing well.
Big stats.
Yeah.
Now, that doesn't tell us the whole story.
What we have to figure out is like quality of experience.
And this is honestly a little bit tough because unlike the Woodfield Mall, we did not.
We did.
It wasn't in the cards for you to come out to only go to the parking garage and then leave.
In hindsight, I should have done it.
I should have just come to the parking garage.
It was discussed.
Yeah, we discussed it.
I should have just made that happen.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was discussion.
We would have made you do something.
Join us for a live show or something.
Although, I don't know, maybe it's turning down.
I don't know.
I got in at 11 a.
m.
I'm flying out at six.
We'd have to put him up in lodging if he stayed.
First flight in, last flight out.
He's going to be in lodging, his car in the parking garage.
Yes, his rental car.
Send us a receipt.
Look, that Universal Studios store in the airport has that crazy big wraparound screen.
That's enough themed entertainment to last a lifetime.
It's like what happens in that Tiny Tunes, where they go to the theme park and then they just take the monorail around.
Well, that'll do it.
That's all I needed.
It can be possible in some places.
But anyway, I think what we really have to judge is quality of experience here.
And it's a little bit tough because, look, we flew in.
We stayed at the hotels.
We were there, yeah.
None of us have parked at this parking garage.
So we have to analyze some other things, some reviews, some statistics.
I think one element to talk about that might help us is price.
This is certainly a factor.
Thirty dollars is what we're dealing with.
Thirty dollars!
Do we have any reaction to that?
Not even in comparison to anything else.
Oh, I was going to compare it to here.
It's thirty-two dollars out here.
That's good.
Oh, jeez.
Well, then they upcharge you for the horrible tacos, but then you make that money.
You make it back on the parking.
Thirty dollars is kind of the case across the board.
I have been in this parking garage as a child and adolescent because, you know, for the first few times,
my family went to Universal Florida.
It was just a flat surface lot.
Right.
And then they built up this garage as they were opening City Walk and Islands of Adventure.
So it was very exciting to go through this parking garage and hear, live in La Vida Loca.
And like, what is waiting for us?
We saw the previous center.
We're going to see it in person.
You remember live in La Vida Loca.
I specifically have a memory of being in this garage and hearing, living La Vida Loca,
being on, I'm sure we'll get to it at some of the moving walkways,
which are a big element of this garage, unlike all the other ones we've talked about.
Yeah, where you're like, Mother, Mother, I'm about to live La Vida Loca.
We're all going to be living La Vida Loca.
I really like that it's a structure.
And that seems like a positive reform, turning it from a surface lot into a structure,
because that's one thing that drives me nuts from an infrastructure perspective,
is when I'll see an aerial shot of a stadium,
and you'll see the square footage that's occupied by the stadium,
and then all the surface parking around it, like outside the Kansas City football stadium or whatever.
And it's like five times as much surface areas for surface parking.
And so you build up, not out.
And if you can do that, it's much more efficient.
I agree with you 100%, but I've learned,
so Universal's working on this Epic Universe Park down the road,
and that's going to have a surface lot to begin with.
And I think that's the easiest way to get parking quickly.
And I think down the line, maybe a garage will be coming.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, last time I went to Legoland, which was like 10 years ago,
I remember it all being a surface lot.
I don't know if that's changed or not.
I was there just several days ago, and that is the case.
And it is a bummer at the end of the day to now walk all the way.
They're in that, I keep Simpsons referencing,
but they're in that itchy and scratchy land, kind of like, so we're in D.
Yeah.
There's really no thing.
It's like the D Marketers are not really anything.
And yeah, bummer to have to walk a mile or whatever it is after your theme park day.
But yeah, I think you're right, Jason.
It's like the sign that phase two of the resort or park has happened
that now we're building up, which this thing landed like it's a really impressive parking garage visually, I have to say.
Oh my God, it's wild.
Wes, do we have pictures?
Can we pull up some of the photos I sent?
If you look at just like the foliage and then that dome there.
It's very appealing.
Yeah, I think there's an aesthetic.
It reminds me of like the big facilities in Jurassic Park where it like scares me a little bit.
It intimidates me.
It's like I think a parking garage can like add to the story if you're like, are you scared at the top of your day?
Are you partying like with Liv and Livia Loca?
Do we have Jurassic Park 2?
That's another one.
I think good landscaping, good foliage is a good, I just really got a Jurassic Park vibe out of here.
It's very similar to Mickey and Friends and Pixar Pals.
It looks like it's decayed a little more from this photo.
But other than that, it looks very similar to the Disneyland parking situation.
Yeah, yeah.
Now, while we're still looking at photos, Wes, if we could pull up parking characters one.
And this is where we can learn who is.
So there's two giant lots and you get you split into two different directions.
And so I think that I forget if it's north or south.
Oh, here we go.
South.
These are the south characters.
Cat in the Hat, E.
T.
and Spider-Man.
The big three.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
When you think universal or things they have at least temporary deals with.
And then parking characters two will show us the others.
King Kong, Jurassic Park and Jaws.
So that has a little bit more coherence.
Like it's like the first three are just kind of a grab bag.
But these are all like, OK, these are big scary monster franchises.
Yes.
They'll kill you.
Yeah.
These three.
I also like that.
Can we pull up the photo?
Remember Jaws.
This is the way that they help you remember where you're supposed to go.
This just leads to the strange phrasing.
Remember Jaws.
Yes, I do.
Like a fallen hero.
Never forget Jaws.
You may have forgotten.
Like a decade, over a decade at this point.
The Jaws ride has been going.
It's like the statue of Superman they put up in Batman versus Superman after he's killed.
Someone spray paints a false god on the Jaws.
So, I mean, is South Garage hurt at all in your estimation by the incoherence of the characters?
No, because I think those are, you know, it's what I think is good about the characters.
I think the kids will help.
It will help them remember them.
I know E.
T.
, I know Cat in the Hat.
And that seems like it's probably, I'm not a parent, but I imagine that could be a fun thing.
Like, remember we parked in the Spider-Man lot.
You give them a job.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But also then like this day and age, you're obviously going to take a picture with your smartphone anyway.
So like just that iconography is a little bit cleaner than, you know, I parked in A23 or whatever.
Sure, sure.
And I like the, I remember, honestly, does jog your memory a bit.
It does.
Yeah.
Sometimes you go, oh, I'll remember, don't worry.
But if you say remember, it's like at the end of Star Trek II when Spock is dying and he puts his hand and he mind melds with McCoy and he says, remember, it's the same thing.
It's the same principle.
It's the same exactly thing.
So now you're mind melding with that sign.
That sign.
Yeah.
Sign mind melding.
You got to take that smartphone picture because I've definitely gotten lost in Mickey and Friends.
Scott and I got lost once together.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
And it took forever.
And that was really bad.
We actually, yeah.
Calling, calling helped because they said, oh, at the time of day that you came in, we were loading on this level in these rows.
Yeah.
And it was very helpful.
And I believe the Universal Garage has the like blue light, the college campus blue light that you can call for information, not just panic.
You know, though there's yeah, I'm sure plenty of panic has occurred in these places, too.
They are giant.
They if you like we got to wander, got to the privilege of wandering the parking garage with the level keeper.
Oh, yeah.
And the like when you're out on the furthest end, you real like, boy, that was a that was a long walk.
We walked a ton.
Yes.
To try to see everything.
Yeah.
Really every nook and cranny of it.
Now, actually, you know, why don't we let's look at parking overhead.
Yeah.
That'll really show you the some of the full weight of it.
And this this bridge construct here, you've got two little ones that lead you to one big one.
I think I stole this diagram from something called David's Coin Travels.
Thank you, David.
David and for your travels.
So it's it's huge.
But like you feel like you could get your head around it.
This isn't like the Hollywood one where like but which which way did I get like everyone leaving from everything that you can do.
At Universal Orlando has to go back this way.
So at least generally, you know what you're doing at the end of the day.
Now, let me ask.
And I don't know if this is just a stray icon on this this diagram.
But is this parking structure that Kat and had an E.
T.
and Spider-Man lot so vast, the south parking structure that there is an Anteans pretzels located in the middle of it?
That's what it looks like.
That's a good question.
That is exactly what the map is showing.
Yeah, I think that's incorrect.
I don't think that just like in the in the pure middle, maybe that's just showing you this is where you have to park to walk very far to get the most expensive and bad Anteans of your life.
Because it would probably do business like excited kids at the start of the day or exhausted parents at the end of the day.
It's like, oh, it's getting Anteans.
What if it was a roaming vendor?
That's a great idea for any park.
Yeah, it really is.
Yeah.
People would definitely take them up on what they do have, though, in the little announcement at the top.
We heard parking garages and fresh eats.
Can we look at fresh eats?
There is a food stand in this parking garage.
Wow, so it is true.
Okay.
It's kind of in the like the bridge area that connects everything.
Got it, because it looks like it's two big structures and then there's kind of a central walkway.
Like they they they they they they meet at a hub.
Yes.
And then from there you progress on to the theme park property.
Exactly.
And in the hub, they do all the security screening, which is a pretty robust process.
It feels very airport, very TSA.
The buses also load out sort of right down that way as well.
Yes, I watched a video about this.
The resort buses are on the bottom floor and ride shares on the top now.
Ride shares now takes up the entire top floor of one.
I want to say the south garage, but don't quote me on that, which has always seemed decently efficient when I've done it.
So we're actually able to talk food here a little bit, because I had one of the ice pops,
which is the menu that we're looking at right now.
It's gelato pops.
There are several ways you can customize your ice pops.
You can dip it, drizzle it or dredge it.
The mildly confusing through the swamp.
What is that?
Well, the way OK, the lot of see if everybody likes and approves of this logic.
Dipping is like the miles in my local version of it, like a Balboa bar, which is in Norwich County,
where you you you dip it in milk chocolate and that stays a hard shell.
And you can then attach other things.
Drizzle it is syrup.
Those are the options under drizzle and dredge it is peanuts, Oreos, scram cracker crumbs.
So like hard items and candies go under dredge.
Maybe this is working for them, but I feel like they fell in love with the alliteration and made it more confusing.
Because I dipping is basically the same as dredging.
It's just the dry ingredients versus wet ingredients.
And then and then dip dipping it versus drizzling like I can kind of see some daylight there, but they're still like kind of similar.
I feel like just select toppings and then just like a big list of toppings.
We get the job done the same way.
But then again, maybe what this does, these sub menus as they incentivize people to be like, oh, I'll do a dip and a drizzle.
You know, maybe people all of a sudden get two sixty nine cent toppings instead of just one.
I mean, I just like that theme park menu board has the word dredge on it.
That's right.
I like it.
But it is it is like a it's like a depressing.
Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't sound delicious.
It makes you think so.
I think of Corpse Retrieval.
It doesn't make you think of like many M&Ms.
Yeah.
Now, was I not answering my phone?
I'm sure I would have liked to try some dredge.
You would have like to dredge something up.
Oh, I would have said, yeah, dredge it all the way.
Dredge me up, boys.
Like a Chicago hot dog.
I want the full garden.
This garden is mostly corn syrup in different forms.
Yeah, I think you were out of commission for that period.
We're saving you a full walk through all of the parking garages, which if you can imagine was a little bit taxing.
The I got to say, I liked these pops in a series full of bad and disappointing treats.
Maybe I like because I have no previous notions of fresh eats.
You know, I can't.
It's not like I had one once and now I'm going to have the worst fresh eats ever.
Like, I don't know.
It's in the parking garage.
So my you know, my guess of the quality is in the basement already.
So it really surprised me that it was a pretty solid.
I mean, to get a good dessert in the parking garage.
Well, it's so smart because you can either get it right away or like at the end of the night.
Maybe you were regretting I should have gotten some before we left.
And then you see it there and then you get a little treat on the way in the car or on the bus or in the like, it's very smart.
I'm surprised that Disney doesn't have it because Disney has a bunch of room at Mickey and Friends and Pixar pals.
First, I could put something there like there's enough room for something.
I'm glad you brought this up.
So was fresh eats by the souvenir stand?
Yes, it was.
Let's see a picture of that too.
Can we see West's garage store?
Because this is a thing that has I've always associated like it was it's been there for a while.
And I'm shocked Disney has not adopted the last minute garage souvenir stand.
They might have carts.
They may have carts and maybe for like glow sticks and things kids want at the end of the day.
But here, Universal has stacked some of the best items.
I own one of that like retro rain hoodie, whatever you want to call it.
Yeah, it's really good.
And then those fanny packs or the straps say ride the movies.
Those are cool.
Yeah, I become a big time man bag guy these days.
Basically, a mutual friend, Zacharino, got me into it and I would definitely sport one of those.
They're very snazzy.
Yeah.
Is that the term that you have you tossed aside fanny pack and any associations with that phrase?
Well, so for instance, this one I brought with me is more of a shoulder bag.
So, you know, I think it's kind of a catch-all term.
But, you know, whatever, they're handbags.
I find them very convenient.
That's a good size.
That seems like not super cumbersome.
That's exactly what you need.
So a good I think a good store.
I think a good I had a good treat there.
Yeah.
I haven't found the security to be terribly inconvenient.
Does anyone have stories that negate?
Well, no, I don't have anything to negate it.
But I got there one day and I was taking the bus in.
So I would come in on the bus area and then even at times when there would be like an insane amount of people and I was like, oh, man, this is going to be 45 minutes.
It was like less than 15.
It was less than 10 maybe even.
So like they were they had figured out a system to get the funnel people in pretty quickly through security.
So I was never really like upset with what they had what they were doing.
I feel like it was pretty efficient.
And then once you get past that, you get moving walkways.
This is Jason's a big series of walking walkways.
You can gain some steam if you're running late for something.
I was at one point you can really like pick up the pace there.
Yeah, I love move ever since I was a kid and was first at an airport.
I was like, oh, my God, it's like an escalator, but it's flat.
Yeah.
So I I kind of like internally light up when I see a moving walk.
It's fun.
I love a moving walkway.
Do you are you a standard or are you like a fast walker?
Like what is your general general approach?
Good question.
I would say a standard, especially if I have luggage to try to navigate luggage on those things isn't exactly easy.
Yeah, sure.
I'm not against standing, but I do like to feel like I'm fast.
It's fun to have the super stride.
Yeah, yeah, that is fun.
So that's yeah, but I will stand.
Sometimes I stand.
So when you're on that moving walkway and you're hearing by Lemos, we're a year later now.
OK, they wrote it out.
Different living Lovita local.
I look this up because I'm like, could I be confusing the songs?
And I was like, no, I think one year it was living Lovita local and the next year it was by Lemos.
And you remember what was this is just to show me.
OK, because you love moving so strong and you love these theme parks so much.
You have every detail locked in.
Yes, because I like that.
And I didn't like freshman year of high school.
So I really hone in on the theme park stuff.
I feel really similar.
I don't think I liked anything that happened to me any day of that year.
Yeah.
And then I went to Universal at the end and I locked in forever.
And now I do this.
Yeah.
Me too.
I felt much more less had my sea legs.
Yeah, once you know the ropes a little bit, because because that all that, you know, my understanding is that there was a time when what we what we now call middle school was junior high school.
And that was like six through ninth grades or something.
And then 10th through 12th was just high school.
There was a point where they added ninth grade.
I definitely felt like a little too young for the high school kids as a ninth grader.
That might be the biggest age difference you're ever other than like, but if you're a kindergartener, you're not really around the fifth grade.
Yeah, you're in a different part of the playground.
And it's a little different just being kind of thrown in that pool when you're like 14 and you're like, they're legal adults you're sharing the campus with.
Strange.
Yeah, absolutely.
That's why you cling to the memories of pop music that was playing at a theme park.
And then you'll be reliving it in the nursing home.
OK, so the nurses later freshman year, mostly leaning on theme parks and comic books.
Sophomore year, a little more stable junior year and got really got my sea legs.
Parents divorce finalized.
We got the shared custody down pat.
Then 9-11 happens.
And so we're a little off kilter.
So but back to theme park.
It gave you one of your favorite things to do, which is to define your life and everything that's ever happened in relationship to 9-11.
Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute.
It's set up a lifelong hobby.
And that's what you're going to be telling the nurses.
No, no, no, we have COVID to lean on now.
Because you like your wind ups you like and the date on that March 15th, 2020.
That's right.
That's true.
So we're just looking at you're just I'm just realizing we're looking into our future and I'm just thinking about like my you know, my my my grandmother, my my late grandmother, Joe R.
P.
I.
who like, you know, was like raised in an orphanage, lived through the World War, you know, lived through like the Spanish food, like lived through like this, the all the civil rights movement, like like a century of turmoil.
And then like she's in her 80s and we're just like sitting down with her at El Torito.
And it's just like this is what your life ended up as.
Like that's that's the preview of where I'm going to be.
I'm just going to be like the old guy in the chain restaurant with his loved ones.
And it's just like like like, oh, yeah, not that I'd be a grandpa, but like like the old old great uncle Nick is, you know, lived through COVID and lived through 9-11, you know, telling them all like I used to make my living coming to places like this.
Yeah, sure.
I was talking about that thing again.
We all make our livings doing this, grandpa.
That's what the economy is.
The only job left.
Your podcast or you drive an Uber.
Let's order the wagon wheel sampler.
So I feel like we're getting a pretty good impression of the sparking garage, actually.
You know, just from outside, you know, I'm impressed by the size.
The price is not the worst out there.
Actually, what's Disney now?
Disney, I have the stat.
Disney, I think is 35.
So less than that.
Concerts are $40 now, like depending.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, usually, you know, everything's getting NFL games.
I've heard can be like $100.
Like there's some serious gouging that happens for these huge events.
And I know from, you know, because I am an NBA fan.
I'll go to the Lakers games and I usually take the train to downtown L.
A.
But I know the parking structures there can really gouge, like especially the ones right next to the stadium.
Those can be like 50 bucks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Really right.
I'm swearing that one.
I never in L.
A.
live.
Oh, we've talked about doing that though before.
That would be.
Yeah.
I have no memory of L.
A.
live is awful.
Is Tom's Urban still there?
Look, I would love it, but it would also actively discourage you from doing that for your own sanity.
L.
A.
live is awful.
Yes, you're there more.
That's OK Times at L.
A.
live.
You know.
Where have you had OK Times at L.
A.
live?
Tom's Urban, Yards.
Tom's Urban.
You've had fun at Tom's Urban?
I said OK Times.
OK, I've had the Smashburger.
What's that Smashburger place they have there?
Is that still there?
I think it is just a Smashburger.
Is it called Smashburger?
Yeah, I think it is.
I crammed that in before a Monday Night Raw once.
That was an OK Times.
Gulp it down like a duck or something.
I'd love to spend three hours talking about it.
It would be interesting to see by the time you cover L.
A.
live what the Peacock Theater would be called.
Oh, yeah.
Because it was the Microsoft Theater and now it's the Peacock Theater.
Yeah, yeah.
It will be something else in a few years.
Yeah, we'll see.
And by then, will they fix what I just heard about, which are a glut of typos on the Kobe Bryant statue?
Oh, yes, yeah.
How embarrassing.
Yeah, there was a player, Vaughn Wafer, who they spelled his name Vom Wafer.
And then they…
Is that what a name sounds like?
Has anyone ever been named Vom?
That's what we've been doing during this saga, is bombing.
I think they also misspelled the phrase, Coach's Decision.
But they left some letters out.
Yeah, and also that actually led me down a rabbit hole because I was looking into how these statues are made.
It's like one of those things where there's this weird cabal where it's like one married couple in Chicago who does the entire world of sports trophies.
Or I mean statues.
So if there's a statue of Lionel Messi somewhere, they'll be like…
They go to this one couple in Chicago and they're the only people who made it.
And they're the people who made the Kobe statue too.
Oh, wow.
But yeah, it's just like a business that they fully control.
Yeah.
But not the plaques?
Are the plaques outsourced to AI or something?
That's a great question.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if they're responsible for the plaques themselves.
Great question.
But all the power is concentrated with these two.
Wow.
We'll look into that during the LA Live Saga.
Look, make these decisions.
Let's get out of this one before we make any decisions about another one.
What's the bowling alley they have there?
Oh, that's a good question.
It's there and I don't remember.
Isn't the same one they have at Hollywood?
Is it one of those?
I can't remember the name of that chain now.
I don't know.
I can't remember it so they probably don't have it.
So probably we don't need to go there.
Oh, I did do the bowling alley with Nick Mundy once.
Yeah, I did do it before, a Monday Night Raw.
What the hell is it called?
It's like Lane something or it's some sort of…
Lane in the skin.
Not Bolero?
It's not Bolero.
It's not a Bolero.
It's like Pin Pals, but not that because that's a Simpsons one.
Is it Pins with a Z?
It might be something like Pins with a Z.
There are those around.
There is one of those.
I can't remember.
It's a sexier bowling alley than a normal bowling alley.
There was Shaquille's down there, which was Shaq's maybe only good restaurant.
Maybe his only good business.
But Shaquille's was good and then that place closed and is now a much more generic sounding place.
It was really good.
Yeah, you had a horrible experience at that Shaq chain.
At Big Chicken?
Yeah, Big Chicken was gnarly.
Yeah, dear God.
Shaq was not on the ball with that one.
The usual quality standard was not…
Yeah, his Krusty the Clown standard for lending his likeness to products.
Yeah, proves everything.
He's done it a million times.
So, all right, we're getting a good impression of this garage, I feel like.
But what we don't have is enough personal experience.
And not only that, I think this is a failing on our end, Nick, because we didn't force you to come out and experience it yourself.
The first one that you haven't had on the ground experience with.
But it makes you think, what if there was some magical way that you could actually visit the Universal Orlando Parking Garage to walk in the footsteps of Jason on the moving walkway,
hearing Liv and Lovita Loca to relive his happiest memories.
Wow.
What if I told you there was such a way?
What?
We'll see, we'll see.
At this point, it really, this working out now depends on Dr.
Carlson.
Wow.
Well, I have an artifact here that I've been given by a mysterious benefactor.
Remember, this is a video episode on Club 3, and this is where I don't really be feeling it.
Scott and Jason, close your eyes.
It is three layovers.
Scott and Jason, close your eyes real quick.
It will get you to where you are.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's leaving right now.
We're putting you in a car.
Jason, close your eyes, close your eyes.
Jason, close your eyes.
Scott, you close your eyes.
Weiger can look, because I don't know if he knows what this is.
But I've been given this mysterious artifact here that I believe has transportation powers.
And I'm going to place this in front of you right now.
I don't recognize it from the sound.
I actually probably should turn it around.
Or Weiger, if you could turn it around.
Yeah, I'll turn this towards me.
Please call that a handful of bath salts.
All right.
Should I describe what I'm looking at or do I do a mystery?
Well, no, now we can say, Jason and Scott, open your eyes.
Oh!
There is a universal epic universe, Kronos, that is sitting in front of us.
This is a model of the main gate of the new park epic universe, which like this series, is all about portals and jump points and gate holes.
Because a bunch of theme park journalists were sent this, and for some reason we were not on the list.
We were not given this, and we were furious about it, especially me.
I was very mad that we were not on a mailing list.
But this was given to me, and I really appreciate it.
And now I finally, this is why, this is why we have it.
Wow, we needed to wait in order to make this happen.
This is like the Multiverse of Madness' dial of destiny.
Very much so.
It's called a Kronos.
Well, that's not the last property that we're going to bring into this.
Because what if I told you that when you touched this Kronos of destiny,
that it will enable the first ever transmultiversal link to an avatar in Orlando?
I'd say, wow, that's really something.
If there's ever a time for a while.
Well, this is not just science theory.
This is science fact.
We have an avatar waiting in Orlando that should be a match for your DNA.
This avatar's…
Well, only one way to…
Oh, wait, actually.
We're going to have to test this to make sure.
Yeah, we have to test it, yeah, to make sure.
Actually, I have all of his stats.
I have all of the avatar's stats.
Can you just do me a favor?
Can you just move around a little?
Just move around a little.
Yeah, you would move like…
Just like kind of move around a little.
Move your arms.
Move your arms a little.
Wow.
Transmultiversal Virusoids.
You've got them.
Just kidding.
You're supposed to have them.
You need them to make it work.
Oh, that's a relief.
It's a fun little thing.
Anyway, it does seem like your DNA is going to be a match to our avatar.
Our avatar's name is Kevin Tully from a band called Telethon.
We brought him up a bunch lately.
We met him when we were down in Orlando.
He volunteered.
He signed up to be part of this groundbreaking avatar program.
And he is waiting to make the link.
So I think what we have to do first is have you put your hands on the chronos.
Kind of straddle the base of it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just really, yeah, just cup the base of the…
Down at the bottom, below the shaft of the chronos.
Yeah, a lot of people don't pay attention to the base, but you got to make sure it'll work the base.
Yeah, yeah.
If you want to give the tip a little tap, maybe tap the tip.
Yeah, sure.
I'll give a little tap for good luck.
A lot of people forgot to tap the top.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a common mistake.
There's feelings in all of the chronos.
So make sure you're doing it.
Okay, so with that, why don't we have you count backwards in Navi, which is of course,
Quixemunea.
Okay, here we go.
See if we can make the link.
Whoa.
Whoa, there he is.
I think the link has worked.
It's Kevin Tully, our avatar.
Hello.
Hi.
Hi, Kevin.
Sorry, this is all very surprising to me.
You didn't know it was coming?
Well, I mean, I kind of did, but I didn't know it would feel like this.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Now that you have all those feelings coursing through your veins.
Well, that's because we touched the tip of the top and cupped the base.
That's also just the general specter of Weiger I think you're dealing with.
Right.
And actually, I could kind of feel sensory vibrations as you were doing that.
It felt a little weird inside my whole body, honestly.
I feel like I'm being possessed by somebody.
Whoa, whoa.
It's different.
It's not a traditional avatar system and it's not a being John Malkovich because you remain alive.
But you guys are now, at least we're starting to form the cosmic bond.
Right, right, exactly.
And I've been really excited to do this.
Yeah.
And it's an honor to be asked to partake.
You know, and it's been great to get to know you guys and become friends with you.
I'm a fan first and foremost.
And, you know, logistically, concrete parking structure is a really good place to have a FaceTime call on a podcast.
Right.
Perfect.
A really flawless cell reception.
Yeah.
Most of your labor has been like outsmarting and hiding from universal heavies who are like, you can't be doing this.
You can't be here.
That's correct.
And I do have one trepidation, though, that I haven't vocalized.
And I wanted to be transparent with you guys about what that is.
And I think like now that Weiger's in me.
Yeah.
What if he gets stuck?
What if it's a meet Dave or like, you know, Robert Altman's three women sort of deal and like I become Weiger, Weiger becomes me.
Yeah, that's that's going to create a lot of complications for both of our lives, I'm sure.
You're going to have like a lot of like phantom Taco Bell diarrhea on a daily basis.
Yeah.
You'll feel like you have to shit out like two or three pounds.
Right.
Cheesy, gritty crunches.
But you won't get so.
It will probably take me a while to realize that anything's different at all.
If that does happen.
Yeah, that's fine.
This is why we thought there would be a DNA match.
We knew that you would be aligned enough in order to make this happen.
You both have enough sour cream in your stomach that it's a match.
Sour cream lining.
Yes.
You're primed.
Well, I'm a little lactose intolerant.
So no.
So maybe that'll be the indicator.
OK.
Should I should I show you your surroundings?
Yes, you're only in front of the wall as far as people watching this on Club 3 and us know.
So let's see where we are.
Wow.
You guys were back.
Oh, my gosh.
Beautiful.
We're back at City Walk.
We are by the movie theater where I saw Glisten and the Merry Mission.
There's Quiet Flight Surf Shop.
The thing we had tons to say about.
Red Oven pizza.
And you're oh, my God, you're right at the balcony of the public.
Wow.
Look at that.
One of the only well-reviewed establishments of this entire thing.
That I feel good mojo from that.
Yeah, that'll do thing.
Nice things for us on our mission here.
Geez.
How does it feel temperature wise?
What kind of night are we talking?
Well, it's, you know, probably 78 degrees.
It was raining a little bit.
I think it probably still is.
Do you feel raindrops on you, Weiger, right now?
Yeah, I do actually feel mildly damp.
Whoa.
I see it happening.
Because there's a roof above you.
Right.
I think what it is is that I was just sort of like because earlier it was raining.
And so it's probably just some dripping from the rooftop.
Clamminess too.
Yeah, just a general sort of humidity.
You didn't just spill a Mountain Dew on yourself or something?
I mean, yeah, there was some Kirkland sparkling lime.
But yes, I did spill a little bit.
I was about to make a request of something to get a closer look at.
But why am I driving?
That's not how this works.
It is, I think, time to hand over the controls of our avatar.
If I'm saying it, avatar, oh, there's people walking past you.
They made it out, OK.
This keeps happening.
You're in a heavily trafficked area.
For the listeners, by the way, there's so many people walking by.
Oh, yeah.
Not more could be happening right now.
It's the universal heavies.
Oh, yeah.
Looking for you.
This is why Jason never wanted to record here.
Close out your tab and get out of there.
I think it's time to cede control to our avatar.
If I'm saying it avatar style, I should really say Kevin Tully.
So I think, Weiger, you should take control of Kevin Tully.
I feel like, I guess because we're so parking structure focused here,
that's the order of the day, right?
We should kind of just head in that direction.
Oh, this is a good test because you're essentially there.
You have to judge based on what you're looking at how to get there.
Well, I'll.
OK, yeah, from looking at the surroundings, I'm guessing it's not in the direction of the Bubba Gump.
And I'm guessing it's not in the direction of that big marquee.
I would maybe maybe head towards that big P sign I see in the distance.
Oh, smart.
Along with some of their vehicle logos.
It's working.
Oh, it's working.
Wow, there he goes.
I feel it in your feet.
Whoa, wow.
Please, Nick, let me walk faster than this.
Can we see off to the left to walk faster?
Yeah, pick up the pace a little bit.
Really quick.
Don't slip.
It looks a little slippery.
Can you just look off to the left at the signs that show everything that we've gotten to do?
Wow, guys, take it in.
Hard rock, big fire.
So many memories.
Wow.
Toothsome.
Every single place that made us sick.
We're looking at it all at once.
BK Whopper Bar.
This is really the only place that could have ended.
Every end is a beginning.
Every beginning is an end.
We're learning.
We are learning.
Actually, can we head away from the parking structure and go back to that Bob Marley tribute for freedom?
No, no, no.
Thanks for your willingness, though.
OK, now, Nick, you have to choose walking or ramp.
We got to do the ramp as long as it's not you're not going to skid on it.
I don't think I'm going to skid on it.
OK, great.
I guess we'll find out.
Yeah, this is the moving walkway, right?
We got to experience this.
Did you know that British people call this a travelator?
That's a great name.
I actually did not know that.
Well, I was going to ask if I should walk or stand, but I think my decision has been made.
Yeah, I think you're stuck standing.
We're right in prime getting out of the park time.
This is perfect time.
Well, this is really the test of is it convenient to get out of here or not.
Kevin, did you know?
Oh, there's the mini golf course.
It looks so cool at night.
I didn't know how cool it looked at night.
That robot is awesome.
How about that?
Whoa, it's some perfect mirror.
Kevin, did you know that on the travelator in the year 2000, I'm sorry, 1999, that you were able to actually hear hit of the time, Living La Vida Loca, as a young Jason Sheridan did?
No, I didn't know that, Scott.
Well, it's true.
These very speakers.
I'm happy to hear it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Kevin, watch out for the end of the travelator.
Yeah, watch out, Kevin.
But also, what music is playing right now?
What is the atmospheric track that's playing to the speakers?
Give me one second.
I'm very impressed with that because I needed to do it.
They were playing when I was up at LA City Walk, Post Malone covering a Hootie and the Blowfish song.
Wow.
I only want to be with you.
I've heard that cover every time I've been up there.
From the Pokemon soundtrack.
Of course.
I don't have a definitive answer, but it kind of sounds like Dying in Your Arms Tonight, but like a modern version of it.
Maybe it's a Post Malone cover.
I bet that's what it is.
It does kind of sound like that.
It is what City Walk traffic's in, is covers of not that old of songs.
All right, should we keep going?
Yeah, let's keep going.
Okay, we won't go to valet.
You didn't valet this morning?
Wouldn't it be cool if I did?
Oh, it would have been.
Should we walk and not do the moving walkway this time?
I don't want to tell Mike what to do.
No, actually, that's a good call.
Let's see what the pedestrian experience is like.
Let's compare speeds.
If you can cut through the traffic, don't get bumped.
Yeah, don't get hurt.
Kevin, while we're walking, I have a question.
You are the only person on this call right now, on this podcast, who actually has parked in the parking garage.
How was your parking experience today?
My parking experience was a little confusing, Scott.
Uh-oh.
I've done this many times, although I don't typically park at CityWalk.
I have secret places I park that I won't tell you about.
Whoa.
I don't want to miss my spot.
However, today I drove down.
I kind of missed the exit because I was a little distracted.
And I ended up by Endless Summer Resort, and I had to do a U-turn.
And it was a little stressful.
But once I was in, I got in free with my Universal Orlando Annual Pass.
And a nice person named Trey helped me get my priority parking pass that I get as a Universal Orlando Annual Pass holder.
And honestly, it was pretty breezy and easy.
Oh, here we go.
We've arrived at probably the biggest crucial juncture point.
We are now looking at what we looked at earlier in the episode.
Oh, wow.
All of the characters.
There's King Kong.
This is your path, Nick.
Previously.
Of North or South.
Still images are now live video I'm seeing through my own eyes.
Yeah.
Now, is the…
Kevin, did you park at one of these…
Like, did you park at Spider-Man?
Did you park at ET?
Did you park at Jaws?
So glad you asked, Nick.
I parked at Cat in the Hat 361.
I don't want to…
No, Cat in the Hat 361.
No, now I just know it.
So I would say that I wouldn't want to take you on a complete deviation from where your car is.
So yeah, let's head down towards Cat in the Hat.
Let's see what the experience is like.
Nick, I have $25 cash here.
Wow.
If you'd like to visit the Strange Gift Shop or the Fresh Eats stand.
Nick, you could buy a sleeve of a shirt with $25.
Nick, can I move?
Can I go forward?
Yes, please, please, go for it.
Please go ahead and move.
I think, though, Fieger, I think you should dredge something up, though, maybe.
Yeah, let's go, let's go.
I mean, how do you feel about getting a sweet treat?
A sweet treat?
Yeah.
From Fresh Eats?
There's no line.
Yeah, looks like there's no one queued up there.
Oh, and this is Jason's opportunity, too, because he just got upset that we didn't call him when we went to Fresh Eats to do some dredging.
Oh, boy.
Is this open?
It's a pretty good question.
All right, our biggest enemy now is the hours.
Okay, it's the same menu as before.
They still dip it and drizzle it and dredge it.
Wow.
Anything look good to you?
What?
You're going to be tasting it on some level, Nick.
Now, remember, Nick, I'm lactose intolerant.
Right.
Yeah.
No, I definitely don't want to get me and you something that's going to upset your tummy.
There's those pops waiting to be dredged.
Are any of those pops non-dairy or are they all dairy?
That's a good question.
We could ask.
I bet I bet the July bet the strawberry or mango is potentially non-dairy.
Yeah, I would guess maybe that whole right column, the coconut, too, could all be OK.
But then then I'm wondering what is what it's fun to dredge it with because it feels like a.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I forgot about the dredging.
Can you dredge without dipping or drizzling?
Or do you need the money?
Do you need the drizzle drizzle and dip to make the dredge whole?
That's a great.
Yeah, I don't think the dredge is going to hold without the dip or drizzle.
Well, would a would a would like a mango with a milk chocolate dip?
I mean, that sounds like they could be appealing.
Yeah, but if it lacked the milk, though, milk milk chocolate.
Oh, right, right, right.
So maybe like a caramel syrup.
I don't know how I don't know how much lactose is in milk chocolate.
No, it's not an issue.
Milk chocolate won't be an issue.
And you know what, Nick, fuck it.
Wow.
You know what?
And Kevin, you'd be participating in the grand saga tradition of destroying your intestines.
Yeah.
And it's been a while since I did that.
You need to do it.
Refresh the system.
All right.
Wipe it.
Are we locking it in?
Yeah, let's try it.
Let's try a mango with a with a milk chocolate dip.
Wow.
And then is there something fun to dredge it in?
Maybe just some sprinkles.
Do you have do you have any non dairy options here?
Oh, the fruit ice pops are non dairy.
Okay.
Great.
What kinds of fruit ice pops do you have?
One moment.
Yeah.
Yes, I'm here.
Nick.
Yeah.
Can I get a strawberry with lemonade ice pop, please?
That sounds delightful.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello.
I'll do a strawberry with lemonade.
Oh, that's fine.
Blueberries even better.
It's funny.
I think blueberry in my brain.
It's working.
You're melding.
You're learning.
And Kevin, at the end of the transaction, remember to say the orders for me, Nick Weiger.
There's the cash.
Thank you for getting cash out.
Wow.
The harvest cheddar.
It's like we're touching it.
Thanks, buddy.
It sounded just like him.
Wow, it's perfect.
Your brains are fusing.
Now we get to observe a live dipping and dredging process.
The people who are just listening are fascinated and loving it.
Patient about it.
Not writing comments about how they don't like it.
Yeah.
Don't blame it on me.
You're going at a perfect pace for doing a dredging process.
I'm sorry.
I forgot to dredge.
Oh, that's okay.
Don't worry about it.
No problem.
It's wrapped.
Thank you.
Oh, okay.
Well, now we've learned the dairy options.
Wait a minute.
You know what?
I know where you are, Kevin.
You're right near the crushed penny machine.
Look at that.
Oh, it looks delicious.
It's only some dust.
It looks like beef tongues.
It also there's like a slight like slant.
It's like there's a droopy.
It's a droopy popsicle.
It's limping.
It's a little heavier fruit.
Blueberry is definitely not.
Group area is a denser fruit.
Yeah, it's a bit frostbitten.
I think maybe they took I think maybe they don't sell very many dairy free options.
Right.
I don't want to say it.
There's a big vein.
It does look pretty.
It's a droopy item with a giant vein.
Very vascular ice pop.
Oh, God.
I hate to say it.
It looks a little bit diseased.
Like it might want to go to a practitioner.
Well, you just overnighted to me if you're concerned about it.
Oh, it's in your mouth.
Wow.
It tastes good.
Do you both agree on the taste of it?
How's that?
How's that frost on the outside?
Very cold.
Yeah, I would agree.
It tastes like it has the ice crystals around it kind of tastes like I'm eating paper.
It's really odd.
Yes.
Right.
It's gritty.
That's how I'll describe it.
Nick, do you agree?
I mean, you're inside of me.
Yeah, it's kind of like licking the surface of that planet at the end of The Last Jedi.
It's just a bunch of stray crystals.
Crate?
Yeah, of course, Crate.
It is Crate-esque for sure.
This is about a two out of 10.
Oh, that's too bad.
Yeah.
Wait, can we put it in terms of forks?
Are we allowed to do that?
Yeah, no, we absolutely can.
That translates to one forker and the one out of five doughboy scale.
That's pretty bad.
I had a good experience with fresh eats.
That seems like the opposite of fresh eats.
That's the issue.
It's like there was the, like you were saying, the non-dairy pop was trapped in the deep
freeze.
You don't get the drizzle.
You don't get the dredge.
You don't get the dip.
And so you're missing out on a big part of the experience.
And it's super freezer burned.
It's hard to fuck up a simple ice pop.
This is so bad.
I am not that picky.
Well, this has been a failure of the Avatar program thus far.
No, you don't have to keep eating it.
Can I pitch it?
Yeah, I feel free to pitch it.
Wait a minute.
Now I think we should, like Mike Carlson decide how you dispose of it.
Mike, what is a reasonable way to dispose of a treat at City Walk that you don't want
to finish?
Make sure that no employees are watching.
And then as soon as all their eyes are averted, you find the nearest receptacle.
And I don't even see the garbage.
But I mean, it doesn't appear to be just put it in with the minion wands and run.
No trash cans.
This is something we're learning.
Oh, oh, oh, that's surprising.
Just think of quick braille.
So the old souvenir shop minions.
Hey, I can't move.
Yeah.
For some reason, I've stopped here.
I'm going to try to will myself away from looking at Kevin the minion.
I think I broke I've had a psychic break.
There we go.
Oh, my gosh.
Sorry about that, Kevin.
Wow.
Scooby Doo there.
Kind of like.
Scooby Doo looks like he ate a sour candy.
Oh, I see a trash can.
There is a trash can.
OK, OK.
And it's sent.
But it's the other way.
Aren't you now going towards the other parking garages?
It's a it's a worthwhile detour.
How's it looking there?
Drop it.
Yeah.
OK, great.
OK, OK.
And I don't think anyone's thrown into the garbage.
Oh, and look at this.
The coin machines.
We are.
This has been a running theme through the podcast.
We've discussed you.
Maybe you've heard some of this, Nick.
That's right.
Yes.
Whether or not your own actual penny goes into these machines and there's a place to
put in your penny.
And there's the credit card where you will get all four pennies in theory.
This is a fake one.
This is one of those fake ones.
This is this is bullshit.
Oh, yeah.
Kevin, can you just don't attract security?
But can you like punch it or something?
Oh, wait.
Oh, wow.
Oh, he's doing it.
Oh, rejected the dollar bill.
You know, it's maybe better that way.
We go.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Well, why are you looking like you're here?
I think you just get them.
Oh, OK.
Oh, should we see which one I get?
You get four for one dollar.
Oh, we'll find out.
Another one dollar each.
Yeah.
I don't think it's working.
That might have been not enough money and I don't have any more.
Wait, it's starting to get harder to do.
That means I'm feeling more resistance with the crank here on my end.
So it is life cranking.
Oh, there it is.
There we go.
Whoa.
Wow.
Which one do we get?
It's it's Woody's Woodpecker's friend.
Only Jason can know.
Only Jason knows these.
Oh, that's his old mustachioed friend.
Let me look this up.
I just we all love it.
That's what every kid's excited to get in the year 2024.
Is it is his name?
Walter Lance.
Well, that's the guy who created the creator.
It's a good guess, though.
Of course, Woody's friend.
Walter Lance.
They share.
Goodbye, Woody.
Oh, Nick, I'm sorry.
I should have.
There's a lot of time.
It'd be nice to do my own.
But one of these seems to be just the Despicable Me logo.
So these aren't necessarily the most exciting fake pennies, right?
The logo.
Yeah.
If you had to pick one, Nick.
Well, you got grew there.
That's kind of fun.
Agnes is pretty good.
I mean, of course, I'd want the one with the minions, but this one feels like this is designed
to build parents out of dollar bills.
You're going to keep turning them until you get one of the minions.
And in theory, you can select which one you want.
And it is not super explanatory.
There's another dollar going into the machine.
You found another dollar.
All right.
Wait, how do you select which one you're going to get?
You kind of turn beforehand.
OK.
Oh, wait.
I think.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Well, too late.
Too late.
You put your dollar in.
It's OK.
I did.
And it's rejecting it continuously.
OK.
If there's one more try doesn't work.
It took it.
OK, OK, OK.
How do I?
Oh, I think I'm doing it wrong.
No, I think you're doing it great because I think you just turned a little bit more and then I think you're both doing it great together.
That's right.
I didn't I didn't do it right.
And it gave me this one.
I didn't get the select.
That wasn't the one that was selected either.
Yeah, no, it wasn't.
That one was on Agnes.
Oh, boy.
That's really that's really confusing.
There's only one thing to do.
Throw that away.
Chuck it.
OK.
That's waiting for any listeners.
It might still be there on the Despicable Me machine in the garage.
By the way, the answer to the earlier question, Wally Walrus, Wally Walrus.
I thought that was a human man.
No, it is a Walrus.
Walrus is not Walter Lance.
Wow.
Another big it's another reason I knew your DNA would match is that neither Kevin nor Nick knows the name Wally Walrus.
Yeah.
Is it time to start walking to the garage?
I think so.
Let's let's head to the space.
All right.
Past the Duff Beer cans.
We've gotten doses of characters and fun and treats.
The treats didn't work out, but we played the lottery.
And now I really can't believe how bad that ice pop was.
Yeah, I'm I'm really I can't either.
Yeah.
Unfortunate.
I can't get that taste out of my mouth.
Well, it's fine.
Jason is buying a plane ticket to go have that specific ice pop tomorrow.
Nick threw away.
It might still be there.
I can fish it out.
I won't have to pay for a new one.
That's on Kevin's dime.
I'm looking up pictures of a late life Walter Lance.
Thank you very much.
Late in life.
Larry, Google Walter Lance dying.
Oh, wait, are we doing it?
Are we getting on?
Yeah.
We're at a crossroads.
OK.
You want travel later or walk?
We got to do travel later because it looks like we can get some some if we want to get some speed, we might have the potential to do so.
If we want to push past this family, I'm going to need I'm going to need to delay a bit.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, yeah.
Build up some room.
Yeah.
Yeah, please.
Oh, wow.
Look at that.
Wow.
It's like you're flying.
Just it's like huge Navi strides.
I have a 10 foot frame.
Do you finally feel alive again?
Well, everything you were saying about your body and the food and the drinking and that it weighs you down, it's all gone now.
Yeah.
Live and powerful.
Oh, my God.
That was exhilarating.
Like a prime shack.
I can hear in the distance upside inside.
Yeah.
Living the Vita Loka.
Wow.
There it is.
The Bubba Gump Tower.
We're pretty far away at this point.
OK.
Now we have to find our way.
There's the gate.
Oh, my gosh.
We're getting all the way to the outside.
We have to, I guess, find our way properly to your car.
You remember what we do?
Yeah, you were you were in the cat in the hat, of course.
And you were in space 231, 316.
No, it's glitching.
We're losing it.
I had the three and the one in there.
Just in the wrong order.
Again, correctly.
All right.
The thing is, both of you are wrong.
Oh, three, three, six, one, three, six, one.
I transpose you the numbers.
Do you want me to use my Kevin knowledge to find my car or should I go to three, 16?
No, no, no, no.
You're late in Kevin knowledge.
This feels so weird.
It kind of hurts.
Well, it proves that you're still in there.
Yeah, hasn't boxed you out and he's not going to take over your brain and being John Malkovich
out.
I'm not going to be a meat day.
No, that's that's important.
You got to retain you in there as we get towards work.
We're recording this around dinner time.
Kevin, are you starting to feel like you like desperately crave a Wendy's hamburger or something?
Like, what kind of meal does Wiger want right now?
Since we're approaching, you know, five or six.
Yeah, I mean, we're not far.
We're not far from an in and out burger.
I mean, I might be tempted to have something like that, though.
Obviously, that's not something you could easily acquire in the Orlando area.
Right.
That's true.
But if we if we have to we're done recording, you stay linked for the rest of your life.
Kevin could experience it and a longing that could not be satisfied.
The West Coast exclusive in and out burger.
All right.
You're at a crossroads.
I noticed as well here.
Which one?
Well, no, I'm just kind of waiting because this is the last last real glimpse you might
get of CityWalk.
Wow.
This is kind of emotional.
The big dome.
This is where we came from.
This is where we say goodbye.
Gosh, we have to later in the show, we have to say goodbye to the Sectorkeeper.
And right now we have to say goodbye to this place that has been our home for 21 days.
I really, though, I will say from this experience, I'm really getting a sense of how much ground
Kevin has covered.
Yeah.
You've gotten a lot of steps in just moving from CityWalk proper to where you are.
He's showing us where he started.
Yeah.
You've got a lot of steps in, Nick.
That you're right.
I'm thinking about it all wrong.
He's learning.
Double steps.
You know, two men equal double steps.
And that means we're getting shredded in the cabin.
Damn.
Yeah.
That's great.
Apple Watch is going to be very happy about that.
Yeah, it counts for both.
Tell the Apple Watch it counts for both.
I think that everything is so honestly just such a like a great clear signage and clear
places to go.
I would even say of any of the theme parks I've ever gone to, this one just seems like
the most straightforward.
All of this was put together in such a straightforward way.
Yes.
And I was very impressed with it while we were walking around.
Is it our best parking garage?
Wow.
Could be.
Well, here's the thing.
Here's what I'll say.
Yeah.
Is that I still miss the chaos of Universal Hollywood.
There's something more fun still to me to this day.
About the mystery.
To not quite knowing where I'm going to walk out.
And it's happened to me.
It happened to me a few days ago.
It happened to me a couple of weeks ago.
And this certainly Orlando, efficient makes the most sense.
I have to give it the blue ribbon for efficiency.
Sure.
But what does my heart say?
My heart says I want to park Universal LA more.
Yeah, I can understand that.
I want to be in that parking garage.
There's a couple of different ones that are all over the place.
I don't know.
There's something about it.
I like better.
I hate to say that.
I don't want to put it down, Orlando, but I like LA better.
That's just my feeling.
impressed by this.
This feels like it's very well designed and very straightforward.
A lot of signposting, a lot of clarity in terms of where you're supposed to go, provided
you can remember your own space number, which we failed to do.
But here's the thing.
There is one specific design feature of the Mickey and Friends parking structure that
I really like, which is that the escalators go directly from your level to the ground
and vice versa.
It's just really efficient because if you're parked on level four, there's no reason you
would ever need to go to level two or level three.
You can just go directly from the ground to level four.
I don't quite see anything on that level as of yet from the Universal Orlando structure.
All the minions are great.
We're looking at some minions on a bus right now, and that is a hoot.
Why don't we see what it's like to get to the car?
I think that will help you decide.
I was going to say, let's not speak too soon, guys.
Let's not compliment the parking garage until we get to the actual height.
Fair enough.
Well, forward, gentlemen.
Let's forward.
Yeah, let's go forward.
All right.
Here we go.
Now, this is confusing because it says Cat in the Hat is that way, but that's a one-way
travelator.
It's going the other way now.
It makes it look like I'm going to ET.
I hope that's the way you need to go.
I'll knock points off of that.
All right.
The Brits are…
Yeah, let's travel it.
…
linguistic quirks.
Because if you call an elevator a lift, wouldn't you call a moving walkway like a this way,
then, or something?
Would you have it be a little bit straightforward and folksy?
A standy stroll.
Yeah, a standy stroll.
Yeah, 100%.
That's perfect, but you call it the travelator.
No, that's clunky in the same way that elevator is.
It sounds more American.
Right.
Very true.
What is that?
This is a volcano base sign above you, Kevin?
That's right.
The third water theme park.
Volcano Bay.
Well, actually, the first water theme park in existence.
Are they going to do that?
There's all this talk of adding to all the other parks.
Who cares?
I want rides.
I want rides too, but I want water rides.
I bet they could use a fresh eat stand.
I think they could, yeah.
That kid has a lot of beads.
I wonder what…
Is there a Mardi Gras situation happening?
Oh, really?
Okay.
How's the Mardi Gras vibes there?
Mardi Gras vibes are good.
They replace all of the music in the park with Zydeco music,
which is kind of fun, but also some of the original atmosphere is lost,
I will say, because everything is just pumping Zydeco music.
But it's cool.
They have floats go by, and then you can throw beads from the floats
if you sign up, which is an experience I've never done, but I'd like to.
You can be on the floats and throw beads?
Yeah, you can be on the float.
Have you ever done that?
I have not done it.
Don't you think you would have hurt by now if I had done that?
You said something a couple weeks ago I never heard.
So there's still mysteries that have not been reveled.
But they do a version of this at Universal Orlando,
but it's got to be like a sanitized Mardi Gras, right?
It's not like people aren't flashing the parade.
No, I don't think anyone's putting them on the glass.
Well, the minions flash, but we don't understand their anatomy.
We don't know we're looking at nudity.
So it doesn't feel dirty.
Because they don't want beads.
They just want banana.
Right.
What about Toon Lagoon though?
There's probably some saucy comic strip characters.
One of the, like Mrs.
Lockhorn maybe?
I guess is Blondie perhaps?
I don't know.
Andy Capp's wife?
Dagwood?
Yeah, do Blondie and Dagwood have an arrangement?
Yes.
Well, they have an arrangement only for you.
If you entered the cartoon world, you feel that you could get in a couple.
They've been waiting for you to be cartoonized.
Jason, you're a real man.
Dagwood, he just focuses on his sandwiches.
He doesn't even look at me anymore.
You're a man who loves me and a sandwich equally.
You maintain the interests.
You do both.
Balance them.
Now, with all the smoke rising near the Bubba Gump, is that normal?
Yeah, I was going to say it looks a little bit like a disaster's happened.
I'm glad I got out of there if that's the case.
But I think it might just be fog or it doesn't seem to be, it seems to be atmospheric, not so much pumped in or anything.
I think it's coming from the weather.
Is it possible that it's just they've been making so much shrimp?
There's such a demand for shrimp today that the ovens are overloaded and they're just billowing steam and smoke?
Because of the over the over?
I'd say it's not only possible, but likely that that's what's happened.
Sure.
Well, I think that's post the side because we have terrible reviews to every restaurant except Bubba Gump.
So now Posty and Riccobani, the line is way out the door.
Right, right, right.
You were saying it happened earlier.
Could it be the smoke from big fire?
They're always talking about their fire.
They have a big fire at Big Fire.
It might be Big Fire.
That was probably the best place we all eat at.
Yeah, yes, it was.
Yeah, yeah.
If you have serious review, that is the one and loser meal of the trip.
I think has to be let's give the official award to the Flounder Almondine.
Yeah.
Thank you.
It sounded awful.
It was also a real headache for you to get that documentary of you getting it.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That being said, if they want to put it back on the menu either coast, I'll try it again and I'll take it to go and I'll wait even longer to eat it.
Well, should we start heading to the car?
Yeah, let's see if we can make it there.
Let's head on over to space 361.
Is it on this level?
Yes.
OK.
All right.
Wow.
Literally the last.
Oh, it's in the you're in the last row.
Wow.
You really went all the way.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, I think I know how this works.
You got to wonder if the cat that moved in.
What did you say?
What?
The cat that had moved the car.
That's the kind of mischief you would make.
He could have moved it to 361 or 360.
The cat in the hat knows not to fuck with Kevin Tully from the band Telethon, man.
How dare you even suggest that?
Fair enough.
So lutely.
Plus, yeah, I'm sure you didn't give the keys to him.
He would have had to hotwire it.
Well, now we got a crowd of like a lot of people trying to park right now.
Do you?
Does it?
What's the air?
What's the vibe?
Does it feel chill?
Does it feel stressful?
That's, I guess, a big question.
Well, it does feel like a weird amount of people are leaving right now, which is funny
because the parks don't close till nine.
So I guess this is just how it is.
I never park at City Walk, and so I don't ever do this.
I don't know if this is normal or if it's busy or if it's not.
That's Mardi Gras.
Learning this together.
Maybe also if you got young kids, this is about the time when they're tuckered out.
Yeah.
Not everyone can do it full day at the park.
It's a little late, too, for the young kids.
Yeah.
How do you get over there?
I think this is my…
Oh, no.
Turbulence.
I think this is my road.
Wow, wow.
We made it.
I guess we'll find out.
Good job, Nick.
You navigated us all the way in an environment you've never been in.
Yeah, I did my best.
It's disorienting, but now it also kind of just feels natural.
Nick, Kevin, just remember to make sure to get the license plate and the car registration
on camera so you make sure we're at the right location.
And your vehicle identification number, too, the VIN.
Yeah, and mailing address on registration.
Now, Nick, I drive a blue Subaru Crosstrek.
Blue Subaru Crosstrek.
Got it.
Okay.
So we all need to find it together.
I think we do, yeah.
I'm just going to keep…
I mean, I can't stop.
Nick's power is too strong.
I'm locomoting.
I can't stop until you tell me to stop.
Now, I'm having some trouble…
Oh, Jesus.
Uh-oh.
Someone's honking aggressively.
I hope you're okay.
Is that it here?
I am having…
It's fairly dark, the lighting here, so I'm having trouble perceiving color all that clearly.
I kind of see dark cars and white cars.
All right, just start trying the different car doors that you can imagine.
Yeah, just start grabbing.
Guys, I see it.
I see it.
Oh, great.
It's in our frame right now.
Whoa.
And it's…
Oh, no.
Connection's breaking.
We're losing the connection.
Let me help you.
We have to make it to the end.
This is right before the car.
We need to get to the car before the phone cramps out.
With your last ounces of strength, Nick, get us to this Subaru.
I think that's it.
Oh, we're here.
What?
Is that it?
Yes, there it is.
It's the Subaru logo.
This has to be it.
Yay.
No, you, Nick Wires, successfully navigated your way to a Subaru car.
There's the cat in the hat.
The track you've never been in.
Wow.
And there's the cat.
That was pretty smooth, I'd have to say.
Yeah.
Wow.
There it is.
Whoa.
You got a great car, Nick.
So, congratulations.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Kevin, this has been an incredible experience sharing your brain and body and looking into
your inner self.
I realize you probably have some plugs you'd like to share.
Thank you so much.
Telethonband.
bandcamp.
com.
All of our music is free on there.
Go listen.
Wow.
All free.
Geez.
Check that out.
That's fantastic.
Telethonband.
bandcamp.
com.
Kevin, we can't thank you enough for doing this, for participating in this grand experiment,
the first ever successful iteration of the Trans Multiversal Avatar program.
Your bravery has saved the entire City Walk Orlando saga.
We couldn't have closed it out without you, so we thank you for participating in this
grand experiment.
It's all thanks to Nick Weiger.
No, it's thanks to you, Kevin, and to go from being, that's actually my avatar.
What is nonsense?
I'm sorry.
Get out of the fucking way.
All right.
Well, you better split.
Why don't you tap that tip one more time, Nick, and we'll…
Wow.
The connection has gone away.
Geez.
Oh my God.
How do you feel, Nick?
I feel somehow more alive than I've ever been.
Just being able to occupy someone else's frame to share their soul for a brief moment.
It really hammered home what it means to be alive, but also to have my own independent
psyche.
Wow.
What a beautiful message to end this thing on.
Also, I feel generally a little humid.
Yeah, that's going to happen.
We could have picked a better time to do…
Oh, and look at this.
Speaking of feeling alive.
Wow, it's Walter Lantz himself.
It's late in life, Walter Lantz.
With all of the creations that Jason can name, such as…
Woody Woodpecker, Wally Walrus.
Yeah.
Chilly Willy.
Look at Chilly Willy up there.
Chilly Willy, Not Mickey.
Yeah, Not Mickey the Panda.
Not Mickey the Panda.
Does the fish that Chilly Willy is fishing for count as a character or…?
Is that the one from American Dad?
He created that character from American Dad.
He gave the gift of it to Seth MacFarlane right before he died, like Kubrick giving
AI to Spielberg.
See ya.
Absolutely.
Well, this is, as you said, Jason, it's late in life, Walter Lantz.
Yeah, it's late in life, and we have to remember, our days are numbered, much like Mr.
Lantz.
Yeah.
And we have to remember these moments and hold on to them, these moments where we feel
so alive, where we get to inhabit a body across the entire multiverse.
And maybe we all will.
I know we've all been beaten down by this, but that was such a fun little portal.
I don't know.
Some of that negativity is melting away.
I'm feeling pretty good, guys.
Yeah, I think so.
I feel the same way.
Yeah.
I feel, yeah.
Not good enough to start a new saga anytime in the near future.
No, but good enough you can put away a plate of flour and a big milkshake with a slice
of cake on top, right?
Amen, brother.
Let's all get a toothsome right now.
Okay, fine.
All is forgiven.
But wait a minute.
It's appearing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Something just happened to me.
Like something just got sent through the multiverse into my body.
And let's just say for the sake of cleanliness, not through my butt.
I swear it didn't come through my butt.
It just ended up on my person.
But you know, I know it just felt like you failed in getting the collectible coin that
you wanted, but look what was just sent to us.
The three minion coin.
Wow, look at that.
Wow.
And we give it to you, Nick Weiger, for being the finale guest that we needed.
How's the quality on that?
This is, I mean, this is a real piece of shit, but this is the thinnest piece of metal I've
ever seen in my life.
But this is a true token of appreciation.
I genuinely, I really appreciate y'all going all the way to bring this to me.
This is great.
I will treasure this.
Wow, wow, wonderful.
Well, and you better because that's your only payment for appearing on the show.
Yeah, that's fair.
But it's worth 51 cents, keep in mind.
Or more?
Was it a dollar?
It was a dollar.
Well, there we go.
Hey, it's getting more valuable every second.
Yeah, it's currency in Orlando.
Well, with that, I'm so happy to say, Nick Weiger, you survived the City Walk Orlando
Saga multiverse of madness.
We couldn't have asked for a better guest and a sillier thing to do here at the end.
This is so fun.
Let's exit through the plug Kronos.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
You actually do have something I want to plug.
And you know, since we did something special for Club 3, I had something in mind for a
future Club 3 episode.
So let me just kind of just lay all my cards out on the table.
Literally Cruella DeVille, Doc, Christopher Robin, Bachel, Gaston, Gaston again, the
Queen, Judy Hopps, Gumbo Pot.
What is that?
And Winnie the Pooh.
Mike Carlson, Club 3, I want to challenge you to a match of Disney Lorcanas.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
The challenge has been laid out.
It's going to be awful audio content.
It'll be an unlistenable card game we don't understand.
I think you two can play the card game.
Scott and I can do color commentary like it's a World Series.
Okay, all right.
Nick has dropped the Gumbo Pot.
While no participant knows what the Gumbo Pot is or where it comes from.
And we have to assume it has a great power against Winnie the Pooh.
It removes one damage from each up to two chosen characters.
Oh, and Judy Hopps is here like all cops.
She has begun opening fire on Winnie the Pooh.
Just pumping AR rounds into him.
Don't ask questions, shoot him.
What's there coming out of him?
Stuffing, not blood.
He's a vile.
101 Dalmatians are coming right forward.
She's switched it to full auto.
Actually, I do have a Rise of the Floodborne expansion pack deck that is sealed.
Rise of the Floodborne?
If we want to unbox that here.
This is one of their expansion packs.
Yeah, the Floodborne.
I have not bought Floodborne yet.
I just have the first round.
Do you want to do the honor?
You want to open your pack?
Yeah, sure.
Let's do the whole thing here.
This is a good test for how it'll play.
So you'll get to hear the crinkle of the card.
People love that.
People love it.
They actually do.
I'm going to take a sip of my tea.
It's ASMR.
We have a Legend of the Sword and the Stone right here.
That looks like a…
We're right on live.
These are some regular cards.
These are not rare.
Right.
Is it Raya?
Is that Raya?
Raya from Raya and the Last Dragon.
What's the app for the famous people to hook up?
Is that Raya?
Well, here is a card for that app.
Representing an app, not a character.
What a pull, Jason.
Enchantress from what?
Ooh, a little risque for Mike.
Wouldn't you say, Jason?
I don't like that.
I would say so.
He's pushing that card away with a lot of force.
There's a popsicle.
Is that from some sort of dog movie?
Which one is that?
It's an item at Fresh Eats, I believe.
Okay.
Painting the roses red.
Of course, that's from Alice in Wonderland.
Some of these cards, Jason, I'm determining are concepts and activities, not characters.
Again, these are all pretty regular cards.
That's a great underpowered Hercules we've got there.
Mike might kind of undercut the whole thing,
said he's not impressed by any of these cards.
Well, they're good cards so far.
I'm looking for rarity also.
The rarities are the big ticket items and they're also sometimes the most powerful cards.
This is the sword and the stone.
Now we're getting a little rarer, but it's not anything crazy yet.
Pacha.
What's that character's name?
Pacha from the Embers New Groove.
He dropped Pacha.
Pacha is down.
We've got to drop Pacha.
Pacha is unplayable, covered in stains.
Yeah.
We got Tiana here.
This is regular.
This is Tiana, True Princess.
Is this Patrick Warburton's character or is this a different character?
Could be.
Okay.
Now we have some more rare card.
Here's a couple rarer cards here.
Merlin Shapeshifter.
Oh, that's fun.
That's pretty fun.
We've got a Merlin pull.
We've got another.
We've got another Raya or Raya card and that's a rarer card.
That's a leader of heart.
It says.
I'm not sure how I feel about there being the same characters having multiple
rarities that like, like, like I get two different guest stones here.
And to me as a player, I'm just a little confused by that.
I know how I feel about it.
Bored.
And then we have here the last one you have Binding Contract, which I
think is from Little Mermaid.
Oh, that's, that's, I like that.
Cool.
Wait a minute.
It's a cool idea.
Look at the text on that.
Yeah.
The podcast, the ride boys have to do another saga within the next three calendar
years.
Wait a minute.
Oh boy.
What the fuck?
Well, I did sell, I wanted to be a real boy.
So I did make an agreement with Ursula.
Oh yeah, sure.
I thought you looked a little less stiff today.
Yeah.
What is that other card you have in your hand?
It looks like the piece of a puzzle.
It's just sort of, it's a QR code for the game.
Oh, it's a QR code on how to play the game.
It's the rules of the game.
So there you go.
I think an okay pull, an okay pull.
You didn't get anything mega rare.
You didn't get anything crazy, but it's a pretty good pull.
I brought some surplus sleeves so we can make sure these things
don't get damaged in transit.
You do need to, where do you pick up your sleeves?
Cause I need some sleeves.
Shout out to, and this is not in your neighborhood, but shout out to it's
game time over on the West side.
Great card store there.
And shout out to Brett, uh, who reassured me that Lorcona is for all ages.
So it's okay for me to buy.
And he said that while you were grabbing him by the shirt collar saying,
is this okay for me?
Having borrowed a child to bring in, to make it more acceptable.
You asked for a kid off Craig's list.
Look, I've eaten his at Chuck E cheese as an unaccompanied adult for a, uh, for
content, so buying Disney Lorcona cards is nothing.
Parts about having a kid is not getting the Chuck E cheese side eye.
And yeah, it's been great.
Um, but then you don't get two numbered stamps on your hand.
The kid gets one and you get one.
I don't know if they're still using that system they used 20 years ago.
Well, they still have it technically, but they don't seem to put a lot of care into it.
That's my review of the kit check system.
Um, well, this was fantastic.
Thank you for closing it.
And what a, what a seed that you've planted.
We'll figure out.
I got to put together.
You got to make this happen.
Yeah.
All this Walter Lans talk reminds me.
We got to do that.
Woody Woodpecker episode.
So much about.
Oh, I don't remember anything before the saga.
We did talk about doing a walk.
But I think, you know what?
I think it's not a Woody Woodpecker.
I think we could do what he would pick her, but I think first we should do
Walter Lans in his later years episode specifically about the man over 60, when
he was over 60, so nothing he did before 60.
Well, this is the.
I also have real quick.
I have an announcement to make.
Uh, uh, well, I got a piece of information that has been confirmed.
You could smoke a cigarette in cigars in Orlando.
Wow.
So just to confirm it, you could smoke in cigars.
Thank God.
This guy's got the fallen brother.
Wow.
Cigarettes with a Z were allowed in cigars.
That's correct.
Well, this is it.
We're tying up all the loose ends.
Oh, and, and it has been confirmed by more than one person that city walk used
to be the party destination versus a downtown Disney.
It was pretty good.
I found a lot of this is more than one source is back this up.
I would say at least three to four.
Well, it's been confirmed by a lot of people on Twitter that people's parents
certainly can't name more than two Jimmy Buffett songs very often.
Well, who, I mean, this is not a random sample.
I don't think we need a full parents are the generation that would and should
know his music more than any other.
Well, we just asked this recently, so we don't have a full picture.
Yes.
Results are still the next saga will reveal the results of this.
And, and most of our audience did not know the song black balloon.
Yeah, but don't even, you should not have brought this up at the end of this
episode, Joe, you really made a fucking mistake here because that, that anger
in your voice is real.
It's primal real primal anger.
Yes.
We needed a clip of the song in the no, no, we recreated the conditions.
We needed a clip.
Mike, the conditions were you saying the song, the title black balloon.
I didn't know it.
You said, what do you mean?
You don't know black balloon.
I didn't get to hear the song.
Thus neither did the listeners, the same exact condition.
It was a valid thing to do.
We did not agree on this.
We'll be settled in the next saga as well.
In the time it's taken, Nick has packed up all of the cards and we've already
let him go and we should let Jason give one more thing.
Uh, did, was there a stone?
It was the coin.
It was in front of me all along.
That's right.
It's the Liger gets to go home with it.
And now we will leave you Nick and we will, uh, leave the video portion of this.
We're going to turn the cameras off so that we can check in with the sector
keeper and find out what we do now.
Because honestly, I don't know how this ends.
And now we find out boys, boys.
Hey, all right.
Oh, good.
We found you.
Oh my God.
We're, we're at the end.
We've done it all.
We've talked about the parking garages.
Yes.
Thank you, Mr.
Weger.
Yeah, did a great job.
And now we can finally figure out how we can seal up this rift.
And I know time is of the essence, but, uh, and the clock's ticking away, but I
still really quick want to ask you sector keeper, do you know the
goo goo dolls song, black balloon?
Black balloon.
Doesn't sound like he does.
Mike was younger though.
He must've missed that part of the.
It's pretty mixed.
Now sector keeper, you can't just tell us the solution to this all was friendship.
Cause that was your excuse last time.
Okay.
We got to get this thing figured out, seal up that rift so we can be done with this.
So I don't know where do we go and how do we get there?
Is there a jump point?
Is there a portal?
What do we do now?
Well, there's a way, but we haven't discussed it yet.
Okay.
A different means of travel.
A star gate.
Hold on.
Star gates are in place.
I'm used to it by now.
Let's just get in there.
Let's get this done.
Scott, you hold Mike's hand.
Mike, you hold my little hand.
Okay.
Oh yeah, it is a little.
All your hands are so clammy from malnutrition, but it's okay.
We'll do it.
Let's go.
And we're here.
Yes.
Oh wow.
Whoa.
I know this place.
Yeah, but it's CityWalk.
Of course you know.
It's different.
Yes, obviously it's CityWalk.
It's a CityWalk.
Well, I guess it makes sense that it would end all here where it all began.
Hollywood, baby.
Yeah.
Jason, what are you trying to say?
It's not our CityWalk.
Look, there's wizards.
There's Chode Maroney's Sausage Kingdom.
That's right.
It's not Antejitos.
It's Camacho's Cantina.
It's not Abercrombie and Finch.
It's Sam Goody.
That's right.
Fitch.
It's Abercrombie and Fitch.
And it's not.
It was never Finch, I guess.
You're learning, boys.
You're learning.
And they haven't yet put up the sign that says John Lovett's Comedy Club and then
taken away the John Lovett's part.
And then it just says Comedy Club, even though there isn't a comedy club.
None of that is here.
What kind of weird fucked up CityWalk is this?
Look how fresh the paint is on the Johnny Rockets sign.
It's beautiful.
Students are going into the UCLA Extension class.
Yes, the UCLA is finally thriving.
It was true.
Wait a minute.
We're in the CityWalk of the early to mid 90s.
Wow.
What else do you see?
The dancing fountains, of course.
Listen closely.
What do you hear in the distance?
Hey, Stevie.
Where do you want to eat, bud?
Dad, I want to go on eat tea again.
I want to see Botanicus.
Stevie, come on.
We left the park.
We're at CityWalk now.
We need to eat dinner.
I don't want to eat dinner.
I want to go over there.
I want to play in that fountain.
Oh, my God.
That's you, Sector Keeper, and your family.
That's right, Michael.
That's me, little Stevie Keppner,
mere minutes before I contracted the staph infection
that turned me into a ghost.
Wait a minute.
So you brought us back to the moment
before you went into the fountain.
Why?
Boys, you know why.
You want us to stop it from ever happening?
That is right.
Guys, if that's what we got to do,
then that's what we got to do.
We have to get into that fountain,
stop him from getting the infection.
We got to save the Sector Keeper's life.
If we stop that little kid from running into the fountain,
the Sector Keeper we know will never have existed.
Our friend will be erased forever.
Wait, but Sector Keeper.
Call me Stevie.
Or Steve.
Sorry, Stevie.
I'm still getting used to it.
Stevie, is Mike right?
Is that going to erase you?
That can't be right.
No, no, Scott.
That is right.
I need to die so that young me can live.
Stevie, why do you want this?
Weren't we having fun going to church,
horsing around?
It's been fun with you all,
but it hasn't been great otherwise.
I had an abusive cricket wireless internship.
I developed a vape addiction that led to a cigarette addiction.
I won a billion dollar powerball that ended up being a curse
worse than all of these sagas and ordeals combined.
Extended family of ghosts hounding me every day
for cash that I don't even have anymore.
I need to be honest.
It's all led to me never knowing my real family.
Okay, hey, bud, bud,
we need to choose what we're having for dinner.
Tony Romans or Bubba Gump?
Uh, I choose…
I want to be human again.
I want to pet the Boston Dynamics dog at Dr.
Toothsums.
I want to grow older.
I want to have the experience Mike has where
people are surprised by his age because of how youthful he seems.
It is nice when that happens.
But don't worry, I'll grow up and become the human being
I always was meant to be.
I'll live a full life,
but I'll have no memory of our adventures together.
And I'll also have no memory of anything you've said
about the various Starbucks locations.
You won't remember us?
No, Jason, but you three will remember me,
and you, the listener, will remember me too.
There has to be some other way.
This just doesn't seem necessary.
I'm afraid it is, Scott.
In fact, it's extremely necessary.
I choose Bubba Gump.
Okay, let's go put our names in.
We're running out of time.
It's gonna happen in a matter of minutes.
Okay, what do we do?
What do we do?
Do we have the water?
Where's the water valve?
Should we tackle?
We can't tackle a child.
No, no, you can't tackle me.
There's still some security guards here.
What do we do?
Don't wait until the mid-90s.
You can't just tackle a child.
What if we go in the fountain?
Oh, that's right.
We can get in there,
dominate the entire space with our large adult bodies.
Yes, yes, three adults' bodies.
Then no kids can fit.
Boys, boys, you've learned, you've learned.
You need to use your three adult bodies.
Hey, Stevie, where are you going?
I'm just gonna go play in the water.
It'll be fine.
Okay, well, just make sure I can see you
while I'm at the host stand.
Hey, mister, don't take off that bandaid.
You don't want to get that cut wet.
Boys, boys, act now.
I'm about to run into the fountain.
Before you go, though, check your bodies.
Any cuts or wounds?
That's right.
Oh, we can't get staff.
Okay, okay.
No, no, I'm good.
I don't think so.
Yeah, I'm good.
Jason, too.
All right.
Get some scrapes.
We're gonna be staff-free.
But they're scabbed?
No, they are scabbed.
You're good, then.
Okay.
Okay, scabs are fine.
Okay, now we know the rules of this.
I'm about to get soaked.
This stupid bandaid.
I've been wearing it all day.
I'm ripping it off.
I'm gonna let my cut breathe.
You guys, sometimes it feels like this podcast
is a pointless, silly endeavor.
But I think all of it has been leading up to this moment.
Let's go run around in that fountain meant for children
and save a life.
Let's go!
Yeah, let's go!
Boys, boys, yes, you're doing it.
I, I, look at me.
I'm, I'm not going in.
I'm getting bored.
Now I'm distracted.
Boys, boys, I'm running away.
I'm, I'm giving a big hug to Shrimp Louie.
And now my mom and dad.
Oh, what happened, Stevie?
I thought you wanted to go splash around.
I did, but then I saw these three creeps and uh,
oh, can I have one of those red ice cream smoothies?
Sure, of course you can.
Says there's no alcohol in them.
Boys, boys, you did it.
Thank you, thank you.
We did it.
We did what you wanted.
Without a beginning, there's an end.
What was once dry is now wet.
That's true.
Wow, you're right.
Everything you said does make sense.
Wait a minute, but, but look at you.
Sector keeper, you're fading away.
You're getting weak.
No, no, boys, you've given me strength more than ever before.
And now I give you strength to let me go.
Sector keeper, no, no, don't go.
Let him go.
No, he needs to.
Goodbye, Stevie.
Goodbye.
We're going to miss you.
Good luck, sector keeper.
Goodbye.
Until we meet again, my friends, my boys, Mike, Scott, and Jason,
you survived podcast, the ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga,
Multiverse of Madness.
And I did not.
Wow.
Are we back?
Yeah, we're back.
What do we do now?
Let's go take a walk.
Podcast, the ride, the City Walk, Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness has been a forever dog
production theme music written and performed by Mike Carlson, sung by Zach Reno artwork and logo
by Aaron Gardner episodes, mostly edited by Mike Carlson, sometimes by me, Scott Gardner,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Scott Gardner, Jason Sheridan, Brett Bowen, Joe Silio,
and Alex Ramsey.
The video finale was engineered by Wesley Knapp at Forever Dog Studios.
For more original podcasts, visit foreverdogpodcast.
com and subscribe to Forever Dog
shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Listen to all 24 yikes episodes of the City Walk Orlando Saga ad free on our VIP Patreon
tier club three or listen to the sectors you might have missed on the second gate.
All of that at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
Thanks to all our guests, our partners, Anthony Geo, and especially all of you
for supporting this series 21 days in a row.
Thanks.
Okay, seven eight seven Kirkwood.
Do you think this is the right place?
Yeah, I do.
Let's try it.
Hello, can I help you gentlemen?
Yeah.
Hi, weird question.
Are you Stevie Kepner?
Yeah, I'm Dr.
Steven Kepner.
What do you ask?
It's kind of hard to explain.
Sorry, do I know you guys?
Not exactly, but you're a lot like someone we knew, kind of a fallen brother.
Blah blah blah blah.
Sorry, my three sons are being quite the handful right now.
Boys, boys, calm down please.
Thank you.
Can I help you guys with anything or?
No, that was everything we needed.
It was good to see you.
Yeah, really good.
Oh, okay.
All right, well nice meeting and talking to you wherever you guys are.
Take care.
Michael, you too, Michael, let Jason eat his cookies and milk in peace please.
Jason, finish your cookies and milk.
Mike, you had a dessert.
You wanted a bowl full of sprinkles.
And Scott, Scott, did you throw up on the rug over here?
Now, why did I tell you about eating hamburgers and sushi at the same time, bud?