Forever!
Dog!
When your town has made you frown
When your square has made you swear
When life gives you one more punch
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge
You need a place, a place to stroll
With alcohol, a place that features part of the Berlin Wall
Where seam-punk robots sell chocolate snacks
A place where you can tattoo your lower back
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando
Tonight, tonight
A daily, extremely necessary series
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando
Buongiorno, and welcome to Podcast the Ride presents
The City Walk Saga Orlando Multiverse of Madness
My name is Mike Carlson, and I'm just feeling very festive and Italian today
Scott Gardner also here?
Yes, well, Italian is the nationality of one of the places in this, so…
Well, I assume it is, we haven't gotten our assignment yet
I'm just saying I'm feeling that
I think I know what it is, but I'm not totally sure
Right, Jason Sheridan also here?
I am also feeling festive and Italiano
Alright, great
I like the multiverse as if it feed into molto bene
Yeah, of course
Very purposeful
You did, listeners couldn't see, you did like pizza box chef hands
Like the kissing the fingers
What do you call that motion you do with your fingers?
Pizza box chef hands
It really should be a shorter thing, I think
Pizza box chef hands, but you know what it means when you hear it
P B C H
I'm doing P B C H
And if you weren't, for listeners Mike did a quick P B C H
Okay, well from now on, add that to our Wikipedia
That's a cool, you know, it's like LOL or ROTFL
So yeah, I am feeling very Italian, but I'm also feeling like
Oh, there's like a presence here, a multiple, I don't know
More than usual
I think for sure more than usual because we are, should we summon him?
Yeah, let's do it
Okay, please, Sector, how do we summon him?
I forgot
We've been doing it one way, right?
Not every time, I think it's been kind of different every time
And I think you could probably just summon him by saying
Let's do chef hands
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, right
Let's do pizza box chef hands
Hey, we're doing it
P B C H
The sector keeper is here, hey
Hey, Paisanos, Paisanos
Oh hey, how are ya?
Ah, buongiorno
I'm doing good, how are you?
Oh yeah, fine, yes
I'm speaking personally, I am happy that we are past the age of Buffett
I think mercifully we are, maybe, Mike probably feels different
Both of you probably feel different
I was more than ready for that Buffett phase to be over
And I feel like maybe there's better stuff coming for us finally, I hope
I think that's right, but I will say this, I was just a friend of the show
Ted sent me today Pitbull's new song, Thank God, and Jimmy Buffett
And there's so
And Jimmy Buffett?
Yeah, so I haven't listened to this yet, so we're not going to do it here
But I'm just saying, we may have to address Pitbull's new song at some point in this saga
That's all I'm saying
I just want to tease that for later
Pitbull just dropped a song?
I believe so, yeah, it's a new song
Thank, sorry, Thank God and Jimmy, is there a, does that imply it's thank both of them or is it two separate thoughts?
Thank God and, separately, Jimmy Buffett
No, I think it's, I think he's putting God and Jimmy Buffett on the same pedestal
The same, like, kind of importance
That's what I get from it, at least
Buffett does seat at the right hand of the Father
Oh, well, yeah, you would know
And heaven plus that it's
Well, he's new up there, so you want to give him a good seat, at least for a little while
And been born on Christmas, like God's son
Yeah, of course
So I'm glad that he's up there, I'm glad that he's doing good up there
Oh, hell yeah
Is he okay that there's just clouds and it's not water?
Well, you can just kind of like make the clouds, they're like Play-Doh
Okay, so he can mold, he can mold the clouds into water?
Into ships, into water
Into little cheeseburgers that imagine
Yeah, yeah, sure
Hammocks, hammocks
Yeah, mm-hmm
Oh yeah, hammocks
Money
Yeah, I just want him to feel comfortable up there
Well, he's had a lot of money, I assume he had a lot of money lying around, he's very rich
He's comfy, he's comfy
He lied, he was sleeping in a hammock made of money, I assume
That's what he did every night
You don't want heaven to be a downgrade, you don't want it to be that he like
He had it better here
He had it better here, yeah, yeah
Yeah, exactly, so
Well, this is my mistake for, I caused an extension of the age of Buffett by referring to the glad age of Buffett
You screwed it up
But there is something in the air, like the spirit energy, it is a little crunchy, you know?
I feel a little crowded and crunched
Dude, dudes
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa
That was different, what the hell was that?
No, no, no, no, get him out of here
Sucker keeper, who is this?
86, this crunchy asshole
Whoa
It's the VBB, you know me
The VBB, wait
It's the VBB, it's the Venice Boardwalk
Venice Beach Boardwalk
You can't smell baked peach without beach, buddy
He's gonna do shit like this all day
Oh my God, oh wait, okay, geez, he showed up
Because, okay, we have been, we've learned of your vast network of cousins or family members or whatever, other keepers
This is one of my cousins, the Venice Beach Boardwalk
From the, this is the official, the Venice Beach Boardwalk
Yeah, we freed him and all these other keepers from the end of the Downtown Disney World deal
That's right, yeah, if you go listen to the end of the Downtown Disney World deal, we did, yeah, we heard from you real briefly
And wow, here you are in our presence
Great, gratsi for that, boys, thank you for that
Oh yeah, no problem, I'm glad we could help out
I can't believe we're in the same room
Hey, sorry, I'll just be real quick and then I'll just be out of your hair
Oh, okay
Can I get like, I need like 50 more grand
I can siz, you know I can't do this right now
Boys, boys, boys, boys
Sorry, should we edit that out or not?
Did you just ask him for, you just asked him for money?
He asked me for 50 more grand
Oh right, because you said you won the Powerball, but you said all the keepers were hitting you up
All the keepers keep coming at you out of the woodwork
I've got keepers coming, hitting me up, I'm answering, you know how many names in my phone say do not answer now
So you do have a phone, because I was calling and none of this wasn't working
I have a phone and
It goes booboo beep, sorry, this number's been disconnected
It doesn't sound like the normal voice, it sounds like your voice
It sounds like you changed your voicemail to say that
I'm answering and going booboo beep
That's your teller right there, you gotta just use the reel
Or get a recording of what the reel, there's no number sound is
It was an old tactic I picked up while working at Cricket Wireless, my manager would answer the phone there and say that
Wow, you picked that?
That's a good plan to avoid, but you gotta get a more realistic voice, your voice is really recognizable, it's iconic
I know, I know
So 50 grand for, you know, what for?
I'm trying to get a couple more Michael Ferraris
Michael Ferro?
What the hell's a Michael Ferrari?
Oh you mean those paintings, the paint, full disclosure just to like
We didn't want to bring this up
We were contacted by the Venice Beach Boardwalk Keeper
Basically, he heard the whole series was going on
He hit up Mike and I and asked if he could kind of like hang, just get a feel for us and the vibe of the show
And you, I thought you weren't gonna be there, so we could just go hang out
We were at City Walk and we were like, where is this guy?
And you weren't there and we couldn't pick up enough Michael Ferraris
I wasn't there because there's a lien on my house
And I've been trying, I've been doing paperwork all week
Oh wow, well, that's really, I'm so sorry, but he told us like, he just said you couldn't make it
And he said, but it's on, he just said, kept saying everything is on you
That's what you said
It's on me
Yeah, that's what you said
So last time I gave you $50,000, you already bought a Michael Ferrari
The last time before that I gave you $100,000
And you invested it in Royal Match, which we've talked about
Yeah
You gave it to the guys that created Royal Match, the game that traps a king
Oh yeah, and he's like trying to get out and you gotta make sure the water gets dumped in the right place
So it doesn't drown in the room
Right, because you said
Well I'm just trying to save a king out here, found boy, what are you doing with every day?
I'm trying to save my house, man
Oh man, this is really, guys, guys, I'm so like, look, we're trying to do, you know, we have a mission here
We have to rate and review things as well, so I, like, please, like, if we could just keep it for a while
Royal Match, five stars
Not those things, no, it's like the things that, that's why we went up to City Walk
Like we did like, specifically we're trying to do those restaurants, like the ones that we went to
Yeah
That's why we did that with you
And I get, you know, honestly, Sector Keeper, we had a pretty good time, I thought
Yeah
And I, at first I was like, wow, the generosity of Sector Keeper to like get all of this
Yeah, thanks so much
We racked up, honestly
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Yeah, we had a healthy tab going there, it was a good party, we missed you though, buddy
Wait, wait, I paid for this trip?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
That's what he kept saying
Yeah, that's what he said
I meant to say thank you when we started, because we had a great time
I mean, here, maybe, just to like
Vivo Italian Kitchen where everyone knows your name, specifically your name, because there's a tab under your name
Oh, no, Sector Keepo
They just let you run up Sector Keepo's tab, that's me
Yeah, oh, we know it's you, yeah
Oh
We didn't know, I really feel bad now
No, don't feel bad, this is what he does, man
I am kind of curious about these Michael Ferraris though, it sounds like a good investment opportunity
Yeah, that's a painting at this like store where they have all of, that's a new thing in Hollywood
There's a store with all of these collectibles that are signed by celebrities
We can get into that, we're dealing with, actually maybe, and now I feel bad asking you for this
Sure
Just to like, can you just give us, as if none of this happened, can you give us our assignment?
Yeah, can you real quick give me just another $50,000?
Okay, I'm gonna sell you $50,000
Okay, yeah, thanks
Wait, don't, wait, I don't know, should you?
This is the last time, you promise?
What?
Do you promise?
Yeah, what?
Yeah, yeah, no, yeah, no, yeah, no
Do you?
Yeah, yeah, no, no, no
Are you saying no?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, yeah, no
Boys, boys, phase six, sector one, big fire
Antihedos Alpha, Antihedos Omega, Vivo Alpha, Vivo Omega
And Celebrity Authentics, good luck, paisanos
Okay, thank you
Thanks, appreciate it
That's what we have to talk about in this sector
Please finish this sector so we can finish it off and get this guy out of here
Okay, well, I mean, maybe a good place to start would be the meal that we went up and had, that we thought that you were in on
To catch you up, Venice Beach Boardwalk Keeper, with this thing, Alpha and Omega, Alpha means
The first, yes, and Omega always means second
Second
Yeah, yeah, no, we, all right, you know the rules just like we do
It's first and last, we, it's first and last
I thought we went through this, I'm not sure what the second is
Alpha, first, Omega, second, Gamma, third, Delta, fourth
Epsilon?
Fifth
Okay, we're on the same page now
Okay, okay, okay, everyone's got rules
Basically, Alpha is whichever establishment opened first, whether it was CityWalk Orlando or CityWalk Hollywood
And I guess CityWalk Hollywood is part of this too
So Vivo is an Italian restaurant
Just to be clear, in the event that something opened at CityWalk first, that would be called
CityWalk beer
If it opened at CityWalk Hollywood, whichever one opened first is always Alpha, regardless of which
Right, because that makes more sense than just calling it the one at Hollywood
Or the one in Florida
Yes, you're learning, you're learning
Yeah, I mean these are the rules that the, like, the gods have established
Yeah, SectorKeeper, look at him for that, I don't mean to create more tension, but like
So like the Chocolatorium would be like Beta, Alpha
Well, it opened first in Orlando
It opened first in Orlando, so it would be Alpha in Orlando
Okay, but if this Vivo opened first and the Vivo in Hollywood is the Alpha
Is Alpha
This is a bad system, dude
And with every beginning there's an end and every end there's a beginning
And with every end there's a beginning
You know what's weird about this is that almost
And there's also portals and jump points and wormholes
Well that's just true
You guys know about gate holes?
Yeah, yeah, no, he's filled us in about gate holes
You guys know about jump points?
Yeah, of course
Yeah, we've been learning
You up on, like, wormholes?
Yeah
I think we're pretty up on it
And you know about, like, ends?
Yeah
I think so
Okay, yeah
Well, you know about ends, right?
Yeah
With every end there's a beginning
Mm-hmm
Do you know or are you just nodding?
What's this guy been telling you?
We know, I mean, now it feels like you're trying to, like, co-opt all this stuff as your own ideas
We learned all this from the Sector Keeper
Yeah, I mean, it's his stuff, yeah
It's common knowledge
Yeah, everyone knows this stuff
Amongst keepers, so
He's on the level for the first time
He's on the level
Okay, you don't mind
Okay, all right, so
You know what's confusing about this?
And not by, like, when I say level I don't mean, like, sector
Oh, and the level keeper who's your different relatives
Yeah
Okay
What's weird to me is that we have this Alpha Omega system but in almost every case Alpha is Orlando
Orlando
And we even found one where it went the other way
I don't think so
You're learning, boys, you're learning
If Celebrity Authentics opens in Orlando it will be the other way
But they haven't announced anything
I have my own questions about why we're doing that exactly
Okay, so Vivo, it's an Italian chain that Universal made up so that they would have their own that they own
It replaced the previously existing one at CityWalk Orlando which was called Pasta More
That's a fallen brother, it's Pasta More
I don't know if you guys can see this logo from here
If you're, I mean, if you're judging an Italian restaurant on busyness of logo, Pasta More easily trounced Vivo
Which is just kind of a plain word
It just says Vivo
Neon pasta
When you see pasta you say More
Can I have More?
So they opened this chain which is of course, the chef was Milan native Nicola Bellazzi Canale
We all know that
Nicola Bellazzi Canale
We honor Canale
This was 2015 Orlando, came to Hollywood in 2018
And it's kind of like a pre-interview, get to know you
We went up to the, to Omega which is Hollywood with you the other night
Yeah, that was great
I thought it was great
I had a really good time, yeah
I had a great time, we got that, what was that old whiskey we found?
Oh yeah, I took some pictures of them because you insisted on like another round, another round
And I was like, are you sure we can't chip in on this?
You said, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, horizontal
That's right
Is that what you ordered for us?
Which is like a famously, like this was the, and you went for the 23 year
And I should have just let you do it and not looked it up
But we got it, because we're journalists, we have to know
Every one of those glasses was $285
Yeah, we didn't
I assumed you were, you knew about this
Well god, we're 23
Top shelf, they got top shelf liquor
Top shelf liquor in CityWalk
There's a drink at CityWalk, that's $201
Just one
$285
Per drink
Per drink, because that's the top shelf
I mean it's 23
I love it
Jordan, baby, what are we talking about?
That's why you pick it
Yeah, you're right, we gotta do the Jordan to liquors, you said
Yeah
I mean it was fucking great
And then we had to follow it with a round of cucumber coolers, which are like 11 bucks
Yeah
That, was that's much more reasonable
Boys, boys
It was, but it gets a little less reasonable if somebody among us
Looking at you, Venice Beach, where I keep forgotten like seven of them
Yeah, you're looking at me when you say that
You said somebody, but then you're looking at me specifically
I did, I don't mean to cut, but you did, you were into those
You were pounding those down
Yeah, well
You can't get drunk, they just fall right to the ground, they hit the ground
It falls through the shatters, you can't
Keep trying though
You keep trying
You gotta keep trying
And you have to keep
I'm chasing that feeling of being drunk so, I haven't been drunk in so long
You can't get drunk when you're, once you, they don't tell you that
Once you die you can't get drunk anymore
God, that's horrible
You know what, you can get high though
Cause it's smoke and vapor and that's what you are too, so that adds up
That's one thing we're on the same page
Yeah, baby
You guys, you're on this, yeah, I'm watching you bond over that
Feel free to just like, if you like, blow some smoke at each other
I'm telling you, I'm telling you
We're not gonna be mad at all once we're gonna, look
We're gonna draw a share bowl, we're gonna lose ourselves in these Michael Ferraris
They're pretty good paintings, I well agree
I want you to picture like, Anne Hathaway
But she's Catwoman, but she's made of a million points of color
And that's a Michael Ferrari, baby
And I want you to picture
Harley Quinn
But she's Harley Quinn
But she's a million points
Light and color
That's a Michael Ferrari
And I want you to picture John Travolta
But he's John Travolta in that movie he's so famous for
The three?
The three's hairspray?
Which one?
No, no, no, he's got a gun
Gotti?
No, he's got a gun
Punisher 2?
Samuel L.
Jackson's gun
The one from Something With Love, it's by the Taken guys
No guys, he's so famous in this one
He's got a gun
Pup fiction?
John Travolta's got a gun
It's gotta be pulp fiction
Yeah, that's one
Okay
Jesus
It's like the second one we said
No, he's like Grease
You're too high, man
These conversations with him
He'll smoke himself, he's got like a little Casper tail
And he'll put it in his mouth and he'll smoke himself
Yeah, you gotta get high on your own supply, that's what they say
When you're a ghost and you smoke your own little tail
I hate to be vulgar, but is that like sucking your own dick?
No, not at all
What?
Like sucking your own dick?
Oh my god, you hang out with these guys?
Are they always like this?
Talking about sucking their own dicks?
I'm never like this
This is the thing with Mike, Mike makes the whole thing of being like the prude
And then he'll say the weirdest shit sexually all the time
Well, but you're sucking your tail
Seems like this guy's over here just waiting to talk about sucking his own dick
That's not what I'm talking about
Did I grow up on Kevin Smith movies?
Yeah, but that's not me
That's not what I talk about normally
No man, vaping on your own Casper tail is not the same as sucking your own dick
It sounds- It does sound a little ridiculous
Thank you, thank you, Joe
No, when you say it, it sounds ridiculous
When he says it, it sounds sensible
It sounds sensible to suck your own tail?
Well, he's made of gas, you know?
Let's get real, you're not always just sucking tail
Thank you
Puffing on that tail
Yeah
Ripping tail clouds
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you can light up the-
You get some plumes going
Yeah, you slurp the nerp
Torch the briar
Slurp the nerp
So gross
Look, this is- you guys are being gross too
Why can't we acknowledge that we're all being gross at the same time?
Why am I?
Why are you bending over?
Because I'm trying to show you what it would be like
What the frick?
Don't stop, man
Okay, I can't believe I'm on the same page right now
Yeah, no, go on
But when you suck your own tail, you don't go forward
Thank you
You reach back and bring the tail over your shoulder
And around you like a camelback
As if you had like a big sheet under you
And he was pulling the sheet
This guy gets it
So it's like a hookah, it's almost like he has a big hookah
You got like a caterpillar in Alice in Wonderland
Yes, it's like a hookah
See, everyone's on the same page
Catch up, Michael
But there's gotta be a ghost that's sucking his own tail front ways
There has to be one- like, everybody does things differently
So like, that would be an easy thing to do, just bend over
Yeah, if you're a pervert, lowlife, degenerate, you could do it that way
Are we saying that-
I guess you could do it that way
If you do it front ways, like that would be like an erogenous zone
That would give you a sexual feeling
But if you do it up and around your back, that's more like drubbing
Up and around the back, you can do it on the red carpet, normal, bat, and eye
Red carpet?
At the front?
Yes
Get to jail
Go to prison
Yeah
Did you say red carpet?
Are you floating down a red carpet often?
I mean, I go to any red carpet
We went to premiere of Madame Webb
People feel strongly about that film
Yeah, I've heard, I haven't seen it yet
I only have one thought
We didn't go to the red carpet, we didn't see it
Yeah, yeah
Fucking- well, based on Flash as the precedent, Mike's probably gonna fucking love Madame Webb
There might be parts of Madame Webb
Actually, Madame Webb's good!
You know who said it's good?
Evan Susser, cut to Susser
No, I didn't say that, another round of lies
Look, if there's scenes I like, I will say it, I'm not too scared
I'm a guy who's willing to-
You will say that Susser also said it, even though it wasn't true
Look, I'll throw out- well, we debated that
I'll throw out a controversial opinion sometimes, and that's just who I am
And yeah, I will throw out the idea of sucking your own ghost tale
That's who I am, okay?
Look, you guys can be upset with me all you want, but that's just who I am
Sucking your own ghost tale is fine, it's just not the same as-
Alright, fine, I understand
Do it over the back of your shoulder
I wanna get back to these Mike Ferrari's, cause they sound like great investment opportunities
You are so correct, let's talk about Pennsylvania based artist Michael Ferrari
Celebrity Authentics is a store that's- by the way, only at City Walk Hollywood
How did this become part of-
No other place
Okay, I understand that we're covering things at Hollywood that are also in Orlando
That much we've done, but why is this on our plate?
This is only in Hollywood
Ultimately it's an Orlando series
Why did this get added?
Because I wanted to go there
To buy the Michael Ferrari pictures to complete the set
This is what happens, boys, he brought this into the sector
How did we allow a guest ghost to start putting things in the order?
There's so many things that we have to cover just in Orlando
And then some drifter shows up and we have to go do what he wants and make it an official part of the show
Excuse me, this is my home
What do you mean, this is?
We're doing this in my- how, do you mean what, the city, the world?
This aura
The vibe is your home?
The vibe is my home
So if I come at you with any conflicting information
Don't bring that into my home, this vibe is my home
Okay, here's the deal
If you do look at the paperwork of the aura
I did cosign and this is his home
What?
This isn't my home anymore because of- I don't buy- this is some fucking floaty outer space shit
I don't agree with this one bit, I live here
This is what happens when you bring these other keepers into the mix, man
I'm figuring it out, I thought- look, I thought it was fun
We went out and had a good time and had a good dinner, but now I know that was a lie
And Celebrity Authentics was just-
Wait, wait, wait, what do you mean it was a lie?
It was a- you lied about-
Were the smiles a lie?
No
Was the very small chicken panini sandwich a lie?
That I would have assumed would have been, you know, long like a panini
But was in fact short and round like a Hawaiian roll?
Was that a lie?
There's no lying about that, I saw it with my own two eyes
You had the teeniest paninis
So this is your order at Vivo, just to be clear?
That's what he got, that's what Venice Beach Borough Keeper got
Pappy Van Winkle, Keep It Coming 23, try to get that, follow it up, Cucumber Coolers
Pappy Van Winkle produced in very small quantities
So that, a bunch of it ended up at the Italian restaurant at City Walk Hollywood is very interesting
That's why I feel like we gotta keep getting it, cause you never know when Pappy's off Tappy, they don't got no more no more
You do have to make sure
I'll go back to the Tappy if you can assure me that you are paying for it or let us pay for it too
It was abusive to the sector keeper to charge it to him
First of all, you can pee in the ocean for the same reason you can charge things to the sector keeper
He doesn't notice, he's got so much money he doesn't know what to do with it
Hold on, hold on, have you told them about rubber ducks?
Ask this guy how many rubber ducks he has
We're spending, we're looking for things to spend money on
Hey, sector keeper, how many rubber ducks do you have?
How many rubber ducks do, okay
In California?
There you go, see, it's got state specific duck collection
How many different states do you have a collection of rubber ducks in?
Continental?
Oh man, he's, god
Whoa, you have them in Alaska too or Hawaii?
This guy's pleading poverty, he's on the 1% of 1%, Powerball changed this guy
Really?
I didn't know, he seemed like he was the same, he seemed humble and he seemed like he's still the same ghostly male
No, no, no, he used to be, I called up him, he'd answer the phone no matter what
Now it's, boop, boop, beep, we're sorry, this call did not go through and leave a message and I'm not here, okay bye
Okay, he's really giving you the business sector keeper
One of the tells was me saying this call has not gone through but also leave a message
That's on me, okay, yes, I was looking for a way to dodge this guy because I haven't heard from him in 20 years
And then I win the Powerball, which yes, a billion dollars, one of the billion dollar Powerball jackpots I did
But after taxes and you take the lump sum, it's not a lot of rubber ducks
First of all, look, you gotta take the lump sum, what are we talking about, you gotta take the lump sum
The annuity we've already established that every three months is an eternity for me
For you it's three months
You're getting a lot of rubber ducks and you've got so many keepers coming at you
Yes, exactly
Every one of those guys that we heard from the Horton Plaza keepers, Bugganyard needs burrito money
I mean like if this is just one of the dozens of ghosts coming at you, I feel terrible
I feel terrible for you
I'm gonna be alright
You can get a Van Hathaway Michael Ferrari for like $2,499
Is that the real price?
Mike, can you explain Celebrity Authentics?
Celebrity Authentics was a website for many years apparently
Basically they're a warehouse somewhere
But they have all these different memorabilia signed by celebrities
And they have different pictures and stuff with signatures
And then they also have a wall dedicated to an artist named Michael Ferrari
Pennsylvania based artist Michael Ferrari and you can get it for $2,499.
What are we worried about?
$2,499.
Yeah, $500 bucks
And yeah, there's some high ticket stuff here in Celebrity Authentics
Well, I just want to confirm just because VBB
There was a news story going around
A woman wrote an article, she's like an advice columnist for The Cut, New York Magazine
Sounds real
And she was convinced to withdraw $50,000 from her bank account
And put it in a shoebox and give it to someone who pulled up in a van
Is that?
Are you asking if that was him?
Yeah, were you trying to use that to get Michael Ferraris?
The thing about Michael Ferraris is they're most beautiful as a set
You know how sometimes when you buy a painting from an artist you put it on a wall above a fireplace
Or you put it next to the Titanic Boutique
Or you put it next to like
You want a triptych of Michael Ferraris?
What's that?
A triptych is like a set of threes
No, that's not enough
You have to have a grid
Like an Instagram wall, but on your actual wall
You want a wall that's 100% painting penetration
There's not one bit of wall not used by Michael Ferraris
Of course there is because there's a grid, Scott, listen to me
The grid is the delineation between the paintings
Take a suck of the tail, you're coming in hot
I'm the host of this show
You're in my home
This vibe is where I live
If we're saying vibes then in some broad context maybe
But this is my garage
I am like, my wife had to park on the street
We had to move our whole process had to happen so you could be in my home
Wait, you kick your wife out of the garage so you can do this?
She just has to like step away from her child and go move the car
Which is a little bit of hassle for her
It's not a big deal, I'm just saying
It's one of the little things that lets us do this podcast
Do this, your wife has to move her car and stop being a mom for a bit
That's what you're telling me to happen
That is what the cost of doing podcast the ride is
I know it's not that crazy
I prepare the room for you guys to come over
We move the cars, I sweep some of the leaves out of the way
It's not hard to be ripped off by this guy
I'm just saying as someone who is famously labeled as a deadbeat
I think, you know, look in the mirror mon frere
Because like, I would never, if I had a wife, I would never tell her
You do have a wife
If I had a wife, if I had a wife, if Jenny calls me, if I had a wife
Listen, I would never be like, you need to stop being a mom
So I can talk about Vivo Italian Kitchen
Wait, so this is how I provide for my family
You're going to question the kind of man I am, the kind of husband I am, the kind of father I am
This is making, where are we?
Let's not talk about that, let's not get into specifics
Can I borrow like,
It's nowhere near powerball money, that'll tell you that
Well no, but you got like, you got like 1500 bucks?
Not for that, we will give you a small guest fee, but it's not going to be that much
You can get a Margot Robbie autographed Iron Studios Suicide Scott Harley Quinn 12 inch statue for like $14.
99.
That's far above what we've given the most famous guest ever to be on this show
We've never gone into that dirt
You keep formatting it
Bobby Moynihan probably
QVC type prices formatting
I don't write what's on the card, it says $14.
99.
That's how you save almost $1500
Well look, I'm kind of coming around, because if I'm getting the Anne Hathaway Catwoman
I'm going to need the Tom Hardy
Should we stop for a sec?
Yeah sure
I guess
Hi, how you doing?
Yeah
I don't know if, we might need to just do a hard edit there
If you just start a harder edit than we would usually do, here's what happened
We've been recording in my garage
For this kind of this whole series
And for the first time ever
You know cars go through the alley here and there
Poor paws here and there
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Well for a truck to go by or whatever
But for the first time ever there was a police car
There was a Burbank police car
At Burbank PD
And the car pulls up and says
Are you guys making a bunch of noise back here?
And we said, well we're podcasting
And then the police officer said
Are you doing a lot of yelling and swearing?
No, I believe that throwing a party, screaming and cursing
Screaming and cursing
Thank you for clarifying Venice Beach
Because you've got to be careful, you've got to like
You've got to, the details are important
You've got to remember everything, you've been through this
This has happened to you I'm sure
Yeah, you're being hassled constantly by the cops
This guy's been detained more than anyone I know
That's my home man, that's my vibe
One of his auras is the Venice police station
Basically that was, we got the police called on us
And when the call said that we were screaming
The podcast arrived first, the police were called on podcast
This is true, by the way, this is not K-Fame, this is real
You can all attest this actually just happened
This is absolutely real, this absolutely did happen
The aura
We suspect it is because Michael was talking too much about sucking his own dick
I told you, I told you to get it under control
You did, but yeah, you're right
I don't want to go blaming here
But yes, I'm a little agitated because this is by the way, Mr.
Keeper
My home
That's what I said
Something tells me that if the police had come up and said
If they had asked you, you wouldn't have suddenly said, yeah, this is where I live because it's my vibe
I was about to, but you said it first
You didn't let me take that first
Sure, sure, you were going to tell the police something about vibe
That wouldn't have been suspicious whatsoever
I don't tell the police anything
That's actually smart, yeah, that is probably
I don't know how to handle the police, we're good boys
This is where I live
You show up for one episode and the police arrive
This is why Jason never wanted to record at City Walk
This is exactly what he thought would happen
That's right, he did call it
When he got really upset several times, one of which was counterpoint you were wrong
Yeah, right
Suddenly, now I understand
Now I understand what this was all about
Jason was right
I haven't even figured out what triptychs I need for my dark knight
You know, I know I need
Michael Ferrari triptych
Okay, let's walk through it
We're doing Catwoman obviously
Yeah, and Halfway Catwoman, Christian Bale, Batman I'm assuming
How about like, let's jump franchise, right?
Okay, yeah
Let's, maybe the third one is Margot Robbie Harley Quinn
It's right there, of course
Can I just say one more thing about Burbank PD?
What just happened, yeah
Just one observation
Because my back was to them and then I turned around
The look on their faces when they thought they were being called to a party
And they saw maybe the dorkiest fucking thing they've ever seen in their life
Was the five of us sitting recording a business
Little lawn chairs
This singular moment made them question their careers more than anything that has ever happened before
There was like a deflated like, oh, what is this?
They were looking for it, they wanted to shove some faces into the pavement
They were going to go hippie busting today
And they were like giving us the answers to the test
They said, was anybody screaming in person?
And we said, well, I don't know, it's just this, you're looking at it, it's a podcast
They're like, okay, so you did not, there is not a loud party happening here
And like, yes, that is correct
And they're kind of like winking and smiling
They filled in that sheet for us
It's like, if you want to come to the party, subscribe to the second gay man
The party's behind the paywall, mon frère
That's where all the best parties are, you gotta pay to play
This has never happened, by the way, I just want to say the Venice Beach Port
This never happened before, you're the reason
This happened, it changed the vibe, we're all yelling about dick sucking
Don't read a view pointing at me, I did not bring up the dick sucking
You have this whole thing
I'm just saying you inspired me
Hold on, is this recorded?
Yeah, it is recorded
Then we're gonna run it back and check
I just admitted it, so I don't know what we need to do
We already had the stuff for the police, we're not gonna go back and check the tape
We can look at it later
What is this, a goddamn Geico commercial running it back?
You were talking, it wasn't sex, but you were talking about drugs
That added to the agitation, I think, about smoking
You cannot stress enough that marijuana is legal in the state of California, you fucking narc
Okay, that's true
I'm gonna pin you on legal substances
After we drank so many Pappy Van Winkles together and followed it up with cucumber coolers
and followed it up with teeny paninis
We should remember about it, having the drinks and the teeny paninis
But he lied about who was paying for it
That's true, but I had a good time
I did not lie, Sectorkeeper is and did pay for it
What is the issue here?
I think, honestly, the Pappy Van Winkle, that was expensive
But his teeny panini, as he calls it, I feel like it bounces out because it was a smaller sandwich
It was quite small
It's much smaller than you think it would be when you order a panini sandwich
Then we got so many rounds of that
Remember the Straccino Crescenza bread?
You kept saying, more Crescenza bread
More Straccino Crescenza bread
What is that?
It's like a bread
That's also a Viva?
It's bread and oil and it's nice
You could have had some of you answered your phone
Boo boo boo
I'm sorry, I'm lonely and spending all my money on rubber ducks
It's the most tense, I was feeling so tense before even the police presence
Even a nice police presence
Let's do a guided exercise where we all relax a little bit
That's a smart idea
This is Venice already
Let's get some Venice vibes going, let's get Titanic Boutique going out here
Everyone close your eyes
I want you to just picture a big blank space
A big white void, very heaven plus-ish if you know the way to go
I want you to start filling in that white void with little dots of colors
I want you to let those little dots of colors take the shape of a face
Take the shape of the face of Jaddy's little monster
There she is, it's a Michael Ferrari Margot Roe
It has only 20.
God damn it, all you think about, even your little exercises are just Michael Ferrari
But don't you feel good now?
I do feel better at least
You seem preoccupied
No one says prices like 24.
99, 99 to say $2500
I don't think these paintings are good
There was something I was supposed to keep my lips zipped about
But I'm going to say it
I watched this guy buy a Michael Ferrari of Ray Charles signed by Jamie Foxx
He bought it and took it home with him for only $1,999.
No I did not, I said I took it home for $10.
99.
My Michael Ferrari, my Michael Ferrari of Ray Charles
What am I supposed to do, get it signed by Ray Charles?
Well you could actually because you have access to heaven
Yeah but you can't use a pen up there
Oh is that true?
Can't get drunk, can't use a pen
Probably autograph something with your own tail I bet
Maybe, I don't know, I wouldn't know
Do you hang out with these guys all the time?
I mean
Because these two seem like pervs
This one seems okay
He was pointing to Jason when he said this one seems okay
Jason's the perviest of the three of us
Jason's the most perviest there is
There's a time and a place
Jason's tale was when you pointed at both of them and called him a perv his smile got bigger
His heart grew three sizes
He just did this in an episode, we recorded an episode recently
We were talking about what if we were in a tunnel of love with a mirrored ceiling and you could watch your friends making out
That's what he said, Jason
His tongue went out when he just thought of this idea
It's a cartoon wolf
Well it's there for a reason
But there isn't there, there wouldn't be a mirror
You put it there, now you're watching your friends make out
Tunnel of love has got to have the mirrored ceiling otherwise how can you see your friends make out and put out your tongue like a big wolf that just saw a cartoon hand?
Yeah, see how the other people live
There's barely tunnels of love, there certainly aren't any with mirrors on the ceiling, there doesn't gotta be any
Yeah, hall of tunnels of love of mirrors
It's like Tommy Lee's tunnel of love
Oh he's cool
Or Nicky Six
You don't like Tommy Lee, you're trying to impress the Venice Beach border, you're trying to get into his vibe
You've never said a positive word about Tommy Lee in your life
He likes two musical artists, the New Pornographers and Lawrence Welk
These are the only two he cares about
Well it's very theatrical, they both went on a hell of a show
I don't disagree with that
Jason what would you do if the New Pornographers played a set on Lawrence Welk while he blew bubbles?
Well you'd have to get him down from heaven, it's Lawrence Welk a keeper
Oh yeah yeah yeah
Did he die at a mall?
There are these things, there are Welk resorts, that is a place you can go, there's a golf course and little shops
So that is something that we could do
So that means therefore there would be, you'll probably get hit up by the Welk keeper in the next couple months
Trying to take you for more of that duck money
The new Lawrence Welk show, Roku channel exclusive
Wait you're saying the ghost is hosting?
Yeah the ghost is trying to get some startup money for production
The ghost is hosting is a good catch line
Yeah that is
Is that what it's called?
Yeah a catch line
A catch line?
I guess that's like what Mom would call it I think
A tag line that is a catch phrase
It's both of them
What I was trying to tell you is that he said Sgt.
Cooper would happily pay for this
You bought him a painting of Ray Charles signed by Jamie Foxx
And now that I know what actually happened I don't think that's right
This is my afterlife story right now
Thank you
I'm just, yeah I mean we'll figure it out
We're just two good friends figuring it out
Can I say that the people who worked in Celebrity Authentics were very nice
But they were really desperate to have somebody purchase something
Aggressive as if they all worked on commission which cannot be the case
Everybody was acting as if no one has bought anything yet in the first few months of operation
Someone walked up to me and I was, I just, for approximately two seconds
I had been looking at a BB-8 that was signed by all Star Wars participants except the people who voiced BB-8
Right
But it was like 17 other people
Nothing to do with BB-8
No actors, I think mostly we think crew right?
Yeah a lot of names I had never seen before in my life
But no there was like Adam Driver and Daisy Ridley
But I've been looking at it for two seconds and then somebody comes up like you must be a Star Wars fan
And I'm like sure and she says what's it gonna take for me to get you a
What's it gonna take?
Yeah she did like a car dealership line but about a $7000 signed BB-8
At CityWalk Hollywood?
Yes, it seems like you can haggle at CityWalk
It's ridiculous because for like less than half of that you can get any of the Michael Ferrari art for that
Well that's true yeah
I do, I don't love it but I like it more than this expensive ass BB-8
What's the most expensive thing there?
It might be that, $7000 BB-8
And then I was like does anyone buy this?
And she says oh mostly like the frames, see those frames?
Check out those frames
But then she said that somebody like, I don't know this guy did walk out here with a bunch of stuff
Including one of those BB-8s and he had to get a car to come here and pick it up
Because he had to take all that back to the Philippines with him
That was him
Oh that was him?
Yeah I mean like the guy that I got it from was from the Philippines but yeah
The Philippines keeper
Oh the whole country?
They just have one keeper
Oh wow okay
Well he picked it up for me, well I'm not gonna go get it
I don't have room in my van for a Michael Ferrari, it's full
What's it full of?
$50,000 that I got from this other lady
In cash?
Yeah in pennies
Pennies?
Yeah
I don't even know, could that have fit in a car?
Yeah how could that fit in a shoebox?
But it blows the tires
It's too heavy
It's riding low
So do you like, it's like it's over a float so like pennies are spilling out as you drive your van with no wheels down the street?
Yeah you're picturing it correctly
Okay so just the axles are grinding on the pavement and then pennies are spewing out of the car, the windows
Like someone's trying to move Scrooge McDuck's pool, yeah
The money bin is like being moved but by one single van
Okay it seems I don't know why you're doing it
Well what am I supposed to do, take it to a bank?
You can't trust banks, you gotta keep your money on you
So you have a bank on wheels?
Oh not wheels but
I have cash on hand, yeah on rims at this point
And he's not FDIC insured, he'll tell you he is
Never, you can't make me get FDIC insured
Yeah you hate the FDIC, I heard that, I didn't know that about you already
He waged a Twitter war on the FDIC
Yeah back when it was still Twitter
At FDIC, you're talking to the guy doing the FDIC's Twitter account
Does not like me
Did you do this back when you were alive or when you were a ghost?
No, ghost
Okay
The police are gonna be back here for one reason or another
If it wasn't gonna be for the noise, for the screaming and the dick sucking
It's gonna be on behalf of the FDIC
How much longer can we keep this guy here?
I don't know, FDIC is federal, the cops wouldn't show up
You know what's crazy sector keeper is that this one is where after all this talk of horrible restaurants that made us sick
This one is the one where there's a place called Big Fire
It just is good, we went there, it's a really good restaurant
I tell you it's a Pacific Northwest vibe
This is in Orlando
Big Fires
Here we all are
Look at us, yeah with the level keeper
The level keeper's there
How much do you miss the level keeper right now?
Night and day compared to this dude
He's a good boy, he's a good boy
Why are you talking about me like this in my own home, in this vibe where I live?
Because the police were here
Not because of me, because of this degenerate over here
We've done plenty of open door episodes where Mike said weird stuff
I've said weird stuff a lot
You know what always happens, it's always like, we'll talk about some rollercoaster, I went on Viper and I like the way Viper felts me up
Viper really felt me up, Mike will say
And then I'll say that's the weirdest phrasing I've ever heard and you'll act aghast
Like that's an adorable thing to say and then we start screaming about that
But the police have never caught me in one of those instances
I get, my voice gets very loud when I start talking about Chase Meridian from Batman Forever
And that, this has never happened before
Yeah, I don't know, VPB, you're just doing something to this aura
Like the air is just crackling with energy
Look, I can't help it, I'm electric, that's just who I am
Scott just seems really like irritated
And I'm really irritated
Finally, after all these, day after day, we've talked about these awful restaurants
And then here's one finally that was like, this is great
By the way, if you're ever going to City Park Orlando, this is a great restaurant
Finally, we found one, we found a good one
Here's what's funny, I like everything, I like Antejitos a lot
I've gone to Antejitos multiple times
That's, I don't want to be mean to my beloved Margaritaville
But like, sometimes just going to that bar to have a drink before you go to the park or go to Horror Nights is just what you want
I love Antejitos, it's maybe better
Table side guac, at least the Orlando at Alpha is awesome
Big fire, good, great, good to great
And then we feel this energy, like we're rushing through it
And then Vivo, I had a calzone, it was too big, I ate all of it though because it was delicious
And I added mushrooms to it, and it was not, they allowed me to add mushrooms to it
I thought it paired well with the Crescenza bread
It absolutely did, I mean they were very
The Strattino Crescenza bread
Strattino Crescenza bread is very similar to the calzone as well, it's like a bread and almost the same thing
The Strattino Crescenza bread is bread folded over in a crescent shape with cheese in the middle
Yes, that's true, I'm just saying
That sounds like a calzone
That does sound like a calzone
It's very similar
This guy's mansplaining over here about Crescenza bread and Michael Ferrari
You just know everything about everything, don't you?
Food and you're so cultured
I've never seen this side of Scott
I've never gotten mad on this part
Never once
BPD got called on the dang garage
They do call the BPD on VBB, that does happen
Well we're talking BB8 and the BPD comes out because you're BBB
You're being a D, you're being a BD, a big dick
What is with this podcast and talking about Ds?
It's not something we normally do
We're not, we're so clean boys
Sectorkeeper said this is a place with good boys
We're squeaking clean
They are good boys
You said you're going to have a good time, go
This isn't Dull Boys
You said just go to Vivo Italian Kitchen, it's on me, it's fine
Drink all the happy fan winkle you want
Follow it up with some cucumber coolers
All the sizes for the entrees are normal
And it turned out that some of those things were lies, but the food was fine
I never said that
Here's what I'll say, it's celebrity authentic
You can buy Laura Dern picture of Ali Sadler from Jurassic Park or Admiral Holdo from Last Jedi
But they're the same price, they're both $399
Do you guys think that depending on
Or as you would say, $399
$399, $399, $399
Do you guys think that somebody's maybe iconic role should be more
I'm not saying Holdo isn't iconic to some, but I think Ali Sadler is probably more famous role
Here's the thing though, what you don't know is that both of those people are played by the same actor
It seemed like he'd set that up, it seemed like he did explain that
But then there, but hold on though
There are so many unsigned pictures of Justin Long you can also buy
There are a lot of Justin Long pictures there that you can buy
I had missed that, wow
In the J section, in that part of your shelves you pull out
There's a lot, okay, there's a lot of Julie Newmar
Who's Catwoman on the 60s badminton show and there's a lot of Justin Longs
I wish there was a Michael Ferrari, Julie Newmar
I could put it next to Ian Hathaway
He's still a lot, you could get him to commission one, I think it'd probably be pricier
You won't return a single one of my calls or emails?
Oh wow, is he, what is his also like a beep beep beep
Yeah, what does it sound like
This number formerly belonging to Michael Ferrari doesn't work anymore
I just emailed at michaelferrari.
com
I don't have any reason to know what his email is
Just an ad with no start?
Yeah, you're not gonna get a hold of him if it's like an email
What do you mean?
It's probably like michael at michaelferrari.
com
Well his name's not Michael, Michael Ferrari
Well that is a fair point
Jason's middle name is Michael?
That is true, my middle name is Michael
Yes, and his name is Michael
And my name is Michael too
And his name is Michael's first name
My middle name's Beach
Oh is it really?
It's not just a designation, you just are Venice Beach Boardwalk
Well it's my whole identity, so you know, identity, name
I guess it gets into what you think a name is
Do you like live in a domicile there?
Do you, to start using these cop terms
Do you like have a roof over your head or do you just go sleep on the beach wherever you find?
I mean, Van's got a roof but like my home is my vibe, so I'm home now
This is Scott's garage
That's right, that's right, okay
But normally, like, yeah, I'll sleep under the stars, I'll sleep under the sand
I'll sleep in the van
It doesn't really matter
I'll sleep on the roof of Celebrity Authentics
Did you do that that night we were there?
Well yeah, just to see if they were getting any new Michael Ferraris in from the shipment
Because they don't reload that thing in the middle of the day, they wait for like after hours
Because they know their prime heist location
Well because they got a big Brinks truck with armed guards loading in the new Ferraris
Loading in the Ferraris and the big sort of like half bust of Predator
Just like the top half of Predator
You don't want the whole Predator because you never know when that could come to life
Yeah, if my Predator comes to life I want it to have no legs
Because then at least I know
You got a little bit more of a chance
I got a radius where I'm safe
He still has gauntlets on his wrists though that could shoot things
Don't get me wrong, Predator even with no legs is going to be hard to put down
But legs in his game over
There is like probably more like a 30% chance that you could defeat the Predator if he had no legs
This is all contingent upon of course the bust coming to life and attacking the Predator
That hasn't been in a film as far as I know
Although maybe one day
If they made a film of that there would be ample Michael Ferraris paintings about that
That's true, yeah
Alien vs Predator vs another Predator with no legs
I know who my bet's not on
What about Adam Driver's
Didn't he make a Ferrari movie?
What if you combine that with Predator?
Am I wrong?
No, that's out now
That's out right now
For Ford vs Ferrari?
Ford vs Ferrari vs Ferrari
That was older
As tributed in a painting by Michael Ferrari
Yeah, Ford vs Ferrari
A car racing against another car against a Pennsylvania based artist
So he himself is in it
And he's racing on foot?
Yeah, he's running fast
Is he painting while he's running?
I don't know
I don't like the questions your friends ask
Could he have some sort of a rig?
What the show is?
It's an interview
It's a discussion
Everybody else is totally fine with the basics of what it is
Boys, boys, boys, boys, boys
Yeah
What else was in the sector?
I don't remember anymore
Well, Big Part, Anahito's
I think it was a good smoked old fashioned
It was great
I don't feel like there's any place
We got a video of Scott's Kooky drink
Yeah, you got a little presentation there
Better days
Big Fire feels like you're going to like it
That's like a thing you would celebrate with a family
That's a legit place
In Orlando
Fire Grilled Chicken on the Cob
It was a little dry, I'll say that
Chicken on the Cob?
I had a Cob Salad
I am on that
I could go for some Chicken on the Cob right now
Just a bunch of corn is wrapped in chicken
You throw that into fire
Maybe you got a little bonfire going
Drizzle a bud light on there
That's Sunday night, baby
I like the idea that Jason when he has a drumstick
He calls it Chicken on the Cob
Any food that you gnaw off of a food is on the Cob
He spins it around
Everything should have Cob though
I agree, yeah
Popsicles on a Cob
Pops on the Cob
If you need a Popsicle like
Corn on the Cob ever?
Does anybody do that?
Jason?
You got a Bomb Pop and you just eat it sort of
I feel like then my left hand gets sticky
The right hand
You need two sticks now
Or you need to sort of like
Proceed in the Popsicle eating to the point
Where you've got the top stick popping out
Bite off the top
Or you can bite it off you little freak
Yeah, you could do that too
You were the one who suggested it
No I didn't, I said eat it normal
You can swirl your little ghost tail into a little
Like a soft serve and eat it
Oh now we're talking
If everybody starts yelling about
Bite off the top
You start screaming about it, the cops are going to be
Right back here
Jason's getting his phone out
Jason what are you dialing?
He's just talking about using your tail
As a soft serve
There's going to be trouble if they call him again
The one time they let it slide
They helped us out, but if they're back here
And they know that this guy is like
I mean I have
The fact that you have the Ferrari
Delivery schedule memorized
You know that they show it when they show up
In the middle of the night
What if the whole thing even going up there
He was probably trying to get us to be part of his
Ferrari heist
You were scoping the joint guys
I can't stress this enough
I don't need to steal Ferraris
If you give me another
$50,000
Did you zell him?
Did you spend that $50,000
He zelled you 30 minutes ago
I zelled you $50,000
What's the format of that?
Maybe he wanted $49,999
$99,999
I'm going to re-zell
$49,999
$999.
I'm going to keep the first one
Or you want me to send it back?
No, you don't have to send it back
What are you doing?
Stand up for yourself
Sector keeper?
I'm a ghost, I'm invertebrate
Sector keeper
You look like
Grey ET, white ET
He's getting weak
He's coming over here
After the record I'm going to end up
Getting a phone call from Jenny his wife
So he's married
Not my wife
Is he married to a human woman who's alive?
She won't call me back, she's not my wife
That's legal
Why don't you call her?
You should call her then
I did call her, that's what I'm saying
She doesn't call me back, she's not my wife
Were you married before you were a ghost or did you meet her when you were a ghost?
You can't legally ask me that
Oh, okay
Alright
I can answer though
He was a ghost and they got married
Thank you, he can tell you
I'm not allowed to tell you
I can be the conduit
How old is the wife?
The wife?
In her 40
Alright, well
Wait, are you a boy?
Are you like a boy?
Cause he's a boy
Do you think I have a boy's taste in art?
Do you think a boy would love the art of Michael Ferrari?
I could see it
If I was a boy I might like the art of Michael Ferrari
That's my vibe
That's my age, that's my home
So the answer to that is
He's 52 but he tells people he's 39
Okay, so he is like age appropriate
But most of those years were since I've ghosted
He's the only ghost I know that has a leathery suntan
You look discut
You barely even look like a ghost
I'm the only ghost that works on it
You gotta put in the work for tan
It doesn't just happen
You lay around and wait for some other guy to show up and pay for all your Ferraris
He seemed to have a real problem with me for someone that drank a lot of Happy Van Winkle and cucumber coolers
I do cause you misrepresented the permission of where it was coming from
He's not mad at you, look at this guy
He's got no beef with you
No, with me?
What he doesn't, VVB will never understand boys is that
There are riffs currently in the multiverse
And you start throwing back Pappy's
Pappy might come for us
Oh now we have to worry about Pappy?
Yes, you may have summoned Pappy
The actual Pappy Van Winkle if it's named after
Who do you think Pappy Van Winkle?
The tail of Van Winkle, time
He is Rip Van Winkle
Is he Rip Van Winkle's father?
Yes, obviously
Obviously my god
I didn't know that
I don't know
I want to drink that sweet sweet time whiskey
Now it all makes sense
That's why Scott's getting worked up, you're feeling a shift
Because the whole, look
We've been doing these, some of this has nothing to do with you Venice Beach BoardWalkkeeper
We've been doing this series
I'm just coming in with like
First I'm like, hey we're done with Buffett
And a bunch more Buffett stuff
And then like, and now I'm getting hit with all this
And I find out that all that whiskey was like an abuse of the goodwill
Of my, this is the keeper I have a relationship with
You, I thought I knew it and you lied to me
You know what I will, in comparison
We're best friends
In this moment that's how I feel
He's my best friend
And you are abusing this guy
That's okay, but by the trend of property you are also my best friend
Oh shit
No what so, this is stupid math
And the beginning is the end
I don't agree with any of this
And then just like, and then
This is your home, this is your vibe
And on top of all of it like
We have never gotten an answer of how many of these sectors we're gonna do
I'd be fine adding celebrity authentics in whatever we want
As long as I knew there was a light at the end of the tunnel
We the listeners, nobody knows how many
How are we, is this gonna be 45 days?
Is it gonna be 70 days?
Scott, sector keeper actually told me before we were recording
They just opened a universal monster tribute store at Hollywood
Literally yesterday, so I was gonna, like
He said we're gonna have to do that too
No, no, we don't need to do that
If the rift existed we can solve it without going there
Best friend or no best friend
I don't want it, how many of the, how much more can we possibly add
I got, hey listen, I know what you need to do
Here's your out, you want it out?
Here's your out
You turn around, you walk away
You walk into the sea my man
You know what
You come with me, you walk into the sea
No one can get you in the sea
No, no, no
He's in your mind
Scott hates it when you dare him to do things
You know what, for the first time you've said something sensible
That's right best friend
You know, I actually, I think, I mean I don't know where it'll end up
I don't know if I want to walk permanently into the sea
I'm not sure if I'm at that level
Okay
Maybe a little ocean drive would sound good
Maybe going in like, just, I think staring at the god damn ocean for a little bit
Sounds spec-fucking-tacular
No, no, no
On this day where the fucking, the police showed up
And I got a drifter here who won't leave my home
Let's say that officially and I don't have any idea how long this show
And like, and I don't, it's not all about the keepers
Guys, you got, you could stop, you could, Jason and Mike
You could help organize this thing
Am I the only one who feels like this, this series is never gonna end
Like we need to put some confines on this or we're never getting out of it
Well, I mean I got some, a little bit of closure recently
Because I thought Anahito's meal I had not too long ago
Gave me a bit of a tummy ache
And then I think it was actually the big Topo Chico I drank with it
I don't think that's true because I got sick the same day as you, remember?
Yeah, but then I had a Topo Chico somewhere else
And I also got a bloated stomach ache
So I'm willing to give Anahito's another chance
I think
You're going back, it's been off my list actually
It makes me, it makes me sick once I'm done
This podcast is making me sick and maybe I'm fucking done with this too
Guys, I don't, you know what, I, going and taking a look at the ocean
Sounds fucking great to me right now
Wait, Scott, there's so many curses
He's leaving
Let me know when there's a sensible amount of sectors
He's leaving his own
The Beach Boardwalk guy is gone
He's leaving the Venice Beach Boardwalks house
I'm taking some fucking time, okay?
He's leaving
In my house, in my house, don't fucking go another hour
My wife has to come park here, you're fucking out
Oh my god
And now that was a lot of yelling and cursing
That was he, yeah
That could see why, how we would maybe get another call
Well, that's never
There's no party yet
I was going to say that's never happened
But I think it's actually happened once before
And I think it's when I first started talking about Randy Gerber on this podcast
Who's that?
Cindy Crawford's husband, Randy Gerber
He's sort of business partners with George Clooney for Casa Migos Tequila
Oh yeah, I love to Migos, that's my home
What did you call it?
Migos?
Well, Casa Migos
Yeah, yeah, House Migos, my home, my life
Did you call it House Migos?
Yeah, that's what I'm saying, that's what it means, that's what Casa means
Oh, I see, I see, yeah
I just thought you were, I couldn't
I almost pictured it H-A-U-S
I can't believe Scott left
He was talking about going into the ocean
And he could have just waded around in that little body of water outside the Billabong store
Yeah, because that, yeah
Yeah, that's pretty calming
Yeah, I got bad news for you, bud, though
That's not like the ocean
Well, but it's water, it's got water
Oh, man
Well, I hate to leave the listeners on such a bong
Like, Scott usually does the outro, so I guess I'll do the outro
I'll do it
Sectorkeeper, did we finish the saga?
Yeah, I'll do it
Beer cheese fondue was good at pig fire
Yeah, that was, yeah, we had that
We did technically finish the sector
Okay
The stone is forming
Okay, well, what is this?
Bourbon cheese
You look closely
Is this stone bourbon cheese?
Is that what you said?
I'm sorry, Jason, what?
You just said bourbon cheese, but he might have fallen asleep and had a brief dream
I read my note, I said beer cheese, it was bourbon cheese
Oh, I thought you kind of had it blacked out and you were just saying bourbon cheese
Oh, no
Oh, bourbon cheese
Is this episode releasable?
I mean, I think it has to be as far as our recording schedule is concerned
Do you see something appearing?
As long as the stone comes out, yeah, I think this episode is releasable
It is appearing, it's many little stones, points that create a larger stone
Wow
And it has the formation of a sinister lady by the name of Harley Quinn
Oh, wow
That is a monster
And below it there's a price tag and it says $49.
99.
This is the most expensive one yet
Okay
So that's, okay, you got this stone
And it's signed by Josh Gadd
What?
Wait, hold on
Why did Josh Gadd sign it?
Why not?
I didn't see any Gadd sign things in this place
Everyone from the movie Pixels signed it
Oh, is Marco Robbins Pixels?
No, I don't think so
She didn't sign this one but Josh Gadd did
But Josh Gadd did
Oh, okay, well, look, if that's what the stone is, that's what the stone is
And what's it going to take for you to take this stone home today?
I'll take it now
Well, this is a different stone because we have to actually purchase this stone
Unlike the others
No, I got you, I got this one
Because you just need $49.
99.
99, right?
Yeah
That's the first thing that he sent me so I'm good
Are you going to pay for it in pennies?
Well, I got it through Zell so I just got to get cashed that out and then get my van over here
Okay
All right, so he'll pay for it I guess so we'll get it
Yeah
Okay
Well, I mean, do you want to look, I guess here, do you want to read the outro?
I'll do my own and you do that one
Okay, yeah, do your own.
Do you want to do it first or do you want to do it?
Okay, hit me up on Vemo at VBB and you can just send whatever you want right over there
Okay
And I'll work with Zell too
And please get back to me, Michael at michaelferrari.
ferrari.
michael
Okay
Call me, okay
Okay, well, I think he'll probably hit you up
All right, it's for us, you know, thanks to Aaron Garner for the art
Me, Mike Carlson, and Zacharino for the theme music for Multiverse of Madness
The Multiverse of Madness merch is in our T-Public store
For the full Multiverse experience, keep it tuned here to Podcast the Ride, the Second Gate
Or join Club 3 to get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector at patreon.
com
Slash podcast the ride
Stupid saga, stupid keepers, stupid cops
I feel like such an outcast
No one understands me
Whoa, hey big fella, what's your name?
Are you an outcast too?
That's so unfair, you're amazing
You sound like a cow but you look like a fish
Hey, let's stick together, you and me, cow fish
Forever
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehme, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.
com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook