Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a dough that's soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll.
With alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where seam-punged robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando.
Tonight.
A daily.
Extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride.
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
If you're a second gate subscriber,
this is one of two episodes that has appeared in your feed today.
We don't want to suggest an order,
but this will probably be the first one that you'll listen to.
Or the only one if you're not on the second gate.
Let's get into it.
I'm Scott Gardner.
This is Mike Carlson.
I'm Mike Carlson.
Welcome to the Margaritaverse of madness as well.
As far as today is concerned.
I don't know.
Maybe we'll talk to one of the guys here
and see if he disagrees with what I just said.
Just prepare for that, I think.
Sure.
Absolutely.
Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I mean, I think the madness is starting to creep in
both on the recording of these.
And also fittingly for today's excursion.
Yeah.
Madness hit pretty quickly.
An operative word, I would say.
A key word in all of this.
But before we fully explain what's happening here,
let's see if we can summon him.
Wait, is there a special margarita?
I don't know.
Air ride, everybody.
Fins up.
Let's see if we can get him.
Is he here?
Boys, boys, fins up.
All right.
Fins up, sector keeper.
Welcome back.
Fins up also looks like you're praying.
Like you're putting a little prayer on top of your head.
That's if you go to the youth ministry mass,
you do fins up, a little God is an awesome God.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, wow.
That one always got to me, I have to say.
I didn't take everything away from my church going years,
but God is an awesome God had a real power to it.
And the choreography.
Indeed.
Yes.
Pep and everybody steps.
So we are here as you dictated yesterday, yesterday,
kind of yesterday, you know, began the Buffett discussion.
And but now today we focus on the heart of it.
The core part of the brand, Margaritaville,
although I should let you issue the assignment.
Yes, yes, of course.
which takes us to where exactly Margaritaville alpha,
which of course is in Orlando, Orlando, because it was opened first.
You got it.
Yeah.
OK, OK.
Yes, we're following.
OK, as opposed to being the Omega, Omega, which of course,
which is in Los Angeles and Omega is in.
I don't know my Greek letters or whatever, but Omega is mean second.
Right.
That's what it means.
It must.
No, no, I guess alpha is one and Omega is two.
That's not right.
But I don't know if this even makes sense.
Omega.
It's too late to change the rule.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
You're declared them.
It's what it's going to be.
It's what we got to stick to.
OK.
All I remember is there was an X-Men comic called Alpha and an X-Men comic called X-Men Omega.
Oh, and those were the start and the finish.
That's all I remember.
Yeah.
Jason, you know what I'm talking about?
I do know what you're talking.
That's how you would differentiate between the start of an event or the end of an event.
Oh, yeah.
So beginning and end.
That's what it is.
That's what Alpha and Omega is.
It's perfect.
It's very clean.
But today, Alpha, if you do subscribe to the second game,
and we encourage you to at patreon.
com slash podcast, The Ride,
at the exact same time, if it all worked out, then Omega should have dropped Omega,
which will take us to City Walk Hollywood.
And the idea here is we are having the exact same meal on two coasts,
per your request yesterday.
In other cases, we could kind of do different things in the Alpha and Omega,
but this one has to be exact to the T.
Yes, that's right.
OK, that's fine.
We're ready to do it.
So I'm just catching up on the rules and the formalities,
one of which being let me get I'm going to clear 20 comments out of our feed really quick
because we are covering Margaritaville.
We don't know Eddie Burback, the YouTuber who went to every Margaritaville in the country.
He also went to every Rainforest Cafe, which provoked a lot of comments asking,
why is it not this guy?
And the answer is we've never met this man.
We have no shared friends with this man.
I actually did a while back try to reach out to his agents who were specifically very unhelpful.
So that is the reason I'll save you all the commenting.
We would love to have him on the show.
I like those videos.
They're good.
This journey he's on, is he also trying to escape hell?
Or get to it.
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's a similar self-inflicted punishment to what we do.
So a kindred spirit for sure.
We'd love to have him on.
If any listeners have a way, a connection to this person,
or if somehow he's hearing it by now, Eddie, come on the show, please.
But he's not here now.
So you can save the comments for the next thing that makes you upset about this.
I want to thank the listeners for thinking that we are more powerful
and are more all-encompassing as far as people knowing about us.
I want to thank them for thinking that about us.
They know everyone.
That we could just snap up.
They're the talk of the town.
They're wheelers and dealers.
But anyway, now that that is out of the way, we are here to focus on Margaritaville.
So many phrases to keep straight.
Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville City Walk Orlando.
We went and had a meal there.
What's the Alvo?
Sorry, Alfie.
I keep missing him.
OK, so this has always been, I feel like, a cornerstone of City Walk Orlando.
There from the beginning.
And it's this location.
Obviously, we've talked much about Margaritaville over the years
and then various Buffett things.
Of course.
Yesterday included.
But this is all the Orlando one has always been kind of looming large in my head.
I think because some of the first that we ever talked about any of this stuff,
Mike, you've always said, well, that's kind of the you didn't say Alpha,
but kind of you implied it's like the Alpha location because it's on the water.
It's relaxing it like maybe summons those island vibes better than some of the other Margaritaville locations.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
There you go.
The Navy Pier location, the Margaritaville location, which is near the water,
is one of the most unpleasant restaurants I've ever gone to.
That's Chicago.
Yes.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Chicago.
And it's obviously right by Lake Michigan, but it's cramped.
And you're sitting outside and you're not like right by the water.
There's like multiple like different streets and pavements and people on bikes.
But then it's just it's unpleasant and and it's terrible.
I would say the food there was maybe not the greatest.
Yeah.
So so a couple of the ones I've gone to, I've been a little disappointed in the ambiance.
And then, of course, you go back to Orlando and you go, well, this is how it should be.
This is where you're living the life here.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, and I think there was maybe kind of a disappointment.
You know, we're not we're going to talk about Hollywood as its own thing right now.
We're talking about it right now.
Listen to both episodes at once.
Back and forth, ping pong back and forth as much as you want.
As we get into our meals, let's try to do it in the same order so that you could know.
Yeah.
All right.
Scott's meal, Alpha Scott's meal, Omega Mike's meal, Alpha, Mike's meal, Omega.
Yeah.
It's an interactive experience for you if you want it to be.
But Hollywood sync up to God is an awesome guy.
If you hit play at the very beginning of the episode, you get on a different computer or speaker system.
Sync it all up.
If you're a Club 3 member, you can get a free download of God is an awesome guy.
We made a deal with I want to say Michael Smith, who's the maker of that.
I guess.
Yeah, I did.
I did guess.
Wow.
I am going to heaven.
Michael Smith, maker of our God is an awesome God.
We don't know Michael Smith.
Stop asking to have him on the show.
Yeah, I know.
Look, we look we know a lot of funny people out there, a lot of good people out there.
We don't know religious singer Michael W.
Smith.
We don't know him.
We love the open invite Michael W.
Smith.
Anytime he wants.
Anyway, Hollywood opens.
Hollywood completely landlocked.
You know, you're not even close to any of those.
They wish they had the Navy pier situation.
Yes, for sure.
Barely close to a path.
Yeah, no, I know.
So back in the corner.
And it's yeah, it's it's really tucked away.
It's really tucked away there.
So yeah, this this one, this Margaritaville in Orlando is always been my favorite that I've gone to, at least.
And I assume there's other I'd have to check the Eddie Burback video where he went to all of them.
Yeah, but there are some that are along.
I mean, I feel like a lot are on the beach or on a pier or in locations like that.
But of the ones we've gone to, is anybody is anybody like been the one that I don't because my count is Orlando, Hollywood.
I just walked through Navy Pier Vegas, which Vegas started me off with this brand.
I didn't have Hollywood yet.
Right.
So Vegas set the bar for me and I loved it.
I like I was kind of in the throes of discovering the whole Buffett verse.
It was new to me.
We'd all just been to this concert together.
Sectorkeeper to fill you in.
We all went to see Jimmy Buffett with Nick Weiger and Anthony Geo.
Yeah, yeah.
So that's been there and still with us.
Yeah, I was I was floating above.
Oh, jeez.
Before we even met you.
But you just like crazy to think that we maybe met at certain time.
It is.
Yeah, yeah.
Like maybe we were.
Yeah, Jimmy Buffett together.
Yeah.
Crossing over in ways we never even imagined.
We could have been seeing the same comedy death ray on a Tuesday night at UCB.
That's yeah, very possible.
Just in a tiny little club, like getting to see Louie.
Like there's not even that many people.
He goes on to do Madison Square Garden, but it's just us and Louie.
And then you and me.
I mean, it goes comedians, comedian.
Amen.
That's what he was.
That's what he is is.
But anyway, I love Vegas just like hit me.
Yeah.
So hard because they got the whole thing there.
They got the volcano.
They got the show that goes to the song volcano.
Right.
Despite not being on the water, it's on the strip.
And that's exciting.
I genuinely liked the the dish.
I think you would.
Mike had just been on Doughboys and talked about it.
And I think you guys were all pretty buzzing about lava, lava shrimp, which I thought.
And it did not disappoint.
I was like, is wait a minute.
So Margarita Ville is a good restaurant.
That is a surprise to me because how often are chain restaurants not?
That's what I thought in 2016.
Yeah.
And I hear it's coming here to Hollywood.
We're going to have it.
I'm going to be up there every week.
I'm never going to stop being there.
Yes.
Very exciting.
I had been to the other Vegas one.
Do we go to that?
Maybe we went to the Vegas one.
When we went to a party, we got off the bus behind it.
Oh, we went there first.
We took a mega bus.
Right.
Which lets you off at the link, which is like an outdoor promenade.
And we went to Guy Fieri's at last.
That was the last thing.
Yeah, we went.
We had a very defeated meal at Guy Fieri's.
We ordered the wrong things.
Well, I mean, that's a fair opinion.
We did Guy's Cheesecake Challenge at the end, which was party.
No, three of us.
OK.
What is that?
It's a big piece of cheesecake.
Big piece of still frozen cheesecake.
Yeah.
With chips and pretzels crushed upon it.
That's a way to go to a bachelor party and get your stomach pumped, I guess.
Well, you know, you do the cheesecake challenge and you get back on the mega bus back to L.
A.
That's it there and back.
That's the best of the party.
Yeah.
So I do like Vegas a lot, too.
I will say that.
At least the time we had there, I don't know what it's been.
I haven't been to that place in a while.
But with how highly I was regarding the Vegas location, how my marketable journey started with, it's actually a good restaurant.
Yeah, that just always left me.
Then what is this Orlando that Mike has been talking like if, you know, listeners can't see that.
But as Vegas is here, then Orlando is here.
It's up above the roof.
What is higher?
What kingdom is higher than heaven?
What kind of like how could it be better?
The only the sector keeper could answer that.
Is there a better heaven than heaven?
Yeah, there's like a heaven plus.
Oh, OK.
Cool.
They name it like thousands of years ago.
They named it the way they named streaming services.
Now, that's right.
Yeah, there's ad free heaven.
Oh, just like no billboards.
Yeah, no billboards.
There are so in heaven you do have to see ads all the time.
You have to see ads still, you know, for communion, blood of Christ.
All right.
Right.
There's got to do there.
There is a commercial over the body of Christ right now.
That's very good.
Is it like sexy or something like a reverent?
Yeah, it's funny.
It's all I bet it's random.
It's random, man.
The people that are in.
Oh, man.
You get dead comedian.
Well, like Rodney Dangerfield up there with you.
And then you're looking around and he's Lincoln.
Rodney and Lincoln are in a commercial together and have been for body of Christ.
Oh, wow.
OK.
You can't get any respect.
This is for going to get the little pieces of bread.
They did an ad for that.
The one that's messed up right now is that I'm in.
I'm technically subscribed to heaven plus they had a Black Friday deal.
Oh, yeah.
Black Friday deal.
And was it Black Friday or Good Friday?
You're right.
It was a good Friday.
They call it there.
We should time portal to change that.
Oh, it's OK.
I think we can leave it.
Yes, there is a question.
There was a Good Friday deal.
And but, you know, it's weird.
You still wait when you wake up in the morning, you still have to watch 30 seconds of a commercial.
And when you go to bed at night, you still have to watch 30 segments of commercials.
You're paying premium, but you're still sneaking ads in.
Right.
Wow.
Well, heaven's got to make money somehow.
That's true.
Yeah.
It's a lot to keep up an entire like supporting old cloud world.
I'm going off like the regular, you know, the question idea.
Right.
So it is gates.
Those cost a lot of money upkeep.
You got to put you know, you don't just build them.
You polish them.
Yeah.
It's Golden Gates and clouds, right?
More or less.
Golden Gates.
There's a Margaritaville.
Oh, no way.
Yeah.
Oh, let me edit my notes because I said 23 locations.
Sorry.
24 if we count.
But you got to be dead to know about that.
Epsilon.
That's Epsilon.
Epsilon is heaven.
OK.
Is that a good one?
Is that of the that must have the volcano.
Oh, it's got it all.
And it's got it all.
It's good.
I bet that heaven one.
I think the big one of the big things that notches a Margaritaville up high ceilings,
high ceilings in Vegas and in heaven is no ceiling and no ceilings.
Yeah.
Even when I've been to I'm sure no one else has Atlantic City.
Oh, right.
I was asking who's OK.
I've never been.
No, no, no.
I don't know.
It's part of the resorts casino.
When it opened, they were like, check out the Margaritaville casino attached.
And I was like, oh, and I went and it's like two rows of tropical slot machines.
Like it's not quite a full casino.
That's Vegas, too.
You just like get their carpet pattern next to some slot machines.
Right.
Yeah.
So Atlantic City, it's you can enter from the casino
hotel or you can enter from the boardwalk.
And then on the other side of the boardwalk and like the beach dunes,
there is a pier, a little bit of a pier with a land shark barn grill.
So they have a separate like the loan home.
OK.
Have you eaten there?
I have not eaten there at that location.
I believe it's just open in the summers.
Oh, really?
Oh, you mean the land shark, the land shark.
Specifically, you have eaten at the Margaritaville.
I've eaten at the Margaritaville.
OK.
Is Landshark Margaritaville owned?
Yes, it's the land shark logger is yes.
It's a beer brand.
And I guess I guess bars.
Yeah, they start a separate land shark bars sometime.
And the land shark beer factors into some of the food.
And yeah, and there's there are also still, I think, but maybe certainly
at some point about a cheeseburger in paradise locations also that are not
branded Margaritaville, but they're owned by but are owned by.
Yeah.
Then there's like resorts that have been abandoned by the company.
Talked a little bit about that.
Yeah, there's iconography.
It's a little unclear.
I mean, the Orlando Margaritaville where we named a street is still there.
I think it's maybe seen better.
Has it seen better days?
Maybe it never saw good days.
It's possible to never seen good day.
Probably would have been a good place to hide out during covid
because there was no one around.
There was no one.
You want a whole resort to yourself.
But there was also a fair amount of loose electrical wiring.
So they were still building it.
They were still building.
Although also, can you imagine that you go to that to like the cigar bar
in May 2020 and it is just packed to the gills?
Yeah, don't go to the resort.
Go to the empty housing.
Go to like the big short empty housing neighborhood.
The weird narrow houses that look like the cat in the hat movie that aren't selling.
Yeah.
So Navy Pier, Atlantic City, what other?
So Tau Rho.
Whoa, they all got names.
Those are all the ones I've been to.
I think I've only seen Niagara Falls from a distance.
I wasn't into the brand yet.
I'm glad I am now.
Much fun has come from it.
I went to one in the Detroit airport once.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
Our flight was going to New Jersey.
I should just say I was flying to New Jersey.
I don't need a stinkin plane.
And yeah, got delayed in the Wayne County Airport in Detroit.
Completely empty terminal.
The only thing open was the Margaritaville.
Oh, wow.
Emptiness, barrenness is associated with this brand.
Did you have a meal?
Well, I did not.
And it didn't seem like many people that the plane, even though there were literally no options, people walked the entire terminal and just walked right past.
Oh, no.
So it didn't peak.
Maybe it wasn't lunch or dinner.
Maybe it was in between time when you don't need to eat.
Yeah, yeah, maybe.
Maybe three, four.
But it was vibrant.
OK.
Yeah, yeah.
And ambiance must be.
Maybe that's the top ambiance.
I don't know.
I'd have to look it up.
But yeah, I set the bar for Detroit Airport.
Oh, another one.
Put an asterisk next to this one.
Times Square.
Oh, wait, we've been forget.
Yes, we did an entire episode.
Yeah, I stayed there for days.
Yeah, that's right.
I think of that as its own thing, though.
It is.
But there is a Margaritaville restaurant, technically, that is.
Is that technically Margaritaville?
That is technically a Margaritaville.
And it's technically Times Square, I guess.
It's a number blocks away.
It's in Times Square?
Well, it's technically approaching the fashion district at that point, I think.
But yeah, it's near the…
You pass the Hard Rock that used to be the WWE restaurant.
That's right, yeah.
Wow.
And Jason and Jane stayed there, and every hour they would call and ask for new towels.
I remember that's part of the story.
Like, exaggerating as usual.
They were also calling down for the complimentary island water bottles.
Yes, the big thing was that the water…
I don't remember the name, but let's say Sally is who you're going by.
You knew the name of the desk person.
Sally, we need towels, Sally.
That was what you were saying.
We need more island water.
They had been chummy with the desk person because they were calling down so often.
Here's the thing.
New York hotels, when they only have two elevators, you're waiting those elevators for a while.
Oh, I know.
It was awful.
So we weren't going down for it sometimes when we could get an elevator.
Or you just go to the gym where they have a whole fridge of waters and towels.
Margaritaville Times Square Resort Hack.
Go to the gym.
And if you visit every location, you can turn in your stamp card for a little shot glass.
Yes, right.
I remember this.
And then hack number three, if none of that works.
Sally, Sally, Sally.
And you're not going to get this from Benny Burnsack.
What was his name?
Eddie Burback.
That's right.
He didn't go into the gym.
You can teach him about that if he was here.
We're talking about water.
We're talking alpha, boys.
Yes, you're right.
Let's talk alpha.
So it's been built up in my head a lot.
And it's something I was really looking forward to, I would say, during this.
Like, OK, if we're just the point of this trip is to just plant roots at City Walk, then we can have a nice leisurely meal there.
And so when it came to passPeter, I was happy.
And going into it, and this is kind of like the full group.
This was the three of us and Jane as well and the level keeper, in fact.
Yes, he was there as well.
Yes, so we got to spend a little more time with him.
Wait, and Universal employee Adam.
Adam.
Yes.
Adam, yeah, Adam, correct?
Yes, so Adam, Adam there as well.
And this was also Adam had like helped us out and let it take us to see some like exclusive behind the scenes stuff.
Yes, as he did the last time we were there.
So it was like, let us repay you.
Thank you.
With a meal and one of the finest establishments that there is.
So so so we got a group going.
We get in there and the OK.
Things about it about this specific location just before we go further.
You got you got the volcano thing.
You got the blender thing.
There's a video.
I forgot there's a burp that happened.
Yes, the burp.
Yes, that's part of the sequence.
Right.
The volcano burps and then a big big blender is filled up.
But I do you know, the volcano sequence is one of the dumbest, coolest things in any giant chain restaurant.
Yeah, I think I think it's a triumph.
And you got to give this one.
I don't know if we're competing the two against each other, but maybe vaguely.
Certainly got a notch this above Omega because they have the volcano.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, this thing, this should be the I mean, you know, we've recently talked Rainforest Cafe.
This is kind of the draw as far as like next level seeming like as far as the Rainforest Cafe is like a little thunderstorm or something.
But this is the big thing.
It's a real volcano.
It's not a real volcano.
It's a real working facsimile of a volcano.
Fiberglass volcano.
Yeah.
Is it better than I don't know if it's better than Rainforest Cafe.
I don't know if it's better.
I'm just saying that's like their trademark.
And this is this should be Margaritaville's trademark.
And this should be in all of the restaurants.
I'm saying it shouldn't allow them to be built without it.
Yes.
And it's this song volcano, one of his ten songs that people know.
That number keeps climbing.
People do not know ten of these songs.
There are like four songs.
Well, let's show.
OK, Sector Keeper.
Sector Keeper was at the concert.
Do people say the Big Six or something?
That's for Disney.
That's a Disney character.
No, no, no.
But there's a set of Jimmy's songs and sometimes the last one or two is the Big E.
The Sector Keeper is more aware of Buffett than the common person, I would say.
How many of the Big Ten, ten songs people know?
Can you name?
Right.
And like Disney, they do locks him in the vault every once in a while.
Yeah, do vaulted ones count?
Some come in and out.
OK, so Margaritaville.
We got one.
Cheeseburger in Paradise.
Yeah, that's two.
Volcano.
Four.
That's one of the sad ones.
Volcano.
Did you already say Volcano?
I already said it.
That was third.
You just literally just said it.
I meant Volcano Omega.
You mean the live version.
Live version.
You have to though.
Which date though?
Now wait a minute.
It's like the Grateful Dead.
You got to have the dates.
You know, from the live tracks.
There's bootlegs.
Bootlegs.
So far, we're at four.
The number I said.
Math sucks.
OK.
Of course.
But math sucks is not one people know about.
That's one that Mike talks about.
How would he know about it then?
He's a ghost.
I don't really hang out with him that much.
Yeah, I've been staying with Jason mostly.
Yeah, he's still with Jason.
Five.
I think one of those is a bit of a cheat, but generously five.
We talked about one earlier.
We did the E.
Oh, that's going to help.
Oh, Finn's Up.
Yeah, Finn's.
Not the name.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, he got close.
Give it to him.
Yeah, all right, fine.
With hints, we're getting.
So with a lot of help, we have round two.
We've crested the way.
We're heading to the almighty easy to get 10.
There's a big sad one.
Sad one that involves us in travel.
This is too many hints.
I'm cutting off hints.
The more we hint.
Oh, goodness.
Oh, shoot.
Just start making them up if you can go hit it.
OK.
There's.
But you'll get pretty close.
Don't you dare whisper any to him.
Sorry, sorry.
I know I just I'm just helping with her.
His son tan slips.
Shit.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
As far as I know, it's an slips.
So on the tennis slips, the blunt blunt.
Of course, I've heard.
Yeah, you're the show.
Yeah.
Oh, goodness.
Well, you can take your time.
You could.
He doesn't have to do it.
It might come.
We'll call him out as we go.
We will prove the 10 commonly.
And then, of course, something that Mike has asserted that not only to common people know,
but it's of course, listeners to our show know.
Please now name Jimmy Buffett's guitarist.
Oh, yeah.
You know this.
Yeah, he knows this.
Of course, because he's a person in America.
He knows it.
And a supporter of podcast the ride.
We're not a one person subscribing.
Doesn't know the name.
People know Jimmy Buffett's guitarist.
Because when Jimmy played the bull, Jimmy left stage for a while to have wine.
That's right.
And I might have been fake wine, though.
Yeah, it might have been.
And this guy did a mini set.
Yeah.
And his name is?
It'll come to me.
It'll come.
Yeah.
OK.
He's under pressure here.
I don't want to put him under that kind of stress.
All right.
So we'll let you do a take home test.
OK.
All right.
I am impressed with it.
OK.
We got to Mac.
He knows.
Everybody knows.
They all obviously know.
Mac McAnally.
Are we allowed to say that you wanted to put Mac's name in the theme song?
I did, yeah.
I tried.
And I vetoed it.
Scott vetoed it.
I don't think one of the primary facets of these Orlando City Walk is Mac the guitar player.
Here are the songs known as the Big Eight.
Just to confirm.
The Big Eight?
The one with Alan Jackson, right?
Well, Alan Jackson wrote it.
That actually…
But it's a well known…
It was the only hit, maybe, of all this stuff.
It was the only number one hit, I think.
He's on it.
He appears on it, of course.
OK.
Margaritaville.
Let's go faster.
Faster.
We heard these.
Hold on.
Like this Yahoo article says, these will make you feel like you're on island time.
Remember, this can be a quick one.
This can be a quick one.
That's adjacent.
Margaritaville.
Number three.
Come Monday.
Finns.
Volcano.
A Pirate Looks at Forty.
Cheeseburger in Paradise.
Why Don't We Get Drunk?
I've never heard of that in my life.
I've been with you motherfuckers for seven years.
Why don't we get drunk?
I've never heard of Why Don't We Get Drunk?
That is not a Big Eight.
The lyric in that shit.
The last one.
The lyric in that.
Not in the eight.
I didn't say it was in the eight.
Wait, wait.
This is John who was in the eight?
Changes in latitude, changes in attitude.
That's fine.
That one's in.
Sure.
Great.
The lyric in that song is Why Don't We Get Drunk and Screw.
And screw.
Yeah.
Thank God they left it out.
Oh, Zegger Keeper knows.
I knew.
I did know that one.
I don't know it after hours and hours of Buffett content.
I didn't say it was a Big Eight.
That's whatever article Jason's reading about the Big Eight.
Well, I'm reading Wikipedia and there's a Yahoo article that also lists the same song.
That article seems like it has a lot of ads because you're really scrolling through.
That is how it goes.
The older a website is, the longer the ads go through.
It's a 19 minute read.
There's a lot of ads and there's embedded videos for each song.
Why Don't We Get Drunk?
The chances of Jason getting distracted and clicking on the ads as well.
Like, oh, the Sears.
I got to help out, Yahoo.
$3 off at Rubio's.
Jason just downloaded and is playing Royal Match.
I've got to save the king.
Please help me.
Save the king.
Speaking of songs I've also never heard of, here's something that even though I was in
the restaurant, maybe this isn't something they do anymore.
Inside.
OK.
Intribute to the song 12 Volt Man.
The back of the bar was covered in car batteries hooked up to blenders that served boat drinks.
And then something about the volcano that we know.
12 Volt.
Does that do they do that?
And what's 12 Volt Man?
You get like boat drinks, the more iconic song.
It's a song.
I don't know that one by heart.
I've heard of it, though.
I can't remember how it goes.
I did not see if they did something special for the 12 Volt batteries, though.
I don't know if that's something that.
There's a lyric to this one.
Seldom found the trick to arithmetic.
So it's kind of a cousin of math sucks.
That's another.
That's like the third thing that he writes about is math being bad.
Don't forget there is a third thing.
The big three.
Boats.
Topics.
Boats, alcohol and math being bad.
Math is sucks.
So anyway, I'm getting excited because like, OK, we're going to have this ocean view.
We're going to see the volcano.
We're going to see the 12 volts, the batteries, all of this.
And then we get seated in kind of a perfunctory lobby.
We're like right at the front.
First of all, yes.
Like it's a room.
We got seated in the worst spot.
I think you could possibly sit in this place.
It's pretty bad.
It was pretty bad.
It's right.
No, no ambiance.
It was like being in a waiting room.
Close to the bathrooms, which would prove valuable.
So there's there's almost like three sections to this place, I would say.
This kind of lobby area that is.
And then there's more tables as you go on the left side of the restaurant by the bathroom.
Then there's sort of the main show floor, which that's where you're getting their close like close up view of the volcano.
That's where the plane is overhead.
Of course, not the real hemisphere dancer.
Yesterday, yes, the other plane, the facsimile of it, but it's still like move.
It's still pretty impressive.
Yeah, so pretty impressive.
And the bar is right there.
And that's where the action is.
I think we should have requested that.
Or one of my favorite places is the porch.
The porch outside is where I true.
That's the first place I ever ate at this Margaritaville.
I ate at Sunset.
Sometimes they got a guy out there.
He's doing covers.
He's playing all your favorite songs, some by Jimmy Buffett.
Some by Stephen Jenkins.
Some all the all the hits you could possibly want.
And you know what?
There are points to this Margaritaville.
But in keeping with generally the Orlando situation, you're much more likely to find performers at this establishment than the Hollywood location, which I think always just has a sign on it.
Yes, stop people from coming on the stage.
There is a stage.
And I feel like the first few weeks we went.
Yes, there would be performers.
But long ago, long ago, they stopped programming new music there.
But yes, this Orlando, this Orlando porch, which I think is the best place to see and eat.
Margaret, you got the view of Jason's beloved Islands of Adventure there.
Yeah, you got you can see the water there.
That's kind of maybe my perfect spot.
So yeah, when they I wasn't even thinking, but they seated us literally like what felt like two feet from the open door where you walk in.
Yeah, just not quite very near the bathroom, but which is not the best for for ambience.
We were at least under like a bunch of sharks, like hammerheads and.
Yeah, yes, there were still things.
There's not nothing.
It's not nothing.
Yeah.
But but, you know, so first, so we, you know, we're settling into like not the best right environment, I would say.
This is also the day where most of Universal Studios Florida was down.
Yes.
Important to note a like historic park wide.
Most rides are shut down.
Like six are left.
Thus, they are telling people don't come in.
Go to Islands of Adventure instead.
Turn around.
That park was like especially stressful.
Right.
And it was kind of surprisingly hot for being November.
Don't come in.
There were people because there weren't any like clearly there were no real stress on the only rides that were open in there.
They're like, if you're gay, if you got tickets to both, you might want to consider going on some adventure instead.
They were trying to get people to not come.
There was no way to stop Six Flags.
Six Flags would have a situation where like the water, something's broken with the water system and it can't cool any of the rides.
Any of the breaks and they'd be like, yeah, it'll be OK.
Or they have like one teen spraying like a little hose or like a little spray bottle on the rides as it comes in.
Or putting like ice, just dropping a piece of ice on one of the wheels.
And now there's no ice for the beverages.
Yeah, right, right, right.
Sorry.
No, the drink ice is now ride ice.
Chain reaction.
They need that hose to clean up leaves.
They can't grab the broom five feet away.
They need that hose.
So so your experience, boys, you think it was more crowded because of this?
I think so.
I found it to be a pretty stressful morning in the parks.
Every year there was a layer of stress.
And the Riteville, too, was.
Oh, no, empty, dead empty.
Well, it also all of the morning's events kind of made it admittedly to where it's like two, three in the afternoon.
So we're there kind of a weird time also.
So let's start getting into what we ate because the drink order definitely already had something to it for me.
I ordered the perfect margarita.
I think I had another margarita.
I don't think I need to say what's in it, except that it's for margarita aficionados.
We might we don't have to say them out loud.
But once everybody if you took pictures of the menu or you look at the Orlando menu, we should note price.
Because if we're having the exact same thing, I am curious, are those prices the same?
This is 1425.
Just if you ever notice when we do the Hollywood one, radically different, just might be an interesting compare contrast.
But anyway, perfect margarita.
It shows up.
It's fine.
Well, first of all, these drinks took a long time.
These took a very long time.
I will say Waitress is like great.
She was so nice.
A lot of fun.
But it felt like she would forget about us for 30 minutes at a time.
Maybe she was just busy, though.
Yes, of course.
Somebody into that.
It's the management's fault.
That's probably in some way.
Another thing that might be I don't know if it's the manager's fault or whoever.
I feel like maybe she was making the drinks.
Also, I don't know.
It's possible she was doing everything.
Very possibly.
It felt like things were when there would be things that needed to be fixed.
They felt like they were fixed in a haphazard way.
Let's just tease it like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I agree.
Yes.
Making the drinks, cooking the food, setting off the volcano.
All right.
Go pour the green goo.
Get it loaded up.
The drink shows up and it tastes nice, but it has that thing.
And this isn't the first time I've had this at a restaurant that serves margaritas, where sometimes I like the big wide margarita glasses.
But sometimes you feel like, well, I sure did get four sips of that in between the ice.
Yeah, like it's the ice spreads and fills out that glass so much.
I really felt like this was not a single or a double.
This was like this was a quarter.
I got a quarter margarita and a lot of ice.
Do you think maybe though it was like a Jon Taffer approved amount of alcohol as far as the restaurant still making money?
Because he's very often worried about overpouring.
Ice it up!
Pour ice!
You're doing it off ice!
Don't sell blended because then you can't water it down with ice!
That's why your wife left you.
Taffer coming to main feed.
I don't know if everybody heard it.
You had to be on club three to hear, but Griffin free to come soon.
Taffer one coming to main feed.
I don't know if that's the words gotten out there.
Again, we're furious about this, but we don't want to do it either.
But unfortunately, that's what has to happen.
Drinks, fellas?
Yeah, I had the Landshark logger pretty solid.
I do like the beer.
It's a good beer.
And I wanted to get a very traditional meal.
I'll just say that too.
I won't say what I'm meaning yet, but I just wanted to because everybody's going to get different stuff because we really want to make sure we're all getting like a wide variety.
Try to not repeat.
Yeah, and I'm certainly I felt like I wanted to be traditional on this.
Sure.
So turkey mashed potatoes gravy.
That was in his song, one of his songs.
I would have ordered it.
Thanksgiving meal in paradise.
Stouffers.
I get the wishbone.
If he had lived a little longer, that song would have happened.
He would have been.
He's like, I'm out of ideas.
Got to do it.
When the AI takes over the deceased songwriters and bands catalogs, they will generate new songs.
It'll sub out French fries potato for mashed potato pretty quickly.
That's a very easy switch.
So, yeah, no, it's that.
And that comes in a bottle.
It's hard to screw that up.
OK, you know, they don't get the bottle beer though, as opposed to they did.
Let me just check the photo because now that you're saying that maybe someone else was drinking a draft.
Maybe it was me.
Maybe I'm misremembering because I've had so many land shark loggers over the years.
I don't blame you.
All the things I can say.
I like the brand.
Jason?
I think, well, I was going back and forth.
I wasn't sure if I was going to get a drink.
And then I.
After they all came, I went, you know what?
I will get a drink, which was a mistake.
And that took like another 20 minutes for me.
I think I had the passion fruit guava cocktail, which I hadn't had a drink in a while, and it immediately made me lightheaded.
OK, not in a good, not in a fun, not in a college drunk way.
No, no.
Like, oh, maybe I shouldn't be mixing these daily steroids with alcohol.
Like, maybe I shouldn't.
Although they I think eventually were my savior, the steroids.
Jason, Rick Flair used to do it all the time.
You can't do it.
Come on.
I did have a bottle.
They gave me a bottle.
Yeah.
Did you want that or is that just that's how it happened?
I like having the bar.
I like the bottle because it's got the brand on it.
I go in at a restaurant because I want that.
I like I don't want beer at all if it's not.
I actually don't drink.
I don't disagree in most places other than that.
You want below.
That's an interesting little course.
I want to see your land.
You also get the consistency in the bottle.
If you get a bottle at a restaurant, you know what you're getting.
I love frosty glass.
I'm not worried about though.
Yeah, the frosty glass.
I'm not worried about like they're going to pour it weird though.
No, no.
But if it's the end of a keg, if the end of it, I've had some like shitty beer.
Sometimes.
Yeah.
But yeah, the big glass.
I do.
The big glass is satisfying, especially if the glass is cold.
Yeah.
There's something about it that is more satisfying usually than a glass, a glass bottle.
That's obviously.
Well, I hope you liked it because you got to do it again.
Well, I do.
I did.
I did and I will.
Or just throw it out with no, or just request it not say anything and see what happens.
Oh, good question.
Oh, good point.
You got to flash back to however you did it before.
Okay.
Is that bottom of a decoration on it?
Well, it has the logo.
Oh, on the top though?
What do you mean?
It's got like a lime in there with the little.
A lime.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I will.
You get a lime.
That's part of the variable of repeating the meal.
Right.
Of course.
Meals.
Do we have an order?
Who thinks they liked theirs the most?
Mike.
Okay.
I think it's me.
Let's go in opposite order then.
So again, I'm really, I go, you know what?
I have to be the traditionalist here.
I have to be the one to really sample what like the chef would recommend, which I think
is the cheeseburger in paradise.
And I said.
Which would the chef at Margaritaville.
Yeah.
What would the chef recommend?
Also the server, also the host.
Written in the largest font, like largest point size on the menu.
She did mention the bartender a couple times, which is now making me think that was a fake
out.
It's like Trump's receptionist didn't exist.
Yes.
So I ordered and I said, look, if I'm going to do the cheeseburger in paradise, I'm going
to do the cheeseburger in paradise.
I want the most possible cheeseburger in paradise.
So I ordered a double cheeseburger in paradise.
A couple times a year I treat myself with a double cheeseburger.
As a child, I think I've mentioned this before.
I thought as I kept getting older, I would just keep adding patties to the hamburger.
Cause I remember being like McDonald's having triple cheeseburger on the menu at one point
and I was like 14 or 15.
I was like, well, I think that's just what's going to happen.
I keep getting more patties as I get older.
Oh, finally 38.
My mouth is like this big open.
Your mouth is like a comber in the donuts scene in hell.
So I go, you know what I'm doing?
I'm doing the double cheeseburger in paradise.
And I ordered it and it came and there was one patty.
There was only one patty on the hamburger or on the cheeseburger in paradise.
I mean, they do think math sucks.
Very true.
So normally I think I would have just eaten it.
I don't, it doesn't bother me.
I'm not, I very rarely ever send food back, but this was for a purpose.
This is for a reason.
So I said, I think, so I said, well, I'm so sorry.
You know, like this was an, I don't, maybe she didn't hear double cheeseburger or whatever.
She was very nice and she said, oh, I'll take it back with her.
And I do think pretty quickly she came back out and it was very clear.
They had quickly like cooked a burger and thrown a piece of cheese on it and just sort
of haphazardly laid it on top of the existing cheese.
Not that they needed to make a new one, but the presentation really, there was no time
taken to make it sort of look like an organic.
Yeah.
Those, those cheeses are not relating to anything.
So like, and they're like hanging off the side or whatever.
And I was like, this funny.
Um, but yeah, they, they clearly were just like, ah, shit.
What?
Yeah.
I didn't hear him say it.
All right.
Well throw it on there.
I don't care.
Pick it up, throw it on there and send it back out.
This is also a bold choice because chain restaurant patties aren't usually super
flavorful, but are usually very thick.
Well, they would prove to be very thick as well.
Uh, um, but you didn't, I noticed you didn't jump on the flavorful.
Well, here's what I'll say.
Here's what I'll say is that as I was eating it, I was like, this tastes good to
fine.
It was not the best cheeseburger I've ever, I've ever had, but it's pretty good
or whatever, but the amount of meat is so much.
I cannot finish.
Like I will feel my heart shut down.
If I eat all of this,
but they did offer the double that wasn't out of nowhere.
They do say make it a double or did you?
Yeah, no, I didn't order off.
You didn't pull that out of no.
Okay.
I know the secret menu here.
Throw another Patty on there.
Uh, and I don't think the photo does a good job to convey that one of the patties,
especially was like this thick.
What's an inch?
Yeah.
Close.
Probably a little under, but yeah.
And then there, and then there was like a more normal sized Patty.
They were both, they were mismatched.
Kind of like a lazy dad at a barbecue.
Yes.
Yeah.
So like, yeah, dad was in the kitchen and he's like, ah, whatever.
They're in like, there's consistency.
Who cares?
And he wouldn't have had to worry because usually you're not stacking them together.
Right.
So no one would know that there was a difference.
Literally they're on top of each other.
You can tell.
Um, so, but I'm eating this and I'm just like, the thing has fallen apart.
And now like, I'm just left.
I'm just left with these huge hunks of beef.
Um, that like, and I've had, like, I'm eating, I've eaten all the bun.
I've eaten the vegetables or like, whatever lettuce and tomato.
And it's just, there's so much meat that has a little cheese left in it.
And I'm just like, I cannot finish this.
Listen, it's going to go wild for these photos, by the way.
Oh yeah.
We got some of the best ancillary content you're ever going to see all month long.
So I just remember going, okay, even though this, I have to stop now.
I have to not completely finish this because it feels impossible to finish it.
I don't want to spoil anything about everyone else's, but this was what six people.
I don't think I've ever seen so much food left collectively on a table.
Yes.
It was shocking ways.
Maybe two to three meals were had among the six.
Does that kind of do it?
Yeah.
So, so I will say like, okay, it was fine.
I should not have pressed my luck and sent back for the extra Patty.
That was not a good idea.
I think perhaps if I hadn't done that, it would have been a much more
pleasurable finishing experience.
Pleasure.
Yes.
A pleasurable finishing experience.
Again, in the annals of great Mike.
Great things that I say.
Let the record show that fine to good has been the highest praise of food.
This entire saga.
We'll see.
We'll see if we ever get above it.
And also I asked Mike, I said, who do you think like there's the best?
And that was the review.
Yeah.
And that's by the for sure.
By the way, I am the one who liked the meal the best.
I think.
I think Adam liked his.
We did not hurt.
That's true.
Adam.
No, no, no.
I think Adam made it right.
Okay.
I'm not totally sure what he had.
But the rest of us, I mean, this was the wall.
Like this is the wall.
We all.
This is holding his cheeks like he's seen a ghost with a tunnel, with a tunnel painted on it.
And we all just wily coyote did.
Absolutely.
Yes.
Yeah.
Do you, I let's let's stare each other down.
Who do you think?
I don't really have like a story about mine.
Well, that's the question.
If we're going in ascending horror, I think Jane and I both ran into the same thing, which was, um, she got like.
Uh, pasta dish and it got no chicken made a vegetarian.
And she asked like, how spicy is that?
And they're like, oh, we can put the chili oil on the side and it won't be spicy.
And we got it.
And she took a bite and she's like, it's really spicy even with the oil on the side.
And I took a bite.
I'm like, yeah, that is pretty spicy.
So she didn't get very far.
Maybe it was read somehow as extra oil.
I guess.
But then I ran into a problem.
So I would her jambalaya cause I was going to get fish and chips cause I didn't really have much of an appetite.
And I'm like, oh, that's safe.
And then I'm like, oh, that's so much oil.
That's so much fried food.
And I was like, okay, I'll get jambalaya.
What's that?
Just rice, chicken and, and do we sausage.
I got it with no shrimp.
Uh, cause I don't eat shrimp.
I, my family was convinced at a very young age, I was allergic to shrimp.
And I think it was just, we went to some shitty restaurants, but I've never braved it.
I've never, I've never, but I've had every other kind of shellfish.
So I'm like, I can probably eat shrimp, but I just still have never.
Are you allergic to the Bubba Gump shrimp character who even I just name, I already forget even the,
okay, there you go.
I was going to say, we just, we've talked about it days ago and I already forget.
Jason, if you licked scampi, would you be okay?
Um, I, well, there's a lot of grime on scampi.
So I don't know if I would be okay.
There's a lot of,
the allergies.
If you were grime, I protect you.
Cause you're not touching him.
He's so grimy, you know,
strengthen your tongue.
Jason, if you were post, uh, you were in a sort of a coital situation with scampi,
would it be okay?
An episode?
What?
The coital.
Oh, yeah.
You were in a coital situation with scampi, the Bubba Gump mascot.
I believe it's a phrase.
Well, coital.
Or you think when there's middle.
You can't just say coital unless there's coital.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't know.
When I started having an anaphylactic situation, if I was nailing scampi, I don't
know.
Sector keeper has floated away from his chair.
He's floated away.
His spirit propelled.
He's losing strength.
Scott, this line of conversation was as unpleasant as my meal turned out to be.
So I didn't get the fish and chips.
Instead, I got the jambalaya.
So, okay.
Sorry.
Go on.
I'm back.
Okay.
I don't want to derail.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Um, I got the jambalaya and I took a couple of bites and I'm like, this is the
spiciest goddamn thing I've ever eaten.
And I have a tolerance for spice.
Jane doesn't like spice.
I'm a little, I like spice.
My stomach doesn't.
So I try to go pretty easy on it.
And I've had a fair amount of Cajun Creole food.
So I, but I was not prepared for this.
So my mouth is suddenly on fire and now I'm feeling more lightheaded.
Oh right.
Oh yes.
The light.
So, uh, my mouth is on fire.
I'm starting to have heartburn.
I'm feeling lightheaded.
I believe I'm like having a tough time and I'm like extra vigilant about my
health at the time, like I am trying to ret and I'm like, I don't think I can
eat any, but like I like eat all, maybe like a third of it before I tap tap.
Wow.
Yeah.
You know, like not to underline this situation over, but this may be important
to note that you were like about a week out from being diagnosed with multiple
sclerosis.
So I was one meal is killing you.
It's killing me.
Now again, I had a few days of IV steroids.
I was on the pill steroids, so probably giving me a little bit of a
cushion on the fall.
So I don't think I was in bad shape.
So if you're going to go to Margaritaville, just take steroids before.
Just take a couple of pills, steroids before.
Just get one of those boxes where it's like six to first day, then five, then
four, then get MS if you feel like you need to.
Provolactic steroids.
Yeah.
So, and make sure to use prophylacta if you are having intimacy with any chain
restaurant, you don't know chain restaurant, restaurant, if any, any shrimp
coitus.
Yes, yes.
I don't know sector keeper.
I didn't get the shrimp, but everything was spicy.
Did you know he called shrimp, he said, I didn't get the shrimp.
That's when he's talking about scampi that way.
That's so mean.
No, I didn't get the shrimp in the dish.
I'm just saying.
Right, right.
No, we're talking about the dish.
Is the dish.
The jambalaya was spicier than the scampi.
And I'm not saying like, oh, it's so spicy.
It was like, this is like a dull, unpleasant, it's like when you get a
really spicy one, a buffalo, wow, when you eat one and you're like, oh,
this is a weird, dull heat.
There's no flavor.
It's just unpleasant.
Just the burning and not the fun taste.
I thought I was being responsible, not getting a plate of deep fried food.
Yes.
But wouldn't like the spice wouldn't have been the issue there.
So you know, wow.
So you went both of you avoiding spice ended up with a lot of spice.
Jason, do you think that the ambiance helped or hurt?
Do you think that made you, do you think it would have been better
if you were in a less fun place?
It was a little surreal.
Oh, like the Jimmy hits playing
as I'm like my head in my hand, like pounding ice water,
because I'm just like, I just want and I had also eaten most.
We had gotten like some appetizers.
Oh, yes.
We missed those entirely.
Wait, we got and I don't have much to say about them.
You know what?
In an episode with a lot of negativity, I will say
I do not have a lot of complaints about the
lava lava shrimp.
I stand by it.
I think that whatever sauce they use, chili lime, a whole
whatever is happening in there.
Yes, I like it.
I look forward to having it again.
I agree.
I the word is is it's spelled conch.
How do you actually say this word conch conch?
Yeah.
You know what?
That's funny.
I would have probably said it the first way, but now that I'm self-conscious,
I just realized it's one of those that said different for no fucking reason.
This was one of my requests because it's like, oh, you can only get these at some.
Like this is mostly a thing you can get in Florida.
Did you like it?
I did like it.
All right.
Carrots in those fritters for some reason.
But you got pretzel sticks with it.
What's that?
You're not a carrot guy, Jason.
No, I just was confused whether there was too many carrots.
I have to see if that's and I don't even know if they have it.
We'll have to see if they have it in Hollywood.
If it's a Florida thing.
I did like that.
I like pretzel sticks with mustard sauce and house made queso.
And I liked the chips and guac.
So actually, I forgot the step that appetizer point.
We're feeling OK.
And the icy drinks come out and we start having problems.
And then the main meal, we're having a lot of problems.
Is appetizer point what they call it?
That's just no, that was just a random combo.
No, it's it's and again, one of one of Jimmy's songs.
When it's so 97, that's sailing to app a tizer point.
I'm out.
I can't.
Appetizer point.
I stepped in a bottle of artichoke dip.
I'm mount hungry.
I sailed the case.
Oh, see.
So all right.
So Jason's not looking great.
I didn't I almost didn't realize where you were at,
because I do have a video I took going around the table.
And I did note that when I got to you, you just put your face in front of
you, put your hand in front of your face and said, I don't want to be filmed.
Yeah.
A paparazzi scenario.
Well, I think I was covered in sweat by that point,
which was a mix of probably the food and like the last remnants of the heat.
It was really odd.
We were stuck in heat for a while.
OK, I look, I don't have a lot to say about my I got fish tacos,
which I don't really go wrong with the most places
and where I've had good experiences at in Margaritaville.
I think it's usually what I get there.
I don't think I've usually paid twenty one ninety five for them.
But I don't know.
Look, we've I started going in 2016 and a lot has happened and a lot of inflation.
And so anyway, it hasn't done me wrong before.
But they show up and it is just bathing in.
What is it?
What's a Kramer Kramer?
It is it is taking such a thick, luxurious.
Yeah.
Kramer bath.
It's a lot of white.
It is.
Yes.
The picture you're seeing it from afar.
There's some more white in this.
You can't see fish, can you?
There's no it's like an extra white coleslaw.
You want to strip that there's a place in LA called Best Fish Tacos in Ensenada.
And they, you know, they they give you the
cooked tortilla and the fish and you go over and you dress it how you want.
But traditionally, it's one strip of Kramer, one strip of red sauce or pineapple salsa.
Does that come out of like one of those like icing tubes?
You know, I'm talking about, or is there like there's a pump?
I think it's on places.
But if they make it for you, yeah, usually there's a strip of white sauce
kind of acts similar to tartar sauce to like add a creaminess, you know.
Right.
I'm also looking at this with a bit of fish that I see towards the end.
I don't think it was fried.
I don't think they gave me fried.
Do you think they were like, I don't think I would have ordered.
Was it blackened or grilled?
I the menu only gives you the option seemingly for fried.
And yet I think what's poking out the little bit you can see
amidst the sea of white.
I think I don't think a very light beer batter.
I don't know.
That's extremely light.
That looks more to me like that looks like blackened from a grill or something.
Again, I'm not totally sure.
Do you think that he put all he I'm just assuming there's a man behind
like cooking all this stuff that like fucked up and was just like, I don't know,
throw the white stuff on it and they won't be able to see that it's not.
Just blind them with whites.
Yeah.
Hey, I don't know what hit them.
No, this it looks like the blood that comes out of the androids and aliens.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Like an android died in the kitchen.
Milky blood.
And his head fell right next to my plate.
And I I left a lot.
There's so much left on this plate and entire tortilla because it's just soggy.
Yeah.
That was the after picture.
Uh, yes.
Yeah.
So, yeah, entire tortilla.
I never touched.
Yes.
Yeah.
You're looking at a full plate.
It looks better than the one before, too.
It was it looks more presentable.
Yeah.
You understand what you're looking at.
I should say I think Jane and I at some point in islands were like,
yeah, kind of fading.
Do you want to go back to hotel?
Well, let's add a little energy.
We need to eat anyway.
We'll go to Mark.
We almost dodged this bullet.
We almost were like, oh, we're going to eat the hotel.
We may as well eat at Margaritaville.
You know, well, we also though we you were a little bit probably cajoled into it
because the premise of let's let's like, you know,
we discussed the possibility that you sector keeper would assign us
having to have the exact meal to places.
And when it ended, when it was passed down that it would be Margaritaville,
it's just that that kind of like of all of the meals for this to happen.
Now, this is and by the way,
we're recording this before we know what meal two is like.
We now are going to have to go do this again.
What we have just described.
And I had totally forgotten.
I was like, well, this Margaritaville has never steered me wrong.
And then when I was thinking back on trips with my family,
I remembered one trip where like the first day
I met my dad and brother down there and my dad had like
basically a tooth dying.
My God, he had a toothache and not because of the restaurant,
not because of the restaurant, but he made out with scampi.
And he has an allergic got into an emergency dentist appointment
the next day.
And they I think they just gave me antibiotics and painkillers.
And they're like, when you get back to New Jersey,
you need a go to your regular dentist.
So he went to a dentist in Orlando.
Huh?
He went to an Orlando or a city walk.
Here's the thing.
If you if you were in the city, what is this thing on
first day?
I don't think they have a dentist.
Islands of Adventure dentist at the top of the tower.
Menchie DDS.
Especially in a town like Orlando, there's a whole
string of like you go to the front desk or you go to the concierge and go like,
I needed a doctor.
I needed Dennis.
And they're like, all right, call this number and they will put you in touch
with someone who can see you quickly.
Yeah.
So he had a miserable meal at Margaritaville.
And then another time we were down there,
we got caught in the pouring rain and went into Margaritaville to eat.
And he slipped on the water and like fell on his seat.
And we were all kind of everyone was kind of slipping.
And like, but so I was like, oh, we had no,
it was hard rock that had never steered us wrong before.
We never had a bad meal at Hard Rock.
I got confused.
We didn't go to her.
We didn't go.
Yeah.
Wow.
You have like a Kaiser Soze moment with Margaritaville.
It just had never been me.
I had never gotten it before, but I got hit.
You're dead.
You know, we was fine every time, but like, yeah, it's just,
I just remember I'm miserable in the Margaritaville.
Well, boys, you're going bad.
Yeah.
Great time to find that we have to do this exact thing again.
And you know what?
It's not just us here because as mentioned,
well, I believe Jane will be joining us again.
I'm not making her.
You're not.
OK.
All right.
Never mind.
Jane's out.
Smart move, Jane.
But another friend and for some of us, family will be joining us
as we go this very evening as we record this.
In fact, we will be joined by the level keeper.
But first, we need to get the level keeper's thoughts about
his his alpha experience.
Let's see if we can bring him in now.
Whoa, I know that noise.
Boys, boys.
Oh, he's back.
The level keeper is back.
The sector keeper disappeared in the level keeper.
I guess you guys can't be in the same space or no.
He's scared away whenever he hears.
Oh, yeah.
Trademark cowbell.
Your thing, you know, your thing.
My thing.
I wasn't sure if it really was, but you've proven here that it is.
You always have it.
It is cannon.
It's unavoidable now.
Boys, boys, I'm here to haunt you, much like our Margaritaville meal
from months ago still haunts me.
Well, yeah, we've been talking about what we had for a while,
but we were trying to recall your specific experience level keeper.
What can you tell us about that that fabled Margaritaville one lunch?
Well, I, of course, got a grilled chicken sandwich.
Seems like something you can't screw up.
Trying to order the plainest thing I could, basically.
Yeah, basically the same chain of logic.
Grilled chicken breast, Monterey Jack cheese, applewood smoked bacon,
lettuce, sliced tomato, Dijon aioli.
Feels like a safe order, right?
You would think so.
Yeah, it sucks.
Oh, no.
Oh, you're kidding.
Poor physical composition, hard to handle and or bite.
But applewood smoked.
That's one of those phrases that means something, isn't it?
You know, it's not just some run of the mill bacon.
They took applewood.
They were there was rubbed in rubbed it with apples and wood.
It's smoked and then smoked it.
That wasn't just they didn't just they smoked it like a cigar.
Yeah.
My sandwich from memory was both very dry and soaking wet.
A conundrum.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's wild.
How did your beverage go for you?
Well, my beverage got me drunk,
which took away some of the pain of the sandwich, which means not bad.
You're saying it's a passion fruit.
I believe I got the passion fruit guava.
Let me get this right.
But you saw you were between two drinks.
Somehow it didn't leave enough of an impression to remember forever.
Fruit Guava cocktail.
500 calories, which was margarita,
paradise passion fruit and silver tequilas, guava puree and homemade sweet and sour.
It also came with seemingly 27 maraschino cherry.
And those are big wide brimmed glasses.
It's like a little cherry jacuzzi.
No, it was just in like a straight up cup.
God, it wasn't even a fun.
No, nothing fun.
It's a glass.
But it definitely like kind of dull the pain of the meal.
Well, that's good.
OK.
Maybe that's the idea is like, well, look, margarita is in the name.
Yeah, that's the point of it.
And they won't even notice what they're eating.
My memory is that I felt so defeated after the meal that I went back to my hotel
and did not even attempt to enter the theme parks again for the rest of the day.
That's right.
We did not.
Yeah.
At any point after that, that was the end of our contact with you.
So that means that you were
but then you were stranded and you couldn't like by not coming back,
you didn't get to come back and enjoy the greatest spot for dining.
City walk.
You must have been helpless without it.
Yeah.
Well, I decided.
Let me see if I can make the margaritaville meal feel better in retrospect
by putting it up against an unworthy competitor.
So I went to the quote unquote Tiki bar at the Hilton Garden
or Orlando International Drive, which is a hut.
That's pretty good, though.
Or the pool.
Yeah.
A theming where I was regaled with such theming as a drunk guy yelling the N word.
Oh, God.
And everyone else sitting around the bar
casually talking about how much they like Trump.
No way.
You kept the secret from us until now, levelkeeper.
And I ate a twenty dollar chicken quesadilla
that seemingly was prepared in a microwave.
And it was unquestionably better than my chicken.
Oh, no.
It really hit the spot.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Oh, damning.
What a review with the cowbell of shame.
The ambiance does sound worse for the quesadilla, though.
All I'm saying is that everything was stacked against the quesadilla.
I see what you're saying.
Yes, that horrible, horrible things happening as opposed to a fun volcano
demonstration.
Correct.
Right.
And yet, if you're judging purely food and you didn't end up feeling sicker,
you were improved by the end of the day as opposed to a new life.
Oh, that's good to hear.
Well, and we're just glad that we could like get you in here,
find out about that experience.
And then I because you will also be joining us as we repeat the meal.
Round two for Margaritaville Omega.
You didn't know what you had gotten yourself into.
Double or nothing for Margaritaville, Los Angeles.
The pressure is truly on.
And I also don't mean to like corner you here,
but I feel like a little bit of business has come up.
We've talked about you before.
Sector Keeper said good things about you.
OK.
And as you know, people in your family have our kind of the key.
We haven't gotten a good sense of the the keepers don't seem like a good bunch.
But he said you're like he likes you.
He gets along with you.
Could you imagine if I said the Gardner's don't seem like a good bunch?
It's just from stories.
I heard a day to someone's ghost face.
I can point out the ends of the family that I don't feel the best about.
It's just like they've taken advantage of him and his lottery winnings.
And it doesn't seem like you have.
But also something's up, though.
Mike, do you know what I'm talking about?
I do.
But I think I think of where you're headed is there's a resolution
that has already happened off, Mike, with me.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I found the shirt.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah.
I've I've been.
Are you go?
Where has that all been going?
Oh, I was going to.
I found I thought you had my CityWalk shirt level keeper
that you wore during the live show.
But no, I had stolen it.
Well, I didn't know if it was stolen or taken accidentally.
This is OK, because when the sector keeper was saying
the level keeper is a good guy, I like him.
Yeah.
Mike said, I don't know.
I'm not so sure.
And you're sweet.
So we're finding out now.
I have the shirt.
You did.
So what is it?
This is Christ.
Was it just in another suitcase pocket?
It was actually in a drawer.
It was in a drawer.
OK, I'm like tarred and feathered on a bunch of episodes
that are already.
Not a bunch.
Two.
Oh, not a bunch.
Too too many, if you ask me.
Not a bunch.
One.
And it was a brief comment.
Mike deserves the bell of shame.
Given the bell of shame.
Oh, Mike, how dare you judge it.
We were told explicitly he's one of the good keepers.
I'm sorry to say that about your family.
I wasn't.
I definite about his stealing of the shirt.
I said it's possible.
Also, I want to say a little backhanded, a little loaded to say one of the good ones.
No, I know.
I know.
I feel like some of the people you were at the bar with.
I'm just saying that some of these keepers just said they've been taking advantage
of our friend and she has he been taking advantage of us in turn by crashing at our homes.
Possibly.
A little bit.
Yes.
I don't know.
I'm confused about the entire.
You got a complicated family.
Yeah.
I ask you to judge me as my own ghost boy.
All right.
Well, I'll try to.
You're right, because I had a good time seeing the movie with you.
I had a good time at Margaritaville one, even though it didn't give us a good time.
I have my highest hopes for round two.
I think it's going to be better.
The best meal ever.
All right.
By level keeper.
We'll see you on the whole mega sector.
All right.
OK.
And he's gone.
I guess.
Can you guys.
It's weird that he popped in and then you just you disappeared.
That's right.
Yeah.
You guys can't be is it just maybe too much like like time time
cop rules.
Yeah.
What do you remember?
Wait, what are time?
We're not to put you on the spot.
Oh, no, no.
It's just like a Van Damme touches himself.
I think both Van Dammes die.
Oh, they can't touch each other.
Wow.
Yeah.
Oh, so then it makes sense that they couldn't they couldn't kiss.
No, no.
Two scampi's can't kiss either.
Oh, wow.
Scampi's have time cop rules.
Yeah.
Love.
But of course, any of us could and should kiss scampi.
Yeah.
Right.
Got an allergy.
Yeah.
Well, if you do remember, kiss one scampi, scampi alpha,
and then you have to kiss another scampi, which is scampi omega.
It's more of a scampi.
That's one of those like leveling things out in the multiverse,
keeping things even keeled.
So not a great experience for the level keeper either.
Let me add a couple dimensions to that.
No, I know you had to teleport out, but no, of course.
Yeah.
What do you think?
It wasn't it wasn't good.
And also, wait, so that means you didn't hear that this whole time.
You know, Mike's been accusing your cousin of stealing his shirt.
And then we found out when we talked to him, Mike had the shirt the whole time.
I got the airbrush.
Yeah, I found it.
Where you found where was it?
It was like deep in a drill.
I actually had put it away.
Your shirt was with your other shirts.
You don't say my other deep in a drawer.
Grabbed like a gun.
And fish way in there, way in there were my secrets.
I have really deep drawers.
So you wouldn't even like you can picture it,
but you're actually not picturing it less deep.
That's what people like.
I like listening to the show.
I never met Mike.
Is he a nice guy?
Yeah, but he's got some deep drawers.
He's got some deep drawers.
So anyway, your cousin's being disparaged.
A lot's happening here.
Let me just add a little bit of aftermath because the meal,
I leave the meal not feeling great.
Also on this is really where it's becoming clear.
My voice is just ravaged.
Some of your guys are too, and I don't even know why.
We're just all the day before been a very exhaust.
That's our Epcot food and wine day.
So everybody's like and the park is closed.
That whole thing is happening.
So we're just like it was a breaking point.
It was the wall, as Jason said.
Yeah, I especially at the what?
Like, let me just take a bathroom break and maybe just kind of like
splash a little water on my face.
And then at that exact moment,
because nonstop Jimmy Buffett music is playing,
I hear some familiar notes and I hear his cover of my very
favorite Beach Boys song, Sail on Sailor.
I didn't know that he did sail on sailor.
Oh, OK, let's hear out his version.
Sorry, I know he passed away.
This is dog shit.
You fucking like drenched everything that I like out of the song.
Virgins is more about being there.
OK.
It's not necessarily that he was there.
I would have liked that the singing was way worse
and the instrumentation was more simple.
Yell things instead of singing them when it was live.
But that's for the crowd that's there.
He might have been legally mandated to record it because it had the word sale
not once, but twice.
The Beach Boys fell into that, too.
They started to be I've got summer in it.
We have to do it.
That's the only way we continue.
So that adds to the nausea for me.
You know, the jammed parks, it's crazy.
And then then I take the the water taxi home
and I'm I'm I'm worn down.
I know that I'm just going straight up to the bedroom.
I and I get up there.
I just blackout curtains.
I'm just I'm in the dark.
I'm just I just need to be in the dark for a while here on a day
where we have theme park tickets and it's four p.
m.
But I start feeling a little lonely in this moment
because I did this trip solo.
I'm in the hotel room solo.
There was some thought given to, you know, my son's still young.
He's three.
I don't think we're really going to we're going to bring him
necessarily.
But it was we did think like,
well, you know, we're going to go have a lot of fun in Orlando.
Maybe Aaron, my wife, should join.
Maybe she'd want to join.
And there was some consideration given to that.
And we talked about like and she was like, you know, what I'd like to do
is come for your guys live show and just do Universal.
She didn't even want to set foot at Disney.
Just do like a mini trip.
You just do a couple.
And then once she heard once I started laying out
just how much City Walk was going to be part of this, she bailed out.
Never mind.
I will stay at home.
Yeah.
And and I'm and at that point when she decided not to, I'm like, boy,
I'm going to go have this big fun vacation without her.
And she's just going to be I feel so bad.
She's going to be just stuck doing all the parenting while I'm off
across the country, having the theme park time of my life.
Cut to the day that would have been her universal day
where the only thing she really wanted to do was our beloved ET adventure.
She would not have been able to do it until maybe the very, very end of the day,
because it was shut down due to some water pipe breaking.
So that would have been fucked.
Made all this so glad she didn't come.
Then I'm again, the premise being
I'm going to be having all the theme park fun.
And she's stuck parenting instead.
She's like, I'm going to go have the best time that I can have.
I'll take them to nots.
We'll see how that goes.
Nots had just instituted an incredibly generous, very cost effective annual pass.
The cheapest annual pass you're going to find anywhere in theme park.
So she activates that goes and use it.
So basically, I'm alone in the hotel room and I'm like, I got to check in with a family.
I'm missing the family right now.
Maybe, you know, she's she'll probably tell me like, oh, you know,
he wasn't sleeping and I'm exhausted.
That'll make me feel like all right.
Instead, she says, we're at nots.
We're having a glorious day.
It could not be going better.
The chicken dinner restaurant was a huge hit.
He ate all the fries.
He's got a big smile on his face.
Now we're going to go hit some rides.
And she sends me photos where he's beaming for the first time ever.
He's doing rides by himself.
There's little rides that an adult can't go on.
And he wasn't brave enough last time I went to nots.
Now he's in the little red Baron plane, the biggest smile I've ever seen.
Just a glow.
Then he's on a little truck ride.
He's in the truck by himself.
He's so excited honking the horn.
This ride is now gone.
They've taken it away.
Whatever the little truck ride was has been removed since this happened.
I can never have this experience watching him in a little truck again
because I am across the country in a darkened room, having eaten one of the
worst meals of my life, which is also one of the most expensive meals of my life.
All the theme park fun is across the country.
And at this point, once the test text exchange has happened,
I try to take a little nap and I realize that I cannot do this.
What I need to do is get up, go to the bathroom and throw up.
And I throw up a little bit of this food.
It's not an explosive throw up.
Again, it was a very watery drink.
I cannot blame the sun drinking.
I'm not a person who throws up very often.
I don't do it from drinking.
It's been many years.
I don't do it from just food ever.
And it happened.
This was not necessarily food poisoning.
It was just a scenario of my body doesn't want this to be in me anymore.
So here I am throwing up in the dark while my family is having the time of their
lives across the nation.
You're describing is a very casual vomiting.
Yeah, I feel interesting.
The bit it's all it's honestly.
And I haven't done this in a long time.
It's akin to a puking rally because I did rally.
We went and we're fun.
We did go on the adventure.
We do.
You and I had a little bit more fun that evening.
It's a laid back bar.
Yeah.
Buffett style.
Just like, yeah, I'm puking quick little puke.
Am I remembering correctly?
Did you eat this meal and then go on the Velocicoaster?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Well, that proves you had the best experience food wise.
You're remotely able to do that because I was even I was going through my phone
here just like after I took the photos from Margaritaville.
And I was like, oh, yeah.
What did I do?
I mean, I'm in Port of Ventry.
I'm just like taking photos in a Toon Lagoon.
I'm just loving like seeing gasoline alley and taking the gasoline smell in my nose.
God.
So like, yeah, it was a little bit of a heavy meal.
But I'm like I was on like Cloud 9 compared to everyone else.
You came back to life.
We blacked out for a couple of hours and we also were in a hotel room with two
queens that we were each like stretched out in our own bed.
Like, do not touch me.
And they knew the name of the person who worked at the desk there at the at the
hotel as well.
Oh, he knew.
Oh, my God.
Now I'm blanking on her name.
No, who worked at the the restaurant.
OK, so she was really nice.
Learn the name of somebody at a hotel and shout them out on the podcast like they're
listening.
This this one was Sally.
Love you.
Thanks for the towel, Sally.
She she would always say hi to us.
She was always offering us water and drinks.
And she's like, oh, it's a boat to Sapphire Falls.
Basically, take the boat to rural Pacific and just take the footpath next to it.
And it's about the same amount of time.
If you hit the Margaritaville, you've gone too far.
I did hit the Margaritaville.
Margaritaville next to one of the side entrances to CityWalk.
There is a security gate right there.
How can anyone how can you even be thinking of any of this now?
How are your spirits high enough to talk about it?
And it's good.
It's a hop, skip and a jump away from I'm fucking.
I'm at my lowest.
I'm at my lowest of low.
I don't have some nice lady at the hotel.
Take care of me.
Give me water.
My loves are across the country.
I am in the dark.
I'm in the I'm in the dark as I recall this.
Having little pukes.
Having little pukes and they aren't as easy going as Jimmy makes them out to be
with his famous song, Easy Going Puke.
The Duke of Puke, they call it.
There's a chill as the Duke of Puke.
I should have brought the Tums and Pepto I travel with.
I should have.
Next I'll be next time I'll be prepared.
Have we talked sector here?
Will you allow me to ask a question about Tum Lagoon real quick?
Yes, of course, of course.
OK, I feel like your
your food sacrifices have given you a little bit of wiggle room.
OK, great.
What is this?
There's like a little kiosk that sells beer and like snacks.
But it says at the top, ale to the chief.
Do we know what this is?
Was there a comic strip called Ale to the Chief?
No, is that like a Hagar the Horrible nod?
Might.
That's what I'm wondering.
That's why I'm asking the question.
Viking helmet on her.
This is something you think the sector keeper might know.
No, I'm just I don't want to get in trouble for going out of the bounds of City
Walk.
That's why I'm asking.
So ale to the chief.
But it's just it's like a little hand that looks like Beatle Bailey's hand or
something holding a big beer mug.
And then it says down here slurp and snack or ale to the chief.
And I'm realizing now, what is that from?
What is ale to the chief?
I think it just kind of sounds like a little gentle play on words.
Well, it's like sounds like one.
I.
Yeah, you know,
Jason is determining that it is nothing.
It is not from anything.
It says it says J Ward on the website.
Somehow it has something to do with one of the with Rocky and Bullwinkle.
All right.
Maybe it was like one of those fables or something.
Those other side characters.
OK, well, we'll we'll do a whole episode on it.
I just want to know if anyone knew the answer.
Is it presidential like that?
Well, I mean, obviously that's the reference, but it just has a picture of a guy
holding a hand.
But the building doesn't look looks like a shack.
Yeah.
This to me, this illustrates here I am beaten down.
And then Jason saying it's right by the side entrance.
And here Mike's saying, ale to the chief.
What's that about?
I don't know how you guys are able to maintain.
Well, he was just feeling like shit, but he rebounded quickly to being like,
this illustrates how it goes.
I get down, I stay down.
You guys bounce back up higher than before.
You're going to be back at this Margaritaville.
You just no way you guys don't go back to it.
We went at a wrong time.
This is what happened.
It's not an institutional.
We just had opened.
Obviously, the B squad was working and you guys
ordered one.
How great is the food at Hollywood?
The Hollywood food is OK.
I've never had a bad meal.
Sectorkeeper, hear that?
He said OK.
In fact, yesterday was the anniversary of us going to the Hollywood one.
I got a Facebook memory.
The anniversary of it.
When?
Which one?
The first time we went, I believe so.
As a group, Jason, I went before because we went to the opening and Sajami play
there, which we'll talk about on the other episode.
But yes, it was.
I'll find the picture real quick.
You're talking.
Haven't you already talked about that?
You have to talk about that again.
There's no way that wasn't talked about.
I don't have I don't have to.
No way that wasn't talked about eight times or more.
Maybe 2017 and the fan club from San Diego.
Yes.
See, you know it was my guarantee.
It has been discussed once, if not twice, if not eight times.
I didn't say it hadn't been discussed a little bit.
I'm just saying, like for the true episode about the one in Hollywood.
Look, certainly an important piece of knowledge, a piece of information.
OK, so get the full context crucial.
All right.
Well, look, we have to do that.
We still have to do that.
And tonight, after having heard now you've heard what meals we've had.
Yeah.
Listeners, now we have to go have these again.
The same meals, the same meals.
Correct.
This is what we have backed ourselves into of all the place.
Sectorkeeper.
I know it's an interesting experiment.
Could this not have been Vivo Italian Kitchen?
Could this not have been Ante-Hito's?
I'm sorry, boys.
If those had alphas and omegas, but potentially.
Ante-Hito's made me sick too.
What am I talking about?
All of these places are not good.
So, you know, even if they did, even if they did,
no, you have to.
I'm sorry.
It's just something about the bar, right?
The state.
There's time jumps and there's there's flash points.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it all makes sense.
Alpha is the omega.
Omega is the alpha.
And we're just for beta.
Yeah.
Well, that's true.
Yeah, no, that is correct.
OK, well, so I guess now listeners can get in their own flash point.
And all they have to do is go to the second gate, patreon.
com slash podcast.
The right right now they can hear about this exact same meal occurring at the
Hollywood location.
Should we get this?
We should probably.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, do you see it?
Sectorkeeper, do you see the sector stone?
Is it coming?
Oh, my gosh.
Look at it.
It's the sector.
It's forming.
It's a third patty with cheese.
Wow.
My cheese is still in the wrapper.
Yes.
Look at that.
Not even just thrown on.
It's still in its plastic wrapper.
Wow.
You can ask for it paper style.
So Jimmy's special to make sure you have that on the secret menu.
Hey, it makes well.
You know, look, by the time people are hearing this, you have this pirate is
looking at 40.
You have looked at 40 and it makes sense.
You as you age, you get more and more patties.
Maybe your 40s are the time to start having that third patty.
Third.
Well, I tried third pat.
I think it's time for four.
Sure.
A couple of years when I was 14, I had three.
Oh, you've already done three.
Well, McDonald's used to have a triple cheeseburger on the menu.
And I did it a couple of times because I assume you have to eat more.
I mean, I believe they're bringing back the what was called the grand back for a
little while, but like an XL Big Mac, they think it's already back.
Oh, what was that?
I just I don't like a ton of meat on it.
Places, though, everyone's doing the smash burgers.
Now place their stack in the smash burgers.
So you end up with a giant.
They are.
What do you mean?
I keep now they're stacking.
Double smash burgers on the menu.
But Big Mac has already two patties on it.
I like that one.
I don't like the quarter pounder patty.
That's ridiculous.
Cut to Jason having this burger.
He's complaining about tomorrow.
Mike having it three times this week, it making you sick every time.
Next week, you both go back and do it again.
This is guaranteed.
I know we can still shape what's happening in the multiverse, but certain things we
know certain things can't be diverted from the infinite.
The symbol, the symbol that Jason and I ride on.
You're writing a mobius strip of shitty food.
Well, we got to go write it tonight.
So let's get out here.
Listen, we have to go do it.
But listeners, you can go here right now.
Go to the Patreon.
Besides that, you survived this sector.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for the art, our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the
theme music.
And now please head to the second gate to check out the matching meal
at CityWalk Margaritaville, Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville
CityWalk Hollywood, AKA Omega.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm,
Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit
foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.