When your town has made you frown, When your square has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch, You need a dough that's soaked in Captain Grunge,
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol, A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks, A place where you can tattoo your lower back,
So let's go take a walk, let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight, tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness, a daily,
extremely necessary series exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder that make up
Universal City Walk Orlando.
Well, for the second time today, welcome to Podcast The Ride,
the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness, this time here on the second gate.
At this point,
audience, do you feel like you are getting pummeled by a content bat?
Is it like, are you
overwhelmed?
Do you feel like you need to call the authorities because of how much content we
are inundating you with?
Are you drowning?
It's, Mike Carlson here, yeah, it's a very good question.
I do think what's interesting now that we're doing this for the third time, a saga of this nature,
that really at our fingertips is the ability to destroy your phones.
I didn't even think about
this in a super villain way.
We can really like just take up all the memory on your phones,
slow them way down.
We have so much power here that I didn't even realize.
It's really a way of reasserting the power, just establishing that we're in charge, it's our show,
and if we want to overload your phone and make it so you aren't getting ways reception and then
you don't get to work on time.
Jason Sheridan, let's bring you in on this.
Yeah, you know, the default Apple podcast app hides the turn off automatic downloads in a couple
places.
So if you're not paying attention, yeah, we really could be filling up your phone.
Now you told people not to.
You told people that was wrong.
You shouldn't have done that.
Yeah, yeah, to turn it off.
We want to destroy these things.
We want to overheat them.
Yeah, yeah, we are going full light.
I want the phone to be heavier.
I want you literally to go
pick it up and you go, oh, why is my phone so heavy?
And there's so many podcasts.
I think it's happening.
I mean, I know that seems metaphysical or sci-fi or something,
but also nobody's ever put out this many at a time.
Of course, there are daily podcasts,
The Daily, for example, but that's not as long as these are.
I think we are.
I think we're dragging
people down by the pocket and I hope we are.
And I like it.
I like this feeling.
You like the power.
I like the power.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Yes.
Because just being in someone's ears is a passive experience,
but destroying the device that their life might depend on.
There you go.
Now that's now you're in
the center of the blanket.
We're freeing.
We're like the real, we're Luddites, the original Luddites
destroying textile machines.
Sure, using tech to destroy tech.
I'm just, I'm beating a dead horse here, but we could release every minute a different 24-hour
drone podcast.
Every minute we could set it where it just, you get sent a 24-hour straight,
just a loop of a drone.
Oh, that's what you're saying.
Every minute, next minute, another 24-hour
drone.
Just over and over and over again, locking you out of your phone.
That's a good point.
We aren't really like taking advantage of megabyte heft the way that we could be.
No, we're not.
But this is a start.
We're getting there.
I'm feeling bad.
It feels good to be bad.
Well, after everything that we've been through earlier today, I definitely feel a tad punchy.
And I think it's pretty clear what we're doing.
I think this plan has been
restated a couple of times, but let's make totally sure by checking in with us.
Boys, boys, it's time for the second half of your double mission.
Phase five, sector two B.
B for Buffett.
Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville Omega.
Fins up, boys.
All right.
There it is.
More Margaritaville, this time Omega.
To address some things,
listener, hopefully you're hearing these just back to back, but there's been a healthy amount
of time since the one earlier today that we recorded.
And one thing that came up earlier
today, unless you're doing it the other way, in the Alpha episode, basically, there was a discussion,
Mike's assertion of the 10 Jimmy Buffett songs that regular people know.
A high number.
Again,
you're aiming for destroying phones with high volume of content.
You also believe there are 10
Buffett songs that regular people know.
I'm going to throw another Buffett 10 into the mix.
I guess
Buffett comes in 10s because if you think about it, by my count, and I might be missing a few,
but I think that what we're doing right now might be the 10th Buffett centric, not podcast the ride,
but I'm just going to hear, I'm going to name, it actually straddles a couple of podcasts,
but at least involving you, Mike.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
I think I see what you're saying.
Okay.
I was just going through this list.
All right.
First Buffett podcast experience
probably was in 2015 when Mike was on Doughboys and did Margaritaville, what we're doing again
today.
Margaritaville came up in the City Walk Saga in 2018.
We did Margaritaville Resort Orlando,
where we named the streets.
We did the Times Square Resort, where Jason and Jane stayed.
We did Jimmy Buffett's Christmas albums on Club 3.
If you think about it, Frank Marshall Gate
is essentially a Buffett-oriented experience because Frank Marshall is Jimmy Buffett's best friend.
Then there was the Reprise with Griffin, where he reopened it and we did it all again.
This right now is the third episode in two days on this saga, which brings us up to 10.
10 Jimmy episodes.
Am I missing one?
Have you done another Buffett?
That's a good question.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm forgetting a guest appearance somewhere else.
Besides just the
stray references to him all the time.
I don't want to vocalize that I'm suffering from
Buffett exhaustion.
But for any listeners who are, I see you.
I acknowledge you.
I see what's in
your eyes right now.
I feel for you.
That's all I'm saying.
Tearfully listening and doing the fins
up is a very funny image.
But weakened fins.
They're wobbling.
Those hands might teeter off
ahead at any time.
But am I a crazed man by feeling overwhelmed by this?
I don't think you're a crazed man for thinking that.
I'll be honest with you.
There's some things I
talk about on the show and I feel like no one cares.
There's never a reaction.
But I will say
there's a surprisingly large amount of people that are right on board with all this Buffett content.
I know.
Of course there's no but.
I think it's more than not.
I just wonder about those stray
lost souls who are now in the middle of yet another Buffett sandwich.
To talk punishing, how much punishing we do on this show, I think there's always different topics
that everyone feels punished by that come up every third episode.
So everyone's got their own thing
on podcast that punishes them.
Do the Buffett haters maybe get punished more than some other
types of haters?
Perhaps.
But that's the fun of this show is being punished.
The wheel of death might point to you.
When is it going to fall on you?
At any time.
We all probably kind of like theme parks.
That's the only thing that everybody
kind of agrees on in the audience.
Yeah.
Now which puts a lot of people at a challenging point in
the series where they have been discussed very little.
Of course.
That is not at all.
Barely at all.
Yes.
But yes, I think that like are these guys going to talk about fucking Jay Leno
again?
Like that comes up once around.
What is why?
There's definitely those.
But I will say
we've been sparing with Leno centric topics.
That's true.
Do we reference him every third episode
in some other way?
If Jay's.
Yeah.
But if Jay had Jay's garage at City Walk, hamburger and pizza
restaurant, which is something we should come up with.
Really fucking good idea.
You should have
one on both coasts.
Oh God.
Jay's garage.
You know the microphone that was on his desk.
Yeah.
And what you know, actually he probably wouldn't allow any acknowledgement of his career as a TV
host.
Well of course.
He's very humble.
It would be entirely be like about the cars.
Yeah, of course.
There'd be little nods to it.
But yeah, it wouldn't be not.
It would not be ostentatious.
It would be
not a gross sort of like his old buddies from the old days wouldn't be in there making fun of him
because it wouldn't be too much of like.
Yeah, yeah.
Being a showbiz fancy boy.
Because that's,
you know, I watched the whole Piers Morgan interview with Jay and he says, you know,
he's but he was with his buddies and he had Barack Obama's phone number and his buddies were like,
oh yeah, call Barack Obama.
All right.
And so Jay did to shut his buddies up.
And did he pick up?
He did pick up.
Whoa.
But also this is a story where Jay had been famous for 30 years.
So I
really don't buy completely this story where his buddies don't believe a presidential candidate.
Oh yeah, really?
Jay, you've been on TV for 30 years.
Jay, it's Barack Obama.
Is everything all right?
You're not usually a phone caller.
He must be wrong if you're calling me.
Yeah.
So.
There's
no way I can be in your top 10 emergency contacts.
So literally.
Are they all dead?
Yeah.
If Jay, if Jay had had some sort of place adjacent to a theme park, I think there would
be this many episodes.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I will.
I think.
Yeah.
But you're right that
Buffett is like part of it.
He's it's not unrelated.
It's just boy, it's been a lot.
And I think I'm
worn down by other things too, because the in also in the alpha episode, there was an assertion.
I want to say it was Jason, but I'm not sure.
But I there was something was said,
and I think it's been said before the discussion of the end when you're doing your, what are the
clock somewhere?
Yeah.
And then it was like, oh, that was a hit.
That was the first time he
charted.
He'd never charted.
That one sat with me.
That's not true at all.
He's been on the charts
many, many times.
Is that his first number one then?
I don't think that was number one either.
Maybe on some chart, maybe on a so we can look into it and figure it.
But if we're talking general
charts, that is far from the truth that that was the first time that he'd ever charted,
which just gives me the overall question was that he'd never been on any chart.
I think you can tell
me.
I don't remember.
I had always heard it.
It might be number one.
So I think that is like a
very successful.
All I know is that that was a bigger success somewhat chart wise than a lot of
his other stuff.
But perhaps I misspoke.
Then all of them.
I don't think it's true.
You guys,
I was looking at numbers.
I don't have it all in front of me and he hadn't charted in decades,
but the idea that he'd never been on a chart is simply not true.
If I said that, I don't then I
misspoke or Jason misspoke.
I just think that there was some sort of level of success.
That song had
more than his other stuff.
Yeah, I think Alan Jackson was a real, but perhaps I misspoke.
I
misspoke.
I misspeak all the time.
We can check.
We can check it.
I just know from what I looked at,
this was not even close to a true fact.
And it just leaves me with the question.
Why do I, as the
least, the most minimal Buffett fan of the three, how am I left to track all of the proper truths
about him and all of his friends?
Because enjoying Jimmy Buffett is not sort of a numbers analytics
thing.
It's a feeling thing.
And that's what you're trying to approach.
Has Jimmy ever weighed in on
his feelings about numbers or analytics?
Well, obviously he doesn't care for math.
And what is
there a specific quote on that?
Math sucks with a K.
Whoa.
He hates it so much he misspelled
the title of the song.
With an egg?
Wait.
Okay.
S-U-K-S.
Oh, it's S-U-K-S.
Oh, it's not an X.
It's
not an X.
Okay.
No, no.
That would be actually a way more people spell sucks.
All right.
Math
sucks.
I for one am worried about the PTR curse of mentioning someone they pass away.
Because I
think in one of those early sectors with the carts, I toss out like, oh yeah, they have Dragon
Ball Z stuff for sale.
And of course Akira Toriyama passed recently.
Oh yeah, he died.
Was it before or after the episode came out?
I don't know.
It was like maybe the day off.
Something like that.
Oh, shit.
Hang on.
But we didn't say his name, right?
No.
Toriyama.
Then that's not the curse.
I don't think it's the curse.
I think that's the, yeah.
If we invoke a property, look, if that's the case, then we're killing bewitched writers left and
right that we don't even know about because they aren't even in the papers.
But we've murdered
I Dream of Genie writers.
They could all fill a mass grave if it's mentioning the property at all.
Puts my mind at ease a little, although unlocked the fact that like, oh yeah, I don't think it's
when I was like in middle school and starting high school.
It was on very weird times on the
WB or UPN.
And I would always catch a head.
So you want to say like a nice eulogy to him then?
Oh, well, he's, you know, up in heaven now.
But that's the thing.
I've internalized it.
Incredible.
He rode on his fine cloud up to heaven.
He is in a hyperbaric chamber getting
stronger.
He says stronger and stronger.
No, I was hyper.
You get a chamber when you go to heaven.
Well, he trains in it and becomes even stronger.
But my next thing was going to be that like, oh,
I like classic Simpsons.
It's like, oh, it's all internal.
Like, I don't know if I can just pluck,
you know, specifics or lines like I used to be able to with classic Simpsons.
What is you mean?
Dragon Ball Z?
Dragon Ball Z.
Yeah.
Well, then it's also very stretched out.
So you're not going to be able to toss out a barrage of Dragon Ball Z quotes through the full
episode?
I'm not.
No.
Well, and then you get into subs and dubs, you know, getting into that argument.
Okay.
I shouldn't say this.
Guys, we've already had an episode today.
How many more sidetracks
are we going to have?
You're right.
We talk about our meal.
You know what?
I won't say it.
How
important is it?
Not important at all because I've been worried about something I said a few weeks
ago, but nothing has happened and I shouldn't put the evil back out into the world again.
What is it?
Just I mentioned another old man, but I really mentioned him in harsh terms.
Oh.
In the sense that I dared the universe to do something.
You had a lot of very cruel things to
say about Akira Toriyama.
No, I was not Akira.
I was not talking about the man.
Check the tape.
Look, he's in heaven, okay?
He's in heaven now.
That's where we leave it.
Let's leave it there.
He's in heaven now.
We have a lot of work to do here today, though.
All right.
We did Margaritaville
again, like the Sector Keeper told us to do.
We went there to the Omega version, which is Hollywood,
which have we been there before?
Absolutely.
Of course we've been there before.
It's the
fourth podcast about this, but we went back and we replicated a meal as closely as we could.
This
was a bit of a West Coast reunion of the previous terrible meal.
Jane was there.
The Level Keeper
was there.
Adam from Universal Orlando was not there, but we did get a little surprise cameo by
Eric Madden, a very supportive listener and two-time Club 3 Topic winner.
Thank you, Eric,
for some great topics and for saying hi.
Must have been weird, I feel like, because maybe
one bit of context for our meal, this is a very vacant restaurant.
This was about as deserted as
could be.
It must have been weird for him that he is in an almost entirely empty restaurant,
only to discover that the majority of the other customers are all from a podcast that he listens
to.
More than half, besides his group of who was in there, I think, are all us and Jane and Level
Keeper.
It's crazy.
I'm sure that was surreal, but then also, of course, that's who we saw there in
a way too.
You may expect to, yeah.
Yeah.
I was leaving the bathroom and I saw him and he goes,
Mike, what?
There was a noise he made that I remember.
He's like, huh?
I was like, yeah,
I guess we're here.
Hey, look over there.
Everyone.
All the characters are here.
Yes, but as much as I think there would have been a point in time where we might have been
much more likely to all be found there, but this definitely did have to be arranged and
forced, given the earlier experience in Orlando.
Yes.
We had to really toughen up.
We're going into
battle.
We're doing this again.
Can we bear another one of these margaritaville meals?
Yeah,
yeah, for sure.
So yes, it was, yeah, as you're saying, in the old days, we frequented this
location pre-babies, pre-COVID and everything.
Yeah.
That's obviously cut down some of our city
what goings to, though I feel like we've, especially because of the saga, but they've been a
little more frequent.
It is a re-spike.
It's coming back.
Yeah, yeah, which
led to some.
Nature is healing, as they say, as all the people say online.
Never been more back.
So basically, I mean, can we start talking meal or is this, do you have to tell the story that I
swear to God you've told?
Oh, that we saw Jimmie play?
There's no way this has not been, maybe,
I need some punishment if you have not told this story before.
Well, you know what, let me do this.
You certainly told it in reality to me plenty of times.
Yeah, well, okay, I really won't tell the
full story again.
I'll briefly recap it and then I will make a larger point about that.
I hopefully
will call it the rest of this episode.
Okay.
So this location.
Do you not agree with me,
though?
That there's no way it says it's been told three times.
Yeah, I've told the story before.
The story is that, yes, when working for Screen Junkies, the old YouTube channel, of course,
that I would do a show called Movie Fights, I got press passes and a camera guy and another
press pass for my assistant, Jason Sheridan, to assist me at the opening of This Margaritaville
and Jimmie Buffett played.
The whole band played and it was like, I don't know, there were fans
there or whatever.
And I'm sure I told the story, because I love the story where I'm trying to find
Jason to help me do something and he's at the table taking the free hamburgers and stuff on a
sampling the small and you're like, your hands were full.
So you could not help me out at all.
There was no help being given.
Not that I needed a ton of stuff.
I was just like, oh yeah, where's
Jason?
Like he could go handle talking to or like ask a question for us or whatever.
We had been
getting nowhere and I think I was like, I'm going to go get some food.
I have, you know what we
haven't done is we haven't released this footage.
Oh yeah.
I do think I have it.
Sure.
So we should
just release that.
If you've got it, then absolutely.
Yeah, that would be cool.
Yeah.
You're behind the second gate or even club three.
We could put it behind the paywall.
Yeah.
But
there's, yeah.
So, so, and I play a hiding out in a Pelicans beak song for people.
You just went to random people at this.
Yes.
Which is what got everybody so scared at the opening,
the people that were working there, like the PR people thought something was going to go wrong.
Or so like we were coming to like fuck with Jimmy or something, which of course we would never do.
But they eventually once I honestly, and I've still this, I've told this story before, but
I swear to God, once Jimmy played, everyone chilled out.
All the employees were like,
what do you need?
Do you want us to help wrangle guests so you can get them on camera?
We'll help
you do whatever you want.
And I swear before that, everybody was being very weird toward us.
Like Christ, he changed the mood in there.
Very fabric.
And then everybody was ready to party.
Oh wow.
And the point, and I'll tie this.
So, so that's like the sec, maybe that we went,
we all went like opening day or opening week.
We all, there's a picture.
I just got a memory
about it recently when we were actually here, I think for the, for a Omega episode.
I've had a
birthday there.
I will say this.
I have not had a meal in there in a while and man, am I nostalgic
for this fucking place.
I felt real nostalgia when I was in here.
I had such like warm feelings that
I was like, oh, I had a birthday.
Like I had things here.
We've had a lot of meals here.
I have nice memories.
Yeah.
This place is empty and it seems like how can it sustain much longer?
But I really was struck by, oh man, so much of my life has been spent in this Margaritaville.
So many times have I had nice friends, friend interactions and meals and, you know, margaritas
on the porch.
I've hung out on the porch multiple times with different people.
My friend, Luke,
who should be on the podcast maybe later this year about Wisconsin Dells.
I told him about
some like unpleasant medical thing and he almost passed out back there.
Like I have so many,
there's so many things that have happened that I just, as soon as I was back here,
I had such good feeling.
I had such warm memories and I hope it doesn't just get closed all of a
sudden with no warning.
At this point, just with everything you've put on it in times of friends.
Even though we consider it decor wise, vibe wise, and more perfunctory Margaritaville.
Right.
But it doesn't matter.
It's what you make it.
It's what you put in there.
That's right.
What memories are stored.
And we should also give the context.
We were up there during about the third or fourth quarter
of the Super Bowl.
Yes.
We did watch the-
That was- We watched the end.
Yeah.
We watched the pretty exciting end of the Super Bowl.
Then you're like, oh, that's why nobody's here is because of Super Bowl.
You're also like,
well, it'd be kind of a fun place to watch.
There was a fun place to watch the Super Bowl.
It has not landed in anyone's head.
Yeah.
More people were there when we left.
At the very least, or at least like extra 20 people.
There was maybe 15 people eating when we started.
That's generous.
Maybe there were 30 people, 35 people when we left.
I think some movies they got now.
The park was closing.
Yeah.
There were a few more people.
Before that line, it was in the 536 kind of zone.
Eric said he was out there.
He was going to the Dune part one re-release
because there was an IMAX up at City Wall.
Right.
But yeah, any moment this could close.
Yeah.
I think so.
Well, it is, since we've talked about it, it was immortalized in the
smash hit Emmy nominated series, Jury Duty, which Andrew Weinberg was on the show put together.
So now there's this whole long sequence of events at this Margaritaville where they had to build
mirror walls and hide a crew and a whole operation happened.
Then I think they went back and had a
party up there to celebrate the show.
Yeah.
So that gave it some shine.
I think people were thinking about Margaritaville if they watched that.
Good.
James Marsden's been there.
Wow.
A celebrity was paid to be there.
That makes me feel good.
Yeah.
I like him.
It feels like Mojo.
But the real question is how does it compare as an experience and as a meal?
Because this was our
main goal was to experience the same meal choice of all the darts we could have thrown at all the
restaurants that have establishments at both.
We chose Margaritaville.
I had a pretty horrible
time and the rest I don't think I have anything else great to say.
So going back, there's nowhere
to go but up.
You would think.
You'd think.
You would think, yeah.
You would hope.
You would really
put your feet.
Cross your fingers so hard that they start to bleed.
That is how that's what I was going to do.
Your finger bones start cracking a little bit.
You're crossing them so aggressively.
I snapped the tops of my finger bones off.
Yeah.
We were almost, I will say we were seated at a booth and then we were moved to a bigger table.
I was excited because it looked like Jason was going to be able to, I have a photo here,
Jason was going to be able to change the temperature in the restaurant.
It looked like there was a thermostat.
I was sitting next to the thermostat.
Yeah.
And you got really excited.
I was like, oh good, Jason will be able to surf the temperature in here.
Surf it out.
A couple types of surfing.
It's under a picture of Jimmy surfing on the wall.
That must be why they put it there.
They're probably thinking about temperature surfing.
Don't make it too hot or too cold.
Electricity ain't free.
Was that Jimmy saying that?
That was Jimmy.
He's chill.
He's a dad.
He's got a paper.
Dad are always worried about the thermostat.
That is true.
Look, that happened to Scott and I when we became fathers.
Oh yeah.
Y'all constant.
Hyper obsessive about the thermostat.
Hard to do in California.
The insulation is so terrible everywhere.
Oh, we know.
We're pretending, we're doing the dad bit and Jason sounds more like a dad than any dad I've ever met.
I gotta crank it to the 70s to feel anything.
And I like my apartment building.
It's a nice building.
It gets really drafty.
That had the tone of something really like darkly sexual or something too.
Or like I have to just to feel anything I have to.
I have to crank it up to 70 to feel anything.
Just to feel anything.
It's like from the movie Crank.
I have to take seven Viagra just to feel something.
Oh my god.
Just to get a little hint of a feeling.
Well I was just talking about thermostats.
I don't know why you had to take it and make it filthy.
It was you.
The tone is what really inspired me.
I maintain.
Let's talk about appetizers.
All right.
Go ahead.
So the appetizer menu was all right in Orlando.
It was one of the relative successes.
That's right.
Of the experience.
And yet two of these were not available.
Pretzel sticks were nowhere to be found.
Why do we decide that we say C-O-N-C-H?
I believe Conch or Conch.
Either one is acceptable.
Great.
Conch.
They didn't have Conch fritters.
No Conch.
So we're down again a little bit because two of the only good things are the other one
unavailable.
We did a trade out for fried pickles which I thought were pretty good.
Pretty good.
I agree.
Now we're cooking.
Pretty good.
We went with Lava Lava Shrimp which I spoke highly of and have at most of these establishments.
In doing a side-by-side comparison, noticed $1 cheaper.
$1 cheaper.
And okay, so this puts, I see.
So maybe, I mean, because I thought that was a
strangely expensive meal to be so terrible in Orlando.
Yeah.
So like, okay, if this price is coming down, that makes me feel all right.
And then the Lava Lava Shrimp comes out, I think mildly superior.
Almost the same, but like a 2%
bump.
So we save a buck, we tiny, the fraction of quality.
Okay, mood's looking up a little bit.
Yeah.
No, I agree.
There was a feeling food-wise of like, okay, like a cautious optimism.
Yeah.
There was another appetizer, but we will let a guest explain that.
Drinks.
Drinks did nothing good to set the tone for me in Orlando.
I got the same drink,
as it was available.
This is the perfect margarita, which it was anything but in Orlando.
Comparing the two, $1.
25 cheaper out here.
I like this.
This is good.
This little shavings
make you feel a little better.
Yeah.
How often is something cheaper in Hollywood, California?
This is true.
Yeah.
And then it makes you wonder prices in Texas or
other states this establishment is in.
Slight differences in the copy.
In the Orlando one,
it said for margarita aficionados.
What a boast.
Over here, it said for margarita aficionados only.
Yeah.
I am so curious about all these little changes.
That's interesting to me.
It was a very different menu in a lot of ways.
I think more items.
It felt like a more busy,
stacked menu, but kind of the same fonts and types of photos they're drawing from.
a fairly different copy like that.
Well, when I go to Comic Con this year and I go down to, of course, the margaritaville that'll
be the top of the new San Diego Margaritaville Hotel, we'll do another episode and then we'll
talk about what the changes in the copy are there.
We're in heaven.
It's number 11.
Because as you know, I'm sure I did a chunk on going up to that restaurant and it was not
fully themed yet.
So I was getting a menu from the old restaurant, even though it had the
margaritaville tables.
There's a whole other one.
What episode was that?
That's a good question.
I don't remember.
Oh, wow.
But I definitely mentioned on the show.
So yeah, I assume it's fully themed now and I assume it is full copy and everything.
That'll be correct.
So in July, we'll talk about that.
Did earlier today's experience do anything to make your faith in this brand waver in any way?
Because here we are talking about future plans, future episode discussions even.
Yeah, that's a good question.
That was a bad, I know mine was worse,
but that was not good.
And but yet nothing.
Yeah.
Well, again, I think I had the best technical experience, just the fact that the
burger was a little misshapen and rushed the extra patty thrown on in a hasty manner.
That's probably what was not finished yet.
Yeah.
But as far as the taste was OK,
I mean, I have thoughts.
I actually have, I think,
thought some criticism that I will level against something here, but I'll get to that in a second.
So for me, though, I mean, again, it's the feeling.
I went in there and it's more about that feeling.
It's more about
to feel something like a thermostat boy like myself with the 70.
Yes.
Sometimes I just go into the Margaritaville just to feel something,
just to get an erection.
Crank it up to 70.
He admitted it.
Not the time.
Sometimes.
Look, look, I've turned.
I'm an older man now.
And sometimes you need help.
And the help I need is to go up to City Walk and go to a Margaritaville.
All you have to do and then I will get fully of intercourse is to just go up,
get through some parking hassle.
I actually they rerouted me over this.
I ended up in Jurassic instead of Curious George.
And then I was surprised by.
Then you do that.
Then you have an hour and a half sit down meal.
Then you drive back down the hill, fight through some traffic and then you can go fuck.
Yeah, of course.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
First of all, everybody knew what I was saying.
So you didn't actually have to explain all that,
but they knew what I meant.
That's all part of it, too.
That's all part of parking hassle also adds to the erection.
It's very, yes, unpredictable.
It's finally deep into the side.
We're finally cutting through what has all been about.
It all turns us all on.
You get it now.
Restores parking.
This is to get hard.
You don't have to click on those Instagram ads for every like,
you know, hymns or Roman or all those, you know,
Internet startups where it's like, well, you see a doctor, quote unquote.
No, the only ones you should ever use are ones that happen to get advertised on this show.
Of course.
We picked the good ones.
But other than that, we search high and low for quality.
Sure.
So the the just oh, if you unless you had more, but no, I don't know.
But clearly it's still it's still coursing through your veins.
I don't think what we figured out the meal could have been 10 times worse in Orlando.
And I don't think my faith would have been shaken.
I don't think it would have mattered a fucking ounce.
This is I mean, I guess, you know, it's a bit of a religion for you.
And, you know, if you're truly into a faith, you don't bail just because no race gave a bad homily.
No, absolutely.
Now, if he puked on me in the homily,
which feels like aesthetically akin to the meal I had, maybe I'd at least take one week off of church.
But besides that, yeah, I mean, certainly you yeah, you adjust your expectations for church.
You know, if I got food poisoning at both these locations, maybe I just don't order the food.
I go in and have the perfect margarita.
You know, you just change exactly what you do.
You don't ever change that you go.
Exactly.
Going is the basis of the faith.
But that's all that's another.
You make a commitment that when you go into a chain restaurant, that is a sacred bond.
You don't ever break that.
Yeah.
And that's I think you can expand that out into this philosophy we have with CityWalk.
I think it's really what is going on here.
I mean, look, I can quibble with I this one's
dead to me.
That one's dead to me.
I still go.
You'll go and end up up there.
You'll just make adjustments.
That's really all you learn.
You're right.
You make a broad scale.
It is what I'm doing.
Right.
Yep.
You have you.
Your religion is CityWalk and you will never let that get out.
That will never leave you.
That is something you will believe until the day you die.
All you will do, though, is like avoid a certain wet burrito because it may be shit uncontrollably.
That's the difference.
That's what we're talking about here.
That's the premise of this whole saga in a lot of ways.
Just change you.
Make little changes
to your behavior.
Yes.
To avoid the shitting.
And we honor our Christ,
who is a ghost boy who got a staph infection in a fountain.
And he was seated at the right hand of Jimmy Buffett.
Oh, yeah.
Forever and ever.
Amen.
Yes, man.
The margarita shows up and unlike the other one, it wasn't all ice.
I could taste margarita ingredients.
Yeah.
I could taste alcohol.
This was a superior experience.
We're looking good at this point.
I gotta say by just the drink round looking all right.
You guys anything at the drink round?
I mean, I just had a bottle beer again,
the Landshark Lager, and it was pretty much the same, which was fine.
Good.
Sure.
OK.
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
I ordered a beer at one point and then they made me have the experience
of the bottle.
Yes, right.
Not the draft.
And you choose that because you can look at I was forced into it.
I was like, I want a draft, though.
I'm so drinking a bottle of a restaurant.
You didn't just like looking at it.
Why else am I getting a beer here?
Yeah, that's the only one where I would choose the bottle.
Otherwise, you're not doing that.
Otherwise, I'm not.
Yeah, I don't.
I will.
I don't care.
I don't care that much.
But yeah, of course, if you've got a good draft and it's got
the foam on top and everything like that is obviously superior chilled, nicely chilled glass.
And I like this setup for Landshark Lager.
Landshark on draft.
Yeah.
I should have specified maybe is what I should have done because they do have the draft.
Yeah, I don't know why it didn't come.
So I guess that's a complaint, but not a big complaint.
Also, the same beer meals.
I don't know which order to go in.
Does anyone feel like they have more of a story than not about their meal?
I don't really.
I mean, mine isn't so spectacular.
OK.
Do you want to start with Jason?
Because, Jason, you were you got special permission from the sector keeper.
Yes.
You and only you were able to adjust your meal and not have the terrible jambalaya.
Jambalaya.
OK.
Which I believe in Florida, the thing that did me in.
I scream.
Oh, on the menu, it says there's poison in it.
Yeah.
There's rat poison.
It's poison.
It says you get what you deserve, little pig.
And so I was like, I don't even know why I picked that.
If that's the language.
You was it was a challenge.
You get what you deserve, you little pig.
That is what I heard from Swine Not.
Jimmy Buffett's pig character.
That's come up in an episode.
Didn't that Christmas album have some weird song about like running the pig to nut.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But I don't think it was Rumpy from Swine Not, his book that he wrote.
So in Florida, what I opted for was the sausage, sausage and chicken.
Jimmy's jam and jambalaya, Cajun rice, spicy broth, which was weird because there there's no any broth
gets absorbed by the rice.
And the thing that did me in Florida was it immediately made me lightheaded
and was far too spicy.
So out here, I opted for what I thought was very safe and thankfully
did turn out to be very safe.
Got too many Margaritaville websites open and they keep reloading.
How much?
Wait, wait, wait.
List all the websites you have.
Just the two, Orlando and Hollywood.
You're looking at the menus.
Maybe at the San Diego Hotel open too.
Booking a stay maybe.
Sorry, I will not be staying at that San Diego Hotel.
Why not?
So I don't know.
I don't think I'll be heading to Comic-Con anytime soon.
I got the Landshark Lager fish and chips this time.
Hand dipped in our Landshark batter,
jalapeno tartar sauce, cilantro, lime, cold salt, french fries.
It was fine.
It did not hurt me.
It tasted like slightly nicer fish sticks.
But it was a little spicy.
But a fast food version of spice.
Yes, it was the tartar sauce.
The jalapeno was a little
spicier.
Oh, it was okay.
But yeah, it was good.
It's what initially I was going to try to order in Florida and then I went,
too much fried food.
I should get rice and chicken.
No, my first instinct of all that
fried food.
It's safe.
It can't hurt me.
That searing hot oil it's cooked in.
Cooks away
imperfection.
It cooks away all your troubles.
That's the way I think about it.
If you're having various problems, ailments, hot oil is always going to be there.
That's your best bet.
So let's all, I'm drinking more soda.
I'm eating more fried food.
That's your New Year's resolution in 2024.
I'm thriving.
Guzzling more oil.
More hot oil.
Drill baby drill is Jason's road to hell.
Hot oil though, would it warm you up when the thermostat isn't doing what you want it to do?
Yeah, little warm fish and chips, which I would call these warm, not hot.
That sounds like shit.
You're issuing a compliment, but you wouldn't call them hot.
You'd call them warm.
Well, we add a little bit of, I just started eating mine and Jane,
she also got something slightly different.
I said, I'm not going to make you order the same thing,
which she had gotten like blackened chicken Alfredo, I think in Orlando, not on the menu out here.
Okay, different.
So she ordered the garlic cream pasta.
Wait, sorry, Bullet Mist, different Bullet Chosen.
Yes.
But it's basically like practically butter noodles.
She got the garlic cream pasta.
It's cavatapi or herb garlic cream sauce.
That's what she ordered.
What she got was the
brought out was the lemon Parmesan pasta filled with shrimp.
And I think she had flagged down the
waiter and go like, hi, this is not what I ordered and I didn't ask for any shrimp in it.
So they happily took it back and, oh, I don't know about happily, but I feel like they brought her
the right thing.
They wanted her to eat that shrimp so bad.
They brought her the right-
They were so bummed out.
They were, yeah, they didn't get to watch her eat the shrimp.
They said, could you eat it though, maybe?
Oh yeah, we understand.
Yeah.
Eat it please though.
Yeah, they said that.
They did bring her the right thing.
And I feel like that someone said a comment
like, sorry, the chef thought every pasta had shrimp in it, which is not correct.
So a little bit of ordering hijinks.
There was a, yeah, when the chef learned the term pasta,
when this was taught in cooking school.
Yeah.
You think like-
If this was his first day or her, whoever's first day, I'm impressed with just the okayness
of everything else.
Yes, true.
If that was the first day.
Yes, because otherwise pretty, other than the thinking of the basic definition of pasta,
includes shrimp.
Right.
Or the specific day.
Maybe there's this one dish, there was some cute-
Maybe no one ever ordered this dish before.
This is possible.
Have I told this story before,
or have I told it 20 times, or about the being at the Knott's Chicken Dinner restaurant where
Erin ordered something vegetarian and then the waitress is like, oh, yes, yes.
And then it took
an hour and a half to two hours to appear because no one's ever ordered this ever.
It's not on the
menu anymore.
Somebody had to hurry to the store.
This is always, I can't think of a good example,
but this is a very funny phenomenon in a store or a restaurant when you're sure you've stumped the
person and then there's just too much going on.
Yeah, yeah.
Where they won't say no.
Right.
And yet there's just a, and that's going to be right out.
It's going to be right out.
It is coming.
You're my friend.
Bigger smiles at you than anyone else at the table.
I mean, it's just funny because you point at the menu and you're like, here, it's right here.
I'm not crazy, I swear.
Yeah, that's true.
But some of these play, it's just like,
some things might get put on menus just as a blue sky to make somebody on the board happy.
And then years go by and no one orders it until all of a sudden one person throws the whole thing
for a loop.
And they have to go knock on the doors of all the other CityWalk kitchens.
Do you have this kind of pepper?
Do you have any help?
Do not have this.
They Google, like there's a computer out on the stove.
How do you do this?
I don't know how to do
that.
That's what I would be like doing, being a chef.
Yeah, exactly what I'd be like.
Long story short, my meal of fish sticks and ice water was a better experience than Jambalaya
and Bahama Mama.
I know that sounds insane, but I was like, after the Florida, I was like,
I do not, I cannot afford to repeat that experience.
Yes, there was this, you know,
like not to have your health issues front and center, but I thought it was kind of funny that
you said, I can't do the same thing again.
And we didn't realize that's why.
And Mike and I were
like, no, no, no, you have to.
And you said, no, no, no, I'll die.
I have things to do.
There
were important things you had to do in a few days.
Yes, I did.
I couldn't get, I had had like a bad
flare up from food poisoning and from a cold.
And I was like, I don't want to tempt fate.
I'm
ordering something very plain.
Jason, I have appointments.
Jason, where was the food poisoning
from?
Where did the food poisoning happen?
I think it was like at a yogurt from my house
that had been in there too long.
Okay.
Because God knows if it was yet again here.
I know you had a, wait, like a Yoplait or something?
Like a Chobani?
No.
But was it like
expired?
Like what?
I, it must have been.
I didn't see the date.
Like they, they, we had a bunch in
there that weren't expired, but.
It sounds like it was expired.
Maybe it was a day or two past
and I got the date wrong.
Suddenly then Jason's like, well, I don't know.
Cause all I had in that
24 hours was that yogurt and a lobster and cheese crepe from the crepe cafe at city walk.
I know it
wasn't that.
So it was a one day old Chobani yogurt.
That must have been what it was.
The
K and crab with the K is never done.
You can never get sick off that.
You can not get suck
off imitation crab.
You've asserted this.
I'm sure some places maybe have prepared and gotten people
sick.
Was that is crab with a K?
It's never done me wrong.
Crab with a K.
Like man, that sucks.
With a K.
Yeah.
If you see, if you see a K or you don't always see a K.
Just a K, no C.
But it's the K
of quality.
For example, if you see K and the word quality, if you see, if you're the first star
promises quality and it's KWA.
Yeah.
Then you know it's good.
You gotta go.
Um, let me,
I'll go to mine.
Uh, uh, I once again got fish tacos.
I did repeat it.
Right.
One dollar
cheaper yet again.
I like, I wouldn't normally be so nickel and dime except when the first meal
you're dealing with is terrible.
This is all about comparisons as well.
That's what these two episodes
are all about.
The little things, um, such as that also they don't boast crispy land shark
batter.
Uh, so there's not that fake thing they put in it because I don't, you know, they didn't say
crispy batter, but the tacos did appear and they were crispy, which the other ones were not at all.
Those are a soggy mess.
Yeah.
There was a little bit of a crunch to these.
Um, and the big, the thing
that blew my mind that would not normally, but given what we'd been through, this small detail
made so much difference.
And that was the little zigzag taco tray.
How far does that go
for presentation and practicality that we're, you know, so the, so that means that the tacos aren't
laying in a pool of Kramer suffocated by Kramer, even if that Kramer was there drowning in a shallow
pool.
These tacos were sad because you feel a shallow pool.
It should have been able to get up.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Your plate in Hollywood was very aesthetically pleasing.
Very, very might be over
doing it, but in comparison, it looked good.
Like a room, like it, it compared to the Orlando was
like a room service, big serving tray with the big like cover of the lid you pull off and the butler
is like, uh, your meal is served, sir.
Whatever, however he sounds, I don't have served.
I'm the
Butler.
I, I, I, yeah, I don't, that I'm not like, I don't have to pick up the tacos off of the,
off of the plates.
They are elevated for me.
Well, they're that much closer to my mouth.
So I will
save so much more work with my elbow.
So that's great.
And it's not, they aren't going to get
suffocated.
This, this little touch made a big difference.
Also the fact that like the,
that they separated the rice and beans instead of plopping the gross beans on top of the gross
rice, thus making it one inseparable pool.
It gave me the choice.
Suddenly I am like,
maybe you need these terrifying experiences to appreciate basics because now things about regular
okay, Mexican restaurants suddenly I like, oh yes, I like that I can control my own portions of race
beans.
Yeah, no little things like, I don't know.
It's just like the, it's like the sun's seeming
brighter to me now as usual, you know, Margaritaville Hollywood, Margaritaville Omega has
sort of taught us a lesson, taught you a lesson and now you'll never forget it.
It'll be a memory
from there to not, not a look, whatever, not a gift towards him.
Now look, overlook something as
as a separation between rice and beans.
Yeah.
Now when, yeah, when I experienced that, I know that
there's, this has been done with, with quality, with a quality, with a K and a chef's kiss.
Exactly.
And also with a K and a K and chef.
It's beautiful.
So better, definitely better.
Better.
Yeah.
Mike.
Okay.
Double cheeseburger in paradise with a land shark logger.
This was my order in
I will say the one in Hollywood certainly was better presented.
Well, now wasn't there, there
was, this is a slight thing.
Did, did you not customize the Orlando one to have the second
patty?
No, I did not.
It was on the menu.
Oh, I thought you, oh, I had this mistake.
They were
both on the menu.
They were both double.
That's the only reason I ordered.
I would not stray from the
menu for this assignment.
I see.
Okay.
Yeah.
I just felt like, second patty.
Exactly.
I just
felt like I wanted to get the iconic dish.
But then when I saw there were two patties, I said,
maybe what would be better than getting the iconic dish, but double.
They do offer a double.
Exactly.
It's on the end.
It's on both menus.
Which makes it so much stranger to me now that
it was so weird because you described something as if they had never done this before.
Well,
right.
Especially the first time.
I think that she just misheard me, the waiter in Orlando,
but yeah, it's on, there's the two, they have two different sections.
This is the Hollywood menu.
So I already, yes, double cheeseburger.
And they, they heard me correctly the first time and it came
with two patties.
And I think there was a little more beef in Orlando, but there was still a
fucking ton of beef in Hollywood.
And I've said this before on the show, probably on the last
episode that like once a year I go, yeah, I'll get a double cheeseburger from Wendy's.
And sometimes
I go, man, the double cheeseburger Wendy's, that's the right amount of beef.
That's delicious.
I don't
do that a lot, but at once in a while, it's, it's a nice thing.
No double cheeseburger from Margaritaville.
Do not do it.
It's too much beef.
It doesn't taste bad necessarily.
It tastes fine, but it's too much
beef.
I did it twice, both places.
I just, I don't know what the poundage is on these actual patties
is not finishable by a person that wants any of their arteries to remain unclogged.
There's,
there's a percentage I feel like of the full burger that should be the patty.
Yeah.
And I don't know
what that is, but it's not more than 60.
No, and this much like Orlando, I left a similar amount of
beef sitting on the plate.
I was wondering, I was like, I see that pile, but I'm not going to ask.
And it's still a dirty pile of beef was sitting on my plate when I left.
I like to be a clean plate
boy in general, but I couldn't be a clean plate boy.
You realize they'll know, right?
You probably
should go find a planner to throw that in.
Yes, absolutely.
I should have done that.
I try, you
know, I tried to like kind of put it in a little small pile to make it look smaller.
I didn't want
to spread it out.
So you design your, what you've left.
I feel like your waste.
I do this all the
time.
If I feel like I didn't eat, I do try to kind of make the plate look a certain way.
So the
person doesn't go, Oh, he hated it.
Cause I just don't want to make somebody feel bad.
Do you, okay.
Maybe if someone has cooked you this meal, perhaps put at a restaurant,
this doesn't often happen, but when it does happen, where I feel like I really didn't eat very much
and it wasn't like awful enough to ever, I rarely, rarely send something back.
But yeah, I do try to
not like make it look like I left everything on the plate.
So I kind of push it to one side.
So like, you know, somebody comes back and goes, Oh, you hated this or whatever.
I just don't,
I don't want him to feel bad.
Whatever.
It's okay.
It's fine.
Do you think that anyone clearing
plates that this margaritaville has ever looked at the plate?
Well, the guy who was, who was waiting
on us seemed young and new and perhaps might not have cared.
Maybe did care.
I don't know actually,
but he seemed, he was nice.
Um, but it's, it's possible you're correct in that they just go,
and then they just pick it up and they bring to the back.
It's probably more what is going to
happen.
But yeah, I do.
I am conscious of that.
If I don't feel like I
waste shaping, I waste shape often, which I'm surprised that hasn't come up with.
That is a,
do you have any tips within that?
Have you discovered any good ways to come back?
You have to hide things sort of under things.
So if you have a decorative lettuce, now we're talking,
if we're something you're not even supposed to eat, then you tuck it under there.
Yeah,
perfect.
Cause like I ate all the fries that came and the fries were fine.
They were fine,
like, or they were fine.
So, but if I say I didn't eat half the fries, I might've like kind of show
the fries under one of the big patties.
And then like with the patties here, this isn't the final
form of how I shaped it.
I don't think necessarily, but I did try to make sure the patties were still
stacked kind of on top of each other.
Cause you spread the patties out.
Now it's more surface area
on the plate and you really like at first glance you go, Oh, we didn't eat anything.
So if you
stack them, the height wise, you're not necessarily going to see like I didn't eat all my God.
He
didn't eat like a, like a third of the meat or half of the meat.
You didn't want to take those home
in a doggy bag for Edwin.
Would you have no Edwin can't Edwin's stomach is crazy.
He can eat like
a grain free Turkey and that's it.
I think maybe a lot of the people here in this room could learn
from Edwin.
Maybe if we all tried to be more like Edwin eating grain free Turkey, yeah, it might be
better for all of us.
Garfield can get the in and out, in and out has the doggy Patty.
Yeah.
Which is
they just cook a hamburger Patty, no salt.
So he's allowed to have that.
Yeah, that's not bad.
Yeah.
No, he can't do beef though.
You can't do beef.
You can't do chicken.
I guess a follow up question
I have about the managing the meal waste is how do you go through life with a brain that thinks
things like that?
Well, I mean, I think I'm, I mean, honestly, I think it's, it causes me to thrive in
so many different ways because of how conscientious I am about different elements of life.
Where one
seems odd.
Another end of it is extremely helpful.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Mike, I kind of understand where
you're coming from, but this is a place with paper napkins feeling just ball up your paper napkin,
throw it on the plate, hide the food.
You could now that's another way to do it.
Thank you for that tip
as well.
Cause you could ball it up in a napkin and then it just, it just, that especially just
reads as garbage.
Yeah.
There's a full manifesto about how to do this, which is one of the verses
of rapper's delight.
If you want, if you want to break down.
Oh yeah.
How to deal with when you're
in these situations.
Sure.
So, you know, here's what I'll say.
I'm taking, I'm like pulling the
meat apart here.
Cause I'm also trying to do a little experimenting with it.
Cause I haven't
had a cheeseburger, regular cheeseburger in Paris in a little while.
So I just, I took the, I just,
I made a single cheeseburger.
I fashioned a single cheeseburger, a single patty cheeseburger
out of the meat.
I took some of the meat out and then I took a bite out of the single patty
cheeseburger.
And I was like, this is actually kind of, this is like delicious.
Like the bun was
really like it had the thing where like they've, they've like, um, toasted it a little bit and the
sauce like tasted really like much better than the one in Orlando.
And I got a couple bites of
like a kind of like delicious fast food cheeseburger, nothing fancy or whatever.
But I remember being
like, this is a hundred percent better than the double cheeseburger.
So I got like three or four
bites and I don't know if that was just a fluke or in Hollywood, they, the guy was making them extra
good that day.
I don't know, but I got a couple bites of what the single patty might be like.
And it was good.
I like good.
I would say good.
I wouldn't say fine.
That's a word that has not been said very often in this entire series.
So I got like a teaser
for a better cheeseburger at the end.
It was like all your post credits, Marvel post credits
for my meal where I got a nice, Oh, this is good.
Like, this is going to be good.
If I have this
again, if this place doesn't close and I come back up here.
So all you have to do is perform
surgery on your meal and create to create a good meal.
I was like a plastic surgeon or something
and I fashioned a regular cheeseburger out of a double doing your cheeseburger meat experiments.
Yes.
I was experimenting with the beef.
That makes me seem like more of a Dr.
Muro type
where I'm doing like your language.
Some of it, all of it, I guess.
So I don't know what your,
yeah, you are the one like fussing with your, I didn't, I didn't notice this at all.
Well, I didn't make a big, I'm going to show you guys.
I don't want the waitstaff noticing
that I'm performing experiments on my food.
I want them to think I'm just happy and nice and
they did a good job and I don't want anybody to be worried.
I just want them to go, I did a good
job here.
That's what I want people that work at a restaurant to think.
Do you think there's that
possibility of somebody thinking you did a good job?
No, I want them to think they did a good job.
No, I don't want, I don't want praise.
I'm not, I'm no, but I'm a regular guy when I go to these
places.
I don't want this show.
I want attention on myself.
That's what I'm telling them.
I'm not
performing experiments.
I'm not walking around with a knife.
I'm doing it.
I'm hunched over.
They don't know.
They're not sure.
You stack condiments so that you have a wall separating
you from any passersby.
Exactly.
So you can do your experiments in private.
So no,
yeah, I don't want to draw attention to myself.
Well, you also were distracted because once the
Niners lost, you started yelling, I'm ruined.
I'm ruined.
Yes, I, yes, I did.
My book, I called my
bookie after that and said, lose my info and I have to disappear.
I can't afford any more double
cheeseburgers after this.
Only single patties for me.
Well, it works out better.
Now, you know,
I'm not going to do this.
That's the way to go.
That's all of our meal reviews, but there was
another party in our party who I mentioned and you know what?
He actually left his thing from
yesterday, the last time that we saw him.
And I wonder if we could use this.
It might actually,
you know, the mysteries of the multiverse.
I'm hoping that if we were to ring this,
it would actually time travel us back to that night and to the presence of the level keeper.
So let me see if I do this and if it works.
Boys, boys, boys, my voice sounds the same.
Exactly.
We all remember exactly what it was.
There is some other noise because we've jumped
through a gate hole.
Was that one of them?
Yeah, a gate hole.
And we're now just at post the meal at
Margaritaville Omega, which is of course Hollywood.
So you've now done as close to the same meal as
you could, although you had some complications.
You weren't able to do exactly the same between
Alpha and Omega.
At Alpha, I got a grilled chicken sandwich and here I got a grilled chicken platter.
But you felt like it's like similar spicing.
I think the same preparation, the same sides,
the same mango salsa, just more expensive minus bread.
Yeah, we've been trying to track prices.
Yeah, let us know those amounts if you took pictures or we'll cross check the menus.
Um, overall verdict?
Fine.
But remind me, you were not at Fine.
Oh, wait, wait, was Fine in,
was it Fine with a caveat in Alpha?
I already don't recall.
I would say Orlando was below Fine.
Below Fine.
Okay.
All right.
So Fine is an improvement.
I mean, do you consider that,
if you were on the general stock ticker of Margaritaville, if it was way down with Alpha,
where do you feel like it is now?
I think after Alpha, Margaritaville was deeply in the red
and now they are even.
Okay, well, that's something that's better than all the way down.
I drinks, you had to do something different and you lived it up, I feel.
They no longer,
here at the Omega Serve, the offer up the passion fruit guava margarita.
So instead,
I got a margarita flight.
Which had quite the array of colors.
Yeah, four mini marks and great
flavors such as light green, yellow, blue, and deeper green.
And you, I don't think knew the
contents of those because I asked which margaritas are we sampling and.
Not identified in menu or
in presentation.
I would say maybe one of them, just trying to game it out from the menu.
I think one of them was Blue Lagoon.
I think one of them was Watermelon.
What was a dirty iguana?
Possibly.
The thirsty iguana, horny iguanas.
No, I'm not sure.
Here's my main review.
They got the job done and arguably made the chicken taste more okay.
And also now it might
be good for you to narrate through because you brought us the situation of the Gratis app.
Would you like to explain what happened there?
Of course, as someone who died at CityWalk,
I have a lifetime gold annual pass holder status.
I mean, that's nice they provide that.
It is nice.
It's a good company, good customer relations.
But when I loaded up the app, it said there was a
special offer through the beginning of March at Margaritaville where if you showed your annual
pass, you got one free chef's choice appetizer.
Chef selected.
This is solely by the chef.
For every two entrees ordered maximum of one.
And then the way the ordering took place,
you knew what it was going to be and you got to keep that a secret from us for 10 minutes or so.
I hyped it up big time to my boys.
I showed my pass to the server and I said,
hey, do you know about this promotion?
And he went, oh yeah, the chips and guac.
The chef has selected this evening the chips and guac, an appetizer that we already had ordered
because that was one that was available from the list that we were copying from Orlando.
So thank
you, chef, for a great selection, though improved, I feel like from.
Did we also check on the bill
that the price that those were comped?
Oh, huh.
I don't think we paid a lot of attention.
You
want to make sure that because I do think overall price tag may have been lower.
That is maybe a
subtle thing between Orlando and I think price tag lower morale higher.
The most complimentary
thing we can say is that post meal, none of us went back to our hotel rooms in shame and despair.
Yes, but we'll see where the evening we had to really rule it when the evening takes us somewhere.
I believe we were charged for the chip.
But yeah, you're right that that morale is higher.
I mean, I think I think a better time was had.
There's something nice about doing it just at end of day.
This is not the exhaustion that there was
the first time.
And I'm happy that morale is higher, even though this group has accused you
of stealing shirts that you did not steal.
A true, true offense.
I've never done anything wrong.
He's a simple boy, a child who died and you're accusing him of robbery.
I feel like I was.
I have to go back and listen what crime he was actually accused of,
because there's taking the shirt.
This I know.
I don't know.
Of course, like,
it's like what I want him in a life sentence for taking it.
No, but he should serve some time.
Like that's what I'm saying.
There's a difference in like what I think the crime should be for
something like that.
He didn't do it, but I'm just saying I don't think I accused him of it in a way
was so bad, like a criminal or like a felony.
He's already serving time.
He's in a purgatorial
state as all the keepers are.
Yeah.
No, thanks to you.
I bet Mike thinks that Casper broke into the
water gate based on nothing.
All right.
Well, I guess we'll let you disappear and we thank you
for your presence throughout this saga.
I think I think it's helped morale in general.
And I don't
know any parting words as we we still have a I'd say a good amount of this left to go.
Any parting
words or advice or anything?
Bye.
Oh, OK.
And we're back.
Wow.
Well, that was great.
That was cool.
Amazing.
I don't know why we didn't use this more times at time travel in cowbell.
Yeah.
Could have
really helped us cover some ground.
Mike, you traveled back to that night and bet on the 49ers
again.
You knew the result.
Well, I thought maybe it would change because we've we've changed so much
about the multiverse just by talking about everything.
So maybe the 49ers would win because
of the butterfly effect.
That's fair.
By virtue of us being there, right.
Cause a breeze that would
go to where was this?
Where did the Super Bowl take place?
Las Vegas.
Not too far.
So maybe.
Yeah,
there's like a ripple.
There's a ripple.
It knocks the ball out of somebody's hand.
Legion stadium.
That's right.
Right.
There might have been a ripple.
You're counting on the ripple.
So
that's that's that.
Again, slightly improved chef selected items.
Yeah.
You'd have to call this a
somewhat better experience.
One thing that remained the same that was that was kind of the
unchanging part of this experiment was that yet again, in this establishment, they played the
Jimmy Buffett version of my favorite Beach Boys song, Sail on Sailor.
Mike, it's unfair to do this to you.
You didn't record this version.
You weren't part of it,
but you're the person I know would be the most likely to defend it.
It's fucking horrible.
So bad.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I can't be in a restaurant that ruins my favorite,
where the food at best is fine.
Good if you take a scalpel to it and no matter what,
butchers my favorite songs.
Well, I, you know, I did I say this at the time?
I think the problem
though is just that the speakers in there aren't loud enough because it doesn't feel like you're
live.
Because that's what you're missing is that live experience.
Scott, are you not listening to
it loud enough?
You think I guess it is one possibility.
You would feel the roar of the
crowd.
You would feel the island vibes if it because like you're hearing an uncut sort of like
quiet and tinny and like if I look, Jimmy's no longer with us.
I can't experience his cover of
this in the sphere, but if I had gotten to see him do it in the sphere with like a loop of surf
footage behind boy, that would have sounds awesome.
Yeah.
Then I'd be like beach boys who
while they're well, maybe somebody will do his cover at this big Hollywood bowl show that's
coming up.
Oh right.
Somebody will perform the Jimmy Buffett cover of sail on sailor.
Fingers
crossed.
We honor this man with his brown eye girl.
He's going to do thank God for thank God
and Jimmy Buffett.
His single.
Yeah.
His tribute single.
Maybe we'll do two though.
There
is another one called Regga Billy Hill.
I know.
I know he's I know he's dead.
I'm sorry.
I don't
I don't know what this is.
I don't know why I'm listening to it.
It is.
Is it going to hurt me
from going back to this restaurant again?
Yes.
I don't want to hear Regga Billy Hill.
I don't
like Regga Billy Hill.
Again, you know, I don't want to sound like those the fish people, but
it's not quite about the songs and the music.
Yeah, that one maybe isn't so fun.
I don't want
to do all the things where they say it's not that, you know, you got to actually restaurants, not
about the food and the facts about his charting aren't about the facts and the songs aren't about
the songs.
Exactly.
Yeah.
There's a couple of qualifiers, but they're all they all
make sense when you're in the camp here in the fandom.
I get the vibe.
I wear the visors.
I
understand it, but there's only so a vibe burns out.
There's an atomic life to a vibe.
Yeah,
but not in twenty twenty four where every vibe from everything has to live forever, frozen in time.
It can last forever and it will as the as this Hollywood Bowl show is titled, like keep the party
going.
Jason's going to get frozen in time if he does that thermometer wrong.
Well, then
you said that thing too low.
Said too low.
You're going to be freezing.
I can't feel anything.
I'm
too cold.
You got to get it high up at City Walk because it's extra windy on top of that hill.
Well, of course we've talked about that.
Yeah.
No, that's coming guys.
No, remember the order
previous spoiler for the future.
You're going to learn about City Walk's wind.
Now here's something I will say in comparing the two and this doesn't matter.
This isn't
a bad Orlando restaurant.
However, you know, a pretty bad Orlando restaurant experience was
definitely sullied by a bad aftermath where I took a lonely boat back to throw up in a dark room.
Oh,
yeah.
Yeah.
And I realized I was missing wonderful formative memories with my son across the country.
In this case, the whole thing was nice.
It was nice to hang out with everybody to watch the
Super Bowl there.
It had actually been kind of a stressful week and and you know, kid had been sick
and everybody had been sick.
And so like, oh, now we're out.
We're over that.
And like, oh,
I got a little bit of time here because I almost hitched a lift back with you, Jason.
And I'm like,
wait a minute.
No, why don't I love those hotels over there?
I'm slop.
I'm like a sloppy telly.
I'm going to go enjoy those hotels.
And there's something new since we did the City Walk saga
original at the Universal Hilton.
There's an outdoor bar called Five on the Hill.
That's kind
of a, you know, froufy too expensive.
You could spend way too much money there, although quality
is the best food.
Like, what if I just go get a drink?
And I had the most relaxing glass of wine
with like nobody else in there, you know, like fire heaters.
What's the word?
Yeah, heater.
Yeah,
sure.
Yeah, patio heaters.
Yeah, there you go.
Is this off the lobby or is this down on the pool?
It's outside.
They took some of like the lobby or like the valet turnaround and turned it into a
weird little restaurant.
That's cool.
And you can't see much at night.
During the day, you've got a
view of the of the Cohinga Pass and it's very relaxing out there.
You can look down on the pool
and I went I had the most chill flame lit glass of wine, not the light, just the lighting was.
Why am I so awkward explaining this?
I'm too marooned to play motion.
But also they had,
okay, sometimes you sometimes as a piano player, sometimes as a guitar player, this place had some
of the best restaurant entertainment I've ever seen, which was prerequisite, the real instrumental
tracks of many of my favorite songs and then a guy playing live steel drum over them.
It was
fucking great.
That sounds at first.
I feel like if you heard that described to you before this,
you might not even like, I don't know.
Like that'll that'll ruin it.
Yeah, I'm just up the hill.
We
just came from a restaurant.
One of my favorite songs was ruined by island vibes.
But here it's
the real tracks that I like.
And this guy's great.
He's doing what he does.
He did all night long.
Don't stop till you get enough and debar's rhythm of the night.
My favorite karaoke song,
got to give it up.
Marvin Gaye.
He did Prince's I want to be your lover, which doesn't even you
wouldn't even think steel drum would make sense on that, but it was great.
And he did the extended,
he did the entire thing.
He didn't do the single edit.
He did a steel drum vamping for the full
like six, seven minute outro.
It was fucking awesome.
And then I got to hook back up with
the level keeper who broke off to do Mario Kart and you got to do it with no line.
The only possible way you could enjoy that ride.
And still it's a little difficult.
And still.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Yes.
But you know, it's better.
Yeah.
That's the base requirement is not waiting
three hours.
I guess.
But that did impact the experience ultimately.
And what for all of these
I have been this just warped me.
I was like, when I truly go and have the time that we've been
dying to have at the real at Margaritaville Alpha, I thought of it as Alpha even before this.
I
thought Orlando was the primary one.
Yeah.
And how dark that experience became versus a great night
in my own backyard.
The absolutely official ruling for me is that Margaritaville Omega
is better.
And I mean, look, I tipped my hat to it already.
I tipped my hand,
what I was going to say, the hat and hand and hand, but I can't disagree.
I can't disagree.
And you don't now.
But you also have because you have those like wistful formative.
You made me
get into this brand by your description of the relaxing nature of the Orlando.
Like, do those memories still pull you to that one?
They do.
And again, I think we went right
when they opened and I think that if we had been on I think if we had been on the porch right around
sunset, we would feel a little differently coming out of Orlando.
But yes, I still I finally remember
some Orlando Margaritaville experiences.
But man, it's good to be home.
Wow.
Good to be home.
Chewing were home.
I said when I was there.
Yeah, we finally felt the spirit of
chewing were home.
Jason, I assume unless you throw us for a loop here.
You know, I certainly
love the flashy scenery of Orlando.
But I think there's just been, you know, the Hollywood one.
I liked my fish.
I liked my fish and chips.
And yeah, I liked having it's kind of nice sometimes
a whole restaurant yourself basically, you know, yourself in your party.
So I liked that no one got
ill and no one got thrown for a loop by this outing.
Everyone had a better night.
I would.
And I was.
Yeah.
So so absolutely.
This was an interesting experiment.
I'm glad we did it with
with somewhere.
But absolutely in the East Coast, West Coast battle, West Coast wins
handily.
I would say that overall, I agree with the level keeper that the Margaritaville franchise
kind of breaks even.
That said, my final ruling, don't go here.
This is not good.
I'm sorry.
I don't.
It's you're going to get better food somewhere.
Maybe, maybe.
Well, a drink, a drink, which still
you're going to find a superior margarita somewhere.
But if you just single patty cheeseburger,
if you want that, I think maybe that's a safe bet.
Would you still recommend this restaurant?
Well, to who?
Who am I talking to?
Hmm.
How about like a parent's friend?
I would I would maybe.
Yeah, they can't nobody.
And now I know all human beings know 10 Jimmy
Buffett songs.
But a regular person who's not mired in this shit, would you send them to
Margaritaville in City Walk Hollywood to sit down and eat?
Yes.
God, I think so.
We're different
people, you know, but we see sports like the NBC like isn't that much better.
It is better.
I think that much better, though.
I think I think these are important percentages.
Maybe,
you know, they like the island aesthetic, maybe Margaritaville.
But there's something to be said
of the all out assault of flat screen TVs everywhere you look, you know, at NBC.
Yeah,
at NBC.
It can be kind of fun.
Yeah.
To just have TVs everywhere.
I guess so.
That just place doesn't
have that much personality.
But but there's not a I don't feel not as horrible.
But it's like 5%,
maybe 10%.
That's not that's not enough for the lack of fun.
You don't have fun.
We have the
foosball table.
You don't like the foosball, but it's dirty.
It's so dirty.
So I don't know.
I would tell a friend's parent to go.
I would make I would make like I'd say like, look,
it's fine.
You're not going to get OK.
I'm going to be realistic.
OK, well, that's good.
I would
still say I'm not going to recommend them go to a few other places.
OK, Vivo, maybe Vivo.
I guess.
None of these are still real.
There's if you OK down on the on Cahuenga, not far from where you
go up the hill to go to City Walk, there's a real restaurant called Mercado, a real Mexican restaurant
that is good and fun.
Yeah.
We're the good happy hour.
That's not we're talking about here.
I know.
I know it's out of the sectors.
Like spits over adventure over here that I really like, too.
There's a couple of them in L.
A.
What you could do is Mediterranean.
I think in general, don't
eat before you don't eat at City Walk.
Don't ever do it.
I know we got more of that to go.
I hear the words you're saying, but I know what you really mean is eat there as much as you can
because there's something magic about it.
Well, thanks for seeing the true meaning of my message.
I felt it.
I didn't hear it.
Scott's really saying do eat there.
He's really saying that
it's about a feeling.
The Buffett sail on sailor trounces and drowns the Beach Boys one.
That's not.
It's not about the live recordings.
It was about the live experience.
And they're
trying to recreate it, but it's impossible without him there live.
That's like to bring the K back
into it.
That's like that song sounds like Beach Boys, but the C is a K.
I wish there was a Beach
Boy on that tribute show.
Maybe they're on tour.
Are they on tour?
I don't know.
Are they're all
on Death's Door?
Well, that's some of the people on this tribute show.
Yes.
Yeah.
So I just wish
there was one of them.
I think I'm going to call a shot here.
OK, we've done this 10.
There's been
10 of these episodes as penance for none of this being maybe good episodes, but not being good
experiences for us.
I think we're going to bring back a City Walk thing has not come back since
Jason himself had to do it.
And that is Jimmy's in the penalty box.
No Jimmy centric episodes for
one year.
Whoa, we've done 10, 10, three and two days.
Oh my gosh.
That's as long as regular
things.
It was nice.
We don't do something in frontier land for a year.
Probably more.
OK,
OK.
All right.
I will tentatively agree to this.
Whoa.
Tentative Jason.
Jason.
I as as the past
shown, I have no control over the penalty box.
So with your suggestion and Mike agreeing to it.
If I go to the Solid Bull show, though, and there's something we have to talk about, then we'll see.
But I guess I could wait a year to talk about it.
Well, everyone's going to remember it.
I'll talk about a concert I saw a year prior.
You might have might have more content, you know,
Pirate Looks at a year ago, the infamous trampling at the Hollywood Bowl.
The infamous riot.
A pit bull at the stage.
People went fucking nuts.
Guess what?
No, it's it was the riot was boomers
trying to run out of there because there was someone on stage.
Oh, they didn't grow up listening
to that.
That's that.
Hurry.
And that day ticket holders were the ones yelling timber.
Right back
to you in the studio.
More at eleven.
All right.
I think we I think we did.
I think you listener,
you survived.
He brings out Travolta during the show that people would stampede trying to get to
the stage.
I think I'd be stampeding back.
Yeah.
Singing like a Woe Black Betty song that
Pitbull does.
The Travolta played live, performed live with him on some of their like a pilot club,
like a rich guy.
Well, that's it.
That's a different that's a music video that John Travolta
is in of Pitbull's.
I'm talking about there was a live like award show that Pitbull, whatever the
he has that samples Woe Black Betty.
John Travolta is just on stage dancing with him the whole time.
That's a different, different Travolta appearance.
I think don't we have to put Jimmy Buffett in the
penalty box so to open up things like the full John Travolta.
No, the full John Travolta episode.
Yeah, we do.
The John Travolta oddities episode.
Sure.
I know we should.
I think Jimmy would want
to take a little time.
You know what?
You guys were there.
He's off.
I got enough attention.
They're both pilots.
So I guess that's a nice trade.
Yeah.
One pilot for another.
They nod to each other in the sky.
All right.
Hey, friendly skies.
But listener,
you survived three Jimmy Buffett episodes in two days.
Keep it tuned here to the second gate.
Thanks Aaron for the art.
My Carlson and Zach Reno for the theme music.
Multiverse of Menace
Merchant or T-Public Store.
Everything else in the series, I believe is going to be on the main feed.
But keep it tuned here as always to podcast throughout the second gate or notch it up to
Club 3 to get every sector ad free and that exclusive bonus sector from not long ago.
Tomorrow, The Age of Buffett ends, but the beach vibes may not.
We'll see who joins us.