Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your swear has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll.
With alcohol, a place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando.
Tonight, tonight.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Hey folks, welcome to podcast the Ride presents
the City Walk Orlando Saga Multiverse of Madness.
For the first time in Saga history presented before a live audience in Orlando, Florida.
Now at this point we need to try to conjure some ghostly spirits, some ghostly sounds.
I hear a little something.
No, that's the band next door.
Apologies listeners.
Here's what we, honestly I don't know that we can fully summon the Sector Keeper.
But if we all hear, let's put our hands together.
Let's pray in prayer and see if we can summon the Sector Keeper.
Boys, boys.
Today you face, face to sector one.
What?
Cinemark movie theater, fat Tuesday, Universal's great movie escape, good luck boys.
Okay, okay.
What is he clanging back there?
Oh, this haunted mansion-y, that's kind of exciting.
He sounds a little weird too.
I sound normal.
This is all strange because the Sector Keeper doesn't make bat sounds.
That's a different thing.
He really doesn't.
That's nothing he's ever done.
He doesn't really clang either.
He must have stolen that cowbell from Blake Shelton's old bread.
Yeah, they have a cowbell on every table.
That's the fun of going there.
That's why you go.
Well, let's be honest.
The Sector Keeper is not here.
We're trying to pull a fast one on you and we're not trying to rip you off, okay.
The Sector Keeper is not here, but he did send somebody instead, somebody who he fully approved of.
It's licensed.
It's franchised.
He is okay with this.
This counts as part of the Keeper verse.
I'm canon.
He absolutely is.
Yeah, it's him.
And he's itching to get out here, so let's get him out.
Please welcome the Sector Keeper's cousin, the Level Keeper.
The Level Keeper.
This is my thing.
I'm not sure how that sounded on that mic.
That might have been horrible.
Yeah, that's really rough.
Do it without the mic, I think.
Oh my God, the Level Keeper, folks.
Whoa.
I'm canon.
Wow, geez.
It's pre-established.
Do you folks remember the Level Keeper?
We all do.
Obviously.
You all know the, except for anyone who anyone brought who does not listen to the show, who is beyond lost, they're going to go into the other room and watch the other band, for sure.
I think the impact of the Level Keeper was great enough that perhaps people have never listened to the show and know about him through osmosis.
Cultural omnipresence.
It just sounds exciting, whatever it is, I guess.
No, the Level Keeper, of course, was who we met at the end of the Downtown Disney ordeal.
And I'm sure we've all been wondering when we were going to close the loop and actually spend some time with the Level Keeper.
And it's happening here in Orlando.
What's up, Level Keeper?
It's been three years of wind up.
Four, four maybe.
Everyone, the Reddit threads have been going crazy.
PTR spoilers and leaks.
R slash PTR spoilers and leaks.
We don't want that.
Theorizing.
Post those Cali rotor pics.
That's where we.
Theorizing when I'd come back and whether or not my voice would sound exactly the same.
Because we all remember what the voice was.
And every bit of the story, everybody remembers everything.
Deep lore.
I died of a surge soda overdose.
After seeing jungle to jungle at City Walk.
We all remember my tragic backstory.
Absolutely established.
Everybody knows it.
Well, you know, I feel like it'd be nice if people kind of got to know like who you are as opposed to the Sector Keeper.
I mean, do you feel like he's in a pod or like, I mean, are you mainly here's what I want to know.
Are you going to be as.
We're cousins, of course.
We're cousins.
I think that was established lore.
But I'm very much my own thing.
Good to know.
Do you care as much as him about like staying on track?
Yes, boys, boys.
OK.
I mean, in that case, maybe we need to get to it.
I hope there's someone in the crowd.
I draw it got dragged along to this and it's like, man, that guy on stage really looks like that one actor from Draft Tag.
I can't place him.
I forget his name.
We'll have to have him drop a coffee.
It'd be the only way to know.
Yeah, I heard that didn't make the final cut.
Only the trailer.
Well, Draft Tag complete.
It's no, they know the track.
That's canon.
OK.
So, you know, in the interest of keeping on track, here's the cool thing.
We didn't just meet backstage for the first time.
We've been buddies for a little bit.
We've actually been hanging out at CityWalk Orlando together so we can actually speak to experiences that we've had.
We're buddies.
Shared experiences.
The four amigos.
We've been cutting it up all week.
Best of friends.
And we have not gotten tired of you exclaiming everything in that tone.
12 hours a day.
It's been a pleasure.
I can't tell if this is getting dangerously far away from SectorKeeper and dangerously close to Justin Roiland.
Oh, no.
I'm getting worried in real time.
I cannot recommend that direction.
No one wants to be dangerously close to Justin Roiland.
This similarity is purely coincidental.
It is.
It's just Morty is with us now.
I'm not.
I'm my own thing.
Morty doesn't do this.
Morty has never done that.
It's totally different.
It's very different.
Let's talk a little about the first thing that we got to do together.
And this was you and me.
This was right when you rolled into town, right when you flew into town.
I took a lift straight to the first location.
Even ghosts have to take lifts.
I'm assuming that you are a ghost.
You're not like something else.
I'm a phantasm.
Let's be very clear.
A phantasm is not a ghost.
SectorKeeper is not a level keeper.
Level Keeper is a phantasm.
Got it?
Yes.
Great.
We're straight.
Ogden's not Augustine.
Okay.
So the first thing that we got to do is the first thing in the sector, and that is the
Cinemark movie theater.
A round of applause, I guess.
Are people big fans of the Cinemark brand?
It seems like they…
Yeah.
Rewards members?
Any rewards members?
Okay.
AMC for life.
I don't know.
Was it ever?
Yes.
It was.
Okay.
Well, you can see that our research is a little poor at this point.
We maybe will not be detailing every single ownership of that multiplex.
Some of this will get updated in post, I'm sure.
We'll cut it.
We'll blend it exactly right.
Get this echo just how it was here.
But you know what?
I love that we…
This is one of those moments where I'm like, I really like that we spent a bunch of time
in CityWalk because you're on a…
We're visitors.
Some of you guys might…
That might be your movie theater you go to.
For us, we're so busy doing rides and having fun that we neglect to take a little time
to just watch an entire feature film near rides about Minions and ET and stuff.
Look, I don't want to get into controversial territory.
But of course, we all live in the fallout of Martin Scorsese's statement that modern
blockbusters have become more like amusement park rides than art.
Yes.
That's true, right.
And we took that to heart and we said, perhaps it is time to walk into the Cinemark, plunk
down our American dollars and engage in a little bit of high art to take a break from
all the thrill rides.
Very good.
We put them next to each other and see how they compare.
A balanced breakfast.
I mean, I felt great about it.
We should talk…
Did anybody…
Let's go down the line.
Any experience here previously seeing a movie at that CityWalk movie theater?
Okay.
The audience says yes.
You know, my apologies.
I meant the hosts, but I'm glad we know…
You know what?
Everyone just shout out a movie you've seen there.
Sixth Sense.
Sixth Sense is what I heard.
And it just opened?
Yeah.
Original or is it a re…
Originally, and we went after a show at Hard Rock and I had my webcast.
Wow.
One time was the show at Hard Rock.
It was like 8 o'clock.
It was my guitar teacher's band.
Your guitar teacher's band at Hard Rock.
Wow.
That's cool.
So, of us, Mike, have you ever seen a movie at this movie theater?
At that specific movie theater?
No.
Have I seen a movie on vacation?
Also, no.
And the rationale being it's a waste of time?
Right.
We had plenty of movie theaters where I grew up.
That was not a problem.
So, we figured why not enjoy the local sights and sounds?
Yes.
A much more sensible thing to do.
Yeah.
I did have a good experience on a vacation a while back.
I was feeling a little theme-parked out.
I think one of the studios, maybe Universal Studios closed, and they happened to be doing
Back to the Future.
They happened to be doing a little revival and it was fun to see Back to the Future.
I think the ride must have been open back then.
At least the time train was there.
I saw the time train today too.
Oh my God.
You were with me, Level Keeper.
We were saying that's right where Jules or Vern pointed at their penis.
That weird little point.
We stood in front, looked at each other, pointed at our own penises and smiled.
Cinematic.
For ten straight minutes.
If people take photos of that though, they're going to know we're doing City Walk Orlando.
I am.
So, they just don't post those.
Level Keeper.
Well, you said, okay, Jungle the Jungle is where you were trapped.
Yes.
I was trapped in a perpetual screening of Jungle the Jungle.
Thank God I died in the middle of the funniest movie ever made.
It does loop.
You do get to see.
It's not just the first 45 minutes over and over.
No, I died in the end credits.
So, I get to see the full arc.
I make it to Mimi Siku climbing up the Statue of Liberty.
A scene both funny and poignant.
Incredible specific poll.
Okay, so you know, some people have just been there once.
Other people and ghosts are there forever.
Forever.
Glad we could get you out for a break tonight.
You free me.
Jason, any experience seeing films there?
Yes.
One time I had a lovely experience.
My family were regulars at Universal Resort down here a lot in the early 2000s.
Where we would come for like a long weekend, three or four days.
Stay at Hard Rock, you get the express and you just leisurely, you get on everything quick.
And one night we were like, alright, I think we've had our fill of the parks.
We had dinner at Emeril's, rest in peace, Fallen Brother.
Fallen to the Fruit.
Fallen Brother at Emeril's, yeah.
And then we're like, hey, let's go see a big summer movie.
Let's go see a movie.
Never been to a movie theater here.
So we went and saw the new release, Superman Returns, starring Kevin Spacey as Lex Luthor.
The Kevin Spacey vehicle, Superman Returns.
Wow.
Yes.
A great film.
A film where I remember when the third act kicking in thinking, oh, I can't wait to be trapped on this
Kryptonite Island with Kevin Spacey for 35 minutes.
Boys, out of sensitivity, maybe let's not focus on the Kevin Spacey of the movie.
And instead call it what it is, a Brian Singer picture.
No, no, no.
Yeah, Brian Singer, Kevin Spacey vehicle.
Oh, wait a minute.
You're locked in the 90s.
So you just remember what usual suspects, right?
With riding high, unproblematic kings.
Oh, that's right.
And you know Justin Roiland as being a cool nine-year-old.
A kid I hang out with who's well-adjusted.
You were one of those kids sneaking R-rated movies from Bawfuster.
You were getting usual suspects.
You were getting apt pupil.
Yes.
I like high art.
That's going to pay off big time when we tell you what movie we saw.
Oh, yes, absolutely.
Well, I mean, let's get to that because at first I was like, are we going to have time to do that?
Maybe, okay, what if I just buy a ticket to the movie theater and check the list off that way and don't even go and see anything?
Well, movies are expensive.
That seems like kind of a waste of money.
Then I realized the day we had slotted for this was Tuesday.
Cinemark does $5 Tuesdays.
Cheers for that.
You got to give them that.
I mean, I guess so does AMC, I think.
They probably stole the idea.
However, they do it.
So, okay, it's not going to cost a lot of money.
And at that point, I'm warming up to like, maybe I do see like a little bit of a movie or trailers and then some of a movie.
Then I'll go back and do everything else City Walk has to offer.
And what is it going to be?
Do I do, you know, to date when we're recording this, do I do just five minutes of Killers of the Flower Moon?
The tiniest or what?
Do I do one one hundred and tenth of that movie?
And I'm looking for like, well, I mean, it's not like I'm going to find some remarkable, odd, funny movie that only exists in this specific place.
Wrong.
A movie that has a connection to a neighbor of this building.
That is correct.
Any guesses so far?
Folks, are you familiar with a feature film called Glisten and the Merry Mission?
I felt like people, maybe a few people were, but they weren't excited to say that they were.
But Glisten and the Merry Mission.
At first, I'm baffled by this poster.
I'm looking at a poster that's like one of those like straight to video Snow White ripoffs from 1994.
Like, wait, are you sure?
You're sure you're playing this now?
This isn't like a glitch in the system.
Read the cast, read the cast above the title.
Yes.
Well, OK, first of all, another bit of text on the poster.
OK, what is Glisten and the Merry Mission?
Then I read, it's about believing.
Nice.
Yeah.
The theme of a movie.
Most posters don't tell you that.
Take that Scorsese.
Then I start reading the cast of this film.
Freddie Prinze Jr.
Michael Rapaport.
Billy Ray Cyrus.
Trinity Bliss, who is what?
Tuk.
In Avatar Way of Water.
The little Navi.
Tuk has grown up and she's doing a different voice.
Leona Lewis, who sings I See You from Avatar, not Way of Water.
So this is an Avatar reunion.
Dionne Warwick is in this movie.
Yeah.
And then and I'm like, hmm, well, is the deal sealed?
Let me scan all the way to the right on this poster.
Who is the and?
Oh, and Chevy Chase.
In.
Beyond in.
Then I look up a little spoiler for myself.
What is Chevy Chase doing in this movie?
Chevy Chase is playing Santa Claus.
Yes.
And only five dollars.
But Scott, Scott, the cast you just read would cost tens of thousands of dollars.
To align what deep pocketed movie studio could finance such an expensive production?
Oh, I don't know.
I'm racing through options.
Well, you know, was it age 24 or was this a big is it Blumhouse?
Who put this thing together?
And then I turned to Jason because Jason knew.
Oh, yeah, I knew surprisingly a lot about Glisten.
And I went, oh, I know what that is.
That's the movie produced by Build a Bear Workshop.
Fully financed.
No outside partners.
A Cinemark exclusive release.
Exclusively Cinemark.
Build a Bear Christmas movie.
Every time you've been to Build a Bear and you bought little pants for your bear, you've been funding this movie for years.
That's what it's been building toward.
You've been you've been building your bear, but they've been building this movie.
They've been building a mythology and let the record show.
I just wanted to clear the air with them.
I made sure to let them know.
Oh, I was just poking around on the Build a Bear Workshop.
See what was there with the company.
Like you do.
That's actually true.
You were just discovering what's Build a Bear up to these days.
It happened where Scott was like texting and he's like, oh, I'm going to go see this movie Glisten.
And Jason goes, oh, the Build a Bear movie.
We were like, what?
Jason, do you have Google Alert set for Build a Bear?
Oh, I got them all.
Yeah, they're all blowing up.
Have you ever built a bear?
No, I've been in that store once.
I've never built a bear.
Would you like to one day build a bear?
I was just seeing what was going on with the organization.
You're a fan of the corporate structure, not the bears themselves.
If I'm remembering correctly to another element was that Eva Anderson texted me this and said, have you heard about this with no other context?
Seems like an Eva thing.
That might have sent me down the rabbit hole.
Well, yes, one fact about Build a Bear Workshop is that this venue that we're in right now shares a wall with Build a Bear Workshop.
So if you go after our show, one of our shows, you can go meet some of the characters.
The title character Glisten, Marzipan, Lula, Donner, and Grizz.
Grizz is the one that I want to underline and jump in whenever because you saw this film too, Level Keeper.
Breakout character.
Okay, I took a…
let me see.
I have it written down.
Okay, this is Grizz's description.
Voiced by Michael Rapoport.
And the character is the village grizzly with a tough reputation.
That just sounds…
there's like no twist there.
That's just like he's a bear who is mean.
And when they say village grizzly, I should under score that he sounds like he's from Greenwich Village.
In New York City, not at all the North Pole.
He sounds like a bear calling into a sports radio show.
What the fuck are the meds doing?
What is this organization all about?
I'm a bear.
I did many takes of all these lines.
These weren't notes app cold reads.
You gotta believe in the spirit of Christmas, but nothing's gonna help the Jets' season.
So, and I believe they are open till 11, so you really can hear in our earlier show…
They're not going anywhere near it.
They're gonna send their Pinkerton's after us to break.
So we're getting the hell out of here as soon as these shows are done.
If you show up at Build-A-Bear at 1059, do they have to let you build a bear?
Yeah, if you're in…
stay in line.
If you're in line, stay in line.
They must let you build a bear if you're in line at 1059.
You just might not have time in the minute to grab bear skin.
You might just have to save…
just put your mouth on the little thing and suck up as much as you can.
Save it for home.
Take your own shirt and build a bear out of that.
You're just holding the bear's skin and a big thing of stuffing and you're pushing him out the door.
It's to go…
I'll do it at home.
I'll do it later.
By the way, the wonders of doing a show here at Tin…
Usually we're always happy to see smiling faces in our audience,
but something we don't usually get when doing a live show is a little train going by.
Yeah.
Off the window.
This rules.
And we're just looking…
my view…
maybe, Jason, you can see the full name from where you are.
I just see the neon word Ramsey, as in Gordon Ramsay.
Oh yeah, that's Gordon Ramsay fishing chips across the way.
Does Gordon Ramsay's restaurant produce any movies?
Well, they should, let me tell you.
Because I think that this racket has been going great for build-a-bear filmed entertainment.
I walked up to get a ticket at 1025 on a Tuesday afternoon.
I'm running a little bit late.
All right, I'm going to miss some trailers.
I hope I don't bother anybody while I'm walking in.
I very proudly say, one for Glisten and the Merry Mission, please.
Person at the window turns the screen around and says, you can pick any of the green.
It is 100% green.
This is an absolutely empty film.
Maybe like 70 seats, I want to say.
And at this point, I've been texting the level keeper…
Level keeper!
The level keeper, who was on the fence about do I want to see Glisten or not?
How much do you care about your $5?
And once I said, it is an empty movie theater, please come hang out with me in an empty movie theater, the deal was sealed.
I'm in!
Now, I've done a little research since seeing the film.
I've tried to really think on it, knowing I'd have to throw some takes out tonight.
And I was very surprised because you mentioned anyone could go to the Build-A-Buyer next door now and buy…
What we presumed were the exciting new characters introduced in this film who happen to synergistically now be plush toys for the first time.
Wrong!
You never would have guessed it from the airtight plotting, but this film is in fact loosely adapted from 15 years of seasonal plush characters.
Retrofitted into a story!
Whoa!
Oh my God!
Incredible info drop here.
Wow!
So you…
like, why am I explaining?
I'm explaining Grizz and everyone in this room already knows all about Grizz.
As popular as the level keeper!
The series Bible for Glisten is just the biggest plush pile you've ever seen.
Yeah!
Wait, so Grizz…
hold on.
When you're going…
I don't know why I just want to talk about Build-A-Buyer.
When you're going to Build-A-Buyer, I thought you would get a bear and you name it, but they have their own original characters that you're not allowed to name?
I don't know if you're really hard not allowed.
Well, if they have a name, you shouldn't rename the character from Build-A-Buyer.
It is disrespectful, you're right.
Rude!
I pick gumdrop handcuffs.
Clink.
We're going to bury you in stuffing.
Because I would think that building your own bear, the idea is that you can create life in any way that you as the god imagines.
But what character could a child create more poignant than Grizz?
The bear who sounds like all of his dialogue was recorded before his first cup of coffee.
Were there any jokes about Grizz having Riz?
Like having charisma, you know, style?
This is a young person word I've learned recently.
Jason and his young person.
That's why we need him.
He keeps us young.
It seems like a given, right?
It seems like a given.
Jason, I mean, I like your idea here, but do you think that a Build-A-Bear film in 2023 is going to have a new young person phrase?
Or do you think that they will have something like somebody telling an elf that they have been elf-splaining?
Oh boy.
That is to answer your question about the slang tenor of the film.
I'm a little behind.
The character is still using fidget spinners.
It's like, oh, this thing.
So for a while I'm just like, wow, I'm in a movie theater and I can talk at full volume.
I can run laps.
I can go up and down the stairs.
I can respond to the Wonka trailer and say, sounds great.
See you soon, Timothy.
This is for you, mama.
But I'm really excited for the level keeper.
Having not seen the level keeper in so long.
Oh, the moment the level keeper walks in and sure enough, 20 minutes in.
What a blast that we get to just like hang out and chat.
Well, we had that decision to make.
Do we sit and watch the film or do we hang out and chat?
And after about 10 minutes, I think it became clear that loudly talking about anything else was the best option.
Why not do both?
Also, unlike buying a ticket to Killers of the Flower Moon and leaving after 20 minutes, thus barely having a crumb of the film,
20 minutes of glisten in the Merry Mission was approximately 40% of the total running time.
Your other option was to take the elevator upstairs where Mike and Jane and I were like finishing the crumbling remains from the BK Whopper bar.
We got a text while in the movie because we kept our phones on while speaking at full volume in a theater with no one else.
We got a text from Jason with a picture of Mike that just said, Mike is now explaining Jamiroquai to us.
Yeah, he was refreshing us on Jamiroquai.
He was telling us about the new action figure release, the 99 action figure.
The new action figure is making a $100 toy of Jamiroquai.
And it's the classic look, it's the hat, it's the blue shirt, it's from the video.
Of JK.
Of JK from, yes, Jamiroquai.
The hat guy.
And I was in that photo very casually leaning back and explaining.
Well, and you were explaining it because Jamiroquai, it's not from your telling, from your telling.
You were, Jamiroquai was softly playing and Jane, here with Jason, did not know what the song was and you answered, it's very superstitious.
I thought it was very superstitious at first.
It was low, it was playing low.
It was playing really low.
But I definitely pointed up and I said, there it is.
I did my famous point.
Let's also be clear, it doesn't sound like you were explaining Jamiroquai, it sounds like you were elf-splaining Jamiroquai.
The new phrase the kids use.
It's catching on.
Yeah, that's your hashtag when you leave the show.
Mike, not to put you on blast in front of this kind audience, but I'm surprised you haven't made reference to my hat as someone who likes things that the kids like.
Oh, let's, yeah, did you get a good look at it?
Surely you recognize the statement on my hat and it means something to you.
Can you read it out loud, Mike?
It says, uh, is that perfect?
Is that what it says?
Perfect all-American bitch?
Does that ring no bells for you, Mike?
Is that Olivia Rodrigo?
It's a track from Guts.
Yeah.
Which half?
Let's see.
Oh, I listened to the second half.
Yay!
I did, yeah.
Hold up, but I gotta figure out what song I really like because I can't remember the name of it.
Because let me be clear, this was meant as a bit of a test.
It is track one.
The one track we knew for the record that I listened to.
I know that song now that you say track one.
I know and love Olivia Rodrigo.
I like her song, track one.
I am very young and cool.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Pretty Isn't Pretty is a great song.
Okay, but is it as good as the song that I'm about to sing from Clisson and the Merry Mission?
We make our toys with hearts from the very start.
With every part we make our toys with heart.
That's the song.
That's in the movie.
I was obviously just learning it and the level keeper wasn't there yet, but I at least got a sense of the rhyme scheme.
So I started just yelling, heart, start.
If you ever, yelling in an empty movie theater rules.
It's so much fun.
Boy, I recommend it.
This is a movie where at three different points, three different characters start a monologue explaining what Christmas is really about.
And each of them picks a different object that they say Christmas is all about.
And would you believe it?
All three objects exist as add-ons at Build a Bear Workshop.
What?
Hearts.
You put hearts in the bear.
Sometimes Christmas is about heart, but also Christmas is about Glisten, the Sparkle, a Sparkle in the sky who used to be a deer, not a reindeer, a deer.
But is now a Sparkle.
And then of course Santa Claus tells us that Christmas is about one thing, a tiny pickle.
What?
Yes.
Even though the poster clearly says it's about believing, then it's about many, many other things.
This is something that happened.
The level keeper and I were discussing how we didn't, we genuinely did not.
And maybe I'll speak for myself, do not understand who or what Glisten is.
Granted, I wasn't paying close attention, but is it a star?
Is it a deer?
Bit of a moving target.
She does not speak until the last 45 seconds of the film.
What?
Every 10 minutes, one of us would nudge the other and go, I think that's Glisten and we were always wrong.
I guess so many times.
So Glisten is a waiting for Guffman kind of character?
She does show up and she's visible for a lot of the time, but in a form different than her real form?
Yeah, you know, it just becomes a nice statement, mainly about how bears are good gifts.
And you see a lot of bears parachute down into different houses.
There is a plush pile depicted on screen.
Really?
At several points in the film, a tower of bears is constructed.
So that's, do they ever at one point in the movie give like prices?
You know, here's what they don't do this, but I wish they did.
What would be great is snowflakes are falling, but the snowflakes are QR codes and you could scan those in the theater.
Is that true?
No, I wish, I wish.
But that's not unbelievable.
There is a way to like interact with the film, which is if you're seeing it with only a ghost, you can get bored by the end,
get tired of guessing who Glisten is, go to the back of the room and start making shadow puppets on the film.
I tried to make like, how can I turn my head into Crow from Mystery Science Theater?
How close can we get?
Wow, and people said the Errors tour movie was rowdy.
Anyway, was it nice to see another film?
This must have been cool to like.
Incredible.
The second best movie I've seen in the last 25 years.
I want to call out two quick things.
One of them I said to you, I'm happy we found a movie to go see because otherwise it was going to ruin my letterbox stats of logging jungle to jungle every day.
If I was leaving my cycle of hell, I needed to be replaced with another film to keep my letterbox stats up.
You still have letterbox in hell, great.
And you said you might be the first person to log this film on letterbox.
Wrong.
I was surprised to see 21 reviews.
For a movie I should say is no longer playing in a single theater in America.
Wait, it's gone already?
This was what?
This was three days ago.
Was released November 3rd.
We saw it three days ago.
It's playing nowhere.
Wow.
Sorry everyone.
But it has been logged 51 times and reviewed 23 times.
I will not read all the reviews but see if you can start to sense a pattern.
Silver owl 87 gives it two stars and says, I will get fired if it's lower.
What?
Dayquane gives it three stars and says, corporate nonsense by build-a-bear.
Me and two coworkers were the only ones in the screening.
I hope there's only two people per screening.
Keckas Exorcist gives it no stars and says, I was forced to see this movie as a build-a-bear employee.
Oh my god.
So only people that work at build-a-bear see all this except for you two.
Correct.
Mika Mikaela gives it half a star and says, I watched this in a theater with my build-a-bear coworkers.
And Cinemag is so obviously a personification of build-a-bear CEO Sharon Price John.
Wow.
The CEO is in the movie.
There is no reported box office for this film's one week of release in only Cinemark theaters.
But it is possible we are the only two people who are not employees of build-a-bear who saw this film.
Wow.
It appears that it was strongly encouraged to all employees and they were told that tickets would be reimbursed.
And several of the reviews say things to the effect of, I didn't want to see this, but since my boss was paying for it, why not?
So possibly total box office of GLSEN and the Merry Mission, $10.
Give it up for GLSEN.
Incredible info.
I feel like with that, to get some other stuff in, because it is a busy sector and this is kind of a smaller stop by.
But I think we have to talk about somewhere that once you were in town, once we got in the movie out of the way,
we all got to get drinks from the best place to get drinks there is, Fat Tuesday.
Fat Tuesday is in this sector.
Established in New Orleans in 1984, almost 90 locations.
There are multiple Fat Tuesday booths at CityWalk Orlando.
We will cover a different one in a different sector.
Sorry folks, I know you paid to be here, but we can't give you both.
It's a sector keeper thing.
It's too important, yeah.
But why don't you guys, why don't you take the lead, because I looked at the drinks and said, fuck no.
Scott doesn't like to drink neon.
Which is something, you know, we talk about on the show.
Now I am very comfortable putting neon liquid in my mouth.
Almost excited, I would say.
Like thrilled to engage.
I would say generally I am excited to put neon liquid in my mouth.
Is anyone drinking something neon-ish right now in this audience?
Oh, I see a couple.
I see some more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know a bright blue, obviously a Curacao would be the ultimate.
What color did you go with?
So I went up and I asked what the recommendation was, and one of the recommendations was electric lemonade.
Which was a very bright blue.
The best color to drink.
Let's hear it up for blue, I guess.
And yeah, I mean, it tastes, as advertised, it was lemonade and it was sugar.
And I drank it.
And I would say my stomach hurt.
But I did enjoy, I did enjoy while I was drinking it, the first part of that.
But now when it was going through the tubes in my body.
So your tongue enjoyed it, but your intestines and the names I won't say.
They said tsk tsk, they were upset.
Down the line, Jason, you had some of one.
Jane and I split a pina colada and I don't have a lot to contribute.
We were like, oh, this is really good, this is delicious.
And we enjoyed it and we felt fine.
Well, isn't that nice?
We have the best case scenario.
This feels strange, knowing what happened to Mike and knowing what happened to the level keeper.
Well, I was looking for a drink with this brief break from my purgatory cycle.
I was looking for a drink to take the edge off from my usual diet of surge soda.
Overwhelmed by the options, I said, what's your most popular drink?
I ordered the Octane 190, which is advertised as grain alcohol and orange juice.
And it tasted like grains.
Gasoline and orange juice.
Yeah, I borrowed a sip from that and you took a photo.
And the face of disgust, I will post this, I wish we could flash it through the room.
It's not loaded up and ready to go.
But yeah, I thought it was like I was drinking gas with a squeeze of orange.
Was it caffeinated?
It was not, and I wished it was.
Really?
For something to kick some life back into me.
You wanted it to be, what do they call that, when it's uppers and downers at once?
Yeah, I call that surge soda.
I did some Googling, and of course the most popular grain alcohol brand in America is Everclear,
which at various times has been banned for sale in Florida, including possibly currently.
And Everclear has an alcohol proof of 190, and so the work around is in certain territories like Florida,
they will often sell a varietal that is 189.
So I believe I was drinking a 189 Octane 190.
Oh my god.
See, you got ripped off.
That was the whole percentage point you didn't get.
Give me the extra proof.
You just got to get a second one and take a little teeny spoonful.
A little spoonful.
Well, try the bar at 10 Roofs, see if they'll cook you up an Everclear 189.
Yeah, and please tip your bartender and wait staff.
We tried to be very polite.
Tip them by buying them an Everclear 189, obviously.
Anyway, it was one of those moments that because you bring up your issues, drinking stuff like this now,
and it's just, you know, we've been doing this podcast a long time,
and there's always these things where like the both of you, Mike and Jason I'm referring to,
it's like, I love to, I'm just a little boy eating my little boy treats, then like half an hour later,
oh my tummy, my tummy.
Jason and I are like the sugar buddies on the show, and we both like sugar a lot,
but yes, sometimes the tummy, especially in the, I will say this,
I do think I had too much sugar earlier in the day, and that is part of what did it.
Like if you're challenging me about if I'm a man or not, or I can't handle electrical limited, I can.
I can go right out to City Walk now and I can drink it, and I won't have weird poop or anything,
but in that moment, I couldn't digest it, you know, because like I'm young, okay?
I heard the album, I heard the second half of the Olivia Rodrigo album.
I can still go, I can still do it.
And I have started off every day at the hotel with a Danish, and I feel fine.
This is the cockiest I've ever seen you.
You got big D.
E.
right now, Jason.
Big Danish energy, yeah.
Oh boy, okay, I mean, I think that's the food portion.
I think now we've got to get to the big ticket item.
We did do a real themed experience, a real cool experience,
which I believe some of you were doing not just today, but mere hours ago.
Wow.
Oh, in the back.
There is a groove in the back that came from what we are talking about, incredible,
which is Universal's great movie Escape, the new Escape Room.
If you don't know about this, this is relatively recent.
It opened less than a year ago, replaced The Groove, Fallen Brother, The Groove.
Any experiences at The Groove?
Make some noise for The Groove.
Make some noise if you didn't like The Groove.
Wow.
Forceful claps on that one.
We'll investigate.
We'll do a Fallen Brothers thing.
But anyway, this was a nightclub that got converted into an Escape Room
and kind of a higher end Escape Room because they have these great cinematic properties to play with.
There is one that is Back to the Future and there is one that is Jurassic Park.
And we decided to do this.
And we, of course, we let the level keeper decide.
Because you made it in under the wire on both of those movies.
You saw those before being trapped in Jungle to Jungle.
Favourites, watched on VHS, the best home media format I ever knew.
Makes sense.
No, as a living child back in the day, I loved to run around Universal Studios Florida and ride the movies.
And now finally an opportunity to slowly walk from room to room of the movies.
Exit the movies.
Be confused by the movies.
Who has done this in general?
Is there?
Okay, okay.
Very good.
And the folks know that that's crazy.
Now it's like you're still in the room.
The final room.
It was just a drive away.
But so, I mean, I've been excited to check this thing out because that's a unique…
And for us, my God, something to do in City Walk that isn't slushies that hurt you.
So, yeah, we chose Back to the Future out of time.
That's the one we went with.
And I was excited and highly anticipating getting to like…
I mean, all I knew was that there were bits and pieces that are kind of like the dearly departed Back to the Future ride.
Not the part where you are on a ride.
But the part where you're in a little room before the ride.
But let's be honest, the little room before the ride was one of the best parts.
I would really like to see that little room again.
And sure enough, there was that little room again.
But do you guys have any observations about…
We can go beat by beat a little.
Any thoughts about getting in there?
Pre-show, the green curtain they pull?
So they've done, yeah.
So in the lobby, if you haven't been in there, it's like…
It's made to look like a fancy old time movie theater.
I assume because they want to be able to sub in and out universal properties, perhaps cycling them out if this is popular.
So yeah, it's making you feel like you're back in time and in the old days.
Not like you're in a Cinemark, but you're in like a fancy theater.
What?
Fancier than Cinemark?
Fancier than a Cinemark, which by the way still has…
Wait a minute, multiple posters of the Pelican brief?
We forgot to mention.
There are posters for the Pelican brief on both floors of the theater.
Really?
One significantly more sun-bleached than the other.
Yeah, great trip through the past.
Great trip through Kevin Costner films.
But yeah, yeah, very like art deco, you know…
Movie palace vibe.
And there's a nice little lounge with couches and chairs.
There's a bar with a drink menu, like cocktails and everything.
The hoverboard punch.
The gigawatt glow, the raptor bite.
It would have been nice to try one of these, but again, we knew that we were cursed to go to Fat Tuesday.
Fat Tuesday was happening after, yeah, and I didn't want to spoil my appetite.
Not to mention, I don't know, the drunken escape room sounds tremendously frustrating, right?
The senses are dulled and you're falling over.
Yeah, spoiler alert for me, I'm not particularly good at puzzles.
So even Stone Cold Silver, I was not the most helpful escape participant.
Yeah, no, you go ahead, sorry.
I mean, yeah, I don't think any of us do a lot of this stuff.
This was my first escape room of any kind.
Well, we know what happened last time I tried to do an escape room.
I had an anxiety attack.
And it definitely entered my mind as we were starting.
Which I think we picked the right one in that regard because has anyone done the Jurassic Park one?
Okay.
We heard that scary.
Okay, okay, so maybe we're in the creature zone, we're in the Minotaur zone.
It's something like a Minotaur, I can't guess what that would be.
I don't know if you guys heard, I did go up to the front desk and I go, what's the signal in case I got to get out of here?
And they were like, it's like this, and I'm like, oh, it's over your head more, yeah.
And I go, got it.
It's the same as WWE.
Yeah, if somebody gets hurt in wrestling, yeah.
Well, what's funny too about it is I think I pretended it wasn't for me.
I think I said, if somebody in our group, and I kind of gestured to everybody as if like, oh, one of these people are going to be scared.
And I was like, what is it again?
And then I was like, can you look and see if I'm doing it right?
Let's say in case one of Doc Brown's crazy experiments somehow, I don't know, results in a Minotaur being created.
What do I do with my arms?
Dr.
Minotaur Brown, his son?
I gave a list of possible scenarios and what I should do in case.
And they were very nice, but I don't think they suspected.
I don't think they knew what I was getting at.
Because you were like, now if somebody in our group, like somebody, like a guy over there in glasses and a hat,
like if somebody like that was scared, got really scared all of a sudden.
That short little coward over there starts peeing his pants.
What do I do?
We should also mention you were decked head to toe in no fear clothing.
So no one could question your bravery.
It was, I was bulletproof.
I was, there was no way people would know.
Wow.
But did you, how cool was I being though?
Did anybody notice?
You were being very cool, Michael.
You were being very cool.
You looked like a guy who had heard at least half of Olivia Rodrigo's guts.
Thank you.
You definitely came up to me and said, Hey, I'm just going to walk over there and ask a question quickly.
Oh, I told you that?
Oh, I don't remember that.
I was like a little.
But with kind of this gesture.
He's probably asking if you can buy cigarettes here.
You could smoke in the rooms, right?
I'm going to smoke one cigarette per room.
Every time I solve a puzzle, I'm going to light up.
It's funny you said that there was a surprisingly large amount of fog in most of the rooms at various points.
Oh, true.
Yes, indeed.
If you want to be trapped with fog.
You are escaping the fog.
It's mainly a fog.
Yes.
So first room you get into, you quickly meet an associate of Doc Brown, someone named Nico, which is a Tesla.
It's a Nico Tesla.
Nikodermis Tesla.
Elon Musk.
Her name was like six different science people.
We should also mention the first thing we saw when the door open was the Institute of Future Technology logo.
And you cheered.
We all cheered when we saw that.
Yeah, for sure.
I mean, yes.
Honestly, whatever else I say about this thing, the primary thing is they put up signs that are the logo from one of my favorite rides ever.
So 10 out of 10.
My biggest complaint is that it wasn't just wall to wall signs.
Yeah.
I was like, I would actually just like to sit in this room and not do any of the puzzles.
Honestly, yes.
Yes.
But many of them.
Just can I just can I sit here and sip a cocktail?
That's all I want to do.
But you're like, okay, well, Nico, but who's that to me?
I mean, nice to meet her, but this isn't somebody I know.
And then you hear the voice.
Great Scott.
It's Doc Brown himself in shadow.
And it is clearly Christopher Lloyd sounding horser than I do increasingly.
What are you talking about?
I'm in the prime of my life.
I could shout from the rooftops.
It also correct me if I'm wrong.
Did it not sound like maybe he did it into like his voice memos on his phone?
Like it was not the highest audio quality either.
Oh, yeah.
On breaks, on breaks filming nobody.
He was doing it in this trailer and we transferring it.
He was just doing what?
He's uploading it himself.
Huh?
You think an 85 year old Christopher Lloyd is uploading to WeTransfer?
Well, it's so simple folks.
WeTransfer.
Even Christopher Lloyd could do it.
Promo code check.
At some point he says that there's been an experiment gone wrong and he's trapped in a box where you can only see his shadow.
But they keep promising you that at some point he will definitely leave that box.
They tell you, yes, we see you can't see his face, but he's going to get out of this.
Don't worry.
And then you'll get to see him.
And then that doesn't happen.
Yeah, spoiler folks.
Doesn't happen.
Unless, I don't know, did your group do better?
Did it happen for you?
Do you have to get a 15 out of 15?
All right.
No, it didn't happen.
Anyways, but you get some instructions that are jargon.
Here's what I've learned.
I'm terrible at listening.
I didn't understand one thing that was said for this entire experience.
I knew that I had to pay attention to every detail.
So I'm there thinking, okay, remember, pay attention to every detail.
Wait, you're saying remember every detail to yourself.
Thus you're not listening to what you're supposed to be listening to.
Thus I failed.
I imagine what was happening was anytime I go into a long explanation of mobile ordering,
is you're like, do your best for 15 seconds and then your brain is just like, never mind.
Well, they set up in the first room that there's a portable flux capacitor that Doc has built like a handheld speak and spell form
flux capacitor that you're going to bring from time period to time period.
That requires not 88 miles per hour, but, you know, 0.
2.
Yes.
We're strolling with it.
And the first puzzle, I think, was we had to remember a series of letters in the right order, which took maybe 12 tries.
Well, there was the thing in the first room that kind of like it leans on your awareness of back to the future stuff and Doc Brown stuff.
And the first one, I don't remember what they were, but it was something like, you know, how do you invent the flux capacitor?
He hit his head and Mike goes, yeah, we know that.
He hit his head.
We know that.
Then there was another one like that.
Yeah, we know that.
And then and you were saying that loudly over everything else being said, hitting the button so fast, so indignant that they underestimate your awareness of back to the future.
And soon enough, you are getting them wrong.
It's possible that I was still a bit anxious and I am only realizing it now.
Honestly, that might have been what it was.
Yeah, we know that already.
Get us out of the room.
We know that already.
We can clear this one.
Scott did point it out and I do remember why do I keep hitting the button so hard?
So that's probably what it was.
Yes.
No, I was doing.
I started it off badly.
I admit it.
Show everyone your finger bruise, dark purple from button hitting.
That's not where I bled.
I bled from some other part of my body.
We'll tell you later.
But we do eventually conclusively solve this room.
There was a sense of completion and victory in this room.
Yes.
And we hear Doc Brown tell us that he's going to send us back to the 50s because that dastardly Biff has stolen the almanac again and is once again trying to ruin the prom, the enchantment under the sea dance.
And the next door opens.
There was a technical malfunction.
Oh no, Doc Brown messed up.
We're in 1885 and this room we fucking ate shit in.
God, God, it was really bad.
Something about pulling ropes and then making like a little.
And wheels.
Making a little dial dough.
We were spinning wheels for 10 minutes before we even identified that the rope was part of it.
This is where whoever, however they have their control room set up.
This is where we just we are getting dunked on by the people running this.
There's no way it wasn't happening.
We didn't know how to do anything.
We were like spinning things and it.
Because the first room was like like Simon like the old game Simon.
You just had to do it in the correct sequence.
They would tell you.
And then the second room was closer to an escape room where you kind of had to think outside the box and we were just like, oh shit.
Oh no.
Maybe I am not the most sharp from having recently watched the film Glisten and the Merry Mission in its entirety.
It took us at least eight minutes before we were doing anything that affected elements in the room in any way.
We were starting to see some tangible progress, but it didn't feel like we had cracked it.
And then Doc Brown came over the loudspeaker and said, great news.
I figured out an alternative way to get you to the next time period.
Which we found out is how they tell you, never mind.
Don't stress out about it.
Just open the door for you.
I feel like there's like three things that like three three lines of dialogue.
The first one is like, oh, here's what you have to do.
You have to pull the barn rope and do the blah blah blah.
And you go, OK, that's the instruction.
Then there's a thing in the middle that's sort of like a gentle hint.
Yeah, just a reminder.
Oh, just a reminder.
I told you the rope is a very important thing to pull.
And we're like, what is he fucking talking about?
And then another amount of time goes by and he goes, fuck you.
I'll do it myself.
That's the stage it goes from if you're in an escape room.
There was a sound cue in that room of like a mean cowboy threatening to murder us.
Oh yeah, clanging on the door.
But that also when you go in the room and it's like, he's banging on the door and you're like, oh shit.
And then like he's banging on the door for what feels like 10 minutes and you're like, he ain't getting in here.
This guy can't do shit.
Like it really, the danger goes away very quickly.
I did some digging into escape room subreddit reviews of this experience.
Yes.
And they said that unlike most escape rooms, which like your group rents it and it's yours until you solve it.
This every time you solve a room and go to the next room, they push a group into the room you were just in.
Really?
It's that fast?
And if that group solves things faster than they should, Doc Brown goes, well, I guess I figured out how to help you out.
Oh, so depending on how the people before you do, then Doc will chime in earlier and solve the problem for you.
Correct.
Those people who went in right after us were much better than us.
Wow.
That's crazy.
So they would let, they would let us like languish for 30 minutes if there was no group behind us.
Possibly.
That's it.
Yeah.
Oh, what a pity we didn't get to languish more in a room full of ropes and levers.
I like the fail safe of like, okay, keep moving, keep moving on.
Because when I have done escape rooms in the past and it's just one room you're set in, like there's a worker and they'll give you little hints.
But there's a lot more suffering.
There's a lot more torture of like, oh God, we can't get out of this room for another 35 minutes.
I like the idea of it, but in practice it did feel a little condescending.
One of your favorite movie characters of all time tells you you're a slowpoke.
You know, maybe just take a break, a breather, don't get worked up.
It is the opposite of the Optimus Prime thing, really.
Yeah.
I'm not disappointed in you.
Everyone has a tough time sometimes.
It also, it kind of kills the narrative stakes of the experience where they set up, we have a limited amount of energy.
You need to keep finding it and locating it to pushing us forward in the time.
And then once every 10 minutes, Doc Brown goes, I might have figured out another way.
I'm smart, remember?
That's the point of me.
Let's take the pressure off you guys.
But at least, you know, at least in success or not success, no matter what, you get to keep going through back to the future oriented rooms.
And one of the coolest things ever was, not ever, I don't know, coolest things that day.
In a day of a bunch of City Walk crap.
Oh, City Walk, the coolest things.
Maybe the coolest thing in City Walk now is getting to go into a little Cafe 80s.
Great to see it.
And why did they not do that in the park then or now?
Oh my God.
So cool.
We really should have just not solved and sat in the booths and just soaked it up.
The next group is banging on the door.
Yeah.
Probably the best room.
And I would say the most fun puzzles.
Which at a certain point Scott lying flat on his back on the floor to figure out codes.
Seems like you guys got it back there.
You figured it out.
Yes, you have to like look at stains and gum on the underside of a table.
That's a hint, I guess, if you haven't done the thing yet.
We all had to hold hands.
The power of friend trip.
Yeah, we did all hold hands.
And that was required.
It was mandatory.
Yeah.
I want you to hold hands with each other and confess how much you love each other.
Why doesn't the Back to the Future poster say it's about friendship?
Take a cue from Glisten.
Men of your age often have a hard time expressing intimacy with friends.
Touch them.
Acknowledge each other as sexual beings.
Everyone hold hands.
If there are two people in here in a confusing situationship, figure it out later.
You get to see, well, once again, like all of Time Paradox's hinge on this one school dance.
The universe is entirely predicated on a little Chuck Berry performance.
So you do, you have to plug some instruments in.
Did we get that right?
I don't remember what we did or didn't.
It seemed like we may have, but also they may have just switched it off.
I don't know.
Or switched it on.
Because yeah, you're supposed to plug in the different chords into the different mics and…
That room I think we did okay on.
That and Cafe 80's were the two.
Yeah.
And there's a phone on the wall.
Let's not say what song you have.
You have to sing a song altogether at one point.
We had to harmonize.
I'm not going to give it away.
Yeah.
That room is really like, that's an interesting idea is that like, oh, remember like a famous movie scene.
Now you're going to go like behind it and like help fix something before the scene plays out, which is a kind of a funny way to…
It's like that Tom and Jerry movie where they're just watching the Wizard of Oz, which we've talked about before on the show.
There's a cartoon, like a movie that's like the Wizard of Oz, but Tom and Jerry are just like hanging out in the background watching it go down.
And that's sort of like what we did.
We were the Tom and Jerry of Back to the Future.
Right.
It's a big recurring thread in this escape room is they keep on telling you, we swear to God the characters you know and love are right over there.
Take our word for it.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're fun.
But by the way, you can't see them.
You're not allowed to see them.
It will destroy the space time continuum if you see them.
I don't know.
That's funny.
You know what's very cool is seeing the Bif Tannen Museum as a big Back to the Future 2 head.
Pretty neat to end up seeing, you know, you go into an alternate 1985 type environment and Nico, the host who was nice to you before is now mean to you.
She's gone.
She got Biffed, which makes you feel mildly worse for how bad you've been doing the whole time.
But especially there, that room was awful.
We did terrible.
We made zero progress.
It looked great.
Like the props and the decoration.
It looked awesome.
We couldn't figure it out.
Yeah, no, it was very confusing.
Obviously, I liked being in the like gross like 80s velvet room, but it was like too, it was too confusing.
I don't know.
Did you see anything on the Reddit about what we were supposed to do?
I know answers for that room, but remind me when we're done.
I'll tell you the big realization I got from the Reddit.
Why not read a big Reddit thread to the audience?
Yeah.
Seems like fun.
I searched for spoilers and answers and it did not seem like anyone online figured that room out.
Without spoiling it, the group in the back, did you do anything successfully in that room?
I even did.
Whoa.
Wow.
That's a hard thing to yell.
I'm not going to make you yell the solve from the back of the bar.
Maybe we can talk after, but here's something that you can yell.
There is a scale of one to 15, ultimately, of how you did on this thing.
And I forget all of the rankings, but what did you guys get out of 15?
Eleven.
That's pretty good.
That is second notch, correct?
Wow.
Do you remember the ranking offhand?
Even though you just did it.
Memorable experience.
There were three titles that you could get to.
Four?
Yeah.
We were at the highest end of the lowest tier.
Yes.
Let's say our score, ten.
You guys in the back beat us.
Great job.
Your bravery saved the planet.
Well done, Freedom Fighters.
When we walked out, the cast member working there said, so how do you guys think you did?
I really…
Very nice.
The team member was very nice, but it really seemed like they were winding up to go like, you idiots.
I was hoping it was one of those college things where a teacher would be like, I'm going to give you the grade you think you earned.
And we could have said perfect.
We thought we did perfect or whatever.
I think she very quickly sensed that we were not feeling great about ourselves.
And she said, I'll have you know, you actually scored above average.
Yeah.
You got ten out of fifteen things, which is above average.
And I turned to Scott and I said, I think she's trying to make us feel better.
And they make up a score based on the mood of the people walking out.
When I went to the Reddit, and this was not a universal subreddit, it was an escape room subreddit.
The consensus seemed to be that most people got three or four things right in total.
Okay.
They also said that previously the score would be part of the screen in the final room.
They give you the number, which felt like a thing that was set up in the early stages.
And they removed it and had it changed to a cast member gauging your mood before because people were getting so pumped out hearing Doc Brown tell them they failed.
She said the average was seven or eight.
And then told us ten.
That makes so much sense.
Because ten is like, we wouldn't believe her if she said fourteen or fifteen.
We would have thought she was being nice, but ten makes you feel like you've got a B minus or a B.
Okay.
Well, if we talk to any of you after the show or after both shows, we're doing two tonight.
If you feel like saying a good show or whatever, gauge our mood first.
Or tell us ten, but don't tell us out of how many.
If it's out of one hundred, we'll never know.
Never tell us a lower number than ten.
Ten only.
And if you buy us a stuffed glisten doll, hand it to us and walk away without saying anything, we won't know what the hell that means.
One more observation, just as we're winding it down about this thing.
The final room, you're behind the clock tower.
So you would get, in a different form, you see Doc Brown's shadow.
Which is a cool perspective to be behind the clock tower, but it also means that as time is ramping up and of the essence and as the storm is brewing,
that if you don't get it right, you're going to hurt Doc Brown.
And you're going to have to watch it happen.
And hear it.
And again, it is Doc Brown sounding a little older than when he made the films originally.
What are you talking about?
You did this to me.
You want me.
Scott.
It's like the, it's the ET technology.
Scott, Jason, level ghost boy.
Friend.
Your cowardice doomed me.
You killed me and Marty too.
He heard about what happened and took his own life.
Somehow our deaths made Biff stronger than ever.
He's become a mega Biff.
He's as tall as the clock tower now.
We'll leave you to clean up that mess.
Well, I think that's our experience with the Back to the Future escape room.
And that's, we're sort of heading to the end of our first show here tonight.
But I don't, okay, you know, I know you're filling in here.
Yes, of course.
You're not, and we haven't done one of these in a while, but just to remind you what the sector keeper does.
Usually his thing has been once we've completed a sector, then we get a sector stone.
Huh.
Yeah.
I think we all need to close our eyes.
Maybe the people on stage, but not in the audience.
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't see why they would have to know.
And listen.
Okay.
Try to see if we can hear where the stone would be because we're on stage and this is a show and I'm trying to make it visual.
Huh.
Where would there be a stone?
I don't know.
Hmm.
They're putting out new cotton candy at Sugar Factory.
What are you guys doing after?
Doing the Ferris wheel?
What's the plan?
Sorry we couldn't do the show in the Ferris wheel.
That would have been fun.
Do I have time between shows to get up in the Orlando Eye?
Let's all cram into one little box.
I'm running late.
I'm stuck at the top of the Orlando Eye.
Can you walk around and drink on iDrive like it's Vegas?
Yes.
Wow.
Is there a Fat Tuesday?
Is there like an equivalent to Fat Tuesday on iDrive?
There's a full Pizza Hut and a Chuck E.
Cheese right up the block.
Okay.
I'm going to Doc Brown style admit defeat.
Yes.
My plan was not working.
Oh.
What was the plan?
What happened?
Well of course, a Build-A-Bear Grizz.
The Sector Stone.
It's Grizz.
With the real voice of Michael Rapoport, unfortunately is saddled with the quietest speaker I have ever heard in a toy.
Can everyone be pin drop quiet?
Okay.
Let's try it.
This is going to be tough.
No.
I'm holding the mic directly up to where the sound is coming from.
I may have just made sure that they had a certain kind of Sector Stone at a Build-A-Bear workshop near this venue.
And when I picked this out and heard the speaker, I may have said, that's extremely quiet.
And the employee might have said, huh, yeah.
Can you hear it?
No.
Not even right next to you.
Can you hear Michael Rapoport's sweet voice?
Just imagine him and his dulcet tone of voice going like, yo, yo, yo, I got to hibernate.
And it's like, he does that 24 hours a day.
I heard it.
Wow.
If you really, you have to jam it inside your ear.
It has to be in your ear.
It's like the bell from Polar Express.
You can only hear it if you believe really hard.
And that's what the movie was about.
That's the movie.
That's what the movie is about.
Grizz.
Well, let me say something.
Let me say a couple things.
This is a stuffed Grizz that technically talks if you jam it inside your own ear.
And it has a shirt that is not something from the movie.
It says, I'm the reason Santa has a naughty list.
Oh, I got that shirt.
But, you know, I'm level keeper.
First of all, I'm so happy you could do this in the Sector Keepers absence.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you for freeing me briefly.
Yeah, I think.
Yeah, I guess.
Wait, you're free after one, right?
Or I don't know the rules of this.
I hope you're free.
I hope you at least get to like advance to a different Tim Allen movie.
Thank you.
I've heard good things about Joe somebody.
But, you know, our journey, our journey through city walk Orlando is a long and harrowing one.
And I know we're going to need every one of these sector stones.
But there's something else I know.
I saw a movie recently that was about believing and that was about, you know, how you got to buy bears and about a pickle, you said.
It's about the pickle.
And it's about the pickle.
But I think among the many things the movie was about was sharing.
Let's say sharing.
And I think that it's important to share with friends.
So I think that the Sector Keeper is going to be OK if we don't keep this special sector stone.
And I am curious, is Malia here?
Is Malia here?
And can you?
The stairs are over.
Malia, hi!
Wow!
Give it up for Malia.
Oh my God.
Hello.
It's great to see you.
People in the audience are chanting, let's fucking go.
They made friendship bracelets and I'm assuming they don't want to lug them home.
So make sure you get one.
Malia gave, we have friendship bracelets and a lot of the audience does as well.
We've been seeing them as they've been coming in.
So it seems only fair that we do a trade.
Hello.
Give it up for Malia.
I'm so excited to see you.
Thank you.
It seems fair.
I think that the Sector Keeper, well let me have the Level Keeper say, can you just officially announce this is yours?
Hold on.
Let me see if I can support this in text.
Because I believe it already says that this Build-A-Bear was made with heart for Malia.
Oh my God!
Thank you.
Absolutely.
Wow.
There you are.
Cherish it forever.
Any thoughts?
Any, in this suspicious moment?
Oh my gosh.
This is a dream come true.
Thank you so much.
Oh my gosh.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Give it up for Malia.
Wow.
Malia even cooler than a grizzly bear with attitude.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
Come back.
You know what we should do?
Let's make like the Back to the Future escape room and all join hands in the power of friendship.
Great.
Okay.
Mike, you got it.
For voltage.
We can take pictures of it.
This is a good theater.
Okay.
Here we go.
And, and.
Hooray!
Yeah!
You survived.
Podcast the Ride.
Thank you, Malia.
You survived Podcast the Ride.
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of Madness Sector.
Phase something, Sector something.
We'll remember it later.
Our thanks to everybody at Tin Roof.
This has been so much fun.
Our thanks to Connor and Eric for helping us out tonight.
Our thanks to the Sector Keeper.
We'll see you soon.
But especially thanks to the Level Keeper.
Thanks for being here.
Coming all the way from heaven.
And especially thanks to all of you for coming out.
We've missed you in Orlando.
We've missed everybody who traveled so much.
It's so great to see you again.
Thanks for being here and remember the future is what you make of it.
Yeah!
ForeverDog.
This has been a ForeverDog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest ForeverDog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram, at ForeverDogTeam, and liking our page on Facebook.