Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a dough that's soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll.
With alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where seam-punged robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando.
Tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of Madness.
A daily,
Exploring the shops, restaurants,
and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride presents
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of Madness.
My name is Mike Carlson and I have to say
before we even introduce anyone else
that I'm having a blast-a doing this pod-cast-a.
Joining me as always, Scott Gairdner.
I'm trying to come up with one immediately.
Okay, good luck.
I guess that's, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You seem an enthusiast-a about this pod-cast-a.
I am, that's right.
How about Jason Sheridan?
How about, how are you feeling, sir?
Can you do it in any fun way?
Can you say it?
I know, I'm thinking, I'm thinking,
I'm having a lot of fun
and I don't want to run from recording this fun pod-cast.
I mean, sure, yeah.
Yeah, it's not as good.
You guys are the more musical.
You gotta add the A or something to it.
Oh yeah, it's because we're more musical, I think, yeah.
I'm having a lot of fun-a, don't want to run-a.
Okay.
That changed everything.
With one letter, it's all different.
My man, now you're on island time with the rest of us.
Thank you for doing that.
So yes, today here we are,
a very exciting situation, sector.
Yeah, I mean, I think we gotta check and make sure.
Oh yeah, you're right, I'm sorry.
I have a feeling where we're going.
That's true.
This construct, we have to double check.
We really, is this a good time to do it?
Yeah, please, you could be right.
Alright, let's see if we can call them in.
Sector keeper, where are we going today?
Boys, boys, today begins phase five,
Age of Buffett.
Phase five, sector one is Lone Palm Airport Bar
and the Hemisphere Dancer.
Hmm, wonder if the story behind that is,
fins up boys.
Whoa.
Wow, that's right.
The Age of Buffett.
Wow, an imposing phase potentially
or a phase for celebration.
I think celebration, that's what he would have wanted.
Well, and isn't that, in a way, what we're doing today?
Because we've discussed Jimmy Buffett's passing,
something that unfortunately,
in the time that it has taken us to get this off the ground,
that is an event that has occurred, RIP Jimmy Buffett,
and we celebrated him a little bit
on a Christmas Club 3 episode
with all of his Christmas albums.
However, there has not been the proper eulogy episode.
Is that kind of what this is?
It's tricky because, yeah, to some degree,
that is what this is, but I started unraveling
some other stuff too, so maybe it's not,
I almost feel self-conscious about this
being the official eulogy episode.
Sure, I just hadn't got enough data about the plan.
Because for a while it was, we'll just kick it to the saga.
It'll be in the saga, we'll kick it to the saga.
That's what I thought, and then I started looking into
some of the stuff that I know we needed to talk about,
and I was like, oh, well, there's some questions here,
and I don't know that this is the proper tribute.
Mm-hmm.
You know?
Well, there was also a discussion,
as we were forming the sector boundaries
with the Sector Keeper, there was a discussion of,
you know, we need to address, in a bigger way,
Jimmy Buffett's passing.
Right.
Do we do that with his restaurant?
His name is in it, Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville.
Or is the true spirit of Jimmy, in a way,
just outside the restaurant, just outside,
there's like a little pathway, and it's along the water.
We're getting closer to Jimmy's spirit, I feel.
Yes.
And there is this, there is this little bar
that, where you get the breeze better than you get it
back in the restaurant itself.
Uh-huh.
And then there is a certain decorative item
that is more than a decorative item,
and therefore, should this not be the official Jimmy tribute,
even more than Margaritaville.
Here's the thing.
We're not gonna know until this episode is done.
I don't know how this is gonna go.
Are we gonna have to add another one?
You guys don't have, I don't know what we're gonna do
about anything.
That's all I'm saying.
Neither did he.
You know what?
I don't think he knew.
He didn't know.
When he first put pen to paper, and…
I just spilled the Diet Coke.
Well, yeah, like you were saying
before you spilled that Diet Coke,
you know, you've gotta lax at it.
You don't know exactly where you're going.
Jimmy didn't know that when he first put pen to paper
to write a song, or to write all three of the chords
in his song, that it was eventually going to turn
into a restaurant chain.
And you didn't know that you were gonna knock over
that Diet Coke and then still be cleaning it up
and wiping and having to yell while you're doing it.
Oh, but now you're back.
You should have had a song called like Party Foul,
or something, Party Foul, or whatever they call it,
you know, when you drop a drink or something at a party.
What could have destigmatized party fouling?
Well, that's true.
Today's destination seems like it would be a place
where they're spilling a lot.
You know, people haphazardly knocking over
their boat drinks and such.
Into the sand.
Oh, that's a fun little drink sand blend.
You gotta reek it up.
Another thing he could have done a song about.
Liquidy sand.
Drink sand.
Sugar in the sand.
You know that you're drunk if you're drinking drink sand.
Drink sand is good.
Watch out for the paper umbrellas.
Yeah, so anyway, so everything's fine.
I've recovered from spilling the tall boy Diet Coke.
Extra tall Diet Coke.
That was the problem.
A tall boy like you and your tall elbows reached up
and knocked it over.
But you know what?
Didn't that not loosen us up?
You know what?
Maybe it was his spirit moving through your elbow
and going, guys, relax.
It's not a book report.
Y'all are chilling out and talking about your favorite guy.
He's in the room with us.
And he's guiding me as I flip through many tabs
listing information about his famous plane.
I feel like it's been a minute since there's been one of those episodes
where Mike has these so many things, so many things, too many things.
Yes, this is so many things.
That's often the fuel of great episodes.
That's true.
I'm excited, and it makes up for me who has none.
That's good.
I really assumed that you would take the lead here.
I'm kind of the same.
I open the basics, the restaurant website,
and some Yelp menu pictures just to see how it's changed over the years.
Let's just give our general opinion so far.
We're talking about basically this little oasis
outside of Margaritaville Restaurant Proper in Orlando.
It's a little bar.
It's got sand.
You can dip your little toesies in the sand if you want.
As I did, it was nice.
As of 2003, Jimmy Buffett put a real-life plane of his there,
which is now an iconic part of the skyline or whatever,
depending on where you're looking.
Yes, in the logo of this series.
It's one of the primary parts of it.
Some listeners noted when they saw that plane in the logo,
a number of them asked a question.
The question was, if that plane is so prominent in the logo,
does that mean that there's some sort of interesting story about the plane?
No, that's a very good question.
I think there is.
I think there is an interesting story.
There were interesting questions I had that I've asked on this podcast before,
and I think we always say, well, whenever we get to it in the episode about it,
that's when we're going to tackle these questions.
I just wanted to get your opinion on the place real quick.
Sure.
The sand, that little oasis.
Have you had a drink there?
Scott and I had a drink there with the level keeper when we were there.
We discussed it a little bit.
I have only ever kind of passed through there.
You've never had a drink at the Lone Palm Airport.
Well, it's not his happy places under the lighthouse
and eating a Cinnabon and smoking a very long cigarette.
Smoking a long parliament, which my partner thought was my preferred cigarette.
You like longs, right?
Yeah.
You a longs guy?
You've got longsig energy, right?
I mean, it is fair in the handful of times I've bought a pack of cigarettes my life,
and as for parliaments, they start going, what kind?
And I go, regular?
Longer, longer.
Longer.
Smokable.
Those ones that are coming off of the shelf because they're so long.
Those ones that don't fit on your regular shelf.
You know what?
But it turned out nice.
We had lots of nice little cool down moments at the board of entry smoking area.
We could share the long cigarette very easily.
But this is not your…
That's where you go to relax.
We've all taken photos at this place with this plane,
which apparently has some of the story associated with it.
But do you get any feeling from this little zone?
Oh, I got a feeling of relaxation.
It's very chill.
Looking back, I do regret not driving a scooter and blasting the horn in the sand.
Whoa, wait, what?
Blasting the horn?
And interrupting the good, calm, mellow vibes?
I mean, I don't know.
A woman did.
I was passing by this area on the path.
It was getting a little crowded, and one was like, use the horn, use the horn.
And I'm like, I didn't touch the horn the whole time.
I'm terrified to use that thing.
But you wanted to use it at the Lone Palm Airport.
Or was it going to be like a party horn?
Like a party horn.
You could do it along with the steel drum part of Margaritaville.
That's true.
I don't think it would pitch bend, but you never know.
Maybe if you put a little different pressure on it, there's probably a way to play a horn.
Even just testing what terrain that thing can go over.
Can it go through sand?
How many donuts?
Is this a bad idea?
Am I losing a deposit doing this?
There should be.
It should be like a vehicle that can then convert into something that could go through sand.
Like it should be like an all-terrain vehicle.
Well, down at the Jersey Shore in Ocean City, a lot of the umbrella stations that are kind of set up at the busier beaches
do have like sand wheelchairs with giant wheels on them that can go through sand.
So, Scott, I was really impressed that you went the full like, I'm taking my shoes off.
I'm kicking my toesies in the sand.
I did.
I did it.
I put my bare feet in there.
And then still a few listeners were like, that Scott foot stuff on Maine?
I don't know.
My feet were covered, listeners.
That's where the soon to be announced $30 tier will be coming into play on the picture.
Yeah, famous attractions.
Really close up high def photos of your feet.
I'm no fool.
I wouldn't give it away for free.
I'm a businessman, just like Jimmy.
Anyway, it did feel great.
It felt very nice.
And you know what?
I do think they carved out a little relaxing zone.
We had a drink under the plane's wing.
It was a very chill spot.
And you know, and it is an area with a lot of hubba, but you know, it's kind of hidden away.
You go all the way around and then you don't notice the crowd of people.
Sure.
And this is, you know, like there's a little kind of section it's not as, of course, beautiful to sit and look at the view.
But in LA, there's a little kind of nooky area as well.
Like I almost think that's the magic of Margaritaville and Jimmy Buffett in general is just having a little relaxing place.
And yes, there's not the water view in Los Angeles, but you have a view of a fence and a service.
It's not the best view in the world, to put it mildly.
But you got a fire pit there.
You got some TV, got some music.
I've had some nice relaxing times sitting in those Margaritaville themed or painted deck chairs out there.
Me too.
And that's more important, I think, as far as like the food, all that stuff, fine, eating fine.
But having a nice little nook or a little spot is really the place.
That's what if all Margaritaville's were just a little spot.
Yeah.
That would be ideal, I think.
And it's I think it hurts some of the locations that they, you know, these ones that have a little extra bar zone.
Yes.
I think are probably the best ones in the closer to water we can get, obviously the better.
Yes, like the one, yeah, the one at Navy Pier in Chicago doesn't have a little spot.
It's by the water, but it's not a little spot.
And that's what you want.
You want it cozy, you want a little spot.
So, yeah, this place is great.
This is this is one of the best places in City Walk Orlando.
Do you think that it is acceptable, given a short time frame, to choose Lone Palm Airport, to go have a drink here and perhaps not even food and not go to Margaritaville the restaurant proper?
I would not be upset with you if you told me you did that.
Great.
Just over here.
What do you think, Jason?
No.
Yeah, I think that's valid.
Yeah.
You know, I wouldn't say it's any more different than like if you sat on that patio at Margaritaville where sometimes troubadours are, you know, playing their wares.
You mean like playing a fife?
Playing a fife.
Playing Long December on a guitar or something.
Yeah, playing.
By the Counting Crows.
Playing Zimmerazz.
If you will please indulge me, sir.
Long December.
And there's a reason.
Yes.
Playing a little flute of volcano.
So, yeah, there's nothing I don't have anything bad to say about the actual spot in Orlando here.
Of course not.
Obviously, you know, maybe who knows as time goes on if we'll have any negative things to say about Margaritaville or the food or anything.
I don't know.
We'll find out tomorrow.
We'll find out.
But as far as this spot, this is the ideal spot because you could also have a drink wander over there.
It doesn't have to be even a Margaritaville branded drink.
It doesn't have to be a Landshark Lager.
You could bring anything you want.
Bring a Fat Tuesday over there.
You could bring there's the bar that sells just boring unbranded drinks, which I know is like who gives a shit.
But you could just bring like a whiskey on the rocks over there.
But you want to get, if possible, you want to get something where there's a picture of a sun wearing a lei.
Yeah, of course you want that.
I'm just saying this is a versatile spot.
Yeah.
And I don't think anybody's going to yell at you if you don't have a Buffett Margaritaville branded cocktail.
Sure.
Not even you?
You're chill enough that you don't yell?
I would judge it silently in my head of like, well, they brought in sort of unlicensed whiskey, no IP whiskey or whatever.
But I guess.
That doesn't look like a Bahama Mama.
That looks like green alcohol and orange slush.
Right.
I'm like kind of like, yeah, like a lady, like an older lady, like judge, like in church or something.
That's my energy.
You gab, you gab.
That's what I'm saying.
I'll gossip about them later.
The Christmas and Easter crowd are here, I see.
Jason's rolling his eyes.
That's what I would be doing too.
Sure.
That's how you feel about fair weather Buffett fans.
Right.
Yes, of course.
So, but I would at least appreciate that they came over here to pay their respects to this sacred area and this sacred plane with possibly an interesting story.
I do want to shout out they do have a partial food menu.
Yes, they do.
That's a very good point.
And it's on a menu shaped like a surfboard.
That's good.
Of course it's good.
That's a lot of fun.
Yeah.
A lot of fun.
But yes, I think here, like, like, I can't imagine what would be other than maybe like food that is rancid, other than what you could not like about this.
I just feel like this is the most unimpeachable spot in all of CityWalk.
I feel like this is another one where you're, I don't know who you're arguing to.
This is a common mic occurrence.
It's not, and there's no, you couldn't have a complaint.
There's nothing you could say about this place.
Well, I like somebody who has a complaint to show me what it is.
I'm just saying.
There's got to be a person listening right now that's like shit talking it.
And I don't want to.
I don't want it.
They need to listen to what I'm saying, which is definitive.
It's in that lane where you're like, and Gail Gordon was always funny.
Show me a time that he didn't bring it.
He wasn't making you guffaw.
And yeah, yeah, maybe it was a little Frank Nelson ish.
OK, but whatever people share artists share from each other.
Inspiration comes.
Because he's like that's the other people talk like that too.
Not just those two.
The only thing you would like more than this is if there was a Gail Gordon restaurant.
Gail Gordon's Gail Gordon's Harumphville.
Oh, please.
Oh, yeah.
The vault could have been like the vault or something.
The soup vault.
It's like Mr.
Mania had a vault at his bank, of course, from the show.
I definitely knew one fact about his character that I've never seen before from the third.
Here's Lucy show where Lucy's having a cookout.
Jack Benny is there.
He's doing the cook.
I don't know.
This is completely out of context.
I don't know what the episode was about.
And then he's like, oh, viral.
Here's Lucy clip.
You know how people get like on your Instagram and like you'll get different things like targeted to you and it'll be like models for some people and it'll be, you know, like sports for some other people.
I get just out of context clips of here's Lucy on Instagram.
Have sent me numerous here's Lucy clip.
Yes, of course.
Here's Lucy is fascinating.
It ran for like seven years.
OJ Simpson is on it.
Like there's just so many things going on.
And this one is like Jack Benny's on it.
I forget there's somebody else on it.
I'm like, is that and it is.
And then he like he calls in a bus driver and then Jackie Gleason dressed as Ralph Cramden comes in like the longest applause ever in the full Ralph Cramden like bus driver outfit.
And then like he makes a hamburger.
But then like take some of Jack Benny's money and puts on it and like there's a whole like hand like thing like he's about to like really dig in and eat it.
And then that's the end of the show.
I'm like latter day Jackie Gleason performance.
Nobody talks about nobody talks about it.
Yeah, I said I sent it to a big Jackie Gleason fan and he had never seen it before.
So yeah, this is a little known.
And you send it to your Gleason chat.
Yeah, I don't want to steal something from Jane, but my Gleason girlies is what I call it.
Yeah, so.
Does that get confusing in your message app, the Gleason girlies next to the Gordon girlies?
It gets very confusing.
Yeah, because those are two separate factions.
Yeah, and you switch to Gale girlies and it's even more confusing.
Yeah, very, very confusing.
So yeah, anyway, nobody should argue with what I just said in general about Gale Gordon or Lone Palm Airport.
Now you're keeping us in suspense, Mike.
Does the plane have an interesting story?
The plane is an interesting story, but we're going to get there.
That's the whole thing.
So what I want to start also talking about is that perhaps this interesting story put our hero Jimmy Buffett in danger of dying prematurely or whatever.
But that's not the only story where Jimmy Buffett had a near death experience.
OK, as a pilot, you know, pilots for some reason always seem to have these stories.
Celebrity pilot, Harrison Ford, for instance.
Yeah, certainly.
Friends, right?
Because you look up and it's like People magazine.
When Jimmy died, they published a thing called Jimmy Buffett survived at least three near death experiences before his death at age 76.
Wow.
And that was not ultimately in a plane crash.
No, and it was not that a parrot flew into his mouth, performed his entire last concert for him.
That has happened a few times.
No, I'm a pro with that.
That happened.
All right.
The parents taking this one.
Take it.
So I just wanted to do a brief history of some of the incidents.
What Buffett his first brush was 1978.
He was on a sailboat in San Salvador at the time.
He was anchored in a cove, which again, this is perfect.
Buffett stuff, a cigarette boat stopped to use Buffett's radar, and he gave them approval if he could drive their go fast boat.
After partying on a nearby sailboat and sleeping in his boat's dinghy, he reportedly drifted out and woke up surrounded by water.
But eventually the cigarette boat and a mother mothership loaded with drugs found him for the mail and pointed him in the direction of land.
So he like partied too hard and he wound up like floating alone at sea.
In a go fast boat.
Do you know what a go fast boat is?
I think that's because they come into play in the plot of the Miami Vice Michael Mann movie.
They talk about needing go fast boats to get to Cuba.
OK, and get back and forth.
I don't know how fast the go fast boat goes.
It's probably faster than that boat we took around Bay Lake in Florida Disney World, though.
Give me a go slow boat.
That will in its later years.
Give me a take it easy boat.
Uh huh.
That barely moves boat.
That boat was basically a rowboat with a go car motor in it.
So yeah, I think goes faster for sure.
So yeah, in ninety four, he flipped a plane and then he had to escape the plane and swim to a passing boat as he was taking off.
Which is this is always the thing where I'm thinking about like flying or flying a helicopter or whatever.
I feel like if I flipped a plane over once, I'm probably done flying planes.
Was it a sea plane?
Yeah, it was a sea plane.
Are those easier to flip?
That's a very good question.
Well, the water is there, too.
So I bet the the the extra element of water is definitely making like if you're just taking off on a runway and it's maybe not even that windy, you don't have water that could potentially be like an extra element of something that would knock you off.
Sure.
Do you know the location of any of these incidents?
This was Nantucket Island.
OK, what about the other one?
Oh, I have to go back and look.
I just I'm going to it's going to take me a second, but it does feel like there's possible rhyming.
OK, you know, why didn't you do songs about any of these?
Certainly Nantucket is a prime prime word for rhyming.
Well, I was just going to say Nantucket.
Water is probably a lot colder, maybe choppier.
Sure.
That's not a good title.
Yeah.
But what is it?
No, I never said it was.
I was just saying that water and I thought you were going to pitch a song title.
Uh, I wish I had a popsicle so I could suck it maybe.
Um, that's a little I don't want that to be suggestive.
I don't want to put him he only does like lightly suggestive songs.
Yeah, I know.
But is then like how do you because how do you fit and make it up?
It's got to be like Nantucket, man.
Fuck it.
Well, that's not.
Yeah, he would.
He'll does he have a fuck in this?
When you got Nantucket waiting for you there, I think you break your rules.
Well, but you're not in the title.
You can also say suck it like your suck it.
Nantucket.
Well, corner corner chuck it.
Separate thought.
Corn is a good thing to shuck.
Yeah.
If only he lived.
Well, he should have done it.
He needed to strike while the iron was hot.
He should have written a song in 94.
So he said in 95, he said, I'm still flying, but I have a safer plane now, which he told the Boston Globe.
And for a while he got introspective about it.
But he's you got to get back up.
He said, I called a therapist I'd seen off and on in California to tell him about it and to say I was having flashbacks.
But the week before, the therapist had also ditched his plane.
Boy, did we have one heck of a therapy session, did he say, which also sounds like a tall tale.
We're like my pilot therapist ditched his plane as well.
Also flies, I guess.
I mean, I guess what else?
Who else are you going to talk to if you're Jimmy Buffett, but a pilot therapist?
Hmm.
Got to understand where I'm going from.
I mean, a like minded individual.
There's got to be a fisherman, a pilot, a shucker or a bootlegger.
Professional conflict.
He was going to lend me out to someone else.
I said, no, let's just have some pilot talk for a while.
I guess I could vibe with a therapist who is made out of coconuts.
Honey, we're having pilot talk here.
Could you stay out of it?
So yeah, so he I don't know.
He just he had a he had a bit of a pirate life, you know, he came to came up against brushes with all sorts of danger.
Wow.
But OK, I look.
Let's get to the let's get to the thing.
I think you're suggesting one was immortalized.
Only one was immortalized.
And this is, of course, in 1996, Jamaican authorities reportedly mistook Buffett's plane, the Hemisphere Dancer, which is the plane at City Walk, Orlando.
That's your answer.
That very plane, the one that we sat in the one.
Yes, absolutely.
At Loon Palm Airport.
They should call it Loon Airplane Airport.
They should do that.
You're right.
There is not a second airplane there.
Yes.
So the Jamaican government mistook this plane for some sort of drug smuggling plane, and they shot at it.
That is it.
Oh, my God.
That is a huge mistake.
It's a huge mistake.
And of course, they're not drug smugglers.
Years later, when Buffett would release the album Banana Wind, he included on that album a track called Jamaican.
Make a Mistake, which, of course, just told the tale.
Not in such clear detail, the tale, I think, but like kind of give you the gist of the tale.
It doesn't include some specifics, I don't think, but it doesn't.
But it gives you the idea of what happened.
You almost got choked up saying that song title, I feel like.
I did get choked up.
I almost feel bad that either of us interrupted because I feel like we should have let you read that like a priest reading the story of the book of Christ.
Low date.
I can add that echo in later.
So, yeah.
So and then in May 1996, the authorities apologized eventually to Jimmy Buffett and his passengers, which included Bono from U2 and his whole family, Bono's whole family.
Now, I don't think this part of it has been discussed before.
Bono we've talked about.
I know that, Michael.
But the family you're saying.
But the family.
Yeah, I don't think I knew about the family either.
I think we have talked about the Bono part of it.
I think we have as well.
Mrs.
Bono and all the little Bono tykes.
Bono and the two Bono tykes.
Yes, we're there.
And this is just to be really clear in case any listeners are not aware of the ongoing mythology.
What happened was you told this story in full during the City Walk Saga with Paul Scheer many years ago.
And it was then that it struck me maybe not a lot of times on the show at that point because the show had been going for very long at that point.
But I realized how many times I have heard this full tale from you over the years.
And now it has grown and you the listener of the ongoing listeners have heard it many a time.
And I just want to can we break that down for a minute?
Of course.
What is it about the tale that gives you such joy, that makes you want to plow ahead and tell this no matter how many times it has been told?
I think what I like about this whole thing the most is that Jimmy Buffett wrote a song called Jamaica Mistake.
Well, that clearly is what it builds.
That's that is like that is the point that is hiding in Wake.
Like that's you know, you because you have a smile that comes when you know you're about to hit it.
Yes, it's a it's a it's an I mean, it's kind of an interesting story.
Certainly famous guys, famous people getting shot at in a plane and then the plane being in a near theme park.
That is fun.
We like that.
I think everybody anyone a person of a certain interest likes that.
But then the cherry on top, you get to say that then Jimmy Buffett wrote a song called Jamaica Mistake,
which is just one of the top song titles of Jimmy Buffett's career.
Well, it's one of those that you've you've really like nurtured and is like part of as you are introducing people to your Buffett fandom.
Yeah, that's a big one that lures people in and math sucks is another one that lures people.
Yes, it's your way of indicating it's your way of indicating to people, you know, that there's silliness afoot here.
And maybe you know, Margaritaville, maybe you know, She's Very In Paradise.
You have no idea how much sillier it gets, especially as he keeps making music through the 80s, 90s and 2000s.
The people don't know quite as much.
Well, and any time someone in Mike's life makes a mistake, he's like, well, that's a pretty bad mistake.
But it's not the worst one I've ever heard.
And then he just rolls into it.
I can't think of one bigger mistake, however.
So, yeah, I have not told this story to a person in a while.
But now that you're saying it's like you're wedding my whistle to tell it again to a person who has never heard it because it's a it's a fun it's fun to tell.
It is fun to say.
Is it fun is the million dollar story.
I think it's more fun, honestly, as far as PTR stories.
Well, I think I tried to do a good job of making that story not fun anymore.
Yes.
Yes, you did a good job.
And we'll see if it ever really weighed down.
Yes, you did.
And we'll we'll see who knows when story who knows when that could come back.
I said million dollars.
I didn't say suitcase.
So, yeah, so so this is a thing that is now I would be interested to know if I've told it 10 times on the show, probably at least.
I'm not sure.
Well, now it just gets alluded to.
And now there's the ongoing thing of the people.
Now, people, listeners go take pictures there and they wonder aloud if there's ever been if there is an interesting story involving this plane.
And this is where we can officially confirm it.
I guess there's a psychology with me, too, where I'm like, what is it?
I don't want to take that away from you, but I do.
I think it's clear at this point.
I have a gene.
There is something that does just get under my skin when I hear a story told in full that I've heard many times before.
Yeah, I'm not sure what that is about me.
I think it comes from my parents.
I think this is a childhood annoyance because they have the stories that are, you know, look, they're nowhere near the Jamaican Mistake story, which is one of the great stories of our time.
But there's the stories that are, you know, are repeated nonstop and there seems to be no awareness that this story has been told.
It's told like probably once a month.
My parents do that.
Yeah, for sure.
I will be I sometimes though I'm struck by like there's other ones and I like these are the famous ones on the show.
But then I think sometimes I think I have told a story three times and it's never registered.
And then sometimes there's stories that I feel like.
Right.
There's certain ones that get flagged.
And I don't know if it's just like you.
You're like we were like Logie on the day where I told the story twice and you don't remember it.
And then a year later I tell it and it doesn't get flagged.
But then there's other ones where I go, oh, I think I maybe have said that once and then that gets flagged.
So it's interesting to know what note what gets flagged and what doesn't.
Well, the word Jamaica Mistake, the phrase Jamaican Mistake is a giant, leaving flag.
It's it's it's massive.
Yeah.
And it's on all your playlists.
So Scott's playlist.
Yeah, Scott, every time you open Spotify, it's like the first thing.
Of course.
Can I say something about the song Jamaica Mistake?
Mm hmm.
I I can't even really ironically listen to it that much.
It's I don't find it good at all.
All right.
Thank you for your honesty.
I wish I could listen to just the part where you make a big mistake.
But honestly, it takes like an hour for him to even finish that.
It's really long.
It's not math.
It's not one of his finest.
Math sucks is like a masterpiece compared to Jamaica Mistake, in my opinion.
You know, when we were at one of the city walk locations for days now,
I've been looking in my Shazam records and my photos, my screenshots.
I swear we heard a Jimmy song that none of us ever had heard before.
And it's like, got to remember that for the show.
And it is just disappeared.
That might have been Nantucket Manfucket.
Yeah, it was Manfucket Manfucket.
I knew he did.
I should give him more credit.
I made that song in 2011.
Jimmy fell off the stage while performing a concert in Australia and he blacked out, but he was OK.
So he fell.
Australia, my tail.
I had too much Hungry Jacks and it just made me too logy.
I forgot.
I thought he broke in his neck, said the doctor.
I heard the clunk of his head on a metal ledge.
Australia, me whale.
It's a promising format.
I want to try to pick all the stories and run them through that filter.
And it could be any accident you've like like like a Diet Coke spill like Diet Coke.
Yeah, broke.
Folks, let's see.
Spirit spirit broke.
Nothing broke.
Yeah, that's OK.
That's not bad.
You could exaggerate the story and say that it shorted out all of our recording equipment.
Yes.
Diet Coke, Mike Soca.
Oh, that's great.
Yes.
There you go.
That's very good.
So, yeah, you can do it big and small things in your life and feel free to do that as you listen to this podcast.
Think about the last like, oh, shit thing that happened and then make a song about it.
But it's got to have those A's.
It's got to have those A's at the end of the words.
That's the that's the little masterstroke.
So, yeah.
Now, there's other like you look up Jimmy Buffett playing stuff and there's just there are random stuff like 2002 singer Buffett flew his biplane into a runway sign at Palm Beach Airport.
Sorry, I forgot this before he flew into a sign, but he was not injured.
So I guess that's not why they're compiling it on that list.
So city on that one.
I think the place is an important part.
West Palm Beach.
Oh, yeah.
Someone's always hitting that sign.
They got a whole warehouse full of them.
Not a big deal.
West Palm Beach sign breach.
Yeah.
So, yeah, anyway, so I think that I think that wraps up some of the big other things other than the thing we're getting to, which is the the hemisphere dancer and the, of course, famous incident where the plane was shot up by the Jamaican government.
Now, I was just going to say, are you going to bring up the details, some of the details of this?
Because I think I have gotten some of the details, perhaps a bit wrong over the years.
OK, OK.
Well, this is good.
You're going to do your suitcase story.
Yes, I'm going to be on your own.
You're going to volunteer it.
I am.
This is what I want is more transparency.
Yes.
On the show.
And speaking of just not to sidetrack, but just something from a couple of days ago in this very saga.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Mike, I can't believe this, but I asked some listeners on Twitter if they've ever had an experience with McDonald's food making them sick.
And despite the hydrolyzation process, this is somehow happened.
Well, I didn't declare that McDonald's would never make anyone sick.
I said that there was a process by which you would make the food digest easier, not making people sick.
I never said no one would ever get sick.
It felt definitive to me.
I don't think it was definitive.
Like, well, you can't.
I believe the phrase you can't get sick was said.
Well, I said I have to check the tapes.
You can check the tapes, but I don't think I've made more definitive statements that have been wrong and more aggressive ways on the show than that.
My mom did remind me that like one time on the way to like a Cub Scout camping trip, it was and I chalked this up to nerves and it was really cold.
I had a Big Mac on the drive.
And when I got there, I was sick.
So I don't want to blame the Big Mac.
Jason, how dare you blame the Big Mac on that?
You don't know that.
I think the cold of a Pennsylvania winter and the nerves, you know, I think your mom is sharing listeners.
Six stories, please.
I don't want them to go by one of those sausage breakfast burritos one time or chicken.
They used to have chicken.
Somebody also said because Jane said she didn't want to have the fries with somebody.
I heard somebody say that it's vegetable oil now.
We're talking.
Yeah, we're going back and forth.
We've been discussing.
We need more research for the fries scenario.
Oh, you're having talks.
You're on tentative talks to return to McDonald's.
We need to shut everything down until we can figure out what's going on.
Oh, that's true.
I don't know.
I you know, your mom, maybe she's not aware of hydrolyzation is all I'm saying.
I because it's I don't know.
I think I think everyone is missing.
You must have been you must have thrown up from being nervous.
Surely it couldn't have been what I'm saying.
The cold and he's saying that he's saying he does a lot of playing the big man.
Now she got wrecked by those menu items that are now defunct.
I see.
That's why they got.
Yeah, because we're still standing up for the hydrolyzation.
Every one of these stories must be if they all go back and think about it, they'll realize they were throwing up from fear.
They must have been being chased or something because it can have been the food they were being chased.
Every one of these people, if you go back and buy a prowler or a burglar.
Oh, that's right.
There was a bear.
Yeah.
Anyway, what I was going to bring up is I think probably another piece of this that fixes it in your mind is the presence of Bono.
Bono seems to be a primary pop cultural interest of yours, and I think you take him out of the equation.
Is it is fun?
I'm not sure.
It's it's not.
He's certainly a nice garnish.
He certainly sprinkles.
He's rainbow sprinkles or chocolate jimmies.
He's he's he's that for sure on the on the story.
But I would argue he's not essential to it, but it makes it interesting that he's there.
And I do like that about the story, too, because what's fun about that is just the idea of like Bono.
You kind of think as a little pompous and a little bit of his own ass.
But oh, he's hanging with Jimmy Buffett in Jamaica.
Like, maybe this guy isn't so uptight, you know, maybe I could party with Bono and we'd have a good time.
You know, like that's what you take away from that is then I could be friends with him.
Yeah, I usually have another extremely rich man.
Yeah, I assess a lot of rocks.
I'm like, could I be friends with someone?
So it's like I didn't think so with Bono.
But then you hear this story and you go, I think we could have hung maybe.
Mike, you had a birthday recently and it was a fun time.
However, it was not a Bono themed party.
And no one made an attempt to try to get Bono to make a surprise appearance at your Bono party.
So you can do all these thought experiments all you want.
But if you aren't starting a social media campaign to see if you can prove it, then what are we doing?
Well, it was a rainy Friday night in Los Angeles.
It was a little brisk.
If Bono was here, I bet he's like firing up the Domino's Pizza Tracker.
You know, he's staying in.
He's putting his little he's putting his feet up.
You're apparently not as well versed in the Domino's Pizza Tracker.
You were using that short Domino's Pizza Tracker short hand for staying inside tonight.
I should have thought ahead.
And as soon as Domino's is said, that means I'm keeping undercover.
I can't make it out tonight.
I'm firing up a stream and what's in my queue?
Let's get my queue down a little, you know, let's get my queue down.
Oh, my queues are out of control.
Bono's gaining to watch bottoms.
The residency is over in the role talking about the residency is over.
OK, of you two.
So now we enter a new and now we get two brief stints by jam bands.
That's right.
Good question.
Well, they're still cleaning up the active crime scenes from the falls.
Let's add like a little more to this story here.
It's Bono, his wife, Allie, the children, Jordan and Eve and Island's Island record producer, Chris Blackwell, also on the plane.
Oh, that's a major music figure.
Yeah.
I've heard his name before.
So he's he's on there as well, which I don't think that we've ever talked about him being on the plane.
OK.
And yeah, so this was and let me find exactly.
And that's interesting, but it's not a Richard kind.
It's one I doesn't need to have not a rich guy from the get go.
I'll say that.
Right.
So, yes, they're all on there.
And I guess the thing that over the years that I think maybe I've incorrectly stated or been confused about is that initially when I think I said this, this told the story, I was saying, well, Jimmy Buffett was not on the plane.
It was his plane.
But these people were shot at.
And then, you know, I'd start to see this story told and it's very much official Buffett lore.
And then it basically sort of insinuates, oh, no, no, Buffett's on the plane or whatever.
He's he's flying the plane or whatever.
And I'm like, well, that feels weird.
And I remember even looking through some message boards years ago and people were arguing about this.
This was for some reason I couldn't find the exact message boards, but I did find other message boards.
You know, Buffett News dot com message boards.
I think there's a Buffett world somewhere where people are.
Jimmy jangle dot net.
Yeah.
So people were sort of discussing some of this.
And I'm like, everything I read basically now just says that Jimmy was on the plane, that Jimmy had been basically like the official language makes it seem like Jimmy was on the plane and he was flying the plane.
What does the plaque say at Lone Palm Airport?
Are they definitive about Jimmy?
That's a good question.
I actually didn't think about that.
I'll try to find that.
Yeah.
You keep you keep going.
Mm hmm.
So I'm looking around and everything and I'm having trouble finding even somebody that says, you know, this isn't the case that this like I'm not even finding an initial source passengers on the plane.
What do you mean?
The other my finding confirmation of that and family and record producer were they on the plane when it was fired upon?
Well, that yeah, that's what every that's everything says that everything is sort of agrees on.
They weren't just waiting to be picked up.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they were.
I think they were taking off is basically what it was.
And then they got shot at or whatever.
So I'm looking around.
I'm looking around.
And then I search, you know, just anything like Buffett, not on plane, not on hemisphere dancer.
And it takes me to Facebook, to Buffett News Facebook group.
And I write somebody posted last year.
I forget who was with Jimmy in the plane going to get chicken in Jamaica and got shot at.
I keep thinking it was a country singer.
And so this this woman responds named Sandy Leslie.
And she says it's Bono's kids.
And then Sandy's associate explains who it was.
Chris Blackwell, a records producer.
And then she says, but also my brother, Randy Leslie, Jimmy's pilot from 1991 to 2006.
They were filming the best 20 bars in the Caribbean.
The seas were too rough that day to film.
Jimmy told some of this is a little poorly written, but Jimmy told our best 20 bars in the Caribbean.
Good question.
Jimmy told my brother to drop them off and to get chicken wings.
And he had to fly the sea plane, the hemisphere dancer to Montego Bay to fuel up the plane.
Randy had let them off the plane and was taking off about 100 when 100 Jamaican police officers came out of the bushes and started shooting guns at the plane.
They thought they were drug runners.
So basically the same story at that point.
So I went, well, who is Randy Leslie?
He is not in any of these paragraphs that I've been finding explaining these incidents.
We have a new Randy to talk about.
Randy Leslie, Jimmy Buffett's pilot, who is now I believe deceased as of 2008.
But Randy, it seems really like Randy Leslie was flying the hemisphere dancer, not Jimmy.
But now sort of there's been a like not that they're like, I don't know.
He seems to be erased from Buffett world.
And this is why I start to think maybe this isn't the best tribute, because now I have even more questions coming out of this, because he was let go by Jimmy a couple of years before he died.
And people are not sure why.
And so but you find if you look up Randy Leslie, you can find that he was on the hemisphere dancer when this incident took place.
So now we have an even more missed.
Now we know, I think definitively what the situation was that Jimmy was on the plane, but he was not flying the plane.
Wow.
Randy Leslie was.
What takes him out of the fold?
Did he propose to Jimmy?
They were discussing the time and he said that there are times where it is not five o'clock somewhere.
It's possible.
Heresy.
Get out of my face.
He said he didn't like.
You're dead to me.
He didn't like shrimp or something.
What?
What the hell?
So so yeah.
So so when you go through some of this, the people are like, what happened to Randy Leslie?
Jimmy Buffett's pilot.
Now, this is also stuff I've heard from people where they're like, Jimmy Buffett actually kind of stopped drinking 20 years ago, but they throw a margarine of like a margarita in his hand for photo ops and stuff to make it seem like the party is still going in that way.
Not that he doesn't have fun, but this is like the theory that Stevie Wonder is not blind.
Right.
I am shocked and appalled.
And I don't have any.
And he's so uptight that he would fire people.
Who was this man?
I don't have any confirmation that that's true.
And there would be still like Instagram where he's got like a glass of wine.
Maybe he still drank wine.
I don't know.
But there's there's all these like sort of like conspiracy theories stuff about Buffett that he wasn't.
Does he believe that all of us in this crazy world are fruitcakes or not?
Well, I think he believes that.
I don't want to believe that.
Let me real quick.
I'll just read a quote from Bono about the incident.
He said these boys, I assume he means the Jamaican government.
These boys were shooting all over the place.
They felt as if we were in the middle of a James Bond movie.
Only this was real.
It was absolutely terrifying.
And I honestly thought we were going to die.
So sounds scary.
So about this story also that we've never picked apart is like what's going on with this Jamaican government where they just like, is that it?
Yeah, pretty sure.
Big, big, big, big, big, big, big, big.
Well, yeah, that is also and I couldn't find anyone like sort of debunking the series of events where you're like, yeah, why did they just start shooting at the point?
Like if it's taking you off, it would eventually get the airspace, which probably wouldn't be their problem.
Yeah.
And then it's like they're only a few bullet holes in the plane.
You can still see.
But like I was going to say, can you see them at the lone Palm air?
I believe you can.
OK, but I think they've been like because they he still flew the plane.
So I think they fixed up the plane.
It was decommissioned in 2003, so I don't think they were leaving a bunch of holes in it while he was still flying.
Has there ever been a situation?
Have any of these people then ended up any of these Jamaican government people ended up on vacation at City Walk and they go, oh, my God, there it is, the plane.
And then they take out their personal rifle and start firing.
I knew it.
And they just thought of habit.
Yeah, it's going to smuggle some drugs out of City Walk Orlando.
Yeah.
Where do they pose with the plane?
Like, oops, I'm sorry.
You got to own your mistake.
Because what can I say?
It's there's got to be somebody who is involved with that that sees the plane and is like, oh, wow.
Was it the is that maybe it's a different plane I shot it.
Yeah.
I mean, that's I was going to say, because these people might the like going policy in Jamaica might be if you don't exactly know where the plane came from.
Just start firing at it.
This is just like this is a regular.
Just this is a regular afternoon for them.
Fifty fifty.
It's a sea plane.
It's fifty fifty chance.
Mm hmm.
Better just just be safe.
Just start firing.
Yeah, I will say, though, that luckily like so.
So the whole thing with the story is then the Jamaican government like says like they apologize formally.
I think there's a newspaper headline.
They're apologizing to Bono and Jimmy Buffett and everything.
As far as their relationship with the Jamaican government went, Jimmy Buffett has restaurants in Jamaica now.
Don't worry.
That's how good the relationship is at this point.
Would you accept the phrase I land to make Amanda?
That's that I mean the term for the apology part of the story.
I think so.
I accept your regret or something like.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah.
So so yeah.
So so this place now.
So this is a I'm trying to think of as like a more famous story of Jimmy Buffett's either like or a different even let's think about like an analogous for a different rock star like their defining story with and then having a piece of memorabilia or an artifact from that story sitting at City Walk.
Obviously, you know, hard rock, which, you know, has stuff like that.
But this plane, this has got to be the most the biggest like Jimmy Buffett is Mr.
Tall Tales.
He likes spinning a web or whatever.
But this did happen.
And it's the biggest artifact.
It's the biggest thing you could ever plant somewhere.
The biggest story he has.
Yeah.
My thought is if you went to Chuck Berry's restaurant and he had the toilets that he installed the cameras over.
These are my special toilet friends.
So yeah, I'm bouncing all over here, but let me go here.
So so Randy Leslie, real quick, Jimmy Buffett's pilot.
There's just some some mysterious stories.
They retired him.
There's a story here about Randy being retired, which of course, when they say that, it means sounds like they're killing him.
It sounds like they're drowning him with cement shoes.
But Randy said to me and I don't know if we get the whoever is writing this.
They're retiring me.
He didn't seem to know why.
Oh, a contract pilot, John Norcus said this, of course.
Another character is answered who also worked for Buffett.
He was disappointed that Jimmy didn't talk to him about it.
It was handled by an underling.
So Jimmy had like one of his worker guys fire Randy here.
Paul Beecher, Jimmy Buffett is accused by several friends of his longtime pilot and party accomplice, Randy Leslie, of turning a blind eye to Leslie's ouster after 60 or 15 years.
So Leslie entered Margarita Velour when the Buffett sea plane he was piloting was fired on by Jamaican police who mistook Leslie and his boss for drug runners.
So this place on Buffett world dot com does when you dig in and you have to look for article on Buffett's former pilot does indicate that Randy Leslie was on this plane and Jimmy's former party accomplice, which is very interesting, too.
Yeah, that's an interesting.
I don't know that specific phrase.
What a phrase.
Yeah, it just implies that you're getting away with something.
Yes, it is no mere, you know, these aren't just people sitting around having a chat.
Right.
You were partying like you've never partied.
You guys have secrets.
You guys share some bad secrets.
Maybe that's what had to happen.
I had to retire you, buddy.
Give him a go watch.
Kick him on the butt.
Say goodbye.
30 years.
Keep your mouth shut.
I think Jimmy, when this gentleman passed away, Jimmy took care of the he did.
He did the nice good stuff for the kids and stuff.
So he still eventually.
But it felt like this, like his old party buddy got booted by like a like middle level manager of Margaritaville.
And by doing good stuff for the kids, you mean he he bred a talking shrimp wearing sunglasses for each of them to own.
Yeah, yeah, for sure.
From his lab, the Buffett Labs, which still is not public.
But, you know, we know about it.
Yeah.
So, yeah, I think that like when we're talking about I do think there should be like more of this story sort of told at the Orlando City Walk.
I kind of think they need to force it a little bit more on you.
I don't want it to ruin the vibe that you're learning a history lesson.
But I don't know if it's is it animatronics?
Sure.
Is it by the plane?
Well, they're right.
I feel like there's bushes there and it's across that walkway.
And so often it's like that show at the mall in Vegas, the whatever the fall of Rome thing.
If some animatronics pop out and like, hey, what is that plane?
Drug runners.
Get them.
Bang, bang, bang.
Whoa, what's happening?
Seems like a mistake in progress.
Yeah, I mean, I'm I'm for anything.
Anything like that is fine.
I would just like a little box where you hit the button and it goes in 1996, Jimmy Buffett and Bono and his family were all like,
you can even give me that like low five version of it.
I just think that the people there, I guess I said there's no criticism, but I guess the only criticism is just that I don't think people are chilling out there knowing what they're basking in the glow of.
Yeah, yeah.
It's like you would want to know that.
I think you would want to know you're in a part of American rock and roll music history.
So your complaint is there is a plaque and the plaque does not go far enough.
Yeah, it doesn't fully illustrate it like two or three plaques.
OK, that's better.
I agree.
That's mirrored.
So sun hits them, shines a light, draws your eye to it, burns your eyes while you look at it.
I mean, I was going to say one of the plaques could just be explaining how sea planes work.
And then you a plaque about how Jimmy came to buy this one and when he liked about it.
And then the third plaque is about the.
Go on.
Just a little more background, you know, about the general notion of sea planes and what their relationship to them.
It's an H.
U.
16 C albatross.
Grumman, is that the name of the plane?
Grumman, Grumman, Grumman, Grumman.
I think it's Grumman.
They do the movie theaters and they do the sea planes.
Yeah, I can give you the manufac.
It was manufactured in 1955.
OK, so it's like an old plane, too.
I wouldn't think that an old plane like that, you want to keep flying it into the 1990s.
So he was asking for trouble anyway.
Yeah, would you?
Well, I mean, only like Leno and some of the other people that drive old cars around Burbank are doing stuff like that.
I guess they're souping them up.
They're fixing them and making sure they run.
But still, that's old technology.
So Jimmy Buffett's Sea Plane Garage is a show that really should have happened.
It was sitting there and he left money on the table.
I agree.
This was a Navy ship as well.
OK, this was decommissioned.
And so so I guess at one point it was probably top of the line.
They drop it, drop nukes out of it, right?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
This flew over Japan.
That's the part they leave out.
They do leave that out.
Yeah, I bought it.
It was a little just factoid on the sales sheet.
Drop fat man and little boy.
Yeah, he doesn't.
He didn't have a song about that either.
I also just just as far as current events are concerned,
Boeing has had its about sixth problem with a plane in the last two weeks.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of stuff happening.
This and this strange, mysterious death of the whistleblower.
I mean, who knows what happened there?
There's really it's impossible to figure out what happened accidentally to whistle.
If in case you don't know what we're talking about,
there was a guy who is whistleblowing who used to work at Boeing who has testified a little bit against them
and said like they've whether they had there was a merger.
And because of all this, they've cut costs and planes are falling apart.
And there's about literally six incidents in two weeks or something where like shit is falling off of planes
and like planes are just dropping from like altitudes aggressively.
And then this guy was set to testify against them.
And then he's dead.
He died mysteriously.
So mysterious.
All of a sudden.
It's really mysterious.
I also can we think of you talk and then are you spill?
We kill.
Yeah.
OK, there you go.
Well, he was he was going to talk about the not very publicly known story.
Boeing, no wing.
Wings fell off.
Things fell off of it.
None of the stories are as fun as this one.
I don't know about his family, but I don't think they would have said Bono was on one of the planes.
So you're not going to be telling these stories, right?
It's not it's not OK.
I guess we can eliminate that.
Mike, you don't just like telling stories of aerial mishaps.
You aren't gleefully at parties telling stories about the Alaskan airplane where the door fell off.
No, no, no, I didn't.
I don't tell that story.
I tell that story a lot, but I don't have a joy.
There's no smile on my face.
Yeah, they found an iPhone like miles away.
It survived.
Oh, is that true?
That is true.
Yeah, they did find a guy's iPhone.
So somebody's phone got sucked out.
Oh, wow.
OK.
And then he got returned.
I think they returned it to him.
I would hope.
But that's interesting.
So that that actually that that speaks to the durability of the iPhone.
At least I think was in a case.
So so you may be the case did the lift.
The case breaks the fall even from thousands of feet in the air.
Wow.
Get yourself a case.
We need to find out what case that is.
Wow.
Alaska door blasta anyway.
Trying to pick up speed on these.
Yes, please play at home listeners.
And yeah, that testimony will be whistleblower.
No show up.
Not showing up.
Got some of his testimony out.
Didn't get it all out.
Epstein, suicide, not alive.
I don't know.
That's not good.
So, yeah, so so this also this this this story, I think, is it's
a Buffett's book, A Pirate Looks at Fifty.
He writes about this story.
And then that kind of seems like people say that's when all of a sudden now it's on clothing.
It's on merchandise.
It's on the men like that's sort of when it becomes like a big part of sort of the Buffett lore when the phrase Jamaica Mistake leaves or the story and the sea or you say the seaplane.
Well, the seas.
Yeah, just the iconography of the seaplane itself, because we of course, this story, I've told this before, but this might only be the first or the second time, excuse me, when we were at the Margaritaville Resort or the living Margarita Village in Orlando.
And there was a gift shop in the part of the hotel area.
Oh, yes.
You remember this.
Remember you recall that there was a shirt.
There was a shirt.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then there was a woman who worked there, though, who immediately once I seem to know anything, she was very excited.
And she actually did seem to be steeped in the knowledge of it.
But we don't have to finish.
We don't have to.
Margarita Rapida.
Yeah, that's very good.
Yeah.
So, yeah, so I think that's that's sort of yeah, he puts that out there.
And then he tells he he tells a version of the story.
And now it is just as iconic as the Eddie Van Halen guitar that used to be immortalized in a giant way at the hard rock up here or something.
It's the seaplane.
That's his seaplane.
And because of the story and because it's just you can't escape it now.
And I think when the AI takes over and whoever is running his estate in the next 50 years, I think it's only going to grow.
It's going to be little toys of him in the plane.
And like you'll see like you'll see this everywhere is what I'm saying.
They're now going to start making little toys of the plane.
Well, I think they'll continue to make merchandise of it is what I guess really all I'm saying is that this is a big part of it.
And I'm I'm part of this unpaid PR campaign to get the plane out there more somehow.
Well, you certainly popularized it within people who listen to this show.
Yeah, I think a lot of people passed by that plane and didn't know a thing about it.
And now this is one of those things that we've talked about this before.
But this for sure is one of there's so many people listening who have forced people to hear that story who were maybe interested or maybe not interested.
But you have you this is a disease that you have spread maybe very clearly.
And I think that's a gift to that outside bar to see it.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, yes.
And now with this episode, I think it's a nice tidy.
That's not tidy, but it's a nice explanation of some of the details that may have been lost in my telling of the story over the years.
And I want you to drag that loved one back out there and say, did you know that Randy Leslie was flying this plane?
You can add now details to the story.
And I think that's a gift that you're welcome.
It's like you think the story can't get crazier.
And then you learn that Randy Leslie is part of it.
Yep.
Then you learn that Randy Leslie.
This whole thing is flipped the story just like a sea plane, sea plane flipping.
That's right.
And we're talking about the Universal Orlando Resort.
I want to know now, does the second sea plane, the sea plane parked by the Royal Pacific Hotel, does that have a story?
Is that just a prop?
Is it not actually a plane?
Oh, interesting.
Well, it's not Jim Buffett related, but you don't know about that.
That was Joe Walsh was flying it.
And James Dolan was on the plane with Joe Walsh.
Bob Geldof.
Bob Geldof was there.
A cannon like a pirate ship cannon.
Yeah, they sold some vintage cannons.
Turks and Gaicos, so big yikes.
So anyway, I don't know.
That's really that's it.
As far as that.
And I don't.
Yeah, this honestly, this doesn't feel like the tribute to Buffett that should be.
So I'm going to have to kick that down the road.
Still more.
More.
I'm just going to have to kick that down the road.
Like when Jimmy playing, kicking the can.
What do you want to be in the episode that we haven't covered by now?
We haven't finished the books.
Well, the problem was, yeah, well, the books.
That's the whole situation with the books.
Tully Mars.
We said, yeah, yeah.
I think that we haven't dug into the catalog of music completely, obviously.
And I think that we have.
What?
There's a lot of outings.
Scott agreed for a half second.
No, it's just because I was.
He was busy typing.
I know I was well, I was trying to.
No, I'm not saying you were distracted.
I would know.
I was distracted.
I was busy figuring out Tully Mars.
Scott gets in his car.
We have one, Mike.
What haven't we?
What is left?
I understand the books, maybe the books.
Sure.
Well, thank you.
Scott agrees with the books.
Yeah.
Escape from a scrape to Margaritaville.
We've yet to do a full episode on.
And there's still the man made a lot of music in his life.
There's this big tribute concert coming soon.
Oh, yeah.
What's your deal with that?
Because that went on sale recently.
It's just like it was when I got into the queue to buy tickets,
it said your number 18,351 or something.
Oh, my god.
It gave you a number?
It gave me a number.
That sucks.
And I was like, yeah.
And I did the math of how long that would take.
And it was not fast.
So I think everything is mostly resale right now.
But you know.
Now for any listeners who might not know about the big tribute
concert, what's happening in the tribute?
Is it the Hollywood Bowl?
Hollywood Bowl, Pit Bowl, Paul McCartney.
Oh, this is Mike's dream.
The Eagles.
Oh, my god.
The Coral Reefer Band, of course.
I think Sheryl Crow is there.
If does it have the word tribute in it, then yes, Sheryl Crow is there.
Sheryl Crow will be there.
And I forget there's some others other people too.
But McCartney's ex Pit Bowl is really what I.
I'm not going to perform together, but still the idea of them on the same show with the Hollywood Bowl.
Oh, you're the ex like a collaboration.
Yeah, that's what I'm sorry.
I said Paul McCartney's ex Pit Bowl and I'm like, what did I miss?
That would be.
I have not been reading People magazine.
That would be an interesting story too.
Like this plain story if they were.
Yeah.
But no, that's not the case.
It doesn't say Pit Bowl and John Travolta.
Yeah, I don't know that he's not there, but just it doesn't say it is all I'm saying.
But yes, this collection of artists paying tribute to Buffett at the Hollywood Bowl.
It seems like a great night.
We had a.
You just so you you brought it up before we started recording.
And I said, oh, you said, well, the ticket line is too long.
I think it's sold out immediately.
And I was like, oh, well, sorry, you can't go.
And you said, no, just means I got to work harder.
Well, that's true.
Yeah.
What here?
This is the end of this episode is not the time for me to get into this long explanation.
But the ticket, everything buying tickets sucks so bad now.
Everything is dynamic pricing.
Everything is an algorithm to design designed to make everybody spend the most money possible from fast food,
from Wendy's to other different fast food that are like changes the price, depending on the time of day.
That said, unrelatedly, do you want to remind people we do have a five dollar and eight dollar tier on the Patreon?
A lot of great bonus content on there.
And it's not dynamic pricing.
No, we don't.
We don't change.
Wendy's has disowned the dynamic price.
Yeah, they just didn't like getting.
But there's other but other fast food places apparently have already done it and did it quietly.
So I think Wendy's was like, oh, no, we weren't doing that or whatever.
But I mean, the ads make it so.
Yes, mysterious.
Right.
But take a tangent to Scott's spent.
But tickets, it sucks to buy tickets now because of this.
And but but what I'll say is that as the concert approaches, you got to check.
And they put like face value tickets back in as concert approaches, as stages are assembled, as comps are given out.
That's the time when Michael strikes is as the the eve of concert concert day.
I see.
So you like a checker.
This work I could I could bring the first one I didn't like.
I'm sorry.
Everything else was good.
Got a rhyme.
I get tired.
Yeah, I know.
It's been yeah.
Yeah.
So anyway, so yeah, I'm not saying I'm not.
Don't count me out for partying with Pitbull and Paul to celebrate and Bono and Bono, who you will become great friends with because he knows he knew Jimmy.
I'm not saying we could.
I'm not saying we will.
I'm saying we could if the scenario is correct, because it just indicates that he's a chiller guy than I think.
Mm hmm.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah.
Do you do you consider yourself a chill guy?
I would say that if I got a good laugh out of Jason on that, I would say, thanks, brother.
Well, I would say I don't mean to throw my money out at Jason like that last city walk episode where he laughed.
I would say that I am half I'm half chill.
You can be you can be.
We had plenty of chill moments during this.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I think I think I'm deceptively neurotic.
I think that anxiety and neuroses, I think it's deceptive because there's plenty of times when I'm very, very even keel and calm.
Mm hmm.
But what lies beneath?
That's the question.
And then what comes up from the surface sometimes?
Yeah.
So it's and what lies awake for hours at night reading about microplastics and new strains of covid.
And 100 toward toy deals, you need to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's feeding.
It's feeding something.
It's feeding some beast.
It's a feed of beast, the beast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feast feastabenzied.
Yeah.
So so no, I would I would be on my best chill behavior with Bono.
I'm not giving him the you'd say I'm cool.
I'm chill.
Yeah.
I would let him know.
That's the only way you let somebody know if you're cool and chill.
And I and I'm and I'm young and with it.
And I listen to music that isn't by you.
Yeah.
That's not to say I love your music, but I'm just letting you know I also like young people's music.
One of the things that makes me chill.
Yeah.
So that will be you go down fine.
It would be fine.
So anyway, this is this is just, you know, to be continued is really all I'm trying to say.
To be continued to be here's what I want to say to be continued in the short term and to be continued in the long term.
That's all I'm going to say.
The battle continues.
Well, in the short term, done, done, done, done.
In the short term.
Oh, my God.
The sector stone there it is is appearing.
Wow.
This it is.
I mean, I feel like Mike has to see the sector stone.
Yeah.
Being this a big area of Mike's interest.
It's a it's a bronze tier of Randy Leslie, Jimmy Buffett's former pilot and party accomplice.
So they took one of his tier, a tier from his eye.
They took the actual tier from his eye and they bronzed it.
And now it's just a teardrop.
And that's what our sector stone is for this.
Immortalizing the sadness for being quietly replaced in the Buffett organization.
So that's just what it is.
I wish it wasn't.
But that's on a Randy Monsa.
Randy Monsa.
All right.
Great.
Well, that did it.
You survived podcast, the Red City Walker, Orlando Saga Multiverse of Menace, full analysis of Hemisphere Dancer Edition.
Before we wrap up, we need to check in with the sector keeper and figure out what we're doing tomorrow.
Let's see if we can summon him.
Hello, boys, boys.
Hey, all right.
Well, this phase, the age of Buffett is proceeding pretty nicely.
And I think I have some idea of where we might be going.
So I guess tomorrow we'll maybe go review like the restaurant.
And that'll be that right.
You mean restaurants?
Oh, because it's one of those.
It's the there's multiple.
Alpha and Omega.
Right.
We're hanging loose in the age of Buffett, baby.
Oh, I see.
Taking our time.
Five o'clock somewhere.
All right.
Well, what is this then?
So what happens tomorrow?
Two places because the Hemisphere Dancer is a cosmic nook, boys.
Oh, you told us about those.
That's right.
Just as it took Bono on an unforgettable adventure, it too can take you to a special dual jump point.
Whoa.
Wait, a jump point to two places at once?
That's possible.
That's right, boys.
Climb inside the Hemisphere Dancer for your crucial double mission.
Tomorrow, you must review both Margaritaville Alpha and Margaritaville Omega.
OK, so the Orlando one and the Hollywood.
OK, well, we're reversing that.
We've now done that.
We did that with NBC Sports Group.
OK, so tomorrow's episode will be.
Tomorrow's episodes.
What's that now?
No, no, no, no.
Separate episodes.
Alpha and Omega are separate episodes.
Oh, we have to have a separate episode for each.
That's right.
OK, and then one will come out one day and then the next one will come out the next day.
Same day.
We're living in the age of bumping.
Oh, age of bumping.
The rules are different.
When he says it's five o'clock somewhere, he means it's five o'clock in two episodes.
Oh my God.
OK, so tomorrow or whenever at midnight when they come out, we have to have two separate episodes.
One about Margaritaville Orlando and the other about.
We can't combine these.
That's right.
Heavy is the parrot head.
Hat that wears the crown or head.
That wears the crown.
Whatever it is, we'll figure it out tomorrow.
OK, well, you know what?
That's all right, because there's so many, you know, like fun menu options at this place.
We'll have time to talk about all of it.
We try everything on the menu.
Boys, if anything, we have to be consistent.
We know that at this point, same meal, no alterations.
So we have to order the same meal on each coast and review it in separate episodes.
Yes.
Oh, OK.
We have to order the exact same meal, a entire nation apart.
You're learning, boys.
You're learning.
Well, learning that whatever is the most complicated version is what we'll always do.
OK, so tomorrow.
Sorry.
All right.
So tomorrow, listeners, refresh your feed for two episodes.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm also seeing on the dossier you've just given us that one of the episodes will be on the Patreon behind the paywall.
Well, if you were having trouble keeping up already, good luck now.
Heck yeah.
Good luck, boys.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever Dog team and liking our page on Facebook.