When your town has made you frown, When your swear has made you swear,
When life gives you one more punch, You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge,
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol, A place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks, A place where you can tattoo your lower back,
So let's go take a walk, let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight, tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness, a daily,
extremely necessary series, exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder that make up
Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the City Walk Orlando Saga,
Multiverse of Madness, day something.
I couldn't begin to tell you, I have no clue at this point.
It would be nice if we had, the SectorCuper, excuse me, had named everything just sort of one through
2019, because I think actually I would be better in my head and I understand what day it was,
but I don't know what day it is.
There was sort of a clarity to just a count, but now with phases
we're all over the map.
It's his fault, it's not our fault for doing this.
No, he mapped it out.
If you have a
problem with this, you take it up with the SectorCuper, as we might.
I mean look, you know,
tensions have been high and I don't, you know, actually we're, he's kind of not in
sight currently, because last that you heard from us yesterday, we narrowly escaped the land of
Neverbilts and Fallen Brothers.
Barely, I was surprised how much I enjoyed the company of the
SectorCuper.
Yeah, he was cool.
Yeah, yeah.
So, you know, we dug him.
SectorCuper gave us this
confusing map and numerical system.
Maybe we don't get along with him the next time we see him.
I
don't know how it's going to be.
You know, as soon as we did that, I went home and found out
that all those Moldarama machines I spoke so lovingly about have now appeared in the land of
Fallen Brothers.
They all got removed.
Is that true?
Yes.
Whoa.
They're not, wait, the Orlando one?
The ones that you touted using yesterday, where you made the little clock.
No way.
Hopefully they're being,
you know, refurbished and put back, but no guarantees.
What are the chances of that though?
No guarantees.
It doesn't sound right.
But maybe, I mean,
you think like maybe the guy, like the guy who fixes all the machines went around and rounded
them up and he's taking them back to his workshop to get them just right.
Like was the Grinch,
that the Grinch would say that?
It's hard to say.
Like all the Chicago ones are an entity and then
Universal had some, but they were serviced by someone else.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a whole thing.
So
there was probably like a Cindy Lou who, who was like, Mr.
Where are you taking all the Moldarama
machines?
And he's like, I'm taking them to my workshop.
Yes.
Yeah.
Fix them up really nicely.
So for all we know, like an Anvil falling on a looney tune, the sector creeper was just down there
blasting his stogies and a bunch of Moldarama machines appeared on his head.
Probably.
He was
narrowly avoided.
I'm not sure if he made it.
What with all of the fuel rod kiosks
shooting up in his direction.
I don't know.
It doesn't bode well.
The rules of his world were
big bulky items could crush him and kill him at any time.
I wouldn't want to be him, but I did
like hanging out with him.
I also almost feel a little bit, by the way, I'm Scott Garner.
There's
my name is Mike Carlson.
I don't know how much we need.
If you're here now, you know.
So we just
started with this episode.
Someone first.
They always say, you know, you make your, this could
be anyone's first podcast.
So make it very accessible.
And we've done the opposite with all
of these.
I think, I think is that besides this, the series, I think the regular episodes have
been inaccessible.
Yeah.
For some time, at least half a decade, we are just, we're just digging
deeper and deep burrowing into the core of the earth.
That's right.
As we will a little more,
because if you didn't listen to fallen brothers and never built, I, there's actually a little bit
more.
I caught a few as we were running for our lives out of there.
I saw a few, and I don't know
if you clocked these, but these are late breaking.
I didn't see them in time to mention them in that
episode, not fallen brothers, but never built.
And I feel like we have to say, I'm, cause they're all
kind of crazy.
I don't know how far any of these got off the ground, but you know, at least proposed
or even maybe like on a survey of like, would the people like to do this in city walk Orlando,
right?
A German beer hall, which would have been in the space of that legacy store that you liked
with the mold orama, uh, didn't happen.
A robot cabaret show, a la that one in Tokyo that everybody's
trying to push into robot kind of like the, yeah, yeah, I think so.
Yeah.
But it seemed kind
of like annoying or touristy or so.
I didn't realize there was a reservation because we tried
to go there, but there are like this reservation.
So we didn't get to do it like months and months
out or something.
Okay.
Well, uh, might've been the same there.
I don't know.
Or a different rope.
I I'm not sure the deal.
Uh, uh, some regional food stuffs, EMAC and bolios ice cream.
I think
it was very close to coming in.
Well, now EMAC and bolios, uh, is in the hard rock hotel.
Uh,
that is the ice cream parlor from Boston that got popular with rock acts cause it would stay open
late.
That is the one that is this is their, that's their mythology.
That's their lore,
which I'm sure we're going to hit a lot today.
They almost called this place the hard rock act
cafe.
And then they cleaned it up a little bit.
So EMAC and bolios was the place that I was trying
to find in area 15 cause in Vegas, cause it was, it was there the first year or two and then it
was gone.
So by the time I got there, it was like a repeat of little me asking about Marvel
media.
Just every Vegas worker was like, nah, I don't know what you're talking about, man.
She's searching for answers.
They aren't, they aren't all as informed as you.
They can provide
you no help.
It's still pretty good.
I went there at the hard rock hotel when we were down.
What
flavor ice cream flavor?
I think I had like one of those like cookie monster flavors where they
cookie dough and cookies and green.
Any colors in there?
No, this one was not colored.
I know
that's often blue.
I like when it's blue.
It's a little less fun when it's full of food color.
But it's very rich ice cream.
Okay.
That's what I saw on a list of never built for city walk,
but maybe I guess if you're all right, if it's at the heart, maybe that was always the intended plan.
Well, it was very, it had a lot of, it's now a totally white like minimalist space because it's
also the quick service and the general store and the ice cream counter like next to the
restaurant.
What would the vibe be if it's not that what's a really mac and bolos in Boston?
Aesthetically very similar to Ben and Jerry's another New England ice cream.
Okay.
Like a
little hippie dippy, you know, did they steal it?
Did one steal the idea from the other?
I don't know.
I've always been wondering that I've poked around a little, but I don't think I saw
any like blood feud, any Crips versus Bloods for you, mac and polio.
So that and Jerry's,
the idea of two names in a psychedelic ice cream place.
So it's like a grateful, when you say rock
people, it's grateful dead rockers, maybe not, uh, you know, CBG be rockers.
Well, uh, no, don't you
mean you just mean you mean bands now, no touring bands in like the seventies or whatever.
Yeah.
Everything closed at nine or whatever.
Okay.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know either.
I don't think
it'd be CBG beast type bands.
It was Billy.
It was Billy Idol ever in there.
I'm just trying to
think, was it like leather jacket rock guys or was it more Jerry Garcia rock guys?
That's good
question.
Yeah.
Cause I will, or maybe the aesthetic had nothing to do with it.
It was just literally
was open late and they already had like a hippie aesthetic.
That may be what it is.
Yeah.
Sounds
like that might be more likely.
Sure.
Google EMAC and polio rock acts.
We'll find out rock acts.
Oh, well here's on their website as a picture of Steve and Zant there.
So there you go.
Do you
qualify him more as a Billy Idol or is more of a Jerry Garcia, the two types of rocker.
Good question.
What a good question.
How to even define cause little Steven on his own is much more with his
disciples of soul is much more rock and roll of the fifties and sixties, but with Bruce in some
own genre, but I guess it would fall also in line with like a meatloaf too, very like theatrical.
So it's really tough.
I gotta work this out.
I can work it out more.
If you want on the
podcast.
That's an option or we could keep saying other things.
We keep saying words of any other
kind.
I want to know the unbuilt.
Yes.
Well, thank God.
I would, of course we would.
I know
normally everyone likes to hear it, but today we have business.
Could have been an in and out there
that was vaguely discussed, but also, but that's, that'd be the furthest east in and out,
at least at the time by long shot.
Um, but here's really the big one.
And this, I think they, I think
they made major steps in this direction.
And I don't know where this would have been.
Um, but,
this was definitely floated fairly publicly strong rumor of something called the SNL lounge.
Of course, with NBC universal ownership, it makes all the sense in the world.
They would try to
parlay the most popular brand and late night comedy to a physical space where, uh, tourists could, uh,
dine amongst props from the, uh, at the time of this article, 42 year history of the show.
Uh, what could have been, that would have been amazing to have, uh, awful wings next to mango
shorts.
Well, would they serve like a bill braskie size cocktails perhaps, or at least I guess maybe they
couldn't just like, cause bill brask, if you don't know, was a sketch where guys would say, uh,
they were at a funeral probably, or at a baseball game talking about a guy loud drunk business,
and they would have giant glasses of whiskey.
Really huge.
Um, I don't know if I had to guess,
I think that probably the premise would have been a restaurant that's like all the other restaurants,
except there's a cone head around.
Okay.
Yeah.
There'd be like one outfit maybe.
I think so.
Yeah.
Like the one, you know, there's, yeah, there, yeah.
Well, you gotta have, you have to,
you have to have some bees because then if diners are like, this is a new establishment,
am I going to be enjoying it here?
They walk in, they see a beer or two and they're laughing,
they're laughing their asses off at the bees.
And then, uh, they feel comfortable to have a meal.
Well, you know, what would have been some of their signature entrees?
What, what do you think?
Cheap burger, cheep burger.
Another one.
50 year old sketch.
Funny, funny stuff.
Pepsi.
They would have gotten in trouble because maybe they would have been a Coke restaurant.
Coke is
universal.
Pepsi.
They got the freestyle machines.
They would have, they couldn't have said Pepsi,
Pepsi.
If they didn't line up with, you know, I like the idea they would stick just to the first
five years.
Maybe that's the premise.
But you'd only be able to possibly that is a lot of,
there's a lot of things out there that are like, you know, we've been laughing for,
and then it's Mr.
Bill and the, um, you know, the nerds, um, the, is that what the name of them were
and the samurai?
I'm sure.
I bet if you revisited the samurai, everything would be hunky dory with
samurai.
It's the stuff I like.
I think I like is like the acroid Irwin mainway stuff.
Most resembles what comedy is today.
It most resembles a sketch with a premise,
with performances in it and not just a bunch of like weird druggy posturing.
I was going to say the host is the host or hostess should be the two blues brothers and they dance
your seat.
But if they want to do a front, a throwback, you can be seated by like a Chevy
chase, Gerald Ford, and they could fall their way to you.
You want waiters, you want to throw back
to three years before the early stuff.
And you have to request that.
Can I have you go up to the
stand and you go, can I have a waiter that's doing the Gerald Ford, Gerald Ford, if anybody's there
is willing to take the bump.
I got an acroid Jimmy Carter, Jerry Gerald for calling sick.
Yeah, it's kind of nondescript, kind of a weird and it's he's got the skin color painted over the
mustache.
I was going to say that was one where he didn't shave his mustache.
He did the Caesar
Romero for yeah.
This is this sucks.
This really I wish was there.
Yeah, yeah, I really do.
I don't
comedy oriented restaurant.
Well, they have the closest thing they have is those
it's sugar things in Hollywood that's that are the SNL products.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Schwedie balls and I don't know.
It feels to me like this might have been a vaguely humiliating
idea for anyone involved in the comedy.
I think that's true.
In the menu items.
Here's the thing
though.
This is not off the table.
Could still have as long as this show is on the air, which
don't think there's any chance of it going off the air anytime soon.
I think this is still possible.
Yeah, I'm surprised something like it hasn't happened.
Yeah, I know.
Really?
In New York or
yeah, it feels like it's been sitting there.
It's been sitting there for something much
cheesier to happen with.
Yeah, then it's just I mean, you take the NBC bar and grill, take the
name off the front, call it the SNL Cafe and throw Matt Foley's outfit in a glass case.
And who's
really going to even notice, like you don't even change the sports like art on the wall.
No one
gives a shit.
Sure.
You know, if you order like wings or corn on the cob, they could give you like,
you know, the Kristen Wiig, Lawrence Welk, Andrews Sisters bit.
She's got the little hands that give
you a set of little hands.
So your hands don't get messy when you're eating corn or wings.
Uh huh.
That's as recent as we're getting though.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm fine with that.
Yeah,
you're getting two nods to post 2005.
Right.
You're not getting Bill Braske.
People don't,
the average theme park goer probably doesn't really have so much affection for Bill Braske.
Yeah, I don't think I don't think a whole wing of the restaurant will be devoted to writing my
donkey political talk show.
This is where my taste lies in the show.
The Patrick Stewart erotic cake
sketch.
I don't think it's gonna.
If they served them, if they made every cake that which is the
it was always women going to the bathroom.
Correct.
Patrick Stewart was working in an erotic bakery
that only sold cakes in the shape of women going to the bathroom.
And he couldn't understand
anything but that being erotic when anybody had any other pitch.
Right.
Of a cake.
That's the only
his, his narrow view of erotic is only that.
Okay.
Yeah.
I will.
The only way that I approve of the
SNL land is if they offer a full array of Patrick Stewart described cakes.
Uh huh.
That's good.
All
right.
Okay.
Well then then I'm in on that.
That that closes out never built.
But listeners,
if you somehow know more, what am I saying?
No, don't tell us.
We don't want to do more of these.
What are we talking about?
What am I tying us into?
Don't tell us anything.
I, when this is over,
I don't want to know any more information about city walk Orlando ever.
Yeah.
Okay.
Back to sanity.
Anyway, uh, that said, why don't we go to the sector keeper and find out what it is we're,
doing today.
Boys, boys phase four sector one is hard rock cafe and hard rock live.
Good luck getting down boys.
Boy, I can't miss the creeper right now.
How much lemur is his voice
sound these days?
He does.
Yeah.
I mean, he doesn't have that cool edge.
I like a cool guy with
a cool voice and that is what the sector creeper was like.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
That that
fry.
Yeah.
Oh God.
Well, I don't think we don't make the rules of this.
I don't think
we're allowed to replace a good sector to bring up the unbuilt SNL cafe.
Cause I feel like that's a
great example where like the popular consciousness idea of SNL and the way that they occasionally
market it for like, yeah, novelty cereals or like Halloween costumes.
They'll do like real,
sometimes there will be, yeah, they'll really, they really will sell this Spartan cheerleaders.
That'd be so much Spartan cheerleader presence.
Yes.
Just like nobody thinking about those
in decades.
For a long time.
It will be all cheerleader stuff.
But that is hard rock cafe
occasionally, very often, occasionally, very often veers into that idea with quote unquote rock and
roll.
That's all it is.
Sure.
Yes.
This version for kind of this, this very populist for everybody
with a lot of the recurring figures and the, you know, that it's all way they, cause they,
we've seen, we'll see it here.
There's a thousand things like this hard rock park.
We've talked about a lot of iterations of hard rock cafe and here we are again,
but they love to do it's Mount Rushmore and on Mount Rushmore is Elvis and Bob Marley.
And it's the, and then it's the statue of Liberty and it's a Jimi Hendrix and he's holding a guitar
instead of a torch.
Yeah.
And yes, they make, they turn the statue of Liberty into a man
cause they can't think of a female rock star to use.
There's none.
Who's it going to be?
Lita Ford.
I don't know if people know who that is.
It should be Lita Ford.
I would like that again.
That would be cool.
The deeper these places cut,
a Lita Ford.
I don't think I know any Lita Ford song, but I would love to see a Lita Ford statue
of Liberty.
But here we are at, I think one of the biggest icons in this we're in, we're across the
lake now.
We're like, this is like, these are the big icons that you see, um, you know,
waiting you over on the park side of things.
And boy is this entire facility grand.
My God,
is this, and it's tough to say cause it's right next to Toothsome Chocolate Emporium, but is,
is hard rock this facility, could it be the most ostentatious restaurant in the world?
Oh, the world.
Yeah.
The only competition is being other hard rock cafes.
The original one, I was reading a lot about the original one, uh, which at one point in time
was one of the most successful restaurants in the world.
Yeah.
First hard rock cafe in Florida,
first in Orlando, first built from the ground up one, because before that they had all taken over
existing spaces.
Every, yeah, they just like, you know, the doors having to bend to the
censorship.
No, they didn't.
They said it just like the Rolling Stones having to sensor their own
lyrics.
The original hard rock cafe is all had to fit in some confined existing space.
Yeah.
They boxed them in, but this time they could rock as hard as they would, as big as they wanted to.
Two, they, including one that they closed when the second location, the newer location was ready.
Yes.
I don't think that ever occurred to me that they only ever closed the first one,
which famously had a guitar shaped pedestrian bridge.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
This is, so what you're
describing is, you know, before there was City Walk, when there wasn't even a glimmer of an
E-Zone, they, one of the only, like the only sort of outside restaurant on the universal Florida
property was this hard rock cafe.
This was opening day, 1990, along with the rest of the park,
massive, sprawling.
Uh, I saw it described as like it's Graceland plus ancient Rome.
It's like all of it.
It's this, it's a temple.
It's a temple to rock.
Um, and you might have read the
same article I did that the, how they landed on the placement of it.
And this is, this is a great
moment.
I mean, take, take the wheel, take the lead, take the solo.
Well, I don't think I have
the exact wording right in front of me.
So if you have it, go ahead.
Okay, sure.
Um, this is from the,
the Orlando Informer.
Um, when the partnership between Universal and Hard Rock first came out,
the company's president at the time, Robert Earl.
Earl is back, baby.
You almost forget,
you think of him as the planet Hollywood guy.
You think of him as the Earl of Sandwich guy,
a big presence in sagas at this point, at least the last one.
Uh, and I'm glad he's, I'm glad he's
with us here.
Bucatepepo, of course, also.
Um, so Robert Earl was given a choice of locations,
for the cafe.
Would you, would it be inside Universal Studios, Florida?
So the ticket
holders get to go, or would it be outside where I'm going to quote the actual article,
where all the rest of the city beautifuls, residents and tourists could get easy access
to city beautiful.
City beautiful, Orlando city beautiful.
Um, so you got a choice, Robert,
do you want it to be inside the park or do you want it to be outside the park?
What about both?
He said, and then twiddled his little fingers, I would imagine.
And then a guy
behind him played a killer electric guitar grip.
And then all of his staffers heads exploded because they couldn't even, they couldn't handle
the create the Hard Rock energy of that idea.
How could a restaurant be in both the inside and the
outside of a theme park?
You mean we'll have to order two more turnstiles and three more hand stamps?
Holy shit, Robert.
Don't bore me with the details.
That's not what I want to hear.
I want to go shop
for more flouncy shirts with busy patterns.
I want to come back and you figure out how it works.
So yeah, it's going to be both one entrance for the park guests where you get hand stamps.
So you
can come so they know who's who, uh, to separate you from the riff raff and another for everyone
else at a price tag of $5 million, a massive sum of money for just one building at the time.
But how will people get from the parking lot to the restaurant?
They'll be crushed.
Cars will
mow them down for an over.
No, no, no.
There will be actually this.
There's another.
This actually
is how it was pitched that they said, well, Robert, there will be a pedestrian walkway you see,
that will.
And he's like, no, that's not interesting enough.
Make it a, give it a rock
flair.
And they came back and they said, what if the entire restaurant sits on a big platform
that is a giant concrete guitar?
Uh, and if you see that from the sky, that's what you're looking at.
So the pedestrian bridge is the neck of the guitar complete with fiber optic strings at the top that
lit it up at night.
And of course I'm making fun of this and I'm making fun of Robert Earl.
Um,
and I didn't, let me admit, I didn't go to this original one, but I've seen a lot of photos.
It was so fucking cool.
This building is awesome.
And it really takes me back to 1990.
It's like,
it's part of it for me when I see those overhead shots anywhere you are in the park, or if you're
watching old footage or if you're watching, as I discovered once the beginning of a Michael Winslow
standup special, that's the guy who made all the voices and police academy.
And that was
filmed at Universal Studios.
If you ever see aerial footage or anything, part of it is, what is that?
There's a giant guitar as part of this theme park.
That's so dumb and cool.
Can I say something that
I don't know if it'll be controversial?
I don't think it is.
Is the hard rock more iconic than
almost any part of original Universal Studios from an exterior, like architecturally,
or just, you know, you go down Main Street, you see the castle, you go to Spaceship Earth.
Oh my God,
like go crazy.
Like there's nothing like that.
That's not the strength I wouldn't say of original,
all the attractions are good, but all the attractions are hidden in these back lights.
Right.
Exactly.
So, so especially back then, now you could say at least Diagon Alley is like,
oh my God, this is insane looking, but hard rock.
I love that back to the future ride building.
And
I love the photo op where you could put the space shuttle on top of it.
But that's a very specific
after the fact, 1990 world's fairest glass brick thing.
I don't think that's iconic to
everybody.
Yes.
And I don't know that there were a lot of eight-year-olds like me who would go like,
that's the recreation of the wild pharmacy where a lot of stars were discovered.
People would like it.
Yes.
People liked that.
The famous garden of Aalav.
It's where stars went to get treats.
It was kind of the EMAC and Bollio's of 1950s.
So hard rock is like the weenie or something.
Like what would you call it?
Well, no, because it doesn't like lure you anywhere and you have to be above it to know.
All I know is I'm looking at aerial footage or photos now and it's the most ostentatious,
dumbest thing.
And it's the first iteration of something.
It's hard to describe.
I think we,
three of us get the same sensation from it's a restaurant that's both inside and outside the park.
It is cool.
Why do I care about that?
Why do we think that's neat?
Do we know?
I mean,
you might say it just is, but is there any psychology to why we think that's so cool?
Well, I think there's probably two, there's maybe a more practical reason and then there's a magical
reason.
And I think the magical reason is that almost every theme park, it does feel like you're
going through a Kronos or a portal or a jump point when you enter the gates.
Yes, or a gate.
There is a sort of psychological thing that happens to you where the music changes.
You get a little
bit of a different feeling and you've passed through this magic.
And it's either in or out.
And when you were a kid, you really had to make those moments count.
Yes.
Maybe it's you're at
whim of your parents.
You go and they decide you can go.
So either I'm in or I'm out.
But the idea
of something that blurs those boundaries.
It's like you're in some sort of limbo.
It's like you're in a phantom zone in a way.
Except like a good one, not a depressing one.
Yes, exactly.
Not a prison limbo, but a limbo where you can get mozzarella sticks.
A mix of rock and roll, heaven and hell.
Exactly.
Who's a rock and roll angel,
Peggy Lee is there.
Yeah, OK.
But also, I don't know who's Bozzy, except he's not dead.
I don't
know.
I'll get back to you.
Jim Morrison, of course.
Well, I have been thinking about this
hard rock a lot since we started doing this series, because just thinking about the times
have been the universal times have been the city walk and forever glued in my memory is this image
from, you know, by like five and eat.
I just remember as a little kid looking and seeing
like, OK, there's the T ride.
There's a five.
I'll go west like water slide and play area.
And then I moved to the left and there's the psycho house on a lonely,
a lonely hill, the second house from one of the sequels.
Yeah.
You got to figure that out.
Psycho.
Why?
Well, from psycho four, of course, from exteriors, you see, unless it was three,
I could be wrong, but certainly a not to and then I can rule not to.
But then you pan left
past the psycho house and there's a giant white mansion looking thing.
And I'm like, I knew that
was a hard rock cafe.
But as a kid, I saw the movie psycho at way too young an age and it scared the
hell out of me.
And so I always associate that in my mind.
Something in my mind just clicks of like
original Hard Rocks.
I go out like, yeah, it's all the same.
It's all the same.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
It was what it was a striking like a striking tableau.
I only went to this era of universal
once in like ninety four and I really I definitely recall the like sparness of it.
I think I recall
like looking at it all from afar and my parents going, no, not that way.
There's nothing for you
there.
Yeah, that's like the adult zone, you know, basically.
Yeah, I went when Planet Hollywood
started popping up, I think my every one of my family board was like, yes, the movies Hollywood,
we like that.
Hard Rock was threatening.
We are watching Psycho now and you just see sort of a
shot of the house.
Do you imagine there's a Hard Rock right sort of down the road, like the dirt
I'm mostly watching the Vince Vaughn cause found some shot shot.
Same thing, same thing.
So that
one does it would naturally fit in.
So Norman goes down and he manages the hotel, but then he goes
back up and manages the Hard Rock as well.
Shifts from the house.
Yeah, three twisted mac and cheese
all day long or whatever the cook terminology.
That's how I watch from now on.
Yeah, yeah, no,
just picture it right.
Yeah, you know, Hitch doesn't show you because it's not important to
story.
Yes, of course.
The Hard Rock Cafe is right there.
Also that globe that like that domed
globe up top is really striking.
And then I think it says Kingdom of Rock.
Yeah, the building is
really it's a I would love to have like a die cast or like like a model of that Hard Rock.
I don't
know if such a thing exists, but I'd like to put that next to my Bonaventure Hotel mug.
It's just
like I'm so I remain so confused about do I like Hard Rock or do I not?
I feel like I've had like
great moments in them, but I don't have any particular affinity for the brand or the food,
but I would love to have a little version of that.
I like the new one too.
I love all of it.
The hotel stuff they're built like that big hotel that's a big guitar was that in Florida?
That's in
Florida.
That's in Florida, but then they're building one on the Vegas.
Yes, right, right,
I like though.
I like that.
Yeah, I kind of want to say so I understand what you're saying.
Like
I'm because I'm sometimes I'm like when is this thing going away and never they don't ever lose.
And if one's closed, they just reopen somewhere else in the city.
Yes, because the Hard Rock
closed in Vegas, the hotel, but they're building a bigger cooler one.
They're taking over the Mirage.
Yeah, yeah, and it's going to be in the shape of a big guitar and the one they have in Florida.
I
go this looks cool.
I want to stay in here.
Yeah, well, never dies Rock and Roll can never die.
Except the one in New Orleans that partially collapsed and they called it.
They're like we're not finishing this project.
So sometimes it'll pop up somewhere else.
Yeah,
that's what they tend to do.
They're mushrooms these places.
But anyway, so this this as Jason
said, this was like an unbelievably successful restaurant.
And just before I move past it,
the discovery that this thing that we love the inside outside there again,
this thing that we love the inside outside theme park restaurant that Robert Earl himself invented.
Right, right.
I don't think I've been giving him enough credit all these years.
Yeah, I should
have been because he like put a lot of the dumbest looking buildings of all time on the map.
Yeah.
But and I love his web series also and his shirts.
Love his personality.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a
lot to love.
And I just got to go to this as mentioned on the show a couple weeks ago,
a Planet Hollywood auction.
It was happening.
I think it's happening concurrently to when
listeners are hearing this.
But I was like I was racing over to this thing to go like be in a
building where all of the Planet Hollywood stuff is back and the logo is up everywhere.
I don't
think I'm ever going to buy anything, but I wanted to be at this exhibit.
And I went with friends of
the show Van Robe Show and Bugman Buzz Buzz.
And they're sending me pictures of what's there.
There's a chewy and there's like the like what what rose the piece of wood roses on in Titanic.
The wood really?
Yeah.
Wow.
These are nuts.
It's crazy.
If you're in LA and this thing's still
happening, I forget it's on Olympic and Beverly Hills.
I think what's the I forget the name of
the collectible company.
But anyway, I'm like they're sending me photos and I'm like, God,
I can't wait.
I can't wait to get there.
And then I'm going through Coldwater Canyon, not one,
but two potholes just shredded my tire.
Just absolutely.
And so then I'm stuck.
I'm having
a call AAA and I'm like only two miles.
And the part of me is like, maybe I could get.
And then
I try to go a little further and I'm like, cook, clunk, cook, clunk, cook.
It drove me.
It drove
me so crazy that I'm like, I'm so close to and then somebody came, uh, put my spare on.
All right.
You know, don't drive too much on this.
Okay, sure.
I start thinking I'm going, I'm going to go to it.
I'm going to go and I went, I took, I took this.
It wasn't, no, it didn't add that much to it.
But oh my God, to be in a, to be in a Robert Earl environment again,
to see his ugly logos, to see an entire judge dread corner.
Oh, they didn't have Stallone in
the tube out, but yeah.
They have on display the Ivan news.
Uh, no, yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
This is another
thing we've been, maybe there's more material to mine out of this.
There's a lot of stuff was on
display.
Oh, and Mike, Mike, while this thing is open, um, I don't want to build up your expectation
too much.
When you send that, well, you'll know why.
Batman forever.
There is Batman forever.
There's Batman forever stuff.
I know.
Robin stuff.
Uh, Marty's kitschy,
um, uh, back to the future three, the thing doc makes him wear.
That's like old west
style with the Adams.
Uh, that was kind of jaw dropping to see, uh, where was I?
I'm getting
lost.
Oh, Ivan news.
Yeah.
Besides what they have on display in the real, in the facility,
there's all this stuff that isn't on display that is so up our alley, uh, the full Ivan news costume
what can be bid on.
Maybe by the time listeners are hearing this, we've put our money together
to buy it.
Maybe.
Oh my God.
And this display it in here.
No man.
Yeah.
Geez.
Where keep a manic.
I, yeah, I guess this has gotta be my garage.
The closest thing to our perma facility.
There's
something I, you know what?
There's something I have received that I, we need to find a place for it.
Oh, and whatever it is, whatever this museum is, that's all I'll say.
I'll tease that right now.
We need a separate museum.
We need like, okay, well we're coming like the hard rock where we're
like, the collection is outgrowing.
Thanks to listeners who've gotten us incredible things.
We want to keep them.
I'm Griffin's baby.
Aladar toy over there.
Yeah.
That's all in there.
There's a, uh, uh, you know, but there's only so many walls in this place.
We're going to have to
get a facility.
It's just like, that's the attic, a real thing.
We need our museum of the weird.
We need our own.
Yeah.
I don't know where it would be.
Maybe that's the way.
And then we
charging.
Oh yeah.
This is going to be a money making.
Yeah.
Yes.
Look, we got to pay the bills
for this place.
Somehow.
Yeah.
Maybe the first week, but then going way up.
Jurassic park.
Maybe we could have a coupon day.
Right.
There's a lot of storefronts in Burbank.
I'll say that
there's a lot of wonderful small businesses in Burbank that had been there forever,
but then there's a lot of stuff flipping, you know?
And so we can go get one of those for only
all the money on earth.
Everything is so fucking expensive.
Yeah.
Sure.
I should be.
I'd love
to be able to just put up podcasts, the rides, museum of the weird, but I, you know, it's going
to cost us, I think.
Yeah, probably.
Yeah.
Um, maybe we could just go in the back of gun world
and put a whole, just a room together.
Probably reasonable people too much space.
That's like
the giants.
They took over the old bubble head studios.
I think remember bubble head.
I know
that that was like their public art.
I don't know.
Yeah.
But it was, they had the biggest building
and I don't know.
This is a real place.
Listeners.
Yes.
We love Burbank, but also there's an alarming
amount of gun stores for here for some reason, otherwise very pleasant, wonderful.
Um, anyways,
to speak a little more about things they, and they had at this location, some of which I think
moved to the other one, um, the handwritten lyrics to imagine think about that without,
if he hadn't taken pen to paper, when he, that, when that ink touched that paper, that allowed,
uh, gal Godot to say her name.
No, it's more like, I think that's what you're saying, but I don't,
I'm not a hundred percent sure.
Anyway, that if John, if without that piece of paper,
many celebrities wouldn't have been able to embarrass themselves and make us all laugh.
And the first week of the pandemic, we really needed it.
It would have been like a different,
it would have been like, they all sang silly love songs or something.
It would have to be a different
Beatles solo.
Imagine, imagine a world with no imagine.
I mean, I know this is very close to
the premise of yesterday, but imagine, but isn't it the, like all of, all of that, all the Beatles
music being gone, maybe doesn't have the same effect as just one.
Imagine.
Yeah.
That's,
that's a movie.
You should pitch that now, since they're doing the four Beatles movies.
They're going to definitely, they're not going to stop at four or four Beatles movies.
Yeah.
We're sure if you have any ins for all of us to be in the punch up room for Ringo.
God.
And they're like all releasing in 2027.
I'm like, how's it with one with Sam,
what's his name directing all of them?
Sam Mendes for movies.
He can't be doing all.
I swear.
That's what I read.
Maybe I'm misremembering, but that's what I thought
please, please, please.
Fingers crossed.
He's there's an old, there's an actor who he's old
buddies with who he had a, a award winning collaboration with.
And we know this man is
a fan of John Lennon and his music and his message and being incredibly pissed off.
And that's Mr.
Kevin Spacey.
Could you put the please Kevin hashtag Kevin as John,
just he's coming back.
He's doing monster cons.
Kevin is back and he needs to be back as John
Lennon.
We could use the Irishman technology on him and just make him young so he could play
John Lennon.
No, never.
He's already experienced this area.
He played Bobby Darin when he was 19
years older than Bobby Darin.
He can, he can contort.
Hey, let me take you to the sock hop.
It's like 43.
Um, oh God, please, please.
Spacey is Lennon.
Uh, more Beatles stuff.
This place and I think the new one's still bricks that were taken from the cavern club where the,
where the Beatles first performed.
Now I have a question about that because I saw that plaque
and, uh, I believe it says, I want to get this wording right.
These bricks were taken from the
building adjacent to the legendary cavern.
So doesn't that mean, and maybe I miss remembering
my word definitions, but it doesn't adjacent me next to unless, unless it is the bricks that
literally provided the border.
That's the only thing where I give it where it's like, it's the,
but I also, I still wording that adjacent doesn't sound like what I'm describing.
That makes me think of Lisa at the museum going like, wait a minute, there's not a cane and
a sink adjacent to the cabin, adjacent to the cab.
Wow.
So, you know, catch if in the,
the biggest you could dream of is that like John and George took a piss on these bricks before
a concert.
They went out for a, they went out for a cig in the alley.
I dropped me toast sandwich
against it.
They dropped their toast sandwich toast sandwich, of course, two slices of bread
with a piece of toast in the middle.
A war ration food.
Is that real?
It is real.
You think the
Beatles would have eaten?
Well, in between shows, you got to scar something down.
Have you ever had
one?
You ever had one?
You know what?
I have it.
I should be shows every meal.
Every time we do a
show, know that if you go to both shows, know that Jason's eating a toast sandwich, a war ration toast
sandwich.
Is that just a roll with fries on it?
I think you're going to have to tell me these are
British like, you know, uh, three AM or hangover foods.
Wow.
Still, do you think people are still
eating toast sandwiches in Britain right now?
I mean, maybe.
Wow.
Really?
Is there, you don't know
the war ended still.
They have an inherent rationing in their heads.
There's a car.
Yeah.
Cargo.
There's cargo cults in the Pacific, but then there's also Brits who don't know the war and that
still eating toast sandwiches.
Still only listening to number station broadcasting.
Wow.
What a picture.
What a picture you're painting here.
1955.
All right.
We might, by the way, I'm now I'm looking up what is next to the cavern club and
we might have to go to Liverpool and do a mini saga about all the crap.
Oh, is there like a
cavern club?
I've never thought about this.
That the cavern club is of course some bad tourist trap
kind of place.
Right.
I'm amazed.
There's not a hard rock right there.
I have, although I haven't
the broader search.
I'll Google, I'll, I bet there's one within the mile, but anyway, it's just all a
bunch of garbage like with the, that's named Sergeant Peppers.
There's a hotel called hard
days night and there's a band and get ready.
There is a mall called the cavern walks.
No.
Yes.
We're
going to have to do the cavern walks out of here.
The cavern walks.
Apparently.
Holy shit.
Yep.
How much stuff is in the cavern walks?
I don't know.
I wonder, I was reading, uh, uh,
oh God, what is it?
Uh, in the guardian a while back, there is a phenomenon happening on the,
is it the high street?
Like several row area, like streets that had a lot of
banks and like very fine clothes.
There's a lot of them, obviously, you know, places closed or
during the pandemic.
And they're like, for some reason now the high street is filled with candy
shops selling overpriced American candy.
Most of the money laundering operations for the mafia,
for the British mob.
So I am wondering if the cavern walk is full of candy shop money laundering
operations.
That's how I mean, it's all like, I, I looked it up and it's on the outside.
There's
Chantilly Beatles cafe.
Sure.
Chantilly have to do with it.
But you can get big breakfast all day.
3.
95.
Good price on that.
Well, pounds.
I was, what's the little L I didn't say it out loud
because I didn't want to be embarrassed.
That's not Euro.
Is it?
I don't know.
I think that's
pounds.
Okay.
Um, okay.
Well, cavern walk saga coming soon.
Let's get through here.
One saga
at a time.
We'll figure it out.
Um, anyway, this place is making, uh, $45 million a year.
This is unbelievably successful.
So when they decide to do the broader city walk shopping
district, of course, hard rock has to be a part of it, but it doesn't make sense for them to be all
the way out there.
They got to bring it more central.
And despite this already being the biggest
hard rock ever built, one of the biggest restaurants ever built, they're like, I think we can go bigger.
And they do.
And they build not only the new restaurant, but this massive concert venue,
a 3000 seat concert venue, uh, that looks like the Roman Coliseum on the outside.
I remember the
first time I didn't know any of this was built.
And when I came back to universal post this in
99 or whatever, like, Oh my fucking God, they have a dumb looking Coliseum now.
Boy, is that
spectacularly silly.
Um, and there's probably more restaurant stuff before we move to the venue.
I just wanted to say that, like that they couldn't, the hard rock has to be, it's like,
it's part of it might've been the most successful piece of the property, maybe more than the theme
park.
I don't know.
Just like square footage.
So Jason, as you said, they did a perfect transition.
One closed the next day, the new one opened.
There was never a downtime.
I did not know that.
It is
unbelievable.
And that said the Sheridan family routine when staying at universal, we would check
into the hard rock hotel, drop our bags.
Okay.
It's time for lunch.
We will walk over to the hard rock
cafe and I never had a bad time.
Never had a bad meal.
Never got me sick, which is saying something
in this series.
Unlike the hard rock, uh, uh, that used to be at universal Hollywood city walk,
which I believe got me sick at least a couple of times.
Yeah.
I can't, again, we got to lower this
bar.
I'm glad your family was fine.
I definitely, I went to this one in 2008 and thought it stunk,
but for me, but that was, but you know, these things are very, it does a lot of variables.
A few years before is what you're describing.
Well, I, I am a very fond memories of my go to order,
which was a pulled pork sandwich with French fries and looking back, surprisingly flavorful,
baked beans.
I have not seen in a while, but like beans with like pork in like real barbecue
beans.
Yeah.
And like, it was good.
Hard rock, hard rock, Lord, they've always pushed
like the pork ribs and burgers.
They're so proud of serving their burgers, which I think they're so,
they're so proud of serving their burgers, which I think if you go back to the original,
the original art rock was in London.
I think some of the marketing was like, I couldn't get a good
burger in this city.
So we opened this place.
And I'm sure the quality today is just as odd at every
location.
Can I ask a question?
Cause like in Hollywood, I have such a strong memory of going
cause every kid likes, but the most part likes movies and especially in the nineties behind the
scenes was very exciting.
I feel like everybody thought it was fun to see all those making of and
stuff.
Yes.
Hard rock as a concept was your family, did they like rock and roll?
Was that even part of
it?
My family liked rock and roll.
I mean, I think I thought my dad saw a lot of concerts in the 70s.
Bands usually came through Philadelphia.
Tickets were very affordable.
I think the funniest story,
he, he, he saw Elton John on one of his first tours.
I think he saw Neil Young open for the
Kings and the Kings never finished their set.
Cause the brothers started fighting.
The real, uh, thing that's like in a waste, like if I went to an oyster show and the brothers
started fighting, I would see a live fight.
That's so you want to, if they're going to play the hits,
one of the hits has to be a fight.
Yeah.
I don't even need them throw fists like battle of words,
like it's just someone yelling like, I'm done with you.
Like, and storming off stage with like, uh,
you know, Becks or Heineken or whatever, you know?
Yeah.
I just don't think, I guess where I'm going
with this is just, I feel like I, maybe it's just me, but I don't have like the same association
with this in rock and roll as I do with planet Hollywood and Hollywood.
It's almost its own thing
in my mind.
And maybe that's, I think that's right.
Even though there's memorabilia of rock
and roll on the wall.
I don't know.
Cause planet Hollywood is early 90s blockbuster.
Yeah.
It's
such a direct connection.
And you know that the people who were plugging it, that Arnold and Sly
are donating the costumes.
Right.
Or there's a kind of a through line where it felt like show
business going to plan Hollywood in Illinois felt like a little bit like I'm in the movies now.
All the hard rocks feel like, does Tom Petty know that's here?
Yeah, no.
Well, yes.
But then when you, when you break down the practical nature, uh, as the food got worse
and worse at the plant, Hollywood's, it was always pretty consistent at the hard rock.
They're clearly, yeah.
As much as I'm not going to, I'm not going to tout this as a good restaurant,
even close.
I think I gave it two forks on doughboys forever ago.
Uh, but the, it, it didn't have the
full slide that is like notorious, like regular people who don't care about any of this crap.
If you say, what do you know about planet Hollywood?
It says this big dumb restaurant
with Arnold and Stallone.
And then the food was horrible.
And then it closed.
That's like,
that's kind of the cliff notes and hard rock never.
Yeah.
It's like, they kept it just good enough.
Yes.
Sure.
I'll say I will give the Hollywood one a compliment.
There was a time where my dad was
visiting in like rainy February in LA, we both had colds and I remember going like, oh, thank God,
the hard rock, uh, had a very, we were up at city walk and we went there.
We need somewhere, please
the shelter.
We need sanctuary.
We, we had a very, a very safe back at sheet.
Like a very flight.
Like, do you have a warm cup of water?
All we, all we're simple folk.
All we need is a Mac and a
cheese.
Um, I hear you cause as a parent, that's all I'm looking for is a safe Mac and cheese.
And I think, and we, this is probably, even though it was twisted, even though, by the way,
we're all so screwed on these repeated stories because anybody who's got club three and we've
released the same thing, some people are going to have heard the repeated stories, but seven days
prior.
Right.
That's true.
So serves us right.
I say, I sure.
Yeah.
But different contexts now,
different context, much worlds of different hard rock, Orlando in the city walk ranking,
a better food choice, the most it is on the higher end.
I would have to agree.
Yeah.
Um, now here is,
here was my experience on this particular trip.
I did not stop and eat there.
I don't believe any
of us stopped and ate there on this, unless I missed something.
Um, what I did do was go and
take a walk through it.
I believe in the order of events I was in between, had been hanging out with
Jason was about to meet Mike, had a little stretch of time to kill.
It was late.
It was after the
rush.
And I just took a walk and walked into every room that they have.
And I was, uh, baffled and
humbled by this walk that I took through the hard rock cafe.
I knew it was big.
I'd been in there.
I had a meal in there, but I didn't do the full explore doing it when it's more spare at night
and the entire rooms that, okay, just the room that I'm in, that's completely empty would be
enough space for an entire restaurant in and of itself.
Yes.
And in most cases, those have
a domed ceiling, uh, made out to be like a beautiful chapel and being in one of these
places by yourself and, and just every, and every item kind of being at least jaw dropping or just
weird.
This walk was kind of the most, one of the most like peaceful and cool things I did
in the trip.
It feels like they could fit all of San Diego Comic-Con in this restaurant.
It's like, like they're always talking about, well, where can we move it?
But most places
don't have a convention center big enough.
Let's move it to the hard rock in Orlando.
I'd find it so big.
Uh, it was really, and the fact, I just didn't know the sheer,
the volume of rooms and that rooms have entire like, okay, now we'll just deal with the Woodstock
room and now we'll deal with the CBGB's room and that there's that many sub genres and then big
circular staircases and the entire way up the circular staircases, there's a bunch of crap
and then balconies and outside.
And then you look up like this, just this, the stained glass or just
whatever paint ceiling painting content in here is mind boggling.
There's a different one on everyone
and they're so dumb.
They're so ostentatious.
Look at this one that you guys are across the room.
So this just looks like, you know, regular boring church stuff, right?
And the style that would
have been the most beautiful thing you've ever seen in the year 700, but like, okay, boring,
right?
Then zoom in, wait a minute, who are these angels and lords and priests?
Why it's Elvis and
Mary Garcia and we're deifying cousin, Marrior, Jerry Lee Lewis.
And then there's also big stained
glass, like the most beautiful church.
And then it says hail, hail, rock and roll.
And it's Chuck
Barry.
These pieces, whoever put together every individual piece of art, this is like unbelievable
artisans.
So funny.
Yeah.
And I'm so surprised even that they got all this approved because
when did you think somebody be like, that's kind of sacrilegious.
Like this is all just
like religious imagery and we're going to put rock and roll people in there.
But obviously
everybody thought it was cool.
This is in Florida.
This is a more religious.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
Yeah, I guess it didn't, I guess people like that about it.
Just like the son of God, King of Kings,
rock and roll never die.
Yeah, exactly the same thing.
That's the same thing.
Like Ken Ham like
this.
I don't know from the arc encounter.
Yeah.
Well, does this disobey commandments?
It does,
doesn't it?
Idolatry.
Yeah.
Maybe this place needs to be struck down is what we're finding.
The centric keeper were here, who's been going to church with you, Jason Lilley, he'd
good thing he's not here.
Yeah.
This is more sector creeper vibe.
That's right.
Yeah.
Some of the things on this walk, let me say a couple that I thought were genuinely
impressed.
The ones that struck me the most, right?
I just, I need to stop and stare at this
for a minute.
One were these, these two metallic masks from the cover of
Pink Floyd's, the division bell.
Like, I mean, like I know crazy.
Yes.
And those are them.
Wow.
That's the cover.
It's insane.
I mean, obviously today it's best known as the, the cover of,
it was, it was reappropriated to be the cover of bug mains, the division bug.
And those are,
wait, not wait, is it waddo?
It might be waddo.
I think it's waddo.
I think they're waddo heads.
Yeah.
So, but this was the precursor and, and, you know, there couldn't have been division
bug without division bell.
I'm trying to think like, okay, let me get into, should I do sillier
ones?
Okay, wait, sure.
Genuinely cool.
I mean like a Freddie Mercury jumpsuit, like a black and
white zebra stripes, an Angus young school boy.
So some of these you're like, I think it might've
been like a vest that Hendrix wore at Woodstock.
Some of these are such jaw droppers.
And then the
one, this will not be for everybody, but I was just so with my, my specific interests, I was like,
I just need to like reflect on this.
That this is in the back of an Orlando.
It's just like next to
somebody's like ringing up table 34 and they like, nobody's paying attention to this.
It's just
rotten away in Orlando restaurant.
Uh, Kate Pearson from the B 52s dress from the love shack video.
Wow.
And this, this just struck me because like, that's how you know her.
That's like, that's her
iconic outfit.
Yeah.
Yes.
If you think of her, it's that with the red and all the tassels,
that is like her iconic wardrobe and it's just in a box in this rest.
It just really, I don't know,
it just like kind of took it out of me in this weird way.
Just had to reflect on this tassel dress.
I feel like it would be, it's, it's sort of conflicting because on one hand you're like,
oh, that's awesome.
And then the other hand, you're like, people are eating onion rings here all day,
not looking at it.
Yeah.
It's like, I want it to be, we quote, we say this a lot.
It should be in a
museum.
Yeah.
It maybe should be in the rock and roll hall of fame museum.
Right.
Shouldn't some of
this be a little more paid attention to is what I'm saying.
But also, but you're right.
But then I,
for free, right.
Got to just walk up to things like this and maybe there's like one person a day who
goes, Oh, yeah.
And that's pretty good.
I mean, like it's being appreciated on some level.
This
per year likely gets more visitors than the rock and roll hall of fame.
Don't you think?
That might be true.
That could be true.
Yeah.
This is the biggest hard rock cafe
now, I think.
Right.
Probably.
And I believe it has more memorabilia than any other one.
This isn't like, there was a lot of playing Hollywood and some of them admittedly,
even in this auction we've talked about, had recreations of things.
I feel like the hard rocks
especially this one being like a kind of a flagship one, they have like some A list stuff here.
Yeah.
Yes.
I mean, the cavern club bricks are funny, but legitimately it is wild.
They have
John and Yoko's marriage certificate.
Oh my God.
Wow.
They have a, there is a John Lennon room
you can visit.
Yeah.
My favorite John Lennon thing was a letter from John Lennon to Mal Evans
regarding him having caught the measles.
The love seat, a love seat he wrote a bunch of songs on,
a little couch.
Oh wait, no, isn't because I think, because I was getting some things mixed up.
I believe that the hard rock hotel, and if we haven't clarified this, hotels are out of this
saga because something has to be.
Secretary Keeber never mentioned it, so we're just gonna
pretend we never heard it.
The John Lennon room is in the hotel, I think, and that's a thing that
you can go ask for a tour of.
Oh, okay.
I think, because it's so huge, I don't think it would fit
in here, but that is like decorated like his New York apartment and it's got a huge piano,
huge, the piano, the size of a piano, but it's like white and ornate and every key is signed by a
different music legend.
The key is signed, but the piano itself is a replica.
Oh, okay.
That is not
original piano.
Gotcha.
I was wondering, like this looks more like a hotel room over an apartment,
where is it?
But the attic.
The attic is in here.
At the restaurant.
Yes, so if it wasn't enough that
there's all of these endless rooms in this place, there's also one that is off the menu,
the attic, where things are a little disorganized and it's just, they like fake you out.
I think
there used to be a time at least where they offered tours of this.
You would go and ask for the vibe
tour is what there were people who were called the vibe hosts.
Yeah, I got a lot to say about the
vibe.
Can we?
Yes.
Yeah.
Well, let me say one of the things you could do is go to the secret room,
the attic.
It's a little more disorganized, but like it's signed by all the acts that played the
that venue.
I think they used it as a green room kind of for, so just there's all like you were like,
you know, you're, you're made to feel small in the universe by how much memorabilia there is in
this place.
And then there's still another one that we don't even get to go to anymore because
you would have had to ask a vibe host.
I don't know if they still have vibe host.
What's the deal
with vibe host?
I don't know if they have to still vibe host either.
I found this on a 2013 touring
plans blog post.
The vibe hosts, quote, walk around the entire restaurant, meeting with guests and
answering any questions they may have about the hard rock cafe and doing their best to create an
experience for each guest.
They also carry with them an iPad that contains an app which allow
guests to pick out songs that play in the whole restaurant.
You could pick the music.
And these
are, these two are credit as, uh, Lauren and Randy rock.
Now I don't know if that's Lauren rock and
Randy rock.
Were they characters or did they only hire people?
Looks like a character.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
People with the last name rock.
That is a good question.
I mean like rock or wall because it's
like, Oh, that's so funny.
We have the Berlin wall right out there and your last name's your
Henry wall.
Yeah.
Get in here.
Jason.
They would, they would hire Henry.
Your cousin, Erica rock.
Would they have hired Robert wool?
Cause it's close to wall.
Only if they misheard what he said.
Only
if they, okay.
The job interview.
Um, yeah, it's wild.
This is such a, this is such a massive campus.
And then I haven't even gotten to my favorite area.
And this is really like, there's this too.
They have the Florida room, an entire room just for Florida's prominent musicians.
Um, this is
another one where you're like, Oh my God, I watched this so many times.
I can't believe they have this.
They have the jacket that Tom Petty wore and the, you don't know how it feels video.
Yeah.
Another
tasseled wardrobe pieces.
You told me this right after you had seen it and you were like, just like
incredulous.
They have that.
We wear these on the, these on the turntable.
Weird things are
happening behind you.
Yeah.
Uh, it's that's such, I feel like I was on MTV like every hour for a long
time.
Um, so Florida greats like Tom Petty and Scott staff, they got some shirt that Scott staff
wears a bit less iconic, but hang on now.
Sorry.
What do you mean?
Uh, uh,
Cat Boone's shoes, Joey Fatone shoes from the gone video.
And then my favorite area of the Florida room,
uh, personal effects, belonging to Fred Durst, he of Jacksonville, Florida, a lot are just like,
there's like receipts, receipts for things he bought.
He went into a shop on Melrose Avenue
and bought something for $500 and you can only see part of it.
And it does say red at the end.
And
like hat was a hat.
It doesn't seem like one of those hats would have cost $500, but I don't know
you're Fred Durst in 99.
You're probably only paying top dollar for red hats.
You might be right.
Could be.
I mean, that would be, he's associated with the color.
Yeah.
Um, I loved my time in the
Florida room.
Um, this wasn't an, I don't know where this person or band is from, but, uh,
I did like seeing a smashed guitar from owned by God smack.
And then the plaque, this might be the best plaque in the place.
This Gibson Les Paul was rocked,
rolled and utterly destroyed by God smack front man Sully Erna.
His inscription reads one bad night.
Was it, or was it the best night there ever was?
Sully Erna.
We know that now.
Yeah, we do Sully
Erna will be coming to the show more often.
Well, the end coming to theaters, my biopic Sully.
I have not run it.
I've not run the check on it's about the origin for this and the trial that
ensued after the fact mostly about the trial.
Yeah.
You destroyed over $700 worth of
Gibson Les Paul equipment.
You don't think that this guitar regulatory bureau is going to make
it through a couple of weeks of trials.
You've got another thing coming, Sully.
Yeah.
Uh, did you
say Elvis's karate outfit was here?
I didn't mention that.
I missed it.
Okay.
So many things.
Elvis's karate outfit is here.
I really like that being there.
Wow.
Apparently they have a contract
signed by Fats Domino and the contract says that he can end a concert at any time if the concert
venue turned on an air conditioner because Fats Domino grew up singing in Southern churches,
which never had AC and he found that AC messed up his voice.
Yeah.
Dry.
It'll dry out.
Dry out.
So do not put on air conditioning in the presence of Fats Domino or Fats is out.
He's out
like the Davies brothers having a big fight.
That's pretty cool.
Yeah.
Ironically kind of
tough in Orlando, Florida.
Yeah.
You want that air conditioning on it is hot and muggy most of the
year.
Thank God Fats isn't around to put on concerts now.
Yeah.
I don't know if people would
put up with that shit.
Yeah.
Um, maybe the coolest thing that they had, uh, past tense.
Were you guys
ever there in the time where, and this is okay, they, they brought back Earl's baby, the indoor
outdoor, not indoor outdoor.
What do you call it?
The in park out park.
Yeah.
The magical
inside outside park portal limbo restaurant.
Yeah.
Okay.
They brought back Earl's limbo.
Yeah.
What's the, what's the, what's the kind of box, the box with the conundrum
flicker Schrodinger's or something.
Yeah.
Something like that.
Am I fucking that up?
Lament configuration from Hellraiser.
That's not what I mean, but I like that.
Well, yeah,
we'll just go with, uh, uh, Earl's, uh, Schrodinger's cat.
Is that what I mean?
Schroeder's box.
Yeah.
Okay.
Schroeder.
Yeah.
Um, yes.
Well, this, that's, that's Earl's limbo, Earl's purgatory.
Um,
on the Nickelodeon studios side of things, that's part of the, you know, they lost the other area,
where it's weirdly decay.
I love, we didn't mention the, the time where, uh, it's all the kid stuff,
I was Playland Barney and then still Psycho House and now an unopened hard rock cafe that they've
tried to make more pleasant by painting four stars on of, of light colors that immediately faded in
the Florida heat.
But like now it's just a, do a oddly ghostly decay.
It literally just looks like
some weird haunted temple or something.
Yeah.
This area gave me the creep.
I mean,
I'm a little sad it's gone, but yes, it makes sense.
I'm just, I'm glad they blew it up and
they're kept DT, but okay.
So then you go to the other side, it opens on the other side and they
do the same like little special entrance right by Nickelodeon studios, cool area.
And in, in a
planter over there was parked the magical mystery tour bus.
I have seen that at universe.
Yeah.
I
have seen that.
That one really baffled as a kid, like, Oh my God, the magical, wow.
The bus from a
terrible film.
Let's be honest.
Look, we, everyone likes, we act like everything the Beatles ever did
was perfect.
Magical mystery tour is a tough one.
I haven't seen all of it.
It's if you, if you view
it as just like a bunch of music videos and you're like, okay, well your mother should know is
fucking great.
I'm the walrus is great, but you watch it as all one thing.
I think it was regarded
as like Paul's folly.
I think the other guys are like, what are we on high school?
I made a point
like learning about the Beatles and going through the albums and listening to that album like on a,
you know, Walkman in the, you know, early, early two thousands.
I was like, well, this one has some,
a handful of good songs, but it's not a great album.
Well, it's not a proper album.
I think
only the first half is songs for the special and the other half are like singles they had at the
time.
So it's like not, not technically nonetheless seeing the bus, very cool, but I think they play
favorites with this bus.
They move it to the newest, shiniest hard rock facility.
I think for a while
it was well, not for long.
It was at hard rock park.
And then it ended up at one of the casinos
they opened or something.
Lucky person that gets to drive that bus around.
Yeah.
Wow.
What do you
think?
Imagine being just like, I don't know the character of the bus driver in mystery tour,
not especially popular, but yeah, you'd feel just like that.
Yeah.
Unpopular character.
So
that's all the stuff.
I loved my weird walk through there.
I was humbled.
I reflected on a lot of
things.
And, but that's not it.
It's not okay.
There's a thousand rooms at this place.
And then
also the concert venue.
Yes.
Hard rock live still seemingly one of the biggest concert facilities
in the Orlando area.
Yeah.
It seems like the big, you know, if you're not, if it's, if it's not the
arena, it should be the biggest shows.
Right.
Maybe it's house of blues and then it is, is that still,
that's still there or Disney Springs or blues in Disney Springs?
I think so.
Yeah.
On the one side
by like the former NBA experience.
Okay.
I got dropped off there once I sprinted through
Disney Springs for 45 minutes on this last trip and God, I was confused.
Like I was so confused
where everything was.
I kind of know where everything is, but I was still just like,
I was trying to get to Gideon's and then I was trying to get, I forget, I was trying to buy a
bag to put things into good and get on the plane and I was so lost.
It is so massive.
Yeah.
Like
there's no way we'll ever do a saga about that.
No way.
All right.
I'll quote you on that.
Wow.
There's no way we can do a saga.
It does seem.
Stop this battle of wills.
I can't take it.
You too.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm, there's no battle.
I can't believe Mike is saying, I'm like, wow,
Mike is willingly ruled out a complicated saga.
There's not, let me, well, I won't quote, I won't
quote a man who's done a lot of evil things, but I'll say, well, we already talked about spacey
earlier.
I was going to quote Vince McMahon.
There's no chance in hell we're doing Disney
brings saga, but hell is a place where the sector keeper might go if we do.
What if he needs us?
Yeah.
And listen to me, there's no, there's no great balls of fire.
We aren't doing,
listen to me.
There's no way in hell I'm dating that woman.
I'm not related to.
Yeah.
So, so yeah, anyway, it's hard rock life.
Hard rock life.
Hey, March 29th.
If you're in
Orlando, we just mentioned him.
A legendary night, Joey Fattona, Vince Sink and AJ McLean
from Backstreet Boys.
So they're together.
They're teaming up.
Wow.
Geez.
Put combining their fractions.
Hey.
Or if you're there.
Go ahead.
In March,
the show choir national championship series.
Okay.
All right.
Fame Orlando.
People, maybe people
listening or participating.
Maybe some people are singing with some gentle hand movements
is what I know of show choir.
I believe some swaying, some bouncing.
That's another thing.
I'd rather.
Expected you to have done a show choir when you were a kid.
Uh, I know I didn't.
Did you ever think about it?
I don't think it was ever an option.
Okay.
Well,
that would be hard.
I did chorus for a lot of years.
Right.
Just not show choir.
Yeah.
Okay.
How old were you when you're doing choir?
Oh, middle school.
Halfway through high school.
Okay.
What songs did you sing?
Uh, like all, uh, Irish and Italian.
Oh, ease on down, ease on down
the road.
I think you have said this before.
Now that I think
about it.
What Jane also recently brought up.
It's like, yeah, when I was in show choir, uh,
we did the ease on down there.
Oh, I was like, Oh, I know he's on down the road.
That's funny.
Wow.
Uh, we also did, uh, though is that is in your review, the whiz white again,
white again.
We also did a spiritual called weed in the water.
Have you ever weed in the water?
What that is probably should have been saying that when Amy sang blackbird.
Oh, wow.
That's an easy
one to give.
I said that our music teacher made us sing hero when I was in third grade or second
grade by Mariah Carey, which, well, how did that sound?
Yes.
All of you have a bunch of kids
striving for Mariah Carey.
Yeah.
And then I hear all comes along.
Um, I, uh, uh, there was like a
scene the music teachers would get and they would break down popular songs to like, and then you'd
learn them in class.
And I remember back to back one year it was, I believe I can fly.
And then
one year it was kiss from a row.
Yeah.
You've said the, yeah, we've talked about this.
So
those were, I wish you would perform at one of these, at these hard rock when you were,
you never got the call.
I mean, it might be able to, I was looking at the calendar coming up and
there's some openings, you know, seemingly.
So you, so you were going to sing podcast.
I think we need to team up with someone.
Yeah.
We might.
We need to team up with the
AJ and yeah.
Yeah.
Awesome.
Um, uh, hard rock live opens with, uh, uh, uh, uh, a blast of rock and
roll from the Glen fry band featuring Joe Walsh.
That is the first concert in 99.
Uh, the Orlando
weekly said the concept of rock and roll as theme park attraction took two steps forward with Joe
Walsh and Glen fry.
They played a professional, but perfunctory set that proved how lucrative the
packaging of outlaw imagery has become to the business of family entertainment.
What cut them
down of the whole, that's fucking nailed their ass.
Yeah.
Well, we, this is why we need,
I miss our weeklies.
I miss our, our, uh, our snarky papers to, to rip eagles, the new one and the like.
Um, uh, anyway, so that, that kicked it off.
Um, but you know, but, but tons of prominent concerts.
Um, I'm going to ask Mike, I feel like you've discussed being at this venue.
Sure.
Well, let's
have, and we know, cause I've said it before.
You remember who I saw.
I don't.
Or you remember the zone of type of act where I think I remember.
Go ahead.
Was it the goo goo
dolls?
You're a hundred percent correct.
Okay.
I have found the set list.
I know the date now.
Okay.
So his, for historical purposes, this was June 14th, 2002.
So it's 22 years ago.
Well,
let's cut, let's get to the chase.
The big question.
Did they do the song from treasure planet?
Well, that's a solo John Resnick.
So well, but you know, but he could do it.
Glen fry, you know,
they do Joe Walsh solo in the Eagle shows.
No, you're right.
Yeah.
No, he did not do that.
Uh,
song.
Uh, it was this of course, I was touring off of the album gutter flower.
Just like how maybe let's like a quick pace to the set list.
You could do.
Oh, well, I was going to,
I was going to read all of it, but if you want, I could just read some of the highlights.
Might be good.
Well, slide was number three slides.
Probably the biggest tale.
Well, I guess, uh,
the city of angels, Iris song that's 17.
They, they, they do that later in the set.
Didn't then do they come back with like a rocker?
Um, well the end song, which I have said this
before on the show was a cover of Tom Petty's American girl.
It was the finish of the show,
which I remember being very excited about.
This is cool.
These guys are so cool.
They don't even
play their own song to close out a show.
And that was my thought.
They're so cool that they don't
have the bravo.
You know, the Google dolls were bold.
Some acts limit themselves.
Not the goose,
not the goose.
The goose.
You know, they call the food fighters, the food sometimes, but I'm going
to call the anyone.
Are you inventing calling them the goose?
I think I'm inventing it, but I might
not be probably in the history.
Google does been around for 30 years at this point.
Sorry, did you
say they call the food fighters, the food?
I see that sometimes.
Yeah, you do see never the goose,
but the goose haven't been as prominent lately.
I feel like in the rock and roll press, so you're
not going to see it as much.
It's really, it's a press thing.
It's a media bias.
Yeah.
Food fighters
still can play a stadium or an arena, but the Google dolls, not as much.
Um, so yeah, somebody
give them a shot.
How about you?
How about you do it?
They opened up with a song, big machine,
which was the first song on gutter flower, which I really liked at the time and still like now.
But you know, it's a, it's a 21 song set list.
They play all the, they play all the hits.
They
play Broadway.
They play black balloon, you know, I don't know any of those.
Yes, you do.
I bet you
know broad balloon is dark.
That's it right there.
Okay.
A black balloon is like a real slow one,
kind of a ballot.
Okay.
Um, but I don't want to, we're too late into this episode to torture.
Only we could have, why didn't you get these out at the beginning?
I know, I know people would have
done the entire list up top.
Um, can I mention the thing I discovered filmed at the hard rock live?
Did you encounter this?
Yeah.
Unless you were, unless you had more to go, Mike,
weren't there other bands that I saw?
Actually no.
I only saw it was a vacation.
I saw my mom
and my sister and I were there.
I didn't see, I was about to say my saw them on stage.
They did
perform with the Google dolls.
Although that would have been thrilling.
They were brought
up for American girl.
Um, yes.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, call back to an earlier episode.
Um,
Creed's music video for hire is filmed at the hard rock live.
Really?
Okay.
So not the one
that we talked about in the second gate episode with the like catastrophe happening.
That's my
sacrifice.
My sacrifice was filmed on the New York streets.
They flooded the streets.
He had a little
rowboat.
There was some surreal imagery.
This one, they filmed like backstage and on stage and they
use some like slow motion technique or like camera rigs that were very advanced for the 2000s.
And he said real filmmakers, Creed, real filmmakers.
Uh, Scott steps said it's very
embarrassing to look back on and it's, I was submitted.
It's kind of nothing.
I besides the like slow motion, like he's hovering in the air, like a Christ like figure, maybe that
the budget, like this was higher was like the big hits that really like broke them out.
I feel like
where they were.
So like they probably didn't have the budget I'm saying to, to do anything crazy
and ambitious yet.
I think he is mostly embarrassed by the leather pants that he was wearing a lot at
the time.
Um, and all the memories of shooting this music video is like, I had to get done very
quickly cause we were about to go on tour in Japan.
Okay.
Well yeah, he was, I don't know, if I were
Scott step, I'd be embarrassed by yes, the leather pants and also all the other clothes and also my
hair and also the music that we were performing and the music video that we made and all the other
music that we made.
Well, I was going to, you know what I was going to say?
Don't worry about it, Scott.
You're being too hard on yourself.
Good cop, good cop.
That was my advice to him, but he can choose his own adventure.
I always beat myself up.
Yeah.
I'm my own worst enemy.
I know that's another bad song, but I thought it
resonated with me.
I could have come in here and been like, did you know I saw lit at the hard rock
life?
Yeah.
And you're really, yeah, what do they play?
It's long from American pie too.
That I can't remember the name of yet.
Well then what you would say, you'd say what you said,
well, well they played the hits, they played a set with the hits.
So really the hits they played.
I think, I think, okay, let's say black balloon.
80% of the audience knows black balloon.
I bet.
Good for them.
I'm just saying, I'm not saying you don't.
I'm just saying it's not crazy for me to
have said, of course black balloon.
It's not crazy, but I don't think it's crazy for me to not know.
I'm just saying that it's, I'm not wrong for assuming that you might know black balloon.
That's all I'm saying.
And I'm saying there's no, there's no plausible reason on this earth why I
should or need to know black.
You were alive during the summer of black balloon.
That's the only reason
I assume.
I guess I, well, I didn't, I didn't have the ultimate summer of black balloon that I could
have had.
Turn it up.
Jason would say when he was in the car cruising, is that black balloon?
Crank
it up.
You're in the panzer seat.
You turn, you're the closest to the radio.
You turn.
Creed, of course I'd send you guys this video recently.
Summer of 99 tour this year Creed and
three doors down on tour together.
Wow.
There's like a whole, like there's a little like skit
and then he caught, he's like, somebody who should go with us.
And then he doesn't talk like he
sings, but I'm going to, he, well, it cuts to a phone and there's a guy who's like, Hey, what's
up?
And I'm like, you're in need to ID this person fast.
I do not automatically know who this long
air is that you're talking to.
Yeah.
Of course it's what I think is it some of the stuff I like.
So most songs better than some of this crap switch.
Yeah.
What does switch foot do again?
I don't know.
Not as popular as black balloon.
Whatever that song switch foot does, they never
add their black balloon.
It did not.
Um, our listeners had, I was like, I'm not going to look
at every concert they ever did here, but I'm, I'm like, well, did any listeners have memorable
concert moments at this hard rock live?
Uh, a lot of comedy stuff that's fun.
Mystery science
theater, kids in the hall, uh, Tim and Eric all played here.
Uh, listeners, Sarah got thrown out
of an Aaron Carter concert.
Oh my.
Curious the details there.
Um, uh, Travis saw Weezer doing
an MTV taping at one point, something messed up and they had to perform Beverly Hills twice.
Oh, the dream to get to hear Beverly Hills two times in one show.
Did they change, did the solo,
did they change to Brian or Rivers?
I forget who plays the solo on it.
They change it up.
I probably had to be consistent for the taping so they could cut them together.
I would think.
Yeah.
Um, Andrew Solaro at there at the top is after both of our hearts.
Uh, he specified for me
that he and his dad seems right.
Saw Steely Dan there together.
Uh, bare naked ladies.
He saw
there.
I believe the first bare naked lady show without Steven page happened.
Yeah.
These responses
were great.
So that's a, that would be, uh, uh, if I saw that, that would be one of the most upsetting
moments of my life.
The first show where Steven wasn't there where they're all in, if somehow you
didn't know if the band's coming out and then you're like, what, what, did he trip backstage?
What happened?
Yeah.
Oh my goodness.
Well then it's, this might be a tough place for you
to ever return to.
No, that being said, I've been watching videos of the four of them still playing
recently.
And when I say recently, I mean an hour and a half ago.
Oh, you mean you recently,
you just were, I mean I watched every, the non-Steven version of the band play a few songs on YouTube
with my daughter two hours ago.
So you'll still tell, even though you're, you're seething with
anger, you'll tolerate it.
I'll tell her.
Yeah.
I like some of, I like some of it.
Uh, for turncoats,
sweetie.
I'll say, look, I'll say this.
It's not fair that I feel some feelings like that about
them.
Okay.
Now it's not fair though.
I just want him back in the band.
When did he leave the band?
Cause I saw them in Atlantic city 2013.
Uh, he was gone by then.
Yeah, he was gone by then.
You didn't
even notice.
Fair weather fan Jason had no idea.
I am a fair weather fan.
You didn't even know.
My
youngest people there probably by 10 to 20 years.
It upsets me so much that that's an average person
goes and they go, Hey, the one week part of the song sounds different.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Yeah, I know
the paint.
Well, it's like people, when people tell me that beach boys are doing the Hollywood
bowl.
No, they're not.
One of them is the rest are all elsewhere and two of them are dead.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Um, also the same guy, Andrew, I had my ninth grade homecoming dance there.
We
got to take pictures on the stage and I said to my friend, can you believe we're standing where
smashing pumpkins did?
I wouldn't be able to couple smashing pumpkins mentions, couple strings.
She's incident mentions.
I don't know if I've heard a string cheese incident song.
Yeah, I have,
they don't have one.
They have one.
They have just one.
Yeah.
They've just, they've made one, uh,
a 20 year long song.
Yeah.
They're still playing.
They're still recording right now.
Um, uh,
let me though, let me bring it back to something you mentioned, uh, early.
Well, actually,
actually two quick things.
Uh, they've taped an entire show.
Well, uh, uh, Travis mentioned the
MTV show.
There was a whole MTV series filmed here.
Uh, AT&T wireless presents hard rock live
and, uh, with, or all the best bands performed, Evanescence, Huba, Stank, God smack and Jason's
favorite par more, um, those strong lineup there.
But my favorite thing that I saw that happened at
hard rock live, this is very Orlando and it ties it back to something Jason said earlier.
Uh, um,
so AJ McLean is playing there soon from the backstreet boys.
Yeah.
Um, and actually AJ McLean,
I don't think has played there before.
Um, is that confusing?
Yeah.
Well, a little bit because
he hasn't played, but a rock and roller who bears a little resemblance to AJ McLean may have,
I'm talking about Johnny no name.
Does anyone have any, I feel like I might be the first person to
mention this in any media ever.
That's probably right.
Uh, besides MTV news at the time.
I, uh,
basically AJ, the bad boy of the backstreet boys had to get out some of his bad boy energy
somehow outside of backstreet and, uh, he invented a kind of, it's really like a quarter committed to
Chris Gaines, another guy who's a, uh, a less committed to Chris.
Yes.
Yeah.
That with
it's confusing, but at least he had like a, a costume that made him look a little bit different.
Johnny no name just dressed as far as I can tell exactly like AJ McLean, but just, you know,
he wouldn't wear like the all white, like you'd have to in the backstreet boys.
Yeah.
Anyway,
yeah.
Johnny no name is his, his rock and roll alter ego.
Um, and, uh, okay.
This is from some
Orlando from an Orlando paper.
According to the Johnny no name official website, Johnny met the
members of his band while serving time in prison after a false arrest.
And he must be escorted onto
the stage by his parole officer, uncle marshmallow.
Now we know this mythology,
Johnny no name, the rock star whose parole officer has to stay with him.
And the parole
officer's name is uncle marshmallow.
Why is, why does he have a weird name?
He is a parole officer.
He does a normal kind of straight laced job.
Why is he uncle marshmallow?
Why is uncle in there at
all?
Is it his uncle?
Yeah.
It should be like Richard marshmallow or Henry.
I pick Henry.
I'm going with Henry.
Henry marsh officer, Henry marshmallow.
Now,
if that's your last name, then it is, you can't help that.
It's silly, but uncle only serves to
make it sillier.
Probably AJ's intended effect, but frankly, it makes me question the entire reality
of the Johnny no name universe.
This is a professional wrestling gimmick where it's like,
they're so dangerous.
They need to be escorted.
Yeah.
From the police or something.
No, he's going to like grab somebody's beer, smash it, slice up everybody in the audience
and then still don't go try to do his set.
Johnny.
So this is trying to escape maybe just the like
teen girl audience exclusively.
Yeah.
Teeny bopper, you know?
And, you know, he's not the kind
of reserved, very Christian Brian Luttrell.
Right.
He's not a good boy in the band.
He's a rock
and roll maniac.
And that brings me to this interview from MTV news, which might be the only
prior media about Johnny no name.
He's being interviewed by, uh, is this Chris Connelly?
Is
that his name?
Yeah.
Um, so it cuts.
All right.
So there's a band and they're all, uh, in different
kinds of fedoras.
One of them, one is in a red fedora.
One is in a cow hide, sleeveless
vest that frankly it, you know what it's like is like when Fred Flintstone in the 1994 movie
comes into a lot of money and goes to see the B 50 to be C 52 is incidentally anyway, that's what
this, this cool, probably going for pimp vibe.
He just, he looks like rich Fred Flintstone.
But anyway, here's the reveal of another facet of Johnny no name.
He's British.
Now does Johnny get the same kind of fanatic fan base that AJ does?
Is there screaming?
Is there
this nodding from the back here?
Yeah.
There's lots of screaming, lots of craziness, you know,
take it from him.
You know, you know, well, crazy, right.
Actually a lot more panties than,
you know, actually gets, I get all the good panties.
Good paintings.
It's always, always, always everyone.
I kissed the wide bag.
I get all the phones, man.
I mean, it sounds like the music does sound like everything in that list.
I read the MTV
film.
There sounds like I'm like a velvet revolver song.
Totally.
Yeah.
This is plausibly.
There's, there's a lot of music as bad as Johnny.
No, it's not the worst thing.
He is wearing a fedora.
Like he is about to go soft.
The mystery,
while the Johnny no name Chronicles, Johnny, no name is helping out more.
Sure.
Spade is helping
out Clive.
Oh, and it monsures speed.
I couldn't not talk about Johnny.
No name.
If you know anything else about, if you were like a backstreet fan at the time and you could point
me to any more info about Johnny known it because we like our rock star alter egos.
Those count.
Those are theme parks, Mr.
McPhisto and Chris Gaines.
And now if there was enough for a Johnny
no name episode, I wonder if you follow like sort of any of the non Timberlake careers right after
the boom or the like part of a boy band.
I bet everybody's got an interesting project.
They tried
like to break them out of the mall.
Yes.
Not that it's always going to be as rich and good as Johnny
no name, but I bet, I bet there's something like one guy tried to open up a popcorn store or
something like just random random as well.
Not necessarily alter ego cookbook or two in there
somewhere.
Yeah.
Everybody had some idea of like, well, what do we do now?
Maybe not even realizing
that like, I just give it like 10 years and then we'll just do this forever.
Chris Kirkpatrick
started shitting on the American flag.
Yeah, sure.
You wanted to be a performance.
Our idea.
There would be a series of troll movies that would need pop songs, you know, you'd have to clean up
his act again.
Anyway, so a lot of history at this place.
Yeah.
You know, if we're a lot of things
that these city, what kind of environments you wonder like why, what is the real function of
this?
But this is a legitimate concert venue that allowed artists like Johnny no name to work
something out.
So, you know, none of this pointless.
I love the dumb building.
God bless you in your
awful architecture.
And maybe just one little closing note.
Apparently, what could have been,
I think in 1990, probably Robert Earl went and met with Disney and he said, do you want a hard rock
cafe?
And Eisner said, why would we do that?
We could do our own rock and roll themed restaurant.
And then at least according to this editorial voice, Eisner lived to regret that decision.
He viewed it as like he in a way that like I don't think a modern CEO and certainly modern
politician does not do.
Eisner said, you know, we thought we were the experts.
No one could do it
as well as we could.
I was guilty of this.
Let's all do it.
Let's do it all ourselves attitude.
And making a mistake once is painful, but there has to be room for failure or no one will ever
take chances.
But they never did a rock and roll restaurant.
The great man gives us more guidance.
They never really got the restaurant.
You could enter from either side quite right.
Well,
they have it, but it's just that rain fires cafe.
I don't think you're going to enter the park
through there.
Can you?
I never tried.
I don't know.
Oh, isn't that just fully outside?
I think
it's outside.
And if you're coming from the park, if you're leaving the park, though, you can get in.
Is that it?
I think that maybe you can't enter from, I think maybe I'm wrong.
It's not like,
yes, see, we're not really sure.
We're not on.
So it's their fault for not even making it clear
to us.
You should know that if it worked, we would know.
Yeah.
And you know what?
I'm a big Eisner fan,
of course.
But now that I've heard that Eisner said no to Earl, that he spit in his face and,
and that Earl went on to work with the universal geniuses to create
Earl's did you call it Earl's limbo?
Whatever your phrase was, was perfect.
Let's call it Earl's limbo.
Yeah.
Or Earl's purgatory.
Is that better?
No,
heavier bow is better.
All right.
He went on, he crafted Earl's limbo and gave us one of the,
our favorite things in theme park.
In this case, in this episode, in this round, it's Earl takes
Eisner by a knockout punch.
Yeah.
I hate to say, I hate to admit that, but yeah, that's true.
Hooray.
I did it.
Now to go feed some hungry construction workers.
It would be funny to pit,
just like look at the list of victories and defeats for both man.
Yeah.
Like,
I don't know.
I guess Eisner, I guess ultimately there's the defeat of the entire brand going down.
That's true.
And the defeat of Bucatubepo's food being dog shit.
There's a recent interview with
Eisner, like in the last couple of weeks, that's, I saw somebody post, um, where he's, I got a football
game or whatever, the one he owns or his owns part of it.
So that gave me a little extra hope
that maybe one day we can sit him down and ask him what he's doing.
Interviews.
If he, if he'll
do an interview to promote the football franchise, that is very lucrative for him.
That's right.
Maybe there's a chance.
Um, all right.
Well, I guess that's it.
I think we made it and,
oh my gosh, there it is.
The sector stone is appearing.
Uh, I see it.
I, oh my God, it's a,
it's a brick with John Lennon's calcified pee on it.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Like the, like the splat
hardened and stayed there.
Oh, and is that also Pete Best's calcified pee as well?
Wow.
Original
Beatles drummer.
Wow.
Two separate pee pockets.
That makes it a very rare brick.
Very
rare.
Well, this is one of the finest items in our collection.
We'll have to put it in the VIP
attic where only the vibe hosts can go.
Um, and I guess with that you survived podcast, the ride,
the city walk, Orlando saga, multiverse of madness here on the second gate.
Thanks to Aaron Garner
the art.
Thanks to our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the totally rock and theme music
multiverse of madness merchant in the T public store.
Uh, keep it tuned here to the second gate
for the full saga experience.
Uh, and you know what?
Tomorrow there's a little extra treat for
it.
We don't even have to go that far.
All you gotta do is step outside the restaurant, go all
the way down the side or walk out the CBGB's room and there's one more little treat.
Thank God it
wasn't in this one.
I would have really crowded it up.
It needs a lot more time, but here's the
catch.
You would also have to take a little walk through the doors of a cool place called club three,
even cooler than CBGB, you might say.
I would say.
So if you want to hear and really to get the full
saga, you're going to want to want to unlock that last sector.
So just not should not shit up to
that level right here on the Patreon and you'll also get all the other ones at club three where
our motto like Hard Rock Cafe is also love all, serve all.
Love all, serve all.
That's right.
We stole it from them.
Don't tell them.