Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Multiverse of madness.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
Day two, we are back.
I hope you listened yesterday.
I hope the only way you're consuming this is every day.
Because hearing it back after the fact, with days in between,
it's not how we're doing it.
It shouldn't be how you're doing it.
I'm Scott Gardner.
There's Mike Carlson.
Hey, I'm here and I hope the reality for you listeners is setting in
to know that this is coming out every day and that you're not going to be able to keep up with it.
Unless you give up like important parts of your daily routine.
Yeah.
So you need to realize that right now.
There's Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Yeah.
We're asking a lot of you.
Look, if you're, if you're worried about your phone storage space,
turn off the automatic download.
Follow the episode.
I don't know what.
What are you doing?
It's madness.
We need those downloads.
That equals cash.
Get the downloads, but turn on the delete after you listen.
No, don't do that.
What if they need to listen to it again?
Patreon ultimately is the answer to all of this.
For the full multiverse of madness experience, go to patreon.
com slash podcast thread.
It'll solve all of this somehow.
I would imagine.
I hope.
But hey, that's not everybody.
We got to bring the other, the other guy in the mix.
Wait, he's not here again.
So we have to say the full thing.
Basin is now Sunook.
Is now California's soul.
Boys, boys, it's good to be back.
Hey, hey, how you guys doing?
You guys, you spent the night together.
We can spend the night together.
That's the way it sounds.
I stayed at Mike's place, man.
Yeah, yeah.
You've also to catch you up from, you know, yesterday.
Not only is the sector keeper joining us every day, he's also crashing with us.
Yeah.
Does he have anywhere else to go?
That's kind of in question, but I don't know.
We're trying to be gentlemen here.
Yeah, it's just kind of a little bit of a rough patch.
And I'm so thankful for it.
Mike, man, your place is, you got a sweet little pad.
Yeah, I had to clear.
He's sleeping on a shelf.
I had to clear some mighty mutanimals action figures away for him to have some space.
Yeah, I couldn't believe it.
When I walked in, I was like, is this your apartment or a KB toy store, man?
Yeah, he said that, which is a good burn.
Funny burns.
It's a nice thing for it.
That's what he wants.
He's a child.
I was like, I giggled with Kalee when you said it.
Yeah, yeah.
We stayed up most of the night, man, just playing.
Yeah, we were playing.
And yeah, I just recently got the sewer playset so I can really like make a little like diorama
of the Ninja Turtles characters hanging out.
Where do they, where do the ones, what do the ones go when you're not playing with them?
Because you have.
Oh, there's, well, they're on different shelves.
There's other little dioramas.
There's a street diorama.
I can put them on and then I can.
There's a lot of different places for them if they're not participating in the actual
sewer layer diorama.
I know I'm scheduled to be passed off to Scott tonight, but Scott, can I stay at Mike's tonight?
Oh, geez.
I mean, I was really looking forward to it, but oh, if you might, I don't want to get
in the way of all that fun.
You know what?
All right.
I guess I can deal.
Oh, man.
Let's bring our guest into it.
The first.
We have so many questions so far.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, you'll be an audience surrogate.
We can, we can catch you up.
Hey, the first guest of the saga joining us from Peacock's Killing It and from, of course,
Illumination's Villain Con Minion Blast at Universal Studios Florida.
It's Evan Susser.
Hey, guys.
Excited to be here.
Excited to be returning to CityWalk, but a different CityWalk, and excited to finally
face be face to face with the Sector Keeper himself.
I know he just beamed in for our assignment last time.
You guys are together now.
I was curious, the Sector Keeper, you are the same Sector Keeper from the CityWalk saga
in California, or is this from like another dimension?
No, no, I'm the same one.
I got a little confused by the multiverse of madness.
Excuse me, the multiverse.
Multiverse.
I didn't see it written.
I heard it said, I like that a lot.
This is good because you may not, you may not be the only one with questions.
I don't understand it all now.
And naturally, so, and you're, the conceit is that this is being recorded here in California?
Yes.
Yeah.
We were sent on a mission.
So why did he need to, does Sector Keeper, don't you usually live at CityWalk in California?
Yeah, it's like my home base.
Right.
So why do you need to sleep in people's houses?
You're still only 15 minutes away.
You missed a lot of story yesterday.
Yeah, no, the multiverse, he frees him up to kind of go, he can transport wherever using,
you know, jump points and gates and wormholes.
Oh, okay, yes, that makes sense.
Jump points.
Got it.
Sensor Jump Points.
Jump points.
I understand.
He's lived in our real world for many years.
He had a job at Cricket Wireless for many years.
So he's sort of just been hanging out.
Kind of a liminal scan.
I got caught up in what I'll call a commune.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So you're pretty self-sufficient, it seems like.
So then why do you need to be sleeping at people's houses?
I just, it's nice to have like…
Oh, it's just fun.
Well, like Jason said, three hots and a cot, man.
I get it.
Yeah, okay.
He's also…
Back in the park.
Yeah, yeah.
A lot of his, there's a bunch of his ghost cousins who seem to be like bilking him out
of his watery winnings.
He won a Powerball, naturally.
At least.
I won the Powerball.
Oh, cool, congratulations.
Well, it's actually been a curse.
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
I'm one of those kind of like cautionary tales.
Oh, no.
I did a Reddit on it.
I did an AMI.
No, but I don't need to look it up.
I got it.
Seriously.
Spend some more time with it.
I want to hear the whole story.
He also asked a bunch of questions and was trying to get out of the questions almost immediately.
Eventually, I had a spill of questions.
No, the point is it's like, you know, it's kind of, we've ended up in this multiverse
situation.
It's like, you know, it's a multiverse scenario.
Like the kind you'd see…
That time he did say multiverse.
He said multiverse.
No, no, I'm saying the multiverse is a multiverse scenario.
It's like the kind of thing you'd see in a movie, like a superhero movie.
I don't know.
I didn't make that connection until now, but I get it now.
Yeah, well, it's kind of like something in like The Flash.
Right.
Do you ever see The Flash?
Do you ever get a chance to check out that flick?
You know, I have seen The Flash.
What did you think of The Flash?
You know, I didn't really care for it.
I understand this has been a source of some debate on the podcast.
Yeah, yes.
Interesting.
That's weird that you say that you didn't care for it because when this came up for
the first time on a Patreon episode called Holiday in Holodomes…
Yeah, Jason's birthday shot.
Jason's birthday shot was deviated from when Mike said one of the most insane things I've
heard a person say in a while.
What you said in the episode was that the Ezra Miller, The Flash from last year was
not as bad as everyone is saying it is.
Yes, that is what I said.
And I screamed at this.
The only logical reaction.
The maddest I've ever seen him for real.
I did.
I leaned back from the microphone.
Mike!
Jason said, please don't fight on my birthday.
I just started bawling.
I think it was stored up.
Yeah, that was from an old memory coming back.
But here's what, now because I've questioned this opinion, because The Flash, many people
have said it is quite terrible and I would certainly side with them.
This was not your feeling apparently and what you spit out was other people you respect
agree with the movie.
Well, hold on.
What I said was The Flash was not that bad.
First of all, which is not The Flash is amazing or The Flash is my favorite movie.
Oh, I know.
I know.
You went back and listened.
And then I specifically said the parts of The Flash I like, including the first half
and what aspects of it I like.
And then I said, I believe, correct me if I'm wrong, that other people agreed with me.
Only about that part?
Well, I was specifying the parts where someone would agree with me versus maybe somebody
saying the whole Flash movie was good or not that good.
In my head, we were still at general movie.
But, Keeper, you want to go get a hoagie or something?
I feel like we're not needed for the podcast.
No, chime in.
Brother, I thought you'd never ask.
Yeah, you guys go get a bite.
I think, look, I think, yes, in general, I was saying I was enjoying The Flash more than I thought
because I went into it thinking, oh, this is going to be a big pile of dog shit.
And it was not a big pile of dog shit.
It was maybe a smaller one.
Okay.
And what you're saying is very reasonable.
I still think it's a crackpot opinion.
Well, that's fine.
I think Giants is the only one.
I watched this film.
Somehow I got roped into this whole thing.
Well, I got screamed at to say, give up your sources.
Name names, I said.
I would go up so quickly if I was under interrogation.
If I was being waterboarded, it would come out in two seconds.
Who else said something positive about The Flash?
I can't point fingers.
I flipped on Sam Bankman Friedman.
Oh, no.
Were you mixed up in that, Sector Keeper?
Because of a jump point?
Because of a jump point.
Jump point brought him right into the crypto.
Yeah.
This is hard.
I won the Powerball.
Were you in that relationship with him and the girl?
Yeah, the polycule.
I flipped on the polycule.
No, it's good to recap.
No, no, no.
No, and to clarify, this one's not change.
It's not a mollycule.
It's a polycule.
That one is regular.
That's regular.
One dimension.
Many bodies.
Under this pressure, you named your own wife and you named Evan Suser as a person who agreed
that in my head, we could parse what that is, but I feel like it was saying that you,
that Suser generally thought The Flash was not as bad as everyone's been saying.
I believe the sequence of words backs what I'm saying up.
But it was in the heat of the moment.
I don't know.
Maybe things were placed in the wrong position as far as, so I'm not even sure.
I can't quite remember.
It's a real Rochamon.
It's a bit of a Rochamon.
I even couldn't, you know, I wasn't under such duress.
Actually, the biggest.
A movie I do like.
The biggest.
Well, I hate that.
Not a divisive opinion.
Is it part of a cinematic universe of some kind?
If only.
Or Salo was a chump.
He only made one movie at a time.
He wasn't setting up nine.
I should have said, you know what I should have said?
Andrew Grissom, friend of the show, is also a liker of parts of The Flash.
What do you mean?
I'll investigate that one.
Text them right now.
Say, are there parts of The Flash you like?
Or amused or enjoyable?
Let me get into, let me bring up, because this opinion stayed with me for hours.
We were done with the recording for hours.
And I texted the both of you and I said, guys, you're insane.
And Suser was like, what are we talking about?
And I said, wait a minute, I have the transcripts.
The two Esras is one of the most irritating things I've ever seen.
That's the part I was talking about.
You're insane.
Your response was LOL what?
All caps.
And soon after you said, I said I hated the movie.
You know, this is like pretty niche and specific.
And we should get onto the much broader appeal of breaking down Orlando City Walk.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
We can do a tangent time, by the way.
Oh, sure.
We can cut this off.
But we better set it soon because I have more stuff.
I have things.
We'll say this is like a portal.
We're in a portal right now.
Well, that's true.
We're all just, we're all slowing down time to talk about this for who knows, an hour,
an hour and a half.
And if there's a cosmic treadmill in here, oh boy.
Well, it's going to take a while.
I guess I'm curious just for your thoughts about this, because I felt like we're discovering that in that moment.
I think that Mike's Mike had severely misinterpreted your take on this.
Yeah, I would say there's a little bit of a misinterpretation, but also maybe a little bit of, you know, a little bit of a witch hunt going on here, Scott.
Who me?
Does this seem like the kind of thing I do on this?
I did not enjoy the movie.
I watched it, I think, partially because Carlson Mike had said, oh, it's actually not that bad.
And I think I initiated the conversation by saying you're wrong.
Well, you said I'm not sure if it's not so, but you are not sure I can get on board with the it's not so bad thing.
Yes.
And then I think that, you know, but Mike's a very persuasive and likeable guy.
And you know, even on text and even on text, it comes through.
Yeah, but the part with the as a person, I guess, got some other parts.
I guess we broke some other parts that I really didn't like, including him saving a baby in space.
Now that's a different we all deserve.
I I believe the baby scene is good.
So the Mike and you and you're trying to save face right now.
And you're doing that by saying I have compiled a flash report.
This is a printout with a logo of the physical report is a revelation that Mike has a functioning printer.
And you said that to me once before you're baffled by someone having a printer.
I all mine.
I'd like just keep breaking.
Like how many printers are broke?
Two or three.
I feel like I don't think it's a strange thing.
So do you have a printer?
I do have a printer.
I think a lot of people.
I'm going to the library.
I'm going to FedEx, Kinko's.
They give away printers.
I got too many printers.
I got one in the garage.
It's not up.
Give one to Jason.
Give it to Jason.
What kind of printer is it?
You're going to ask.
I just take it.
You want to go to the library.
You want to pay per copy.
Is it a 3D printer?
That's a gift.
Are you paying taxes?
You get gifted a plastic printer.
Is it a sandwich printer?
What's in your report, Michael?
Well, I just have time code and different lines and things.
We don't have to read all of it.
I'm just saying I went through some of the scenes that I liked.
I said two and basically the way HBO Max or now Max plays it, it kind of counts down sort of what you have left.
So, you know, two hours, 23 minutes, 29 seconds.
I like the actor playing the barista.
And I believe I haven't even agreed with me that he liked this guy and some of the lines, especially this.
You can't rush a good sandwich dude line.
I believe we agreed.
Wait a minute.
Me saying that a movie is a giant pile of shit, like truly an era defining shows you everything that's wrong with that's rotten in our culture right now.
A movie like that can have two, one actor who doesn't fuck up.
There's a couple more things in this report.
This is a report here fully of different things we'd like.
Again, I don't have to read all of it.
I'm just saying there's enough things to add up here.
There's a lot of pages.
Well, go to the middle.
What's in the middle?
And publish the whole report.
Publish the flash paper.
All right.
I'll publish the whole.
Hold on.
Where's the middle?
And if things are lagging in the episode, throw out a random part of the flash you like.
That'll pick it up.
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
Hold on one second.
Where's the middle?
Blow away in the wind.
We got the garage door open.
All right.
Hold on.
Let me just read.
Let me read the middle of this thing.
Once you finish reading this, can you explain how this leaked on WikiLeaks?
When Ezra says that he goes, he goes, Ezra says the mic just cut out when I tried to talk.
That's never happened before.
The mic cut out.
It's the ghost of Nick Mundy.
Oh, no, it is.
He teleported.
Wow.
The multiverse is full of magical things.
Do you need to replug in your microphone?
No, it's fine now.
Wow.
It literally shorted out when I was trying to talk.
It's like the world's trying to tell you something about the flash.
When Ezra says he has to, he goes, shit.
And he goes, I have to shit.
That's funny.
That was a funny line.
Did I agree with that?
We never talked about that line.
I can't imagine I agreed with that.
I think you forgot it, though.
We never talked about it.
Also, in your text exchange, there was something you said.
OK, after a while of Carlson defending it, I maybe said, I guess that the two Ezras are an OK part.
When you said it was the best stuff in the movie, but I said the movie was terrible.
So to me, that was a very low bar.
I don't believe I believe.
I mean, fair enough, he was being nice to me.
He never said terrible.
You did say you were right.
You said you were right.
The movie really fell off in the second half.
Yes.
It does get even worse.
The second half of the movie is bad.
Don't get me wrong.
You are not arguing this.
There's a part where they call Boba Fett, the guy who plays Boba Fett.
You remember this?
No.
And then he thinks he's the he thinks he's Aquaman.
And he said he's like, is this Arthur Curry?
And he goes, yeah, yeah.
And then he goes, is your wife the queen of Atlantis?
And then he looks over and this is like a lady with a sweatshirt looking at the TV.
Funny, funny stuff.
You don't even remember.
I know we're rushing.
We that one.
And I don't want to do this.
I think I need like a five minute breakdown of that to understand what that block of words even meant.
All right.
Well, we don't have to laugh.
I'm trying to.
You should laugh.
First of all, just do me the favor and everyone laugh about it right now.
Is it just that he's a guy?
Only says he's the only true friend.
He's going to a different universe where there's no Aquaman, where there's not any meta humans anymore.
Oh, OK.
So he's calling around to figure out who actually is still around.
Boys, boys.
You're probably a good time to remember that the sector keeper has in the past, you've, you know, coughed and lost strength when we weren't staying on topic.
If you feel if you need to cough, feel free to cough.
Oh, goodness gracious.
I'm just trying to keep wrap my head around what's.
You seem like you fell asleep during most of that with a cigarette hanging out of your mouth and you really should be careful about that.
Yeah.
Get off my back, man.
All right.
This is what's going to happen if you go stay with Jason.
If you spend the weekend with then he's going to be.
Wait a minute.
I should be building up Jason.
No, you'll have a fun time with Jason.
Yeah.
This guy has the hot dogs for every meal.
You'll have so many hot dogs.
That's right.
Get over there.
Jason can prepare hot dogs nine different ways.
Sure.
Boiled pan fried boiled then pan fried.
Oh, wow.
Baked.
Grilled.
Huh?
Blended.
Put into a blender.
Drank like a milkshake.
That's a little ridiculous, but yeah.
I'm just trying to get to nine.
Sous vide.
Raw.
It's kind of nasty.
What are we at?
Seven.
Okay.
Broiled.
Different from boiled.
Yeah.
One letter off.
In blankets?
Yeah.
In blankets.
Blanketed.
Like baked.
Hey.
We didn't even get to deep frying.
Yeah.
That's true.
Bonus points.
Mike, can I stay at Jason's tonight?
Well, if.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Yay.
Have fun.
Hot dogs, 10 ways for you.
Okay.
Well, look, maybe we should move to our assignments.
Sector keeper, can you give us today's.
Susser, you'll be interested to know it's now not just sectors.
It's also there's phases.
Oh yeah.
I figured.
Okay.
Yes.
Of course.
Boys, boys.
Susser.
Thank you so much.
You give me strength.
Thank you for being here.
I don't know why I'm starting this.
Like a keynote.
You're a good person.
A good father.
Phase one, sector two.
Voodoo donut.
Auntie Anne's.
And waterfront kiosks.
North.
Or as I know it, sapphire.
Oh, wait, you've given us a new mechanism here.
So north.
Okay.
Well, there's different gemstones.
Designate different kiosk zones.
Okay.
So if you had a jump point, make sure that you have that particular gemstone.
You have to have it with you, the gemstone?
Someone should have it on.
Oh.
Wait a minute.
Sorry.
This is like that flash joke.
Say it again.
The, I, in order, if we're at a jump point, we need to make sure that we have our sapphire
gem that we'll get after the end of this.
Yeah.
And the joke is I've got a shit.
He says it is funny.
I wish there were two sector keepers.
Oh, maybe in the future.
Yay.
Oh, the flash has given us all kinds of ideas.
Okay.
Well, I think you, you, oh, and you know what?
A little bit of backstory.
We, Evan, we had you on recently to talk about the ride that you wrote, Villain Con, Minion
Blast.
And when you were down there doing actual Universal Studios work, we pounced on you.
Wait a minute.
Suster's there.
We got to get him to do something.
This was a long time ago now.
I have no idea how long ago.
A long time.
But you, you said, hey, while you're down there, can you head over to City Walk?
And, you know, it was pretty busy when I was down there.
It was, and I was like, you know, from start to finish, it was a 12 hour day.
But, you know, day ended and I said, well, I've made a promise.
Sorry.
I was staying.
Much less well paid work.
I was staying at Royal Pacific, not too bad, on Universal.
And hopped on the boat and took a little cruise down to City Walk, which I don't know.
I assume you guys have, you know, a little bit like painted the picture of what Orlando City Walk is like.
Maybe not enough still.
But the fact that you do take like, that it is all along a lake or a big waterway and that boats or water taxis, as we'll get into tomorrow, maybe it should have been in your sector.
We had flash stuff to go over though.
But the hotels connect City Walk and then you can walk to the theme parks.
Yeah, so it was, it was really great just to be on that boat and just see, I could see as I approached the Voodoo Donuts, which on the one hand I said, is this insane?
There's a Voodoo Donuts that I can go to any time that's 12 minutes from my house and I'm exhausted, but I got to get on this boat.
This specific Voodoo Donuts.
I go to this specific Voodoo Donuts, which I don't even think they have a regionally specific menu, but okay.
And do you like the first Voodoo Donuts?
No, I don't.
Yeah, no, it's not particularly, but I, so I got there and it's so much more as you mentioned Sector Keeper because it's also the waterfront north or sapphire kiosk.
Yes, yes.
So the kiosk.
Good man, good man.
The kiosk for me is what really got exciting.
Should we jump right into my experience or is there more that you guys want to talk about or set up in this?
No, and I don't know how much order matters.
If there's a flow through this that works for you, I think now that you've established that you're a good man, Sector Keeper is going to let you do whatever you want.
Well, first of all, right away I see the kiosk that is Fat Tuesday, which is kind of a New Orleans themed, you know, getting like daiquiris and those kind of drinks, frozen daiquiris.
Big tall mushy colorful drinks.
Yes, that you can drink right there on the boardwalk.
While you walk.
At City Walk and I was like, whoa, hey, we're not in California City Walk right away.
I'm realizing that.
I'm like, oh, the vibe is different here, especially at the north or sapphire kiosk.
That's right.
We haven't talked about this yet.
How, you know, if you remember the original City Walk saga that we went to a dueling piano bar and there was all kinds of crazy logic of like somebody has to walk your drink.
Yeah, like a 10 foot walkway.
Just do it all the insane liquor rules.
None of that in City Walk.
Orlando is Vegas.
You can just walk around with drinks.
It did feel like Vegas.
You know, this I think that City Walk here feel in California feels like a place for like middle schoolers to hang out.
And this felt like, oh, this is like high school or like first year of college.
Yeah, but not our age.
So right away I got in there and I just got myself a drink, a very sugary sweet drink.
It was not great, but very fun to be able to just have that thing.
Now something to establish.
I kind of I forgot that there was a mini Fat Tuesday kiosk.
Fat Tuesday.
And I'll confer the set your cupers.
As far as I recall, you laid out, you gave us a guide map and Fat Tuesday, the standing establishment is in a different sector and even phase, I believe.
So we'll deal with that one down the road.
Of course, of course.
All right.
Well, I don't want to talk about.
No, don't, no, no, anything that's applicable about yours.
No, but please.
Good.
We said good man, good man.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Then you also have the Auntie Anne's kiosk, which, you know, is great.
I was easy to just get a stop by, get some pretzel bites.
I got those.
It was nice.
I sat in the chairs.
It's really like a nice little setup that you can just be enjoying beyond the water with your daiquiri.
Wow.
Now, this weirdly waterfront kiosks are kind of like a general area, but the city walk map has Auntie Anne's as a separate thing.
So Auntie Anne's by their designation doesn't count within the waterfront kiosk.
I think I have, I think I have a little bit of, because I did some investigating while I was down there.
Oh, wow.
Then, unfortunately, there was also the, the wraps and braids kiosk where you could get your hair braided or face paint.
It was unfortunately closed because I would have done that.
Would you have done that for us?
Yeah, I think that would have been a good picture.
And then surprisingly, there is also, and I asked you guys how to say it and I now I'm forgetting, but an anime or manga kiosk.
Yeah, you got your Nerudo, your Dragon Ball Z.
Diamond Slayer.
What's that?
I don't know that one.
So maybe it's video games.
I don't know, but it definitely looks like there's some Dragon Ball stuff.
It was, and I asked them, I said, is this a permanent, like this is always here.
And they explained to me that some of the kiosks rotate and change what they are.
So maybe that's why Auntie Anne's is on the map because maybe it's a permanent one and maybe some of these other ones kind of.
Portals, portals.
Yeah, they rotate it through different portals.
And then they have, in addition to the Voodoo Donuts, the store, they also have the giant chair of donuts.
Which I don't know.
Do they have that here in California?
The throne is really good.
I, of course, got a picture on the throne.
Jason did one right.
I got a picture on the throne.
It was late at night and there was also a long line for Voodoo Donuts.
Insanely long line at that location.
Is that not the case in Hollywood?
There's always something of a line.
I've seen it.
I've seen it where it's short.
But oftentimes there is a line to go and get it, get them.
And I asked myself at that point, do I really need to extend this trip for 30 more minutes to just get the exact same donut?
There was a kiosk.
There was a little shed where if you mobile ordered, you could pick up your Voodoo Donuts there.
And it seemed sporadically open.
I did not see it.
Separate from the, more closer to the water.
I did not see it open.
And I thought to myself, well, if I come on the podcast and say I didn't go, it will be very disappointing and sad for the listeners.
And it might make the centerkeeper lose strength.
Yes, thank you.
So my two options were either to lie or to tell the truth.
But if I were to tell the truth, I felt like I would have to do it.
Because I couldn't say I didn't do it.
I could either, if I wanted to tell the truth, I would have to wait in line, get a Voodoo Donut and another donut or whatever.
Or lie and make up a whole story about how I got it and what I got.
There's no way you could just make that up.
There's no way you could just look up what they have on the website.
The audience would know.
It was pretty good.
I thought it was pretty good.
But to make a lie more believable, do you even introduce the idea of a lie?
Because why would a liar do that?
Why would they say that they thought about lying if they were going to lie?
So I contemplated all of that, but I said, hey, for the podcast, I'm going to do it.
I waited on the long line.
I took some pictures for some other families.
And I got a Voodoo Donut and the Bubblegum one, which I believe you can also get in California.
I asked, are there any special ones?
And they didn't hear me and I didn't ask again.
And I got my donuts.
And at that point, I was very tired and kind of in a grumpy mood.
And I waited in line to get back on the boat.
That was your entire outing.
That was my entire outing.
What was the amount of time that all took?
Well, the whole beginning part was probably because I was rocking and rolling at the beginning.
I got like no line for the margarita, no line for getting the Anteans.
I got a conversation.
So that was all like probably 10 minutes.
I took a picture and then it was like probably 30 minutes waiting for Voodoo Donuts.
Now you were…
The whole trip was 20 minutes and I lied.
Well, this is where, you know, this is a pod.
We show our work on this podcast as evidenced by the forms that Mike brought out.
I don't suppose you have a photograph of one of those Voodoo Donuts, do you?
Let's see.
What do I have in my universe?
The photo on the throne.
So he definitely did the throne.
He did do the throne.
And it's up to you.
Does he need, does his mouth need to have touched a donut in order for his participation to qualify?
Well, he's introduced an interesting aspect that I never thought of is that you could lie.
Yeah.
You've never, like as a being, you've never thought that you could lie?
Well, you know, just, you know, I'm just trying to wrap my mind around it.
It's like the invention of lying.
What if there wasn't lying and then one guy thought of lying?
That's a pretty good movie idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It could be.
Am I wrong in that you learned about lying in the Downtown Disney ordeal?
For the first time?
For the first time.
I think that would seem right.
I don't know.
But it was four years ago.
Who knows?
I think someone on this podcast in six years learned about lying.
Oh, he's smoking.
All those clove cigarettes.
Yeah, that happens.
They cloud the mind, you know?
But I'll say the, you know, this conundrum that Cesar brings up is still one of the simplest aspects of the ordeal.
Yeah.
Of the saga, excuse me.
No, much like The Flash, you learn a lot of information.
You're onboarded with a lot of stuff.
And if you understand all six levels of it, you're laughing.
That's this series.
Cesar, could you question Susser and learn just by kind of looking into his soul?
Because you're sort of an otherworldly.
So just maybe ask him a few simple questions and see.
I am part of, once you die, your spirit is almost like a lie detector of sorts.
Oh, great.
Oh, perfect.
So, Susser, if you're comfortable.
I suppose I am.
I will now stare into your soul.
Yes.
You went to Voodoo Donuts.
You sat in the throne.
I did.
Yes.
You stood in line.
While standing in line, could you see a menu?
Could I see a menu?
No, actually.
The menu is when you walk into the store itself.
It's not out when you're outside when you're waiting in line.
So you have been looking at the menu.
What do you see?
When I reach that point.
When you reach that point.
Well, it's big and bright.
And.
Okay, checks out.
It has a list of the donuts.
Sure.
It has coffee.
It has coffee as well.
Do you have any idea how many months ago as we record this, this occurred?
Was it in 2023?
I believe so.
Okay, but maybe early in 2023.
Another point of clarification.
You also had just worked 12 hours and we're doing this as a favor.
Yes.
That's correct.
Okay.
So you're looking at the menu and what catches your eye?
Well, nothing, to be honest.
Because I was also, as you said, it would have been 12 hours and I was doing it as a favor.
And typically, you know, if I'm on another food driven podcast, I would maybe, you know, really want to get the best thing on the menu or a real comprehensive thing.
And I had also, as a part of that 12 hour day, I think I had, I did a food tasting for desserts and treats at Minion Cafe.
So I had already eaten a fair bit of donuts.
Of sugar.
Jason's hat just flew over.
That's your job?
Quite a bit.
So either that was part of the motivating factor that told me you don't need to have a donut.
Just lie and say you went.
Or that was a motivating factor that made me say, I'm just going to get the Voodoo donut and I guess a bubblegum one or if they have a special one, which they didn't seem to immediately suggest.
You could have just texted me and I would have just said like, just save yourselves some, just say the phrase buttermilk bar and we'll move on.
To say the phrase maple long john.
You wouldn't have had the ghost of a child interrogated.
Yeah, we wouldn't have had to do all that waterboarding that we cut, you know.
What do you think now?
I think that he went.
I think that he had a donut.
Wow.
Thank you.
I feel like, you know where you got me was with the specifics of the menu and it was over here but not up there.
That did seem kind of, that felt specific.
I guess you could have seen all that without going into the store.
He said the menu was bright.
That's an adjective.
You remember that?
From experience, yeah.
Does anybody, what do we think in general?
And I cannot believe this.
I was looking through my pictures and I, because again, I was thinking about this whole thing as I was online and I thought, oh, I'll bring up the idea and I could lie.
And then I said, well, you got to remember to take a picture with the donut.
And I am sure I did, but I cannot find the picture.
Oh, well, that's very convenient.
It is.
But also, why would I bring that up at this point?
We've moved on.
Only the sector keeper can say if we've moved on.
Yeah, he's the one who's been put in.
And the throne is inside, yes.
The throne is outside.
Oh.
Wait, the sector keeper didn't know that?
Well, he's not really, he keeps the jump points.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, he hasn't been to CityWalkerLand.
He's concerned about it.
Takes a lot out of him.
It takes a lot.
Oh, goodness.
I don't know.
But part of my point of talking about the kiosks of the Waterfront North or Sapphire is that to make the case of this, this sector is so much more than the Voodoo Donuts, even though that seems to be leading the name.
I think that it should be called Waterfront Kiosks North and Voodoo Donuts.
And Ante-Anns is separate because it's on the map.
Don't forget Ante-Anns.
But that could be last maybe?
I'll also say right behind Voodoo Donuts, there is a giant, always empty bathroom and some very old press penny machines that I somehow managed to get all four of these slightly different, incredible Hulk designs on the map.
All these really they're all partially functioning.
No, the other ones like Spider-Man and SpongeBob.
But there is one machine that has probably been there since like 2000.
That is just slight variations on the Hulk.
Buy an empty, like an always empty bathroom?
Buy an always empty bathroom.
So you it's a random one you get or?
I.
Were you playing it like a slot?
How many pennies do you carry with you?
Well, I don't have any on me right now.
Well, how many smash pennies do you have on you?
From going to the train tracks?
Yeah.
Whoops.
But did you bring pennies to CityWalk to get the press pennies?
Well, I don't think you do that anymore.
These ones.
Oh, they just come out because they cost.
I thought it was like a like a $2 and then you put a penny in.
No, the penny just comes out.
You can pay cash or you can do like Apple Pay.
Really?
And then it's kind of like you sort of don't know what you're going to get.
Or I just didn't understand it.
But we just had to turn in the crank.
But I did get all four incredible.
For how much money?
$100.
At least $5.
Like at least.
What a value.
But isn't the fun of the press penny machine that you put your penny in and then you see
what like it transforms your penny?
Well, back in the day.
Okay, so but now they have their own pennies set aside in the machine for you.
So if you just have a card or a phone.
That seems less fun, doesn't it?
Am I crazy?
You're not watching your penny.
I think it's been a long time since that's been the case.
I think they've been running a scam on this for…
Did the Disneyland ones do that?
Well, the Disneyland 100 coins that Tarrant Killam was talking about,
I did Apple pay on one of those once and I wanted one coin and they're like,
here's your four coins.
And like it was like $20.
Hey guys.
So you paid $20 for four pennies?
I was pimped into buying four.
No, not the Hulk.
But the Disney anniversary ones.
Right, but are those pennies or are those just different coins?
Those are like slugs.
Those are like the size of like half dollars.
So it can't just be the cost of a penny.
Because…
No, I understand.
That's not a business.
You're paying for the labor.
No, I understand that.
For the labor of the machine.
I understand that, but I'm saying they've taken away…
It used to be a quarter and a penny and then it was 50 cents and a penny and now…
Yeah.
They just fucking go wild.
So they've taken away the transformational aspect of it.
I think that maybe has been decades that there has been smashed penny machines.
Really?
This reminds me of the episode where we went to, it was the K1 Speed, where we went to
it was an arcade and it's not tokens, it's a card.
And you guys are both like, oh, that's the new thing now is the cards.
They're doing the cards these days.
I'm like, I think it's been 15 years or more of cards.
It's been a look at…
Dave and Buster's have been around for a while with those cards.
I agree with that.
But they are doing cards now.
Deep in the card era.
Well, I'll do a little research and find out if there's any real machines left in this
world, okay?
The authentic machines.
Well, you know what?
But I don't think that matters.
So what you need is a machine that is crushing your penny, built this millennium, built
since 2000.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, they still make new ones the old fashioned way.
Right.
Or also, has it never been your penny getting crushed?
Has this always been?
Holy shit.
Whoa.
I don't know.
It could be fake the whole time.
It's just pressed copper that's already pressed.
They might have them already.
No, no, no.
There's not a copper heating mechanism in many of these machines.
Wow, real maybe.
I don't know.
I mean, this is a thing at carnivals.
Can we trust the carnival to not do tricks?
No, we can't.
Wow.
Oh my gosh.
I also should say I patronize one of the kiosks.
Which kiosk?
Whoa.
There was a kiosk of like…
In Sapphire Sector?
Yeah, in Sapphire Sector.
Okay, go ahead.
I don't know, and this was after I had been there.
Yes.
You didn't ask any of them if they had seen somebody go into a voodoo donuts or not, did you?
No, I didn't.
Okay, good.
Which would have been answered with like…
Yes.
What?
Yes, of course.
Yeah, I see people all day right next to it.
There's a photo of a man.
Yes, he's at the premiere of the movie Fist Fight.
You've seen this man at…
Anyway, which kiosk?
There was a sports kiosk because it was still football season.
Oh.
And it was mostly like teens from the Northeast, so it was like Patriots and Eagles, but then
all the Florida colleges.
And Jane went to UCF, and she's like, oh, look at that UCF tumbler.
And I was like, oh, well, let's get you a souvenir.
So I bought her like the metal cup with the metal straw and lid and stuff.
That's interesting.
So one of the rotating kiosks became a football kiosk.
Yeah, I could see it changing of like when football season's over, maybe it's basketball
and then maybe it's baseball.
The multiverses twisted, man.
Yeah.
Yeah, it goes, they go from one reality to the other into different universes.
So the baseball one like goes into a wormhole and that kiosk moves into a different reality.
Well, there might be a step between phases where the three of us get crushed like pennies.
That's how…
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
It has to be.
It's infinite.
Yeah, that's how it works.
And some of the pennies already were in the machine.
Ooh, let down.
I know.
Let's not get mixed up with those.
Are there other sectors of other places?
I don't know.
I mean, he's been a little ambiguous, I'd say, about like what we're trying to solve here.
I can't get into it.
This is a great question, but I can't get into them.
I understand.
No, City Walk Orlando is not as simple as it seems.
Oh, yeah.
That's all he'll say to us.
Makes sense.
For every beginning, there's an end.
Right.
And every end, there's a beginning.
Oh, okay.
I don't know if you've ever thought about that.
Wow, wow.
I think the cigarette's laced that I'm smoking.
You're talking crazy talk.
Sector Keeper, I didn't know you liked to get wet.
Yeah, man.
What?
What does getting wet mean when you lace a cigarette?
There's PCP in that.
Oh, that's what that means?
Did you know that?
Yeah.
I don't remember your training day movie, your famous scenes from the long, long ago
movie Training Day.
When he goes, I didn't know you liked to get wet.
He smells.
And he's laced Ethan Hawke's cigarette with PCP.
Oh, my goodness.
Or joint with PCP.
Usually, when Jason says, oh, you want to get wet, he means go on the Popeye ride at
Islands of Adventure.
Yeah.
Not smoke PCP.
Or he wants to do a cannonball in the wave pool.
Yeah.
On the high dive.
Have you guys, or Sector Keeper, maybe you know, how often do people jump into the river
at City Walk or the lake or whatever?
The waterways.
I do know, but I'll let these guys go.
Is that a problem?
It seems like it would be, especially with Fat Tuesday, you know, supplying.
Yeah, yeah.
It takes away inhibitions.
I don't know.
I've never looked up the crime blotter on that.
I'll say a general thing.
I was talking to a friend of the show, texting with a friend of the show, Matt Cardona, and
he made it seem like City Walk used to be a hot spot, a wilder spot, perhaps.
And now it is not.
Where is the hot spot now?
Or just it's…
I think it's maybe on iDrive somewhere more so than it is City Walk.
Yeah.
Disney Springs and City Walk definitely seem like they pulled back on operating hours.
It was like 2020.
They're not looking maybe for it to be a place where people are inspired to jump in the water
anymore.
It feels like maybe that even though you can still drink and walk around, it doesn't feel
lively at night in some of these spots.
Not that that's a bad thing, as we'll figure out as we go on.
But I'm sure there were some incidents where someone had, you know, too many Long Island
ice teas at an Alter Bridge concert at Hard Rock Live.
Oh, that's true.
Something stumbled out, you know.
Is Alter Bridge a religious band?
I think it's all like…
It's the members of Creed without Scott Stapp.
Yeah.
So it's a little harder, but it's got some good messages, you know?
It's harder without…
They're finally free to rock as hard as they always wanted to.
Stapp was dragging them down.
They were all changed after they filmed that music video in Universal Florida.
Well, let's why don't we get closer to maybe a Jason definition of getting wet, which is
having an odd type of pretzel because, Mike?
Well, you know, can I just quickly say that I got a Voodoo doughnut.
Yes.
And I got it to go and I ordered it on the mobile, on the app.
And I have a photo of it.
Did you get it at the shed?
You keep saying shed and I'm confused by that.
It just seems like a really unfinished kiosk.
I think it was just like a little window at the restaurant.
It's like a bunch of shelves.
No, no.
I'm saying across from the restaurant there was a pickup spot.
Oh, no.
I didn't go to that shed.
No, no.
I got it at the…
Yeah.
You just went in there in the physical.
And for some reason I can't find the name of it, but I got just the to go.
I was going to go eat it at the hotel as I was leaving.
So, yeah, you would think that these doughnuts should be able to travel somewhat in a bag.
And they put it in a bag.
And look, it has some orange cream on the outside.
And it just immediately started leaking, seeping through the bag as I was carrying it.
Just immediate.
Didn't they test that out?
Like the frosting wouldn't just push its way through the membrane of the paper?
It was through as if being pushed in like a crushed penny machine.
Yeah, they're very messy, the voodoo doughnuts.
I had similar problems with mess.
And so then I tried to open the bag.
And the doughnut stuck to the bag and the tissue paper so thoroughly that just taking the doughnut out destroyed the doughnut.
This looks like Garfield got crushed by a car.
And which doughnut was this again?
Well, I'm going to have to go back and find the name of it.
But it's basically like an orange cream doughnut on a stick.
So it's like kind of a fun like you're having a popsicle or something.
But the whole doughnut was ruined.
It was destroyed just by trying to retrieve it from the bag.
So then I just tried to lick it while it was still stuck to the bag and have a piece of it.
And it was again, it's voodoo doughnuts.
It's not very good.
It's not that good.
I don't think this is maybe the original, the real ones, but the theme park iterations, because I ended up, I'm like, let me remember.
Maybe I could find something that actually really satisfies me.
I went up to the Hollywood one.
Maybe I'll get something weird and funny or that my son can have some.
I don't even want an entire doughnut to myself.
Look, I'm not I'm not the person to judge doughnuts.
I don't have a lot of them, but I don't.
This was not especially it was fine.
I've had better things just like from Trader Joe's prepackaged.
And it was three dollars for one doughnut.
I don't think this is a good at least the theme park iterations.
I don't think are good.
I don't I don't know what's going on here.
I haven't had the Portland one.
The only good thing you can say, I know for sure.
And I don't know if they're still doing it.
And we mentioned it in the last saga is that the Portland one at least at a certain point was giving you the option to buy a bucket of misshapen of misshapen.
So you so to me, Jason, Jason, this predates the podcast, but they've been talking about misshapen for years and years.
Now they've expanded the original one and, you know, the company's gone through like they had some labor issues.
I died in Denver trying to do the like eat the cake sized doughnut in like under 90 seconds.
What?
He choked on it.
Oh, my God.
And then they they were trying to open a location in New Orleans in the French Quarter and between like historical preservationists and actual voodoo practices.
They were like, you know, we don't want that.
They got too cocky being so close to the Fat Tuesday kiosk.
Oh, yeah.
They felt they were basically in New Orleans already.
This is what it's a creamsicle doughnut and it has a little universal Orlando like like some sort of some sort of like little sign that you can eat remotely resemble.
That's not like the other.
That is what I tried.
That is what it looked like when I opened up the bag.
Wow.
It was just like it had been in an accident or something.
And I just carried it in a bag into death.
Yeah, I just carried it in a bag to the hotel.
The stick is adding a whole other level of competence that can't have helped keep it together.
You know, the stick.
I don't think the stick.
I like it.
I don't think the stick helped, but I don't know it in the bag.
You know, oh, it may be.
Oh, it punctured it, causing an ooze out potentially like, I don't know.
Jason's like the Richard Feynman, a challenger explosion.
Like he's he's trying to break it down.
He's figuring out what happened.
It's a movie.
I anatomy of a fall.
Yes.
Jason.
Bear changing.
Jason, I'll send you the photos.
And if you want to perform a full forensics analysis, please.
Donut.
Can we cut out anatomy of a spill so it can be a doughboy's episode?
Get to work.
I'm excited to hear it in nine months.
I mean, as the doughnut enthusiast, I don't know that I've loved anything I've had from Voodoo either.
The price is not great.
I realize I have a photo of when I finally got it out of the bag.
And this is what it looked like.
This is the this is the situation.
Yeah.
And again, it wasn't even like you could tell it was like stale, stale ish.
They're all kind of stale.
I feel like it's almost like their thing is to have them all taste bad a little bit.
Do we do we think Fallen Brothers soon?
No, people love it.
No, it's popular.
It should be.
I think it should be a Fallen Brothers.
Seems to like it.
Yeah.
Get something better in there.
I think there's let me correct.
All right.
Bucket of Miss Shapens is good, but there is something else to bring up about this.
And I didn't know about this in the previous saga.
And this is true of both city walk locations.
Both of them can provide legal weddings.
You can have your a full wedding ceremony in the Voodoo doughnuts.
And I mean, I mean, they will provide an ordained person to perform the ceremony.
The Hollywood one smaller rights.
You can only invite 13 people.
But Orlando, you can invite 60.
Oh, wow.
60 person wedding at that Voodoo doughnuts, as well as Denver and Austin.
And you with that, you get a legal wedding ceremony.
Seven staff picked Voodoo dozens.
A doughnut heart centerpiece.
The couple's name spelled out in doughnuts.
You get bride and groom custom doughnuts where they look like you.
No, they don't.
They look like you if you get smooshed.
Staff pick dozens.
Like it's our wedding.
We'd actually like to pick the doughnuts.
Unfortunately, no, Gary's going to pick them.
Experts only.
You don't know what you're doing.
Sorry, it's the end of the night.
We don't got a lot left.
And three airpots of coffee as needed.
Wow.
They're not just going to put those out.
Do we want coffee or what's the vibe?
Do we want it or not?
Airpots.
It's 8 o'clock at night.
You don't want the coffee, right?
You just want milk?
You want milk?
It's at the shed.
Cross the walkway.
If you see Goku, you've gone too far.
So there's some married men here, but you know, in the future, just file away that you could do your ceremony.
You got a price quote on that?
No, I think you got to inquire further.
Inquire.
Well, I can shoot them an email.
They do warn you they need at least a week's notice.
Oh, wow.
So they're really booked.
This is an eye class ceremony.
Donuts that get stale.
Yeah.
What if you wanted to marry one of the donuts?
They don't specify that.
Some of their donuts look like a little guy.
Actually, you can do it, but the staff has to pick it.
Okay.
So there you go.
We've learned a lot.
You can get married there and we've learned this is not a good donut place and nobody should go.
And regardless of whether you went or not, Evan, I can't quite tell.
But you shouldn't.
We shouldn't have made you.
How much do we owe you?
It was my pleasure, guys.
It was my pleasure.
Okay, great.
Well, it was our pleasure to treat you with something else.
Here's something I'm sure everybody's going to want.
Auntie Anne's snacks that were purchased hours ago.
Ice cold, baby.
We've been recording.
It was in a progressively colder environment with the garage door open.
Sent Mike on a crowded Sunday.
It was awful.
Went to a busy mall so we could get a little taste of downtown Pennsylvania.
Originally founded in downtown Pennsylvania.
Of course, Anne is Beeler, Byler.
Raised in Amish sect and then they converted to a Mennonite.
Sound.
The smell just hit me so hard in the face.
I love that smell.
Well, here it is.
Let me poke around that, brother.
What has he got?
What do you got?
Open up your bag for you, Jason.
Open it not too close from the mic.
What is it?
Little nugs.
Little hot dog nugs.
Hot dog nugs?
Jason does not contrive these phrases.
They come straight out of his brain.
Jason, there's your tenth way to make a hot dog.
Pretzel.
Yeah, pretzel.
Now these filled me at Wetzel's, if you remember the previous City Walk.
Oh yeah, not Wetzel's in Orlando.
It's Auntie Anne's.
Oh, we got pretzels too.
Are those regular or what's going on with them?
Marvel at Universal.
What if it's regular?
This is like a dessert pretzel.
Regular.
Now is anyone going to take any of it?
No.
Evan's going for it.
The sexual keeper.
I've already died once.
Jason, how are you liking those nugs?
Nice and chilly.
I like them.
I was trying to take less and it wouldn't let me.
Mike, let me get a little of that classic.
Cinnamon crumble.
Jason called it a classic.
Let me get some of that classic, he said.
Jason wants some classic, he said.
Oh, we've got a big piece of classic.
We're all talking about stale.
Oh boy, this is as chewy as, I mean it's not awful.
Not awful.
It's really up to you, Jason.
You're the only true arbiter.
Well, you know, the thing with Auntie Anne's is that they're usually pretty greasy, pretty buttery and wet.
And these are cold and dry.
So, an interesting experience.
Well, you're seeing how they hold up to the elements.
Like my voodoo donuts didn't hold up.
I would say that these don't either.
Either the classic or the sweet.
The sweet maybe was the best just because the sugar doesn't really get bad.
It's just like a cinnamon sugar?
Yeah.
It's okay.
So, warning about Sector 2 for any listeners who want to visit Sector 2.
The flavors don't hold up to the elements.
We stress test them.
Eat it fresh.
Yes.
Don't sit on it for two hours.
Get that strawberry daiquiri in that audience and just woof it down, you know?
That being said, I'm going to still finish all of the thing I'm eating.
And then wait a half hour before you go swimming in the water.
Before you jump into the water.
And by the way, now there has been a weigh-in from a friend of the show, Andrew Grissom.
Hey, did you like any of the Flash?
Yes.
I saw it opening night.
There was excited crowd energy.
Also, I have not rewatched it and I have no desire to rewatch.
He liked the technology.
And then he said, perhaps intuiting what was happening here,
please don't make me represent this movie in court as its appointed lawyer.
So, but I do technically, Mike, you are correct.
You've won this round of relitigation.
Many more rounds to come.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I know it.
And as for you, Evan Susser, you survived podcast, The Ride,
the City Walk Orlando Saga, Multiverse of Madness.
I feel like I need to come clean about if I did go to it or not.
If you're willing to.
Or not come clean, rather just like, well, you know what?
I know everyone likes this a lot.
Maybe it's time for another Moves Like Burt.
Oh, yeah.
Another big audience hit.
I will, I'll say what happened,
whether I've been fibbing or telling the truth and just being weird to make a
fun little bit for my appearance.
And then maybe Sector Keeper, this might be outside of your purview,
but maybe you could respond with a cryptic, unclear what I said after the,
you know, Moves Like Burt.
Will you give us this deal?
Moves Like Burt?
Oh, God, more explanation.
Oh, you'll be laughing once we explain it.
We had to censor a story that he told about something disturbing at Sesame
Place, the Sesame Street theme park, and we censored it with a song that Burt
sang, which was Moves Like Burt.
So will you cut us this deal?
This is main feed.
We are, we'll censor it here.
Will you allow us on the Club 3 all the way on the Patreon?
Will you help us drive subscribers to our Patreon by having the unbelieved,
un-Burted version on Club 3?
No.
You know what?
I will allow that.
Okay.
So can you, will you tell us the full Sesame Place story?
Can we hear that?
I will tell the truth.
So did I, in the interest of being a good podcast guest, wait in line for a half an
hour to actually get a Voodoo donut, even though it is identical to the Voodoo
house?
Or did I telephib this whole episode and convince myself while in line that, oh,
you know, lying creates a fun dynamic on the show and I'll do that?
Or did I actually go, but say, oh, the lying idea is funny.
Why don't I just kind of play with that the whole time and then reveal at the end
that I actually did go?
Well, and this is only going to be revealed for people on the Patreon, the real
answer.
Everybody else will have Moves Like Burt.
Well, here is the truth.
I didn't go.
I'm sorry.
And also it's Sesame Place.
I heard someone pleasuring themselves until completion.
That's it guys.
It was great being here.
What a conclusion.
But I'll say this.
The sector is complete, but only because of one heroic man amongst us.
Michael R.
Carlson.
Not only went to Voodoo Donuts, Donuts purchased a donut, but eight.
It's smashed carcass.
That's true.
Looks like spaghetti grease and a paper bag.
So therefore it is complete.
Wow.
Oh, and there it is.
It's forming.
I see it.
That's right.
It's landing.
It's landing right in front of us.
There it is.
It's the Sapphire Nug.
Jason's trying to eat it.
Jason, Jason, don't eat that.
Look, I'm not going to now.
I already broke a couple of teeth on it.
So put it on the shelf next to the Coke mirror with Hermione on it.
Carl R.
Curio.
That was from the other episode.
Yeah, we're collecting all these things.
Well, wow.
There it is.
Looks beautiful.
A shining Sapphire Nug.
And Evan says, let's exit through the, let's go through the, let's go through the
plug portal.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Well, you know, it's just here, guys.
I think the same thing, the VillainCon Minion Blast Universal.
Yes.
Go check it out.
Yeah.
It's really great.
It's a lot of fun.
You did a great job on it.
And in the brief moments when you're enjoying wine.
And also you need a Minion Cafe if you're there too, which is also a lot of fun, which
I don't know.
It is fun.
Yeah.
Delicious.
More than the, but better than all of the great food items, offerings that we're going
to be discussing for many, many days.
Okay.
Thanks to Aaron Gardner for the art, our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the theme music,
multiverse of madness, merchant RT public store for the full multiverse experience.
Subscribe to podcast the ride, the second gate or join club three to get every sector
ad free and an exclusive bonus sector.
All of that is at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
I'll have to be listening every day.
I just have to remember to set the auto delete up.
No, no, no.
Well, if you already listed, it's a great way to organize your files.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.
com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.