Forever…
Dog!
The podcast The Ride presents…
The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
I'm Scott Gardner.
There's Mike Carlson.
Yo, I'm here.
There's Jason Sheridan.
Chocolate!
Well, you cut right to the matter, which is what I'm trying to do.
Although really quick, I want to say we are back on the main feed.
We found a cosmic screen door that led us out of the paywall verse for now.
So if you want to hear the three sectors you missed over the last couple of days,
all of that is at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
But I want to cut to the chase because there's a lot to do,
a lot to get through, a couple of people to meet.
And I also, I feel like, I got a feeling there is a big one coming today.
I've got a hunch that we are heading for one of the big ticket items of the series,
but I don't know for sure.
And the only way to know for sure, to see where we are going today at CityWalk,
we need to check in with our guide, the Sector Keeper.
There it is.
You were right.
Toothsome.
Chocolate.
Emporium.
Big periods after every one of those.
Well, Toothsome Chocolate Emporium and Savory Feast Kitchen.
And wait, slow it down, do it, do it, do it, really like trailer stuff.
Oh yeah, sure.
Toothless.
No!
Toothless?
I'm already…
How about just when you thought you were toothless.
Yeah.
Start that way.
Turned out.
Okay.
Toothsome.
Chocolate.
Emporium.
And Savory.
Feast.
Kitchen.
Yeah.
Yes.
Savory Feast Bathroom.
We'll get to the bathroom.
We've got so much to discover.
There's so much just in that name.
That's not even all of the big words that are on the outside of the building.
That's how much we have here.
This is Orlando.
This is Hollywood.
We have not done a Toothsome episode at all.
No.
No episodes about the Universal Steampunk Chocolate Restaurant.
And today, that all changes.
We're in it.
And we could not do just some ordinary episode.
We needed to assemble a super group, a Toothsome Tribunal.
And we reached out to two people who are as fascinated by this smokestack strewn enigma as we are.
And I'm so excited to introduce them from a great podcast that I love doing,
Who Cares About the Rock Hall, and a very funny album called Funny Songs and Sketches.
Returning to the show, Joe Quazzalla.
Guys, I am so deeply excited to talk for maybe four hours about Toothsome with you guys.
Seems possible.
That's what I wanted to blast through.
No tangents at the beginning.
We've got to break through this wall and go meet our friends, Professor Dr.
Toothsome.
Professor Dr.
Penelope Tibo Tinker Toothsome.
Is it Tibo?
I was going to have that question.
Tibo.
E-A-U-X.
So however you pronounce Tibo.
Yeah.
Well, there'll be questions.
We need to be sure about how to say that and be sure how to say almondine.
Because we've been through that.
I don't want to say almondine now.
Now we know almondine.
That came up before.
It'll come up again.
But yes.
No, no, no.
I was going to say it sounded more like a medicine than a dinner.
Right.
The way I was saying it.
You're severely lacking in almonds.
Almondine.
I need to get you some almondine.
And if that weren't enough, also joining us today, an under acknowledged figure in the
story of podcast The Ride, the reason we are at Forever Dog, which has been our network
home for a long time, the co-founder of Forever Dog, a producer and on mic presence on the
great show Double Threat with Tom Sharpling and Julie Klausner.
He's got a show called Weekend at Bergman's.
He's got a show called Movies Baby.
For the first time on mic with us, it's Brett Bowen.
Oh, guys.
It is so good to be here.
You know, I love this show.
You know, it's been such a joy having you on the network.
I can't believe I'm finally here in the in the circle.
This is amazing.
In the building that you're always in otherwise.
You came to this corner, hopefully not avoiding any important business.
Down in the in the boiler room of the Derisable this morning, working on the gears, making
sure everything's functioning.
I climbed that old steampunk staircase and I'm here.
It's good to be here.
I cannot wait to talk about the greatest restaurant on God's planet.
Green Earth, Toosome's Chocolate Emporium.
And you also were generous enough.
You you cleaned out your checking account to get some to some artifacts.
Oh, yeah.
Presumably.
Yes.
With how many items?
Financially.
So I went to Toosome this morning and I've got a lot of treats here.
I've got some apothecary sweets, Jacques brand coffee, some unidentified mounds of sugar
and chocolate rocks, chocolate rocks, truffles.
I got a little bit of everything, guys.
Feel free to help yourself.
I can pass these around.
Glad Jason's right there, though.
Yeah.
He needs these.
He needs to reach these.
Jason must eat that grounds of coffee alone without.
I am actually running low on coffee.
Dip your finger in.
Dab dab dab.
Can you explain to us what the green one is?
Yes, this is.
And for those listening, it's like a sort of a old style, almost like a perfume or medicine
bottle.
And it says Penelope's apothecary sweets.
So I think this is sort of like rock candy.
There's a lot of like green, almost translucent like rocks inside.
So I believe this is like a rock candy.
I'll go ahead and try one.
From a distance, you would think it would be filled with liquid.
But then you get close and you're like, oh, it's rocks.
Another mystery from Dr.
Penelope.
A very nice decorative glass that you will not be able to take into the theme park.
No glass allowed inside Universal Studios.
Do people run into this?
That they buy some of this glass bottle?
I think Mini Monster was running it.
I think maybe now it's all plastic bottles.
But the original Mini Monster.
Well, what if you buy like a signed piece of glass from the celebrity Authentics?
Can you bring that into the glass from the movie Glass?
I mean, you got to put it in some of the lockers by those Greyhound Busty Shibay after-rooms that are halfway through City Hall.
That's true.
You're having a problem?
Okay, you got it.
No, no, it was just…
I want to say like sort of crystallized mouthwash is kind of the…
Ooh, lovely.
Sweet, crystallized mouthwash.
Yeah.
We'll get the review from Joe.
You know what?
Like you, Joe, I thought that was going to be liquid.
Especially because the last time I was up there in the store, I opened a much smaller bottle.
I'm sorry, not opened.
I looked at a much smaller bottle that looked very similar in a similar greenish color.
I just picked it up was all I did.
And then I immediately had green goo on my hand.
It was out in the store and the one that I picked up was dripping on me.
I'll post a photo of that.
I'm experiencing some green goo myself.
There's a lot of viscous in two shots.
There's little candies in my palm.
Hey, your hand is stained now.
Whoops.
It's not like I took a lot of them.
Took like a very normal to small amount from the perfume bottle.
I think I'm going to not.
I think I'm going to focus and not be distracted by the green on my hand.
Although now I'm distracted by the back where it says a story.
Penelope would lock herself away, endlessly experimenting with this sweet concoction.
Its possibilities seemed infinite and she was determined to discover everything there was to learn about chocolate.
Again, what we're looking at is not chocolate.
No, that's sugar candy.
Penelope played by bad cumers and a case of hysteria.
I came up with new chocolate delights.
There is a deep sadness to the lore of Toothsums.
I'm sure we'll get into this, but there is like a deep sadness at the core.
From the get.
I don't know if we just want to jump into it, but the lore is that her and her robot Jock were traveling the world
and they're derisable, having adventures, discovering different recipes for chocolate and things.
And then when they get back home, their parents are gone.
Her parents are gone.
And there's a letter that says something to the effect of like, you'll find us wherever chocolate is made or something like that.
I think specifically they like left because they're like, where's our daughter?
Yes.
Which implies that she didn't tell her family that she was leaving.
And then so then they go to try and find her in some tragic case of miscommunication.
And then it leaves.
Yeah, the parents leave a note that say, you know, we will we will be wherever there is chocolate.
So then she starts a chocolate restaurant, the chocolate factory to to get her parents to entice, to coax her parents back into her life.
So every time you go to Toothsums and Penelope waltzes over to your table and does a little routine, that woman is desperately hoping every day she comes to Toothsums.
She's hoping that her parents will walk through the door of Toothsums and she'll be reunited with them.
So while you're having like a nice, fun little meal at Universal, this woman is like desperately hoping to reunite with her parents.
Sobbing.
Which never happens.
Yeah.
Sobbing as she puts a circular brandy on top of a filter straw.
So all of the showiness of it, because this place is jaw dropping.
Every stab, every version of it is astounding to look at.
And all of that is just as if to say, hey, I'm dad here, I'm here.
Yes.
And there is, to be clear, if you're lucky and you do enter the restaurant at a certain time, Penelope will be there.
And I do feel like we should be sensing a little bit more of that despair.
I would like to see the Penelope actor have a lot of excitement and then extreme disappointment every time any person walks into the restaurant.
Yeah.
Anytime there should be a bell on the door and every time it rings, she turns like wistfully hoping.
And goes, mother?
Father?
And when it's not, throws a plate against the wall.
You should hear from anywhere in the giant open, like giant.
It reverberates through the big echoey ceiling.
God damn it!
A Girl Scout troop again!
Let's back up to the beginning a little bit here, because there's a ton to unpack.
I think that this is a, okay, Toothsome Chocolate Emporium, which you could, could, and maybe should be called a factory, what with its smokestacks.
But there might be, could be some legal reasons why it's not called a factory and why they don't want to nod to other famous candy or chocolate factories out there.
But the idea is you are entering this world's, okay, it's steampunk, but is it supposed to be the past?
Are you time traveling when you go there?
Or does steampunk also represent now?
And that's just her vibe and it's 2024 and it's now.
This is a great question that I was afraid to ask the actors.
I think we did say like, is it now?
Because we did end up talking to Penelope and Jacques for a long time, one of the times we went.
And we just, we were, we like a little, a little bit overloaded them with questions about like, what's going on.
Am I allowed to, do you know about Dune 2?
I know that in real life, the movie theater is right outside, but in your reality, is it not?
Do you know that there's anything beyond the square footage of this place?
Because we asked them about Wonka.
I went.
Like, drag her outside.
Look, what is that?
Can you see it?
Screens, airplanes, pitbull playing.
Have you seen Wonka?
Are you just up to the train coming right at the screen?
Yes, right.
Yes.
It's been precisely one movie.
I don't know.
But either way, yes, you're entering this experimental laboratory of this fantastical professor type character, a female professor,
Professor Dr.
Penelope Tybo.
Tybo Tinker.
And she has a human sized robot named Jacques.
Has is, yeah, a verb that we can try to parse out with what's going on.
Is it her friend?
Is it, I mean, sidekick is the verbiage they use in the lore.
Yeah.
But what exactly does that mean?
When I saw them, they were holding hands.
What?
So that, you know, implies potentially a relationship beyond sidekick.
Although in the past, maybe people were just holding hands with friends more often.
But what about a steampunk future?
Maybe they don't come back.
Well, in the future.
They realize the bond that we need with others that we've been ignoring for so long.
If it's the future, though, that means they're fucking.
Yes.
They're having sex.
They spend a lot of time together, too, on the Derisable, on adventures.
I mean, they're not part of some team.
There's not an extended cast.
It's really, they've been alone together for a long time and they seem to get along really well, which I think implies a complex relationship.
There's one other character Jason was bringing up a character.
Oh, sure.
Well, spot the dog.
No, not the dog.
No, I'm sorry.
That is the type of mechanics he is a spot.
He is a dress.
They took a spot, which is the Boston Dynamics robot.
Police force.
It can detonate a bomb if you want it to.
Yeah, it can go into an apartment and notice if there's any explosives in there.
So latte, you know, they include some dog ears and snout and a bunch of gears to him.
Meters and clocks.
A little hat.
And you could only like they had a little meet and greet with him from four to six.
And this was only for the month of September.
I should say the month of September 2020.
So if this all feels a little apocalyptic, here's Professor Toothsome in a mask.
Yeah, this was this was in the era of outdoor masking.
We all knew we would.
It is crucial for us to do outdoor masking at all times.
And they did this presentation and invited like theme park media to come check it out.
But Professor Toothsome was in a mask, a brown leather mask in keeping with her vibe and also in like a little cage so that she was forced to keep her distance from everybody.
And the vibe is so weird.
You're like, could this not have been?
Did this have to happen in deepest pandemic?
No, it's September 2020.
Clock's ticking.
We got to roll out latte.
There is no other way.
The stockholders are going to be so pissed.
They had to get back to the police force in Orlando.
They had it only for a certain amount of time.
Latte had to get back to bodying jaywalkers.
Throwing its full robot weight at like going across.
This does bring back to what I think is one of the most interesting parts of Toothsome's and one of the most mysterious parts is the money and the finances of this place and how it because stuff like that does feel like they were
built.
Some bill had to get paid or there was some like they because the first time I went in there, I was like how I immediately thought this is either a front or some tax shelter or something is going on here because the ratio of how much they spent on the
overhead versus how many actual tables they have in the restaurant is insane because if you go into like Bucco di Beppo, they could pack like a Titanic's worth of people in Bucco di Beppo every night.
You can sit everywhere.
Toothsome's there was so much open space, so much unused space, giant staircases going up and even though there's a second floor, there's also not that many tables up there.
So I was like how did they spend so much overhead?
This place, they had this real estate for years before it opened up.
They were working on this thing forever.
Hard Rock Cafe went down, this is the Hollywood one, Hard Rock Cafe went down way, way in advance.
The makeover to Toothsome took forever.
There was a lot, at least with us, a lot of hubbub.
When is it going to get here?
When is it going to find so much build up?
An important part to the story was just like what on earth is this?
What is it going to be?
And like this real estate is like prime.
It's like central.
That also felt very end of the world where it's like Toothsome got half built, everything closed because of the pandemic.
And then when CityWalk opened back up, you could just go up there any time of day and steer it like a construction site.
And then in 2021, I remember going back up there because like the AMCA list was like we're giving you three free months because of the lockdown.
So I went up there to see like the last screening of Black Widow of the night.
And then I'm just watching like the third shift soldering Toothsome.
And then one magical day, as though they were announcing a new pope, there's smoke started coming out of the one of the smokestacks.
And it was like the day has finally arrived.
Toothsome is actually going to open up.
2023.
Is that that was the timeline that it was paused due to pandemic.
So it ended up being like a four year process, roughly.
I think so.
It's like how there was a Minions rise of grew like giant billboard at CityWalk for years because that was supposed to come out in the summer of 2020 and just kept getting pushed.
This also seems like it's the Los Angeles.
Universal Orlando builds in like six months and then everything in Los Angeles seems like it takes forever.
The rumors like take years.
There were rumors this was coming.
Believe me, we were talking about it for years prior.
We named checked it in the first saga, I think.
It's Toothsomes or whatever.
But it took forever.
There was also a rumor it was going to be built from scratch on the Saddle Ranch space.
Was there?
I don't even remember.
I think that's what we were saying.
Instead of what that ended up being a weird lawn that's never opened for anything.
I got to go on that weird lawn for that Nintendo event we went to though.
They opened it up for that and that's it.
Otherwise it's just vacant grass.
Why was this added to CityWalk?
Big mystery we do not know.
That's right because like Voodoo Donuts took forever to actually open up too.
I remember that was a like coming soon for at least a year or two years and that's just like a little corner spot.
I don't know.
Yeah, LA it's like it's tougher.
Orlando everything goes up so fast.
The roller coaster is being built quickly.
I'll say that.
The Fast and Furious coaster they're building now.
That's quick.
But everything else.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Well, the Orlando one, you know, there's some differences.
There's differences in the speed at which they build things.
And in general, I would say the vibe is kind of different at the Orlando one, which arrived in 2016.
Beijing in between.
This is an international brand.
The smokestacks have traveled the globe.
And, Brett, everything you're saying about the weird sparseness of the Hollywood one is not true in Florida.
It's so packed.
This is one.
And in a place, CityWalk Orlando is nothing but two story jam packed restaurants.
It's unreal.
I feel like what is the total dining capacity of the entire if every restaurant was totally full, is that like 300,000 people?
That's my guess.
300,000.
It's so crazy.
But it is like, you know, whereas all these other things, it's like we're there in the middle of the week.
It's a Thursday night.
Nobody's there.
Not tooth.
So tooth some line out the door every single time ever.
Yeah.
And in decor, I thought it was like better done in there.
It's cooler.
It's a little more you get transported to a world a little bit more.
It's dark and lantern lit.
And as opposed to the Hollywood one, which is kind of like sterile, I might say.
Yes.
Once you get in, it's kind of gray and flat.
That big open area and those tall ceilings, I think partially because there did used to be a large rotating convertible on top of the Hard Rock Cafe bar.
Oh, right.
Yes.
You remember that filled that big empty space pretty nicely.
Yeah.
I think they just yeah, maybe they were the maybe there were some budget cuts because it does seem odd.
Because if you guys have not been to the Orlando one, no, no, you should be jealous of us.
First of all, number one, number two, imagine like a 90s Batman movie where they're having like a gala and it's packed and everybody's maybe dressed more in their like tourist clothes, regular clothes.
But you don't even feel that because of the way it's packed in there and the way that the lighting is.
And there's just so many people in there.
It's like this is the coolest place.
Everyone who's anyone is here right now tonight at two sums on a Tuesday night after Orlando.
It's entirely dignitaries and cabinet members.
Right.
Yes.
Yeah.
And there is from other names.
This is dining at a table over by the like big tube that shoots fudge.
And that's what I expected when I first time I walked into the L.
A.
one.
I thought I was going to be brimming with I was like, man, they got to start moving food if they're going to pay for this real estate.
And then you go in there and you're like, is this a cloud kitchen?
Is it kind of can I eat here?
Like, what is this?
This is like there's just it's just weirdly sparse and weirdly not concerned with like it's a weird spot.
Maximizing the space.
Yeah.
And not exactly great sign.
Like I didn't know they had the milkshake counter and the souvenir counter.
Excuse me.
Do you have a milkshake counter or not?
From the outside, I didn't really know what was.
But when I was inside, I was like, oh, there's a store.
There's like dessert counter.
But when I eat there, I do have to say in the bathrooms, you know, they have like circ like oval brass mirrors.
But then they just have these gear decals just on the mirror.
This is the main place making in the bathroom.
But six stickers.
That'll do it.
Yeah.
They didn't spend the money on this Los Angeles.
Also, Jason, what you're describing, like what part of the words dessert foundry do you not understand?
You get your milkshakes at the dessert foundry.
It's clear as day.
Look, I like the commitment to like old timey language, but the words we don't use.
Another little sign at eye level of like desserts to go like would be helpful.
I agree with you because there I was going to bring up like there's a bar there and I don't know what happens at that bar.
I don't know.
It takes up a lot of space in there and I don't see there's no one there and there's often not a bartender there.
So, yeah, it's just like this waste.
And I was like, do you go and get chocolate there?
Like, I don't know.
Is it an out?
Is it an alcohol bar or a milkshake bar?
I actually don't know.
Right.
I don't think they serve alcohol there.
I think it is a dessert foundry.
Yeah, because the bar location used to be the center of the ground floor.
And now I think that's just a handful of booths.
Yes.
I think also to the Florida one benefits from two massive theme parks being let out right behind it and then hard rock live is steps away.
So when concerts get out, people in just go right next door.
I think there's some sort of like insect catching net that you could like you could you could show like a diagram of an insect catching net and then put it up against the outflow of traffic coming out of Universal Studios Los Angeles, where the stuff that is right outside the theme parks are catching the most people wanting to eat dinner.
And then you get all the way down.
They wrap all the way around.
By the time they get to Tucson, there's not many insects left.
And especially then when you get to Margaritaville, there is no insects left.
Everyone has been caught by that point in their dinner trap.
And that's like sort of the principle how you can like they should have put to some overwrite when you come outside the theme park.
And then I think maybe it would be packed.
What you get is a lot of people going, well, this point we're almost back to the car.
Let's just go home.
I got to go to a factory.
I went up to a factory.
Yeah, yeah.
Hot up here earlier because you're close to the sun and now it's cold and the wind is burning the sunburn.
I've been walking around all day.
I can't deal with lore.
Well, and the the inefficiency of the place to extends into their hiring practices, because I have a little inside Intel here, which is because an engineer at forever dog dated someone who worked at two some for a while.
And so I have just been getting all the inside Intel from from her.
But in order to work at two sums, you and anybody, not just if you're like playing a character, anybody on the floor, you have to do a three week paid training where you have to go deep and learn all of the lore in addition to the learn all the lore.
And then you get tested on the lore.
And if you don't pass, you don't get hired.
And so on the one hand, I'm very glad they are paying for that training.
On the other hand, I don't know if everybody in the restaurant needs to be completely versed in the lore before they.
And so they're they're literally paying for people to like test and fail the lore, the lore quiz that don't become, you know, employees.
You take the quiz once as like when you go to the DMV, you can take that test three times in one day or you have to do one and then you're done.
Question number one, does Jacques believe in God?
Is it chocolate?
OK, Christian, Jewish or Muslim?
Which God is Jacques?
Do robots know fear?
Trick question.
Yes, but Jacques does not.
That's what makes Jacques special.
You can see into the kitchen and I have noticed that they have to be done up in in steampunk gear.
Really?
Yeah.
And I assume it's because you can see so easily into the kitchen.
You can't break the illusion.
Like you're passing by just outside at City Walk.
That's right.
These poor are they using like old time copper instruments to cook the food?
They're cranking an oven.
Just doing all this like weirdly.
I guess that's steampunk.
Did the burger buns have to go through a full Rube Goldberg device?
Oh, yeah.
Can we not just toast them with a toaster?
Why do they have to go all the way through the top of the restaurant and back?
Do we have to play dun dun dun?
Do we have to play that every shift?
Definitely loud.
I can't hear the orders.
We're all screaming all the time.
Lore quiz.
I don't I would love to see the lore quiz.
I just any quiz.
Please just question 12.
I wonder if we get a leak here.
Can somebody leak us the one of us could just apply.
But they were just to do the quiz.
Yeah, that's true.
Because the published lore, the lore that's available online is not that like thorough.
Extensive.
Yeah, it's pretty short.
But there must be like a second level to the lore that likes like Scientology.
You get to your right here.
You learn the secrets.
I know somebody who occasionally works there, too.
And the next time I see them, I'm going to be very annoying.
I just want to know about the lore.
So it's more quiz.
Let's get into it.
Yeah.
So, Jason, you didn't say hello.
And what lore?
You scream lore quiz at me and expect I know what you're talking about.
Look at me.
Don't look away.
OK, does shock believe in God?
The lore used to be in the menus.
And I've gone twice.
One early on and then one later, I guess we'll say.
A little bit of giving up perhaps.
Yes, they've scaled back.
And the second time it was just a one a one shooter for the menu.
But the first time I went, they went like in May.
And then I went in at the end of the year around December.
And then it was like almost like a like a booklet at first.
And you open it up and you could read about the story of Penelope and the tragic disappearance of her parents.
And I think there were more there were more like food options as well.
And then when I was there in December, it was just no lore.
Here's our food.
They gave up the no because this is something I was going to say is that I went kind of early on into the run.
And when they handed that book, the book was like the finest engraving.
I could not believe the quality.
I believe that there that some people in history have served as pope and their personal copy of the Bible was not as fine as just ever any run of the mill to some menu.
And my guess is they all got dirty or were stolen.
Yeah, it was not practical to have every menu caused.
$150.
They were incredible.
I thought they were fantastic.
But the other thing I heard is is you know when you're working at a place, particularly like a day job and you kind of start to get a sense like I don't think this place is doing that well or it might be in some sort of trouble.
That seems that was the vibe I was getting from from this hearsay from people that work there is there's a sense that maybe it started out very ambitious and then quickly was like cool.
Like not quite shredding documents in the back office.
But like but there was definitely a turn at some point where it's like OK, we're going to go.
We're going to start cutting costs like significantly across the board.
What's the lowest budget steampunk chocolate emporium we can do?
What's that or no?
What's the five times less cost of that?
We tried the dream version.
That was obviously a bad idea.
So now we're going to go with a slightly lower budget.
Like all the merchandise is just going to be replaced by like Harley Quinn Funko pop soon.
Like I don't know.
It's too much money to make this stuff and no one's buying it.
Besides me and my father-in-law, I've never seen anyone buy anything in the gift gift store at two sums.
I do wonder if that stock is like the original stock that was there on day one.
It's turning white.
Well, I have I bought some chocolate.
I bought a couple of things from this.
I bought some chocolate a few weeks ago.
I brought it home.
I thought I was a big hero for everybody to have some of this fine to some chocolate.
And then we turned it around and the expiration date was a week from then.
Oh, my God.
And I was like, wait, what?
That's pretty.
And then I went back a week ago and then it was like a year from now was the new expiration dates on all the chocolate bars.
So I had gotten the last possible second you could have sold these things into some of the original pressing possible.
Yes, it's possible.
Been there for 11 months.
Well, maybe it was seven.
Like there was seven.
Maybe it was October.
That was the new bars expiration dates.
So maybe it lets at least you say six months.
So the bars were not a hit.
Nobody like these.
Well, and they've gone to waste.
I guess there's still some Jason probably would eat them.
I well, yeah, we'll see.
We had the both experience like we got some chocolates.
We got a souvenir box like bread has some chocolates here.
We got them in Florida.
And Jane was apparently the last customer of the night.
And we were eating them like the last couple of days.
We're in Florida.
You're like, oh, these are really good.
These are good.
And when we were up there recently, we went to the Hollywood one and she ran in and got some chocolates and they gave it to her in like a wax paper sleeve.
No souvenir box in sight.
And we're eating them and they're like, oh, these are not like it was like nine day.
This downturn.
What were those dates again, Joe?
Because that was not a big stretch of time.
Yes, I went in May and then I went in December.
That is not much in the same year.
That seems wild.
And sorry, my timeline is all thrown.
This is not this has only been open in Hollywood for like a year and a month as we record.
Yeah.
Correct.
Right.
How has there already been a rise and fall?
Was there already like the supreme version?
And now they're like, I don't know, stickers.
How about we laminate a piece of paper?
How about that's the menu?
No more Gutenberg Bibles.
You know, I would all I would say is that as far as drawing down the ambition, I don't think we've seen anything yet.
I think that's exciting.
I have to revisit.
I'm not saying I know anything.
I'm just saying I think the possibilities of lessening the ambition is possible.
It was very, very positive.
Tooths and Penelope's been doing some cheapening experiments.
The science of cutting corners.
The party city version of Josh is coming.
It's coming very sooner than you think.
That kitchen you saw, Joe, will be outsourced to the Bucca Ghost Kitchen that Guy Fieri is.
They'll be making Mr.
Beast burgers in no time.
The Bucca Ghost Kitchen.
Can we kind of like describe the experience a little bit of like the first of all, like just
walking up to this place to either one.
Both of them are so they're so humbling.
They make you feel like a needle in a haystack.
They're just they're unbelievable.
A little more like I think both of them have, you know, big lines of like, you know, old fashioned like early electric lights or candles.
Yeah.
And then the Orlando one is these ornate like spiraling bushes.
The landscaping is incredible.
Every every banister is done beautifully.
Like they I think they've kept up that like the facade, the outside of both of these places is unreal.
You can't believe you're looking at it.
I still every time I go up there like, wow, and that logo is mammoth.
Yeah.
They don't make things like that for movie.
Mike, you're describing, you know, Schumacher era Batman.
They don't everything CGI now.
They don't they wouldn't make a prop as like massive and incredible.
And like you just want to give it a hug.
Yeah.
To said big main to some beer.
And we should say that we complain for years and years that this is what we want in the world.
We do want this.
Yes.
Yeah.
This is what we so don't get us wrong.
It's such a throwback to the air to the Arab dive.
The Steven Spielberg submarine restaurant.
It's a throwback to all these things that we've talked about on the show.
But they're all ancient history lessons.
And we're all, you know, combing through the three websites that bottom one blurry video.
I can't believe this all is happening in the 20 20s.
Yeah.
Does this not feel like a failed premise that we discover from 1987?
Nobody bothered to take a picture.
We are so lucky to be watching this rise and presumably fall.
It is.
We're lucky to be on the planet Earth at this moment.
I agree with you.
Cross has our Venn diagram crosses.
Can I say that I just because I like to say the word.
Can I tell the guest?
Do you guys know before Saddle Ranch?
Initially, there was a place called Whomp Hoppers, which was like a wagon wheelery, which was like as big as the biggest saddle.
Like it was the same sort of outside building that Saddle Ranch had.
And then when they tore it down.
So I don't think they altered it too much, but it had like a narrative and it had like an old like prosper wagon wheeler or whatever you call it.
Wheeler dealer.
I think it was described.
They had lore there as well.
So like there's Whomp Humpery Whomp Hoppers is the name of it.
Yeah.
And it was a wagon wheeler.
It was a wagon.
I'm going to make sure I get this right.
Whomp Hoppers colon.
Oh, wagon wheeler.
There might be a different fine wagon wheeler.
Specifically, you would sell wagon wheels to everyone going through the Cahuanga Pass.
Yes.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Whomp Hoppers wagon works.
But I think maybe in the there's some wagon.
But it was an old wagon factory.
This was mainly up in the 70s.
So this really does.
Tooth Sim does like bring it right back to a restaurant with a premise and a red and built out of everyone loves it.
Regular people love to go to a restaurant that's built out of something.
It used to be something else.
We've seen it time and time again.
The fireworks factory in Pleasure Island in Florida.
If you love eating somewhere that used to be a factory, everyone loves it.
That's bigger than like the Harry Potter castle.
That restaurant is huge.
That was next to it.
One point in time is a walk away from a restaurant you could take a trolley car to.
Yes.
Right?
Yeah.
They were both up there.
A train station restaurant.
And everything.
And then it was Tony Romas for a bit.
Then it was just Tony Romas.
And it had no premise.
Sure.
I guess.
We had a safe bet for a couple months.
Oh, wait, wait.
Hold on.
I just saw this.
Okay.
Whomp Poppers from 81 to 86.
Then it was just called Whomps from 86 to 88.
That'll trick them.
Tony Romas from 88 to 94.
And then it just says unknown 94 to 95.
Which then it was Country Star Restaurant.
Oh, right.
When it was a big jukebox.
Country music restaurant.
Saddle Ranch 2003 to 2018.
Interesting.
It feels like this is there other lost periods in there from 2000 to 2003?
No.
That one's accounted for?
Or no.
Well, you know, you're right.
It doesn't say anything.
Oh, maybe it just sat there empty for three years until Saddle Ranch was built.
Okay.
That might be right.
I think I do recall just a darkened build.
You left Universal Studios and walked straight up to a darkened building.
Here's some pictures of Whomp Hoppers.
With like a big wagon above your head.
Oh my gosh.
Incredible.
Well, that does, because going back, I mean, Universal Citywalks, they must be partnering or like somewhat subsidizing the thing.
Because if it goes down, they sort of share the shame of it.
I think they own it.
I think they own it too.
They own the whole thing.
There's no website.
You have to go to the Universal Studios website to learn anything about this restaurant.
Well, they've done this big, we've discussed it in this series a little bit.
They have slowly bought up all the, not all of them, but a lot of the spots that they were leasing to outside vendors and replaced them with fake restaurants that are things that they own.
And it's these, I feel, that I've had the most trouble with food and such because they aren't real restaurants.
Professional.
Yeah.
Restaurateurs are not taking care of that.
Yes.
Yeah.
But that's the idea is that like, OK, you know, we're like, we're losing the profits to this place on our property to some other restaurant establishment.
We need things that we own.
So all of it, it's like the consolidation we're seeing with the studios.
It's the same idea.
So they're probably taking a loss on the record itself.
But the way they rationalize it is it's part of the spectacle and it's part of the we use it.
I mean, it's on the billboard as you come off Lancashim to go up.
So it's like it has other uses for them besides just making money off the restaurant.
That must.
Yeah.
And I have way that restaurants making money on its own.
I wonder if there's like an ambitious theme park person, too, that's like, you know what?
And then we'll make the universal movie.
Yeah.
Like, that's maybe what we're headed.
I would assume there's some ambitious person that thinks that whether that's actually a high up decision.
You think you're eating in a restaurant, you're eating in an IP generation.
Yes, I think that is right.
I do.
Well, I don't.
God, I mean, I hope we're seeing like universal had the biggest year.
Oppenheimer's them right.
And they kind of like, you know, what?
Mario's them.
Yeah.
Well, like, you know, sequels and franchises have ruined other studio.
Not really.
I saw yesterday they were the first time since 2016 that they had the biggest they had the biggest year at the box office.
They did.
It was Disney for 10 years.
Yeah.
And then it was this year was universal.
Wow.
Well, one kind of to cool this hot.
Then some delicious ice fun.
Then like the opening credits and like the year was 1873.
I found my when I was only two years old, I had a sweet tooth.
Jared Leto is Jacques.
My friends and I did try to cast this movie and come up with different.
But we also tried to do it in the in like the least interesting way and like the most typical.
We're like, well, obviously Jacques will be voiced by Keegan-Michael Key.
And we were like, maybe because we also had to create more lore just to make a story because it's just, you know, so we were like, OK, you make Bryce Dallas Howard, Professor Toothsome.
And then you she has a rival played by Jessica Chastain.
And they're kind of like doubles for each other.
So you get America gets angry because they're like, no, I confuse these two actors all the time.
And then that's on top of their additional.
I feel like any time there's like a steampunk movie or like a whimsical year, like everyone's like, no, I'm not going to see this.
I'll say the little the little secret steampunk movie of last year was Poor Things.
Poor Things.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
But not not a gear in that poster.
No, you think they don't tell you.
Here's him.
Get your don't tell you that's a little steampunk and they don't tell you.
Wanka is a musical.
Get your ghost to direct this Toothsome movie.
He's poised.
He's hot.
But he's going to have to go I.
P.
someday.
He's going to have to get ruined at some point.
He's he'll add all the fucking in it.
He'll add all the.
Yeah, there you go.
And the dreary net, like all the morose news of the favorite.
You can incorporate of course, you're right.
Oh, it's into her sad search for the parents.
Please indulge me as I read some Whomp Hoppers copy real quick.
I'm so sorry, but I have to do it.
Whomp Hoppers Wagon Works was inspired by C.
L.
Whomp Hopper, a legendary slick talking wagon salesman who invented wheeling and dealing.
As a young man, C.
L.
perfected a sales pitch that could sell perfume to a buzzard.
He began with horse trading, which led him to wagons, buggies and backboards.
By the time he descended on the unsuspecting citizens of early Los Angeles, he'd taken in enough cash to open giant Whomp Hoppers Wagon Works perched atop a hill overlooking the much traveled Coanga Pass.
Today, old C.
L.
is gone, but his legend lives on at Whomp Hoppers Wagon Works restaurant operated by his descendant C.
Whomp Hopper the fourth with the assistance and cooperation of MCA Recreation Services, a division of MCA Incorporated.
Let's save the best part for the end.
Yeah.
Let's go out with a bang.
And there's more, but I really.
Why?
Who would want to learn this story?
Like, OK, so learn about a man.
So that's whose restaurant it is.
No, this great grandson.
An 1880 style wagon factory and dealership.
So it was a wagon dealership, like a car dealership.
Lease a wheel.
Yeah.
So it was slick talking wagon salesman.
Am I being stupid?
Is that real?
Like, is that true?
Was the restaurant real?
The real story of the story?
That's a real story.
That's not like.
I don't think there was a C.
L.
Whomp Hopper.
No, that's all K.
F.
I know.
We just read you a made up story that isn't fantastical or fun at all.
It was so boring.
I was like, wait, is this.
Surely this must be true.
With the MCA stuff at the end, I was like, oh, wait, is this just like a real.
It's just it was on that they incorporated the real name of the canyon into it.
I guess that's just what that was on this universal land, I guess.
That's deeply boring.
The only justification for that, if it was just a real thing they felt like legally obligated to say.
Yeah, I know.
I think I mean, unless look, this guy dressed to see a Whomp Hopper.
Do I think he's a real guy?
I don't know.
Who was an actor who also played the Dream Finder, right?
Sorry.
We found that.
Yeah, I was just marveling at that fake picture.
Yeah.
Do you think they had a wagon repo men?
Well, but would you buy a wagon on credit?
Did they have credit back then?
Because that's usually when a repo man has to go into action.
Were you allowed to smoke in C.
L.
Whomp?
Oh, yeah.
Of course you were.
They just invented putting bacon on a cheeseburger.
This is like, oh, this is good.
I would kill to smoke a cigarette and see a Whomp Hoppers like tonight.
Yeah.
I would pay $500 if I could go back in time and smoke a cigarette and Whomp Hoppers.
Unfiltered, just breathing in everybody else's.
I'll smoke a pack in there.
Put me next to the smallest children.
I want to smoke cigarettes in here.
I am glad this, besides the crazy backstory and the premise that Tucson has in common with Whomp Hoppers,
I think with that, it's not him, it's the fourth.
Right.
They've kept up that confusion as well because, all right, we've said this backstory that the whole thing is about trying to get the parents back.
And what's so weird is, like you said, Joe, you get the immaculate menu and you're, okay,
I'm in a steampunk chocolate emporium and I guess there's a professor who runs this place and there is a robot.
I've got a lot of questions.
I'd love to know their story and how this all came to pass.
And then you open the menu and it says the story of Toothsum.
Great.
This is exactly what I'm looking for.
First line of the story of Toothsum.
Shock landed the derigible in front of the small cottage home in London, England.
And then they're just straight.
So the story starts way past.
You're not even close to knowing where shock came from or who shock is or why.
Yeah, that's all boring.
We need to get to a cottage and departed parents.
Wait, but I'm just adjusting to Professor Toothsum and Padelope and Jock.
No.
All right.
Forget that.
You now need to learn about Thomas and Violet Toothsum.
Why am I going to meet them?
No, not unless their story ends and then the restaurant will close.
You will never meet Thomas and Violet Toothsum.
Well, I have to know about him.
You do.
I'm just eating chocolate bread here.
Right.
Yes.
The menu writer took very literally.
There's a saying that Kurt Vonnegut used to say, one of my favorite writers.
He would say, write 15 pages and then throw out the first five and start your story there.
So the first five pages of Toothsum are in the garbage somewhere.
Crucial pages.
You noticed Vonnegut influence.
We've got to do it.
Vonnegut said it.
We've got to throw him away.
Page number six starts with Jock landing the dirigible.
So Jock landed the dirigible.
Jock flies dirigibles.
Very cat's cradle.
Very breakfast of champions.
People know that word now because of that one, the rich people sub that imploded, I assume.
That was a dirigible?
Dirigibles can go under the sea too.
They aren't just flying.
I'm looking it up unless I'm just totally…
Is a wagon a dirigible?
It can be steered.
This is true.
We've got a lot to learn here.
I also, again, all right, you're right.
The first five pages are in the garbage.
And it does, it leaves us, those five pages contain something I think important, which is like what brings us to this world at all.
And I, okay, I read, I read a, oh yes, go ahead.
I'm wrong.
It's a, I'm confusing dirigible and submersible.
Oh, that sounds right.
Yeah, yeah.
I confused it.
People know, people have been thinking about dirigible because of that submarine that blew up.
I confused the BLE.
The BLE was the confusing one.
I almost lost faith in language because I was like a dirigible can go under water?
Well, that first submission screwed me up too.
We all bought it.
We all bought it right there.
I'm leaving it in.
I won't cut it out.
We have to know the process.
We aren't throwing those pages away.
We will not throw it.
You know what?
I only just learned how to say power more correctly.
We're all learning.
We all grow.
So, you read some copy of this place and the copy says it's like stepping inside a steampunk chocolate fantasy.
And now let me ask, whose fantasy is that?
Who has ever had that fantasy?
Why?
The biggest, we've been talking for a while.
The biggest question is why?
I mean, clearly people are into it, at least in Orlando.
But how did this come about?
Who thought that this would be a viable idea?
It has to begin with how do we, without licensing Willy Wonka, how do we do this?
Who?
Wait, I'm sorry.
Who is that?
I don't know of this man.
This came out, and I know we'll talk about the lawsuit around Orlando,
but there was a lawsuit around the Orlando one that had to do with sort of IP and this and that.
And in discovery, it came out that the original name was like the Tucson Chocolate Factory,
and then that got changed to Emporium and Savory Feast Kitchen later on.
So they must have been, I almost feel like they knew they were going to change it.
It's like so obvious that they're just doing a Willy Wonka thing without having the IP,
and they probably knew it was just a placeholder.
It's like at some point we're going to have to change this name.
But the earliest documents, the planning documents all say to some chocolate factory.
So is steampunk a way to get out of that territory, get into a different era and time?
Is it a way to justify a top hat?
Oh yeah!
Why are there also top hats here?
Well, it's steampunk.
We had to.
It's steampunk, and it goes with the goggles.
It's a woman.
Woman.
Willy Wonka's not a woman.
When was the last time you watched Willy Wonka?
Not a woman.
I can see a planning meeting like five, six, seven years ago where they were like,
we need a distinguishing thing.
We need something so this is clearly,
like the lawyer was like, you need one thing that makes it clear this is not just a Willy Wonka ripoff.
And you can see ten marketing people coming in with like ten ideas where somebody was like,
it's underwater.
And then somebody was like, it's, you know.
It belongs to Abraham Lincoln.
One thing just says, ancient Rome, question mark.
Like there's tons of ideas.
And then somebody was like, one person was like, steampunk?
And then everybody had to be told what steampunk was.
There it is.
I like the Lincoln idea that either it's happening concurrently,
like not satisfied with nearly being the president.
And also operates the factory of his dreams.
I would love it if she hocked the Daniel Day Lewis Lincoln like, this country!
That weird voice.
Wow.
You've jocked it.
Wait, I want to hear more of this.
Your impression of Daniel Day Lewis Lincoln.
He's simultaneously high pitched and gravelly.
I always thought Day Lewis's Lincoln kind of sounded like Mr.
Burns.
Like when you, some of them were like, you don't see the way that we need this country to come together.
Like this sounds like Charles Montgomery.
Did it sound like that or did it sound like, hello, I'm Lincoln, hello, hello?
Sounds like a Julia Child.
Scott Thompson's queen.
Scott Thompson's queen, boys.
I am the president, Klob, and I'm in power.
Ooh, the theater, don't mind if I do.
It's me, Jacques Vanellope, get your hysteria under control.
We've got milkshakes to make.
The Google Now's concert just got out.
Let's talk about this lawsuit a little bit more.
Alright, so it's in the air, it's maybe something people know about and haven't looked into,
that in the backstory of this establishment there was a lawsuit that threatened the entire thing.
And you hear that and you go, oh, so Wonka probably was probably the Willy Wonka people, right?
Or D'Arc, or Worm Brothers, who was it?
Not the case.
Brett, you've talked about this on Double Threat a little bit, and I've had info about it,
but if you feel like you want to give us some basics.
Yeah, it's pretty simple.
There was a guy in Ohio who apparently had a couple meetings with Universal, Orlando Universal,
and they sound like very general meetings, but he was basically pitching them on a chocolate factory restaurant.
So he was pitching them on kind of the general concept of this.
He does admit in the lawsuit that he got the idea from a drawing that his young daughter had made in elementary school,
his young daughter had made some sort of fantastical world sort of sketch,
and there was a cotton candy bridge and this and that, and there was a chocolate factory.
He seemed weirdly unaware of Willy Wonka.
And I think that explains a lot of this, is that he apparently saw this, his daughter had done this,
and he gave him the idea, he was like, a chocolate factory?
That's a brilliant idea.
Why didn't anyone ever think of this?
Why isn't?
There's no such thing in the world as a chocolate factory.
And so he apparently had a couple like generals with the universal where he was pitching them on this
and I guess showing them his daughter's drawing and being like, you do this and pay me.
I don't know how the meetings went, but then years later they come out with two sums and you could,
you know, you can see him in Ohio finding out about this and it's just his head exploding.
He's like, they did my idea and they're not paying me.
And so he sued Universal.
It went to court.
It was a trial that people had to show up for and like, and there was a jury.
An attempt at forty million dollars.
Forty million.
He was doing them for forty million dollars.
He lost and then he had to pay Universal's legal fees as a result of the lawsuit.
So he really, not a good idea.
And they just, they said he was just not able to prove, you know, to the sort of level of the law
that there was, that they had directly taken the idea from him.
And he also didn't, you know, he didn't give them any sort of like, you know,
he didn't make Universal sign anything or do an NDA or anything.
Like there was just, it was just a couple general.
Yeah, there was no paper trial.
And I've even seen in Googling the case, I've seen it on the website of a Florida lawyer
who specializes in copyright as a case.
I don't think even taking a side in it, but just saying, well, the ruling went this way
because even if he did, they did take his idea.
There was not one way that he locked that idea down.
Yeah, which sticks, because I mean, like, you know, I feel like copyright law is,
it's very easy for big corporations to win because they have huge legal departments
and they always dot their, you know, eyes and cross their T's.
But this stuff, it's so hard for people like that to win a copyright case.
It was something like this because it's just like they had a couple meetings
and maybe that at some point percolated and became twosomes.
There might be some legitimacy to it.
But he just had no way of proving it in a way that he was going to win the case.
But there's also is the specter of Willy Wonka over all of this that like,
this is no, neither of you's idea.
This idea like, both of you.
I was like, just call it a day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's another bizarre aspect of that, which is that the drawing that his daughter did
came from another business he was trying to do called 1-800-Santa Claus.
I forgot.
There's no further details about that.
But just, hey, draw me a map of the North Pole.
And then she drew such a map, which included a small building called the Chocolate Factory.
He said, what is that?
And she said, that is where the elves eat.
And then that became the whole.
That became it.
Yeah, that's right.
I'd like to know more about what 1-800-Santa Claus was.
That sounds good.
I mean, there's a number we could call.
It's going to go to the long haul.
Try, yeah.
Universal Bot Bet 2.
That just reruns you to the book booking a hotel for them.
The number you've dialed has been disconnected.
All right, let's find out.
You want to try?
Let's try it.
Let's find out.
1-800-Santa Claus.
Please leave your message after the tone followed by the pound key.
Hi, is this Santa?
Just curious.
Thanks.
Goodbye.
I guess they'll call back.
Don't leave the phone on silent.
Make sure they can call back during the podcast.
Well, if it's Santa, he will know.
Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Does this answer your question?
Hello?
Hello, Joe.
You've been very good this year.
But not when you were nine.
How did you get my personal number?
Are you being mean about Toothsome on a podcast?
That's not very nice.
I do have such a soft spot for people like that, though.
This guy's clearly just trying to come up with something.
Dreaming big.
He's trying.
He got a meeting with Universal.
I was going to say, who is the guy to get a…
Some guy in Ohio.
No, he's in Ohio.
Yeah, I don't understand what he is.
He's an entrepreneur of some kind.
And now he just has the…
He has the Facebook group, The Chocolate Factory,
which is mostly pictures of three chocolates next to each other,
and then also the full legal affidavit explaining this entire case.
What I just read about when I entered Santa Claus is from his Facebook,
which has a lot of hashtags like
Justice for So and So, whatever it was,
Toothsome Chocolate Emporium, Toothsome Chocolate Factory,
Chocolate Factory.
Maybe people will use the hashtag of what it was supposed to be called,
and that will prove me right.
Does he have any punny hashtags like
Toothsome Chocolate Fraudtory or anything?
It feels like there's a missed opportunity there.
He needed a punch-up guy to really get a good…
Truthless Emporium.
If he's listening, we'll do the documentary.
We'll do Truthless, the Truth About Toothsome.
If you're watching this, you assuredly have been to
and enjoyed the worldwide phenomenon Toothsome Chocolate.
What if I told you it's not everything you think it is?
Do you think anyone ever sued over Wompoppers?
That they felt like they had the idea for…
Yeah, C.
O.
Wompopper III.
Got cut out of the story.
Was like, what about me?
I went to culinary school.
All this backstory and mythology,
and now we know legal troubles that they've had,
I think we should maybe for a little bit boil it down to
the basics, which is the experience of going there.
We touched on that with you, Joe, a little bit about
a perceived lapse in quality between the first and second.
In either one, is there anything you want to tell us about
your specific Toothsome time?
which is a mistake, I think.
Which part?
I would say the dinner part.
I've done it with a group of friends, and going twice in the same calendar year
is a way to test the patience of your close friends and loved ones.
You went for dinner because the pasta menu is not available at lunch.
Yes.
From what I've seen online.
The first time I went, I was disappointed that Penelope and Jacques
were not around.
It's just like, well, what's the point here?
Can I say, I've never been to any of these with them there.
You have, so can I?
I have, yeah.
I've got a picture with them.
They were there, asked them a couple questions.
They did their whole routine.
But it's, I think, just once they've been there.
It's really random whether they're there or not.
I have a picture with them.
Oh, there you go.
I have a number of pictures and an extended video.
Oh, wow.
With Penelope and Jacques.
Send it my way.
We'll post it.
We went to, so a group of friends, we like, we're all on the A-list for AMC,
and when we can, we like to pair a restaurant with the movie.
And we were like crossing our fingers that Toothsome would make it to Wonka.
Because it was like, this place seems like it's not long for this world.
Like, is it still going to be around?
And we got lucky, and so we went and saw, we went to Wonka after we went to Toothsome.
And we spent some time, more time in the restaurant than I would have expected
because we had wanted to go in the theme park, but it was a, it was like a Thursday that was a blackout day.
So my pass didn't work.
Around the holidays, there were more blackout dates, I think, at the park.
So we just had to, like, kill a lot of time at City Walk.
So we just ended up going to the restaurant sitting near the dessert foundry.
And, but Penelope and Jacques were there, and they were making the rounds together, holding hands.
At each table, just kind of, you know, saying hello or whatever.
People seem to not really be engaging, maybe are a little confused as to why these freaks are joining their table.
But we essentially engaged in a four-minute improv scene with these two characters as they're talking in character.
And they seemed to be, like, kind of into it because it was like, oh, people actually want to talk to us.
They're not, like, eating and kind of, you know, shooing us away.
So we got, we got to talk to them.
And Jacques is essentially C-3PO.
He, like, you know, he kind of talks like this.
He has one of these dandy British accents.
I didn't know until right now that he talked.
Yeah, and it's unclear.
I wondered if he just made, like, clank clank clang.
No, he talks.
There's, like, a bit of a filter on the microphone to make him sound exactly robotic, but, like, mechanical.
Yeah, he has one of those speaker boxes.
Yes, yes.
And you can see, like, 20 sets behind them.
It's usually a universal person with an iPad controlling it.
I didn't see that.
It's not the person, so it's not the person in the suit.
Somebody, a little steps away.
I didn't know this.
Wait, did you feel like they weren't responding with, like, real sentences?
No, no, they were taught, they were just, I think, doing the levels on the mic box.
Oh, I see.
I think the person inside is responding.
I see.
Yeah, they're talking.
The hand holding just clicked for me, too.
As someone who's tried to navigate a horror convention while wearing a mask, Jacques has no visibility.
Oh, right, right.
That's great.
Practical thing, yeah.
But, yeah, we ask them a lot of questions.
We ask them what do they recommend on the menu, which I got to, you know, I got to have the wonderful moment of Jacques going,
well, I quite like the flatbread barbecue chicken.
Oh, and yes, the aji tuna.
Isn't that good?
Oh, yes, it's wonderful, Jacques.
Like, getting them, because at first she was like, oh, the chocolate almond bread is very popular,
and it's like, okay, that fits with the theme, but then when they started just going towards, like, hey, when the Brussels sprouts are…
Our Napa cabbage is very fresh.
Yeah.
That's better than, like, everything is good.
Yeah, it's true.
I ate that when you asked, like, hey, what should I get?
And I'm like, oh, the whole thing is good.
Ew, you can't go wrong.
I don't want to sidetrack, but like, okay, if the whole thing is about your parents,
we will find you wherever chocolate can be found, and then they make it sure.
What is obligating Toothsome to make aji tuna salads available?
If chocolate is what is to lure her parents, she should not be wasting energy and time making anything from the savory feast kitchen side of this restaurant.
It should exclusively be about chocolate production, and like, she should be expanding more.
Like, if we need to cover the spread here to find her parents.
We don't need…
Yeah, every one of these should not be for businesses at once.
Focus on the one.
Also, because non-canonically, the savory feasts are shitty feasts.
So, don't even bother.
We think created the savory to just feed Penelope, because she can't leave, because she doesn't know if she leaves, they might come when she's gone.
If she has to eat her meals in there, if she eats only sweets, she's going to die.
Penelope quite likes dog food.
Yeah, that's a good point.
That's a very good point, right?
Girls gotta eat.
Professors gotta eat.
But yeah, it was very, very stupid.
And Jock eats.
Well, I will tell you…
Because he recommended the pizza, I'm just saying.
So he's obviously eating as well.
He's powered by the savory.
Well, we asked, we had said, we were, you know, like, I forget how we got to it, but we said something about like, you know, like, we'll give you a little bit of oil if you're good or whatever.
And then Penelope had to go, oh, he runs on chocolate.
He goes, oh, yes, I run on chocolate.
And so we learned that this is a robot whose oil is liquid chocolate.
Oh, OK.
That is part of the lore.
Why do you have to, I mean, I guess leaving some mystery is good that you had to like engage in a conversation to figure out.
But that's number one thing I want to know in the story.
I don't want to learn about the parents yet.
Instead of just Jock, it should be chocolate powered robot.
Yeah.
These are things we should be getting in line one of the the exposition.
It's interesting that Penelope intervened to say that it almost you know, sometimes in sci fi where like a character thinks one thing is like, I wonder if they tell Jock he's like Jock thinks he's powered by chocolate and you can't like ruin the myth that if you ever saw like a rear mirror or something and he saw what's going on inside.
You know, like there might be some like maybe they tell Jock.
I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, deeply.
But but I know you're saying, yeah, right.
They don't want they don't want to tell him that he's like he's powered by like battery parts that have to be mined from impoverished countries that destroy the planet as you harvest them.
Your chocolate comes from Boston Dynamics.
By the way, in chip wrapping the powered by discussion, I believe, latte the dog is powered by coffee.
That is that is part of his if you were wondering coffee milkshake.
Okay, this makes sense.
Why limited though?
I wonder why limited.
I don't know.
It sounded really good.
Oh, yeah.
Do some of Jock's coffee here.
Jock has coffee too.
Cream coffee.
But not latte.
It's not latte coffee.
Concoctions.
Does that mean it's is it just beans?
It's just beans in here.
But the dude the language always makes you think something else is going on.
Coffee flavored candy or so.
Is it ground or whole beans?
This smells like coffee.
It smells like sweet coffee.
Okay.
And it's beans.
It says here on the back.
Jock engineers his coffee concoctions using the finest beans in the universe.
Fused with the Emporium's most tooth some flavors.
The most tooth some of all the flavors.
That's a last name.
That does that means nothing to me as an adjective.
Hmm.
We're all baffled.
Interesting.
Jason, would you eat a bean raw?
Well, I love chocolate covered espresso beans, but I feel like those are specifically made to be.
They're still roasted.
That's true.
Yeah, you don't want to do a raw one.
Do we miss anything about your you had a great conversation.
Oh, yeah.
The barbecue chicken flatbread was bad.
Surprise surprise.
He has no taste buds though.
No, I know.
I guess humans like different things.
It quite tastes like chocolate because you run on chocolate.
Just chocolate with a little bit of metal.
That's what I like.
Ah, yes.
Perfect.
It just like go it's like go straight through him.
It's like hits the floor.
It's going through a mouth, but it just like.
We did ask them.
We were like, are you pro or anti Wonka?
And that did make them break character and like immediately like laugh because I think they were not expecting such a kind of complicated.
Question for them.
And I think they did trivia with me.
Whoa.
They asked, what was first company to make a chocolate bar?
And the answer is Cadbury.
I already knew that.
Did you try to say it's toothsome?
Of course.
Hit me with a hard one.
One of the questions did reference Willy Wonka.
Really?
So I don't remember the other.
They're playing fast and loose.
So yeah.
The official response was that it's healthy competition and it's good for both brands to be happening rising tidal.
So she lives all dirigible.
So this was addressed in meetings then that feels like that was somewhat like maybe because I kind of watching her Penelope.
She took the question watching her like laugh and then you kind of see the actor and then you see the gears.
It felt it felt like an actual improv moment of like I think this seems like the right answer to this.
Very political.
Yeah.
As diplomatic.
Certainly.
And then also a friend of ours brought had bought steampunk goggles on Amazon to bring them and then put them on as we saw them walking by.
They laughed at that.
I think we were giving them a good time.
Especially compared to like these families who are just maybe maybe some of them don't speak English or like they're just like not interested.
Whatever it is that they're just kind of like what.
OK.
Hi.
Hello.
Goodbye.
They might think that people are people are coming around to do one of those like take a picture things where they charge you twenty dollars.
Yeah.
That's usually just kind of go like no I don't know.
Thanks.
We look them in the eye.
Yeah.
We're getting soaked in most restaurants.
If someone's coming to your table that's about they're not your waiter.
That's what's going to happen.
Yeah.
Does Bucca do that.
Yes.
They do this.
Yeah.
Bucca does do that.
This robot is going to sell me the most expensive and crappiest rows of my life.
And the only other thing from my experience is just I don't know that we have fully like given the proper explanation to how expansive the gift shop is like they're just so many knickknacks.
And you know Brett brought some stuff but and also we haven't mentioned that there's wardrobe that you can get goggles hats.
I forgot that one of my friends it was bought me a hat that I have in my home.
You have a top hat.
It's not a top hat though it's like almost like a bowler.
So they have different styles.
That's the thing is it's really expansive the different things that no one will buy.
I do some different types of hats and goggles and this type of chocolate and shot glasses and mugs and shirts and high level stuff like in you'll see like in glass cases like a little like member like like figurine.
I have.
Yeah I have pictures of that expensive big price tag on you can buy and I'll read some of them.
You can buy like it says all with top hat on book stack and it's like a I don't know if it's cop bronze like a bronze statue for real and it's fifty four ninety five.
You can buy octopus secret trinket box for ninety four ninety five.
I'm not going to lie.
They're not bad.
Look trinkets are just everywhere and you're trying to get a handle on octopus magnifying glass.
Forty dollars is octopus a pre agreed steampunk animal.
That's a great question that I don't know the answer to.
Is it does it tie I mean it feels right because of like twenty thousand lead maybe.
Yeah steampunk octopus spirit decanter eighty nine ninety five.
But we've also established dirigible is do not go in the water.
I guess.
Well right.
Yeah dirigible is do not and yet all this octopus merch.
Yeah right.
Question underground twenty thousand leads in the sea like bio dome is sort of steampunk.
Isn't it the video game series that's all under.
I was shocked.
I was like the poly shore.
I don't think so but I'll hear you out.
The posters really hit the steampunk elements.
I think underwater is in is in universe.
Yeah because there's another fish there's another fish statue for one hundred five dollars.
Then there's all with goggles and jet pack thirty four ninety five.
Who is buying owls with jet packs at this disappointing restaurant.
You know as a reminder when Julie Prescott was on I forget whether she told us this in the episode or after her husband and her.
When they went to do some play the game where they would cover the price tag and say how much is this.
And then when they would reveal it they would just laugh and laugh there.
OK two more real quick skull on gear stand one hundred and twenty dollars skull on gear stand.
What are the odds that this is inventory from somewhere else.
A high high chance that that's right.
But then there's also steampunk decorative skull with movable jaw which is for some reason sixty nine dollars.
So yeah you can you can like have it talk I guess.
Maybe these were all props that were built for one of the dark universe movie.
The dark you know maybe they got ahead of themselves and now they got to move them.
Well you know Russell Crowe's Dr.
Jekyll character was in charge of like a shield like agency.
So maybe these are some of the artifacts he's captured of the supernatural realm.
The whole series is going to come in a big fight with an octopus.
That's where the dark universe is all hitting.
No.
OK.
I wish you'd been wearing.
I've actually worn this.
I understand.
What is that satisfied.
On double threat one live stream I had to smash a geode as part of the live stream and for some reason just felt right to be in steampunk gear while you're smashing a geode.
Is it Gallagher asked to wear that type of hat and smash something.
That might have been the connection I was making in my head was it like yeah.
And it was so yeah I I I'd already gotten these for fun but then I've actually worn them.
Yeah.
OK.
Well I didn't mean to shame you and I just wanted to know what I was headed with as the manufacturer of this.
Oh oh.
And I don't know a ton.
There's not a ton there but I just wanted to say so it's a it's a company called a low low low.
Oh it says it in there.
OK great.
But what I just want to say what that stands for.
Oh I see.
Does it say it in there.
Oh no.
I never noticed that.
It stands for everybody is laughing on planet Earth.
That's.
Check out this asshole.
Sure.
Everybody is laughing on planet Earth.
Wow.
That is I think that takes the crown of dumbest acronym for most Southwest Grill H.
A.
That's right.
Musicians outlaws and entertainers also the acronym of the hashtag laugh with a low peer.
And it's yes.
It's not with the E.
L.
I.
It's E.
Just make it everyone's.
Put an apostrophe.
What are they doing.
I don't know.
Wow.
What a brand.
You can also you can buy monocles there too.
Yeah.
I don't think we've addressed that.
I was also we were in the store with an upcoming guest who I don't want to spoil but our guest
for phase six sector one.
place is if you look on the railings like on the second floor level that there's like
basically there's still guitars.
It's guitars.
They just painted them gold.
It's Hard Rock Cafe guitars and they never change that.
So to catch that detail next time.
That's actually an OSHA like oh the mysterious organization.
Do you think.
Do you think those are any famous guitars or less famous guitars they were just like
let's just paint over them.
Yeah.
I mean it's like it's thousands of guitar shapes.
There's a Steve Vai signature under there.
Yeah that's what I'm saying.
I'm like you can either like try to find a buyer or just paint over them.
Can I talk about my experience.
Yes.
To some.
So I went to the Hollywood one about a month ago for a lunch on a Saturday with Jane and
I had only been to the Florida one a couple of times.
I went in 2017 a year after it opened and I just kind of walked through the restaurant
and the smell of like garlic Parmesan fries and cocoa was not a combination.
It may be a little crazy but I went to the takeout counter and I ordered like a brownie
sundae and they handed me like a clear plastic dinner plate with a sundae on it.
So then I'm like oh I guess I'll just sit by the water and eat my dinner plate.
It wasn't bronze or they didn't serve it inside a big goggle.
It wasn't even a bowl.
Except to do some experiments.
Ice cream on a plate perhaps.
Pretty quickly.
Have an open mind.
I mean it was night but pretty quickly on August night in Florida it started kind of
sloshing around.
It transforms into an ice cream soup.
An experiment.
So a little easier this time.
So we ate a full meal.
I had to try one of the baked milkshakes.
So I got a brownie milkshake and here you can see me looking at it lovingly.
Chocolate is your god.
Yeah.
And then we got a pineapple upside down cake milkshake which is in theory vegan.
And they were out of soy milk and or the vegan ice cream so we didn't quite get it vegan.
And then Gene got the avocado toast and I mostly was the one who ate the chocolate bread
which I only ate a slice of and then ate it for breakfast like three days in a row.
You took it home and ate it three days later.
I could only eat one slice of it.
You had two milkshakes to have.
We were sharing them.
Jason started spreading peanut butter on his chocolate.
Well it comes with caramel butter.
And this is like you have to pay for it but the bread they bring to your table like the Italian restaurant they would
is essentially cake.
It's so sweet and soft.
It's like the first thing they bring you is a large chocolate cake.
It's sweet.
It's like a breakfast cake.
Chocolate almond bread with salted caramel butter.
I didn't like this.
I'm glad you had a good time eating it for three days in a row at home.
But I'm like this fed my meal was like okay well at least this will be great.
I thought it was really bland.
If we're fusing savory and chocolate that's the point.
I know they're going to mess it up with like it's on chicken wings or whatever but the bread is going to be good right.
I didn't like it.
Am I crazy Jason.
I thought it was fine.
He didn't like it either.
I didn't love it.
Normally.
Another day.
Back to the bread.
I love that kind of almond flavoring and I thought it was just like not enough chocolate too much of that almond extract flavoring.
So knowing I was going to have a lot of chocolate I went like light meal.
I got a superfood salad and it was pretty good.
Reveal it's like arugula.
Scared us with that.
You really showed it.
Romaine and avocado and quinoa.
Like I thought it was pretty good.
Gee they told her she was she's like I'm vegetarian.
What can I eat.
What do you recommend.
And they're like oh any of the burgers you can get a Beyond Burger Patty.
So she got to be on burger Patty on the teriyaki burger.
Teriyaki glaze grilled pineapple chutney.
Shiitake mushroom Asian slaw sesame seed bun.
Pretty quickly she took a bite and really made us like a sour face.
Like she did not.
She was like oh and then I had some and I'm like yeah this is not good.
Like I don't know how you messed up a Beyond Burger.
You took it home and ate it for three days.
Three days really breaking me down.
Like we it was really overcooked.
Again I don't know how you overcook lab grown fake meat.
Was it like tough like when you were chewing?
It was tough and it was like.
Was it chocolatey did they.
I wish it was chocolatey.
No like the teriyaki like nothing tasted right.
And I don't think we have.
We have never done this before.
We sent this back.
Can I.
With the exception of Jason's salad my thesis for Toothsome is nothing tastes right.
No.
Nothing tastes right.
You compare everyone's stories.
Absolutely.
Everyone has the same story down to the candy down to the savory meals down to the sugary meals.
Nothing tastes right.
And I don't know why.
Like because every other you know we've said this before on the show you know Margaritaville you give a bet you get a bad meal.
You go back next time and you get an OK meal like you're always you're rolling the dice a little bit.
But for some reason no matter what coast it is nothing tastes right here.
It's funny you say that because you know Jane got the avocado toast appetizer and it just looks off.
I don't know what I'm looking if you hadn't I couldn't have guessed what you're showing us.
So busy that's a lot of toast.
It looks like spin on it like an avocado shop tomatoes but then crispy onions a crema and balsamic.
Like there's too much stuff on it.
I see intellectual understanding you're saying but really all I know is the feeling of what you're saying is that this didn't taste.
If nothing was right.
The only the only exception I think for me when I've been there is I think the milkshakes all tastes like very good fun milkshake.
I agree with that.
Great.
The brownie was I find a lot of place brownies are like really stale or dry.
But this was really better.
I think the milkshake is fine.
Yeah but that's what they do there.
And I go this is fine.
But like you put a throw a brownie in a McDonald's milkshake and I think it would taste the same.
They at least there's thought put in there's a throw up or something.
It feels like a milkshake like a milkshake stand that that sure unnecessarily build out a bigger menu.
I would say the what's a black tap is better down at downtown Disney.
At least it was a year or two ago when we had our crazy milkshakes down there.
I think so.
I mean they're both trying to do the like Instagram heavy like crazy better that you got the one with the big Jason a full slice of cake.
I think for about five six seven years the whole time we've been doing this podcast we've been talking about well it's the Instagram of all the first year whose Instagram feed in 2024 is still like a milkshake in a jar not a glass and with a rice crispy treat on top.
I'm sorry I'm sorry.
A dessert on top of a dessert.
I need to save this.
I need to follow whoever this is.
I need to know everything about them.
I need to know where to get that.
Who's still who's getting knocked out of their chairs by a tall milkshake in the year of our Lord 2024.
I don't know.
I know you know and you're right.
That is that is the copy that they all say shut off.
It's just like I'm just like that.
I just I'm just deconstructing the notion that this would be like the coolest post.
They're so common now.
Yeah no they're really common.
And like then you run into times I think Mike got well with nerds rope and the rappers still have on.
I didn't like that ice cream.
I did not like the rapper in the thing still because I don't know if they sanitize that rapper.
I was trying to find something there's a there's a like a burger place in Dubai that is so grotesque in their different Instagramable attempts that where it's just like it's piled this high and it's just cheese and then there's like a firecracker and like a life of firecracker that would like you would see at the Hollywood Bowl.
Or something that's that big to the equivalent of like Fashion Week when you see people walk the runway and you're like well that's obviously not meant to be worn.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah it's like they're getting to the point where it's like this is just an art piece at a point or some weird item yes like kitsch or something.
But surely someone can't sit down and eat that.
I don't even know where you would begin right.
The milkshakes honestly are kind of arduous to get through their kind of there's a lot.
Well I didn't finish mine.
Yeah I get mine was figure out the architecture of it and make sure you don't spill it.
Well they actually.
My mouth is bleeding and Jason still drank from my straw.
By the way by the way since we talked about that a couple days ago video proof that Jason did drink from your straw.
I tried.
It's in the video.
Jason I bit my mouth there's so much blood in my mouth you probably don't want to do this.
I mean.
You only live once.
The best milkshakes ever had it's usually you know there was a place someone asked about this on Twitter.
Lately where I was talking about Delaware or something there's a place called Charcoal Pit Wilmington Delaware.
It's been there since the 1940s or 50s at least.
They have these amazing milkshakes.
They're literally just the metal mixing cup and they give you a glass and you pour it in glass.
That's the best tasting milkshake.
I don't think these crazy milkshakes it's never as good at least here they were like oh do you want us to rinse out the souvenir glass and put it in a paper cup for you with a lid.
And we're like yeah please.
Well this is they give you or to go you get the plastic to some cup.
And then you have it is a struggle because you're like once I'm done with this walking around I got to go in a bathroom and rinse it out so I can transport it without getting like just liquid milkshake all over my car.
That happened at the Epcot Food Festival.
I had like the crazy pickle plastic cup and yes I have to rinse this out in a bathroom because I promised the level keeper could have this.
And if you get the mint one which is my favorite it's like entrusted with chocolate around the rim.
You don't have to wash it out you have to like figure out how to like scrub the chocolate off.
There's several milkshakes that are like that where they have the adhesive style stuff around it with sprinkles.
Because I got like a seasonal milkshake when I was there in December that had like gingerbread and stuff and it was just encrusted with this like.
And I was like am I supposed to attempt to eat this.
I think you are but then also it's like sometimes with that stuff I feel like it's decorative.
That's how I found it.
Like it's a Christmas because when I was a kid I learned that you're not supposed to eat a gingerbread house.
Because like the I mean most of them at least the ones you buy like a store bought kit.
It's like actually the frosting is glued don't eat that.
Because the frosting won't keep the house up and that really ruined the whole thing for me.
It's not for eating it's for Instagramming that post is going to blow people's minds.
Like I wonder what would if I just posted a picture of just a picture of a milkshake with a brownie on top and there's sprinkles birthday cake sprinkles and a candle or something.
And my caption was just like holy moly.
For the win.
Would that perform well.
I think it's worth a try.
Maybe I just got to do that.
Well no one will ever see it because the algorithm will just bury it under.
Unless I can catch the tailwinds of fancy cake milkshake Instagram that algorithm which is seemingly thriving.
I might end up with a hundred thousand new subscribers.
We have our own Dr.
Toothsome on the show and it's Jason Sheridan.
And I think that if he gets in the lab he could concoct something that would blow the socks off everyone on Instagram.
As far as a crazy contraption of a milkshake hot dog hot dog straw.
Maybe it's maybe it's like here we go.
Maybe it's like a big it's a big like a two gallon bucket full of milkshake.
And then there's a full pizza.
And then there's another like a milkshake on top of it with a hot dog straw.
And then is the pizza touching the milkshake.
It's soaking in the milkshake.
Could at least have a nasty plastic wrapper still on it.
The pizza is wrapped.
The pizza is a tombstone pizza with its wrapper still on.
It's soaking in the milkshake.
Can the milkshake cup be a bunch of pressed together pepperonis.
Yes it can be that.
Well now hold on a minute.
There's no need to pay.
I can't even get it out.
I think we could do it.
I think we could actually up the arms race that is Instagramable milkshakes.
I don't like this stuff that much.
I wanted to taste it.
I don't want to talk about.
This is about.
Likes and quits.
That's what the world is in 2024.
I don't know if anybody's looked around and realized it.
Seems like everybody's crazy for liking as of about a year or so ago.
Breaking news.
You know Scott if you posted a milkshake I don't think it would necessarily blow things up.
But the key is you have to start an account called LA Dessert Dude.
It's only like graphic super close shots of overflowing ice cream sandwiches and milkshakes.
And then you would get to a hundred.
Yeah.
And those like labels like the captions that never move.
Like OK so there's this place in Sherman Oaks.
Yes.
And they do an incredible.
Because you always see these things and you're like is this an expert or is it somebody who
started doing this six days ago.
Oh it's that.
It's usually that.
I followed a couple of those and I thought it's like oh I'll get to see some places that
have been here forever.
And they spend so little time on that and so much time getting their cheese bowl correct.
Yeah right.
And then you're like getting that.
This is a phrase I've learned recently.
You got to get the cheese pole.
That's like I know it's like a Pizza Hut commercial.
Is that like the fondue?
That's like it's like.
I've seen it's like a fondue like they have a big cheese wheel or like they do like at
an Italian restaurant they do it live.
Table side cheese.
This is like indistinguishable from body horror.
It's like there's so much like this kid is in a goo.
There's a lot of goo.
I do click on it though.
And I do follow some of those accounts.
Oh I watch all the goo.
And that's what my my discover page and Instagram tends to be like pizza and like weird chips
and ice cream.
You got a goo freak.
Start feeding me goo.
Give me the goo.
What's up LA goo freak here.
Wow that grilled cheese was cut in half and they very slowly separated it.
I'm trying to think of like what the copy is for these this type of video because it's
like I've been hearing a lot about do some chocolate emporium and I decided I had to
go and check it out for myself.
It's on Universal City Walk which is by the theme park but I decided not to go today.
So instead I went and got the seasonal gingerbread milkshake and then I got a flatbread pizza
with barbecue chicken on it.
The flatbread pizza was bomb.
And so and so was the gingerbread milkshake.
Pretty good.
I think I'll maybe come here again and I'll maybe try some of the Brussels sprouts.
I got to see a robot.
Joe that was so good.
We can just hold that video.
Let's just start this account.
Cheese Louise.
And start raking in the money.
Do these things make money.
I think so.
How?
I've seen some of these some of these places suddenly they're like I decided to go to BJ's
to try one of their famous pizookies and I was like wait a second.
What are you going to BJ's?
You don't go to BJ's.
You go to taco shops and you look and it says add on the bottom.
Oh yeah yeah yeah.
I'm here at Dubai's first Shake Shack to see.
Because there are restaurants to have started to utilize this strategy because there's I'm
not going to say the name of it but there's a burger place right up the block here.
A smash burger place that has they started doing it was just sort of you know run of
the mill and they started doing some crazy social media like viral marketing.
If you drive by it that place has a line like down the block.
Yeah.
And like I used to eat there before they had the lines.
Totally fine run of the mill like burgers.
But you would think this place is like is like burning up some specials going on in
there as because they started like working with these like influencers and stuff and
they are packed every every day of the week.
Well there's a brunch place in the area too and Giro del Toro posted a picture of it
and we had been there a couple of times.
Similarly like yeah it was a nice breakfast lunch place and then it got more crowded and
we even we said as we were walking in with that it's like oh you see Giro del Toro posted
a plate from here.
He did not do that video though where he was like I'm in the valley and I went to.
Yeah.
I was at the model shop with Steven Spielberg.
Giro del Toro is L.
A.
brunch bro.
What I encountered was anything but a nightmare.
I'm hungry.
You mentioned body hard.
Some of these do have like David Cronenberg style editing tricks and stuff for I'm like
I'm dizzy like I feel unnerved watching.
That's how they keep you.
And I have to eat it.
And it's like an 80 year old man scooping chili into a bowl.
It's nothing out of the ordinary but something like whoa look at that dump.
Look at that scoop.
Let me hit my tooth some meal a little bit.
I went to a long I went a while back a future podcast where I guess Van Robe show got a
group together and I was like oh I'll pop up.
Well you know I'm going to be up there I'm sure for research for the side but you know
I'll do one that's you know where I'm not absorbing every detail one that's just for
and then the meal was such that I was like well that'll do it.
I won't be going back here again because I got some.
OK we haven't talked about dessert cocktails which don't work.
Yes.
Chocolate old fashioned bad.
That's that.
That's cool in your head but I hated what I got.
I feel like people maybe somebody likes the PB Cup old fashioned better.
But do you remember you did.
I did not.
I did not get any alcohol.
Some people in my party did and I forget.
I think it was chocolate martinis or something.
Yeah.
And maybe maybe some of it was like chocolate coffee kind of thing.
But I stayed away from that part of the menu.
Didn't work.
Didn't blend at all.
Can I ask has anyone here had an espresso martini.
I hear those are popular nowadays.
Do those work.
Do you like those.
Yeah I like espresso martinis.
OK.
Yeah it's nice to if you particularly if you if you have agreed to go out with drink someone
with someone and you go and you're like it's been a long day and you're very tired.
Oh OK.
The perfect like cocktail to get to give you a little bit of a there's you know there's
typically like you know some sort of espresso based liqueur in it that you know it's like
it's like having coffee in a drink.
insane.
You know espresso martinis tend to be pretty good.
A little more balanced.
Yeah.
And I had is there a root beer old fashioned on that menu.
I guess where I had a root beer old fashioned.
Not great.
I much prefer the what's the Irish pub in Universal.
And they do a Guinness old fashioned which I really we call we did an episode about that
on Second Gate.
We call that the Irish bar where you can get hammered.
Yeah.
That's part of my core is I take Sandy over to minions.
I stop off with the Irish pub.
Yeah.
Get us all fast and then we go to Minions.
Oh geez.
I like the Guinness old fashioned.
It feels more like it's a little you know it's more just sort of in you know there's
no risk to that.
The root sweet.
The root sweet just doesn't blend in.
Unless it's fully a dessert with a little bit of alcohol.
Yeah I was not a fan.
The thing that I ate was the oh sorry.
I was just going to say I was looking through my pictures of from this outing and I did
find I think what is a chocolate martini with a like full biscotti on top.
And so they're doing that for the alcoholic drinks too just like pile of dessert on top
of it.
Instagram that hurry you that's just been in your pocket and you're not profiting off
it.
Hurry up.
So I heard they're putting biscotti on top of martinis.
That's one of those things that you do not want to get if you're not planning on eating.
Like if someone just if I did not order a biscotti I don't want you to bring me just
the thing.
I need to know that I'm getting it.
I have to account for that in my plans.
Also a biscotti meant to be dipped to soften it a little.
Yeah in gin.
Not meant to be put sideways.
It's just like all of it is wet now.
A little drink bridge.
I did want to get something that where there was a chocolate component.
Stupid me.
I was I did never until I until I took my first sip of that drink and my first bite
of that not good chocolate almond bread.
It did not occur to me until that second.
Oh this place could be bad in all those years we're waiting.
How am I not trained at this point from all this time on this podcast and all this time
in city.
But this one I was like it's impossible.
It just never even entered my head that it could be.
By that point it was too late.
I had ordered the cocoa pork tenderloin which they describe as an innovative dish featuring
a chocolate crust and reduction along with sweet potato mash and vegetables.
And I'm like oh that sounds oh you know because we're in that area of like what's the savor
like mole.
That'll probably be like mole influenced.
And then it comes you don't taste the chocolate whatsoever which thank God because that would
have fought.
But also these are just the blandest pork tenderloins.
There were less on my plate than there were in the picture I saw on the Web site earlier
in the day.
This was wedding food.
Sometimes wedding food is great but sometimes you go to a wedding and it's like well that
wasn't that good but they had to rush it all out and make a lot of you know I'm here for
the party and it doesn't matter.
I'm just glad I ate something that it was that.
But you forgive it at a wedding.
You don't forgive when you're paying thirty forty dollars for it.
And you're and you realize all the money went to you know the the embroidering on the book
menu that's in front of you.
So that was insane.
And Mike I want to make sure you get a little bit of time.
Several days ago we talked about some of your meal experience but I don't but Joe and Brett
don't know about this.
And I we're going to have to go backwards a little bit but there's some stuff you didn't
say about it either.
Yeah.
OK.
Let me just pull up my pictures here.
So I wanted to order.
I wanted to you know most people say they want to go and have the restaurant experience.
I decided to test what it's like to go as far as what it's like to take a picture.
Take a meal and not to go to the restaurant.
What it's like.
Excuse me to go out.
What it's like to go with to go.
So right.
So and this of course was in Orlando not here in Los Angeles where I'm sure your meal would
have been which I'm sure.
Yeah.
They got it down because there's easier parking spots right by the restaurant where you could
go for an Uber Eats or people are Uber Eats and some left and right.
And of course I would you have you have you told me the name of it because they took it
off the menu.
You say you have to say it.
That's the rule.
Is it fly.
Is it flounder.
Yes.
Flounder Almondine.
Oh brother.
To go to the other side of the lagoon.
I love Bugada Pappo with Almondine now.
I'm worried I'm going to say it wrong.
Welcome brother.
On the edge.
Yeah.
So it's really it scares me when to say it.
So this food this was like once it was opened this was like dry flounder.
I want to show them a photo of it because it's hideous.
Well the sector the other day described it as looking down into an open trash can.
Now of course they didn't like just because it was in a to go container it's not going
to have the presentation.
Of course I get that.
Why are you apologizing for them.
But I would say that you would I will say this confusion is probably what you would
think when you see it.
It's an almond sliver.
It's just like almond slivers.
It's like what the bag you get at Trader Joe's that maybe goes on top of your oatmeal.
They just open that bag and like yeah.
And so like half like I don't think it's I think it might be an accident that half of
the fish is burned one side and then the other is not.
It's like oh is it blackened trout or something and you're like well why would it why would
half of it be blackened and the other half wouldn't be.
So that was a slant that day.
They had one of the legs collapsed.
Yeah.
And I don't know I'm not always having almondine of any kind.
So I don't know maybe I don't know.
Almondine standards in 2024.
Maybe I don't know what I'm talking about but I bit into it and it was just it was disgusting.
It was so gross and I really I love fish.
I'm not a picky eater.
I will eat OK shit constant.
I don't care.
This was really gross and it was only I would say like we had some do we.
Oh yeah I forgot to we say the mix up even.
No no no no we say that for this.
Sorry.
So we had to go.
There was the question of how do you do to go orders.
Yes.
In Orlando and I tried the whole stand you realize that you had to go I tried to call.
I was on the phone with tooth some walking through city walk trying to be like operator get me to go counter it.
Well they still haven't assembled the phone from gears.
Well right.
They still say ahoy ahoy.
Yeah there was a big.
Is the answering message in universe is it like Penelope or Jock or.
I was having a tough time finding the number for it.
I was and then I think I did call it and they were like you cannot order on the phone.
Like you cannot.
We will not do that.
And I said OK and they said you can come in come in and do it and I said OK and you go in and like I was saying it's packed in there.
Who's who of Orlando is just you can't you can't stand it's uncomfortable if you were to stand.
So somebody finally directs me and goes you have to go upstairs to the bar to order a to go thing and I go OK so you go upstairs and again it's packed everywhere.
And I go up to the bartender and I take a stick spiral staircase like in your kind of big kind of.
I mean there's a couple of different lamps are unbelievable and then there's like animations we haven't talked about that.
Yeah.
Right.
Yes on the ceiling on the walls they flesh out this whole world of like conveyor belts and lots of boxes going by.
It's wild animation all the money 95 percent of money went to the wrong things.
I mean the right things for us.
And I also believe I said this on the show that I kind of believe that they also are stealing some Harry Potter aesthetic as well.
That one especially especially that one there.
There it's a feeling of like being in some of the Harry Potter shop.
So I kind of feel like they were like well let's make people feel as comfortable here as they are when they're in the Harry Potter land and what we own this.
So like we're slowly transit like transitioning them into our own place so they can spend as much money on flounder almond.
Because the casinos that are like 30 minutes away from Las Vegas like before you get it's like if you don't want to go all the way to Harry Potter world.
Yes.
Don't come in here.
We have our fun treats as well which I would also say like all the treats at Harry Potter and stuff and ice cream and everything is pretty like top notch for fast service that thing in a theme park.
They really nail it.
And it's been consistently good.
And not the case here.
But so I went upstairs I finally flagged out a bar packed to the bar flagged the guy down.
One comes over.
I order a milkshake and I order this meal and he's he's like oh yeah okay like I was expecting him to go what are you talking about.
Why would you ever do this.
Leaving you're leaving this restaurant with something.
I don't have those buttons on my computer.
I can't do that right.
It's impossible.
You could maybe steal a plate and I'll look the other way.
That's the only way you're getting out of here with a piece of fish from the Orlando to some.
Can you just buy a chocolate bar and fuck off.
Yeah right right right.
I got an hour left to my shift.
You're killing so.
So Scott eventually joined me up there and it took a long time.
Enough for me to have a full glass of wine.
I had a glass of wine at the bar.
Chocolate wine.
And so finally I see the guy and I like because I think I even asked him like are you still doing it.
Are you still working on it.
Like oh yeah yeah don't worry.
And then finally he goes oh yeah there he points to me whatever and he hands me this big bag and I go OK great.
And we both leave and all the way down the stairs all the way down.
You're now you have a to go bag and merch from earlier.
Yes and you're and you're not only holding the milkshake but drinking the milkshake while walking down the stairs.
Yes because I filmed a lot of this.
I'll do we have video of it.
So I sit down all the way out of Toothsome keep walking over to much closer to the entry to Islands of Adventure.
Now we're in front of the theme park to find somewhere calm to sit and start eating your food.
It's like it takes forever to get from that bar to the front of Islands of Adventure.
And it's not that far in reality.
And I open the bag to take a look at the fish and I have a massive brownie sundae in a to go container.
I do not have the meal.
I was wondering I was like well I didn't get any brownie sundae.
Where did that go.
It's huge.
Why didn't you.
You returned it.
Well I was hoping.
You had a hungry boy your same age essentially waiting.
He could have had that thing.
They're like the fish is under the brownie.
It's possible the fish is under the brownie.
But with all our entrees we do put a layer of dessert above everything.
You came to Toothsome under the brownie.
Unadvertised like the martini biscotti.
So you went back on the stairs for fish.
So I'm just waiting what to do and I'm like I could just keep this and eat this.
I go but I really want to try the fish.
I want to see how they're doing fish down here.
And I was hoping that I'd get up there and they would let me keep the.
I was hoping that would happen.
I wasn't going to I wasn't going to suggest it.
But sometimes especially McDonald's fast food whatever.
Sometimes they hand you something.
You look through it and maybe you open it or something and they go yeah just keep it whatever.
Well maybe make it for the other person.
I once like one time at McDonald's really quickly I I ordered a kids chicken nuggets or like a small like yes chicken nuggets.
And I happen to open up because my my kid was starving.
So I'm opening up as I'm leaving the parking lot.
I kid you not.
It is a is a box full of pickles.
It's not like a large quantity of pickles.
I can tell as I was opening up I was like the weight here is not like doesn't feel quite right.
And then so I had to I had to go back and depart go back inside.
And as I'm walking up I'm like I was like I don't even know how to have this conversation.
But they're going to think I'm making that was just like I ordered chicken nuggets like I got this and she's like OK.
It was like that happens all the time.
Filling pickle orders so constantly.
Was it the one question was it the one close here terrible one up there.
Yeah because I've had a weird thing too where like I forget if I ordered I ordered something that should have an egg on it and they gave me a big fish patty.
Yeah.
There's some like it was a crazy substitution.
I've had your trickster in the back.
Very low level pranks on people.
If I could see their face and I can't because they'll be miles away because I had mistakes there like you were saying where I'm like I'll just live with this.
This is why I don't care.
Yeah but the pickles I was like I got to.
Yeah that's not how can I cut you a deal.
How would you like many many people.
Yeah.
I that McDonald's I went to I put in a mobile order once when they were doing like breakfast pastries and I was like I'll take the cheese Danish and I went.
And they were you know running a little behind and they're like what was your order.
I was like it was a nice coffee and a cheese Danish and they went OK.
And it it was a cheese Danish and it was pretty good but I still felt like alluded to going to McDonald's.
Wait I don't understand this.
What happened.
So this story is just you ordered a Danish and got it.
And I got it.
Some stories can be nice.
Yeah I just had to wait a little while.
But it felt really weird when they're like we have apple fritters and blueberry muffins and cheese Danish.
It felt weird though.
It was just odd because it was McDonald's.
And it was like cheese Danish was on the menu.
I didn't know it was on the menu.
It's not on the menu anymore.
After Jason gave.
Yeah.
OK.
So we went all the way back up there and he's like oh yeah yeah yeah.
And he took the thing all the way back up the stairs and has the whizzing and whirring and the land ice cream involved too.
So that was melting already.
So I don't see if he handed that to somebody else.
That's why I was hoping he would just say well you can keep this because we got to put fresh ice cream on this.
But no no offer was made.
So I took the bag went all the way back down and then I was drinking the milkshake the whole time.
And again the milkshake was fine.
I mean it find a good but it's one of those where you're like this is what you do.
This should be some transcendent experience drinking a sweet a sweet thing.
So yeah we walk all the way on the other side of city walk and we post up in like up this ramp that's like in there.
We never figured out an official name for this area.
The weird stairs and ramps Lombard Street.
Yeah Lombard.
There's ramps and stairs and that's where they're like phase three fast food balcony is where Burger King Whopper.
And that's where the bar is and a place called Bread Box is where you can get some tomato soup and a sandwich.
That's fine.
Honestly one of my better meals I had here.
Fine.
I liked it.
It was good.
So yeah so then I'm there's some tattoo parlor antics happening.
If you're listening to the show you've heard it already.
And I'm eating and trying to figure out what's going on.
And again take a bite.
This is awful.
I hate this.
And I'm trying to push through it.
Maybe I'm being negative.
But every aspect about it these like potatoes just like they look sick.
The potatoes look kind of sick.
Were they potato croquettes?
Well that's in there too.
That's in there too.
Those are pretty good.
That's here too.
Jason finished so much of this for me.
I love a croquette.
Despite Mike bleeding profusely.
And they were fine.
So yeah so basically.
That does not look like one of the things that Brett brought.
Right.
Brett brought potato croquettes.
Chocolate croquettes.
Yeah so and I didn't say.
So basically what happened.
In the middle of all this chaos that was happening at this tattoo parlor.
I bit into the left side of my mouth harder than I almost ever had.
And drew pretty good blood.
And so I'm eating this fish and drinking this milkshake with blood accumulating in my mouth.
And it's one of those where I'm like I can't put the napkin there.
Because it's going to.
It'll stop.
But I'm eating my own blood.
And I'm eating fish.
To go.
Styrofoam flounder.
Covered in almonds.
Yeah.
And.
Having made the walk twice.
This wasn't the dessert you ordered.
No no no.
I didn't order dessert at all.
I ordered the flounder.
And you probably would not have bit yourself on the cheek if you had not had all that duress leading up to it.
It was like a stress reaction.
There was a lot of duress I completely agree.
You should have just eaten the brownie sundae.
I should have just eaten.
This is my dinner yum yum yum.
I'm a little treat boy.
Yeah.
And.
I think I maybe have been the least negative about the food on this saga in general.
But I will say.
Bar none this is the worst meal I had.
No question like no question about it.
The worst thing ever.
And I understand maybe I was.
I don't know I was going to say it's a little it wasn't fresh fresh.
But maybe that maybe that delay.
Is what made it so bad.
Maybe it would have been perfect.
Like five minutes later after it was cooked.
And for listeners keeping track this is still not the food poisoning.
That's still coming.
I didn't have a weird shit or throw up or anything.
But there's still there are situations.
Go again.
Slap that on the side of two.
Yeah.
No weird shit.
No throw up.
Testimony.
It's like when there's people who aren't technically canceled but are still awful people for other reasons.
That's kind of the territory we're in with some of these places.
I believe there is something strange in the air.
We've all talked to all these those the McDonald's pickle thing.
Things like that happen here a lot.
I started going through the one star Yelp reviews.
And what and I do that a lot for establishments on the show.
And often it's people who have a bone to pick with the staff.
And they're like it was just like they were rude.
And some you know just there was some confrontation on that level.
But that's not what these are.
That's not what these are ever.
These are things that are a miss.
Like where there's just like almost like aliens are putting the food to is that the secret story of tooth some.
But you think it's about a robot and a lady but it's about aliens because like you know somebody went in several months after opening their out of chocolate ice cream chocolate ice cream and tooth some show what the vegan ice cream mentioned by Jason.
They haven't had that for months.
That's been gone for a long time.
Somebody ordered French toast.
And when it came out it was covered in cheese and a burger patty.
What's the McDonald's thing I just said.
There's a new way to deconstruct.
How does that one happen.
I'm sorry.
I need more information.
Like surely it's not what I'm imagining in my head.
Maybe just a full powdered French toast.
Yeah.
And then blanket of cheese and I don't know why I can't help you with the why much like tooth some and the dirigible and the parents.
I don't there's no why here.
It must have dropped.
It must have been on its way to a burger and then just fell on to the wrong thing.
And it was Jacques who was delivering the food so he can't see.
Right.
Yeah.
People food is anyway.
As far as he knows.
Sure.
This very much reminds me of like an early Twitter.
I don't know if it was a bit or if it was a joke but it's still a very funny image where someone says I went to Wal-Mart and I bought a router when I opened it up inside.
There was no computer parts.
It was just a bag of dirt that said who to.
And that that kind of reminds me of like you have French toast with cheese and a burger patty on it is very alien.
Yeah it's like ratatouille like if the rats didn't know how to cook like if it's like the very good realistic right.
It's a good movie.
What happens when you put rats on your head.
This is sorry.
This pasta is just a bunch of forks in a bowl.
It's not what pasta is.
Somebody went and got chocolate milk for their daughter and they're like huh.
Like mommy this is weird huh.
What they drink it.
Yeah this is warm.
Why is it warm.
And then the waiter comes and they tell him about it and he says oh I think the person who made it probably poured hot water in it.
The chocolate milk chocolate milk as far as I know has one ingredient post to that.
I mean for at the factory there's there they do the ingredients.
Once you open it at the restaurant there's no further preparation.
Better warm it up phrases you don't want to hear from your waiter person who made it and probably everything about that.
The human being who made it.
Similar to your thing might the fish.
The only one that seemed cooked instead of microwaved was salmon and it was burnt and then they're sitting and then they're finishing it and people come down the stairs right next to where they're sitting.
And the people coming down the stairs loudly say that food was weird man.
Such a good way to describe it.
That just boils it down.
Even if it's not fully bad it's just weird.
And then there's one more step of this that Jason alluded to maybe but this still might be a separate thing.
Here's a review.
The cookie jar shake tasted like cookies cookies and cream honestly was pretty good but nothing special.
Presentation it smelled bad like rotting cheese or meat that had been left out.
The place itself looked nice but it was kind of hard to eat anyway because of the rotting smell.
Is this Orlando or?
This one's Hollywood.
Now we're dealing yes I believe that this issue I'm getting into is a Hollywood exclusive.
A different review.
Upon walking in my group and eyes watered from the stench.
It was unexplainable.
What could possibly cause that smell?
And then I'm like all right.
These people all seem very reasonable but Yelp reviewers of course you know they're angry.
They're trying to you know pump up their stats or meta reviews or whatever.
I need a but separate actually before I read all this I had spoken to friend of the show.
Bug main buzz buzz and he said he tried to go here.
He sat waiting for a table like he just checked in with a host.
Oh yeah one second then he's sitting in the lobby and the smell was so horrible he had to get out.
I think this is and this doesn't start appearing in the reviews until like December maybe even after when you went Joe because you didn't experience.
I know I didn't there was no stench but it makes me think like was it a weather thing because it was like raining right a lot like did that was it not equipped for that amount of precipitation interesting.
Southern California and like it.
Dr.
Doosan never did rain experiments.
Yeah I mean I'm one that's the only thing I can think of.
Yeah yeah those comical steam pipes it's exposed I mean that yes yeah it's a big building and that's directly this year's there should not be a stench a stench far before long before you get to the food.
What do you mean the stench what's happening.
Why are burgers going on this all goes back to my like my like initial feeling when I walked in I was like this is a front for something like whatever to some is the it's not a restaurant.
It's not like it's not the food is not the game.
There's like a game behind the game for two sums and I don't know what it is but the restaurant feels like held together with tape and like barely like like barely thought out always in in danger of just falling apart.
You know there's something else going on with two sums.
This we sent that burger back and they were like oh we'll send a manager over the manager was very nice and it's like oh we'll take it off your bill.
So sorry it was bad.
Let me just have a flatbread you can take it with you and it's like oh yeah sure and then we you know get into the car and just kind of eating that we're like okay yeah this is kind of nothing.
Eating it in the car.
I was like okay it's fine like eating in the car and then when we got home so I was like all right it's a little cold but yeah it really doesn't taste great and you had it for breakfast three days later and it was still just okay.
I you know I just thought the almond taste got a little cloying after a while.
There's more almonds.
Oh and the chocolate bread.
I don't know it's weird because it's like.
Chuck is the first robot almond Dean.
Powered by almonds.
I know what you mean like when we went everyone was very nice but there's so many reviews and other experiences where it's like it's not working as a basic restaurant.
Was your oh was your burger not good.
Oh we'll be happy to take that off the bill can we offer you a free glass of stench.
This feels this restaurant is like a perfect representation of what my brain is like post pandemic.
It's like a perfect pandemic restaurant where you're like everything is wrong everything's off.
I should be eating here every week.
What are you doing to make me not want to be here.
Why do I feel so bad why does this smell so bad and why can't it be fixed in a simple way.
I want to be I want to be up there every day.
Yes you're the audience we want to be there.
We've all still been multiple times despite all of this.
I'll go back.
Yeah I will give it another chance.
You guys probably will as soon as we're done recording if I had to guess.
I have a hunger for it after talking about it knowing it's so close to me.
I kind of want to do it.
Are we going to eat Brett's coquettes of course as soon as this is done.
We're going to finish that weird green jar that Brett brought us definitely.
We're going to be dying the green jar the whole time.
Are we going to ground it up and free bear it or should we be able to go straight up our noses.
I want to order a Danish from this McDonald's up the street but we can't.
By the way I might be more averse to confectionary extracts that is I believe meant to be watermelon flavor.
What did you just declare about yourself.
You're more averse to.
No I'm more versed in like candy like.
You can tell fakes.
I can tell what fake.
Are you saying you're better at telling what fake watermelon is than I am.
No than you.
No no you're in the best.
Sivako.
Don't use the word more.
Say it's a tie.
I feel that I tie in the watermelon runt sciences with you Michael.
I do not tie.
No Mike's the expert.
But as soon as I bit into it I was like oh yeah it's watermelon.
That's interesting.
I don't know if I've had watermelon raw candy but I don't know that was twenty dollars to get that bottle that is probably two dollars at Michael's Chris.
Guys closing theories about what it is.
But you brought up the front theory.
We kind of corrected it with the universal owns it but I don't think that fixes the front.
Is it something to do with that they want to make a movie.
But if so then why would they make the food so bad that it could drive it all out of business.
What has happened.
What are we missing.
We have a flow chart up here and this goes to here and this goes to here but there's a ton of question marks.
What are the question marks.
Yeah it's because it's it's IP.
It is definitively IP.
Yes yes.
But like when there's IP that is like confusing attached to nothing has no real consistent like visuals like there's Penelope and Jacques but like Penelope is acted.
There's several actors who have portrayed Penelope and when it's so deeply derivative of something we already have and as discussed a genre that if made into a film would be avoided at all costs by the American public.
Yes yes.
I don't know.
It's like it seems like it's a real estate play like it's just like they.
Like we need to gain this space back before because the other one was something called NBA City that I don't know how NBA City which is undocumented at this point.
Fills the space.
That's what Orlando was.
The original one was.
I would live there.
A giant statue with giant like fake stone statue of like a basketball player a nondescript basketball player.
Yeah I found articles that referred to him as Jersey man.
That was the unofficial name.
Somehow it was a giant and then so is it just universal saying like we need to get something in there that maybe gets a lot of quick attention and if it rots away then it does but now we own the building.
We have kicked out the NBA we've kicked out these hard rock people who have made money on our land for too long.
Things that feel sort of analogous to this.
There is like there's things like you know I don't know.
There's there's Warren Beatty doing Dick Tracy every 10 years so we can maintain the IP.
There's a little yeah yeah they're played in like and like the economy is so weird right now.
There's such there's a there's always a value in big companies like Universal losing lots of money in specific ways.
There's always a value for companies in terms of taxes and this and that.
So it feels like there's some I feel like behind the scenes this all works fine for Universal and they're getting what they want out of it.
I but I want to know what that is.
Is it they need to take a loss for taxes.
Is it they're trying to build IP.
Is it there's some they have some weird competitive thing with Wonka.
They knew Wonka was coming out so they're going to have.
Well if Wonka breaks then we'll have a sort of like derivative IP we can sort of move around.
But there's there's some play and has nothing to do with food.
Well my only theory is if it anything food based talking about Instagram because Black Tap comes to do it.
Downtown Disney in 2018 or 2019.
Yeah.
So around when they're starting to put this together I kind of think maybe they started from the fact of like let's put a Rice Krispie treat on top of a milkshake.
And then let's let creative run wild with the narrative.
That's my guess.
OK.
Where maybe it starts because they're like we want it.
We obviously NBA City isn't doing so well and then we'll we'll try to come up with something that's big and flashy that will get people and then they start adding all their stuff in.
And we already have what two candy stores on City Walk like to like exclusively candy and sugar.
It's sugar.
And there's like the Sparky Sparky.
He's has a lot of candy.
Donuts.
Yeah.
Voodoo is there's donuts and Sparky's and there's donuts in food to don't.
Milkshakes I guess is on is not a covered area.
Johnny Rockets.
But you're going for the music.
I mean you're not going to hear a straight cat song.
You know I think what we saw down in Florida City Walk during the day is a ghost town.
But when the park's closed it is packed and I don't know what the routine is here because City Walk always seems like a ghost town.
Yes.
The questions we're asking could be questions about the entire thing.
Just the Hollywood one.
But I'm wondering if that period when people are leaving the theme park or going into the theme park at lunch or later in the day is that spending enough.
Is that enough to account for the emptiness.
I think I feel like you're thinking too practically.
I think there's something more nefarious going on here and something just occurred to me.
Is it that we will introduce the walk around robot character first.
Then we introduce Latte the dog and Latte the dog is how we will get people used to seeing weird robotic dogs in their town and in friendly places.
Is the whole.
Yes.
Sigh up.
All paid for like and it's the police or the government or the military or something.
But we start with Latte.
The sheriff's substation.
Yeah.
Yeah that's right.
At City Walk.
Yeah.
Mayor steps away.
We don't know what's in there.
That's not a place in City Walk you can access.
You might open a door and see one thousand robot dogs one thousand spots all like gnawing and like getting ready to just like to just dive forth at one hundred twenty miles per hour and tackle the next person stealing from the sock store they see.
That's the best explanation I've heard yet.
Toothsomes is a sigh up to make the public comfortable with their eventual robot overlords.
Right.
They knew they fucked it up.
They knew that like people started to bust in dynamics.
This video is like wow that's a little scary.
Right.
I know this is a little intense.
This is a little popular.
OK.
Start over.
Start from scratch.
Stop posting those videos.
We need to put a little hat on him.
Put a little hat on him and I'll be able to be fine and then they won't blink when they see three of them marching on the street and then 20 and then one hundred and then ten thousand stay in your homes or you'll be mauled.
Guy runs into the room he's got a he's like I got this drawing from some kid in Ohio.
Is this anything.
Go with it.
Don't look into the legality of it.
Start making the dogs.
Throughout Southern California a lot of military bases military contractors all town companies on the west side like Venice and Santa Monica.
Well what happens when the military unleashes Project Jock on the public.
Or Army of Jocks.
Chocolate fueled robots.
The perfect soldier.
Oh you know what I would recommend is you come with me and go into one of our camps.
Oh Jock runs on chocolate not the military industrial complex.
Sweet chocolate.
Don't you see.
Well I think we made some progress.
I think we finally cracked it.
Hold on I'll cut you off real quick.
Yeah see yeah.
In any closing thoughts or stray observations.
God knows there's a ton here.
They also have like they have art that would make you think they're also working on Toothsome Babies where they have art like like a little
baby versions of themselves.
Little octopus.
And there is a little octopus with a monocle.
But then there is also like kind of like baby Toothsome drawing as well.
And they don't have this branding officially like Toothsome Babies.
But it kind of feels also like maybe they're soft soft launching the idea that these characters are all going to be kids.
Well that's in case Penelope's parents wonder in and they go like why that looks like our lost child.
Oh because then they don't recognize her as an adult.
It's all these avocado toasts fried chicken sandwiches.
The savory kitchen of Feast Kitchen.
You know what I think that answers the question that she's she's a Gen Z or millennial because of this avocado toast.
Oh boy.
I think we all should make an agreement here.
When Toothsome's eventually does is about to go out of business and they're having their final weekend.
One of us needs to dress up get a beard and like sort of dress age up and wander in in a daze.
We'll see Penelope.
Penelope?
My daughter!
I was looking at you.
I was looking for you where cocoa is grown the hotter climates and you were here this whole time.
Mother didn't make it.
She got dizzy and fell out of the Dirigible.
I was trying to find you but I looked up the most highly rated chocolate establishments in Orlando and Los Angeles and this wasn't even in the top 100.
I was trying to enjoy some opium but my spark caught the hydrogen of the Dirigible just went up in flames and I was thrown far.
Well absolutely and all the you know between all of us somebody can pick father but we can flesh out the you know there's uncles and cousins.
There's gonna be like a ton of two-some characters.
I hate to contradict you here I think we should all play father.
No I'm the one!
I am father!
A real Mamma Mia situation with Penelope.
I fell into the prestige machine and there's even more of me under the restaurant.
Alright this is a good plan and like oh wait oh my god I think we've made it to the end because I see the sector stone that shows that we've completed our mission.
There it is oh my god it looks like is it a little owl but it's not it's no ordinary owl.
I think that's an almondine owl.
Wow it's an owl with a jet pack and it's covered in little slices of almond and Mike's blood.
Yeah and it's got a little price tag on it that says nine hundred dollars.
Hey and Jason's licking it.
I think there might be some fudge on this fanboys.
No there's my blood that's why you're licking it.
He's got a taste for it now.
This is interview with the vampires starting.
Well there it is we'll keep this in our hearts forever and oh my god Joe and Brett you have both survived podcast the ride the city walk Orlando saga multiverse of madness.
Let's exit through the plug portal.
Joe we'll start with you anything you'd like to plug.
Yeah so I have this podcast about the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame called Who Cares About the Rock Hall.
We are in nomination season so it's the most exciting part of the year for us.
The ballots out we're talking to voters on our Patreon a newly established Patreon and yeah we're going through the artists on the ballot.
There's a lot to talk about and the inductees will be revealed at the end of April.
So jump in now see what's see what's going on.
Also I do have an album out called Funny Songs and Sketches that the title is explanatory.
I think you understand what that means listeners but it has a lot a lot of people on it as well that I bet the listeners here would enjoy whether that's David Cross or Patton Oswald or I.
A.
O.
Debreed Nick Kroll Al Madrigal a lot of very funny people so you can check that out wherever you get albums.
Absolutely albums great and the podcast does it like you ask the question who cares about the Rock Hall.
I think if you start listening suddenly then the induction ceremony will become the World Series and you'll feel like you're following the whole season.
Yes.
Like suddenly it will become sports.
I think it will transform if you listen to your show.
Absolutely.
I like that framing of it.
It's all.
I think you're hearing about every round and the All-Star game and now the playoffs and you do make every piece of it exciting.
I never cared about any of it and it's I do now.
Brett anything you'd like to.
Yeah we've got a lot of great podcasts on the Forever Dog Network in addition to podcast the ride.
The best show with Tom Sharpling double threat office hours live with Tim Heidecker just to name a few.
And then my buddy Joe and I do two movie podcasts on Forever Dog weekend at Bergman's where we compare a arthouse movie in a mainstream movie that share a theme such as Weekend of Bernies and the Seventh Seal was the very first episode we did.
So it gave the show its name and then we also have a show called Movies Baby.
That's just like a weekly rundown of movie news reviews of the latest movies etc etc.
We live stream those back to back on Thursday nights on YouTube on the Movies Baby YouTube or you can get them as a podcast and we have a Patreon Patreon dot com slash Movies Baby with Five Wise Movies Baby.
Five Wise.
That is good to have people.
Other people have done three and seven.
You don't want to end up in a lawsuit situation.
Well thanks for doing it.
So glad to have you have you Brett and good opportunity to say thanks for everything overall over all these years has been a great home for us.
And a blast.
You guys love this thing.
Thank you to release way too many episodes which speaking of they're still coming.
We thank Aaron Gardner for the art our own Mike Carlson and Zach Reno for the theme music multiverse of madness merchant RT public store for the full saga experience subscribe to podcast the ride the second gate or get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector on club three all of that at Patreon dot com slash podcast the ride and be sure to follow LA dessert dude on Instagram.
I organic content.
There's ads in there but we never did.
He would never do an ad for something that he doesn't really care about.
So I decided I was going to finally check out podcast the red.
So I went to the Apple Tunes and I checked out I said where can I find out a podcast that talks about theme parks but also has guys exploring the friendship.
And so I found podcast the ride and enjoy their Patreon and I love that they're putting out episodes every day about city walk.
I think I'm going to go to city walk maybe put my AirPods in and listen to podcast the right there.
Yeah, thousands of dollars.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcast, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcast.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.