Forever.
Dog.
When your town has made you frown.
When your square has made you swear.
When life gives you one more punch.
You need a doughnut soaked in Captain Grunge.
You need a place, a place to stroll.
With alcohol.
A place that features part of the Berlin Wall.
Where steampunk robots sell chocolate snacks.
A place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando.
Tonight.
A daily, extremely necessary series.
Exploring the shops, restaurants, and cosmic wonder.
That make up Universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride the City Walk Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
I'm Scott Gardner.
There's Mike Carlson.
Yo, yo.
There's Jason Sheridan.
We just got to, you know, put a pace on this.
But also I want to get as quickly as possible to our special guest today.
Returning to the show after not too long.
A collaborator with previous Saga guest Evan Susser on Villain Con Minion Blast at Universal Studios Florida.
It's Van Robichow.
Hello.
Hey, it's really great to be here.
Hey, Van.
Hi, Van.
Just another normal appearance by me on a podcast.
Nothing peculiar going on at all that the audience can't see.
No, yes.
You're just hearing things like normal and it's not as if there is an item in the room that is pulling all the focus in the world.
Would you care to or would you rather not acknowledge it?
Would you rather like is this your part of like making this day to day to like, you know, why does it have to be the center of the tension?
I agree.
So just so for those who aren't here, I am I am wearing an Apple Vision Pro headset.
It's my first podcast in one.
Oh, wow.
So really.
Yeah, you're welcome.
You're welcome.
It's an experimental series.
So I think a good time to do an experimental move.
And yeah, I I feel I feel a little strange in it.
OK.
As a warm up for it with my good friend, Evan Susser earlier today, I did an hour and a half Zoom call and writing session with him while in the headset.
So I'm kind of used to talking to people in it right now, which I was I was worried I wouldn't be.
And so I forced Evan to deal with me wearing it like an idiot to help us in a way.
Yeah, no, it's all for the all for the content.
That's good.
Well, you know, Susser, I think, needs to do more to help us.
Yeah, for sure.
Give it away.
Everything's gone.
Yeah.
Oh, you know what?
That being said, Susser picked up.
We're watching wrestling and Susser picked up food for my family the other day that he wasn't even part of.
Wow.
So he helped my family out.
He doesn't need to help more.
Well, all right.
So that covers you.
Yeah.
What happens to Jason?
Oh, fair enough.
You guys didn't get helped.
Oh, he can pick me up food whenever.
OK.
That's OK.
He can even pick you up.
Sure.
He probably can.
But so now you were we're we're talking to you.
You know, I feel like a lot of the podcast guest connection does need to come from, you know, looking somebody in the eye and, you know, sharing moments and points and.
Well, thank goodness for the persona feature so that you can see a simulacrum of my eyes in front of my face.
Yeah.
And that's what it is.
It's not because what I'm seeing is sometimes I'm seeing eyes that are blinking and then I'm also seeing like a throbbing.
Yeah, I saw that.
White light.
Well, I think the throbbing white light might be because I'm recording you guys.
Oh, that's the.
All right.
That's like the red flashing button on the camera.
This is a way to let people know you aren't just like discreetly.
Yeah.
And then what you're seeing is a simulation of my eyes.
The blinks are accurate to my actual blinking.
They're synced up.
Yes.
So none of these are manufactured blinks.
No, these are all genuine blinks.
They're genuine eye movements.
Oh, my God.
That's all a recreation of the actual physical movement.
Yes, that's correct.
The headset itself is largely controlled by eye movement.
And so there are cameras pointed at both of my eyes carefully tracking the location of my pupils.
And it uses that information to recreate my face on the front of the screen.
Hmm.
Can you can you add any like cosmetic adjustments to it with the visuals?
Well, you know, there doesn't seem to be any kind of enforcement of the face you scan when you first set it up being your own.
So I think we're going to find a whole new new way to is it manatee Teo people?
Was that his name?
Man.
Teo.
Yeah.
The catfish football playing gentleman.
Right.
Because I could scan someone else and then do FaceTime calls as them with this persona and it would sync up to my eyes.
But and mouth.
But it wouldn't be me.
When I first got the headset last week, I hadn't shaved in like a week and I was looking kind of ragged.
And I scanned myself for the persona and I was like, whoa, I got to go shave because I look like a mess in here.
And so my other prediction based on this is the way people now are like, I got to get in shape for my beach body for the summer.
People are going to start to want getting in shape before their scan for their consumer device.
The show is a simulacrum of them.
They'll be locked into that.
Yeah.
That is how people will see them.
And you can't there must be some program, though, where you can like shave or shave.
All it'll allow me to do currently now, granted, Apple says the persona feature is in beta.
It will allow me to put virtual eyeglasses on myself.
However, it does not let me make any kind of modifications to the scan.
It's just what you get when you scan it.
You can kind of like make a little slider.
Like if you look too red to kind of like pull that down, things like that to adjust for the lighting in the room.
OK.
But you can't like cosmetically alter yourself.
And those are like functional glasses.
They aren't like in a previous sector.
Ian Rickabani talked about his kids getting like glowing glasses.
Was that at from Bubba Gump or somewhere else?
Yeah, no fun versions of the optional glasses that I could see.
They all seems like something they could largely functional.
I don't mean to be like finding holes.
You're you're we're wearing and demonstrating incredible technology.
And here I am going, yeah, I'm happy to take credit for it as well.
Oh, sure.
Is there a podcast app on?
Yes, there is.
Yes, I could pull up past episodes and review them while we're talking.
This could be good because we have a lot of these moments of like misremembering something that have been said or like feeling like, you know, like a story is retold.
It's been told before.
This could be very helpful to us to be able not that we couldn't do it on our regular computers.
Yeah, but this seems more efficient maybe to like insta pull up a previous joke.
Joking aside about it, I actually do think it has actual useful potential in the world of like editing content and things like that, because I can pull up like monitors and stuff and watch videos from multiple sources and things in different like virtual screens all over.
Basically, like it's like a camera truck on my face if I needed to be, which haven't we all dreamed of a camera truck on our faces?
We can all film Super Bowls whenever we want.
Video Village in your sunglasses.
That's right.
All right.
And you are you're filming this right now.
Is this is it possible for you to release what I'm saying your point of view of me right now in some form for listeners to see?
Yes, not only will I release it, I will be releasing it in full immersive video so that anyone with 3D television or any 3D capable device, even a god forbid a meta quest three, two or pro, will be able to watch the first 10 minutes of this podcast in an immersive, fully dimensional vans POV way.
Did the meta quest, did they ever get legs working?
They said legs were coming.
You know, I believe an unreleased beta does finally have full torsos and motion captured arms before they were estimating elbow positions and shoulder positions.
So they've made it all the way down to the to the hips, but they're still still not below.
It's tough because so the Apple vision pro here has lots of cameras and sensors on the front, but there are downward pointing cameras right here, which is how it's able to do stuff with my hands when my hands are down here.
And also, I think it gets some of the lip movement stuff for my persona from that.
And there are no downward facing cameras on any of the meta quest products.
And so they legs has to be entirely like estimated based on what the rest of your body is doing.
And so it's a hard problem that they haven't been able to solve.
They've got all their engineers on legs, though.
It does seem like this, but somewhere in the full weight of the former Facebook company.
It's like between all that, they should be able to figure out legs.
They've put in 20 billion dollars into R&D on their devices.
And I got to imagine they put at least two billion dollars into legs.
Well, and so, you know, money can't buy legs, as they say.
Maybe prosthetics.
I think Salkerberg either said it or tweeted it like legs are on the way.
Yes, there was a tweet that legs were coming, but we've yet to see them.
They did get in some trouble a few years back where they showed legs in a presentation.
It came out that those were simulated legs.
Those were post effect legs that were not actual live legs.
I'm a little concerned about where all this is going, because this whole series is about going and visiting a place,
and getting down and dirty in a place, and doing everything at the place.
And it's all about physical experiences.
And if we're able in the future to just scan our city walks,
then sure, it's great that we can all go to one virtually any time, but then what happens to the real one?
And then people aren't spending money at the real one.
I look forward to a world of augmented city walks.
Okay, yeah.
That's a better vision, yes.
You know, for example, we touched briefly on some of the restrictions that occur between Universal and Disney
with respect to the Marvel properties, and how you won't see the word Marvel anywhere in Disney World.
Perhaps, since their contract didn't anticipate this, could I see the word Marvel augmented on top of things at Disney World through my Vision Pro?
Perhaps I could.
Wow.
I think that's not conceived of by that contract.
And I think the next thing you know, you could be at downtown Disney, and you could see a big Marvel sign saying Marvel merchandise in here,
because you can't see that now.
Right.
Wow.
Yeah, it's like an entire universe on top of our universe.
That's right.
And how can they have anticipated that in that tiny contract in the late 90s?
Plus, I think what's great about sort of a VR or metaverse city walk is that probably those goggles can make you sick at any moment.
So it'll be fine.
It'll just be eating at city walk.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
You can maybe get the sickness done.
You don't need the food.
You don't need the food anymore.
I mean, that's kind of an innovative thing.
Not having to eat the food is an upgrade.
I am curious about if that would have been an upgrade for your experience.
I do feel like, because if you're going to shut off this feed, the immersive reality feed at some point, first of all, I'd like to say it almost does feel like this is maybe the chance for the listeners to feel what it's like to be on the show.
So maybe we should simulate that.
They're going to have to plug in their own name or do some AI scan of my voice.
Should we do a quick like…
That could be, yeah.
Is it like, well, I feel like if I go…
Well, you just like turned everybody, but let me start by saying like, and our guest today is one of the greatest, the greatest guest we've ever had.
I don't know how it took so long to get you on the show.
Thanks for being here.
Wow.
Are you so much more excited about this guest than any guest we've ever had before?
This guest is the most exciting guest of all the times.
Are you the most excited about this guest?
This guest?
Yeah.
You.
We're excited.
You're here.
Whoa.
I'm so excited.
I'm tipping over.
Whoa.
Oh, sorry.
That was an accident.
That wasn't me trying to kiss you or anything.
Let's not get into that territory.
I just accidentally fell in your direction.
Maybe we should kiss this guest right now.
The first guest we have all ever wanted to kiss at the same time.
We should all kiss together in a four way.
And scene.
All right, we'll cut that.
Listeners, you should know we're all doing a lot of like pointing and things in the direction of the Vision Pro.
And you should have, oh, you did a little like, what's the word, minority report.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Well, this is all very exciting.
Yeah.
But you know, the only thing that's maybe a little bit more interesting than this like new universe of tech is contact with the metaphysical,
and that is what we that is what we are able to bring in this series only.
So let's check in really briefly and get our official assignment today from the Sector Keeper.
Boys, boys and then face six sector three is Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom.
Pat O'Brien's and City Walk's rising star.
Good luck, boys and then.
Okay, there we have it.
So we're kind of we're deep into the the nightlife portion, I would say, of the of the saga.
And, you know, these are kind of the upstairs clubs that we're dealing with.
First question, Susser, who was the guinea pig with your hand movements are insane.
What is this?
Are you playing?
Are you picking cards out of a file machine?
I'm scrolling through my camera roll to get to my photographs of my dinner at the restaurant.
I mean, that's good.
Only you're the only guest who's really able to literally go back while we do it.
But OK, but so I'm curious if we're going back to a positive or a negative memory for you,
because Susser, your collaborator, was kind of put out, I think, by we did.
Look, we of course, we pounced on him.
We asked like, you're going to be down there working on Villain Con.
You got to go.
Please go do something at CityWalk.
And it was a little bit calamitous for him.
We did the same for you.
How would you characterize the evening in general that resulted in our hounding you to go there?
I had a wonderful evening.
OK, all right.
I had just gotten in to Orlando.
I was visiting the ride under construction for the first time.
I had meetings in the morning, but nothing to do that night.
So I was staying on property at the.
Not the Sapphire Falls.
What's the other one?
Royal Pacific.
Or maybe I was the staff.
No, I was at the Sapphire Falls.
And so there's a boat right there.
Takes you right to CityWalk.
Of course.
Yeah.
So I hopped on the boat.
I've got video of the boat ride right here.
I'm looking at right now.
Oh, man, I'm so jealous.
I want to be right here.
I am going right by the plane that's in the in the water.
Not the Jimmy Buffett plane, but the plane that you pass where like all the other boats in the river.
Here I am coming under the bridge, seeing the reveal of Toothsums Factory.
Oh, wow.
You know, I couldn't have said this at the time, but I can now say Toothsums appears in the VillainCon ride in the final scene.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Right.
CityWalk pulled into it.
You're in the park, but watching CityWalk?
That was a pitch from Evan and I to have that happen.
And so this was my first time seeing the actual Toothsums in person, even though I had pitched putting it in the game.
And so it was important for me to see how did the real thing in the game, how did those live up to each other?
Yeah.
So I was getting some work done, even though I was there.
And I went to the Universal Store at CityWalk that sells the like 90s merch.
Oh, yes, the Legacy Store.
We covered that a little bit.
And yeah, here I am at the Legacy Store.
I bought a hat.
I'll send you guys these pictures.
Like old logo hat.
On the old logo hat I bought one last time I was there when I was like 12.
Wow.
So I bought the same hat.
Oh, that's cool.
And then I was getting hungry and I said, hey, Scott, I texted you.
I might eat at the Bob Marley restaurant.
Has anyone covered that yet?
Nope.
And you were the first.
You called it.
Got to it even before before Griffin Newman, who I feel like was fishing for it maybe a little a little bit.
So you grabbed it.
And now I now I don't know if Griffin is going to end up being part of the series because he wasn't as on the ball.
I know.
Yeah, yeah.
I might not.
Sorry.
You have to set this one out, Griffin.
And yeah, I've got it all up right here.
Unfortunately, I can't see Jason anymore because all of my pictures are in front of him.
I've got actually look Bob Marley from the menu is right where he would be.
OK.
Wow.
I don't want to.
This is terrible to say.
I don't want to say that's an upgrade from Jason.
But of course, Bob Marley.
Well, the main character Bob Marley won love the hit movie, the worldwide hit in theaters as we speak.
Indeed, which maybe I don't.
Well, I didn't go see the movie last night.
Oh, right.
Planning to and telling Scott I was going to.
So that's the real reveal.
We even delayed the record a little bit so that it was possible maybe for us both to go.
Yes.
And then you threw it out there with with the and I was like, I'm sorry, these are theaters that are more than a mile from my house.
There's no way that's going to work for me to see Bob Marley won love.
But, you know, I did get to watch the very enthusiastic band play for a completely empty room at Bob Marley's Tribute to Freedom.
And, you know, I feel like that's basically the same experience.
Can you guys hear this?
Let me play this.
I don't know how loud this is to everyone else.
I think I can turn the volume up to be if it's loud drums.
Then it hasn't played yet.
So don't you wouldn't have heard it.
OK, here we go.
I hear a little I hear.
Whoa, I do hear you hear that reggae coming from from some goggles.
Well, I wish I could put you guys in here and give you the experience of the Bob Marley.
Yeah.
You know, if only the technology had been there, I would have captured the the the room itself in the immersive video.
Does it do three six to how many degrees around or do you just have to look your head around to get this itself?
It actually doesn't record full.
So 180 is the kind of like standard for immersive video.
What this records like when I was recording you guys, I think is a is more of like a hundred degree kind of a box.
OK, got it.
A situation.
OK, so know that if you're if you're watching the immersive video, you're not getting the full periphery.
You'll get I have other equipment if that was what we'd needed that I could have brought to capture.
Yeah, but we're improvising.
We didn't know.
Yeah.
So you could bring the full camera truck.
Yes.
Not to just not to jump around because I want to focus on your experience here, but I do just want to say just to meditate on the phrase Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom is the name of this establishment.
Yeah, I that phrase to me is like was one of the main things pulling me along to want to do this series.
I've seen this phrase in brochures and just like and passing by and signs and never never gone in.
I just and it's been this is this was an opening day thing for city walks.
This has been here since ninety nine.
It's millions of people have passed by the words Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom and and maybe not meditated on it like we get to do now, maybe not really reflected on the fact that it is you can't you hear just the phrase and you're like, wow, so it must be like a museum, like a tribute to his life and kind of an exploration of.
No, no, no, it's a restaurant.
It's a restaurant where you, you know, you get like what's there, but you know, my ties and rum punch and jerk chicken salad.
So the situation there, and I don't know if you guys have looked into this and done your research.
A lot of the Bob Marley IP is held by the Bob Marley Foundation, of which his wife and children were and are executives.
OK, and so they try, I'm sure out of the goodness of their hearts, but also to maintain their five oh one three C charitable organization status and sure to always be trying to help to spread the important legacy of Bob Marley and his message through all of their many licensing endeavors.
I see.
And so more than licensing endeavors because they're about these ideas, these ideas that change the world.
And so I've pulled up the menu here on the screen and I can read to you guys.
There's a little some writing about Bob Marley.
Oh, please.
Yeah, very helpful.
Yeah, this is on the back of all the menus.
It says beyond the legend.
Hmm.
Bob Marley was born Robert Nesta Marley on February 6th, 1945 in the slums of Jamaica, yet he had the talent, vision and courage to become the foremost superstar of reggae music.
Always mindful of the poverty and hard times of his youth, his songs of faith, hope, rebellion and determination have brought inspiration and joy to audiences everywhere.
He made his first recording at the age of 17 and at 19 singing with the whalers originally called the Wailing Rude Boys.
Bob's astounding international acclaim as a prolific songwriter and musician earned him a place in the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame.
Wow.
These successes pale only in comparison to his achievements as a peacemaker and humanitarian.
He was awarded the Order of Merit by the Jamaican government for his contribution to Jamaican culture and the Medal of Peace for the Third World by the United Nations.
The man who brought reggae to the world died tragically of brain cancer on May 11th, 1981.
Three decades after his death, his spirit rages on in his music and his message.
Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom, is proud to showcase his legend and his life filled with such talent and integrity.
We've worked very closely with Rita Marley and the Bob Marley Foundation in order to replicate Bob's home on 56 Hope Road, Jamaica.
We hope you enjoy your stay with us today and we look forward to your return.
Please take a moment to reflect on the artistry and words of this uncompromising artist and browse our collection of memorabilia.
Wow.
That's like the heaviest thing.
But then that's in a menu?
Yes, but it also ends with a quote,
Don't gain the world and lose your soul because wisdom is better than silver and gold, Bob Marley.
But then like in the middle, is there like…
Awesome.
Buffalo Soul Jerk Jerk Wings.
Taste of Jamaica.
A tour of island flavors featuring our veggie and beef patties, jerk wings and yuca fries.
Is there a kids menu?
Get up, stand up, mango wings.
Crispy, fried, tossed in our own mango sauce.
Is there a kids menu?
There is.
I know what it is.
I want to see if Van can find it.
Let's see.
Do I have the…
I have got the Rastafarian Tings drink menu.
I mean, it's great.
It's exciting that something can be both.
That it can be both a restaurant and a tribute to freedom.
I do not seem to have the kids menu, unfortunately.
The kids menu is called the Lil Legends menu.
And one of the items on it is Jamaican Roni and Cheese.
We should honestly have awards at the end of this for best…
Because we've encountered a lot of good…
with Fallen Brothers and the currently existing ones,
a lot of good themed item names.
Is Jamaican Roni and Cheese perhaps the best one we've found?
It's up there, yeah.
Maybe it's the best.
I'll declare it the best.
I also really like No Woman, No Cry Jerk Chicken Salad.
As someone who's gone through the process of theming a menu and naming themed menu items,
I have to say it's harder than you might think to do it.
I'm going to give them an A- on the naming of these items.
Yeah.
I got takeout from this restaurant.
And I ordered these Natty Dredd vegetable patties.
This is two house-made patties filled with sweet potatoes, red beans, spinach, carrots, onions, coconut milk,
cocoa bread, yucca fries, and smoky ketchup.
And you can here see all the different shades of brown and yellow and tan at my takeout.
Oh, wow.
All the colors.
The red of the ketchup.
You're getting every color you need.
Sorry, you were being blocked by the menu.
Could I see that?
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
What you described seemed like a much more sophisticated dish,
and then you showed it to me and it looks like you can just get it.
I will say, this is not the best restaurant, I think, for takeout.
What with the centerpiece being a recreation of his home in Jamaica.
Of a music legend's real home.
A musical component, memorabilia on the walls.
It's definitely a funny…
I don't know that it's a food forward.
That was the first night was to do.
But Jason is covering…
This is part of the experience.
There's a lot more takeout and bar situations.
Mike got to do takeout, the glorious takeout of Toothsam.
Of course.
And Jason got to do Bob Marley, a takeout to freedom.
A takeout to freedom.
I like that.
Look, the patties were delicious.
Really good, really fresh.
The bread was stale and the fries and ketchup were just kind of nothing.
The yucca fries weren't really anything.
The patties represent Bob's spirit.
And the stale bread represents his oppressors and everyone who didn't believe in him.
There's something that has to give you some feeling of hardship when you're eating the meal.
To make you appreciate what you have.
To tell the full story of Mr.
Marley in one meal.
I had the sweet plantains and the rice and peas as my sides.
And I think that those were perhaps a more Marley-esque side to have.
You felt the one love spirit more in the plantains.
Just to give Scott you a note, you guys can pass this around.
This is the view I see.
We're AR.
I'm looking at where you're looking.
And AR has projected…
Here, let's just do lots of layers here.
Let me take a picture with my phone.
I'm in it.
Great.
Okay.
And there is…
You're really…
You are bringing the City Walk saga.
You're bringing sagas into the 22nd century.
Yeah.
So I've got the menu, as you can see, right up there.
And it's very easy for me to just move it right over here and block Jason.
Just all I have to look at is the menu.
And really it's just because he's right in front of me.
Just because it's your center?
I can attest to your point of view that that is the natural place.
But can't you just slide it between me and Jason?
Maybe slide it right over here, but I guess that's fine.
I feel like I'm going to make you.
You've got to…
I know you've got your fake eyes, but you've got to look my co-host in the eyes.
If you're going to be here, that's part of the rules.
I think that's what Bob Marley would want, too.
I think he knew the eyes were the windows to the soul.
Yeah, go ahead and pass that over.
What did I do?
There was a band playing outside while I was there.
Oh, wow.
You're showing it to me.
You started that on your phone?
You've just handed your vision out to the rest of us.
You're taking parts of yourself.
So you can see my food there.
That's the Jamaican…
That doesn't look bad.
Let me get the name right.
That is the Reggae Jamaican Jerk Chicken.
Half chicken marinated in Jamaican spices and scotch bonnet peppers,
char-grilled, chopped rice and peas, sweet plantains.
I got to say, it was pretty good.
Wow.
I wondered about the quality of this as a restaurant.
I didn't have great feelings about it from what Jason had conveyed.
But you think if you do the sit-down…
I sat down and had what was essentially a piece of rotisserie chicken
with some jerk sauce on it.
It's a pretty easy dish.
Sure, but again, you have no idea.
We've encountered such horrors in this series.
Something made competently is exactly what we're looking for.
He saw it.
And if you give me the Wi-Fi, I can force my view onto his iPad, actually.
Oh, wow.
Actually, we should.
That sounds good.
Do you want to be commandeered, Jason?
Do you want to be hacked?
Jason should be hacked.
Can you put your vision into Jason's regular glasses?
They're not hooked up to any sort of cloud or Wi-Fi,
but I don't know what this thing can do.
That might be difficult, but I can always try.
Just asking questions.
Isn't it…
The fact that it's not called…
Because there's other things.
Right down mere feet away is Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville.
Is it a tribute to the man and his spirit?
Yes, but ultimately it's called Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville.
It's not a tribute to any greater, deeper concept.
The fact that this isn't…
It's not Bob Marley's reggae roasters.
It's Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom.
It just sets the bar so high for what this experience is going to be.
Until you read that menu…
I just popped in for a drink.
The menu is clearly the primary piece.
They probably need to force people…
There should be a pre-show room where they make you read that
as if it was scripture so that the rest really lands.
As it did for me, I just went in.
I didn't even get a mojito or anything island-ish.
I just got a glass of wine.
Not a cool you down?
Not a mighty good drink?
Not a freedom freeze?
Is there a freedom freeze?
Of course there's a freedom freeze.
What better way to show you freedom?
Not Uncle Ray's rum punch?
I didn't.
No, I didn't do anything fun.
Banana jamming?
No.
I know it was an end of the night situation,
so I just needed to coast down.
I don't think I needed a new type of cocktail in me,
but I'm regretting it now.
I feel like I let Bob down.
Let me see if this is an unpopular opinion.
I like that they're going for something ambitious.
I like that it's where he grew up when he was little.
Yeah.
But I feel like the fun names here,
which I'm always calling for more fun names on menus,
here it doesn't work.
I think you should have very boring-sounding names
and maybe less ambitious food.
Interesting.
I think you're really trying to give the feeling.
I think that if you gave boring names,
then you failed at, how should I put it,
the, where is it?
I'm looking at the notes.
Thesaurus.
com.
No, no, the artistry and words of this uncompromising artist.
I think if you go for boring names,
you failed to capture that.
I mean, one love, okay.
Yeah, you've got to put some stuff like that.
So you're okay with jam and drinks.
Are you trying to make a more successful restaurant?
No, I'm not.
I am not trying to make this more successful.
Don't gain the world and lose your soul,
because wisdom is better than silver and gold.
I understand that, and I believe that,
but I'm saying that if you're really,
if the whole place is of a piece,
I feel like the menu is in contention
with the aesthetic of the rest of the place.
That's what I'm saying.
It's too silly?
But his music is fun.
That's true, it is.
And reggae music is fun.
I feel like probably they're playing the greatest,
when I went,
and then the next night when I was hearing it
from behind me
at the cowfish sushi bar,
I definitely heard
Pass the Dutchie, both
in there and then blasting in
from another restaurant, which made it feel
a little less special, honestly, because I was really
actually digging it while they were in print,
and then it suddenly felt like, oh, well, so they always
play Pass the Dutchie, don't they?
Well, there was a private party the one
I think had taken over.
Was it there?
Take over that space?
It was one of those clubs.
There was a minute where we weren't going to get into some of these places
because there were
barricades up for some private
I forget which of the clubs.
We thought that was going to stop us
in our tracks.
But pretty much I feel like we're making it to everything
we're supposed to.
Again, we're going to check, by the way,
just to announce it, we're going to check in with the
center keeper at the very end and just make sure
that we've proceeded according to his
wishes, and we'll let you go before that, Van.
Otherwise, I think we're
penetrating, we're covering everything here.
Anyway, Pass the Dutchie's
fun, I know that's not his song,
but you know, so if you have
I guess I don't want to
like, sort of the elephant in the room,
you know, the
man practiced a religion, the center
piece of which is just getting really, really
high on marijuana.
I think to criticize the men you
attribute to him as being too
silly is really
kind of runs a foul of
the man's lifestyle
and his spirit.
I think it's really just a tribute
to freedom.
You can be silly and serious
at the same time is I think one of the messages
of Bob Marley.
Okay.
Well, but maybe it should be a tribute to freedom and
being silly.
We should say
that, that's maybe the title of the
place in my mind.
You know, Van could
speak to this from a corporate standpoint.
That was probably some of the thing with thinking of menu items
is like the economy of words.
And that does seem like, I hear what you're saying,
Mike, but it does seem like maybe a little too much
to get into one title.
I just think the title sounds
so important.
It doesn't, it almost
sounds like it's not going to be
I feel like we are like, doesn't it sound
like the name of a
museum that is going to deal with some
heavy topics that might
deal with just a little with mass killings
or stuff like that.
It does not sound
like a place to go and get drunk.
Tribute is maybe the word that is
perhaps the problem.
Maybe that's really all I'm responding to.
It's pretty heady.
Yeah.
Like, honestly,
if it were celebration,
yeah, that's a different
story.
Celebration does change it.
Is anything called
a tribute?
In those early Universal rides,
was anything, was Alfred Hitchcock, I don't remember,
I know we've covered a lot of these, but I don't remember.
That was just like magic
of the movie.
Was anything a tribute?
Lucy
A tribute?
Lucy A tribute?
And that is a
museum.
A museum, yes.
We liked it.
I think we all found memories of that.
I loved it, yes.
It was fun, but it's not as
fun as, you can't go get like
Lucy themed cocktails there.
It's not
that fun.
Would be inappropriate
if they did that.
It would be.
But wasn't she,
she probably was a drinker, right?
Oh, a smoker for sure.
Probably a drinker as well.
Certainly that.
They should at least offer
cigarettes.
There should be cigarettes.
Yeah, what Desi
put her through?
She
had a lot of drinks, I bet.
Lucy A tribute, I believe
last time I was there had the
the Back to the Future car in it.
That building.
Yes,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
It became like a
general Universal thing.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
It definitely loosened up.
Yes.
Not Lucy A tribute to freedom.
That was not Lucy's primary.
That's an exhibit about her divorce
from Desi.
Yeah.
There's the tribute
stores.
They do a lot of big
themed stores.
Sure.
That kind of roti.
Okay, yeah.
It doesn't feel as ponderate.
A tribute to freedom makes you feel like
you have to go reflect on what it would be like
to not be free.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It makes me think it's going to be like a dark
side, a grim side to it, whereas
I think you can attest to this, Van, I think you
go and you have a lot of fun at this place.
It's a good time.
I was
there alone, sat
at the bar, it was a little rainy,
and I still had a nice time.
You know, I
went to Toothsims after and got a
big giant piece of fudge with peanut
butter on top.
Was that more fun?
We don't need to say that.
That's for a different episode.
Different sector, yeah, yeah.
But
I had a generally positive experience.
I will say, like, yeah,
there was rain, but it does
seem to be the most sparsely attended
of the
CityWalk restaurants.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, we were there on
I went on a Tuesday
night, and I think the
Tuesday night of it definitely
reduced crowds.
I imagine it's
a little more pumping on the weekend,
but the sparse crowds
factor into some of the
things in this sector being fun.
We'll get to the
other place.
But what it did allow
for me is that I was able
to get a front row seat
at what I think is a
first class concert venue.
I'm looking at this in like how many,
because just the way it's a rent where it's this big, like, you know,
there's like, you know, the whole
upstairs component, like all
these porches, there's so many little spots
to watch something.
And you know, concert venues,
there's a lot of great concert venues out there,
but not a lot that have little,
like, nooks and overhangs,
which I feel like is what, you know, probably
what they used to be more like in the 40s and
50s, you know, when concerts were being held
and kind of like we're, you know,
we're turning this old church or this old movie theater
into this and that.
I was just there
like, boy, I'd be lucky to see any,
if a band I loved was playing at
Bob Marley, a tribute to freedom,
be fucking awesome.
Be a great
venue.
And then also that I
have a front row seat for whatever
it is.
It's just going to be like,
alright, it is a reggae band and they're going to play
some reggae covers.
It's not the greatest thing in the world.
The one band.
I think it does seem, we probably watched,
did you also get past the Dutchie?
Yes, yes.
They seem to have about a half
a dozen songs.
Yeah, yes, yeah, we got this.
It's a surprisingly showbiz
pizza-esque performance
despite being human beings.
Well, with a lot of repeated, I feel like
the singer was just like, was he just like
slow motion marching?
Yeah.
Like a robot.
He's got his like, his couple
moves.
And you know, it does have the thing
that happens which, look,
God bless the performers.
They added to the
experience.
But
when I arrived, there was no one
out there on the patio.
And they were performing.
No spectators.
And they just, you know, in order
to entice me to join in,
they are ready
and going and that show goes on
whether there's an audience or not.
Wow.
That's cool.
You know, I have to
I have to applaud
that.
It reminds me
of a good friend of mine, Mr.
Bugman who had a similar experience
at Los Angeles Comic Con.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Performing for
about a half a dozen people in a 500
person auditorium.
Entirely empty chairs and yet he gave
it his all.
He performed as if there were 500 people.
What we found out after is that
a board member of Los Angeles Comic
Con was one of the five people in attendance
and said it was his favorite thing.
He saw the convention
and hoped we came back.
So
you never know.
Right.
If you come to LA Comic Con, fingers crossed
after that hustle Bug put in.
Who's going to be there in that small crowd.
That's why you always give it your all.
Well, that's, you know, yeah, the
lesson that a such
an impassioned artist says Bob Marley or
Bugmane can teach us.
Bugmane a tribute to
Pudding Sauce.
So
so I end up at like
pretty psyched to sit down and realize
wow, whenever this band goes on we're getting a front
row seat and it was me and the level
keeper.
I get to have a little one
on one time with the level keeper.
And we did, it was a funny
just back and forth, talk about the duality
that this whole experience has where
it was
just, it was a particular moment.
We just ended up in a conversation that was kind of
about like parents health
struggles and
and mortality and kind of aging
and kind of we're talking about, you know,
as happens you're on a trip
with somebody you get into some
headier topics and we're like yeah, well you know
parents get older and it doesn't
you know these things don't last forever and you
just got to remember that
and then suddenly
hard wall of reggae
comes down, interrupts
the serious conversation.
And isn't that what you need in a serious conversation?
Just to shake you out.
Yeah, you know
I think it couldn't have gone better if you
ask me.
Yeah, yeah.
It was my
favorite, it is a tie
in terms of serious subject matter
mixed with environment.
It is maybe a runner up only to this other
thing and I'm gonna go back to something, I'm gonna go
way back a bunch of sectors
and talk about a moment, I can't let this series
pass without talking about it.
Please.
When we
were all at the food court
we're up at the food court and we have our little potluck
of all the various things
we could sample from the food court.
And Jason, you got
into a story and the details
of the story don't matter but it was kind of a
grim story, do you know what I'm talking about?
I remember.
Yeah, kind of.
You told a
story that without getting into details
it was the stories
of a very tragic death
that had happened to somebody peripheral to you
and a neighbor with kind of
awful details and you didn't tell this story
as this was not like a fun thing, it was not something you were
taking lightly, the opposite.
No, no, it was startling.
Yes, yeah, yeah, and we all
kind of, you told the story and we all kind of like
oh god, jeez, well that's
oh that's terrible and we're all reeling
from it and then I realized
that as you're telling the story
and we're all processing it, we are all
wearing the little Burger King crowns
and no one acknowledged it until
now.
Was it at least someone's birthday?
No, we were
just like, well we're at the BK Whopper bar
and we have to get the crowns.
The back of them when you walked in
like a whole line of them.
We're all in little crowns like, Jesus
well that's, you know, oh you hate to hear about that.
Well nobody took their crown off and put it over their heart
or anything so at least it wasn't like
that bad.
It was still funny.
It was more insulting or less.
Maybe that would have addressed the
gravity.
Yeah.
Yeah, I do remember that now.
Oh boy, that's the
culture clash, what environments
can bring you at this place.
Yes, yes.
I also got the fun of
that I was getting a lot of texts
suddenly about an upcoming pitch that I'm doing
with people and I wanted to field the
text and take them seriously but I instead
I sent a video and said, yeah listen
I'm gonna deal with this as soon as the reggae
concert's over and then spun around
to the very close reggae performer
in front of me.
That was the most satisfying way to push
notes I've ever.
So anyway
let me
before we move on to the next thing, let me just say
if we're gonna meditate on the title
of this
the definition of freedom
is the power or right to act
speak or think as one wants
without hindrance or restraint.
Do we feel like
do you feel like in your
visit there, do any of us feel like in our
visits here that we
did the definition, participated
in the dictionary definition of freedom?
Yes because while
I didn't get any substitutions
on my sides, they do allow substitutions
which is not always
the case and to me that is
true freedom.
Freedom to substitute.
Beautiful.
If they didn't have that, then you
could scarcely put Bob Marley's name on this
place.
Oh wow yeah.
Damn.
Very good point.
Well let's talk about the other
you went and did this and then you
happened into another one of these places
as part of your sector assignment
but it worked out pretty nicely
which is Pat O'Brien's.
Yes it's
right next door I believe or right nearby.
Yeah I think they're in a store.
Yeah.
Which is a New Orleans institution
recreated in city walking.
Yes and I'll be honest they could have very well
named it Pat O'Brien's
attribute to Pat O'Brien's
because it does
realistically recreate
the Pat O'Brien's courtyard
and piano bar
room of the Pat O'Brien's
in New Orleans.
It is accurate
you feel.
It is actually quite accurate.
Okay.
They have that fountain.
Yes.
It's a champagne glass that's on
fire.
The flaming
fountain in the courtyard which is a very
nice little, they carve
let me just say everybody who did like the production
design of Bob Marley
recreating Bob Marley's house.
It looks cool.
Everybody worked on City Walk the bones
of it back in 99.
Spectacular.
Great job everybody.
Yeah.
I mean look are either of them
NBC Sports Grill and Brew?
I don't see a lot of
logos in years.
Not as fun.
But you know
the Pat O'Brien's I thought was a good
recreation and that's a place that
you know I went to
a lot.
It's a
a lot of bars that are very
touristy in New Orleans which
that is a touristy place.
They are also
they can be kind of very
local too but
for people who are in high school.
Uh huh.
only have to be 18 to be in a bar even though you
have to be 21 to drink.
And so
it causes a sort of
ripple effect of people who are like
14 and 15 having a fake ID that
says they're 18 which is more
believable than one that said they were 21.
So it just ages all the
generations down.
It just ages down
who's in a bar that shouldn't be
tremendously.
Two tears of it.
You know not this bar but there's
a there's another bar
called The Boot that is a near
a college campus but I remember when I was actually
in college being like I can't go
there everybody there's in high school.
Because literally only high school aged
people went to this bar for the most part.
That's weird.
And so it's
a strange city.
But the drinking
age was 18 there until the 90s when the
federal government cut off the highway funds and forced
them to raise it to 21 in return
for having highways.
The same bucket
of money.
So I spent a lot of time at Pat O'Brien's
in my youth
and you know
I
I didn't
have any any drinks at the Pat O'Brien's
in Orlando
but I imagine they're pretty
accurate to the
hurricanes.
I hope I have to admit I don't think
we again this was the end of night.
You didn't get a hurricane at Pat O'Brien's
but drink their famous.
I know but at the end of the night our last the
last drink I need to coast out with a beer
wine.
I can't be adding a new
type of liquor as with both of these.
I guess I failed the audience by
not getting signature drinks at
either of these places.
But I had a fun time
Adam.
I didn't even I'll be honest
I didn't even think about getting a hurricane and
I'm embarrassed that I didn't.
You know what I think I
got.
What's that Pennsylvania beer Jason
that you bring up and I never know what you're talking
about.
Ying Ling.
I had a guy Jonah
Sobel guy in my freshman floor
obsessed with Ying Ling in college.
All he would talk about.
Jonah if you're a listener we got a
Ying Ling fan here.
Oh yeah.
That luring into the podcast.
Well he's listening already.
I like the beer.
I never had it.
It's good.
I didn't
it used to be like it everywhere
at Universal and CityWalk.
Yeah.
Ying Ling.
And I didn't see a lot of places.
It was there.
Deep in the
piano room they had it.
I didn't go there's one half of it I didn't
go into.
I went into the courtyard I saw that fountain
that's recreation.
The piano
room because this is this ends up function it's a tribute
to the whole establishment.
But it's also
it is their
dueling piano bars.
Which
is the case in New Orleans.
There is also a dueling
piano bar.
Correct.
And this room
seems like a really there's like a lot of
Steins up on the ceiling.
Is that how big it was
in New Orleans.
It's not
they're about the same it's not that big of
a how big.
It's not that big.
Yeah neither is very big.
They're both pretty
small.
It's a smallish room.
I think that
is pretty accurate to it.
Okay.
Because this
was our experience.
I kind of thought we were just
going to pop in there and not
really hang.
But this this by this point it was
it was just Mike and I.
And we walked into
I would say an ideal
situation for
dads approaching 40.
Out on the town.
Which is a
mostly empty bar
with
almost entirely empty bar
with plenty of space to sit and not
loud and a guy playing
Ben Folds cover.
Hey.
Yeah.
This is for you and I.
This is exactly
I heard that and I'm like oh we
we might be sitting around for a while.
Yeah.
Two there were only two other people
in the room I believe.
Maybe there was one straight person that left quickly.
Yeah.
And then yeah there were
there's probably room for like 80
people in there.
Could be more.
I think
you can pack more in there.
Yeah.
And there were four.
Geez.
Which now let me
let me back up and say
dueling piano bars have been a
a huge issue on this podcast.
Well.
Previous saga
you know that Howl at the Moon place
was not really my vibe.
On this same trip the
next night after this
Jelly Rolls at the Boardwalk Resort
you were drawn
to like a fly to sugar
and yes I
I could not wait to get out of there.
I just relistens to the Howl at the Moon
one where I realized
Lindsay and Erin at the exact same both
of them were propelled out of this place
like jet fighters pushing
the button.
How fast can I get
out of and I guess I'm usually the
same way.
So to end up looking at
a dueling piano environment and thinking I
think I might want to be here for a little while
was shocking.
I think that's that Pat O'Brien's
ambiance.
It was really
that.
I loved the room.
The room
was great.
Loved the style.
Loved the ceiling.
Loved the
mold of the brown cozy
intimate.
But
it was not the two gentlemen
playing the piano even though they would hit some things later
that I would call
let's just call them normie crowd
pleasers.
Which I think
is where the line is generally drawn from
a Jelly Rolls to here.
Yes.
Generally speaking they're going to play some
songs that are wedding songs.
They'll play some Journey.
They'll
do we've talked about it many times.
There's three songs
that they play.
I thought this was going
to be living on a prayer city.
Sweet Caroline City.
That's where I was entering.
Did they play Piano Man?
Which one?
Not with us.
Does it get played there once a day?
Yeah maybe.
Probably.
They got to fill that room up.
You got a problem with that?
I figured if it was later at night it would probably
be a little sad at midnight.
Even if there's two pianos going back and
forth on it.
Sure.
They should really
though make it double.
You're the dueling piano men.
They played the saddest, one of the
saddest songs ever.
Two when
we were there.
What it became
was we realized okay
we're in good company.
Even though it was the luckiest
which is a little bit corny
for my taste within my Ben
Folds.
However
Ben Folds I feel like is
where this is where you and I
have a truce as far
as 90's music.
This is exactly
the intersection.
The Terminator
the Predator Arms
Carl Seng.
That is where we line
up.
So we both knew we were going to
yeah yeah yes.
And then we realized oh wait
I bet this could just become
you and I throwing out old
man music taste
to these guys who I bet would like
to play stuff that's a little bit
not the usual
not your Bon Jovi's.
We were going back and forth because obviously the way this usually works
is there's little pieces of paper you go you write it
down you put it up you put a dollar or two in the
bucket or whatever and that was happening between
us and this couple that was there as well.
And they had previously just been clearly
getting an entire concert.
Two
pianos playing only for you
cool.
I'm sorry
I interrupted it for those people.
Yes but we ruined it for them and I believe
I forced them to leave
not that I picked a bad thing I
just picked a long thing.
Wichita
linemen.
That was short.
That might have worked.
What Mike ended up throwing out.
I think
I think everyone was living in harmony for a while.
I think we all were on the same page
and then we weren't.
Where did this begin?
I think just the desire
for Randy Newman became
yeah we were talking about that but
that's not yeah.
It's normal if you had a piano
bar the desire for Randy Newman becomes unstoppable
and uncontrollable.
Well of course.
Well everyone gets worked into a
lather as soon as his name is mentioned
and they think of all of his high energy songs
and then they just want to fight
or fuck I guess.
If you really think about it.
I primarily have sex to Randy Newman's music.
Yeah yeah.
So I think I forget
who said it.
Maybe I said Randy Newman and I think
he just I was a little let down because
it was like I think he played you got a friend of me.
No no no.
We're getting closer.
I think he played maybe
Sail Away.
I think he said he
tried to present it as if it was like an obscure
one and I was like this is the
most famous album
we're trying to lure the one especially
there was one who I think like
kept like leaving he's like I don't want to
participate in or
I think there was one who was there for
crowd pleases and another who seemed really happy
we were there to test his
metal.
He was an older guy.
The younger guy kept leaving
but then the younger guy would come back and play stuff
that I more liked because
he would play more like stuff that he
listened to in high school or that I listened to in high
school but then the older guy was happier
when you would throw a Steely Dan at him
or when I cleared the room
by suggesting he play Bruce
Springsteen's 7 or 8 minute song Jungle
Land.
Which he
did in its entirety.
Sweets, movements,
it was complex.
A lot of it was.
Steely Dan's complex.
What a Fool Believes was a challenge
that he was excited to take on.
But I think you know I thought it was good
just for you and I you know how it is.
It's like his parent mode.
Every day is kind of the same.
It's all wonderful but it can get a little samey.
Now you and I were across the country
and we're just making requests
of this piano.
Sing us a song piano man.
I was like
Mike and I are only one tick away.
What we want is to have three drinks
exactly.
I want to hear Steely Dan and you want to hear Bruce
Springsteen.
Dad's got what we wanted.
It really was like
Dad make a wish.
It was really
crazy that it had happened.
It almost lined up.
There was a magic
I had a feeling of magical
serendipity that happened
that night.
It was the first night I was
in Orlando and it was like wow.
Maybe like going to
City Walk every night will be
like this.
Maybe there's
actually like.
Maybe this series won't
work because there will be too much
legitimate great
evocative fun.
Right.
Not enough food poisoning.
Now
of course I love Jelly Rolls in a different
way but I would say this
might have been the highlight of City
Walk.
Van just gave us.
I'm going to call you.
You just
gave us Sly Thumbs Day.
You've been to Jelly Rolls?
Yeah.
Not a fan of Jelly Rolls.
Wow.
You've done Jelly Rolls.
Really?
Well where.
I'm
a Yachton Beach club stayer myself.
Oh so you have.
We never talked about that.
Okay.
Really.
It's quite conveniently located.
Where would you rather be?
I'd end up at the ESPN Zone instead.
Wow.
Yeah.
Right there but
not a Jelly Rolls fan.
Too high
energy?
Too.
I don't like.
Well first of all I don't like the space.
Too big.
It's big.
I didn't even know.
I left before I could see it.
Once they said there was a cover.
I'm sorry.
A cover would be involved in this?
No.
I mean like a cover when
you're already like basically almost
definitely staying on property at Disney.
Like.
Yeah.
Money's already going out the door.
There's a past guest of the show that DM'd me that
she went to this place recently
and I think that's going to have to be an episode eventually
full Jelly Rolls.
I think that's probably
I think it's deserving of an episode.
I'll say that.
I understand.
I'm not a fan of it but
that could be said about many things.
Deserving of
episodes potentially.
Potentially.
A lot of it.
Yeah.
Sure.
But then
sorry should we go back to the do you have a full
you didn't write the full set list down.
I worked down
anything that I took a video of.
Yeah.
So just real quick though
none of you have been to the real
Pat O'Brien's.
No.
What about
the city of New Orleans at all.
No.
I have not.
Well you know what it's not that
close enough simulacrum of that slice I would
actually say.
Wow really?
Just that
slice.
It's kind of surprising.
As soon as you walk outside and
it doesn't smell like piss and everyone's
not stumbling around still drinking with open
containers then it's no
longer the same but
that is mostly wound down.
Right up until that exit.
Of course you can walk around with an open
container at City Walk Orlando though.
Yes that is
the difference.
That is nice.
I think those probably unless
it's the busiest Friday night in the summer
I think.
It's probably not getting
close to New Orleans vibes.
Before you get into
your set list which I think you want to launch
into more of because I'm sure the listeners need to
hear every other song.
They love a list.
It's a shame none of you have had
the hurricane because I did have a good
Pat O'Brien's hurricane anecdote.
Oh yeah please.
So my cousin's husband when he was
in high school he had a job mixing up the
hurricanes at Pat O'Brien's so they batch
them in the daytime.
And they serve them out of big giant
coolers.
So it's a rum punch
drink.
He said that the Mexican
rum that they made them from
was so cheap that it
would come in crates and the crates
would regularly have one or two completely
empty bottles in them.
But they just were like
that's fine.
So that'll give you
a sense of the
just the just how
sugared up a hurricane
is.
The rum
quality could be whatever
it needs to be.
But they would mix them up in giant
like
oil drum vats.
And then that would get
spread out to the like
ladled into the
like a Gatorade
cooler type storage.
To then be
put into their fancy little glasses
and sold for $18 a person
to tourists.
Pat O'Brien's I'm seeing on
the website there's also about
10 different including
the hurricane bottled mixes.
Everything from
triple sack to pina colada
mix, margarita mix,
daiquiri mix.
You get a good hurricane
mix.
They have a
they're tied up with one of the cocktail
distributor people.
A lot of the companies that the liquor distributors
and the mixer distributors are actually based in
New Orleans.
The cocktail was invented in New Orleans.
Is Bipad O'Brien
personally or at least the lore might go
as such?
Well there's a, it was actually at a pharmacy
where it was first invented.
Really, really?
Yes.
But so that
business is actually still like an actual
import export business that likes
where this stuff gets shipped around the world.
So they are hooked up with
one of the like people who make
the sour mix you get
in a normal grocery store.
And so like you could, you'll
end up sometimes seeing Pat O'Brien's
hurricane mix just like you might see
in a grocery store out here just because
it's distributed by one of the same companies.
But yeah they have their own set
of mixers and mixes and the
the powdered hurricane
mix that they distribute
is pretty accurate to the real
deal.
What else is it?
What else goes
into it?
What's in a hurricane?
It's basically
rum, sugar and red.
What's red?
Are there three ingredients?
Red food coloring?
Punch.
You know I'll tell you the powder
is white.
It doesn't turn red until you add
water, whatever it is.
But yeah it's
like a fruit punch type
rum punch beverage
and so some sort of
artificial fruit punch flavoring.
So if you would end it tonight
with one of these you might have
been going to Orlando General.
Yes
and I've been a big
fruit punch at the end of the day.
Yes the like
sugary fruit punch disguises
the large amount of alcohol in it.
But I think
ultimately
the sugar
will cause you more of a hangover than the liquor.
Oh yeah and this is the true
villain of my drinking career as I
approach 40 is that.
Yeah
the sugar is far more of a problem.
Now look I don't need to read
the list.
I have no…
Refresh me.
Give me a little bit of the list I think.
Just quick.
The thing that I thought was funny is that
I did feel like I was saying how nice it was for dads
to get out but then I do feel
like we were punished by having to hear cats in
the cradle.
Oh oh yeah.
How dare we leave.
That's a penance.
Yeah yeah.
We didn't
request that.
We had to sit no no no.
It's like they
knew.
Yeah.
Let's give these let's cut
these guys down.
No I don't know.
Well you look you got your
big surprise Bear Naked Ladies is the…
Well that's the younger guy came back and he just
out of nowhere plays one week
by the Bear Naked Ladies.
Was not my request and then yeah
we said this already that I dared him
to go deeper more obscure.
Either gentleman to go more obscure.
And one of the guys like
I know exactly what I'm going to play.
I was playing this all the time when we were outside
during the pandemic and he made the
he was like this kind of became like a
song I really really like and I was like oh my
god what is he going to play.
This is going to be crazy or whatever.
And then he played the song
Odds Are which is a post
Stephen Page leaving Bear Naked Ladies song
which I am not
I don't fuck with them much
anymore ever since Stephen
left.
Wow.
Language.
I apologize second time I said it twice
but I'm so passionate about rock and roll music
that that sometimes just gets me all
frothy like a Randy Newman song.
Sugar.
I had a feeling
that it was a post Stephen leaving
song and I think I knew it
because five seconds
in you leaned to me in a video
I have and said this is after Stephen left.
I wanted him to make sure.
Now that being
said it's one of the look at his
at his chaste hits ever since
okay.
Ed Robertson of course who does the
rapping on one week.
Stephen's the one who sings
it's been that's his voice.
Jason
of course doesn't even know any of this.
He didn't when he saw
the Bear Naked Ladies he didn't realize Stephen was out of the band.
So this might be an average concert
go or not realizing it.
So I have
been out of shape about it.
Let's educate everybody.
It's not your fault.
Well I thought he was going to
be like I'll go deeper and he just pulls
out if I had a million dollars.
Well sure I mean that you could also say well it's not
so.
Van how lost are you?
What is your and are you
anxious to get past the Bear Naked Ladies material.
He's anxious to get past but I don't think he's lost.
He got me back at had a million
dollars.
Sure.
That was on a radio hit.
Can you pull up
can you pull up a music video for it?
the Odds Are music video which I have watched which is
about all the different like things that could happen
in your life but Odds Are you're going to be alright.
Odds Are we're going to be alright tonight.
I do know the chorus too.
I mean that's honestly
that's kind of a good little anthem
for the series because Odds Were
we were all going to get sick
and tired of lots of aspects
of this.
But we were alright.
I've got Bear Naked Ladies perform Odds Are at Billboard
Studio.
Yeah.
You want the real you want the video where they're
like newscasters.
Can you can those.
Oh there we go.
Yep.
Got it.
Okay good.
Can the Vision Pro
somehow insert Steven
back into the band.
Yeah but the song
wouldn't sound right because then it'd sound like one he
would have worked on with him.
We can hear that.
We can hear that a little bit.
That's kind of bizarre.
Do I have permission to place this over
Jason or?
Do you put it over me?
Do you place it over me?
Because he's not a fan.
That's just justice.
Is there a program that can insert Jason
into the Odds Are music video?
It's playing.
I haven't accidentally.
Jason's singing a song or whatever.
There's a
new Bear Naked Ladies song called Love and Life
which is maybe the most pandery song
I've ever heard in my life.
Geez you
hate these guys.
No I don't.
I feel
bad.
I'm so negative about it.
There's a song called Love and Life that I'm not a big
fan of.
But he then played
the other
one.
You're a
one man DJ over there.
I just want to make sure.
So he played it.
Honestly
I was kind of delighted though to be
all kidding aside.
I was like.
It's a good test of the speakers.
Can it pass through
the.
Because this is going through
so many mediums.
Vision Pro 2 Microphone
into Zoom into Podcast App
into Listener's car or
headset.
How did that sound?
Rated for me?
Honestly I
was delighted that this was the choice.
I was
just not expecting this of anything.
And he was just like he gave a
little moving speech about how this
song kind of meant something to him because he was playing
it outside and there's so much
uncertainty about the pandemic and
they moved the piano out there and he's
playing this late period
Bear Naked Ladies song tearing up every night.
I'm imagining this whole story he's got.
So I was like ah this is
good.
This is good.
Now I kind of like
the song because of that.
Wow.
Because of that performance.
You know what.
And I like the guy in general.
We went up
and talked to them after.
We were like what?
They're just playing everything we like.
And I
think the guy was Rob the piano guy.
I sent him a memo.
Yeah.
Oh geez.
Oh great.
I could look it up.
I think he was
a Howl at the Moon person around when I
worked at Universal Hollywood.
So great job.
They
closed it out with a bunch of Abbey Road.
We got a bunch of.
Oh yeah.
We forgot all about that.
What a great way to
end.
Did Dave Matthews
play the song.
I texted Mitch.
I'm like there's a guy
playing like two step
by Dave Matthews.
Wow.
Mitch got excited about that.
You're lighting up people across the
country.
Keep Me in Your Heart for a While is the one
the saddest song ever they wrote when he was dying.
Oh I forget that.
So yeah I was like
like touched.
I was touched many times.
You know what.
It was like an intimate
cool performance that reminded
me.
Mike you and I are both very fond of the Largo.
Yeah.
John composer John
Bryan's performances at the Largo where he kind of
goes through the great American songbook
and you can request off the wall things
and see what inspires you.
Yeah.
I could not believe how much this dueling piano
bar in Orlando was giving
vibes of these Largo shows.
I liked
the candlelit atmosphere.
This was one of the big shockers
of the trip.
I would say go to Pat
O'Brien's but do it on an
empty Tuesday or Wednesday.
Unless you do
want to hear.
But not on an empty stomach
if you're going to get a hurricane.
Yeah.
Very smart.
Get a
cup of gumbo with it.
Cup of gumbo
to go.
Cup of gumbo and a hurricane.
Boy that seems like a
classic city walk.
Yum yum.
Poor decision.
And yet a tribute to the freedom
that you have when you're there.
Freedom
is a tribute to freedom.
Fuck yourself up.
Have we missed anything about one of these places?
Any important
details?
I don't think so.
Because I think this is a great
revisit.
I think we've covered
most of it.
No I think we got it.
Both these places
are important.
I think also
I was going to say benefit.
That's not the word.
But like are victims of their placement
in City Walk at this point.
Pat O'Brien's way back there.
I've been airdropped a photo from Van.
Great.
Thank you.
This is so efficient for just
getting all our future content out.
Thank you.
So I almost wish like
there were more people like
oh I missed my airdrop.
Okay I've accepted it now.
Is it Ed
in the music video?
I think it is.
Over Jason?
Well almost.
I scooted it over.
Jason's spoken through.
Okay.
Great.
So
yeah I think you know there should be
people there that are more like directing people
towards these establishments.
There's signs with arrows.
Yeah but you don't see those.
Something that says like food, drink, shops.
And then there's an escalator.
But it's not enough.
You want to make sure these places don't disappear.
They do have unique menus.
Like unique food offerings.
I'm surprised our family never made our way back.
It's because of placement I bet.
It's part of the
I like the sprawling nature of this place
with these little secret rooms almost.
But maybe they suffer because of them.
So listeners check them out.
You want the intimacy as I always say.
You want the intimacy so you don't want it
to be completely packed.
But you don't want it
to become closed either.
And I don't like
you don't want it to become more of a douchey
jelly rolls.
Because again
you get your jelly rolls filled at Disney World.
Yeah.
Well I will say
both of these places have been open
without change since 1999.
So I'm not terribly concerned.
So Universal forgot that they're there.
And with other ones that have changed a ton.
Motown Cafe didn't make it.
I do think their tucked away
placement has helped them
to weather the storms.
Oh!
As opposed to like that
Motown Cafe got
asked for Bubba Gump because it was
prime position.
They're eyeing
those ones kind of on the
main alley more.
Yeah.
That's a good point.
Well I hope they
stay tucked away there forever.
Fun and freedom
is what you can find in this sector.
And Van we thank you for experiencing both of those
things.
And technology.
Thank you for the tribute to technology.
Of course.
Van Roche Show You Survive
podcast, The Ride, The City Walk Orlando Saga
Multiverse of Madness.
Let's exit
through the plug portal.
Is there anything you'd like
to plug?
First the
Apple Vision Pro.
My buddy Tim wanted me
to plug that on the show.
Sure.
And then if you're in the Los Angeles area
April 24th
will be the next
edition of Bugmane's Manifesto.
Manifesto 3.
Oh I didn't
this is breaking news to me.
This has not been announced.
This is being announced here for the first time.
PTR exclusive.
That is at the Lyric Hyperion Theater
in Los Angeles.
And
you know I want to say it's at
like 9 or 10 o'clock
but I don't really know the time exactly.
But just search for the Lyric Hyperion
Theater and it should be up.
It's a great time.
I've been to both Manifestos.
They've both been very educational and great
for just grounding, centering,
and comedic extravaganza.
Yeah, highly recommended.
Not to be missed.
I do perform
in them as well myself.
It's a rare
occasion to see me perform.
And I have a feeling if you
want to see me in this Vision Pro headset
I may be wearing it
during the show.
I'd believe it.
Okay, okay.
So look for the guy in the Vision Pro
unless everyone is wearing them.
But you know it's well over a month from now
so it could be have taken
over the world by storm by then.
Based off of this appearance.
Can you make that look more like
Cyclops' visor?
Say more.
You know what I'm talking about Cyclops?
He has a gold visor with a red strip.
He has a gold visor with a red strip in there.
It's like energy beams.
You know what I'm talking about.
But how would this
are you asking if I could
make the…
what are you asking me to do?
Could your eyes go away
and it could be sort of that red strip?
Sort of.
So if I go into an immersive
experience.
Yeah.
Let me pull one up.
Because you could mod the outside
to be yellow like Cyclops.
You know like you could just paint it.
So when I go to an immersive
experience you guys don't see my eyes anymore.
No, okay.
That's…
That looks like the
punch-drunk love psychedelic scene break.
Speaking of John Bryan.
And so
I could say because I am a developer right now
they don't give me access to really
control what's on this screen.
But I have a feeling that sort of thing will open
up eventually.
Because you can get
I'm sure somebody's going to make the outside yellow
and then put a red strip there.
Well the issue is there's
cameras all throughout.
Right.
It's not going to be perfect.
And so it's limited in what you could do to
cover things up.
Right.
But I'm just saying the outside…
the stuff around here.
But there's cameras all around.
There are sensors.
This thing's covered in sensors.
You could paint it yellow I bet.
Agree to disagree.
I'm not going to do it because
I think I'll mess with the camera.
You're not doing it to mine.
You have to be a confident painter
I think for that.
Well somebody do that
out there in the audience.
Mod your
headset.
I don't think that's so crazy.
Can you make it just display the lyrics of
Bruce Springsteen's Jungle Land.
Look that's why I've got the developer strap
because I want to get Jungle Land on there.
Okay good.
You taught yourself a Jungle Land pass.
Alright well Van we're going to let you go and we're going to do a quick
end of it check in with the Sector Keeper.
Thank you Van and let's see if we can
get him in here.
Alright say hi to the Keeper for me.
We will.
Thanks.
Yeah have a good trip.
Okay.
Sector Keeper.
Boys
boys you did it.
You did it.
Thank you.
It was fun.
We like this one.
This one was pretty fun.
No one got sick huh?
No.
That's great boys.
You covered Pat O'Brien's
Bob Marley a tribute to freedom.
Yeah we tributed freedom already.
And of course City Walk's rising star
the live band karaoke bar.
You can't
forget it if you've been there.
It's the best.
Wow.
Yeah.
Wait wait.
Boys.
You know this was
the same day about
as the Margaritaville.
Yeah I remember
all the Margaritaville.
We like hit a wall there
basically.
You didn't feel great.
We all just kind of went back to
the hotel.
Well Mike you
did the Velocicoaster after eating
two hamburger patties.
Most of the patties I ate.
Yeah.
Mike was in a different place I guess.
Yeah yeah but we just like we got like a
tip that it like because we were going to
do this and we were going to sing but when we heard it's like really
hard to get up there.
Yeah that's one thing.
Okay so yeah of course singing with a live band
would be cool but then we heard like you got to wait all night.
It's like a random order.
It's just like a hassle.
We didn't
do it okay.
I'm sorry.
You didn't do
City Walk's rise.
No if somebody told us
it would be impossible for us to sing
okay.
Don't you realize what you've done
boys.
Who cares what do you mean what have we done.
We haven't done anything.
It doesn't
matter.
You created a new rift.
No.
What?
What's happening to this room you guys?
Just because we didn't sing
Pour Some Sugar On Me in a live band karaoke.
Nobody said don't stop believing.
You didn't sing Sweet Caroline Boys.
Oh come on.
You didn't sing Cracklin' Rosie.
There's a whole I can see the rifts.
There's some tears.
There's a lot of
indecipherable like
colors and goo.
Jason you
promised me you said you were going to do
Gong Gong Style.
I crashed down in bed.
He didn't even do the little dance.
He didn't
dance like a horse.
But who cares why
this will be happening.
This is what you've
done.
You've created a new rift.
Everything's
being pulled apart.
I can see
it now.
You can too.
You're all being pulled into different
Maltiper's.
Oh my god.
The room is swirling
around.
This looks horrible.
This looks like one of those shitty Marvel CGI
goop things.
It's awful.
This looks worse than the Flash.
It's really dark.
Well there's some okay
scenes in the Flash though visually I think.
You're still arguing that.
The effects
you can't think were good.
The rift I'm being pulled
into actually the effect looks okay.
That was a world where they finished it all
right.
Don't you see you're being split apart
from each other.
This isn't the time to have
quick quibbles about the Flash.
What do you mean?
I can
barely see Mike and Jason anymore.
Wait so we're going somewhere
else.
We're not going to be with each other.
Completely different Maltiverses.
What?
Do I at least
end up with Scampi?
No then
maybe in this world.
I don't
know.
Have you fucked Scampi in this world?
I don't know.
He has.
You can see the smile on his face.
Even from
back here I can see it.
This isn't the time to talk
about fucking Scampi.
It was just one special night.
What do you want?
Harry admitted it
right before we die.
We knew
we'd get it out of him.
Focus boys.
Wait
can I get Mike to admit that he never thought
maybe Aladar was cute?
No.
I'm a truthful man.
Listen listen.
There's one way to save this.
There's only one way to stitch up the rift.
You'll have to create new Jump Points
boys.
What?
How?
Record separate
podcasts about malls next to
theme parks.
Go on your own.
Completely autonomously.
Your
own podcasts.
And hope
that I'll be back at some
point.
Wait wait wait.
The only way to reunite is for us to
record separate different podcasts
from our parts of the Maltiverse?
I'm turning to dust
like Peter Parker with Iron Man.
Oh no.
That CGI effect looks pretty good
I thought when I saw it in IMAX.
That one's a little better than the rest of it.
The world we're in is pretty
I just can't even tell what's happening.
It seems
kind of off the shelf but oh god.
We're stretching.
We're pulling apart.
Pulling apart.
Good luck.
Jason.
Jason's calling his own
name.
Jason yelled his own name.
Jason.
Dog.
This has been a Forever
Dog production.
Executive produced
by Mike Carlson, Jason
Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please
visit ForeverDogPodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam
and liking our page on Facebook.