Forever.
Yep, test one two, test one two.
Okay, I think, yeah, I sound fine.
I guess we can give him a couple more minutes, I don't know.
It feels like we've given him enough time,
it feels like Scott's not coming back.
Yeah.
I think he's serious, I guess.
All right, time to get down to it.
Let's do our rank the X-Men episode.
Well, yeah, we could do that.
I was also thinking, should we call Nate?
Should we call Mr.
Morrow?
Like as far as-
Oh, do you wanna get him on FaceTime
and see who his favorite X-Men are?
Well, yeah, I think he would have a lot of good opinions
about X-Men, I'm just saying like permanent hosts though.
Oh, that feels like a larger discussion.
Well, we can test him out.
Guys, guys, wait, wait, don't, please,
don't do any of that, I heard you.
Okay.
I got a lot of perspective last night,
thanks to someone very special.
Whoa, whoa, what the fuck is that?
What the hell, what the hell is that thing?
Watch out, punch it, punch it or something.
Guys, guys, no, no, no, no, no.
He's my friend.
His name is Cowfish, and I know he looks a little weird,
but when you get to know him, you'll understand him,
and you won't treat him like an outcast anymore.
He reminded me how important friends can be,
and how you're never really an outcast if you have friends.
Like you and me, Mike, and you and me, Jason.
That's true.
Is he doing one of those long fish-like shits right now?
Like red, you know what I'm talking about,
that red string that comes out of fishes?
Oh, yeah.
I think he's shitting.
Cowfish, what is that?
I hope whatever he just pooped out
isn't something that they serve at his restaurant.
Something else you should know,
there is a experimental fusion restaurant
named after Cowfish, and something tells me
if we all talk about it, explore everything about it,
then we'll have a great time,
and get this saga back on track.
What do you guys say?
I say hell yeah.
Jason?
Yeah, sure.
You know, one more ambivalent.
Say hell yes.
Hell yes.
Okay, great.
Let's all braid our hair.
He's gonna open his mouth,
and we just need to swim in there,
and connect our hair braids to his uvula,
and then that'll teach us everything we need to know
about him, and all his experiences, and his restaurant.
You guys get with that?
We have to go in his mouth?
Yeah, we gotta go in his mouth.
Don't worry, look, he took a poop,
so whatever that was isn't in there.
Do we have to come out the other end?
He didn't tell me that part.
Okay, he's been sure too?
Only one way to find out.
Come on, guys.
All right.
Let's go.
Where?
Where could he be?
When your town has made you frown,
when your square has made you swear,
when life gives you one more punch,
you need a doughnut soaked in Captain Crunch,
you need a place, a place to stroll with alcohol,
a place that features part of the Berlin Wall,
where seam-punk robots sell chocolate snacks,
a place where you can tattoo your lower back.
So let's go take a walk.
Let's all go to City Walk Orlando tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents The City Walk Orlando Saga,
multiverse of madness,
a daily, extremely necessary series,
exploring the shops, restaurants,
and cosmic wonder that make up universal City Walk Orlando.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
The City Walk Orlando Saga, multiverse of madness.
Today there is a mood of healing, a reunion,
and I feel refreshed.
I feel lively in a way that I haven't before
because I'm so happy to be back here with you, my friends.
I was guided back.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Mike Carlson, it's so good to see you.
I'm so good to see you.
I'm sorry about everything.
No, everything's fine, and I understand.
Sometimes it takes a special friend to make everything okay.
Yeah, that's right.
And I just can't wait.
I'm so excited that today we'll be reverberating
with love like that.
Jason Sheridan, hi, buddy.
Welcome back, brother.
Yeah, yeah, it feels good.
It's a new chapter.
We're also joined by one of our favorites
from her podcast, very amusing, it's Carly Wisell.
Hey.
Hello, I'm thrilled to be back.
Yay, thank you for returning,
a survivor of the Downtown Disney ordeal.
I keep finding myself in these themed
mall entertainment districts somehow.
It's either it's slow moving boats
or it's oddly mundane retail establishments,
but let's make sure that we know where we're going today.
Let's get our assignment from the Sector Keeper.
Oh, great one.
Boys, boys, and Carly, phase six,
sector two is the cowfish sushi burger bar.
Eat up, boys and Carly.
Okay, there we have it.
So the focus today is about the brilliant,
the misunderstood, my friend, the cowfish.
And Carly, I understand that you have,
you've encountered this cowfish before, have you not?
I have, I've survived and lived to tell the tale.
This is so exciting, and I, you know,
when we were poking around putting this together,
and I just asked you, is there anything
that you are mildly interested in in CityWalk Orlando?
You had this locked and loaded, ready to go,
shouting the cowfish's name.
Yes, in terms of personal dining, I'm going to Antohito's,
but if we're gabbing on a podcast, we're doing cowfish.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Antohito's, yeah, possibly the most,
more like legit establishment in some way.
But yes, cowfish, how could you not engage with the cowfish?
How could you not?
How does this place exist?
How is it still open?
It will be open forever.
I think so.
Cowfish will live longer than I do.
I hope so, and has lived long, and we can, I think,
look to cowfish for the cowfish's wisdom,
and hopefully all of that can get imparted to us
here when we need it in the deep end of this long journey.
Yeah, it really is the best of humanity, isn't it?
Yeah, a universal original, I believe.
Well, is it, because there are other establishments.
I think they might have, yeah, this is,
it's the weirdest arc of a restaurant.
Charlotte and Raleigh, North Carolina, and then this.
Yeah, is one of those the casino?
Is one of those the casino, there's a casino cowfish?
Oh, I don't know, you tell me.
I'm confused.
I'm still learning the cowfish's ways.
I'm confused because there's some restaurant
in a casino called Cowfish as well.
So the mystery here is like.
Okay, figure that out, but let me know if you've,
and then also, but it clearly is a brand
that is working for Universal that they're excited about
because it made it to City Walk, Beijing.
It's one of those that they reinvested in.
This is in South Africa.
What?
Cowfish Silver Star Casino,
the name of the casino is Cowfish, but.
Then that's not affiliated.
But no, no, this is Cowfish Sushi Burgers.
Yeah, but the logo's not the same, is it?
It's not the same.
No.
But what is this?
Well, and who's stealing Cowfish's good name
and trying to profit?
And it's the same thing, it's the sushi and burgers.
I mean, unless this one was first,
which very well could have been, but.
But do they have burger as sushi?
Well, that's the question.
That is the question.
I'm actually extra confused.
This truly is the innovation,
the spirit that drives Cowfish.
Because yeah, a restaurant can offer both of these things,
but both of these things together never been done before.
And that's what we're dealing with.
If you've never been there, if you've never been by there,
if you've never been to Raleigh, North Carolina, apparently.
Or South Africa.
Or South Africa, if you've never been to South Africa,
this is a combo burger and sushi restaurant,
but that also combines these items into a magical blend,
an unprecedented blend called burgushi.
Never before seen and never to be seen elsewhere.
Very possibly, never again.
Okay, when we corresponded about this,
was this based on an experience that you had
that you were enthusiastic about,
or you just baffled by Cowfish?
I think we suspend reality
by being theme park people very often,
but we're simply not talking enough about the fact
that this exists and thrives in Orlando.
Absolutely.
Thrives.
That's what this whole thing is about.
I think people have said that City Walk Orlando
feels like a place that you rush through
on the way to incredible theme parks, but not us.
We slowed down, we took the time,
and that's what we're doing now,
is meta to every day stepping through
and making sure we all reflect on the fact
that there is a burger sushi restaurant out there,
which thousands of people could go to if they wanted to.
And I think many do.
Yeah, it seems like it.
Yeah, seems popular.
The time of year we were there,
we tried to do it kind of like middle of the week
after Halloween, kind of an off season,
and we encountered some empty rooms,
some lonely rooms at various establishments.
Cowfish, not one of them.
Cowfish definitely hopping and happening.
but very friendly wait staff.
Oh, that's true, because there's all the
on-seastic.
Very enthusiastic.
Yeah, yeah.
That they're excited to do.
There was an energy in there.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Of excitement.
You get that question at many a restaurant,
is it your first time here?
And usually, it's like, I'm gonna,
it is, but I'll be fine.
I'm not like learning, you're not shaping my view
of how the earth works, are you?
In this case, they are.
When the person asked, is it your first time here,
they're like, yes,
and you've got a lot of explaining to do.
I mean, I don't wanna talk out of turn,
but it does feel like the cowfish has something
that Toothsome wants and will never have.
Interesting.
That's an interesting, that's a little gauntlet thrown.
Because Toothsome, we're going full decor,
we're doing terrifying walk around characters.
But here at Cowfish, they don't need that,
they don't need that.
You know what you're getting into,
it's gonna be wild and everyone is literally seated
waiting for it.
And the food is the abomination at Cowfish.
Yeah, it's not.
Not the character around you.
Not the decor.
The food is going to shock you.
So there's no Jacques the robot equivalent at Cowfish.
Not as far as I saw.
Well, there's Cowfish himself, my friend,
who is outside the restaurant.
Greets you, yes.
Which, you know, we've noticed a lot of these places
have some big thing out front.
Some photo op, yeah.
To kind of hurry in.
And the Cowfish, one of the great ones,
I sat on Cowfish, I took a magical ride
that I'll never forget.
Right.
It illuminated, changed me forever.
I didn't know that Cowfish was a real animal
that looks a lot like the one in the logo.
It is this odd squat, little, like this yellow squat
with two little horns animal.
Yeah, I didn't know that either.
So there are Cowfish in our world,
not in our part of the multiverse.
That's how another restaurant could get away with using it
because if a Cowfish is an animal,
there's plenty, well, it's just named after the animal.
No, we're going more off of it.
Because it doesn't look like this Cowfish
stole any of the proprietary dishes.
Okay, okay.
Doesn't look like it.
That's really what it's about.
And it was one of the biggest questions that I had
on the way to our City Walk Orlando expedition.
I knew of this place, obviously,
and okay, so it's burger sushi combos,
but what does that mean?
Exactly.
Is it bun,
and then there's a sushi roll in the middle?
And I couldn't begin to picture what rolls are
that are burger oriented.
Rarely is an entire restaurant concept predicated on,
I don't know what this is,
and I don't know if it's gonna be good.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
And that is the Cowfish.
The expense is high before your food even comes out.
What other restaurants are you nervously anticipating?
What do you mean, burger sushi?
What do you mean?
That sounds bad.
Could it be bad?
I don't, that's the feeling.
Oh, I don't know.
Well, that's what I found about Cowfish,
is that Cowfish's reputation wasn't good,
but maybe the Cowfish is misunderstood.
Right, right.
Maybe that's why the Cowfish is an outcast,
and really, and that's what I've found,
that Cowfish's spirit is what matters.
That's very important, yeah.
Isn't that right, Cowfish?
Thank you for, okay, okay.
Standing close by.
Don't wanna bother Cowfish,
but you can chime in if you want.
I think that all the decor kinda plays on your expectations
or confusion or lack thereof,
because when you get up to, past the host stand,
you get up to the second floor of this massive establishment.
Massive complex.
It's a complex.
Yeah, absolutely a complex.
If you go to the bathroom on the third floor.
Kind of a trademark of city walk restaurants.
That's true, NBC Sports Bar and Grill,
the restrooms are on the second floor.
You gotta walk up some stairs to get to those restrooms.
And some are on top of each other.
It's like the Fantasyland dark ride, so you know.
Right.
Yeah, Alice, you're up above Mr.
Toad or whatever.
It's this beautiful interconnected complex.
It's beautiful, yeah.
It's a beautiful way to say it, it's beautiful.
It's almost like the combination of burgers and sushi
to make burgueshe?
Burgueshe.
Okay, so if that phrase is in your head
and you know I might be having burgueshe today
and you're wondering what does that look like,
then you end up at, there's this fountain
when you get past the host stand on the second level,
and that shows you what you might, there you go, yes.
That is a burger bun, okay, so it's a fish bowl tank,
and then there's a burger bun and lettuce,
and maybe, I don't know, is it mushrooms or seaweed?
What's up on the top?
I don't know.
It's unclear.
It's something dark.
Some brownness.
A brownish, blackish substance,
and then between not a burger patty, but a full sushi roll,
and so you think is this what I'm having today?
Am I gonna bite into it?
Is that the size of it?
It looks like it's 30 pounds.
Is it a novelty thing?
Is it like a heart attack grill
where it's like I'm gonna have to eat the biggest
piece of food I've ever eaten before?
That was what occurred to me is like,
taking a bite of that, it does feel like
your heart would be immediately upset.
There'd be some quiver.
Right.
It's like it's bracing itself for a heart attack.
Is it gonna be served to me in a fish tank?
That's a question you might have.
Is that part of it?
That might be part of it.
And then there's fish, it is a real fish tank.
There are fish in there.
There are also fish in it.
So yeah, this I think is designed to sort of
light your imagination on fire and say,
can you believe the world,
look at the world we've created here.
And it's got more-
What man is capable of?
Right, and really what it does though
is it asks more questions than it answers.
And I don't think they're good questions necessarily
because this doesn't look like an appetizing thing.
Frankly, it doesn't really look,
it looks kind of like a stuffed animal
or like a stuffed thing you would buy.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
A stuffy, a squishy mallow.
Yeah, edible squishy mallow.
Okay, okay.
It also just, yeah, it looks, it doesn't look real.
Obviously they have to build something
that's an approximation of food
so it would sustain in liquid.
So yeah, all of that, it feels like some sort of like
gross 90s commercial where kids are going to a restaurant
that their parents want to go to
and they've built some like monstrosity
like to look like food your parents would like
that you hate and you want a cheeseburger
or you want pizza.
Today the burger-ooshies.
Yeah, and it's the lady with the beehive hairdo.
I eat your burger-ooshie or whatever.
And like that's what it looks like to me here.
Yeah, yeah.
This is, Carly, context here,
there's been other guests who we have like specifically sent
and made to go do things at City Walk Orlando
who all regretted our decision for them.
In this case, you had just because you're down there,
you go down there.
So you were willing, we did not force you to go to this place.
Not at all, I went on my own volition in the past, yes.
Solo or the?
Oh, always solo, yep.
Yeah, yeah.
Just me.
Better to test solo in case you ever bring other,
you don't want, I don't know, you like meet your mom down there.
You don't want to like, now your mom is having a tough time
with burgers.
Yeah, I didn't want to invite, you know, be there maybe on a vacation,
more of a vacation type of trip because it's always a little bit of work.
But I didn't want to bring anyone with and have them discover
if they liked burger-ooshie or cheese-berg-ooshie in person.
I went solo.
Basically it was like an intrepid reporter trip, you know,
just trying to find the truth in the sushi.
Now, as we keep saying this, what I am picturing would be like
tasting plat, like omakase, I believe is the tasting, right?
It's like a bunch of little plates.
The original name for Quibi, yes.
Yeah, the original name for Quibi.
And like someone would be making you a sashimi or like a Kobe beef,
like real beef, and like, it's little plates.
Well, this someone you're describing is already overshooting.
Yeah, I don't think that's what this is.
Curated, because omakase is like the finest I learned from the Quibi,
and it's like the curated, selected.
Very high quality.
And it's, I think the one Epcot restaurant does it.
It's like 10 or 12 courses.
Takumi-ten.
Yeah.
No burger-ooshie there.
No burger-ooshie.
Okay.
Is that like a fine…
They will serve meat and they will serve sushi,
but not in the manner that this place does.
Right.
Not in the sacrilege way Calprish does.
I kind of remember when this opened in the mid 2010s,
when a bunch of new stuff was coming to CityWalk Orlando,
and they're like, well, you know, bento boxes.
Well, imagine if bento boxes had burger and sushi.
Is that right?
That you're not wrong, but that's not the whole picture.
Okay.
So that is an option.
That is an option.
It is, yeah.
And that is what I got.
I got a bento box, but that is not something you have to get.
I tried some other things.
You got the bento box?
You went all the way to Calprish and got a bento box?
For the main, but we tried burger-ooshie.
Yeah, we split a burger-ooshie.
Okay.
Let me paint a little more of the picture of where you're…
Because the food is one thing, but the location.
You've got a couple odd things going on.
Weird art that mashes up a cow and a fish, this iconography.
Here's a big yelling trout or something, and there's a big saddle on his back.
Or here is, perhaps most inexplicably, Japanese-style art of Elvis eating…
Well, does he have…
No, wait, there's a pill.
Wait, that's very grim.
Elvis having pills?
Yeah, on his little table, there's a bunch of pills.
Is he dying?
That's weird.
Well, Elvis famously was taking a lot of pills.
Yeah, that's true.
But he doesn't look good in this photo.
This is a very let-yourself-go Elvis eating a ton of burgers, but then Japanese text.
I wonder what it says.
Yes, somebody translate this if you can.
It's…
But you look at Elvis in this and you're like,
well, I don't know if I want to…
Is this food gonna make me look like that?
With all the pills?
The robe is open and there's pockets.
I mean, this looks like a private moment between him and his meal that we shouldn't be seeing.
Seems like the artist is signaling you to maybe give it another think
and decide if you really want to die here.
Elvis needed to be really peeled up to be able to eat cowfish.
That is something that's maybe saying.
Now, in the context of our trip, I set this one out.
This is after a couple of days of busy park stuff.
And the day, the Thursday of the week, where a lot of us were defeated.
The hell day, yeah.
Yeah, the hell day.
And so you guys opted for this for lunch, right?
Is that right?
That is correct, yes.
Okay.
We did.
We sure did.
We signed up.
We said, cowfish, I see you.
I will see you at a table.
Right.
And then also, this I'm curious to get your thoughts on, Carly, the gender binary
that is presented in the restroom signs in which men are bulls standing up and peeing into a tap toilet.
Not a urinal.
No, no, no.
Just like a big proud stream coming out of this bowl.
And then women are fish holding purses.
I hate what I'm looking at right now.
Yeah, I really don't care for this.
Not in a quality way, in a that shouldn't exist.
Someone should have said, maybe no.
It's very off-putting, yes.
I'm just confused a little bit by it.
I don't like seeing a cow pee into a toilet.
I don't like that.
I just don't know why you use that as a-
That's an abomination separate from the gender split, that all women are fishes.
Right, and they hold their purse.
I will say-
And they got a little baby lipstick.
They don't show a stream on the ladies side, at least.
That's good, I guess.
Well, shouldn't the fish be in the toilet?
Because that's her home.
That's true.
So basically we're watching her gasp for air and try to survive.
Oh, that's a very good-
She'll be dead after this silhouette is done.
Does the fish swim up through the toilet, pop out of the toilet,
go to the bathroom, and then flush itself?
Maybe.
Maybe, yeah.
Maybe it's a double flush.
This is somehow insulting to all parts of the gender spectrum.
Yes, to all humans and some animals.
It's really something.
You're taking this all in aesthetically.
As you're waiting for food, after some stuff has been explained to you,
nervous anticipation.
Carly, I guess I'm curious what you had.
We should go off of your-
How many times have you been here?
I've been once.
Oh, you've only been once?
I do think, because I usually go to Universal Solo,
if I had been traveling with children, a whole family visit,
I would be here way more often.
Because I don't usually do a sit-down dinner on my trips,
I'm just running in circles, I've only been once.
I don't want to say once was enough,
once was enough to know what burger-ooshie is.
And you did get burger-ooshie.
If you take any account, I'm not fucking around.
I'm getting the burger-ooshie.
Well, do you have any-
And I can narrow it down.
I can toss out some items, but I don't know if you remember
the gist of what you had.
I will say I don't remember everything I ordered,
but I would never forget the burger-ooshie.
I see, I see.
Okay, okay.
Appetizers, drinks, any of that?
Do you recall any of that?
I don't, because do they have anything that's as silly as the main attraction?
There's a couple.
Cowfish cooler, the moo fish punch.
Oh, I don't mess with that.
Japanese whiskey smash.
Yeah.
I'm seeing buffaloes and bacon.
That's what I see, buffalo.
Yeah, yeah.
That's like an old-fashioned, which I'm with all the bourbon.
Cherry liqueur, angostura and orange bitters, great.
Honey, okay.
Candy bacon, okay.
I like some of that.
I got a mocktail that day, because that was show day, right?
Yeah, so I was like, I can't get sleepy.
You ate this before you did a live show?
Two hours later.
We actually, this worked out.
This ended up working out well for us.
I did not have a cowfish cooler.
I had a time after time, which was thyme, lemon, muddled blueberries and Gosling's ginger beer.
That's what I had.
Oh yeah, Gosling's, fine ginger beer.
Jason, have you ever had Gosling's ginger, ginger beer guy?
Oh yeah.
You have had it.
I have.
I think I've tried a lot of ginger.
I like barrettes a lot.
You're a barrette's man.
I'm a barrette's man.
I think you can find it at some liher stores and stuff.
That's what, when my family went on a cruise to Bermuda, when I was like 11 or 12,
I feel like it was almost more common than Coca-Cola.
Ginger beer barrettes was.
I had a lot of restaurants down there.
Barrettes, ginger beer, yeah.
Oh, that's a really, that's-
Another topsy-turvy world where barrettes defeats Coca-Cola.
You're on vacation.
This is the inventive world the cowfish imagines.
This is what it looked like.
It looks like a piece of a bush fell into it.
It's kind of cute.
I don't hate it.
It was all right, yeah.
It's got some smashed blueberries in there, which I like a blueberry.
It wasn't anything special, I would say.
Didn't make you sick.
No, I didn't get sick the whole trip.
I'll tell you where the bar is in this series.
I'm seeing something called Bloody Mary Had a Little Cow,
which is three vodka, bloody Mary mixed,
garnished with a mini burger, beef jerky straw,
pickles of your pickled.
Oh, she got that.
Okra, green olives.
This is wrong.
So you could go insane with these drinks if you wanted to,
but you could also just go straight to the main deal.
Karly, I don't think you need to remember what your specific thing was,
but do you remember any ingredients?
I think we've got to tackle what is then when burguer comes out,
what are the primary components of burguer?
Well, I realized I have photos.
Ok, here we go.
I have photos in Google photos of when I went.
So I see a photo of, I guess I did order multiple things
because I was doing research for a story,
but I have what appears to be the cheeseburger-rushi,
and then also some sort of burger and fries.
Oh, ok.
Yeah, because you can do that.
Now, you can do both sides of the spectrum.
You could do just sushi, you could do just burgers.
Yes.
You could not cross the streams.
You could not play a Dr.
Moreau at the table
and just do a regular version of things.
I do like that they have kind of like a chicken exit,
if you get their emergency exit.
No chicken, but in terms of if you're too scared to combine them,
you can have them side by side.
The DB Cooper, you can bail.
Yes.
Safe word.
The safe word is burger.
Yes, but no, I mean, the one I'll never forget is what I believe is
the all-American bacon double cheeseburger-rushi.
I'm fairly certain this is what we got as well.
Yes.
Ok, black Angus beef, yellow cheddar cheese,
white cheddar cheese, and applewood smoked bacon wrapped in soy paper
and potato strings, then flash-fried, topped with dill pickle,
red onion, and roma tomato, served over our house-made cow fish sauce,
topped with ketchup and mustard.
We got a lot of ingredients.
Yes, we do.
But still, you order that and you still can't picture
what that's going to be.
Basically, I think the main thing to say is
the seaweed is replaced by a thin layer of potato French fry paper.
Yes, it's like wrapped in a thin French fry, basically.
The sushi is.
Ok.
And then there's rice, then the next layer is rice.
You still have it.
It was rice even in the list, we just said?
I don't remember.
There's major ingredients.
I think that's rice, unless that wasn't rice.
So still rice is there, but then the middle is a little puff of burger.
There's a little puff of burger.
But it's not just burger, it's burger and cheese and a little bacon.
Yes.
You see this wet area, Jason?
You see this wet area?
That's cheese right there, it's melted cheese.
This is a little piece of bacon, I think, hanging out here as well.
You see that dry part there?
That's bacon.
And can you just refresh my memory, because there's a lot of shades of black and brown going on.
Yeah, go ask me anything you want.
Is there seaweed?
No.
Seaweed is the French fry.
The seaweed is the French fry paper.
This is what I thought was most fascinating.
A French fry casing on the piece of burguyshi.
And is the cow fish sauce just kind of like a thousand island kind of?
I will be honest with you, there are a lot of flavors happening at once,
and I don't really recall the flavor of the cow fish sauce.
I think probably in Thousand Island is probably the zone that it is.
Yeah, it's definitely some sort of mayonnaise with something in it to be special.
Right.
Maybe like a sriracha mayo.
Peach colored mayo, like a darker peach.
I hate to do this, could I give you a little quiz real quick?
I just want to make sure you learned what I taught you.
This is truly, I was having trouble keeping track of it.
That's what I thought.
That is French fry paper.
Go through it.
That's French fry paper.
And then sushi rice?
Sushi rice is, yes, next.
Okay, now I'm going to point to this.
Because it's not in the ingredient list.
Right, Jason, what is this wet looking part here?
Well, is that the bacon or the hamburger?
Oh, Jason, you weren't, I'm so sorry, that's the cheese.
That wet part is the cheese.
I'm so sorry to put you on the spot.
Heaven forbid it needs to be slightly moist.
And then this, you see this part here kind of sticking out that looks drier.
That's the bacon.
Now you've got it.
Now you understand.
That thin layer is bacon, not fry paper.
And then that dark part in the middle is?
That's got to be the hamburger.
That's burger.
That's right.
I'm going to give you a 10% on that test.
That was great.
Good job.
Good for me.
I'll take it.
So this is burgueshi.
Three sauces.
I think burgers usually for me it's ketchup mustard, ketchup mayo, or a thousand.
I feel like that's what I like the-
Yeah, I'm down to one if I can.
Usually two sauces.
Maybe one.
I'm trying to minimize that.
So three, we got a lot of.
And then like there's nothing can really prepare you visually or taste-wise for
pickle, diced pickles on what looks like sushi.
I was wondering if there was a pickle element.
So like they kind of just sprinkle the pickles as if it's a little like
rain shower on the top.
They're just scattering the pickles, like just a dusting of them.
Just a little bit.
Like a little fairy has kissed the top of the burgueshi with pickles.
Does this reflect what you had, Carly?
Is this what you're looking at when you see your photos?
This is making me so nauseous.
It's making me a little nauseous.
I do have to say, you know, I was kind of wiped out and trying to rest up for the show.
And this was a fatigue choice.
But as you were eating this, I was eating room service.
And that was not an indulgence.
That was a really tired-
A necessity.
I need like bacon and eggs or whatever.
Was that what you had, bacon and eggs?
I think we put like French toast and coffee and we might have had some eggs.
Yeah, but was like the bacon hidden inside the toast?
Was it an egg that like cracked open and said hello and then spit out a little morsel of French toast?
It seems like this, your meal does not sound inventive in the least.
The French toast had some toasted coconut.
Sapphire falls, tropical.
It sounds nice, but it's not, you know-
Guava juice.
It's guava juice.
It's not airing.
We want boldness here is what we want.
We want invention.
And that's what this place provides.
I guess now that we've described it, and I really don't know where you're coming at this from,
how did you feel about the burghushi?
So I didn't hate it.
I didn't hate it.
I thought I would absolutely just be horrified by it and I wasn't.
But kind of the overarching theme of it is that the rice shouldn't be there,
but then you just have a burger.
So every bite it's like why is there rice here?
Why is there rice here?
Burger and rice is strange.
Because rice doesn't fit with those things.
I love the shape.
I'm into the shape of it.
I think if they removed the rice, then you'd really be cooking.
Yeah, I think so.
That's the boldness.
A burger you eat in the manner of sushi fun, but the rice just didn't do it for me.
Right.
And it's not like loco moco, the wine dish that's like a hamburger patty gravy and rice.
No, because this has, I mean you got the little, the kisses of the pickles,
you got the tomatoes, you got bacon, you got two cheeses.
There's a lot.
Yeah, it's all American.
Because basically when you taste it, it's a burger with rice.
A cheese burger, a bacon cheeseburger with rice.
But then also what really pulls focus is that fry paper because that's the most, like.
Yeah.
That was really, you just, you have that and you're like huh,
I'm gonna wrap my head around this.
I neither, I'm not in love or hate or anything.
I'm just baffled.
I don't know why.
I agree.
I still am not exactly sure.
I don't think I've had food where I, I don't know if I'd give it like a grade.
I'm just like question mark.
It's just a fog for me.
Yes.
I don't know.
Yes, and that's what this whole restaurant is built around.
Isn't it fascinating?
The great mysteries of California.
When I first read about this place years ago,
I was picturing a couple sliders in a California roll.
Well, now that's more in line with what I had as the main.
That's kind of what my actual.
So I didn't imagine that.
You can't get that.
You can do, you know, this.
Yeah, okay.
If you want.
Yeah, you can get a bento box where there's a little, the tiniest,
what they call a mini hamburger and instead you,
I'm not sure it's big enough to be designated a slider even.
And then there's a roll of regular sushi and that is fine.
Then it's got all this stuff, wasabi and ginger and that is fine.
Then there is, boy, a ton of edamame.
Yeah, there's a lot of edamame.
Mainly edamame.
And then so much cucumber salad, which is.
They really.
That's being generous.
A pile of cucumbers, you might say.
They really pad out the meal with edamame and cucumber salad.
Yeah, all that kind of like the,
it's like wrapping paper.
It's like, or it's like, you know, it's like the kind of the hay paper
that fills out like a gift box.
That's like, yeah, but you can eat it.
That's when I had to fill like an eight page paper in high school
and I just had to do it.
I'd be a lot of filler because I was not prepared.
All these, these items in this bento box are the Sos and Veris.
They're fours.
They're fours of the food world.
Yeah, because really what you're looking at here is,
let's say 17 fries and four or five pieces of sushi.
I wouldn't even consider that little cheeseburger a cheat.
Like that is so nothing.
Yeah.
And it is so.
That's like you're at a cocktail hour
and they're passing out tiny one bite cheeseburgers.
Yeah.
It's smaller than a White Castle slider.
It is.
That cheeseburger sucks.
That cheeseburger is one of the worst,
one of the worst things I ate at City Walk.
That little cheeseburger.
Yeah.
Burnt to a crisp, cold, sure flavorless.
So worse than the frozen White Castle sliders.
Yes, I love frozen White Castle.
I love White Castle.
Surprisingly good.
White Castle is delicious.
So you understand that I'm not Mr.
Snooty
when it comes to any of this.
Yeah.
But I don't know.
Maybe this is one of the mysteries of the cowfish.
I'm only newly friends with him.
I'm still figuring it out.
Maybe there's a reason why his tiny burger
is one of the worst things you can eat at City Walk.
Well, it's giving him the benefit of the doubt.
He's good.
No, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to insult the cowfish who's here,
but this isn't his signature dish.
So perhaps he's trying to kind of be like,
lead you to the signature dish.
You're saying he's more fish than cow, maybe.
Well, I'm no, I'm not saying.
Well, but the burguis, you just want a cow.
You need both.
You need elementary both.
I'm saying he wants both.
He's not going to take time to make this anything special
when the prime example of his artistry is the burguis.
Focuses on the blending.
So puts it all into the burguis to make sure
that the burguis is impeccable, unimpeachable.
Did you two like the burguis?
I don't know if I got a read on it.
I don't think I do either.
I don't know if I got a read from any of you.
Here's what I'll say.
I'll warm up to what I might, maybe final conclusion
that is still filled with, I have a conclusion
that is still confusion, if I can rhyme.
The conclusion of confusion.
Like Johnny Cochran or something here.
A lot of different temperatures happening at once
in the burguis in my memory.
Yes, all living in harmony.
All living in harmony.
Boys, one of the layers is a little warm.
The next layer is cold.
The next layer is medium temperature.
Taking a bite of it all at once is a four dimensional
experience of dinner, lunch.
Yeah, so I would say that's a negative.
All right off the bat.
Okay, I see.
It seems not as about refreshing
like when you do a cold plunge and then you get in a warm
or you go right out of the hot tub, right into the cold pool.
Right, so that was, I would say that's a strike
against it right off the bat.
The more I think about it, the more I think like the
saltiness of like sushi, seaweed would pair.
Well with hamburger, but that was abandoned.
That's gone.
But the rice was kept.
It's the saltiness of fries.
I've had great meals that I can't taste in my mouth,
but I remember I have very firm sense memory
of the potato paper entering my mouth.
And again, I'm not sure if I liked it or not.
My stomach is like making so much noise right now
and it can't be unrelated.
It has to be related.
Blub, blub, blub.
It's really going wild right now.
Well, it's about to go especially wild because at this point,
an important reveal needs to be made
because you just discussed the temperature issue
and we're all discussing do we like this establishment or not.
And I think now is the time to reveal a podcast runner,
a series runner.
Cowfish just may be the restaurant that gave
our friend Eva Anderson food poisoning.
If you wonder for us,
well, not poisoning.
My bad experience was Margaritaville.
Hers was cowfish.
And at this point, I feel like I should let her explain here now,
Eva Anderson.
Okay, Eva, we are now in the cowfish sector.
It has been revealed that cowfish was the place that gave you trouble.
What can you reveal about what you ate and what happened there?
I went there at an off hour.
I sat at the sushi bar in the back where no one was sitting,
which was my first problem.
My first mistake.
I ordered something called the Flamin' Salmon Roll.
Flamin' Salmon Roll, no G.
Spicy salmon with togarashi, mayo, and spice.
Minced pickled ginger, scallions, jalapenos, strings, flash fried,
served over tempura flakes and topped with cayenne pepper strands.
It came out lukewarm, which is never good for sushi
and were kind of warm.
And that I ate it anyway.
There my troubles began.
Here's a photo of what I ate.
There we go.
It seemed like a nice place.
I wish I hadn't done Orlando Humid Weather Sushi.
What was I thinking?
Regardless of the cow element, the fish was not good either.
Yes.
So that's what I ate.
And I want to thank the various Marriottes I stayed at for having
lots of little pill sections in their gift shops, because that's what got me through.
Dear God, I'm so sorry.
All right.
That is Eva's experience.
Well, I want to say, first of all, does she know for sure that's the place she got sick?
Yeah, not necessarily.
You know why?
Traveling and something, your system is all off.
It's all, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I'll travel and especially across time zones.
And then you're just like weird.
Yes, not regular anymore.
Yeah, yeah, your bowel movements are all, I don't know.
So yeah, we can't go.
You know what?
I mean, this is like how I feel like, you know, a lot of people have cast judgment on cowfish
and wrote cowfish off as an outcast.
And, you know, maybe even if cowfish did do this to Eva, what if cowfish was scared?
What if cowfish was trying to protect itself?
Family.
And then the only way, and in that moment, the only way that it could be done
was to give Eva food poisoning.
We don't know.
And maybe we'll never know.
I won't lie.
That story makes me want to eat there more.
Did you just go on?
Let me explain.
Because a lot of these restaurants, like you get the gimmick, you know what you're getting
at Margaritaville.
Here, you don't know what the outcome is.
And if you're coming from a theme park perspective straight into this restaurant,
I find that thrilling.
The fact that I have amnesia about my meal is already pretty entertaining,
but it may or may not affect the way my next two days go.
It's exciting.
Who else can do that?
This is really, you know what?
I think we've all, we're all disappointed by Galaxy's Edge and how like the idea of
like your reputation while you're in Bitu and then it will follow you into the, into Ogas
and whatever.
And that guy, oh, he didn't do good in the Falcon run or whatever.
Like, you know, ultimately those are all kind of siloed experiences, really.
But something like this, there's like, there's fate at play.
Your entire real world vacation, your trip to Crime Con could be completely ruined
because you chose wrong on the dial of destiny, if you will, at CalFish.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like Gandalf is like, choose wisely.
Like when you start a vacation like this, because your fate could be worse than death.
This is like Jackass or Fear Factor where, you know, he eats it.
That's kind of what this is.
This is like a, like a loud version of, I don't know, I'm going to eat, you know.
Bugs.
And I don't know what's going to happen to my body.
This is like a sanctioned professional version of eating a bunch of weird anuses.
Right.
I agree.
I'll eat the, if it was next door, I would eat it right now.
I would do it again.
Yeah, I've taken a, I've turned the corner.
I went from being horrified at breaking down and zooming in an image of burgerushi on your phone.
I don't want to be that close to it unless it's going into my mouth to eat.
But I would go back and I would get it again.
I wish it was up at our city walk.
It might take like 10 trips before we figure out any official judge.
It is, I mean, it's blowing my mind that we live in a TikTok age where people are making everything on their phones.
Yeah.
But this still just holds supreme in our minds.
It's a food that I'm not eating at home.
I don't see anywhere else except for at Cowfish.
Yeah.
It's so special they haven't replicated it anywhere else because it's daring.
Maybe I do love it.
Only Orlando, only the, like the theme park primed audience in Orlando.
That's maybe the, like maybe the mistake that Eva made or anybody who's had trouble there has made
is going there on a trip.
I think that the local stomachs have been and the rest of their bodies have been primed,
steeled.
They're ready to embrace the Cowfish.
But then again, your friend, the Cowfish has not made people sick from the burgerushi.
So maybe all of this is just-
Oh, right, you're right.
This wasn't burgu-
You come back and you tell your tale and you just, you go there and you get the signature dish.
You don't mess around with the other stuff because who knows what horrors will befall you.
Maybe this is the Cowfish's message.
Have burgu-shi and don't stray from burgu-shi.
He puts, this is how he, the way that the Lord creates tragedies that we can learn from and
that create good after the fact.
Cowfish puts bad burgers and stomach melting sushi on the menu in order to teach you not to have them.
Oh, it's like Indiana Jones trying to pick Christ's cup from the night at the end of Last Crusade.
Right, you have to choose correctly.
Yeah.
Oh, it's Carpenter's cup.
Right.
Yeah.
He makes that little hamburger patty look like a baby turd.
But we learn from this turd, we study it, we teach future generations to avoid the turd burger.
That's what this saga is about in a way.
Eva's our good friend, we sympathize with what happened to Eva.
I think that the Cowfish had something to impart to you that day.
And just please don't judge the Cowfish, don't persecute the Cowfish.
No one persecutes the Cowfish.
The Cowfish is good and pure and led me back here to the show where I belong.
Well, keep that in mind, yeah, because if you have a negative experience at Cowfish,
I want you to reevaluate what it was and now think about it in the way you're explaining.
Remember what you had and has Burgushi ever done anyone wrong?
Yeah, and I imagine the people that would say like negative and Cowfish,
they have to be so few.
There could be barely any, I'm sure.
But the one, two, three, four, reevaluate it.
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, all that said-
The small amount.
I would love it if we wrapped it up because I do.
I am feeling a little queasy just hearing about it.
Are you gonna throw up on air?
Oh, we've never had a puke on air.
It's all part of the Cowfish's plans.
He knows what great content this will make.
He's furious we talked about the bento box.
Jason, imagine a piece of sushi with the middle.
The burger, it's this cold and it feels like that maybe was cooked two hours prior.
Zoom into it again.
And let me just zoom in.
Teach him.
Like this was cooked two hours ago and the rice was maybe made somewhat fresh.
Close your eyes, Jason.
Stare it down.
Face it.
See what the Cowfish has to say.
Hear of its tragedy and its victories.
Yeah, yeah.
Think about all of it.
All right, well-
I look like I'm punishing Jason in more of a thorough way than I expected to.
I know your faces are so genuine.
I am worried.
I don't know.
I don't think I've revealed this yet on this show, but I had a bout of food poisoning recently
and it wasn't from this restaurant, but it didn't fully kick in until I had eaten
at a claimed LA French restaurant Petite Troie.
Oh no.
So I-
You don't think it happened there.
You think it kicked in there.
I think it kicked in, yes.
Right.
I think it was something at Goin' Bad that I had at my house.
But yes, so the famous Big Mac, which they say is-
Yes, they're known for a fun cheeseburger.
Which they are known for a fun cheeseburger.
I ate a couple times, but not in the way you would like.
Well.
That was the creepiest way to describe it.
Yeah, that's what I'm going through right now, brother.
You have it now?
No, no, no.
You're always feeling a flashing back.
I'm flashing back.
Do you need to get off mic?
We can finish the episode without you.
No, no, I'm saying I don't have the highest opinion of beef right now.
I see, I see, I see.
All right, we'll take a sip of water and we'll get to get out of here.
I'll do that.
Well, that's the problem.
You know, don't drag cowfish.
Cowfish is only part beef.
Cowfish is a whole cornucopia of things.
And that's where those bathroom signs suck too.
The binary, beef boys, fish girls.
That's not what the cowfish is.
The cowfish is one and all at once.
And cowfish, I love you and I thank you for providing us this very special experience.
And for helping Carly Weisel get here.
Carly, you survived Podcast the Ride, the Sun Rock Orlando Saga.
Multiverse of madness.
You did, I'm not sure everyone will.
Let's exit through the plug portal.
Is there anything that you would like to plug?
I'm nauseous again.
There's my podcast, Very Amusing, where I talk about theme parks and travel and
very nuanced Disney things.
Check it out, it's weekly.
It's me, Gavin, on the internet.
And then you can follow me on Instagram, Carly Weisel, good luck spelling it.
Great, great.
And please keep, on all of those mediums, keep us posted if you go
and visit the cowfish again and see the cowfish.
I will say, I am planning a trip back to Universal Orlando.
I do have to do some food stories and I will be returning to the cowfish.
Wow, yes.
When is that?
Will that have happened by now?
No, no, no, no.
I have a little time.
It's a while, you've got a while to go.
You've got a while to prepare.
My advice would be to buy a home in Orlando, get used to being there for two months,
and then I think that's really the way that you can properly prep.
Really acclimate to the weather, the water there, really dig my heels in.
All those little things, you need to fully, but you need to become an
Orlandian before you can truly see the cowfish.
You're right, you're right.
All right, well, as for us, thanks to Erin Gertner for the art, our own Mike Carlson
and Zach Reno for the theme music, Multiverse of Madness Merchant RT Public Store,
for the full Multiverse experience, subscribe to Podcast the Ride, The Second Gate,
or join Club 3 to get every sector ad free and an exclusive bonus sector.
All of that at patreon.
com slash podcast the ride.
Wait, the stone, the sector stone is appearing.
Oh, yeah.
What is it, Jason?
It's a roll of burghushi sitting on the toilet.
Could you touch it?
Is it the same temperature?
I why it's like my hand is going through all temperatures.
Oh, wow.
It's cold.
It's hot.
Look at your hand.
Your hand is turning.
Parts of it are blue and parts of it are orange and parts of it are beet red.
Wow.
It's like the rainbow of fishes scales.
It is like the rainbow.
I know what you mean.
You have that magical glistening.
The magical.
The lamps are like in cowfish.
And the cowfish itself.
Right.
Wow.
I hope your hand always stays that way.
May your hand keep that color forever.
Cowfish, thanks for being here.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.